[Music]
reflection going confused obession I
still wonder I was for you if I
could
[Music]
pleas you
I don't even know what
[Music]
you you see you are me everyone
want bre
[Music]
good Play Your Part around
and
[Music]
your heart me
I I
[Music]
coulde for you pretending like it's all
just
[Music]
see what I want I need do you
and
[Music]
I know bre shake
me you never see what I want what I need
you
[Music]
K KY oh goodbye chunky
wony ah she turned that she turned down
my microphone when she left she always
has to step on my mixer always has
to
K hello hello how are you guys' wallets
doing how are your savings accounts
doing do they feel
robbed are you okay how you doing
guys dead
bad
fantastic don't
lie wallets are on fire broke as [\h__\h]
let's go let's
[Music]
go I had to splurge on a nendo today
finally oh oh oh what n are you talking
about I wonder
H
well let me introduce you
guys finally it has been 500
years
but the the Legends I thought it was
just a myth I thought my whole existence
was just a
myth funny
well it is finally
real I I knew that this was finally
coming for
like a month or so I knew that this was
uh finally becoming a
reality but even before that I was like
H is it ever going to
happen I was just like you wondering
wondering wanding
[Music]
finally is this the other merch yes I I
I didn't expect it to also be announced
on the same day though that that that
feels a probably like a big shock to
everybody's hearts and
wallets like oh oh
[\h__\h] right after checking the prices for
all of the V prod products
together I hit you with
this uh well you
know well I told you to like expect
something I don't know how expensive uh
nids usually are but um it's just one
one itty py little
B just one okay V has many things for
you but this is just one on ity Bey wah
wa yeah okay that's like I mean not like
you know not it's not going to um
destroy your dreams of buying a
house uh this dbd N word
Wawa I actually I I did some research I
asked a question for you guys that you
maybe I don't know are you guys a type
to
unbox your
little itty bitty
Wawas if it comes in this kind of shape
would you take it out of the box or
would you leave it in the
Box yes you oh okay oh oh oh everybody's
unboxing oh everybody does oh oh do you
keep the Box you put shut up do you keep
the Box
though would you like to keep the Box
and if you keep the Box you like keep it
like in a nice place or just in a in a
Cell in in the
underground yeah usually I've kept the
boxes so far keep the Box yeah okay okay
okay okay so
apparently they stopped using the usual
boxes usual
box um with the window the plastic
window and they started using like like
no plastic
boxes uh so I was like
hm are they going to use the new box for
me because for everybody who has been
collecting the myth nander roids and was
envisioning them standing next to each
other mine would look very different
from the others just because it took so
long to finally get painted so I asked
about it um like are they going to use
the old or the new box and they said
they're going to use the old box because
they had the same
font yeah so old box with plastic window
so if you have other n roids and you are
keeping the box or you're keeping the
whole thing in the Box you can keep it
next to each other it won't look weird I
will be fitting in
[Music]
might buy that good idea well I
retweeted it a million times on Twitter
thank you for the raid MOA I just
started my
stream and I'm advertising a little bit
because today
today
today yeah yesterday last night today I
know this got announced I finally have
my Android with a it bitty chicken with
a little baby
chicken my little
chicken so let's let's look at the poses
yo but it saves everything as [\h__\h]
chif do you really have to be like
that you have to
change every single
time yay look look cute
cute
cute she has the crazy face of course
too kind of matching with the big uh
figma
figurine yeah yeah yeah oh so cute oh so
cute okay and then on the other
hand let me
show you this image I guess has
everything so in case you also haven't
seen this
yet oops see
no one more thing of course that
hopefully you didn't miss hopefully you
hopefully all of you guys follow me on
Twitter is of course the things yeah
yeah yeah um so if it's out now now if
you are buying it uh if you watched all
of the
videos uh there apparently throughout
all of the videos there's a secret
discount code hidden but also I think
for the emails or so somewhere uh they
obviously also in an obvious way told
people uh about another code the early
Phoenix code but there's another code
somewhere in the videos
hidden um yeah but there's the early
Phoenix code that you can use that I
really recommend cuz it's 15% off um it
was uh yeah if you got the email I think
then what it gets applied automatically
huh I miss both disc well well well
should have signed up for the email or
whatever I don't know codes don't stack
yeah they don't but uh there's also the
shipping there's a shipping uh discount
code um it's it was applied to the big
bundles by default
aha oh I
see yeah there is a yeah international
shipping code the discount code
Also let's see what was it
again
uh what was again you guys probably know
too e i NL KF
maybe that's the one kfp hey which one
is
[Music]
it
huh yeah at least those two stack
anyway kfp i n t
l please make use of it and then I also
asked another thing like because you may
expect uh it to be like the other
collaborations that V had done before
that some products are like staying in
the store forever no um you know we have
a different deal they have like a
permanent deal we have a Time limited
deal or something like that um different
contract so the pre-order window
afterwards it won't be available unless
we do like a a rerun and they said that
they're open to doing a rerun but we
don't know when that would be uh but
maybe we'll do at least one who
knows but yeah so for now only the
pre-order and then it will be out of the
store yes so that's finally we have some
nice uh product pictures too the knife
it has like orange elements to it it's
really nice and beautiful
and it should lie really ergonomically
nice in your hand I
suppose waa colors and then we have the
Chopsticks that are cute with CI and the
spoon that are cute with CI and the
ceramic
Bowl yeah there's some product pictures
with Ramen in that bowl it looks really
good and the name tag looks really
shiny nice you can write your name on
there and then the apron nice uh up
braed apron and the hat cute hat with
wobbly wings and then the ramen of
course that was really yummy I tried it
really high quality Ramen and The
Cutting Board I wonder how big it is I
IRL um I really appreciate another
cutting board I have like I hope it's a
little bit on the bigger side cuz mine
are relatively
small cutting board looks so nice you
know The Cutting Board it's like
obviously my my my uh uh Shield but um
it's like in in wooden style it gives me
big Zelda
Vibes is it just
me
right
yeah
yeah yeah than
I don't know it doesn't have to be Deco
Shield but it just it just looks like
that to me so cool
M so you know also it's great to have
these items at home in case someone
brings uh in case someone um uh uh
breaks into your house you can either
completely smack them silly with The
Cutting Board I'm sure they they'll be
flattened properly or well you can you
know you know what they do with knives
wink
wink protect
yourself cook them in me y someone braks
them to your house cook them in nice
[Music]
Ramen they probably they're probably
just another kfp breaking into your
house trying to steal exactly these
merch items from you because they
themselves could sadly not afford it
that's what they're here
for maybe you can share sharing is
caring protect your V items guys protect
them so yeah this is um unfortunately
very expensive alog together uh
especially also if you want to get an
Android
too I'm sorry it uh came at the same
time but as I said I don't think I have
anything else in
December uh even like in terms of group
merch I don't I can't recall
anything um so and the pre-orders for
all of these are open for a while the
nro is open until 15th
January and the Vite stuff I think until
31st
December I
think
oh wait
money what do you
know may okay maybe there is something
additional coming but in any case I want
you to focus on these
a teaser was posted for that long time
ago a teaser I'm like on the Twitter and
I can't find anything a
teaser
bro teaser oh is it on the H live
English
Twitter ah wait I see it
now
oh
[Music]
oh bro
I didn't know they teased it didn't hear
anything about the
teasing I
lied I forgot about
this but but uh so I guess that top one
will be my
pattern
cute God damn
it oh c
C uhat and Hol myth winter collection
coming holiday season 2024 well surely
uh you don't have to buy that in
December you could buy it in January or
so I'm I'm
sorry that's it though that's surely it
I don't recall anything else at least
nothing of utmost
importance maybe a voice pack but that's
you know that's you know
there also Advent calendar merch what no
what do you mean Advent calendar merch
why what makes you think we have Advent
calendar merch we don't did we have
Advent calendar merch last
year we really
don't the
merch yes no no I don't think we had I
don't think we had Advent calendar merch
I mean last year it might have been
likely because it was
um kind of kind of
uh financially taken over by management
um but this year no it's me again so uh
I'm not going to give you guys any
merch it's free videos again and stuff
we're working on the website right now
it's looking really nice look forward to
it yeah yeah yeah yeah
so I'm say I'm showing you all of this
now and now I need to get rid of it
because I cannot have advertisements on
my screen at the same time as playing
Diablo but just keep this in mind guys
keep it in
mind yeah no more merch for a few months
well I'm I'm I I'll I'll try I mean you
know my my next birthday my next U
anniversary is a while to go and until
then there's usually like only smaller
things from the company side that you
know you can get if you want to
but I don't even get that much of a
share anyway so um yeah you know less
priority I mean about these things that
I just
showed
it's same thing but I'm more excited for
you guys to get it so please get
it I want these things that I just
showed you to do well even if um maybe I
don't make a fortune out of it uh but
you know I'm really proud of them those
items especially the Vite items yeah and
neroid we waited for a million years so
those are
pretty
important yeah thank you for your
support guys I saw a lot of you guys
already purchasing it you guys are crazy
thank you very much thank you I
appreciate
it first the game of Subs drops yeah I
saw I saw I was like oh my God
what what gamer Subs this feels like a
like such a twitch
thing nice looking cute yeah yeah yeah
but I don't need anymore let's let's
let's keep it at that for for a while
I'm pretty proud of my Vite releases
so Vu cups yeah stop sending super
chats what are you
doing what are you
doing crazy Mad
[Music]
Lads what are you
doing do you really think you have the
finances financial means for
that careful too much Mone money be
careful kfp careful kfp too much money
too much going to break your bank
account
careful careful careful
kfp I'm making a reference in case you
haven't noticed
anyway I guess we're going to play game
now um oh yeah I'm back Hello nice to
see you again feels like I wasn't gone
at all to me at least don't know about
[Music]
you had a nice nap today damn little
little nap not huge nap but when I say
little it's still
long thank you thank you thank you thank
you crazy people thank you crazy people
thank you for the super chats and the
memberships and stuff thank you
you how's the Casper pillow Casper
pillow good me me like Casper
pillow uh cat likes Casper pillow also
very much she's so cute cat so
cute like I've never had this before
like maybe only because previously my
pillows weren't big enough to fit
two heads on the pillow and now the
Casper pillow is so big that when I'm on
it uh smoothie wants to get on it too
like even when I'm already on it she's
so clingy right now
what's she's so cute she's the size of a
head can fit two heads
n if it fits as it's so cute
it's so cute I
can't yeah no it's pretty good but I
still like to for example this night um
I feel like my neck was okay like it
didn't get worse from sleeping like it
did previously the past days before the
Casper pillow but I still felt like a
lot of pain and un uncomfortable
feelings in my spine and all that so
maybe it's really time for a new m
mess U before we start one more thing
schedule uh Today l
diabo tomorrow Fallout New Vegas New
Vegas baby we're so
back uh and then then we have cookie Yi
there's a new cookie Yi game yay so
happy I played all the others too and
then you know World Tour is happening in
Singapore let's go so so I'll be a bit
busy um but then after that I'll play
inscription I guess didn't couldn't
think of anything
else and then members watch along the
the okay so Rec previously we were like
I don't know where to watch it I think
you guys just I don't know if you have
to type in like in crunchy roll it's on
crunchy roll mon off End monser season
type it in it shows
up it's properly there I couldn't find
it at first either because I guess I
typed in B I don't
know but it's properly there yeah yeah
yeah yeah and it's a lot of episodes so
we'll start with one to six where's the
rest of
them okay
now sorry it took a while to get
everything out of the way
[Music]
126 episodes that is certainly not what
I
said that is so not what I
said wait
actually let let me not show
you my a been loud
mhm let me not show you my character
[Music]
screen Play
Born send hell's arm is running with
Diablo Diablo 4's most agile class
yeah for
free they're they're trying to make me
test it out and and want want more it is
it doesn't ah from now until December
2nd 10:00 a.m. P PST you can play as the
agile spirit board up to level
wow yeah but no I got other [\h__\h] to do
welcome back booster I wasn't even the
game is welcoming me back I wasn't gone
for that long for a limited time
instantly boost one Eternal character
well let me show you
I
transparent H
okay claim the Boost travel to Tavern in
Kill Shad wait instantly boost one
Eternal character am I an eternal
character I didn't buy the
DLC you chosing did I I don't I don't no
I
didn't
so what what kind of boost is it
not eligible for hardcore good that I
didn't
change oh I am Eternal oh cool ah non
season aha oh I get something good out
of it then explore San falize yourself
with new phone power and prepare to face
new
challenges but I'm not level 50 do I
have to be level someone says auto level
50 what what does that mean
well there's another
thing beware the Crimson Reaper Kaw pimi
the red cloaked T has returned to sanctu
of Vengeance hor RS down the demon of
crion this member the demon of crimson
dismemberment the demon of crimson
dismemberment what a
name is this like an event
be sure to keep alert while saying Fen
hell tight infernal hordes and dungeons
is known to look around defeating him
will reward you with the potent Gillian
Brew for 30 minutes your damage is
increased by 20% wait but that's surely
high level content right be sure to stop
by midwinter SC K was to obtain our gift
from Grim cheer for the season only one
per account may be claimed oh well
that's I want to have that I do want to
have kill thead remember mid square and
kill Shad wait I can click Vanquish him
or close oh is this like me
accepting I do I have to otherwise I
guess Crimson Reaper will not show up
I'm kind of scared though I say
no I'm a
[\h__\h] here we
go appear don't worry
it's like what do you mean
that welcome back
booster like this is meant for people
who haven't played in months or so I
suppose
but thanks I guess I played like last
week or
so your voice kept getting cut out no no
no no no that I don't believe you that's
the you mean what whatever don't worry
it's fine just don't worry about it just
don't worry you guys have witnessed this
before you know how it
is you know who it
is huh
[Music]
can you feel R now
sorry I was
um listening to KDA songs again uh I
guess in connection with Arcane um and I
was watching the music video actually
like some of the songs I didn't realize
they had this like new not so new song
but anymore but it was so cool to hear
it for the first time like the song More
was also really
nice um I was I was trying to say when I
was s uh watching the music videos I was
thinking
damn I can kind of like Envision them in
the Arcane
Universe I can see
it I they they would totally fit
in they could even be like you know an
underground like z uh like band idle
group that performs
sometimes
yeah yeah I know we can do covers yeah
I'm thinking
maybe
maybe I can use their songs One Way or
Another in the
future
yeah yeah they would never be done more
like
sine HH what do you mean what do you
mean more like
seraphine what was that supposed to tell
me sarapen is from
joh oh
oh
really well whatever like I'm just
saying they could be a Arcane CLE band I
can totally see them in there and
and now I want more like I wish I wish
they would make a Side Story Side Show
with the KDA girls or but anyway they
announced that they're working on more
shows and oh my God we got to talk about
it anyway like cuz I finished it of
course I watched um I watched it uh uh
here I have some tangent
notes uh
[Music]
Arcane uh yeah
okay we'll get there uh I have muchos
Grande
tangents H yes we need more K we do we
do
it was golden gay time oh oh oh yes it
was it always has
[Laughter]
been so
[Music]
what interact with the faded Relic query
okay what
what what what I don't know what
huh
oh I the Boost to level you to 50 give
you full gear for chosen build There is
five no [\h__\h] that oh the Boost will
level me to 50
50 find your character at level 50 all
alars of all alars of live unlocked and
be equipped with powerful legendaries
and items no but I want to go for the
story
normally I thought it was an exp buff or
so I could make a new character and just
oh but would that still be an eternal
character but I wouldn't mind like
leveling that one up and keep it as a
side
option to you know play with a different
class which is interesting that I'm
saying that when I very strongly spoke
out against leveling up your characters
like this with a boost in my last Diablo
stream um but
yeah uh yeah after I beat the game or or
like I do it now but
whatever whatever I'll forget about it
anyway
probably so yeah leveling boosts are
lame but I appreciate all of the altars
being unlocked and and getting another
Peak into a different character could be
nice could be nice this could be I guess
helpful for the other girls if they just
want to skip to the DLC and they don't
have time to play and level their
character like I'm doing
could be very good for
them but is any character you make just
Eternal what what if they start now and
make a new character now is it not like
the seasonal
thing the game scales I know but I think
it would be nicer to have them at like a
good
level it lets you choose aha aha I see
okay
ah the usual people are in my
chat well the usual kfp and the usual
Diablo Pros welcome welcome welcome what
were we doing H can I get rid of this
Quest here like I don't want to see it I
don't want to up space constantly
because I'm not going to do
it um I'm sure if
I like Mark a different quest to show it
will
what click what do you mean click on it
nothing's happening when I click on
it q q q q doesn't do [\h__\h] I here there
it
just
um apparently my sister got sick by the
way she got a
cold I'm feeling fine right now but I'm
wondering if I'm going to go get sick
too
uh campaign this one I suppose meet Don
at this C the Cathedral of light
okay that's what we're going to do how
far is it oh
it oh all the way over here oh
okay I'm
coming you wanted to get your free
gift okay but I don't want the I don't
want the boot the the other thing is
just a normal like gift right is
that they said something something blah
blah blah this is not it where is this
maybe it's because I rejected it left to
the Waypoint something something Square
okay um but
um Mid Winter W was that it no was it
whoa what the oh is that the gift is
that the
gift what the [\h__\h] is that the gift
gillions brw gillions BW gillions brw
Gillian brew that was the
gift suddenly who what do you want why
you following
me greater midwinter purse ancestral
unique midwinter cash a a purse suitable
for level 60 containing gold and
ancestral items let me put that into my
chest um this one's for level 20 this
one for level 60 this one's for level 40
well I'm awkwardly in between 40 and
20 uh chest
here that's not the Boost I know I don't
want the
Boost uh 16
40 but I'm 40
soon oh my
God I love that oh they even gave me a
want oh they they like kind of know what
I am do they yeah sorcerer only oh
[Music]
she okay okay all right all [\h__\h]
right
W
um no okay this is it
greetings who's talking to
me this is fine that I don't I I don't
want it uh uh because I we want our
incinerate split into free beams
imprinted
thing what stop
talking and um this one's too weak mhm
this one's too weak this too weak oh
[\h__\h] they're all too weak okay but maybe
the level 41 will be nice all too weak
to
[Music]
weak are these just other things I had
in my
inventory they look so nice though wait
this one's
good
uh but not good
enough okay I guess wait what
I guess I'm getting rid of
everything father bless what do you need
I'm talking about my level of course of
course are you sure you want to destroy
no I'm not yes I am you can take what's
left give me give me nice aspect and
stuff and
materials good boy good boy I'll get
better things soon the level of 40 will
be in demand yes
yes
okay oh yeah so okay we got these
gillions Brew enemies take 20% more
damage enemies routinely drop additional
herbs and crafting materials and you
gain 50% nice okay we have three of
those and they go on for 30 minutes
that's that's
good me likey meyy likey me likey likey
[Music]
likey where am I going warning your turn
Port oh where am I
going oh yeah I'm going there okay
[Music]
glad you're back after your spy break
thank you I am back it's almost as if
I've never gone somewhere faithful
penitent oh [\h__\h] A Prophecy has been
delivered to me one that speaks of a
glorious
Future Okay Tears of
Blood rain on a desert
draw and the way to hell
was torn
aunder then came a spear of light
piercing hatreds heart and he who was
bound in
Chains was set
free like my
Android you've all heard rumors of the
demon lth the daughter of hatred [\h__\h]
it is my spear that shall pierce her
your heart no mine the chains that hold
us to this world shall be cast off and
on my wings my wings I shall Lift us all
to Heaven oh pierce the heavens pierce
the
heavens I kneel that was amazing speech
speech speech more speech speech
5,000 and that's
it wait how do I ah Donan are you Don
wait where the [\h__\h] is Donan Donan
y Don is it you no donut
Don oh there you
are speech
100 I can't believe he's there that big
Angel guy can't believe
it
um what was the um he's he's not related
to Lil right wait what I
forgot inarius he was was it was he no
right yeah he's her ex okay oh okay okay
okay
okay and they've got issues they've got
issues down there and up
there good news for once I
hope it's from
lorath wonderful wonderful
[Music]
[Applause]
indeed so Stone I like his noises is he
serious what does it say he didn't tell
you no of course not that would require
some basic degree of consideration
it's written in our
code he sent a
plan though calling it that is generous
he's he's got he's got concepts of a
plan probably with My Soul Stone the one
that held
astero can it
work certainly
not the stone needs to be attuned
first and he will need an expert oh I
will be that expert Trust thinks that
expert is you oh then then he is even
more foolish than I thought H it is me
after all go to the Horadric Vault will
you mhm I'll dig up what he needs you
can deliver
it and maybe then he'll leave me alone
get a bit
louder okay oh okay no why not go
away why always come back
enter Horadric vault at mistal
Woods see seor oh it's not so
far how do I get on my Mount
again
Z there we
go yay yippe
H so this continuing no way it shows
that stupid [\h__\h] again [\h__\h] get out of
here can I
like disable auto pin there we go and un
track and track that [\h__\h] track it
enable autop pin there you
go yeah yeah big
cat boy I think he's
possessed you not
so should I start with my I feel like
the trip will be too short for me to
tangent but let me begin me and my
sister wait
what what why the [\h__\h] is it tracking
down
again me and my sister went to do lovely
nice sister
bonding in spa hotel
Yi and it was
um was a place I went to
before so you know I already really
liked it last time I went there so I
thought I really want to go again but I
don't know with whom oh my sister was
open to go with what
the okay what the [\h__\h] why is it still
show why is it still tracking that okay
F I'll look at it in a moment
unbelievable wait oh forgot about
this anyone else who wants to
party okay better not come close to me
what the hell is going on I turned auto
back
on I turned it on here does that what is
it for both
can I not just I don't mind Auto pin I
just don't want it on this
one
heck
it's it shouldn't be tracking it now so
now it it's it's tracking the right one
don't you dare change that up again
but yeah um my sister likes to go to
spawns and stuff
o so she was a good
candidate
and yeah I don't know I can't tangent
like
this wait I'm still I'm still like my
mind is
[Music]
still give me a moment
can't
stand guys have to repeat if it re
checks hope it's in a bug
um at least if it's a bug then I feel
less
stupid for it's
constantly doing that again oh ah ah I
have one I had one
[Music]
yippee
m m
M legendary dagger ritual Dagger of a
cursed touch that looks cool but not
going to use any of
these she won the casting for the
spot
yeah yeah she
has uh some go-to places apparently
uh but this one was a first and you know
the one that I brought her to is kind of
expensive and yeah very luxurious very
good very
nice so I I'll tell you all about it but
I need
to figure out how to
tangent while playing a game again I
seem to have
forgotten Don and have you found your
things I haven't even gone in yet we
have an
intruder it's not like that she's but a
child she you brought a child I brought
a child it was she who brought my ID
prob that's my
child a child like a legit
child talking about a real child
should I look
around I I've been to this
place
mhm oh Nel I wouldn't call her a
child ah oh okay I would not have called
her a child
okay could confusion
solved watch where you swing that stuff
it's not a
toy who is
he he once lived in this Vault the one
you're trespassing in explain
yourself I'm a student conducting
research on the harrim what's left of
you all anyway a student huh you have a
teacher Don't Tell Me Lord has taken
another Apprentice I don't need a
teacher to study
Lilith
Lilith threaten sanctuary as we
speak I need to prepare for that with or
without
help you against
Lilith
well I came to get my things I pray they
were free from your meddling
what a
diva what a diva why is he such a
diva the way he walked away
too I used to be like that
girl really I had more dreams than I
knew what to do with let me unseal this
okay let me see how you do
it just be him
what disappeared for a second there one
frame you feeling good Stone will need
to be ATT tuned to Lilith before lorth
marches up to her it won't hold her well
otherwise I put together some notes on
the process before I
left uh-huh okay cool
Co he was a girl with a dream
once and now he's a diva
oh look at
that it's on the other
side
fat fat o sorry uh I streamed Sparks too
hard forgive me for messing up your
place he should be more mad at me than
at
Nal I'm making bigger mes than her first
things first lorath will need my
notes Soul Stone magic is treacherous
even in the most skilled
hands bring Donna to his desks tread
carefully okay we summoned the spirit in
here let me bro R them up thank you
morat assured me that he banished it for
good but spks I've always doubt who the
[\h__\h] what nice got me a lot of Little
Gems did we not need to enter this
place where is your desk oh there
apparently damn spiders always find a
way
in what if I just use nothing else
besides my fire
Beams I recall this I feel like a
project the physiology of the
goatmen in the end it devolved into a
debate about whether the creatures dream
like goats or
men I kept a
map
somewhere ah here mhm all the places
mephisto's hatred yet
lingers there's just one last thing
okay guard Don from what oh bring down
to his desk okay okay hey he's got them
so scattered all over the place why
doesn't he just keep
them in one place one
office would make it a lot less
complicated
would about here or
there all
right speak to
me is that your herc amulet on the table
oh yes
I bet lorth still wears his the order's
mission was his
lifeblood I couldn't give up my life for
it not like
him I wanted to be a
man I left to chase
family
fellowship he wanted to be a man I
thought you wanted to be like that
girl you saw how that ended turn down
for what my son
I can't do
it it wouldn't work
anyway Donan Donan you don't understand
the stuff Soul stones are made of
they're old as the Eternal conflict
itself with magic so primordial you need
Faith you need
spirit I have none would you lack in
faith you have in allies believe in
yourself Donan who
you yeah yes you're the only one who can
help
us unfortunately you may be
right I can't make any
promises really but I can try mhm for
you
too I'll try mhm for YouTube he'll try
let's hear what the old man has to say
YouTube I'll try that's what I heard
he's very aware immersion broken
guys
you
you return to the study
okay what about this door open it oh
that one just leads to one small room
open it D you don't want
to fine
Nel still here
yeah speak of Nal okay Nal what have you
been up to these past two minutes this
place is a treasure
Trove look at this masterpiece callus
Beyond the Veil of the Southern
jungles you're familiar with khus
work she's brilliant one of my
favorites mine as
well have you read maybe they get along
now never mind you can tell me on the
road on the
road I'm going to help you huh I know
the haram's ways your magic even that
coded writing system you use and and
don't tell me it's too
dangerous Lilith took my mother I'll do
whatever it takes to stop her
her that's a good
speech might even convince the man you
should be telling it
to come on I'm headed to
him isn't this your
Vault it was
once
now I suppose time will
tell why would it not be his level
38 let's
[Music]
go meet with your allies at The Forsaken
Chapel
okay bro what do you mean until 40 are
you talking to
[Music]
me oh
it's so
far I guess we could teleport to tarar
rock my
Champs why does leveling make you loudly
fart what it didn't sound like a fart to
me teleportation make me go little
little
laggy
yit
lag okay we
good
[Music]
um where are we going
what [\h__\h]
you get out of my
mind stop make like trying to force me
to skip all the content in the game and
level to 50
immediately stop
it don't you want me to enjoy the game
that you worked so hard
on no Skipper
Skipper I feel like there's not enough
time to tangent on this little trip
either maybe if the dungeon is kind of
long I can tangent in the
dungeon why tangent you were right to
call upon me you know Soul stones are no
trifle they're already talking without
me I remember why are you starting the
party without
me I need air where where'd you come
from what's going
on I'm still muddy on the details of
this
plan the bones are there l aims to take
mephisto's power for herself before she
can reach him we use the Soul Stone on
her preparing the stone will take time
we don't
have why don't we fight her who Among Us
you her corrupted blood still runs in
your veins F no fighting her kind is
always a last resort even if you could
defeat her she'd eventually come back
but a smarter weapon the stone would be
up to the
challenge Soul Stones usually fail given
enough time it might not
work you can make it work there's no one
I trust more to do it the wind is
picking up I can't I can't see her oh
TAA oh I'll find
her wait what does she mean the the lady
that walked out like before I started
the
conversation now she's like oh I can't
see
her
girl oh my
God what the [\h__\h] you're fumbling El
leted me right to your little
C if you hurt
her hurt
her I elevated her you did indeed the
room is in into her skin form a from oh
nice she is a beacon across
Realms
ow get her out of here oh [\h__\h] it
matters not her part is done so dramatic
your part is done
too save your breath it has only just
begun my friend
wait where are we not
finding no oh andariel andariel
andariel
andariel oh [\h__\h] wait a [\h__\h] I forgot
how to use
that okay okay okay W oh [\h__\h] I don't I
forgot how to fight like a a smart
person
C where
she ah the
[Music]
chains un chain me now woman woman of
evil nice okay okay I've got it under
control
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] why was that so
strong she she's already dying
there you go there you go easy darel
really that's
it
really am I just too strong incinerate
is
strong
she I was a bit like lost in the
beginning but I'm I'm back in the game
we good we
[Music]
good I'm
darel kind of
weak I'm surprised what are you guys
doing it wasn't such a big deal you can
pop the bubble
now what happened out there nothing
nothing no
biggy don't worry about it just a little
bit of a
misunderstanding to be honest andario
from Diablo I is also easy is she the
one I I fought in Diablo 2 when I
streamed
it oh was that someone else did I fight
her on
stream yeah oh I think that was a little
bit more challenging in Diablo
too I think I think I um it was still
manageable but I was actually I think I
was just super panicky because I didn't
believe in myself confidence is all you
need bloody hell we finished the Ritual
from the volan then he's he's he's
Australian that's the man who summoned
Lilith you're saying he summoned a Lessa
evil too kop girl less is andariel
gone
yes and
Elias he
fled before going to the steps Elias
came to howar took something that wasn't
his it's why I'm hunting him I have
a friend in aazar who has mastered the
art of
immortality she might know his
secret let me take you to her okay I
thought we were after Lilith not
Elias all the same finding him may lead
to her and while we look for him you'll
have time to work on the stone that's
what you wanted isn't
it damn it I'll
bite on one of those rare occasions you
gave me good advice
you said the answers you need are often
in the place you least want to look oh
that's wise it was you who said
that ah you're
right A wise man blah blah blah oh turns
out it was
me what a diva he knew he knew that was
him who said
that uh oh I guess I could like talk to
them and individually but yeah we ready
we don't talk in this
place listen I didn't mention it earlier
but you did well oh thanks you stood
against andario a lesser evil go and
lived that's no ordinary feat oh but
don't let it go to your head huh the
arrogance and fool Hardy never lasts
long in
howar I don't know surprised talking Kan
would have written in his Chronicles if
he had seen us Two Old Friends
reunited new allies eager to learn from
our vast knowledge bound as one against
the encroaching Darkness like the harad
of
old they were probably lost and bitter
just like us but Cain had a
gift one thing was certain at least bth
meant to devour Mesto and claim his
power as her own that been her goal all
along not sanctuary but a bid to
concerning the damn fool was
too perhaps we weren't
perfect oh he's just British had to make
a stand we were the world's only hope
think gravel for breakfast wouldn't be
surprising for a a a a a British person
level 39 Oh [\h__\h] we're leveling so fast
without even doing anything ooh
what oh I got a necklace Nex to Star
oh oh did I just I finished the uh uh
act four we're in Act five now
sck
nice so we have
these probably won't use it but it's
pretty oh oh
legendary chest armor that is better
than what I
have when you cast a skill you heal for
1.3% Life double this bonus while below
50%
life oh nice I
guess um oh wait this one too oh but
this this is about oh wait no I can
still use that even though I'm I'm a
fire Mage it just freezes close enemies
when I evade and Deals cold damage to
them sure why
not but I want to do that in the city so
I can put the
sockets
in
so uh we kind of have to go through
tarar anyway I'll I'll get laggy
again for a
moment he also the guy who knocked out f
for being giving to the
boltons
what wait you mean as an actor not as a
voice actor he was in Game of
Thrones hey I'm not
laggy oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
what did he talk did he have talking
lines in the uh
show she
he was the a-hole that helped F take
Windell
a when they showed up there only them
two yeah I think I remember something
like that but I don't remember his voice
in there at
all so we're going to wear the helmet
and the new chest
piece and for that I take this
off you can still use this for is always
hot now one of them has only one socket
but whatever for now I'll just leave it
like that because we are probably
getting some
new things with the level
a gift
bag
okay going
to oh wait what Oh I thought it was like
up here never mind we are going down
there again meet your allies in zarban Z
okay I'll try the tangent on my
way so on my way uh first I was like
traveling alone and then I met up with
my sister Midway through but it was a
long travel for me
bro
uh yeah I met with my sister and we
haven't met in a long time and then we
continued our journey
together and then we finally arrived at
the hotel I think nothing really in
particular happened on the way
there um but yeah we were pretty tired
from the trip but the hotel already was
like it was so nice to be
back and my sister was immediately
impressed by the atmosphere and like the
whole like when you enter the furniture
and the mood everything is just so nice
already and cozy and then the reception
ladies they were really
nice just as
always like the service was as good as
it was back then really really nice uh
staff and everything and they gave us a
welcome
drink and so we sat down in the lobby
and my sister uncon unconsciously
subconsciously without without
unknowingly yeah unknowingly she ordered
uh like they said you can order anything
from the uh menu for the welcome drink
and I just ordered like a little
mocktail it just tasted like a lemonade
was good but but she unknowingly ordered
something that was actually really
expensive TW like 25
bucks for a specific
drink
normally pretty
expensive so good that she got it there
generally like alcohol was pretty
expensive apparently not my problem
sounds like a you problem sis
sounds like wait where the [\h__\h] why is
it
leading what's happening why is it
leading me why was it why was it leading
me to the boosting pack
again it's on the house why not yeah
yeah now the drink was fancy the glass
was fancy my sister was
delighted it was
[Music]
coing yeah and so we already got like
some pamphlet little booklet with
information of what they offer and
everything and the thing is we booked a
package um that comes with a little like
20 minute horse ride that you can
do uh you're not really riding it
they're just sitting on it and they like
lead you through the
area yeah you don't really have to do
anything besides sit on
it um you were a student of eliis but a
long time ago I I was hunting probably
like in junior high school I think maybe
my first year or so I did go
to oh way point I did go
to H like a one week course riding camp
thingy that was the only time in my life
that I did something like that
uh yeah I I learned horse riding pretty
fast back
then yeah and it was of a special sort
of horse uh that had like its own riding
style uh I think in German they're
called eish uh F but I don't know what
they're called in English but they have
their own writing SK style Iceland yeah
I guess so
which is like before
galop like in between like a half galop
or something like that I don't
know yeah Iceland I I guess so I guess
so
to I don't know I think everybody can TR
TR I don't know I don't
remember don't know but I learned that
back then and I loved it so much and um
but I I was like never able to go again
cuz it's like an expensive hobby I guess
um
yeah but I was dreaming of going again
one day maybe I never got to do it but
now
it's I don't know I should probably tell
it in the right order but here we had
the opportunity to go be on a horse
again uh you could also just actually
book horse riding slots like if you're
able to ride a horse you could indeed
ride the horse there on your own or you
could also learn how to ride a horse of
a teacher there but we just had like a
little a little
walk yeah little walkes with the hores
and my sister was never on a horse
before so it was a real first time for
her so we had that horse appointment
yeah uh looking forward to that but on
the first day basically we just had the
welcome drink and then yeah my sister
was very happy and we got had an upgrade
we had separate rooms now I would have
been
fine uh if we would have shared rooms it
would have been a lot
cheaper but my sister warned me that she
also kind of snores uh just like my
mommy but not as loud as her um but she
does snore a little bit so she was like
maybe it will bother you and I indeed
like especially if the person is right
next to me
o not sure if I would like that very
much um so she offered to get different
separate rooms which I honestly
I I like that because I like to have you
know my my privacy in the morning and in
the evening just like chilling and doing
things at my pace and getting up when I
want and and just not like not talking
and recharging my batteries my social
batteries
yeah so appreciate it so we had two
rooms we booked like uh somewhat normal
rooms but we got upgraded so both of us
had huge family rooms with several bunk
beds in them in the separate room they
were huge those rooms I was joking oh we
can like get some more people in here if
we wanted to let's call up some
people
yeah it really really nice and the view
was nice cuz we had a view I mean I feel
like most of the rooms have a nice view
but had a view over the whole um like
like place the whole uh Hotel
area and a little balcony and had like a
dining table and big closet and bathtub
and a shower that I didn't use because
uh I was just using the shower
appliances at the saunas
Etc a big big
bed big bed and I don't know that was
just really really
huge yeah so free upgrades and welcome
to drink very nice and then we just had
dinner after we checked in into our
rooms cuz they gave us a little tour and
and then they left and then we just
chilled a little bit got dressed
properly and then we had our first
dinner and the dinner was really nice it
was like free courses no free
menus one 12 three yeah and two like
normal ones and one vegan one and you
can still like mix and match if you want
to and they they were like I think five
course
meals and just like back then the food
was really really good
yeah they have other restaurants too but
this uh this stuff was included in the
prize so breakfast was included and
dinner was included and lunch you could
either choose one of the restaurants ala
cart and pay extra or you could just go
with like they have every day they have
like a kind of like one
dish in a few different
variations just there for you uh at the
buffet to take for free so usually that
was pretty good so we just went for that
for lunch it was plenty filling so one
time it was like uh Austrian style
dumplings like round balls mhm but like
bread dumplings eh with
like spinach mixed in so spinach
dumplings with cheese sauce like one of
my favorite foods ever that was so good
uh or a different variation of that was
just normal bread dumplings with like
bacon inside and then like melted brown
butter I think and a
sauerkraut sauerkraut very Austrian
geran
M that was also good I tried all of them
very yummy so we got fed quite well in
that
place I want to eat
those spinach dumplings again like I I
don't like spinach in general but as I
told you guys many times before only
when it's like mixed into the dumpling
and then served with cheese sauce
oh oh that's the best thing
ever I need to make it myself
sometime
yeah so anyway for dinner I don't
remember what we had but we had some
good stuff good dinner my sister enjoyed
it and and yeah she was she was really
happy and that made me happy because
last time last time I recommended a
place to some
body I didn't seem to impress that
person very well talking of Nissa and
the
moldes so it feels certainly nicer when
you're
like really confident in something and
the the person actually receives it well
and likes
it uh very much but yeah this place
definitely is worth the money like they
they really serve you good food have
great rooms and great customer service
and great saunas and pools and
everything so basically yeah uh they
have like many pools they're outside too
and they're heated partially some are
more heated than others and they have
many many saunas and you know I'm not
really a sauna type of person but this
trip especially I
really um how to say
I tried my best and overcame my fear of
being naked around other people a little
bit
more I was a little bit less
awkward I was way more surrounded by
naked people than in previous
times it was like really crowded uh a
lot of the time
um but thanks to my sister really liking
sauna I want wanted to uh tag along as
much as I
could and I just uh
yeah I I tried my best and it went okay
mix or girls only unfortunately
mixed unfortunat I wish it was like
separate but that's you know sauna
usually is
mixed huh eh yeah it's usually mixed
huh yeah I'm brave right thank you
exactly like that's like one of the big
things if it was only women I would be
less uh worried about it towels Well
normally normally you don't really like
but you go for example if it's a dry
sauna you go in with a
towel to place the towel on the space
that you're sitting or lying on but you
don't really cover yourself with it most
people just even walk in without
covering themselves cuz they're that
confident and don't give a
[\h__\h] and they walk in just like so
openly
naked nothing is censored yeah people
are very open yeah I guess that's just
European sauna culture it might be
different in
America I would prefer to like generally
when I walk walk in I'm definitely
covering
myself and then so oh oh I I um still
like even if it gets really hot I still
like try to cover myself um especially
when there's people around um and then
my sister she brought something that she
was going to use herself but then she
borrowed it to me um like a like
basically a towel
it's like a little bath robe for the
sauna it doesn't have sleeves it's just
like a towel that you wrap around your
upper body uh but it has buttons so it
stays in place so she lent it to me so
that I could wear it so in the dry on I
was wearing that but everybody else was
just like walking around like they don't
give a [\h__\h] uh yeah very naked very very
naked
uh but then I actually like
the um humid sauna more the like the the
foggy sauna I like it more than the dry
sauna um because it feels like something
is actually happening you know what I
mean cuz you breathe all that humidity
in and it feels like it's really opening
up
your nose and throat and everything and
then also you the the more time you
spend in there the more you're like
super
wet your body is dripping everything's
dripping and just yeah the sinuses it
really feels like something's
happening and then one time we had like
appealing
they H they uh they they had like
specific times where they were doing
like specific sauna events where a sauna
dude comes there to uh I don't know I
don't know what he really does because
we were there too late but he's
like going around with the to towel he's
like alus yeah what's that in English I
don't know he's he's he's just like a
professional sauna guy and he stands in
there and he's like okay in the dry SAA
he will he will will pour some oils or
whatever nice smelling oils over
the sauna stones but he was in the humid
zaa uh and there I guess he also did
that but he also like brought these
peelings that people were supposed to
rub onto their skin um in the humid SAA
because there uh it's so wet already
that it doesn't matter it can get messy
he's a sauna elf
yeah he knows everything about
sauna yeah very very very professional
SAA Guy where was I going with this I
don't know but so I I was going to say
cuz you guys were so shocked in in the
uh humid sauna it is so humid and it is
foggy so it people don't go in there
wrapped in towels like
it it would feel really uncomfortable
too U but at least it's like kind of
foggy so you don't see that
clearly so yeah for that you kind of
have to be really
[Music]
naked just avert your
gaze yeah for me I don't really like it
either but everybody is like really
normal about it
so yeah the cool thing is and I know I'm
just standing around because I want to
focus on telling this tangent but the
cool thing is so the first night when I
woke up it was snowing like [\h__\h] when we
arrived it wasn't snowing yet but when
we woke up the first night it was
snowing so so much and the snow was
lying everywhere like it was staying in
place it was beautiful it looked so so
beautiful like a winter
wonderland and first I was kind of
worried about it because of the horse
ride but turns out it wasn't a big issue
and uh it just made everything more
beautiful and it made the the feeling of
going from cold to
warm even better and it made it even
Cozier to stay inside of the hotel but
also since there were several saunas one
sauna was placed in like um a bill a a
building that was just for the sauna
outside next to a lake that they have so
that the whole I'll probably show you a
picture later but the buildings all the
room buildings and the restaurant and
everything they're like all surrounding
a little Lake in the middle and in the
lake there's also a pool kind of built
into the lake that one's heated and then
there's another like onand pool that's
like really heated
next to it and then there's a sauna
building that is also right by the lake
and so that sauna was so cool it didn't
look like the other saunas it wasn't
just like normal brown wood no it was
like dark black wood and really cool uh
like architecture mhm and so I've I've
watched so many
people on these days uh go into the
sauna and then and come out and jump
into the ice cold by the way
freezing Lake that was right there like
they come out and they go into the water
naked and I was like damn these people
are
so so brave and strong
jez yeah some of them could stay in
pretty long and some of them were like
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] and pretty
quickly uh walking out again but I
noticed like pretty much everybody was
there either like with their partner or
with their whole family with kids um but
usually you know the kids stayed in like
kids areas and the the couples the adult
couples they stayed in the sauna areas
and
everything um but I noticed when there
was a couple of a man and a woman and
they went into the water
often the women were more hardcore than
the
guys and stayed in longer in the ice
cold water ha
strong that was quite funny but not
always sometimes some couples only the
guy went into the water and the woman
just
watched they were naked yeah they were
hella naked and the lake was frozen in
most places except for the places where
you enter because people kept on going
in and out but it was like everybody was
trying to prove how cool and brave they
were how hardcore they were but it was I
guess it must have been really nice like
I didn't want to go that hardcore like I
get really hot in the sauna too but I
don't feel the need
to you
know jump into an ice cold lake at that
point like the moment I'm already
stepping outside I'm already cooling
down enough I don't feel like I need to
go into the Ice Cold Lake to cool down
but I know it's like you make your body
stronger with that whole process it's
more about just cooling down you
strengthen your body with
that I'm sure it feels great or maybe
not maybe it doesn't feel great actually
but you just still do it you still do
it what was I saying I don't know but
yeah that was a fun thing everybody was
doing and I was watching I was like [\h__\h]
couldn't be
me temper it like steel yeah temper your
own
body brisk and refreshing yep yep yep
yep
yep sounds like something wild someone
would do at least once while on
vacation yeah well we didn't do
it we didn't do
it it feels terrible and then great from
what I hear well I guess also especially
if you do it more than more more
regularly then you know it's really nice
probably okay I'll talk more about this
[Music]
later he must break his hold on
immortality mhm he cannot continue to
escape his judgment mhm yes and without
Elias we may have more success against
Lilith where do we
start call him seek out Timo in the
marshes she traded with the power in the
swamp and and received long life she may
have the answer to killing Elias for
good Nal and I will start looking for
her what about
Donan he has his hands full with the
Soul Stone a heavy burden to bear alone
might be wise to offer him assistance
[Music]
mhm okay
wait what
a it's why does it always do that it's
looking for the purple Quest again the
welcome back
booster can I just like [\h__\h] get rid
of
that I guess if I were to do it uh
activate it with a different character
then it would be
gone but I don't have time for that now
bro I think not I have to take care of
the Soul Stone
lth will be fine
alone Northeast of here is a zachar room
keep mhm we know hatred has a strong
presence there perhaps we can use it to
prepare the Soul Stone to trap Lilith
mhm I could use your assistance if
you're
able sure I guess uh okay ah do I have
two spots to go to now and it's just
showing me the God damn purple Quest
you have to do both in the end anyway
find Lura Andel meet with Donan I don't
know I I I'll
do whoa they're really far oh they're
really
far
okay
well plus click the quest toop
what what
ah ah wait I didn't see the first part L
then
shift shift what does shift
do doesn't do
anything what do you
mean ah ah wait PL okay wait now I get
it no
plus no shift plus clicking this doesn't
do
anything oh maybe Str strg
no
no whatever it's
okay half of EXA I don't know I've never
played or looked into Path of Exile
games
before so hard to
say uh what no no
okay but I have two points that I should
probably use
um but can I put points into the others
I guess it doesn't make any sense to do
so
okay really similar to
Diablo skill trees is a tiny bit intimi
oh that's
[Music]
okay 10 times bigger oh [\h__\h]
oh ask GGY if you get per oh does she
also want to play
it hold why did okay I am
not
having uh like I'm not losing my mind
right 100% it was tagged on like pinned
on the yellow Quest the golden Quest but
it changed it
again bro
always got to pay attention when I'm not
wrong
place bro okay let's see tangent so we
woke up to lots of snow and then we had
big big big breakfast and oh my God
breakfast was so good I I already missed
the breakfast buffet that was like one
of the
oh oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah wait wait wait wa wa where is
already dead wait I killed it so
fast
nice
nice yeah I think that was the best uh
breakfast buffet I had in my whole life
I can tell you
that Austrian style you know so probably
different
from uh I don't know American or British
or Asian breakfast
pets but so good so much choice
so much high quality because a lot of
the the thing about this hotel is like a
lot of the uh products there are like
organic and made uh like cuz they're on
the countryside they're made from close
by um
oopsie how'd you say I don't know like
milk makers milk
maids and yeah you know yeah locally
grown
ingredients and
stuff local
milkmaids yes yes so really yummy and
they had like so many berries they had
like insane amounts of berries for you
to just take normally I feel like Hotel
breakfast buffets they don't give you
[\h__\h] when it comes to berries when it
comes to fruit they give you maybe
bananas and apples and [\h__\h] but berries
no no berries are too luxurious you
won't get
berries but no they had so many berries
I had a million berries each
morning
no what the [\h__\h] thanks for letting me
know bro
what okay whatever uh so yeah uh on I
originally had massages booked for um
the first day after their arrival the
second day and the departure
day wait where how the what for here
till first day massage and then uh we
just chilled a little bit we like um
since there are so many different saas
and so many different pools we mainly
stayed in one area on one day and the
other day we like went to a different
kind of area where the [\h__\h] am
I so
lots of variety and different
Vibes it's right there did it change
again
[Laughter]
bro bro bro
stop can't believe it Savage Oh wayo can
I get in no how do I
they have to go
like well let me talk to the quest
first uh
and and so in between SAA and pools we
were like just chilling in the silent
quiet rooms everybody was like just all
these couples were cuddled on these like
nice
comfortable uh beds in front of the
windows where you could see a beautiful
panoramic view of the mountains and and
the hotel area and the snow everything
was so snowy so really relaxing
everybody was quiet and just cuddling
and reading a book or something and then
you walk out that door of that room and
you go into the sauna and you chill in
the sauna and then you go out of the
sauna and then you go into the pool or
you go back into the quiet room
basically that and then um I had a
massage and then we had those dumplings
and those were so good my sister also
was really excited and then um then oh
so there were like free programs every
day uh that you could sign up for
usually when I'm talking about free
programs it's like uh like a guided walk
outside or uh
I don't know uh yoga course or workout
course or stretch
course stuff like that yeah uh every now
and then they also have like something
more like creative like they had the
Advent
ref crafting course and stuff
mhm but for this day I signed us up for
yoga course my sister does weekly yoga
like she's a yoga
professional okay okay she doesn't
really do like hardcore
yoga but she goes to yoga a lot and if
you recall my first and only experience
with yoga was at this hotel 2 years
ago and it
was all right but I think already back
then I
complained that I like the whole
like stretching and posing and stuff
that feels okay but I don't like the
yapping the spiritual
yapping yeah cuz I
cannot immerse myself into it I feel
dumb I I really um Envy everybody who
can listen to that yapping like oh feel
how your body is connecting with the
nature or with the floor whatever if you
feel that and you feel good with that
and you relax of it amazing I wish I
could feel like that but I can't so if
only it was without that yapping I would
really like
it so back then I was like okay I guess
yoga is not for me but this time because
my sister really likes uh yoga and
because I just wanted to do anything
really I thought let's give it another
try it was the same
instructor and it was the same kind of
routine but I feel like the yapping the
spiritual yapping was a little bit more
toned down this time but also it was so
exhausting and I thought this is how it
is but my sister told me afterwards that
no this was a really intense and fast
yoga session that felt more like a
workout than a yoga session I'm thinking
the instructor probably just wanted to
to pack as much volume into the one
session as possible so that it's you
know that it feels like you did
something um I think it was like an hour
or 50
minutes it felt pretty long and it was
like so fast like Bam Bam Bam Bam going
to this position and to this position
and then hold this position and it was
really really rough yeah definitely it
was a workout I didn't realize yoga is
supposed to be like that but no my
sister sister said no this is like not
how they do it in her yoga yoga
class
mhm I was like the most [\h__\h] in that
yoga class but it did feel good yeah I
did feel like I did something uh good
for my body and I also stretched out my
legs quite a bit in that
session it felt good and I did feel it
in the following days
also uh yeah definitely burned some
calories and felt good to just do
something and to do it together with my
sister yeah jelly legs very jelly jelly
arms too everything
jelly so yeah did that and then we were
pretty tired after that yoga the yoga
thing was pretty late in the day and
then uh we just chilled a little bit
and then had dinner but yeah the whole
day we also spent a lot of time in the
sauna and I went into world poool
alone uh the
whirpool what do you imagine when I say
whirpool uh it's not like the kind of
whirpool that's like small and that you
put into your garden or so it was more
bigger than that and it's heated and
it's
bubbly but I was alone in it and I was
just swimming some laps in it because it
was kind of nicely warm tiny baby laps
jacuzzi yeah but like
bigger just a bit bigger not as big as a
proper swimming pool but I could do some
laps in
it yeah hot tub but like a big like in
the shape of a
pool
yeah baby laps yes so that was day one
you know nothing special but I did yoga
session lots of sauna getting used to
sauna
more and lots
of observing people doing crazy stuff
and getting a m I didn't say anything
about the massage but I got a massage
and the massage was pretty
good um but not as good as I experienced
it when I was there
before and like I I said like hey I I
mainly have I have I have a full body
massage but I mainly have issues in my
shoulders and my
neck and so please focus on that H and
like the massage staff was really nice
and professional and everything but it
still felt in the end like there was not
as much focus on my shoulders as I
wanted to at all it felt more balanced
overall and then
he squeezed like for example it still
kind of hurts there but I don't know how
to explain where this is but he squeezed
some parts of my
skin so hard that it still hurts now it
was not comfortable and you know when
you go I go to massage a lot you know
and I try to say when something is
really too strong but also a lot of the
time I will suffer through it because
I'm thinking okay like like when when
they start a move in a spot that hurts
I'm like thinking okay maybe they'll
just do this once or twice I can live
through that I can survive that and then
I wait it out but then they do it more
than once or twice and they do it three
four five six seven eight 10 times and
I'm like oh [\h__\h] and I'm just like
waiting it out like oh surely they will
stop now surely they will stop now oh oh
they're still doing it okay but surely
they'll stop now oh they're still do oh
[\h__\h] I should have said something way
earlier this hurts so much so often I'm
just like suffering through it and just
awaiting the end of that particular
movement so I wish they would check more
often and ask like oh are you okay do
you like the pressure but often they
don't ask at
all yeah sometimes I did end up saying
something though I was like oh sorry
like can you go less
strong and then he was like okay no
problem
but it barely became weaker that was the
issue but I was like worried about I I
felt awkward about saying it again and
again and again so I just spoke up a few
times in different
sections but it barely became weaker
so I still suffered a lot for that
massage even though in theory it was a
good
massage but it just didn't feel right I
was like okay whatever I have another
massage
tomorrow I'll make it even more clear
even though I was already pretty clear
I'll make it even more clear that I want
to focus on these areas because
particularly the areas that I wanted to
focus on didn't
feel like really treated at all and and
even though that guy was so strong he
didn't use that strength from the areas
where I wanted
it so I was like okay tomorrow is
another day I'll I'll bring it up
tomorrow and I'll hopefully be more
satisfied but then the massage on the
second day was even more
disappointing by far this time it was a
lady and I asked beforehand I called the
hotel and I was like guys do you do what
do you call that in English the sh
massage the suction suction cup massage
and they were like yeah it should be
possible to include it in this massage
because here in this massage you can
just like make your own program pretty
much and make requests and I'm like okay
then yeah cing please let me choose this
massage so that I can do the cupping cuz
I really like the
cupping and there was some cupping but
out of 80 minutes even though this was
so important to me I think she only did
it for like five
minutes uh so I was kind of
disappointing I thought oh maybe she'll
do some more later but she just packed
it up and continued with different
stuff
yeah and then even those 5 minutes were
that
good cuz she mostly went over the spots
that were already sore from the
uncomfortable massage on the previous
day I was like at some point I was like
sorry can you please not go over this
point anymore my my my flesh is really
sore over there please stop she's like
oh okay I didn't see it and like yeah
it's like inside you can't see it from
the outside worry about it but just
don't go over it anymore please she's
like okay she still went over it several
times after that I don't know why but
she went over it less strong at
least um but yeah the whole massage was
kind of mid because she like you you
have to understand I go to massages so
much over the past years I've been to
hundreds of massages in different
countries so um I can judge quite well
if a massage is good or not and her
massage was pretty mid like she kept on
repeating the same moves that weren't
even that nice if it's a good move okay
but she kept on the uh doing the same
move over and over again that wasn't
that
satisfying and basically the same moves
as from the previous day just less
intense and more
repetitive and after a while after
halfway through the massage I was
so
like like I just I just wanted to get
out I just wanted to walk out I I grew
so impatient I didn't walk out but the
whole time I felt like can this just end
like this feels pointless I feel like
nervous anxious weirdly like how to say
just what's the
word I just wanted to Restless yeah I
felt so Restless not relaxed the whole
time I was like ah this move ain't good
is she going to do something
better just couldn't relax ansy yeah and
uncomfortable so after the massage I'm
sorry but these massages they're like
double the price of what you usually pay
for a massage outside of this luxurious
Resort um it was like 180 bucks for and
80 minute
massage
so right I can I can complain if I don't
like it right but I wasn't sure I wanted
to complain but in any case I wanted to
cancel the massage that I have was going
to have the next day on my departure day
because I
thought I'm already sore and these
massages are not satisfying so they're
never going to probably really work on
that area where I really want them to
work on so whatever I'm just going to
can cancel it so I was sitting there in
the like office room for their massages
and I was awaiting the lady um who was
like putting in the the schedule stuff
and she's so nice I I was listening to
her talk to other uh guests beforehand
and they were talking about how the
hotel is fully booked right now and all
the massag massage slots are taken right
now and unfortunately and we can put you
on the waiting list but the waiting list
is also so full right now so yeah you
kind of got to book in advance you know
and I was hearing that I was like okay I
guess I'll at least be able to cancel my
massage without any problem because
they'll appreciate it
actually so then I went up there and the
customer service is so good even though
they have hundreds of guests she saw me
she knew my name she greeted me with my
name and like Tak hello and asked me
immediately how my massage was even even
though I was still kind of hesitant on
bringing it up but she asked me directly
so I told her that I wasn't satisfied I
was like I was like U yeah actually um
actually I I wasn't that satisfied
actually and she's like oh no what
happened what happened and she took out
her notes and she was writing it down
and she was really open to hearing
feedback and I I so I was like okay I
guess I'll tell you you
yeah I told her that in theory was good
but it didn't really work on the issues
that I had and the cups weren't really
used as much as I'd like to and the
pressure was weird even when I said
something and I don't know it was just
like
unsatisfying and this and that and the
massage on the previous day was okay was
better but still not as good I
experienced it two years ago that was
really great I had that in really great
memory and then she was like yeah I
think you had she looked it up uh she
said yeah I I had the the massage
boss back then who's currently on
vacation so I was like oh no but I'll
put it in the system for you that if you
come back we'll give you the boss
again yeah and I had I had a different
person too but that person quit so I had
like two different people back then and
both of them weren't available this time
the boss yeah the boss of all
massages
yeah give her the boss I wish I wish but
she was then so nice to give me like a
huge discount I think she gave me
like 50 bucks or so or even more a
little like 60 70 bucks
off I was like okay and she's is she's
like is this okay for you like first she
started with like 40 bucks or so
discount and was like um you know I hope
this is okay for you I'm like yeah that
would that would satisfy me a bit more
and then and then I like she asked me
about the massage from the previous day
and I go a little bit into the massage
from the previous day and then just's
like oh oh okay let me go down the a
little bit more on the price she really
wanted me to be happy so great customer
service I mean I felt bad for like
getting the price knocked down so much
but it was already so expensive to begin
with and for
that especially since I know that the
massages there can be really good and I
was really hyped for
that you
know then I felt like
[Music]
okay I take
it
MH so that was okay and then I just
canceled my massage for the next day
hopefully somebody else enjoyed a nice
massage
instead so that was Takashi
Karen but I'm a nice Karen I really I
wasn't even going to necessarily bring
it up then when when I did talk about it
I was like
o I'm
[Music]
yeah yeah do you feel that Mesto touch
is heavy here all that
hatred it's just what we need to attune
the make it ready for Lilith little
gaming I'm too old to climb but you can
get in and open the port
Callis mhm okay too old all right I
guess that's how we will we will get a
way point
[\h__\h]
burn I'm what's her name L Golding or
something what was that song Burn Burn
she sang something like burn
burn how's that song Go Ellie Gold
yeah I really like that
song bernus no not
burnus yeah she has a song Cold
bur I like her
accent could go up here I think the game
wants me
to raise the port coolies
what ah and we're going to let it burn
burn burn yes
yes but somehow it's mixing with another
song that I have in my head right now
the cat's eye
[Music]
song Safety and Sanctuary we did seek
here in this most cursed of
places but evil endures so the ages say
unto us so have we seen and heard
here we seek shelter or light and here
we find n and yet still we turn to thee
my RPG senses are not sure where I
should go
first damn
it should I
go there's a chest on the map should I
go in
here take the Waypoint first okay I'll
try
what was I talking
about saw mod for burn
really s do Sor mix dry
I'm is that really what she SS no that's
not what she SS I'm lit you can't deny
that sounds
accurate I'm lit you can't
[Music]
deny oh she's a bartender oh okay maybe
she does sing that then huh
wait there's another one of these doors
here so maybe I can't enter them now
maybe I
should
oh cat I touched no that song wasn't
touched that song was uh like one of
their less promoted songs that was like
in the
competition like a kind of emotional
pretty song
like their usual slay
songs oh there's a boss in
here what do you want what do you want
from
[Music]
me speak it now or be forever
silenced and what was I talking
about don't for
call these rooms are bigger than I
thought are these
[Music]
optional
H golden no even before that
massage oh yeah massage massage massage
all right St free depending on if you
see oh if you see it as day three or day
two I don't know but we woke up again to
even more snow falling yipp so
beautiful ah more
snow and yeah again nice breakfast
buffet and I think this time we didn't
sign up for anything in particular on
that day but we went to one of those
scheduled sauna peeling thingies peeling
with guided sauna
thingy with the SAA
professional you
know um but even though we were on
time like cuz the humid sauna is kind of
small it already packed with people and
so we couldn't participate but they
still had some leftover
feelings so after the the sauna guy was
mostly done and the people all left to
seea we just went in
me and my
sister basically did it alone but then
the sauna guy came back
in and you know he did a little bit he
he poured some more of those oil drops I
think it was Mint or
something he did a little
bit Yeah and we we we did a honey honey
sugar or something like that peeling
scrubbed it all over us my my sister
scrubbed it on my back I scrubbed it on
her
back it was nice and the sauna guy said
yeah this is all made from our own honey
our own collected honey and organic
whatever so in theory if you wanted to
you could eat
this
yo special
amazing fancy wow
oh
yeah the [\h__\h] is that P
Lord
ow no no eating after applying no no no
no just rinse it off Blood Stone gain
moment wait I should I mean I'm tangent
to and stopping so much so I feel bad
about using it but let's try to not stop
so much I drank
it yeah and on that day we had the horse
thing so we actually went outside I was
kind of worried about going outside um
because I didn't expect it to snow so
much or at all so I brought two pairs of
shoes I brought 40 shoes which you know
when and part of the fabric of sporty
shoes can kind of be like not
transparent but it has like holes to let
the air go
through so that's not really meant to be
worn in snow obviously right and the
other pair I had was really warm and
cozy but they're uggs and ironically
even though they're so cozy and warm and
fuzzy and fluffy you're not supposed to
have them touch water too much like you
shouldn't have them be rained on or
steep through a lot of
snow from what I know because of the
lever yeah you can seal a of chemicals
to make me more waterers okay but mine
are definitely not sealed so I was like
uh I don't know about wearing these I
don't want to ruin them cuz they're
new um so I went outside with my sporty
shoes it was okay because at least most
of the path to walk to the um to the
horses most of the path
was
uh like shoveled so that you don't have
to step into deep snow
atast it was kind of cold but it was
okay it was
bearable I also didn't bring my best
winter
jacket cuz again I didn't expect it to
be so snowy
but we were so warmed up from all the
sauna
going that it felt kind of refreshing at
least for most of the time later felt a
little bit freezing
but what Uggs indoor only they don't
look like indoor only
shoes they got some like us slippers and
stuff that I would understand if you
would see them as in or
only but besides
that oh they're proper
shoes proper shoes you're back Buzz yes
I
am you're L did you see my nendroid is
on on preorder now finally he's
painted did you miss it I hope you
didn't miss that
info but yeah where was I and
where was I oh yeah so we went up to the
hes on on our way
there and we saw a lot of other animals
they have like a lot of animals they
have like donkeys and huge Bonnies
rabbits and even alpacas but they're
kind of small and sheep really sloppy
sheep I saw the sheep from the
distance like running around and
they they were so cute and one of them
reminded me of chunky wonky the way it
was moving and the way it was like extra
fluffy it was so
cute the Sheep were so
cute and um yeah the Ala were so cute
but we came back later after the horsing
was
done to check out the donkeys and
alpacas and everything from close up and
the donkey came out for us from the shed
but the alpaka was like the alpacas and
the donkeys were together apparently
they're friendly they're
besties U but the the alpaka was like
loafing like a cat you know when the cat
loaves around with the paws tucked in
the alaka
was
oh oh FL oh holy mother of
lag
what I don't know what just happened
happened and the alaka was like loafing
around too it looked so
cute and it was just loafing right at
the entrance of the shed looking at us
judging us so cute but the donkey came
out and then my sister both me and my
sister were like super
super you know when it comes to animals
we're both the same like we have the
same kind of
reactions not what's the word not skib
skidy what was the word
again sky right that's no
word there's not enough enemies for this
to be
wored
skidish skidish is the word I was
looking for I think but
yeah what the
heck
enemies where are
you I guess that's nervous yeah but I
but anyway we were we were really happy
about seeing so many cute animals you
you rarely like now in this day and age
we live in a
society especially if you live in a in a
city then you rarely get to see like you
know Countryside animals so closely also
and my sister was
like getting so close to these animals I
stand having the donkeys and the horses
and renounced having the donkeys and the
horses like eat her hand basically
so she got so smelly after
that her hands are really smelly I just
was like petting
the woo I was petting the
the just a
fur but I didn't let
them like eat my hand that was fast
bro what was that dungeon clear
y good tons good
tons fluffy did you pet out no they
never came to us they were just like
loafing and looking at
us
ooh that's a lot stronger but I want
intelligence damn it
Twi for of splintering
energy maybe you missed getting spat on
again what the heck
no but yeah it was really nice seeing
all these animals and being able to like
get close to them and touch them even
and the horses so when we went to the
horses can I teleport out they were
already like like ready ready it up for
us and they gave us a helmet I actually
I did ask because I was so worried about
my shoes I asked if they had riding
shoes uh but they didn't they didn't
have them to be like borrow rented at
least I guess if they're all like that
we do the other
ones maybe I'll do one more I want to
get the way Mark at least way mark wayo
um yeah so they only gave us a helmet
and then they were like okay time to get
up on the
horse and they put a little stool on the
ground I guess cuz we're small
relatively small and the horses the
horses were really
tall uh they put the little stool on the
ground and they like okay there you go
just put your foot into the thing on the
left side and then and swing over and
there you go but I was like even though
I was the one who had experience with
this many years ago it took
me a while I had to think about I was
like oh my God oh my God I don't know if
I can make
it I don't know it's kind of challenging
it's kind of
overwhelming
okay uh but after you know Gathering my
courage I did it
I went with one foot into the one thing
and then I swung my body over I wasn't
sure where to hold and the and the and
the horse was like moving around a
little bit and moving further away from
the stools while I was wasting time so I
had to
move uh my stool closer to the horse
again I guess the horse was skidish SK
oh I can't walk for here
why
not that's a boss never nervous oh no
definitely
was what is going on
wait does that not open up until I do
all the dungeons by any
chance cuz there's
free it's like an invisible purplish
Port uh
wall last time I heard a horse it was
just a line of horses that followed each
other down a trail in a loop oh that
sounds nice
too oh okay let's do another dungeon I
guess oh
what maximum comp of the murmuring opal
has been increased by five yo random
[\h__\h] hidden altar of
Lilith
mother why are you murdering there all
on your
own safety and Sanctuary we did seek
here in this most cursed of
places but evil endures so the to us
most
Diablo
advice person leave cuz I was tting so
much where is my
[Music]
py where'd you
go where'd you go did I tangent too much
after all just standing around
I'm still here yeah you're also good we
got
separated my friends were cut down oh no
slay as many enemies W waves as you oh
my
okay as you can before time runs out
okay no
problem
easy I got my dragons out I got my walls
oh I'm already at
eight
wow and
nine
oh and 10
and
[Music]
11 and yeah I did
12 and I needed to do five thank you wer
yay about you wait was this not a thing
where I could Master it think I can
manage from
here didn't say anything about master
did it even though I did so
many huh
okay moving
on what was I talking
about I a horse So eventually I got on
the horse and it immediately felt so
familiar to me even though it's like a
million years ago for me that I was lost
on a horse it felt so familiar to me
and so fulfilling and cool and I was
suddenly literally so high up on my
horse it's so high like you have to be
on a horse to really understand how high
it
feels you're so
elevated it's really
cool do it can't click it why
not return oh I need to return the
Bloodstone where is The Blood Stone
maybe a little drop
somewhere this is
like the way I'm fighting in this game
now it feels like I'm playing power wash
simulator but just with fire
usually that's why cron also clicks with
the
game makes sense
can't find any Stones so
far oh oh there we go oh my
God they the way they descended so cool
anyway my sister was like super focused
I guess she like cuz it was her first
time I also felt really wobbly on the
horse though I felt wobbly and like I I
I was just holding on to the
saddle uh and the lady was walking the
horses basically so I wasn't really
riding it you know but still I felt so
wobbly
and
unsecure I used to have confidence in
writing I was a good Rider back then
okay back in my days but this time I
wasn't so confident anymore
wobbly
horse and the H's poops were not um
ready for the winter and the snow yet so
sometimes the horse would
slip like not completely fall down but
you could feel it how the horse slips
with one foot and then you just kind of
like wooo woo
it doesn't completely lose its fooing
but it's enough to make me go each time
it happened a few
times but the whole time I was on the
horse I was trying to take like videos
and pictures because the scenery was so
beautiful too because we were you know
surrounded by beautiful mountains and
snowy area and Countryside uh houses
very aesthetic very
beautiful and fascinating to just be on
the horse while looking at this
beautiful scenery I really enjoyed it
even though it was such a short little
Triad you know it was just 20 minutes
but it felt really nice I thought it
would feel really unfulfilling because
it was so short but it was really really
nice you know did I pick it up
okay now I want more
I want
more
now I really feel like I want to take a
horse and learn riding a horse again I
don't want to buy a horse cuz I feel
like there's a high chance that I'll
just like just like my air fryer I would
buy it and then not use it and get bored
of
it so I wouldn't want to do that oh my
God I missed the shrine
bro I already killed everybody
no I'm a horse girl now yeah but I was
like you know I was talking a lot to the
lady um while my sister was super
focused I was doing a lot of small talk
wait what what about the other one oh
was I only able to carry one at a
time no where's the other one did I like
exchange it where I picked up the new
one where is
it but I was doing a lot of small talk
and I asked the lady like uh what kind
of muscles and stuff do you build like
what do you do for your body when you
ride horses
regularly and she basically told me well
you know uh a lot a lot of your muscles
mostly like
your uh stomach and your legs and your
butt and stuff but also a little bit
your upper body and your upper body will
like pick up a nice posture and I
noticed it cuz just the moment I was
sitting on the horse my posture was so
good and I was like damn if only I had
this poster when I was while I I am
streaming
my
games on YouTube it's a really good
poster yeah core exercise good for your
SP yeah I thought so so I was like maybe
I really should try this maybe this
would be a good hobby to pick up because
it's really fun and cool and it's really
good for my posture stream on Horseback
from you're right right I should get
like a rodeo horse uh thingy for home
usage
imagine broo
machine also it was stretching out like
my inner thighs so much it's not even
like that crazy of a spread aart
pose but I felt
like
damn my I need to stretch more
this is stretching my legs thank you
horse totally encourage you to try it
out yeah I just need to find a place
where it's like not too crazy far and I
can somewhat cuz usually they're like on
the countryside right and I don't have a
I don't have a car so it has to be
somewhat
accessible but I'm really thinking about
doing it cuz if it's fun and a nice
Hobby and it like feels
like a nice thing to shut off my brain
and just be
happy uh on a horse horsing
around I really feel like I can just
shut off especially if I can ride
outside I mean during winter it's
probably it would probably mostly be oh
my god
um on the inside Halls
horse
Trooper maybe I'll Vlog my process
even of relearning how to ride a
horse what do you think something in the
fort has followed us inside these awful
tunnels or been here for long
ages now knew you walk I thought to
flee to abandon my fellow Crusaders to
think for myself for
once although I don't know I'm kind of
this will no doubt spell my Doom worried
I can smell death in the
air shut up I feel
like
yeah even if I or especially if I put
like the camera on my head or on my
chest
um feel like oh level 40 one could
figure out where where where I am
forcing
around
maybe oh my God what is going if I make
it into a
video maybe maybe
not maybe if I uh like don't film like
at my us usual horsing place but if
every once in a while I go to a
different horsing place
a a horse outing so to
say uh and that I can film cuz I would
be in a different horsing place than
usual just you know visit different
horses different stalls
Stables yes yes
indeed where the [\h__\h] what am I supposed
to do in here now oh there is it open
now
no I I don't mean necessarily a
different country but just within
Austria oh my God what is
this
Blood you're going
down oh
beesting power wash that
bastards yippe
woohoo nice nice nice nice oh am I full
I'm full was it t t yes
T going to city try Italy I hear they're
very horsey there what
really but no I really want to do this I
don't know if I should start it
with might be I feel like I've got
some encoding over
loaded okay you good now you
chilling sorry
laggy oh yeah when we came back
from lag lag can you hear me properly
when we came back from the little trip
the horsing trip they were readying up
some ponies or should I say miniature
horses because I think Ponies are only
just Young Horses right and those were
miniature
horses um uh where am I going and they
were so cute I was I was petting them
they were so cute they look like Hobbit
horses so
adorable yeah my 4080 is struggling what
the
[\h__\h] there there a different species
maybe I don't
know in any case they were so cute
should I really let this go
there's that they were so small tiny
horse I think they were readying it up
for some other guests because when we
were walking out we came across a family
with two small small small kids almost
toddlers
honestly so it was probably for
them I want to be on the small horse too
I'm still lagging oh my
god fulmination of armor
G 57
intelligence a hail of meteorites Falls
during infernal weight do I use Inferno
maybe not dealing 125 fire damage on
impact your meteorites immobilize
enemies for 3 seconds I don't think I
use that but I could still change
it oh that's the snake spell oh okay
cool I should switch to this one
huh I think I'll switch to this
one I can break that
down I had a shaton pony when I was a
kid you had one the they're the
grumpiest que don't man
oh cute
you can still use
these I read knickers but it was kickers
nickers was more
[Music]
funny I can break that down
limic boundary of the
moonrise uh damaging an enemy with a
basic skill grants you 4% attack speed
for 10 seconds stacking up to five times
upon reaching maximum Stacks you enter a
vampiric blood range gaining 64% basic
skill damage and 15% movement for 10
seconds what wo wow yeah uh does that
apply to my flamethrower I don't know
lag lag we had to sell her when I moved
but she was a wonderful horse I named
her Shimmer what for real you had a
horse
too only my left click attack okay I
don't really use that
anymore all
right only left with the
staff
um Let Me Wait right if I I can switch
it right now
if I get rid of
this and
then do this purple and
diamond oh
wait purple and Diamond there we go nice
what I'm
nominated what really is the Nom did the
nomination start or the the voting wait
what wait let me check
twice what
n uh
YouTuber
Awards let me check let me check what am
I
nomin where is
it
vote okay shall shall I let me let while
I'm here okay let me put down my words
best just
chattingan vtuber
uh mat s Mi M or S FAA well I got to
vote for somebody in my company FAA it
is oo best art
YouTuber I did nominate Ora sorry Ena
but I think I nominated you in previous
years so and ala has been doing a lot of
art
streams sorry
Ena I'm going for that uh best FPS
vtuber doy bird ban
fruit okay uh well we'll go with
ban I'm biased best RP ASMR
vtuber uh don't really no I'm well I
would vote for FAA but uh apparently
fauna doesn't do much more ASMR but what
is RP then a role play without
ASMR well still vote for fa
now even though she doesn't do much more
anymore because I don't I've never I
don't listen to ASMR so I can't really
judge best music vtuber oh CI is in
probably again I'm sure she was in there
before B su su is also there Calli and
[Music]
Su bro that's
mean how can I choose between call and
say I'll make my choice but I won't say
who okay I chose Cy because yeah myth
loyalty CI won last time she
did oh then I'll choose
Su uh best tech
V2 I won't say who I'm voting for
funniest YouTuber oh we got from Holo we
got gigy and bi boo funniest the V whose
humor and WID consist only in stes I
will
say giggy has been very entertaining to
me most chaotic B also has two uh uh
holos I will sorry Cobo your mommy is
not impressed uh at your chaos anymore
gig's chaos has been impressing me too
like every [\h__\h] stream she starts is
already chaotic because in the beginning
of her streams her screen is already
filled with a million acrylic stands
whatsoever I love that that's already
chaotic she is so chaotic everything she
says is chaotic too like oh my God
Hidden Gem I don't know these so Skippy
the scoop Rising start I don't know ah
pale is there let me vote for pale
yuk League of Their Own oh I'm in there
but there's a typo and gole is in there
too oh there's a oh I'm not going to win
this one there's too many good insane
people there's oh oh n that's
yeah I mean I guess I'll still vote for
myself but there's no no way that I'm
winning
this no
[Music]
way okay I'll vote for a whole star for
myy
tuber gav gav
ble oh miss vtuber the vtuber whose
fashion sense is as trendy as their
content this is also where I'm
nominated ooh yeah I mean I will say
with my 3D outfits and stuff recently I
definitely have been very
fashionable they have a typo in my name
again but I oh mint is in there too but
mint I hope you're voting for me
too I think maybe I have a chance in
this
one I have a good amount of outfits and
and you know with my music videos and
stuff I think decent decent chance
the other one no way this one
maybe Rising vtu org okay I don't know
most dedicated fan
base jail birds are in
here
H
H okay jail Birds I
guess are
jailbirds
like like I don't know I I know they're
really like cute and everywhere and
they're you know friend shaped just like
kfp but I didn't notice are they that
like dedicated huh kfp got
some uh
Rivals some competition they just they
do just let her call them fed [\h__\h] and
eat them yeah okay they have a similar
relationship doesn't there best V or oh
is Idol is in here too and H life and
like okay all the all the well-known
companies but is Idol I'm glad they made
it in here as a you
know Korean based mostly Korean content
company I'm glad they made it in here
recognizing the collective of vtubers
who work seamlessly together to create
engaging and diverse
content okay let's let's be honest here
let's not be super biased but even then
I think that does apply to H
life yeah yeah H life gets my
vote be to a parent of the
year I don't
really wait is
that Kaa 7 is that uh sh's
parent yeah right
interesting why recognizing the talented
and creative individual or team
responsible for crafting exceptional
vable character models that bring unique
and captivating avatars to life huh okay
I
mean sure
I really love her art
style surprised it just feels kind of
random well I freaking love it her artst
definitely stands out
uniquely mhm best vtuber
event
oh wait oh that's weird they have like
gaming events such as Holo
GTA as well as concerts in here here
such as breaking
dimensions that's weird they should have
definitely separated those and then I
feel like Ian REO should have been in
[Laughter]
there it says not concert then
nominated no but it says the best vtu
event or concert streamed this year or
do you mean like in the nomination
process it said not concert but then
maybe a lot of people nominated concerts
and then they were like okay well ah
okay I
see well I'll be honest I didn't follow
any Holo GTA content cuz I wasn't in it
anyway but it's weird to put a
concert up there it's also the only
concert
there but I will choose the concert
because it was
sick stream game of the
year uh recognizing the most beloved
game for YouTubers H lethal company Li's
bar Buckshot rouette Elden
ring I had most fun with bushot roulette
and Liar's
bar uh I think maybe a little like in
terms of playing with viewers and with
other people I think lia's bar was a
little bit more funny than Buck rouette
but bu relet is a lot of fun playing
alone in Solo mode as
well and as a collab
game but lias bar I think from the
viewers POV was a bit more fun but yeah
bushot has more game to it yeah I
know but considering that it's
recognizing the most beloved game for
YouTubers and fans alike to stream and
watch I think maybe libar was
stronger in that
sense gamer of the year has two Hollow
members bibu and
[Music]
Kyla I've been more aware of bio's
gaming so I will vote for Bio but Kyla
surely is a gamer too
but also if I look at the kind of games
they play I'm also more interested in a
little bit more interested in interested
in what bioo
plays um Kyla plays cool games too but I
think they're a little bit more
Niche but they're both great so you know
either way lud vtuber skip because I
don't watch that but maybe I should be
in there
and vtuber of the
Year
oh fuok is in here as the only whole
life
member well then it's got to be fuok the
best overall YouTuber this year the
Charisma talent and dedication have made
them The Stand Out amongst all
vtubers that'll be two vtubers of the
Year
double double vtuber of the
year yeah they put in a lot of work so
yes wait I can't ah I have to check
check check submit vote okay I did
it you guys do it too Baba is nominated
in two categories I feel like I only
have chances in one of them but you know
let's give it a
try already did damn you guys are so
fast okay oh okayy sorry even more
Tangen thing
today I'm so torn between what between
homes voted for waa thank you I did it
earlier thank you we're voting for you
of course you are thank
you will you make a Twitter post maybe I
didn't want to like even for the
nomination phase I try to do it kind of
lowkey like the promoting cuz I don't
really want to
like make a too much of a big deal out
of it you
know I'm glad I still ended up being
nominated even though I didn't make a
huge deal out of
it I kept it pretty
lowkey thank you guys thank you must
have nominated me even without me
pushing it endlessly thank you guys I
appreciate it what was I doing ah right
I have a portal I have a portal I forgot
I forgot where's my portal
I was going to walk to the next Quest
Point
okay I nominated you in like every
category thank
you thank you very
much by the way guys I have a headache
right now too and I've been having a
headache for the past two weeks every
day except on maybe one one day
partially is that concerning I think
it's concerning why am I still
lagging I I never had such a longl
lasting headache ever before I generally
never have
headaches like what the [\h__\h] is going
on why am I still lagging the [\h__\h]
hello why am I so laggy where is the
pain just in my forehead
really yeah mostly and then like uh
above my
eyes stay hydrated I've been trying to
yeah are you hydrated I think
so where what am I am I done in this
dungeon is this dungeon done
I think the dungeon is
done it's
oops [\h__\h] it really hurts maybe I'll
take a pink
color Japanese pain
color should I restart the game it's
like still lag even in places where it
normally didn't
lag take easy thank you I took the I
took the painkiller now
so
hopefully I usually that should do the
trick but I just don't I don't want to
you know how I feel about taking
painkillers cuz it doesn't get rid of
the pain really it just makes you not
feel it and that just doesn't seem right
to me doesn't seem like a solution to me
how did I get to this last
dungeon yeah exactly but I'm streaming
right now
so I want to mask the pain for now okay
we'll do this thir dungeon hopefully
that will make sense get then
but yeah I might have to go to the
doctor cuz that's kind of weird I got
head out for a long road trip so I'll
catch the rest on Bo okay if you read
from was
English don't worry thank you what
language wasn't
in thank you have a good
trip serpent cultist serpent C
danger
noodles
dungeon just the game is so laggy now
what's going on
should ow
ow if I uh restart the game
now will I be in the dungeon again when
I come back
I'll be in
town loog in and log out I'll still be
in town then right well well no so laggy
well let me finish this
[Music]
dungeon wait
where did those me oh wait the meteors
come with my snake now right she wait
what what wait no I chanted that so much
a well the 30 minutes were still going
from my uh from my drink
what have I
done I keep up pretty well of the Mana
production
proud as we feared yeah I forget about
it and then I accidentally tangent my
way through the 30
minutes who would have thought that this
would happen everybody
lot of types of headaches and harder
triggered yeah but
like even if you think it's like because
of PC and
stuff uh I have
a little bit of that headache still on
my spot
trip but I think it was less but I still
remember
having some of
it and still
dare if I saw 20 of my friends charge
someone and get barbecued before they
made it Hopper to Mele range I probably
wouldn't
charge what do you mean charging
charging at
me yeah these enemies are not
smart yeah time to see a doctor this
there I haven't been to a
doctor since I moved I think oh no wait
I might have um did I tell you about
that one time I guess that that was was
after I moved the one where I cried out
of
frustration while eating
cake why I couldn't stop crying while
eating
cake oh man I was really so [\h__\h]
depressed that was this here I think I
don't know if I want to go back to that
doctor I mean he's all right but
I don't
know if that was worth
[Music]
going all the
way yeah but like it really sucks trying
to find one good general doctor
I've been looking for a good one for
ages
now so baby thank
you to try multiple doctors I've been
trying multiple doctors so ever since I
came back from
Japan from the from when I lived there I
mean I've been trying
but it's it's difficult I think I just
especially I think I need to give up
on
um uh like there's so most of the
general doctors that I can find are men
and I'm sorry but uh I as a especially
cuz like I I look young than I am and
I'm sorry but male doctors don't take me
seriously and not just me like this is a
recurring issue my sister and I were
talking about that too and it's a
recurring
issue they just don't take me seriously
for you know being a young looking woman
for my age and for just you know you
know I'm sorry I'm not saying that
they're like misogynistic or
anything but uh it's a little bit harder
to get taken seriously as a woman for
some
reason and then like with fibro mialgia
I'm I'm not really when I say I have
fiom mialgia it's not really me ex like
thinking that I have it I'm just using
it as a placeholder
word uh because like when I got so to
say diagnosed with fibromyalgia even the
doctor was like yeah that's just like
something we say when we don't know what
else you have it's
like really you might have something
else that we just don't know so I just
use it as a
placeholder cuz I I don't know do I
really have that do I have something
else that's just undiscovered whatever
fiber mialgia is just placeholder but
with something like that I think the
moment you bring it up a doctor will
like high chances are they they just
stop taking you serious
seriously because fiber mialgia is like
something that's just it feels like you
can't pinpoint what this person has it's
probably somebody who's complaining
about pain that you can't tag to any
particular illness
and just
it I don't know it
yeah hard to find the solution most of
the people who have fiber probably went
to a lot of doctors
already and it's just like
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah I think a lot of
doctors will
think exaggerating or
like I don't know I'm not like I don't I
don't want to talk down too much on
doctors
like there's
surely at the core they want to help
people but then also especially when
they're not private
doctors uh the prior the priority of
someone with like chronic pain that is
hard to pinpoint and cure and fiber me
Alder and stuff like that will be way
less high and
like like whatever deal with it kind of
attitude
nerve compression look into treating
that interesting tell that to my doctor
I
guess like if somebody goes there and
has something more that you can grasp
like oh I broke a [\h__\h]
leg or I don't know I have uh uh
diabetes or whatever you know then I'm
sure the doctor will take you seriously
but something as vague as fibromyalgia
or any chronic
pain just well I don't know what the
[\h__\h] we're going to do with you just uh
I guess I'll send you to 20 different
doctors so that you're out of my office
now
goodbye so I I don't want to be too
pessimistic about doctors you know but
my experience hasn't been very
good and I know like maybe it would be
better if I had less vague
issues it's
unfortunate at least most of the things
are oh wait this is a wave thing oh [\h__\h]
most of the
things are free at least
so would be more devastating if it
wasn't
yeah I already did five six waves they
only want
five why are we still doing
this
fun for
sure give you
that the lagging is [\h__\h]
though I will restart the game when I'm
out of this dungeon don't
worry more okay there we
go there we go
Yoo
fun thing is pain is pretty subjective
and can be affected by all sorts of
factors social and psychological yeah
yeah yeah that's the thing like usually
they'll be like oh I'm sure it's like
daddy issues for me
bro it's not D
issues it's
not I told my doctors that I have crazy
aillis pain and they're like just take
these pills
[Music]
bro good doctors who listen do exist on
this planet I'm always praying you can
find one I hope so too where where I
grew up I had a really good doctor you
know my mother really liked that doctor
too
but that that guy he was so old he's
probably dead by now but also uh he's
really far away so can I free
them
okay
hello they take so much time to
spawn don't kill my hostages
yeah stop stop stop don't hurt them I
hope my Fire doesn't hurt them
either oh no oh
no stay strong stay strong my oh well I
couldn't stop that okay maybe I
shouldn't have stood there
[\h__\h] keep at least one hostage alive uh
oh that's for Mastery just one I thought
you'd have to have all of
them hello anything else no
okay
oh for Mastery you can let two of them
die how
nice you get more stuff of all damn it I
shouldn't have stood there because that
like poison bomb I couldn't stop it but
also if I stood somewhere else it would
have spawned
elsewhere damn it damn it slay zorm and
collect the sanum key slay zorm where is
that zorm
guy well well
well I'm also like even though I've been
talking about it for months and I keep
on telling myself I need to get therapy
I need get therapy for for years I'm
telling myself that for years but then
all the time I I'm also like well I
don't need therapy I'm strong on my own
I've been I've been through so much [\h__\h]
on my own I'm still here I'm still
strong I'm still
functioning
but I'm I'm really getting closer and
closer to that point where I'm
really I I think I'm really going to go
get it I just need to find the like
somebody the right person I'm probably
going to look for women of course also
cuz yeah I do think for
therapy a guy could be very
um especially cuz they're private anyway
the guy could be very efficient too but
I think also look for
women I think
I would
trust a guy too in like
for
psychological
help but not trusting a general doctor
anymore for that no no no no no yeah I I
I need to go I'm like I'll be honest
I've I've been trying to stay strong but
there's like a lot of [\h__\h]
um Weighing on me right
now that's like even during the spot
trip I couldn't turn that off and
especially on my departure day where I
tweeted that I'm not feeling so good
that was a combination of me feeling the
chronic pain stronger than usual because
of a really long train ride and just
generally feeling
pretty depressed about some
things H why are we already full
again
oh thankfully cat therapy has been as
efficient as ever
but
uh yeah I think I'm really at the point
if somebody would just book an
appointment for me I think I would
just make my way to therapy much
quicker much
quicker where is this guy down here by
the
lady I wish I could have continued as a
psychologist oh you you wear a
psychologist
before hello I'd like to reserve a
appointment for my
friend please because she just she wants
to go but she's just too dumb to make an
appointment and you know schedule
something
yeah there's
that selfcare my friends it's time to
take care of my body again
like that that time when I went to that
doctor where I cried that was also a
while ago and after that you know I was
kind of busy with like traveling a lot
throughout the summer so I gave up again
for a while to try to solve my issues
but now I got time again and I've
settled down a little bit after a lot of
work so maybe maybe
maybe maybe I can try
again selfcare baby I can break that
down mental health
baby we love some good mental health
care
yay we love that [\h__\h]
You' be surprised by how many people
actually do that what wait what do what
special up like therapy oh my God sorry
even my chat is
lagging this game is making me lag so
bad one sec one sec we're almost done
with the dungeon I
think you can still use these
good thing is I'm I'm very good at just
getting my mind off of things for work
for the sake of work and focusing on
work and powering through
it
so
I'm I'm just very high
functioning uh I have a high functioning
depression
probably of course I'm running it on the
same PC you really think I have a two PC
setup you really think I would have such
a
thing do you really
think I would have
that I just took whatever without
reading I'm sure they're all
good I need to look at my level
40 gift also
high functioning streamer low
functioning computer it's not my
computer it's this game though for real
for real will all know this game has
issues with like being
optimized and normally in this kind of
regions I don't lag in other streams so
it's just something something weird
about the resources being hogged
yeah we all know how it is but it's okay
I'm still moving and you can still hear
me this is
fine yum yum yum yum yum
yum this should be the end of the
dungeon oh yeah defeat the mother's
judgment mother why are you judging me
so harshly
mother oh
[\h__\h] can't
see this is such a comfort game for me
oh my God it's so comfy
[\h__\h] maybe I'll go back to Diablo I at
some point
after I'm done with this I've unlocked
the vigorous aspect let's
go you remember what CPU you had nah you
think I remember anything about my
computer I don't know nothing oopsie
what is this claim cool thanks it's not
really oh claim let's go what skill
point skill
point SK point
okay I think now I will restart the
[Music]
game
okay is it okay to but I want to see
does this open now no it doesn't I don't
understand uh Diablo Pros what's going
on here is this just like forever going
to be closed here
it
is not sparking happiness in me went to
therapy in college for about 17 sessions
while it's not a fixed at all it does
help to put into perspective when you
have an outsider to talk
to
uh see that makes me think about it
again like an outsider will have a hard
time understanding my whole life anyway
but
well yeah story Quest okay well um okay
uh I'll restart the
game I won't lose any progress
right explaining it is part of how you
heal I guess I guess I guess so I don't
want them to just listen though I want
them to say something at
least no you shouldn't
okay leave
game cuz some I think some just like nod
nod and don't say much don't give much
input from what I know I don't know but
whatever don't be a man
T are you saying men don't give
themselves much chance to
heal they don't like therapy or
what
a up come here group hug group hug men
bottle up everything I also bottle up a
lot I
do feel cold out a babies okay I go
therapy you go too okay if you can't
afford I mean you probably can't afford
it now after buying my
merch I'm sorry I'm sorry but the merch
will cure your depression believe
me for sure it will just H having the
tiny baby it w in the world and the
white cool [\h__\h] like everything the good
food the good ramen the the warm Ramen
will heat up your heart and your insides
loud having a moment here can I quote
you on that no no no only if it works
then you can quote me chicken soap yeah
like literally chicken soap heals your
soul right and my uh Ramen is chicken
based so some of you guys will have to
die but uh it's for a greater
cost
so well you know how it is
what's that wasn't that some kind of
famous phrase some of you may
die uh where is that from ah but that's
a sacrifice I'm willing to
make but I am from Shrek of course it's
from Shrek some of you may die but it's
a sacrifice I'm willing to make for the
sake of my bite sponsorship not it's not
a sponsorship it's a collaboration
you know what I'm going to make can I
when I make a new character does anybody
know can I really quickly but I don't
start out in Kil Shad so I guess I can't
really quickly activate the the purple
Quest purple thing the
Boost okay Lord fog
one we can see if it let you skip
campaign you
can h H
really you do start there if you skip
the campaign okay does that off does the
game offer you that
like right
away let's make a new character then
really quickly am I going to lag oh I
think I'm fine
yay I I guess I could start with start
out a spirit born I think I'm going to
get the EXP wait but now no the spirit
born is currently Capp at 25 so I guess
it won't work
[Music]
um Druid is the one that turns into
animals right is Rogue can Rogue get
animals to follow them no doesn't look
like
it what else should I maybe that would
be fun maybe Droid would be
fun become
animal
whoa
hicups sporn animals
but I can't the thing is the reason why
I'm doing this right now is because I
want to get rid of that [\h__\h]
Quest so quickly want to boost a
character cuz it only works once
anyway so wait so see how my sorcerer
could have gone ice or fire or
lightning what directions can they go
summon Golems skeleton Warriors Mages or
priests interesting so it's not all that
dark be a fast agile werewolf or a
powerful resilient we bear
oh
bear we're still all over the place
today aren't we not very efficient
I don't know I don't know I can't decide
I if anything I would want to do this
but I couldn't boost it probably now as
long as I don't have the actual
DLC [\h__\h]
it I'm just going to survive this stream
with
constantly having my quest
sabotaged
whatever whatever
I'm almost level 50 anyway maybe it will
go
away but okay I'm not reaching level 50
today I guess DLC is on sale yeah I know
but I'm too lazy to get it before I need
it also they're so mean the cat the cute
cat is only at like the most expensive
DLC version cuz they have like five
different versions right and like the
cute cat is only in the most expensive
one
bro I I might not get it like I don't I
want to buy the cheapest one I don't
care I'll forget about the cat I have
cat's IRL one is sleeping for 3 and a
half hours now next to me on the guest
bed looking like a snail really cute
smooy she's so so
cute she's rudely
cute do you feel that my fist tou heavy
here all that
hatred it's just you said this [\h__\h]
before the Soul Stone
I have to take off my mask so that you
can see how angry I am but I'm still
over 40 yeah wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait what happen
what shut the [\h__\h]
up uh they don't have the chest anymore
so maybe they are and I do have the
Waypoint find a way what do you mean
find a way
in
h Huh
don't you said I would
WR is it a
bug claimed it got the progress I don't
understand huh what does this
mean find a way wait what do you mean
find the way in what does that
mean maybe it's fine maybe it's
fine raise the port kolies oh wait we
might be fine okay we're fine was this
possible before doing all the free
dungeons were were those
optional and now it's open there we go
oh we are finally back hurry everything
here makes my skin crawl it's okay they
were optional oh well they gave me a lot
of time to
tangent all right
then look at those wow
tapestries I haven't released the
tapestry in a long time and I'm thinking
too like after all the this like really
useful merch that I've released not only
with Vite but on my uh anniversary and
birthday merch I think maybe next
birthday merch can be a little bit less
useful so to say again right maybe I
should release some like a nice big
beautiful tapestry
again and I don't know what else but
something that doesn't necessarily have
to be really
useful more decorative this play we've
had also I'm running out of ideas I
guess but we've had enough I guess maybe
a little plushy again I don't know we
have froggy waa so far but maybe I can
think of something else to make into a
plushy we already also have K chicken
plushies but I don't know vampire WWA I
don't know it's not as iconic as froggy
Wawa maybe froggy Wawa in a different
outfit
and then right I could make a new froggy
baa version for next frog week I could
have a wear different clothes maybe a
little dress a little green
dress or crabby yeah I honestly I do
kind of want to do Krabby
wa
kanwa I love like the idea of that and
it feels perfect because orange that
would be kind of orange or red I I would
go for orange and I just really like
crabs and I feel like it would be the
perfect
uh ver variant varant
variant oh froggy wa but then wouldn't
it be crab week instead of frog
week it's so cute though I can wor here
somehow I I have a vision must the
place would they be the same person you
think and just wearing a different maybe
it's froggy Wawa trying to be undercover
like pretend she's someone else but we
all know it's just froggy Wawa but
because so many people are trying to get
her and put her in prison she puts on a
this is the lore she puts on a crab uh
onesie instead and pretends she's a crab
now but you know to escape all
the yeah
people hunting her hunting her
down she's in a crappy mood
yeah so cute I I can see it I can see
it crabby
wa I
love lot of
crap I haven't fought much I love so
much I don't eat them even I've lost the
grit for it they're cute to look at what
are you
doing just poking at
it accompany on into the black tomb I
think we're here that's crazy that looks
really
cool let me look around this place looks
really nice so
shiny
wow wow this is so cool
this is the vibe that that one sauna had
the darker
sauna it actually
is whatever else is here hatred persists
don't try to eat crabby wa strong enough
to attune the Soul
Stone Soul
Stone protect d n is something going to
Spa damn
it what's wrong with
it don't know you tell
me oh there's something there now
manifestation of
hate he's going to be okay he doesn't
even have a health bar not protecting
him
really take too much work to e right so
don't
good argument it's too much work to eat
crabby W her crab Lings no don't how
cruel are you especially cuz you got to
think about it she's not a real crab
she's just pretending to be a crab if
you rip out her
legs you are
evil come on come on she's just wearing
a Wonder old fool what's wrong with
it why won't or froggy W in a duck a
chicken onesie froggy W in a chicken
onesie it must have been damaged when
you're
in astero cute do you know how to repair
it cute we'll need rare materials cuz
she's trying to blend in silver to
start and tools makes sense are chemical
tools she's trying to be accepted and
blend in here and then destroy us from
the inside we need meet me there when
you can
okay where sorry meet me there Vin
honey that sounds
Korean
H he's in
pain oh okay have to I have to walk
froggy WWA in chicken onesie or in Crab
onesie that'll be a difficult choice to
make I started planning uh I put out a
proposal I started planning for my uh
next birthday
life while I'm also still working on the
other one but I have to do it early so
that I get the birthday life on
time this time it will be on time I
think for the first time
time
yes maybe the closing the game fixed the
thing of the quest the purple
Quest like maybe
did which one's going to be in time well
the birthday one that's the only one I
get from now on for like solo stuff from
now on I say but it's not like we ever
really got got the usual
deal that was before they changed it to
only one solo live solo fry YouTube live
per
year except for this one year where
they're giving us two to make up for
it yeah that's why I'm planning this
other one
too I'm hungry
now the winter one that's the extra
one which I am
glad
have but honestly
I'm planning to
at the same time while also doing like
uh the anniversary life stuff was
extremely stressful oh and World T like
I've been I was doing so many things at
once so
[Music]
honestly probably too much anyway like
too much
workload I think it's fine
to actually I think I've come to the um
agreement in my soul that just having
one solo YouTube 3D Live per year might
be okay because for me time passes by so
fast I think as a viewer it doesn't feel
as overwhelming of course because you
just watching a 1 hour thing but for us
it's like months of planning and
stuff and very busy and like dance
lessons so many dance lessons
but for me it's
probably actually a
lot less stressful so even though I also
want to do
more it's probably for the best to do
less not that I have a
choice but you
know also best as well you don't have
big appearances to hold us over yeah
yeah f is
cooking speaking of cooking I'm trying
my best to hold back but man I can't
hold back much longer with watching More
Fry M I finished the third season
and I I think I had something to say but
do I remember what was my what was
my what happened it's a couple days ago
what
happened
um ah oh wait
Gail
Gail I didn't expect him to come back
after he was fired
once so you know when cie replied to me
on
Twitter like when I wrote about Gail and
she's like oh yeah he
was just a really nice guy or something
something like that and I was thinking
she means was because he just got
dismissed
later but turns
out yeah the booster pinned again
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] am I not supposed to be
here at all no I'm supposed to be here
okay I still found my
way let me get the
Waypoint he was so sweet he was so cute
and I think yeah I had this specific
thought okay spoiler alert a little bit
if you're still watching on plan
planning on watching it somay but here's
some of my deep deep thoughts while I
was watching the shows my
observations um there was this time
right when the boss forgot his name he
had this meeting with Gail and asked him
like okay how much longer do you need to
have all the skills us yeah to take over
and and he was like I don't know like he
really wants to work with
[Music]
um uh not
Vander Walt
Walt uh right so he was like really
hesitant and all that and then the whole
reason why all that [\h__\h] went down is
because Walt got really
uh paranoid right but
I
think even though there was reason to be
paranoid from the POV of like Gus
wanting to get rid of both I think Gail
when they were in the lab and Gail was
asking some questions those questions I
think were not because Gail was really
trying to quickly get gain the skills to
take over for Gus I think was what was
going on in Gail's mind was because he
was he just found out that uh Walt had
cancer and Gail really cares about uh
and and has a lot of respect for Walter
I think he was just asking those
questions because he wanted to like talk
about the cancer thing not about gaining
skill Etc whatever like gaining
knowledge like trying to pull it out of
him you know what I mean that scene the
way he asked his question yeah seemed
more like he had a like concern on a
person
level
and was worried about him but Walt
interpreted it kind of correctly but
also not really as oh this
guy wants to replace me or like Gus
wants this guy to replace me while Gus
definitely wants to replace him with
Gail but on Gail in Gail's mind he was
not necessarily trying to to go for that
and do that he was
just trying to you know be sweet and and
ask about you know bond with Walter Walt
yeah and and and you know he was just
worried
that's yeah that's what I felt in that
yeah Walter definitely read it wrong but
in a way he read it right because that
was kind of what was
happening but not really Gail's
intention do you think I think I read it
right I'm pretty sure I that's like saw
coming out of the tower this morning
what was going on in Gail's mind she's
been gone for so long
yeah I felt like Walt I I read it wrong
too I guess damn yeah I think you did I
think I got it right
yeah yeah and that that's what makes it
even more
unfortunate
cuz I mean in the end even if Gail was
it once more trying whatever it is
you're looking for to have that happen
according to Gus
wishes um it probably would have ended
up that way anyway whether or not Gus
was really helping with it or
not
so
yeah at some point maybe it would have
gone that
way but yeah it's unfortunate
you can upgrade your potion oh where in
here too at The Alchemist or so
right
yeah so yeah and I stopped watching
after that even though I really want to
watch more I'm I'm giving you some time
breaking bed oh yes step into my
kitchen mind what you drink what are you
cooking
here um I was going to I check my
chest them up there see what's in the
present bag level 40 60 60
okay lots of money lots of wow resources
sheesh did I get another level up did it
did the bag give me exp
crazy look at that wow
oh looks so fancy we need to we need to
transmog Warf I don't
know
um Frost Nova
size yeah it does look kind of Frosty
here damn
it damn
it intelligence 1.6 o okay but more
maximum life you gain no okay it's all
very ice based bro
why it's all ice based I know I can
change those effects
but I don't think I want to bother with
it uh you have 30% increased Critical
Strike chance against injured enemies
while you're healthy you gain 40%
increased crowd control duration
requires level 44
mhm um
I don't
know I guess I'll just get rid of
everything fire and eyes death and life
now
yeah but it might look cute as a
transmog um oh oh These might be good
plus one to firewall bro bro I get an
extra
firewall and movement speed
taking damage from an close enemy oh
These are
nice finally
something good they don't have
intelligence though but can I not I
think I could put a slot in these can I
not uh
slot slotting was at the jewelry person
right can you put slots into the boots
wait no you are not the right person
[\h__\h] roll intelligence the life for 5
seconds should be rolls to roll to
intelligence
okay free life for 5 seconds okay uh
where do I do that
again a cultist oh
okay wow
[Music]
oh that got
more the next level 60 set better not be
ice focused
bro um how does the thing work again um
here we
go okay
uh ooh I
see o
wait
H we going to go Blue
I think we we're going to go for a
refreshing blue
look these are called War warlord leg
plates do I have that
here
war
no no so we'll just go with something
else no no no wow those look like
Arcane things they look very arcane came
to
me maybe not the best look oh these okay
these are okay
cute
and I don't really have a whole set of
this
huh
maybe this one could look nice together
in blue oh you're
cute have a nice scarf Cape wow wow nice
embroidery yeah and it's got like that
golden armor continuing so that matches
with the
bottoms all right all right uh what do
we change
here I feel like I did get a hat
but maybe I
didn't I don't like that though
[\h__\h] dead bird on top of your head
that's what that looks
like that one's pretty
badass that one could work
too oh
yeah something about this just
[Music]
works pretty sure that is a dead bird
yep
could change my weapon too but I kind of
like this this is like the narissa
tuning fork what I have right now my
weapon I think I like this one cuz also
it has
blue uh details on
it
ah appearing
okay nice look at me look at me look at
me okay then I'll move quickly to
Kad I'm not going to you though oh no no
to do the thing occultist this can I
make the slots and the rrolling both of
the ulst I
for World BS spawning
soon uh what all right traveler how does
this work
again CRA Sal enchant imprint aspect we
want that on the boots right or do we
wait
no enchant replace aics
here this
one
ooh
intelligence 28
yo
sick
sick and then
[Music]
I mean the the AIC is
fine I guess why not but I want a slot
okay is that possible sorry I already
asked maybe you
answered sorry I'm late oh don't worry
about
[Music]
it jeer
she in there
for weapons
Jeweler add sockets ah okay I can't but
I could yeah I wanted another one on
this o it takes like some fancy stuff
and I guess on
this mhm okay am happy with that
and
then ooh gems gems gems wait are those
all my
gems
uh
uh this goes here fine and then oopsie
oh wait I have this one too now I put
uh armor but I'll max out my armor if I
put that in huh over
th000 need to craft bigger ones oh yeah
cuz I got rid of all of them ah there
you are py Palamino I missed
you go to Jeweler to craft more I I want
to take it out now I put it in
no craft gems what do I want if I don't
need the skull on
it only show up for the Apple but like
you weren't there when I was tanging did
you leave because I was tanging too
much you only show up that's so sad you
hate me if I don't play
[Music]
Theo wait we need to talk about that we
need to discuss this emeralds are good
okay
uh I'll make one of these do you leave
poison resistance poison resistance on
the ring
really I guess they're all yeah just the
element
resistances yeah except for the skull
which is extra
armor and I guess poison is the most
common took a nap during the
T it's 5:00 a.m. it are you Japan bro I
mean the name is Japanese but your
English was so good that I thought maybe
not this is their taste test
game well deserve
nap sea bro
ah yeah may maybe let's just say for
Diablo you're willing to pull an all
nighter you surely still would watch
other streams if they're at more
comfortable times for you
right I I I respect that I I can get
behind
that uh anyway I guess poison is okay
diamond or skull and JY depending on if
you okay yeah yeah what what
Diamond I have one of these
already yeah resistance to all elements
h
[Music]
I'll I'll put it in
the
oh uh
oh why was I keeping this
one
unsocket did you give it back okay
uh put that in here and I'm happy for
[Music]
now
okay I'll be here for all your streams B
thank you armor Marx already so get
diamond to max out
yeah sure
any kfp from Europe yeah where you at
European
kfps k ofp k of
people ohai you're
one European Bros where and girls where
you from where you watching from what
country Finland you okay where
Portugal Scotland let's
go Belgian let's go Germany lots of
Germany Portugal Hungary Hungary oo
Sweden Switzerland Netherlands
Czech Spain UK Norway oh it's like all
over the place Finland Iceland Italy
Italy UK Switzerland Italian ger Germany
Ukraine Italy PSA Denmark Germany Korea
okay uh come I was actually just asking
for the specifically the European Bros
but I'm happy about my Korean Bros too
Canada I'm asking about European Bros
give the European Bros some time to
shine yeah good amount of finish
Bros and Swedish
and Italy and Germany and UK UK actually
surprisingly little why do you hate me
is it because I make fun of your acent
I'm not really making fun I'm just
paying respects in my own
way I guess
um I guess
I I guess that's why they hate me [\h__\h] I
love them so much though it's unrequited
love
[\h__\h] what am I supposed to do
UK would love to see more UK
right Belgium but live in the US oh we
have Liz now what do you mean that
doesn't matter you just replace it with
somebody from your country That's how
little love you had for
me damn so
patriotic but think about how much love
I have for
you oh well at least I have a lot of
German speaking uh people the town
doesn't seem to have anything that we
need we're a village in the middle of a
swamp there must be something I can feel
the Magic in this swamp and where there
is Magic there are users of
magic if a witch is what you want go to
the tower then fire's lit she's
home sounds as though we go to meet a
witch of the swamp Okay guys this cat
guard just also that cat it's so cute
it's
fluffy oh my God but this cat just
reminds me of something one thing that
happened in the in the uh Spa weekend
that I
had uh saw this on was this on the last
day I think it was on the last day on
our departure day after we checked out
we still stayed a while longer and
um we and so we let me let me talk about
the last day okay here we
go I'll try to keep it short so we had
our the best breakfast ever again and
then we um did sauna and stuff again but
also we went uh sliding down a water
slide they they have a pretty fun water
slide and then uh this time I took my
sister to the whirlpool with me and we
were chilling the whirpool is like
really up high uh kind of like built
into the
mountain this is like the highest body
of water that they have and so it has a
really good view over everything and
there's a big sauna building that they
have right next to the whirlpool also um
really one of their biggest saas I think
has a really nice panoramic view over
the mountains while also being being
very up high itself but we were chilling
in the world
poool and leaning over the ledge and
looking at the scenery and because of
all the
snow uh there was a family out
there uh with SL sleds yeah cuz you
could rent sleds to slide down mhm and
so I was watching that they were going
up and down and this one time the the
like Father guy he was pulling a
sled and there was an animal on it and
it was really far
away it was a white fur animal and I
first thought it must be a dog but I
pretty quickly thought okay even if this
is a small dog the body shape is kind of
weird and the more I watched the more I
realized the movements are weird too o
this is something else wait there's no
way is this a [\h__\h] cat and then I saw
the tail and the cat was like pawing at
the like uh the Rope or whatever that
was connected to the sled and it was
like playing around while like lying on
the sled it was a beautiful beautiful
white cat that was really energetic and
like holding on to the sled while the
guy was pulling it I like what the [\h__\h]
is going on and then the cat jumps off
and runs away and Blended in with the
rest of the snow but it was so cute and
I'm wondering now is this a stray cat
because such a like I I rarely see white
cats especially among stray cats but it
could be or does it belong to the resort
or does it belong to the guy but I feel
like the cat like cuz it ran away like
he you can bring your pets to the hotel
but but bringing a cat seems kind of
unusual and then taking it outside
without having it on a leash seems even
more unusual so I think it might have
been from the
resort it was a well it was like really
far so far that I couldn't tell from a
first look if it was a cat or a dog so
it was you have to imagine it was that
far I couldn't tell if it was stray or
whatever but I noticed from the behavior
and then seeing the tail when it turned
around it was so cute just a random
white cat in the middle of the snow
riding on a sled and fighting something
and pawing at it it's so adorable and
then jumping off and running away such
cat behavior so adorable I wanted to
find the cat and I kept on like staring
and observing the area in the whirlpool
trying to see the cat again but it just
disappeared and I never saw it again
[Music]
afterwards so God damn it
cute made me really
happy God look look sister there's a FY
cat there all Mirage no it was a real
cat I know it it is true it is
true oh you have the crazy dead bird hat
or something
similar you're the witch in the
tower you changed I thought you Journey
to the
keep yes
well
ta TAA we need your help reparing the
Soul Stone and why would I help
you I'm pretty we all want Elias's
dead we do but fixing the Soul Stone
does your sister have a pet is don't
even get me started and she does not
concern me that's a tangent for later I
don't need much just quick silver and
the tools you have
there such small asks rarely remain so
surely you must know this but you did
help me survive
onon so and you ask why you would help
us [\h__\h] we save for Quicksilver though
find her and she will give you what you
need
bro old Rabbit doll what the
heck find Vala in the cindo waste okay
have fun
Donan where exactly are we going oo okay
pretty
far oops
sorry so
yeah oh my sister when we were having
breakfast she noticed there was a
celebrity a German celebrity I'm not
going to say who but a pretty well-known
German celebrity I wouldn't even have
noticed I was kind of sitting uh like
two tables next to us we were assigned
to a table to always be there for
breakfast and
dinner so we always came back to the
same table and this one morning she
noticed
that the family that was sitting over
there the guy it's a famous German
celebrity
first I didn't
even I looked I peeed and I didn't even
recognize that guy as that guy
but it seems to have been
true so you know it's that much of a
fancy cool place that even celebrities
show
up back
[Music]
well it was not the only celebrity there
at the time what is this is a quest
chain side quest I guess oh wait wait a
second now there's a lot of enemies on
the map so I guess it has something to
do with that side quest
probably have to get rid of all of
them um it's leaving
behind am I supposed to pick those up
aha yeah okay it's similar to what we
had
before they want me to collect these
things I'll do it I'll do it while I'm
here why not
well why doesn't it just pick it up
easier I have to get so close to
it wonder how many it needs last time it
was a
lot but of course we didn't talk to the
Celebrity by the way I thought you know
first of all I don't really care that
much about the celebrity I mean it would
be maybe something else if there was
cat's ey sitting in the same [\h__\h]
restaurant as me but even then you know
celebrities when they're having a
private moment like that you should be
leaving them alone as much as it feels
like you're you're never going to
see celebrity like that ever
again it might feel like you're losing
your one
chance it is done it is done indeed okay
nice yeah like I also like if I'm in a
restaurant or so please I think I want
to be
chilling I mean I'm not
even like I feel
like that guy probably gets talked to
much more than me even cuz like the
people that know me they like uh I don't
know it's not as much the common folk
folk more like you know very
Niche people if you know what I mean so
I feel like
I get recognized less often
[Music]
mhm which is good I guess what the [\h__\h]
is that
stronghold
stronghold oh that's where I had to
go
o what is going
on what is going on what is this
you need help how do I help
you speak of the spirit of the
fire wait what how do I speak to
you okay really close
here you still
alive are Eternal that's not the quest
though huh this body get a little alar
and a new way point okay
I
see I don't think I ever came across a
stronghold own people let's go let's go
let's
go fight
now we Feast on their ases hopefully not
my ashes I need them to
revive Yi party party party party Yoo is
there master here
too retrieve the villagers remains oh
this was too simple retrieve the use
them to extinguish a
okay that
easy oh
okay do I need more enemies to spawn
first it's locked it's
locked oh wait oh CH the up look at the
map I have to go up
there
okay oh wait even further up here
easy easy easy easy easy
easy remain all right I feel like I
won't even ever be using this
Waypoint so maybe it's not worth
spending my time on this but you know do
you know you are trying do sa do you
know I know
I know not
actually maybe this is a big mistake
maybe I'm Reviving something very
evil Mass grave
cool who are
you who
you
nice nice nice nice
oh okay so I talked a little bit about
finishing Breaking Bad let me talk about
finishing not finishing breaking bad but
finishing third season let me talk about
Arcane spoiler alert uh I guess if you
haven't finished watching it yet I might
spoil
something
um
I was really confused when I was
watching um the new episode because so I
first watched the first three episodes
and then I took a little break
right before I watched the fourth fifth
and then the last couple
ones and then I watched them
Aller the the the fourth to the finale I
watched
those on
my vacation now
I was really confused
because when I was
watching the fourth and the fifth
episode it it it was so weirdly paced
and I was like what is going on the
first free episodes didn't feel so
weirdly
paced and stressed and
like quickly changing from scene to
scene and the way they were represent
presenting some of the
scenes felt a little bit like it was a
recap episode you know even though it
obviously
wasn't I don't know how to explain this
best I don't I wonder if anybody felt
the same way
Crusaders yeah it was trippy our
neighbor summoned is the oh hey let's go
with this act of good faith we beg
needed an entire person I would have
loved that but that that would have mean
that would have meant another four
[\h__\h] years or so to wait for it so I
don't want to like roast the show
creators or so because I still feel like
they put a lot of work and love into
it but it was kind of crazily rushed the
pacing was so weird H starting from the
fourth episode espe especially to me
once I noticed that I Tred to observe it
really
closely I felt the fourth the fifth was
weirdly paced the sixth was okay again
the seventh was really weirdly paced
too and surprisingly the the finale I
think was the eighth right that one I
felt was more okay again but maybe
that's just because it was coming out of
a really fastpaced weirdly paced episode
on its own maybe the finale would have
been or should feel too fast paced and
two rush but I thought it was okay oh
ninth was okay I think eighth and Ninth
yeah felt okay for me
surprisingly I think other people are
saying the finale was also really
rushed I think it was mostly four five
and
seven well I don't know I I I've seen
similar opinions uh for sure that it was
really rush they had to shorten it to 50
minutes oh
wow so that's of course unfortunate and
I was so confused okay one thing that I
thought was so
weird the
way that Jinx and by were suddenly okay
with each other
again it feels like they skipped so
much
of fixing their friendship
relationship like I I can see how that's
probably because like how why she was
okay with her again was probably because
she was not with Caitlyn anymore and
just on her own and she was like super
emo now but no it was still too
fast I think it was still way too fast
like why are they suddenly so okay with
each other and working so well with each
other I don't think that was
good that was really unfortunate because
their broken
relationship is one of the main points
of the show and the storyline so you
can't just rush through that that was
something everybody was so invested in
Vander yeah van bringing them together
sure but like uh no it was still too
rush like they were they were too nice
to each other like Jinx was way too nice
to buy already so soon so
quickly like surely deep down she always
cared yeah yeah yeah but it was just too
sudden of a okay let's be besties
now like what's the other day you hated
her the other episode let's just say
because surely a lot of time passed in
between
but we're just not being
shown this passing time cuz VI is
suddenly [\h__\h] emo go it's
gone so many years I held it at
Bay then the Crusaders game yeah it's
just I don't know I understand them
getting back
together as sisters I cannot hate you
for giving me to the
P wow I for give you wow
sweet and
now
where did
I up here oh
yeah nice level up too we there's an
extra dungeon too I have a feeling that
dungeon might be pretty nice in terms of
rewards but wait where's the
Waypoint do I not get the Waypoint until
I do the
dungeon what did you think of the
scene
uh
spicy spicy spoilers over
yeah I don't know it it was the final I
will not say anything specific but I
will say uh there was a lot going on
like they had man too many arcs at or
like story
lines a little bit too many to try to
like fix them all at the end
there look at this
later who is your favorite my favorite
character
character uh Mel I think and I
really love how badass she
became
yo love Mel she's so
hot yeah her skin is glowing girl
slay absolute slay
where's he there
Goblin oh he's stronger
oh go go go
bats is he dead hey he's dead he
what the heck is going on
here these are strong what
the I'm just here hunting the goblin
leave me
alone what am I doing where am I going
what
AM bro what am I actually I'm still
supposed to be here
huh okay surpris when they
chose show because the other regions
have more interesting stories but they
really our what do you mean they have
more interesting stories I thought LOL
had no story but I guess they have like
concepts of a story right I suppose they
give like hints of a story throughout
the
game
so there was bios
M
okay all characters have
lore but it's mostly on the website
comics and
stuff yeah I've seen like cuz they made
that announcement that they're actively
already have been working on another
show that will feature several
regions I'm excited for that they've
been working on it for one year already
so who knows maybe in the next two or
three
years can expect a new one I'm so glad
cuz there's obviously still so much
potential with all the other characters
that they could add a lot of lore to and
and build themselves a spiderweb of
connected stories
around have them intertwine what the
[\h__\h]
I think starting out with Jinx and all
that is great because Jinx is somebody
even nonl players recognize and you know
very iconic
character so I think that was a good
choice and now that they've already
gathered so much
acknowledgement and Trust from the
viewers that they make great shows I
think now they can experiment a bit more
with characters that are not well
known cuz the only other characters that
I can really
say have uh like how to say big
recognizability from even non LW players
are the KDA
girls and I I I doubt that the KDA girls
would show up and would they may
in their story like judging from the
region that they're going to be using
does it make sense to include KD
AER is from Iona
Iona
uh-huh o Ari too ooh okay okay then they
would have some strong hitting
characters for
promotion cuz
Ari very recognizable a too from
KV a pretty famous War which will be
huge
ooh oo I would love
that where's this freaking Vala
girl
hello
hello I'm just laying and I'm not
finding what I need
go
nor why would she be at the top of this
egg guess come there's a nice spot for
her
there oh by the way throughout my trip I
was uh using audible to listen to the
hob wa I didn't finish it I got somewhat
far but
uh I kept on getting really tired
because the voice I'm listening to it in
German and the voice is just
so
soothing it's hard to stay
alive what my sisters do not understand
is that we have more in common with Lil
than with our enemies the tree may exist
outside the Eternal conflict but we
don't our survival lives of the mother
of
sanctuary
okaya spell book The Prophecy oh
something happened lives in my dream
Sanctuary Falls and I along with it but
Elias says there's another path L live L
I feel a connection with her deep in my
bones I know she is the answer no she's
not
Vala baa TAA sent me to get your
help but yeah um I don't know uh like
cuz I was listening to it without
reading so I also zoned out so much I
kept on zoning out and getting sleepy
but I zoned out during parts that I
anyway like recognize from the movie so
I guess it's
okay but still I don't know maybe I need
to read
along
H maybe audiobooks aren't for me after
all and books need NE neither audio
books nor books so I just need to stay
with movies and
stuff I will never
read time to give up on reading yep y
although I am really curious about
certain you know extra
[Music]
lore TAA has unknowingly sent you to
your death o spicy in the end she will
see the foolishness of her pursuit of
aias and she will know that Lilith is
our
future you keep reading a fair
chance girl where are you walking
to waa more ashes for The Cauldron
he's crazy kind of insane I like it oh
[\h__\h] I'm right in it cannot escape the
fire true fire fire light the fire we're
going to fight fire with fire let's go
ow all right she's she's got an
interesting skill set she also turns uh
invisible which is not necessarily
Fair J okay already dead
though already [\h__\h]
dead too bad too
bad
okay a good a good uh enemy in
Fury just needs to be stronger like your
attacks
though uh guess here
another vain put dust yeah we got a nice
ring that I'll look at try reading on
the toilet instead of doing whatever
with your smartphone bro who says who
says I'm going to the toilet in the
first
place well both bonuses from Asus
verocity key passive are active your
attack speed increased by Asus
verocity
Verity where is that
that don't use it for incinerate because
you care about burning damage damage
over time
for oh okay okay has a search function
oh so this ring is not for me is what
you're saying that's
okay oh what's this serpent Stone of the
[Music]
expectant no no no
need oh you have 8% increased Dodge
chance when you dodge for well I don't
think that uh AIX is
useful now
whatever could change it but no need I'm
going
to this
place which of the
wastes return
that's fun I think this is on
purpose ah you're back I'm back place
the purified quicksilver in that bowl on
the table bowl bowl
bowl on the bowl oh
here okay cool we're crafting we're
cooking and how was my
sister kind of bad
friendship Elias convinced her to join
him that can't be she would have known
not to trust Elias you don't know your
sister very well it was Elias that
seduced her but
Lilith she found her
ideals
convincing Vala was my
teacher she guided me when I first began
my
service this this
is difficult to believe I
know even more Restless than before he's
lost a son and inside his grief chips at
him every moment he refuses to face
it mix the
quick
what first off the I'm really cooking
the quick over mix some of it into the
turn the wheel free
rotations
wheel this oh that's a wheel one two it
three
times yeah give it another turn yeah I
was planning on it grind the
sulfur grind it in the morar we have to
cook
Keandre more I'm now observing now okay
it's I feel like I'm the gaale in this
relationship and you are the Walt cuz
you're bald
sh
you you not good that means uh I don't
have a plot armor no it's not
working [\h__\h] what did you do
wrong BR I could have done it
better me we're going to gossip about
him out here as pretty blue
ladies this is like croni and Nissa
together he is not up to the
task what can we
do I suspect he no longer trusts
himself we cannot erase all his doubt
but his most recent grief his son there
is a way he won't enjoy it
though him you could simply leave us to
our Fates maybe everyone needs a
reminder every now and then that you can
defeat danger you only have to try MH
haradrim come
here what why I want to take you
somewhere a place of old Power in this
swamp M I think it will do you some
good okay we're going to a
spa we're going to bathe in dirt like
let's
go oh hey look at that it's actually
targeting where we need to
go the hungering
swamp
Okay thought it's almost 11:00 p.m. I
wonder how much further I should go
today we can go a little bit past
midnight it's just I tangent it so much
today that we didn't get as far as we
could
have
oopsie wait should I sell things first
before I go yes I
should how's your headache doing it's
gone thanks to
[Music]
painkillers k
after midnight I know it's a rare thing
and dangerous very
dangerous good
Salvage that got most of
okay yeah I know very
necessary I'm going to miss Arcane
that's good really good really
pretty it made me cry
too the last couple episodes had some
crying moments
you can play league in the
meantime I feel like the whole Victor
Arc went a little bit would crazy
there's nothing left for me to do can't
you see that let me return what do you
think I return
he went too far too
fast no
har you will remain with us there is
still more to do it's definitely too
fast
because some of the
scenes towards the end were also
like hard to really understand what is
going on at least in that story
line don't worry I won't say any details
again but overall I mean it was still a
great show and the season was still good
but it was really
Rush
m
m yeah if I play League of Legends I I
would only play with friends so you guys
can stop
worrying nothing's
here what even is hex te anymore
right
bro fit insane
and then the whole like as much as I
really love Mel and her
Arc I don't think I understood
everything properly like when she had
her special moment you
know I I I I don't know if I really
understood everything that was going
on yeah
yeah I agreed but I didn't understand
mhm still confused about
it but they're done with the story so I
guess we'll never really get a good
explanation about the questions that I
still have in my mind
game is nothing like the animation well
I get that but I do want to kind of
fiddle around with those
characters you
know the cool thing is Mel is not a
character yet but she's going to become
a character I've
heard her mom's already a character
recently swamp's magic is important here
this looks like Shrek's
house
Shrek V is really fun to
play I think Caitlyn is
hot even hotter in the
game might want to try Caitlyn I don't
know Vala brought me to this place when
I was
younger here you can face your demons
whether they be fear or grief easy to
use who is no no I've had enough of this
and what will you do instead H nothing
in this swamp is free haradin not even
your magic whatever logic you think will
win the day you are
mistaken I where is your sense of
adventure huh not buried in your youth
is
it go outside and make an offering to
the swamp m a ring a necklace something
you hold dear while you do our friend
here will collect two things maggot ior
and yellow
Lotus this is
foolish old man being told by younger
lady what to do
Grumble Grumble this is fo this is
stupid I'm doing
this am I doing
sucks Grumble
Grumble where do I collect
things ah
let me just clear this really
quickly so are they all all those things
are down here no only the maggot
Queen
thing so maybe there is something up
here but it doesn't show me yet cuz I
didn't uncover the
map let me move on a little bit
further do you have an overall favorite
scene in the second season
a hard to
say all happen to fast it's like hard to
register anything as a favorite
[Music]
scene
yeah
same part what do you mean I'm not are
you complaining about uh spoilers I'm
not saying anything
there is the other
one we all know what's in
no I didn't care that much about that
SC oh yeah echo echo Arc was really
sweet I yeah not
necessarily the whole like Echo Jinx
stuff more like his invention and
stuff and oh yeah yeah yeah okay okay I
don't really this is not a story spoiler
but the way he
fought uh with his
thing his invention I guess that's a
little bit of a spoil that he's
inventing something
but yeah especially in that last big
fight I
guess is really cool but then yeah yeah
know I really like
that it's not as SPO he's like that in
the game ah is that his way of
attacking cool yeah I like how
everything works towards like showing
how they built their abilities and how
they perhaps also built their looks cuz
like by and Jinx and everybody they
start out as kids right but then
throughout the show they get closer and
closer to what they look like in the
show or not so much I've heard that some
look kind of different in the in the
game I mean make Haste The but generally
they're like all working towards that
right and I think that's pretty cool
it's pretty
awesome very annoying in the main game m
Victor looks very different Warick yeah
I've heard about Warick looking kind of
different and they're apparently they're
adjusting Victor's looks in the game to
what they look like in the show
now mhm cool spare thank you right I
know it's
cool yeah Jay no Jay Jay looks like
super generic in the game from what I've
seen so I think it's good if they like
the way they changed them up for Arcane
also like Caitlyn's face for example
looks like really hot and cute in the
game from like uh I watched like some
trailer where Jason and Caitlyn were
like fighting or like playing a game of
like shooting
targets um so I saw her face there
looking really
generic she has way more interesting
features in the Netflix show so I think
that's cool
do you see the braur light each of
them then we will drink the tea and
wait no I think not her outfit I I mean
her face looks super generic in the game
wait for what for the to call out to
your soul and draw what festers from you
like poison from a wound
I was going to I was sure since the show
started how vior was going to end I
don't know if they need to update him
much on the game well seemingly they
do yeah wild Rift wild Rift is that a
different
game oh is that the like fighting
game mobile leag Ah that's why they look
different but her face probably still
does her face look like in the main uh
the the in the main League game does it
look like how it looks in the
show oh we cooked something
crazy I'm just chilling
oh we're all tripping at least girl is
on her side they're
coming
father I will don't worry so he does get
to
talk with his
son father
in is he
real how it
did we summon a dead person or is it
just in his head my
son please come back to me he can't back
I should unless you become a necromancer
I should have said no I should have kept
you with me at Al
time why did you let me go I don't know
okay that looks like more in his head in
your face that doesn't sound like
something he would say you were ready
you needed to
go I
did and I do again stop
just
father I'm ready
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm dying I'm
sinking my
festo what does that fiend want from me
now of all times
I'm sorry that wasn't even I just had to
think back
uh that wasn't even like that funny of
course
but yeah
what's going
on she what is this world excuse me
Alice madness Returns or whatever that
was
called I warn you the horod would hold
you back you Fluffy
Boy well look at them so consumed by
their emotion so fast that they forget
what really matters what matters
tell me fluff fluffing you matters lus
is the true threat not Elias yeah that I
agree with
that such such a pretty boy such a good
boy doing a s you want to
Tre I know why you're so afraid of
her actually my fate is tied to yours if
she devours me Sanctuary is lost look at
him pondering he's so cute uh but you
still have a chance to stop her you know
how this world gives me Alice Vibes what
if I opened a portal for like the cat
out of this
swamp let the horra LI is their sin to
Bear you and I can work together to stop
Lilith you gastl
me piece of
[\h__\h] sounds full of [\h__\h] I know who my
real allies are my friends take me back
to them take me
back come on the Day of Reckoning will
come and your true friends will be
revealed friend reveal no more 3.0
reveal back to your allies okay bye
thanks I don't know what this VIs it was
for but okay if L prevails e you'll only
have yourself to blame shut up shut up
got those brain worms out of my
head wait I just had some I had a
thought ah fre yeah I don't know if you
guys saw um but so mik Senai was like in
our like big General chat she was like
hey I I'm going to um graphic design do
a graphic design stream again where I
make people's
thumbnails uh who wants to do one and I
was like the first one to sign up
immediately uh even though I was on
vacation I was on my phone so I was
like please I suck at making thumbnails
and I have something important coming up
that I need a nice thumbnail for so she
made a thumbnail for my 3.0 which we all
know is coming anyway at some point it's
not quite finished yet I'm still asking
for like another thing to be adjusted
but soon soon soon thumbnail is ready
now thank you m sa by for making the
thumbnail so cute that she's doing that
really appreciate
it yeah Elite thumbnail it's going to
give me luck right for my reveal I'm
sure it's going to go better thanks to
her
thumbnail she revealed she made it on
stream I said yeah no problem like
obviously I know that
by asking you you're going to be making
it on the stream so but it's not like me
having a 3.0 at some point is a secret
because C already revealed hers right
yeah we all get one eventually so I
don't know yet he wandered around for
hours until the tea wore off a long
journey through the swamp is more
rewarding than a short one yours was
even longer it's seems MH did you face
your inner demons as the harod did mhm
yes hopefully for the last
time hopefully
indeed let us
begin yeah I guess we drank Mi the quick
silver in the pot wait we
again wait what what we're repeating
everything
and the fire turn the wheel twice twice
only okay no more no less got it got
it now grind the
sulfur
carefully
okay apparently we did too much last
time he's confident determined yeah wow
he's cooking for
real going do it D cook
yeah the blue stuff
Mallet oh [\h__\h] just chill you
chill we're cooking sulfur now okay got
you Boss chef yes chef careful now stand
back careful too much sulfur careful
careful d
stand back he got
to what did I just throw in there did I
have permission to do
that going to [\h__\h] it
up it's going to work this
time
oh intense
hammering
a a
a b how much longer
bro that's that tiny
little it's a tiny last
bunk you
good is it
done was it so easy then you have no
idea the toll of such a thing no idea
what one must
face overcome
to perform this act of magic okay
perhaps not but still
enough it is done let us not TR
yes we have our task at zachar room keep
he's funny let's finish
this such a
diva it's making the CP knife o yeah the
CP knife was definitely forged in fire
right we did
that I guess yeah now this this would be
the next
step which is down here
[Music]
okay how L are you for supposed to forge
things
uh
well shut up makes it sound
cooler let let's pretend it's
special it's not even why is it not
showing
wait
bro I saw it switching I literally saw
it I witnessed it
rude
Quest wee
[Music]
what are you
doing what are you
hiding mhm this is mine
now I find it
I I want to watch
Wicked in the
[Music]
theature I want to watch it I need to
find time to watch it yeah had the AR
granded
one red was so good really because I
know some people like I guess that was
only before people watched it people
were like trying to like hate at it and
be super skeptical about it but I think
now that people have been watching it
there's more good feedback than bad
one mhm better than it seems people gave
Ariana too much too much hate just
because they feel like
hating on her is the way to
go she is so qualified for this okay I
love
Ariana she was an activ for
exactly people in the internet just hate
everything by default yeah no cuz they
were like oh this actor would have been
better blah blah
blah
bro like Ariana's voice is one of the
best voices of the
century and I mean 100 years I'm not
sure if I chose the right words this
time just so you know I mean 100
years did I choose it right Quest
we're good I'm going to be
fine know in the current
century definely one one of the best I'm
not saying the best although could be
but I'm saying one of the
best what are you here for greet
shrine what are you here
for where are the enemies wait let me
run over to cck Quick click whatever is
here someone
there yeah just start whatever you want
to
start my child quick start it
now oh
okay is a walking
Quest quick s more
my GRE can only ah it's
over scort the Wayward sold to their
loved
[Music]
one find their loved one Before Time
runs out wait how do I how do I
influence
that oh dear oh dear oh dear oh dear
yeah why did I do
that are we doing
well where is she oh she's just chilling
here who
lag
W what the
[\h__\h] ah it's kind of insane
[Music]
did we do it I did it
ly
me well I think I killed no no there we
go I killed the loved
one okay got some cool stuff haven't
done an event in a while
so good to do it every now and then
[Music]
hours
longer do you think I objectively even
though I tangent it so much you think I
still made good progress in the
story
Diablo Diablo Pros oh my
God yeah
an act well yeah but it was already
pretty close to being
beated hard has a lot of running around
pretty good after the free dungeons okay
yeah cuz I I did a lot of optional stuff
those dungeons were
optional the ones that I
did that Fortress
place and now I'm also just running
around killing things because it's
fun what a loome place to come seeking
knowledge he must have thought he had no
choice neither do
we I need like finding Timo another set
of eyes at last I've been searching for
Timo with little success was that
randomized oh yo
uh lady is it
you
no who's T did I see that person before
feel like maybe I
did power Wasing with fire yeah it
really feels like
it that was just a random NPC minor
character okay yeah I I mean they didn't
seem to have that specific Aura but was
so
Random what else what else what else
happened that I wanted to talk
about do you think Elias knew Ty she
went to his I I think while I was gone
what do you know call oh the C oh I I
have to talk about the C to but I was
going to say
Call's uh second
solive has been
announced Let's Go cie it feels like she
to me it feels like she already has done
several but like she just had a lot of I
guess like Ira life appearances besides
Soul lives it feels like she already
had more than
one but this time yeah it's in
America and I I hope that I mean even if
it's even if I'm not the one benefiting
from it perhaps in the future I hope
that it opens
up more doors and
possibilities for Ian to get concerts
particularly
overseas like solo
compers I'm honestly not very confident
in filling a venue like that and if it's
not a big enough venue it's probably not
really worth it
for our our like management
to you
know like book it and organize it like
to really make
profit so you know I'm fine you know I
don't really have High Hopes anymore I
used to not anymore I'm very realistic
about it but I I just hope that it opens
up more doors for other willing
motivated um girls to get a
chance it would still be cool like if I
ever get the offer of course I'm not
going to say no even though I would be
very worri
still yeah it's a good
start a good start
to a brighter future with soul lives
outside of
Japan going to bust the do I don't know
it's it's
okay what where where is this person
not in the dungeon
right feel like it would tell me to go
into the
dungeon keep a chance on positive kfp
will F Vue for you well it really
depends on the
size I
[Music]
think well but anyway it doesn't matter
now because it's not like anything
is uh for the
bait wow wow wo wo whoo whoo wo
W doesn't matter to talk about something
that might never happen so let's not
talk about it I'm just happy for
cie
um well
yeah I'm glad she gets another chance to
show off her sick wrapping skills and
stuff and her big discography
I will not be a guest at it whatsoever
though in case you are thinking thinking
that that might
happen Cy will rock the
stage she will
rock La kind of for old
team those running away from
trouble and those running toward it
which kind are you I wonder maybe we can
do a a watch
long of her show on my channel
M never heard of him we think Elias the
time zone though on the time frame TAA
said you could help
it
taisa only she would be coldhearted
enough to send a child to die out here
this person looks [\h__\h] up you have no
intention of dying one of you will
that's the way it always
ends go back where you came from I won't
have a child's blood on my hands I saw
my mother possessed by Lilith driven so
mad it killed
her I'm not a child anymore
exactly so be it if this Elias made a
pack it was with the tree of
Whispers there are many paths to reach
it
400 a.m. at the nearest I'll think about
itani I'll incense is kept in the temple
there retrieve it and your path to the
tree
begins I some of you guys planning on
going in person Nel and I will see if we
can get some more information
Tim are you trying for
Ticket
me nice of course you are I wish I'll be
trying
to yes
yes well good luck you had a soul life
where would you want it see that's a
really difficult question too but you
know Europe would be nice and all but I
think I still have a bigger audience if
anything in na so I would also hope it
was in an NA but I'd love for it to be
like on the east
coast East Coast bias it's a bit closer
to Europe
too I just liked it more on the East
Coast like New York New York was
sick well yeah that's just too many
hypotheticals
Vegas Vegas
no what if all H you members would do a
group concert together in
Europe sorry I sucked my lip um I don't
know if that makes any sense to do if
there's no like big connection like a h
group go Amsterdam or col yeah but like
does it make sense to like make European
an travel to na or does it make more
sense to make NA people travel to Europe
when more viewers and more possible
concert goers are in na unfortunately
that is the reality that the answer is
make him travel to
na we are fine going for dami yeah but
like not all of Na people are you know
there's just more possible
audience uh in
na yeah if Europe grows more you know
that would be
nice
but I feel like would be nice to maybe
look into having even though there's
time
zones like s cuz like we're virtual
right so I wonder if we can't do like
rent aent men you in Europe and in na at
the same time have the concert at the
same time like live at the same
time and be in two places at once yeah
that'd be sick but that means I have to
fill two venues I don't think I can do
that at the same time yeah but like SLE
casting
yeah but if it's in like two continents
that are are like close is like Europe
and na then maybe you can still find a
middle ground in terms of
time can't do it in like three
continents at the same time though that
would be like Asia Europe na certainly
impossible it's a cool
idea
right yeah yeah theater screenings you
know that's different in my opinion
because that's set up in a
way that they're just screening whatever
is happening in a different venue like I
don't
know different different but worst case
that could
definitely why why you making me talk
about something that will never happen
anyway but if it were to be an NA surely
I would hope to fight for uh at least a
simultaneous screening in a theater or
something and
in Europe but don't let don't make me
talk about things that are never going
to
happen no no let's just uh you know
let's just live in the reality and
celebrate C's win big
win thank
[Music]
you let me let me end the uh gaming
session here for
now cuz CU we just finished a quest that
should be good point to end it and we
got so far today thank you for watching
more Diablo soon maybe next week
actually I think I have time next
week
yeah be kind oh my God is that the the
club in
Berlin bro that place is scary no I
don't want to be live
there not long until you finish the
campaign from this point let's go pro do
you think I could do it in one more
stream if I focused on the game and not
tangent it for 30
minutes what do you
think you should try out Poe too early
access next week oh Early Access so it's
something
new Path of Exile you
say should be close enough to the end
really oh I can start a bit early I
don't mind starting
earlier wait do you really think I can
do it I only saw like one
answer just don't go inside dungeons
okay okay like no optional dungeons H
but then again do I want to rush it so
much it's been really nice but then
there's a DLC like it's not like you
know there's still more game
afterwards yeah it's not like I'm really
ending it I'm just ending the main story
[Music]
H I'll think about
it I think about it don't think you
could focus on the game and not tangent
for no no I could this time was special
because I was gone for a couple of days
so I needed to let my tangent out this
time was
special you know
I recommend running act six in one go
instead of splitting it but yeah I also
like if it's manageable to do in one
stream I prefer to not split it
too also for the
immersion can't believe we had another
moment of laughing at
Donan I didn't expect that I'm sorry
he did like he it did sound again like
he was laughing but it was very way
shorter and more compact so normally I
think I wouldn't have laughed it if I
didn't already have this previous
experience yeah I'm sorry I'm so sorry
I'm sorry that caught me so off
guard I have so many DMS oh wait is the
video out
they oh wait yeah right it's not out
because I'm supposed to put it on my
Channel all
right oh they finished the
video I guess I'll upload it right after
should I put up a I need to I want to
kind of check it though a Vite video
M does it matter what time you put it up
now I'm streaming but I could make a
premiere for like 1 hour from now or
so right into it at the end of the
stream could do
let me see what they say it was supposed
to come out yesterday but it wasn't
quite finished
yet so I want to watch it before I put
it up
though let me let me let me quickly look
into
it while muting it for you
guys oh
cute
oh
oh okay okay it's probably fine I don't
have to watch the whole
thing looks good looks like they figured
it out cuz I sent 3D
footage you can hear it a little bit
whatever close your
[Music]
ears yeah they they they made a really
cool ass professional set looks like a
kfp I mean I think you already saw like
some Snippets of it
possibly but yeah I'm also in there no
need to Max your audio I'm about to put
it up
anyway all right okay then let's if they
don't have an issue with it I guess I'll
schedule it
to maybe an hour from
now and we'll just R into it so it
doesn't matter if it's kind of last
minute because I'll be ring into
it yeah they put so much work into
it so much love I really want that that
that K I wonder like did they 3D print
that or what cuz it's
huge
oh ho macaroni who crafted that
crazy what do I call a
video is there a title they were
envisioning and envision i n or e n
envisioning right
envisioning for the video
and
vision okay well suan I'm going to prep
this while I'm talking to you guys
and then we'll watch it together first
time together me too also first
time well let's go to
here
chat I'm cooking
something World premiere hope you had
fun watching the diabo part
though I really like this game it's such
a chill Comfort game while still having
like cool action PE PE fire fire fire
fire power fire
simulator what is it I just got back uh
Vite
related video like like launch video I
guess it was supposed to go up yesterday
but it wasn't finished so now that I'm
gone from the game let me put this up
again and you small
wawa little
B saw the email
mhm I'm waiting for an answer let
let me I guess so I do want to read
super
chats I
wonder where we need to
continue let me check
H
oh oh okay I got a
title I'll add something to do it light
collab launch trailer there you
go okay uh early Phoenix let's put the
codes into the description early Phoenix
and was it kfp inl or inl
kfp liar what's a liar's bar
oh oh oh
something superat okay I
see for
15 uh where the [\h__\h] is 15% off of your
purchase as well
as for an international shipping
discount okay ifb IDE
okay you can get all the cool stuff
here can't think too much about the
description this this will'll have to do
uh and then they sent me some thumbnails
too which one do I
use yeah I think maybe the first
one don't tell about about the other
code but does the other code give more
percentage off I don't even
know that one is only for people who
watched all the videos and figured
something
out couldn't be me I can't figure out my
own
life where did it save here
um should I write a little bit in
Japanese too
uh
uh well I don't know what what to write
eh
[Music]
get get
true and I wanted to sound professional
what what do I what would I write if I
was a professional
early
Phoenix uh shipping shipping what's
shipping in
hongo uh uh uh uh
uh
shipping
shipping I should know
help
shiing
uh ship
[Music]
uh might be
C the go
so these clothes are so in your face now
you can't miss
them okay this will do for now and then
did they say anything about the time is
that
okay I guess they
didn't they didn't say they're not fine
with it so I guess they're fine with
it so uploading it now is okay with
Premiere in 15
minutes uh my video contains paid
promotion like product placement
sponsorship or endorsement
yay yes it
does let's add some hashtags by cooking
knife
uh
Ramen
uh uh yeah
maybe
that uh
category
entertainment
yeah I think there's a cooking category
maybe but I think entertainment is
better in this case cuz it's a funny
video
[Music]
my stomach is BL bloing for a while
now
schedule
premere
um 27
so half past
midnight I
think so we have like 50 more minutes to
read super
chats I hope the video is okay CU I
didn't check
it but I I saw a rough of it before they
properly put in the 3D
footage and it was okay like as long as
the and it looks looks fine the first
couple SEC uh seconds yeah it's 8
minutes long I'm not going to watch this
whole thing on
stream she'll be okay she'll be okay
yeah
oh
okay
well okay
I hope this is
right so it's like opening a gotta but
it's a video yeah and you already know
what's coming out of
it okay premier's in 46 minutes bring
your own bgm today yeah I guess I was
just like busy right now
but maybe I'll tweet about it
too let me tweet about
it a big
V trailer reveal in 50
minutes I'm still streaming but no let's
leave that out whatever so I can retweet
it later and it will still make
sense uh what do you call these like is
it QBC or so and what do you call that
show that the commercial shows where
they show off
products was it V Q VC or
so
QVC
special
QVC uh oh infomercial okay let's call it
special infom I think it's really an
infomercial special
infomercial about all the sick products
we have to
offer
[Music]
St okay there we go right Ramen became a
member
wait wait is that
real am I being observed and
watched I've done so much communication
about this on
stream and this whole time I think our
staff that I'm like talking to
actively has never been
like like realizing that I'm doing all
this on stream and like talking about it
on stream oh hey private account as well
let's
go uh where's the thumbnail
here
CA very funny okay I guess we have the
approval stamp of putting this out so
suddenly at least we can write into it
that's good you
know I wanted to put it out on my off
day ideally because you know I don't
want to clog up the algorithm too much
but this will do which one's
the where's my
thumbnail sponsor disclosure in
description
uh H wait a second my brain empty uh I
hate like when I open my download folder
it takes like 5 million years like it's
trying to load everything it doesn't
even load in a in a particular order
it's like loading randomly but of course
the thing I'm looking for takes the most
time no even when I cleared it out
before it still takes a million years
but okay I got it I got it I got it can
I tag
bite on Twitter yes
okay all
right there we go tweet is
out now we wait and read super
chats the clock is ticking here we go uh
uh what am I doing uher
holderer should I should I should I play
music I'll play music I'll play music
guys the trailer is going to be good so
you guys better stay for
it it's so oh my God so
professional all the cooking shots and
the close-ups and everything you're
going to like
it Li bar you is me okay okay okay chill
chill I know I
know um which
music I want like an infomercial
music I don't know but I have this one
that I used a long time
ago oh wait you don't hear
it it's going to turn me insane it this
feels like shopping music some kind of
like I don't know Nintendo DS shopping
music or so
[Music]
okay Liar's bar found it hey I'm not
even that far back
woohoo all right Jacob 47 action oh wait
I should put the thumbnail
up ooh that Godly
[Music]
artwork here we
go Cruz
dun it has such an awkward
pause doesn't Loop
nicely wait changing
music anything
[Music]
here I
like Cruz thanin D thanks for the red
chat wait I need to add something to the
description of the
video
[Music]
CH isn't this
nice audio St audio St we all love audio
St audio St audio St everybody loves
audio stop audio stop audio stop this
stream is sponsored by Audio stop no
it's not why am I lying why the [\h__\h] you
lying audio St audio St AIO St AIO St
AIO St AIO St
St
AIO AIO
St AIO
St audio St
[Music]
so what's wrong with
me I love audio
stong strange super
[Music]
chat D face R buy and kiss from minin
happy birthday to an outstanding chicken
miffin are you
here oh yeah it seems to have been your
birthday mff happy
[Music]
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday happy
birthday to you happy birthday to
you
[Music]
ah I got the infomercial music f
oh sick is this like originally
composed did you guys commission
that why is it a
W.C download file what is that do that
[Music]
plain oh yeah let's
go k King I'm here to offer you many
products that will make you wallet cry
and your future will be destroyed as
well as your children's future in the
future if you ever happen to get
children this will me a big mistake
because you will not have the money to
support them and their dreams of course
also not to support your own dreams
because now we have many many many many
things that you must have because
otherwise like it'll be so sad to not
have these things that are so exclusive
I'm so nice but of course I'm just
kidding of course I'm just making jokes
you don't have to buy this by the
way of course not but if you want to buy
this and destroy your life with it but
also enrich it and give it a nice flavor
with the amazing Ramen that we have to
offer made by our own companions our own
colleagues and when I say made by I
don't necessarily mean the production I
mean the ingredients are provided by our
own chickens one of us one of us one of
us we love this kind of of patriotic
feeling that we feel in kfp we are loyal
to ourselves and one another made by and
for kfp we include each other we don't
let anybody be an outsider you can now
join KP to be part of this great cycle
of Life what was first the chicken or
the egg we will never know but what we
will know is what was last the chicken
because the chicken dies and goes into
this beautiful Ramen that you can now
try yourself if you order the ramen
perhaps it will arrive before you will
also be sacrificed to be made into more
Ramen hopefully you can try it before
you die for it try it or die it yes
indeed thank you thank you now let's
read Super
Chat the cycle of ramen
[Music]
am I just ordering my last meal
yeah yes
indeed try it or die for it maybe that
sounds better try it or die for
[Music]
it made by for and off kfp for kfp by
kfp using
kfp using using homegrown local kfp your
neighbor might be in it your friend
might be in it
your brother might be in it or you might
be in it before you know it yes that's
where that flavor comes from the Flavor
that just feels so familiar It Feels
Like Home you know why because it is
taken from your home it is you inside
the ramen that's right hey I maybe I
should have had a hand in writing these
scripts I feel like I'm popping off
right
now may I of help writing the
[Music]
script at least for the
infomercial I think it's very
convincing am I eating myself yes do you
remember the anime that we watched
recently where the snake came up that is
eating itself and becoming a cycle that
is literally you if you look down at
yourself you will notice or if you look
into a mirror your feet are currently in
your mouth right now at this very moment
it is a beautiful cycle of chicken life
you are literally chicken botles right
now isn't it
[Laughter]
[Music]
fascinating no it is also very
terrifying I realize I realize how
terrifying all of this sounds but trust
me believe me believe in your boss don't
think of anything else # woke #
yolk by the way the ramen might be nice
if you add a little bit of egg yolk or
just a Ramen egg aama on top of it don't
forget the aama
[Music]
I am supposed to be reading super chats
but it's okay I'm not that far behind
let me take my time with it don't stress
me out I'm going to throw you into the
fryer if you stress me
out stay calm
kfp thank you for the Super Chat D hood
and thanks for the uh sweet sweet
support from miffin also happy birthday
miffin D Ro to Berard d oh oh you
already got the wishes right yeah yeah
James
Jackson than for the RP chat thank you
for allowing me to save other people's
[Music]
lives yeah C right jail jailbirds eat
garbage and taste terrible really see
wow kfp are
delicious it's a small price to pay to
be delicious
we're feeding hi it's like a cycle so
well I guess the first ever kfb chicken
I'm already stopping reading super chats
for a moment but the so high quality
chicken eating a high quality chicken
gives return of more high quality
chicken this must mean that perhaps
maybe the first chicken was fed other
things than cannibalistic foods but ever
since then KP are just feeding off of
each other
so yeah it carries
over chicken
sap wow
sooy the end is never the end is never
the end it's never the end we're like
British cops what what the plot chickens
you mean
[Music]
uh yeah so uh thank you for allowing me
to save other people's lives thank you
for your music giving me strength sorry
only using Google trans ah you mean
maybe me saving your
life thank you for music keeping me
strong you're welcome thank you for
listening to my music I'm glad you enjoy
it and I'm glad I can make your day
nicer hopefully thank you Rupa for the
support and all the love I hope I can
continue giving you the happiness that
you
[Music]
deserve thank
you Game 8910 Dan by the way you know
what this means V Ramen you heard it
here
first V Ramen
supports
cannibalism oh my
God y b
I'm not helping their marketing right
now am I a
bit well well well they should have done
their research properly we thought they
did their research I mean I mean I think
they're
aware I think they're
aware
mhm
wellow we will we won't cancel them why
would we we're in it with them they're
in it with us no
comment I'm too blind to
[Music]
see where I can't see the
comments I'm so
blind at least you guys are um quoting
it where
ah ah there we go
no you're blending in too
much it's almost like it were a
[Music]
kfp well I hope that comment I just made
won't get you in
trouble T dun Alin dangun orange Fox W
thank you for the pinky orange Fox
M M fox I'm foxy for sure thanks for the
support I see you're probably just
promoting your newest furry W in your
profile picture just trying to show it
off fome D MP thank you for the pinky I
missed a classic Kata with two hats it
reminds me of when you first debuted it
my baby well you're lucky the endid W
has two hats and I doubt I can take them
off but also I have the tiny hat in gold
on right now
too
mhm mhm it looks nicer in gold and it's
smaller I feel like isn't it too big in
the N isn't the small hat like barely
small it's not small at all why is it so
big
small hat too big it's not supposed to
have so much
presence such a big
presence CU big head yeah but like
compared to the
Beret feels like
huge redo the whole
M uh 4 years later finally
[Music]
releasing in total 8
years nah it's out
now I won't take it
[Music]
back we got Android before GTA 6 yeah
mhm surpris who would have thought 5
months ago I wouldn't have
[Music]
bought and EX version that's all the
same but the small hat is
[Music]
gone anyway thank you m I'm sure you
will like the neroid
huh num that b b
b f dun bad ghost dun fish yummy D sa D
Galaxy D and H D thank
you okay fers
[Music]
bar eat in the
tal is next
up really short
one so cute I really like this
art take 47 n and out for f for the
pinky sneaking this in before I Scurry
off to work today is my fourth birthday
I've celebrated as part of kfp last one
I have to spend at the office for a
bit glad there's what I'm sure will be a
very fun stream to keep me company
cheers pause
a okay so at least you were able to
watch while you were at
work well working on your birthday do be
like that sometimes if you think about
it I also always have to work on my
birthday happy birthday
offer offer offer
congratulations happy birthday to you
you're at work right now too oh how was
your
birthday besides working did you treat
yourself to something at least after
work what is the V Ramen code for
shipping if it's international shipping
then kfp I NT L should do the
trick I don't think there's a particular
code for national shipping but I think
you are international
Anyway by the way uh so like for South
Korea uh everything seems okay now after
doing some research on the V
side uh so perhaps if you're trying to
order something and it doesn't seem to
ship to your country
maybe throw an a Twitter message to Vite
and they could look into it if something
was possible for that country after
all yeah like what about
Mexico Tim while you're here what about
Mexico is Mexico no good or is it only
particular products because I did see
somebody trying to like order to
makeo wrote to their email and they
added it in minutes what a specific
country within
[Music]
minutes
really wonder if they'll be able to do a
UK knife yeah they said they're they're
looking into it crazy [\h__\h] about the
zombie knife and that's even like a
pretty recent development what the
heck no money for the merch right what
perhaps you can get something smaller or
so you don't have to get all of it
unfortunately Mexico has extremely
strict laws on Imports which we're not
able to get the documentation with at
the time ah too
bad maybe for a reun in the
future we could try to get a a couple
more countries
[Music]
in I don't know if it's a Time issue or
so
[Music]
but hope there's a rerun
right yeah
we can make it happen I'm
[Music]
sure it's hard to order anything bled in
the UK and Ireland UK yeah I know I
looked into the zombie knife
thing was like oh but that's so recent
[\h__\h] why did my knife have to be so
fancy I like it
though I like it but it will also still
look fancy even without the the cuts at
the top
anyway where was
IIA simp
[Music]
Ty naan cotton thanks for the pinky
hieno the brief fire blem talk earlier
reminded me of a recent game that I
thought you might like I suggest
checking out unicorn Overlord seems
right up your alley unicorn Overlord
oh
[Music]
oh some of these screenshots remind me
of um what was that game that I
[Music]
played was that um I mentioned it a few
times before something Ain spere yeah
Alin
spere it's like similar in style
but I don't like there's this like
closeup where they talk and stuff but
like there's the shots were I see like a
whole castle and everything that looks
very strategic I don't
[Music]
know yeah I guess it's kind of fire and
blendy in that
way same artist oh I miss Ain
spere but you're making me remind myself
of check if we have what was it Poe Path
of Exile
perms of
ex did g say anything about it cuz you
guys mentioned G did she like say we
don't have them or we trying to get them
what
companies okay we don't have them now
don't know how fast we could get
them halfth of Exile to
[Music]
grinding gear games okay I don't know if
we ever got perms for a different
grinding gear game
[Music]
game but they're the publisher and
developer and yeah that looks good is it
like not continuing the story of the
first
[Music]
game it's daunting for a beginner
you good to start with this one okay
just grind
gear 20 years after the first R another
hotel I can try to get PRS for it I
don't know if it'll be in time for the
release or if I even have time to play
on release
date but we'll see I'm interested seems
like a lot of people are hyped for it
too
[Music]
okay thank you Nathan for reminding me
of a different game that you weren't
even bringing up zero2 dun and Sai dun
happy belated birthday
Sai congratulations thank you so much
don't worry about not being able to
Super Chat as much take it
easy take it
easy relax take it easy
[Music]
relax take
it you're welcome hope you had a lovely
birthday celebrate yourself cuz you're
amazing I I love my cfp chicken
sty okay next is again the
hello wa look at her wow SLE beautiful
gorgeous love her I love her what a
woman what a woman
[Music]
maybe I'll get the product earlier than
I thought I would I probably would still
take a
while oh
I might get the products this week if
Customs isn't the
[\h__\h] hopefully they'll not be a [\h__\h]
please don't be a
[Music]
[\h__\h] then I'll have to set up a cooking
stream for next week can't set it up now
for this week
but next
week
[Music]
ooh ooh okay stress I'm nervous cooking
stream is making me nervous
[Music]
okay I'm look into
it oh how smovie you got up finally she
slept for 6
hours the whole time in this room baby
16 minutes
okay she a
baby I think she also without me
noticing went to toilet and eat
something really quickly
now 6 hours 6 hour
nap catle got more sleep than I
did that's well depressing I mean 6
hours that's just like her
nap you know she gets even more sleep
throughout the day at
night well it's sweet though you know I
mean you know I I feel kind of bad
because it's not like I'm giving them
anything to do while I'm streaming so
all they can do is sleep but then
usually after my stream I eat and then I
go to sleep so then they sleep again so
I feel kind of bad but I guess cats like
sleeping
[Music]
anyway
so sometimes I do feel like I should
entertain them
more wait let me quickly read these
super chats and then go on the cat
tangent take a 47 D and done drone D
sandwich D Tanaka from
kfp what did you do to the K I don't
know I I I most
I I did it better the first time but I
know I know I'm
trying I'm not putting cream in it at
least
John fancy d m g d
h see me
H I hope it's correct
P let me double check
[Music]
Papa
Chim
not
pretty
come not yet and
[Music]
oh El Anon web d and
r o big red Danish Super Chat your name
even says key Railway engineer and four
years Lear ER it's like you're so proud
for being a four years ler okay the red
super chat says took me about four years
to finally be settled and have an
earning to pay for my main job at kfp oh
thanks for all the years for now and to
further on and now back to more silent
Ling are you actually like is your job
actually like Railway engineering or so
cuz you gave yourself that title if
you're watching right now get out of the
shadows and answer my question
immediately don't you dare hide from me
while I'm openly questioning
you answer
me answer me are you
here come
on or I'll put you into the
ramen you'll be the first one to be sent
[Music]
out okay maybe not you're not here but I
hope you will hear this and thank you
for supporting me like I it's some
somehow surreal to me like weird like
until lurkers say something at least
once every once in a while you know it's
obviously like they don't it it feels
like they don't exist like I don't have
any more viewers besides the ones who
always type in chat that's how it feels
like so please say hello you know here
and there to make yourself known to me I
would appreciate it even if you're shy
and you don't think you have anything to
say in chat just you know you know or
like say something to me on Twitter
reply to my tweet on Twitter hello here
and there thank you oh there are the
lurkers hi guys I look in I exist
[Music]
yay thank
you no it's nice to see you guys say hi
because you know
if I only look at the chat and I only
see the usual people I'm like
H is that all the viewers I
have like the CCB says I have more than
the people than that are just like in
the chat it's mysterious where are these
other chickens
hiding yeah I have like 20 fans what the
[\h__\h]
yeah surprising amount of lurkers thank
you for checking in all the time with me
thank you to the VOD Watchers also thank
you yeah the VOD gang the lurker gang
and the always D
gang thank you so much and with that
this infomercial music is lowkey
uh emotional but with that
hi
baby eh she's using my chair as a
scratching pole mhm and she always gets
caught in it and struggles to get set
free and it's I think we've heard this
enough good job you s yourself
free oh so in 12 minutes the premiere
starts maybe I can read one more
might be able to read one more oh yeah
easily um what is
this what is this oh is this
a there's one super chat from paty In
The Stream that doesn't have a title
here in hyzer but I'm guessing this is
the Twitter Space Room
maybe that I had yeah the wa waiting
room and the whole cure stream
I think for me the hure arc is over by
the way I don't think I'll be scheduling
another Hol care stream anytime
soon was a bit short but
H I don't know I think I'm probably done
with it for now maybe H you're
[Music]
sad okay maybe one more I don't
know maybe maybe I can play it members
only
though ja 47 D of fancy dun exre dog who
loves bread and Hungry Jacks dun Tanaka
from kfp d ultim k d for the pinky we're
so back baby I only had time to check
out some new stuff and one new stage
this morning but I'm so excited to test
my Ki F brand build on the new stages
let's go oh a new W build teach me teach
teach me how does it work he for real
send me the strats and how was it I
guess you didn't even test it out yet so
only teach me if it was
good could the wee D the Jolly Ram raner
Dan normalized Phantom dun thank
you what quacky thanks for the pinky as
an IT Tech let me just say that it's
rough to diagnose issues in houses
there's so much that interferes
however note that even things like Cloud
movement or cards uh can mess with cell
signal bouncing antennas are also
different per model yeah we figured this
out by now finally although I think that
was more about the internet
maybe but yeah my internet has been fine
thankfully and my phone well I figured
that one out even though it was
ridiculous fighting o Dan Jackson FB Dan
thank you and
hied
[Music]
MP
sc one more
timean and Bruce J
[Music]
Lee
wow wow before you'll know it I'll be
caught up
guess I'll read the last Diablo stream
super chats
also I got nothing better to do I guess
wait no TS I forgot never
mind I wanted to talk about one
thing
ah oh my my sister was watching a lot of
the stream it seems she sent me some
DMS reacting
but
why why John who in the chat told my
sister or just said to call the the
sauna guy John
sauna oh John Cena
ah had to say it out
loud I don't think she's watching
anymore anyway yeah I wanted to talk
about my sister's
cats oh so so okay so I haven't met my
sister in a long time right um but also
I haven't visited her home in a long
time and she has cats you know and so
since I haven't visited her home in a
long time also haven't seen her cats in
a long time I haven't seen them since
they were kittens and it's been years
yeah she loves cats too the whole family
is like cat people my brother also
prefers cats my mom also prefers cats my
sister prefers cats everybody prefers
cats actually yeah my father also
preferred cats they had a cat too
everybody loved good jeans good jeans
very based yeah cat
family H I see but I mean that makes
sense like you grow up with a cat the
children that grow up in that family
start to like cats then they also get a
cat they make children those children
also grow up with cats then turn out to
like cats and just goes on and on and
on
yeah the cycle will not be
broken so anyway um so I was excited to
you know on my way to travel uh make a
stop at her place and meet cat again
after cat grow up because they were
kittens when I last saw them she has two
real
killed orange Cheeto cats and orange
Behavior cats and they're so cute they
were so cute and they were babies they
were really like snuggly and I snuggled
with them yeah they were so cute and so
funny and they're boys you know so they
were
like cute you know orange cat and then
they grew up and I haven't seen them
since they grew up so I was excited for
that but my sister has since gotten a
third cat an additional C let's say okay
let's give this one a special color this
cat is
um let's say purple
[Music]
colored this cat is purple colored
yes um she got this cat not that long
ago but also haven't met this cat of
course and so I was like mostly looking
forward to meeting
the orange ones again because I haven't
seen them since they were
kittens um but purple cat my sister was
like showing me a lot of pictures of her
cats and purple cat had a lot of
personality and was really cute yeah
grape
cat so yeah but I thought like I I
didn't think that the orange cats would
like remember me after all these years
but I thought I don't know they they'll
they'll surely still be friendly like
back then so I arrive and orange cats
are being cute but very distant uh and
like not really coming up to me they let
me pet them they're also keeping their
distance meanwhile purple cat
immediately comes up to me uh rubs its
body against my legs lets me pick it up
the moment I pick it up by the way very
very
chunky uh purple cat is like purring and
making air cookies with its paws and
just like letting me hold it forever and
ever yeah the purple cat really loved me
and was constantly coming up to
me so cute so cute man they all had such
cute faces the orange cats man they have
such they their faces were so like sad
looking I love it okay I don't have much
time left um but yeah cats were
cute they were so energetic though they
were constantly playing and I also
played with purple cat uh and made it do
like big jumps and stuff while uh you
know throwing around the the thing the H
cat and
and Ang
angle yeah want I get a purple cat as
well no I think I would be you know to
overwhelmed with a thir Cat still even
though I would love to have one but I
I'm already I got my my hands so full
with my current cats um 2 minutes no
it's four minutes and then another I
think three minutes or I don't know
what's the
default so yeah so cute but I don't know
they're so energetic I'm GL I think I'm
glad that my cats aren't that energetic
but at the same time I think I made them
that way I raised them to be super
chill 60 seconds on my side what the
[\h__\h] 60 what do you the
[\h__\h] okay well guys uh in case you don't
know what we're waiting
for go to this link
now
me I will mute it on my side but yeah
yeah I think I made my cats really calm
but that's probably because yeah I just
like didn't play as much throughout
their life with them which I'm
lazy but they play with each other when
they really want to you know and
sometimes I still play with them but not
that often I'm guilty guilty but in
exchange they're like really chill you
know not constantly dooming but when
they doom it's
cute I'm on my phone I can't watch both
well then prioritize the trailer go go
go go go time for a scheduled training
video that's
right
yeah okay and one more thing I will say
before it starts uh no I'll say this
maybe tomorrow okay I'll keep a tangent
for tomorrow um tangent
note uh
chocolate that's right I need tangents
for tomorrow
at least one or
two it's good to keep
one I'm looking at both chats now oh
it's starting 2
minutes
oh
[Music]
he it says for me 144 43 42 41 40
there's obviously some stream delay
but yeah I know you hear it should I
mute it
now I'll mut it
[Music]
I'm like zooming a little bit through it
apparently I need to catch
up
why okay whoa what's happening I guess I
CAU up okay 36 35 34 43
[Music]
oh smoy is sleeping behind me again
cute watch this guys watch it click the
link we're watching a Premiere now wait
I was going to R into it [\h__\h] is this
better I don't know go watch
it don't you dare to not watch it with
me
now two
one okay I was Dumb and like refreshed
it
[\h__\h] suddenly I'm so
behind I'll catch
up that knife spin was kind of weak
what are you guys seeing right
now he's putting on the apron the
beautiful
apron he's also got his name tag on and
now here comes the Hat it looks cute on
him MH
mhm oh
okay A little bit of SCU
maybe
slay he's got like s Gana items in his
pockets
[Music]
no they included my meme
dance why was I even doing that why was
I
flossing a the bow is so
cute is that no that's noodles I thought
it was cereal
oh
[\h__\h] oh he water
[Music]
ging oh oh [\h__\h]
C
SPO I love these spoons I can make a
mini Ramen on
them this Ramen is so this spoon is so
essential for
me
oh oh yeah it looks pretty big in his
hands oh true yeah you can hang it up on
the wall I think that will be really
nice
too oh
really oil
treatment should oil
it oh [\h__\h]
special effect they got the
sfx uh
money
pineapple K
kiwi let's
go woo
maybe don't try to shave your armare
with
that
oh ooh that pineapple looks
weird why is that pineapple that
color yeah copper
Damascus pink pineapple
whoa who I eat the chick who it's on
fire
oh
whoa holy [\h__\h] wait it's on
fire oh
yeah Fried Chicken in there
that's really
filling yeah those noodles are still
good wait I've heard some of these
script oh probably because I listened to
it
before I've heard some of this stuff
before what why is that pineapple a
color M
egg
uhuh let's not elaborate on any of the
ingredients
oh
what's I'm
confused
yay ended on my
side Shameless Shilling of course it's
my product have to shill
it what a beautiful set and what
beautiful products wow wow wow wow wow
wow I didn't uh yet use my wireless
microphone on that day uh when I
recorded those scenes so the audio is
like really far sorry about
that sounds a bit distant did you record
the motion for it of
course of
course yeah I'm glad they were able to
work with it after all there was like
some some stress going on behind the
scenes I'm glad they worked it
out yeah still like there was big time
pressure so please excuse any kind of
like small scuff in the video but I
think overall because just the whole the
IRL footage is is just so high quality
oh it looks so
good looks so good thank you so much for
this beautiful beautiful trailer yipp it
looks so professional and how the [\h__\h]
did you get that uh that that blade to
burn m m Mia that looked
amazing I need to I need to look at the
slicing scenes again in slow
motion yes that was the scene oh of V
yeah the one and only
Tim you never disappoints of trailers
yeah they're like putting so much effort
into
these
[Music]
trailers oh thank you thank you thank
you for creating this to promote our
marvelous products even more thank
you it's so cool it's like a like a
proper commercial that could possibly in
a shortened version be played on
[Music]
TV it's so cool the whole set is so cool
what are you going to do with it now are
you guys going to destroy the set is it
going to be
gone you should bring
it f have you never thought about uh
like opening your own booth at like
conventions like omocat and so
on and then showcasing your stuff there
and making it also open for
purchase bro you totally could you're
putting it away you do have a ton of
storage SP okay so then I would say sign
up to have a v booth at a
convention give people
uh you know the chance to look at the
products IRL and then order to and then
bring the the kfp set or parts of it we
got to do some conventions and we do go
to some conventions but there's ton of
PR of food have noticed well well well
well well well well well I mean whatever
you can't sell you can just like
showcase maybe and then let them like
sign up to buy it online or something I
don't know I don't know I'm sure you can
make it work you should make it work do
it do it just do
it showcase those beautiful products
promote those kfp maybe like I don't
know like you can aim for one cool
convention this year why am I making
these suggestions but I think it would
be cool and then at the time when that
convention opens uh happens we can open
up uh pre-orders again or like a rerun
at that timing yes yes yes yes we SL to
go to a bunch but got last minute
rejected from three of them because they
all said no food sales allowed
not even package to what there's plenty
of other place like stores in
conventions that sell
food why are they getting special
treatment with this merch we definitely
can make it work okay okay then maybe no
no Ramen to sell but we have lots of
other things to
sell and the ramen people will just have
to buy
online yeah I guess they it that's no
that sucks but okay I'm I mean at least
the packaging can be
showcased that would be so
cool I wonder if you could like pretend
like you're cooking the whole time like
you your your boo will be like you
constantly showcasing the knife and
stuff but that's kind of dangerous
maybe I'd grab a bowl of the con
right like come
on let V into the food business at
conventions come
[Music]
on will the ramen be sold indefinitely
no generally as far as I know all the
products are time limited for me because
of our contract Etc but a rerun is very
possible
mhm let fight cook come
on
please like come
on what's wrong with
you but no I I think it would be very
worth it even without being able to sell
the food I know that's your main thing
obviously
[Music]
but
yeah we would finally get some good
ramen at conventions the ones I got at
do me were pretty mid no but like we're
talking about not not freshly prepared
Ramen we're just talking about selling
the packaged Ramen even that is
apparently a
nogo but
[Music]
still p
is The Shield of cutting board
yes P
[Music]
Pina Toma is cutting board in Korean
apparently
yeah
yeah Korean
Bros you can buy and ship
these products to Korea
too h
[Music]
yeah but I don't have the link in the
description right now but uh link is
pinned in the comments pinned
comment wow wow wow Ramen knife cutting
board hat Bowl yeah I I said this while
we were watching but uh to me one of my
like most important items in this lineup
is also the surprisingly the spoon cuz
for me the spoon is so essential for
ramen eating for an enjoyable Ramen
eating session cuz I can't slurp so what
I do is I pull out the
noodles and then I plac them on the on
the ramen spoon has a good shape for it
and then I put like the corn and
whatever I have on it also there and
then I dip it in to get a little bit
more soup and then I eat it all at once
yeah mini
Ramen mini
Ramen bigger the spoon the better but no
no no no no no not too big because if
it's too big then it doesn't fit in your
mouth anymore but I was testing actually
I I was sent some V products before a
while long time ago I didn't tell you
guys about it because I thought it would
spoiler you guys uh about this coming up
but uh I would stand like some knives
and some other stuff like uh Chopsticks
and Spoon and ramens um and so I was
like testing out the spoon also and the
spoon has the perfect size and shape for
me to create a mini Ramen
to eat my Ramen
with it's perfect
perfect
perfect so I think it's
essential wow can't wait to order it or
you got to wait a little bit take your
time take your time no
stress if you also not order the Nando
you can eat your Ramen with tiny waa
exactly but tiny waa wait no well uh so
I think currently the shipping date for
the Vite items I think did it say
something like May or so takes a bit
longer Unfortunately cuz you
know we I guess we really rushed this
and the they they still uh got to
produce everything you know takes a
little while I don't know when the
shipping for the neroid
is
Jun o
so you guys still got to wait more than
half a year no about half a year yeah
seven more months to have it really in
your
[Music]
hands it's going to be a while
still but at least now I'm
colored yippe the gray jail I broke out
of the gray jail next month will be four
years thank you since my first read them
oh since my first read them you are you
counting some weird times
days W finally is col yay why would the
green no
more what will be the thing that we'll
be waiting for um I guess you could wait
for a solo live an unrealistic solo live
um it'll wait
forever uh or just generally my next 3D
YouTube
lives that I'm working
on and Next original song there's always
a next original song most of the delay
comes from the combination of holidays
going directly into Luna New Year we're
hoping for faster but also definitely
busy days yeah it's okay we can wait the
good thing is by the time these things
arrive you will have forgotten how much
money you spent on
it and maybe you'll be homeless by then
but
no hopefully not um but yeah the pain
will be mostly gone and there will only
be Joy by receiving the items with a big
delay and you you have
forgotten I'm sorry like I think you
know
um it's just the reality that the full
set is really expensive but you know I
can also say the quality is really nice
and I test it out
the knives as well I've been using the
girl DM knife because I gave I gave the
other knife to JMA she really wanted
it but the gam knife is so nice it
slices so nicely it's so beautiful wow
such a beautiful
knife and the other items I'm sure they
will also be really high quality as I
have already tried the food itself the
tester was really yummy really thake
flavorful broth with fake high quality
noodles I said this on Twitter I was not
joking when I said this is the highest
quality instant Ramen I've ever had
like I that's like it's insane like
what what so I think the price for the
ramen is reasonable because it's unlike
like any other instant Ramen like not
the crap that you get in the supermarket
or even in the Asian
stores those noodles are so
thin these noodles our noodles are
really fake and really
nice yeah good texture good MCH MCH MCH
MCH good bite h good quality good
ingredients we have the good nudes yes
good Longs yeah shut
up so yeah uh eventful day I'll see you
tomorrow for Fallout New
Vegas Yes yippee I'm going to figure out
what to eat
now goodbye
guys uh yeah yeah thanks for welcoming
welcoming me
back thank you for watching go watch the
trailer again all right go watch it
again when I'm
gone thank you see you tomorrow in
German does byebye
[Music]
chunky Wy
hello blessed oh she jumped up
[Music]