[Music]
so
you
[Music]
do
hmm uh
[Music]
do
ah
i'm tired
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
hello
come on
i am
taking down
the decorations to make space for new
ones
um
i don't know if we have enough to fill
up really completely everything but you
know what
whatever
bye bye beautiful decorations bye bye
oh no
my obs is so clean now
it's so clean
new ones coming in because i said i
would bring in more and um that's what
i'm doing
[Music]
you
bonus balls balls balls okay
uh
maybe only if it's not so many on the
tree maybe only but this one's so cute
and sock
kawaii oh wait let's put on music here
i picked out a lot of xmas xmas
christmas songs
uh behind the scenes
i hope you like this jazzy cafe
song
[Music]
hey jingle bells jingle bells
wrong one
[Music]
hey
a lot of kotori ones
this time
okay for now
i'll leave it at this
yeah very orange decorations
[Music]
thank you guys for the cute uh
decorations you can still if you want
you can still make some new ones and uh
put them on hashtag kiara's balls
everyone who puts them out as a png
uh is is first
is prioritized
[Music]
i wait no i wanted to add one more
which is another kotori
but i have the green screen no you know
what let me let me do that in the
photoshop separately
[Music]
let me squeeze that one into
hey
jingle bells jingle bells jingle all the
way
oh what fun it is
is it horse or house
jingle bells jingle
[Music]
are they thinking about a sleigh that's
only pulled by one horse
i guess that's the meaning
hoy can't say this
this one kotori is so fake in that one
that's that's uh before kodaki started
lifting
[Music]
so welcome to this gorilla super chat
stream where i will finish
the super chats i figured um i could
probably just do it next week but
oh
well
nah why not why not today what you
master heart that comes beswan
of morgan here's a german saying
that probably exists in english too but
i only know it in german
and what you can do today don't do it
don't don't don't push it to tomorrow
is
generally
a living that i do not live by
but
uh today today is
[Music]
i guess we can make the schedule
while i'm still on stream i mean i
already have like
in mind what i'll be doing
uh i already have it on my google
calendar just gotta put it into a pretty
schedule
um
decorations for casper this tree is so
tight there's already decorations on
there i already put them up
if i put the chias balls on there you
won't even see what they are
[Music]
yeah
so so so
and apparently we were not finished with
ori's super chats i guess i left it off
where like
was i not
i thought i was
i think i was finished i don't know was
i finished with ori super chats i think
i was
i think i was was i not
you i have me
too
i thought
okay okay and i already put them the
rest of them into the excel sheet
shit's creek i'm so addicted to it
it's so good
[Music]
[Applause]
uh where's my sheet here it is
shit's creek vision vigil out really
okay
turned it down a little bit slightly
[Music]
so we are starting
sorry
[Music]
we're starting with diablo superchat
does
but really there's only 272 in total
which
is not really that much
so i was like
man
is it really worth it making a whole
stream for these but okay
we're doing it
[Music]
oh
oh my god brain
whoosh
this one that was fun
that was so much fun man
i was a good collab wasn't it i i was
worried too
um
saying two because i think i wasn't the
only one
about like how good we would work
together uh
like because it was my first time and
she's a very different type of person
compared to
who i am
um
but we
matched pretty well didn't we
i think it was a great game to collab
with as well um
wait my thing is broken
i have broken now
no
why is it broke
i twitching because i'm pissed off
my excel sheet is
[\h__\h]
okay i'm going to youtube then after all
i'll read it for youtube then
whatever
[Music]
the shy goofball and the outgoing danky
boss dank
dank you call me dank i think that's a
that's a cool thing right
yes i asserted senpai dominance on
cronie
yeah
uh no couldn't watch uh cali's tea party
because she uh
streams at horrible times for me
horrible times
absolutely horrible times
whoosh
i want to sleep early tonight
but i always say that and i never do
well tomorrow tomorrow i gotta wait at
home until i receive my christmas tree i
hope they helped me to put it on onto
the onto the thing that hosts the
christmas tree because i i ordered quite
a big one one that is bigger is me and i
don't think i can lift it and put it on
top of the thingy the base
and then i'm also like receiving i
ordered a million of amazon things oh my
god i'm not the biggest customer on
amazon right now i bought a million new
cookie cutters i bought a stupid tripod
for my camera i have i
already i already have tripods i tried
so many things already okay but nothing
works but the tripod i i have one that
you guys recommended to me on twitter
but the thing is it won't work anyway
with my with my webcam because
it doesn't mount on the webcam and
i know there's like things that you can
put on the webcam so that it will mount
a normal camera camera things
but surprise surprise doesn't work for
my webcam
um
so now i'm thinking of uh am i even
gonna get a new camera for this
uh but if i get a new camera i have to
think about it i don't know which one
yeah if i make it if i make a purchase
how do i need it to be a good purchase
right i'm going to be worth it
why not buy a better webcam this is the
best webcam like i've i tried a million
webcams this is the best one so if i
want to get go better than that then
i'll have to buy like a like a
proper camera but with those i don't
know like there's no not an easy way
like the webcam to just put it into usb
and
yeah slots
like like it's more difficult use duct
tape that's not really what i was using
right now
because i had it on like a
a
thing on the tripod that's not that's
not really a tripod
um
but yeah i couldn't attach it to it
even though oh my god you don't even
understand how many things i tried to
make this current setup somewhat
workable
and stable like i have so many different
like smaller tripods
so and some of them come with like uh
you know these like
adapter thingies with which you can
mount certain types of cameras and other
types of cameras and some types of
cameras uh like phone cameras or or
webcams or whatever so i tried to mix
and match but some some of these
adapters don't fit the webcam and some
of these adapters that do fit the webcam
they don't fit the
the tripod you know what i'm saying so
it's like three pieces and
uh
three pieces that come together but most
of them just don't come together so
i just ended up putting it together with
uh
the duct tape not not even duct tape
just no like weird stupid tape
so
i i don't really like i don't mind
getting like a proper camera but then
i'll actually have to like look into it
and um
isn't it kind of overkill to use like a
like a speaker flex camera what was it
again uh
a proper mirror thingy camera for a
stupid cooking stream
have you tried asking them nicely
go to the usual room you guys one day go
go
i feel like it's not necessary i could
use like a
webcam or a phone camera but with the
phone it's like i'm using the phone i'm
using it
i could use my my tablets but they're
huge i don't want this huge screen in
the way of me taking space up
so that's not an option for me either
it's kind of overkill like i wouldn't
really be using it besides for my
cooking streams strips
[Music]
have we tried turning it up in anything
um well i bought the tripod and i will
try to
for for now i will try to tape the
webcam onto the tripod
the new tripod because i'm sure it won't
be able to
mount it onto the tripod
yeah so for now for now we'll do it like
that
more tape tape is the way to go
um
i was i
i was also not sure if i really should
buy the tripod because i wasn't sure if
that really is going to work the way i
need it to work
like
because like these these these tripods
they go like
you make them tall but they have these
huge legs on the bottom that take up so
much space too
and i think i've thought about how to
position everything with that tripod and
it's not gonna be easy either
it's not gonna be easy
but i will make it work so yeah i have
like a million purchases from amazon
coming and i also bought uh even though
i don't use them i bought four red wine
glasses four white wine glasses and four
champagne glasses or whatever to be
ready for when my family comes over
i bought so many things man that poor
delivery man yeah well
there's just so many things that i need
those are all different kinds of glasses
are you are you a child
[Music]
even i the one who doesn't drink alcohol
know that yes uh well i think if i were
to offer them red wine in a champagne
glass they're gonna be like
kiwawa no i'm not drinking this no you
it's just how they do with the wine
drinkers
it's
weird you can't drink
red one in a coca-cola class
[Music]
sorry i'm a little bit aggravated
i'm a lie it's not like
i'm not mad at you guys i'm mad at
myself and
the fact that i need so many things
yeah i wouldn't care but i mean
the
the flavor of the wine
um opens up better in specific types of
glasses okay
it just it is what it is
um
yeah you gotta shake it and swirl it and
then
oh
smell the bouquet
let them drink from the bottle
nah
oh man
i'm already running out of water right
now i only have one glass of water here
i usually always have a whole jug of
water
thank you for renewing your membership i
drinking tea you drink wine in a tea
club oh my how how unsophisticated
ah show up as a webcam when connected
via usb
and look at a c stand they work well for
stuff like that i'll tweet you okay
thank
you
why is my chat not moving i only seen an
obs
[Music]
stupid chad
sorry not you guys
i just mean youtube okay let me refresh
this [\h__\h]
let me refresh this [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
jingle bells shouldn't this christmas
music make me happy
why am i so aggressive
what's going on
what's going on calm down
calm down
[Music]
open the [\h__\h] chat there it is
okay
wonderful welcome back
[Applause]
okay so uh back to topic super chats uh
yes this this this uh stream went
well
um i'm happy i'm happy i was finally
able to bond with crony typhoon
[Music]
mr casper
and harbor line
thank you for the pinkie
empress kaiser and kiara congrats on the
new outfit oh
i'm a bit late but i'm so impressed on
how you nailed it the colors the details
it looks fantastic and it's a favorite
of mine so proud of you for standing up
no matter how tough the challenge is
i mean you mean because the first stream
failed oh
oh thank you
because it's full moon i'm aggressive
i don't know if i believe in that um
[Music]
anyway thank you yes um it's a bit more
of a how to say a dull color
um
but i'm i'm glad you guys like it i
i i i wasn't sure if uh
you know after seeing the really bright
color
uh from cali's dress you know we both
have red dresses but hers is way more
bright
i wasn't sure if you guys would like
mine
but i guess you do
thank you
[Music]
for two pinkies
everyone calls me that now
it's been a few days since the outfit
reveal but i just want to say you look
absolutely gorgeous oh come on
every stream since i look at you and
every stream since i look at you and i
fall in love all over again that alpha
is just so good god bless hookah papa
sorry for piling on more supers to your
backlog but i just got paid at my new
job and i couldn't not send some love to
my aussie when she's looking so damn
cute
[Music]
thanks for the membership welcome
navid
i wanna give you a hug
i want my i want my hug animation again
where is it
is it here
whoa oh my god where are we
yeah no this is where i wanted to go
did i leave my animation here i want to
copy paste it
[Music]
it's behind oh
you missed you missed
you missed chimpkin there we go ah
jingle bells jingle bells does it work
with this outfit
where are the arms oh you don't even see
them
okay we can probably make it work
somehow
come over here to the christmas office
what year is it
oh my god see it's the wrong hands but
we can make make it work it's not like
this outfit has anything on the hands
anyway
so
um
[Music]
at least it doesn't look like completely
off you know what i mean
let's see
so it has to be like here and then
smaller
look maybe like here and i will uh
oops i will go maybe a little bit lower
let's see how that looks
oh
i mean i could i could even go a bit
[Music]
aren't you a cutie pie
wait one more
[Music]
oh
i love you
[Music]
okay we made it work somehow it's not
perfect but
it is what it is it's gotta go like
where did this chicken go they go under
my table and they kiss my feet
[Music]
while they're
[Laughter]
[Music]
no they okay no they they don't kiss my
feet i don't like that it tickles they
massage my feet
and my in my lower uh
thighs what are they called hamstrings i
don't know
yes i need those massages give me
that's that's good that's good yeah
that's the spot that's the spot yo
yeah stronger please
a bit more to the left
thank you
yeah yeah yeah lower lower
oh yeah yeah that's that's right that's
right yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'll leave in thank
[Music]
instruction is unclear blind shock
favorite
oh yeah i haven't told you guys at all
how the
um
how the therapy has been going let me
tell you in a moment what am says while
i was away i'm happy to see canada and
kfb grow prettier i live hard uh without
getting tired and come back soon for
support kfb can you tell me to quit
smoking if i succeed i'll support red
super chat every month to become a
healthy chicken you know what i don't
care about the red super chat but
you really should quit smoking if you
you already have like
a tiny bit of motivation or like the
will to quit it's not like you're like
why would i quit smoking stupid because
you're asking me to motivate you that
tells me that you already kind of want
to to quit so do it you can do it and as
you i guess realize you will save so
much money too i heard and i've seen
that smoking is so so so expensive and
it's so bad for your health so um
i mean everyone can do whatever the hell
they want but i think you should quit
you will live longer
and you gotta keep up with me i'm an
eternal phoenix so you're gonna live as
long as possible
yeah
a few years more i'm definitely gonna
help
i need you guys to be alive as long as
possible
otherwise i'll be lonely what if you all
die and i'm just
here alone
sorry it's a bit dark but
yeah stay alive guys keep up keep up
with me
so
stop vlogging
[Music]
or let me tell you in korean then
maybe that's even better to understand
[Music]
okay listen up
listen up
[Music]
for
foreign
[Music]
does that make sense
how are you even at the craziest times
koreans in my chat
you guys
where you come from i mean from korea i
guess but
well who is in korean
i said
stop smoking i don't want to die alone
[Laughter]
[Music]
good morning
yeah okay good morning everybody
die alone not live alone
wait wait that makes no sense yeah cause
i uh
what i said makes no sense does it
i mean i do die but that still doesn't
make sense like because i re revive but
uh
you found you found a mistake in my
logic a flaw in my logic
whatever whatever don't don't get don't
don't get too cocky
4 33 am yeah that's crazy
i mean i'm also usually awake at that
time but i would be watching netflix and
trying to sleep
is there a delay until you revive um
we have we have a scientifical uh
knowledge and proof
that there is a delay
uh how much was it in the first phoenix
down a few hours not really not much
though
[Music]
one two three
thank you for the pinky six hours oh
there you go
the t in tk stands for spilling the tea
you mean tk for takanasi kyara
me spilling the tea yeah apparently i
spilled some tea about cronie
uh
i guess she
she doesn't uh share that much on her
stream usually
uh oopsie
no but i did ask her before the stream
when she told me about the the car thing
i'm pretty sure i asked her if i can
uh
like like tell the people about this on
stream she was like yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
but i'm glad i was i was able to share
some
intimate knowledge
it's not really intimate though it's
like
okay you guys know every freaking detail
about my life like by now
um i'm actually surprised that crony
fans
don't know much about cronie
she keeps things pretty secret i guess
and i i am amazed by that i don't know
how she can do it like i keep on
babbling and babbling about the smallest
details of my life
i do
maybe overshare a little bit every now
and then but
but but but i i you know i want i want
to have a conversation with you guys and
uh
okay i need the topic to talk about you
know
[Music]
oh um
but who knows maybe crony uh after a
while will also start telling you
her most private intimate thoughts and
experiences
[Music]
eventually it has not even been half a
year although i already started telling
intimate and private stories in the
first week probably
[Music]
but that's just me that's just i guess
how
how the chiara brain works
[Music]
i told you so many things that now i'm
literally lacking stories to tell
and
i'm sometimes a little bit scared of
doing longer gaming streams with too
much space to have conversation
because like i don't i don't know i
don't want to repeat myself it's it's
been over here and i'm sure there's here
there's people here in the chat
who
maybe forgot some stories or they have
never heard some stories that i told
before so i feel like i could be just
telling the same stories again
but then it feels kind of awkward i keep
on every time i do that if i already am
doing it then i say like i think i've
told this story before but
i always start with that because i feel
so awkward
thank you for the membership thank you
soon
you're probably the first pizza would
you ever tell me your blood
[Music]
yeah i told you guys in detail about my
blood test results
um
[Music]
uh
yeah i was even close to showing you
guys an x-ray of my of my
book of my back
of my
of my bag
i mean it has come that far it has come
that far
um
[Music]
spine reveal
oh yeah you guys would be like why the
hell are the wings
well um
i i i mean my human form okay you just
you just don't see it
um
and jingle bells oh yeah one more thing
that we did uh
i guess wait was that i think it was
outside of the stream not in the stream
we talked about netflix shows
why did we do that i don't understand
why did we do that for some reason i
told her that i'm watching this show now
shit's creek
no it's really really good and then she
was like telling me about the kind of
shows that she likes and and uh
recommending me some shows
um i wonder if she ever recommended or
told people in her chat about what
netflix shows she likes
i wonder do cronie do crony fans know
that she really likes action shows
it's her favorite genre
[Music]
no if she didn't then now you know
[Laughter]
you can impress her by going to the chat
and and be like send a super chat and be
like
let me just guess let me just guess i
think cronyc i know you so well now
and i feel like we have a special
connection
i think i'm just gonna i'm just gonna
guess and say you like action movies
don't you you seem like the type of
person to like action movies could i be
right or could it be right and then
crony is going to read the super chat
and be like
how did you know you really do know me
well
[Music]
but maybe she did mention it already who
knows
maybe she did
[Music]
[Laughter]
potential spreading inside information
can't talk more about myself so talk
about crony true
only only oxen freedom
bird of steel duncan
cyrus
[Music]
korean stream i would be very happy i
think it would be it would make a good
stream but that's just my opinion the
writing system is so simple you have no
idea it's way easier than english or
german alphabet
oh
yeah if only duolingo didn't do such a
bad job teaching me
the language the writing system
could do a better job at that honestly
[Music]
yeah i already forgot everything that i
learned to be honest but that's just
because i didn't
i didn't um try to remember it
because i didn't have the time i knew it
i knew i wish i wish i could like
take
lessons now now this is a case where i
think taking lessons is better than
teaching it yourself because
um
you will be kind of forced to learn it
when you teach it teach a language
yourself like how i'd learn
studied um japanese
then you're on your own
you need motivation
but
yeah when you're when you're an old burp
like me
you don't have motivation you don't have
uh the talent anymore you don't have
the time
yeah that's the problem
i need a teacher to force me
to make appointments with me
but like a serious one you know these
teaching streams that we do like when i
teach someone japanese or when i teach
someone english or german
it's just always like a one-time thing
for a stream i don't believe any of
these people continue to properly study
the language that i taught them
i don't expect it and i don't think
they're
that serious with it
yeah also like the indonesian lessons
that the indonesian girls do i highly
doubt that everyone who takes these
lessons continues studying the language
it's just you know one time thing to
kind of connect and have a fun stream
and i mean i i understand like why we
don't have time to learn a full language
but yeah if if only we're that easy to
learn a full language
yeah if it was a regular thing then it
could possibly work of course but
i don't see anyone making a regular
thing out of this with the same members
that's like
yeah a lot of effort
yeah
[Music]
this collab feels like we're referred
wheeling a date hiding in the bushes and
feeding here at tips as we watch it
happen i didn't need your tips no
i was doing all this on my own
it's not like i need you guys to help me
on my date with cronie
teens at kkk thank you for the rest of
the chad just showing love and support
for you very happy to see you playing
one of my favorite games take care much
love thank you tjk
a case for you perhaps
thank you very very much i'm glad that
uh we're playing a game that you like
it's a very nostalgic game and
uh um i i know that there are a lot of
people in the audience who also used to
play it and therefore
you know it's always fun to see someone
enjoying one of your favorite games and
if it's like their first experience with
it it makes it even more interesting i
think
to see how someone is
experiencing it for the first time in
their life
could remind me you of the time when you
first experienced it in your life the
time that you can't go back to sometimes
i wish i could experience things for the
first time again don't you guys wish for
that too
yeah
i think we all do
not
[Music]
wish i could watch the movie for the
first time again
[Music]
wait
thank you for the pinky enjoy the stream
and sending my support happy holidays to
you and your family thank you
i wish you the happiest holidays as well
hopefully with your family as well
thank you for sending your support
i receive it safely
and wish you all the best thank you very
much
happy holidays merry christmas
ah christmas coming soon new year's eve
coming soon oh my god
oh my god oh my god i don't want to
think about it i'm going to have like a
crisis
um
[Music]
sugar
any holiday plans no
um
nothing like
holiday-ish if you mean like going on a
vacation
um
after christmas however
uh like after the christmas week
um like around the 27th 28th
i might be taking two or even three days
off
in a row i'll be back for new year's
but
yeah i have i'm i i i took a look into
my future
and i saw that i'll be feeling really
bad on the 27th and on the 28th um you
know
the the tea leaves told me
that i'll be having a really really
tough time
so
um
yeah i just have a feeling
i've been told so
thank you for the membership thank you
soon hopefully i won't be feeling bad
for too long
who told you the tea leaves
yeah you can see your future in tea
leaves
thank you guys thank you
i need water
chicken can you fetch me some water
[Music]
chicken
huh there's no one here
all right i live alone oh and my cats
can't fetch water damn it damn it i'll
go get some lunch the mizza tote
dammit
[Music]
hello
your shop
[Music]
tea leaves don't leave me tea
wait why are you making fun of me did i
pronounce it wrong tea leaves what
what's wrong with that
[Music]
i'm always so happy to see
all the people who sent the super chats
or like also in the chat even though
it's like a completely different stream
on a completely different day maybe even
on a completely different time uh zone
time time slot
thank you guys for picking up your order
i always feel like i'm preparing like
some food for you guys and then giving
it to you because you order it online
and then you take it and then you go
home or you stay around for a little
while until my shift ends
[Music]
my order's a bit cold well excuse me
excuse me at least you got your order
[Music]
advanced hug for the 27th oh thank you
i'll get my hugs for my cats for sure
uh
yeah i i'm gonna be fine hopefully
hopefully hopefully hopefully
crossing my fingers
my chickens are cold can i talk to the
manager now if they're cold let me just
warm them up really quickly
gummy oh
you should use
[Music]
there goes now it's really freaking hot
it's also pounding
because of the doki-doki
[Music]
release the music video you know what
should that
[Music]
no i'll keep the song uh still secret
but i will definitely
definitely put it on my schedule
yeah
but i still keep it a secret which song
it is
until like maybe 24 hours before or so
but i'm so excited
[Music]
remember sneak peek
oh
perhaps
possible we did it before
maybe
yeah i don't know this one this one
really really
um
is a special one to me
the song choice is just i think uh
divine and the art is exquisite
yeah
you guys gonna like it
[Music]
uh
um you said it this way on purpose and
no i don't know what did i what did i
what did i
imply
what did i imply
is that
no why
how did you guys get an idea that it
would be a bakamanukatari song i see two
people
why
why would it be no it's also not chinozo
overanalyzing
you guys are over analyzing me now
because i always hit that things don't
it
you can never be sure
oh man
[Music]
got him
conspiracy chickens
[Music]
um
all right all right we're done with uh
these super chats almost
um
thank you for the pinky sorry that i am
late to the new outfit party hookah papa
work is great as always how much your
dress is divine exquisite it's just a
supplement to your beautiful personality
oh thank you
oh how charming
thank you i appreciate it no worries
about it i'm glad you are liking my
outfit thank you for your support
and friends crew thank you for the red
super chat can't wait to see more
collabs of cronie tension that was
amazing crotody love
it sounds like croutons
a lot of a lot of different couple names
that i've heard already before
well thank you i'm glad you enjoyed it
fried screw
um i think you know the next two weeks
are gonna be busy so i don't know
um
if if i can do anything with cronie
anytime soon
but it's on my agenda of course there's
just now there's a bunch of
whole live english members to collab
with and there's so many whole japan
members it's just always difficult to
balance it well
um
but
yeah
i just if if i were to
really
collab with everyone on a regular basis
then i would have collabs all week
and that's
not what you guys want either you say
more collapse but then
in collapse i can't interact with you
guys that much
and in collapse i often can't read super
chats
and all these kind of things so
um i want to keep it very balanced
not overdue collabs collapse only once
per week or maximum twice per week
that's that's what i am aiming for
um
[Music]
and that was the last diablo super chat
thank you everybody for your support
next up we have some blue archive super
chats
i'm so sorry that you know i was
actually really
really um
[Music]
i was really
hard on myself
because this stream didn't go well i
felt really bad uh
if it was a non-sponsored stream
whatever but it's a sponsored stream so
i felt really bad i apologize like a
million times
um
uh
unfortunate that it didn't go so well
but
by by crashing so many times
but besides that it went well you know
all the meat don't you blows what the
hell was that
[Music]
but somehow there's some curse because
for cronie she had the whole cortado
thing right during her blue archive
sponsor stream
which was so funny
i first saw a clip of that somewhere
and i was like no way there's no way
like the description says they didn't
edit anything but there's no way that
this is like really how it happened
right so i went to the actual archive
and i i skipped through it and oh my god
what is going on
it was really like that
you really showed off the fun side of
the game i'd say that a success thank
you you think so thank you
could have seemed stable the last four
secrets i i know she
definitely just uh
captured it differently i wanted to use
my ipad but
i had this whole annoying thing again
that like my ipad is like on a
on a currently like there so it's
connected to a
japanese um
google play account and um i tried to
change the region because supposedly
it's possible but it wasn't it like kept
on like blocking me from doing it
even when i input like card information
from austria billy blah blue it was so
annoying
um
i tried to
um do a different account but that
didn't work either for some reason a
different google play account that i'm
100 sure
is
austrian
um
like regionally but it still only showed
me what's in the japanese play store so
i couldn't download the app
yeah
so
i ended up uh doing it on bluestacks
with uh
yeah
uh
yeah um on bluestacks it's just kind of
easier
[Music]
but then for some games it's just not
very stable unfortunately
yeah
next time
next time i do a phone game uh stream i
i'm gonna really really try to
have no issues and and and make it as
smooth as possible i mean the last one
we had the tails off stream uh that we
had for that phone game that one went
well as i remember
that one was fine i mean i got an ipad
just for the sake of doing that stream
[Music]
looking for the top
so let me get this straight i have to go
for five years of college and
months of observation in order to teach
and this guy just wakes up and gets the
job to a bunch of cute anime girls i
need a refund on my degree
hmm
[Music]
i i guess life's not fair
deal with it
thank you for the pinky even after
watching it live i had to rewatch
yesterday's collab
rock you watched it two times
it was so much fun to watch and it
looked like you were enjoying yourself
too
definitely even arco article
mama talked about it on twitter thank
you for crony for such an epic collab uh
thank you and crony um but her mama
that doesn't mean anything her tweeting
about it because her mama tweets about
all of
uh cronies streams
uh quote retweets everything saying i'm
starting to watch this now i'm starting
to watch this now
she always lets her followers know when
she's catching up on crony's archives
it's so cute
[Music]
yeah
based
cute
yeah hookah papa also always retweets my
streams but i'm not sure if he actually
watches it anymore he's a busy man and i
mean i speak mostly english though it's
not like i'm blaming him or anything he
used to always also comment on my
streams
but yeah it's it's been a long time he's
got other stuff to do
it's understandable but he still
retweets everything and i appreciate
that very kind of him
yeah my streaming times are [\h__\h] for him
too he always goes to bed like at
reasonable times like i think before
before midnight and my
streams are usually
after midnight for jst
unfortunately um
[Music]
pudding channel donkey soon motion thank
you
[Music]
well i went on a flight back home for
winter break and now i can have my own
cat dancing while watching you have your
cat tensions
nice oh yeah it's got some cat cuddles
nice
daisy thank you and kitty oh thank you
soon i might be a little bit late but i
need to say it
m-i-l-f kiara everything about your new
outfit is just bloody gorgeous
absolutely stunning you're calling me a
milf
okay can you calm down calm down
[Music]
and
do it really look look like that i don't
know i don't even know what exactly it
is just some kind of like mother
term
and whatever it's kind of embarrassing
shut up
i'm make sparky dance
[Music]
going to be the first whole live ian
member to use up all the free gotcha on
stream find out in 10 minutes
aya did the others not use it all up
how could you leave some over
how
that's like
impossible
you gotta use it all up
if you got some godzilla currency you
gotta use it up what the hell
what are you waiting for
[Music]
eh
ah someone only rolled until she got
middle in home like yeah i saw i saw she
was doing like a drawing on the side
that was cool that was original
wanna see sana draw some more
her art is so so nice
i love her art
[Music]
i get that but for you know the sponsor
stream i figured why not why not use it
all what the hell
thank you brisket man duncan
[Music]
yeah i want to see kyle draw some more
thank you i was planning on
drawing myself
soon
but the next two weeks are busy so i
don't know when i wanted to draw myself
in in my new outfit perhaps or
i don't know
[Music]
drawing
oh thank you thank you you guys are so
excited about it but i just don't have
much confidence
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
you know i'm so excited to put out our
song cover
whoa whoa whoa whoa
[Music]
[Laughter]
we're doing a stream after right after
the release of the music video and we
didn't talk about yet what to do but
today i was thinking about it
and i was thinking we could do like a
little celebration drawing stream where
we draw ourselves in the in the outfits
from the music video
while talking about it and listening uh
like i don't know if we can listen to it
but yeah we could do like a little small
drawing together if you don't mind i
don't know because i feel like you know
you know you draw a lot right in your
stream so i don't know if you want to
draw again you know you draw so much
every day so it's like it's like um i
don't wanna i don't wanna
uh
overburden you with drawing
but when you say yes okay but but oh
damn it uh i don't i hope i didn't like
okay okay okay
the legs uh
um um uh scribble scribble together
doodle something together
that's nice too yeah okay let's do it
don't try to whistle out kiawah
[Laughter]
okay
and now i'm nervous
now i'm nervous
uh then
damn it
[Music]
we did draw something before one time
when we had a tails off a sponsored
stream
we did doodle some hoodles
doodle
but we never threw
something proper together except for
that one whole myth collab
and where we all were doodling something
gosh i love that word
doodle
doodle is like a tongue twister
how many hooded dudes can you doodle
while hoodle is doodling
or something like that
all right anyway i'm surprised inna is
here what are you doing you're just
hanging out here
what are you doing
sounds like a turkey call yeah
[Music]
yeah she heard she heard me say art and
she was like
what
what what what
[Music]
afterwards so i want to finish this one
before she starts
just just because
because i just wanted to squeeze it in
nicely
um
[Music]
jingle bells jingle bells huh
oh there it is
[Music]
justin why not thank you until we're
speeding
[Music]
oh i didn't see that one
yeah
[Music]
oh
oh come on
yeah
oh man
shut up
[Music]
um
jelly water free duncan kevin fairy
sapling for mom duncan running donkey
soon
and thanks for the birthday wishes may
your luck never run out kfp strong happy
feeling the birthday andreas
teddy is done
jim tracy duncan and coco
we're done
[Music]
oh wait
oh [\h__\h]
did you guys say anything about me
putting up the wrong thumbnail
did you guys notice i put up my first
draft of the thumbnail
[Music]
did you guys notice
i put up this one but it was actually
this one i changed it before putting up
the stream
and i i put up the wrong one on here
you didn't know this did you
even though it's quite different i put a
different character on there
i
i first made this one with like random
resources that i picked up on on google
but then i realized i was sent a folder
with graphics with high quality graphics
and was like okay
okay let me try it all over again and
then i made this one which where you see
the graphic uh the quality is just way
more higher resolution
so yeah i went with that then
you didn't notice
kusa
this one is next
very funny superstars with viewers
another fun stream but that's normal
because every stream on kiara's channel
is fun
yeah
spread the word
um this one really worked out great
thankfully i'm glad we were able to
play games rather smoothly i mean there
was one time where
uh it was unbearable
because of the lag but besides that one
time
we went well so i definitely want to do
this again after mario kart arc because
we're starting a mario kart arc again
[Music]
you confused me i was reading debbie's
comment while saying it and they said
kiara so often that i
said kiara hester kiara so simple
okay petrichen danger lunchbox thank you
[\h__\h] you have to make sure you have a
mario party collab soon right after this
oh yeah wouldn't want the practice to go
to waste right yeah but uh it's not
happening anytime soon
but
next time i do a practice stream i'll
try to follow it up with a collab stream
um
yes
[Music]
70 resets by now and sadly no nice shiny
well i think you have no right to
complain look at fubuki senpai please
holy [\h__\h] she's still doing it
how many
how many hours
has she been hunting
before by now for that shiny fish
oh my god
every day i see her streaming around
this time or like uh i think usually she
like kind of ends it somewhere around
this time
but i go on my youtube and i see oh
fubuki streaming
[Music]
if it was me i would have already given
up ages ago
oh my god
she just ended now
but she still hasn't found it huh
she has hunted for longer than she has
played the main game yeah yeah
oh my god
and all that for his stupid useless fish
it's really useless fish
it's useless
oh my god didn't she even write on her
screen i don't know maybe i'm go maybe
i'm imagining this but didn't she say
she doesn't even plan on involving it
it's useless fish
i'm gonna say it the way it is
maybe garrett jarrah does but chiara
does
but okay but but i mean still
it's not worth it that stupid fish
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh oh well
oh i mean okay i don't no no no no no we
have to say it's worth it because we
don't want um fubuki senpai's
effort to go
to to waste or like seem
uh like it's not worth it it must be
worth it it must be worth it that fish
is a legendary fish
it's a legendary pokemon
for sure
and uh totally worth spending
like a whole month on getting a shiny
for
yes
[Music]
ah
let's go
jingle bells jingle bells
and
uh eduson dancing jesus the gondra thank
you for the red super chat kfc loves you
mama oh thank you wow i think this was
after
like 48 hours or so
uh without a stream you guys were going
crazy huh
cheese sauce come here come here i love
you too come here oh there you go
cute i'm sorry for keeping you waiting
but mama's back yes mama always here
don't you worry
thank you for the red super chat
mwah
[Music]
candy man
this week oh no so understand the
dentist hey glad you're feeling better
thank you
oh
i'm not ready for that yet
not lu thank you muff muffins thank you
dominique
thanks for letting us play i'd make a
joke about letting you win but i got
destroyed
hey yeah you are one of the participants
saturn helps duncan
that attack
thank you for always bringing us great
stories and lifting our hearts and
spirits i'm looking forward to another
holiday with you and the rest of the
whole life ladies it's great that you
can spend a very merry christmas with
phoenix mom and bro glory to kiara thank
you
yeah it's oh my god it's the second time
since whole life
since i joined her life since whole life
english since the beginning of whole
life english because we are the
beginning of our live english it's the
second time that we're spending
christmas together oh my god
that's crazy
[Music]
wow
and the second time that we'll be
counting down to the new year as well
damn
that's crazy
thank you dr jack for staying all this
time
thank you so much ma
let's hope that we'll we'll be able to
spend another christmas after that as
well together um
[Music]
will myth have a minecraft christmas
call up again no but we're doing um i
think it's already on
did did callie publish her
schedule i think she did didn't she
i think it's already on her schedule so
i think i can say it i'm gonna publish
it too afterwards but um
uh there's a an early christmas collab
because we figured we can't bring
everyone together on uh christmas this
year
um
we're doing a
vr
chat collab again
yes um however i'm not sure if it's only
amma's channel this time or
if we're doing a few other channels as
well this time
um
not sure
if there is more than one angle then i'm
gonna ask if i can
uh do a point of view this time because
i didn't do one last time
i'm gonna try to
uh be one of the
one of the streamers if if there is need
be for what more than one
oh inna leaking well no problem i mean
we are all gonna put up our schedules so
no problems no it's not like she i
wouldn't say she leaked it
[Music]
god i love these virgo labs uh well i
like them too but to be honest i was i
was i am or i was i'm not sure loki
considering doing it without the
trackers this time and without the vr
and just doing it on desktop especially
if i am going to stream it
then i might just do it on desktop
because with the whole
stuff it's just exhausting
um
i'm not sure about it yet though
uh
might also have to look at the program
i'm not sure what we're doing
anyway i'm not really that sure what
we're doing yeah good out in the very
first vr chat collab buddha was without
trackers um and it was still i know she
wasn't about trackus but she was in the
vr chat she was with with the goggles
um
but she didn't do it on desktop but
still it wouldn't make would it make a
little bit of a difference ah
i know it's just like a tiny bit more
charming with all the trackers but
i don't know
i'll see what i can do
i guess i could also swap
if i wanted to if i felt too exhausted
but
your frog dance was hilarious thank you
[Music]
you can't dance with trackers
you can't dance with trackish yeah
but i'm not sure if we're gonna
really dance
this time
um i think it's gonna be like more like
a wholesome
uh gets together
rather than like a crazy party like
halloween was
um
[Music]
either way it's going to be amazing
thank you i hope so too
vr stream collab is always amazing i
can't wait to see tantra's 3d debbie
from what i saw that halloween we are
streaming you got some serious dance
moves
well well
um
oh yes when i hit the club then i am
always the hit of the club so
um i mean i never hit the club but if i
were to then i would be the hit of the
club
uh so yeah look forward to it
um
[Music]
excuse me excuse me why are you doubting
me
excuse me oh my god a hit tweet
oh my god it's tweens yes
[Music]
um what
literally on oh my god
remember oh my god
oh great phoenix your present has buffed
my luck i finally got a shiny diagonal
for this i will give you the honor to
name it let's go
he got a shiny diagonal when even the
stream before that he tweeted
he he didn't tweet he uh sent a super
chat no wait it's the same it's the same
[\h__\h] stream
where he said uh
i want your luck because 70 resets by
now i want the shiny diagonal and now
he's like
i got it i got it
uh okay you give me a chance to name it
name it
fubuki
because
i find it
i find it unacceptable
that you have the shiny and true bookie
doesn't
[Music]
[Laughter]
you're asking about retaining the
ornaments well look look at look at what
i did i did it big sweet dankest in
motion
[Music]
as a native spanish speaker i promised
version luis fonsi your version is now
officially a cover
tangent is official now
no
it was so bad
my version was so bad
no no no no no no
i think it would sound better though if
you guys were able to hear the bgm i
think it would have sounded better so
it sounded better in my ears because i
was listening to the music
gym tracy thank you and people pretty
dang
wait did i get let me see did i get a
dmca strike
i i wouldn't have noticed but let me see
did i get through with it again
yes i [\h__\h] did i always do
i'm invincible
oh what is this
what is this
what is this what is this style
what is this what's this
what is this
i found something on a different stream
i wonder what what this what this one is
about
it
jingle bells
[Music]
okay
no it's not a dmca i think it's just uh
recognized as
a song but it's not a strike or anything
no no no no
it's just youtube sometimes recognizes
certain songs and it's like oh that
belongs to someone else
without like striking you
um
[Music]
jingle
thank you mate for being very so
considerate love this verb what did i do
ah because of ripping out your legs
you're welcome
[Music]
was that what you were um
uh talking about
[Music]
gd
probably probably not i mean that was
probably the most considerate thing i
said in that stream so
understandable
baron man thank you also for pinky thank
you for your work don't burn yourself
out though
thank you at the moment i'm feeling fine
oh the
ah the timing of the cookie stream ah
okay okay yeah that was considerate too
not as considerate as ripping out legs
but still yeah
you're welcome i hope you were able to
watch it today
and bear man yes don't worry um i i
uh currently feel
fine
it's a very busy season
but
i'm looking forward to when it's over
well i don't i don't feel i don't feel
burnt out i'm actually looking forward
to something that's gonna happen soon
and i think that will take off uh
all the pressure by finishing and
finishing off a busy season
yes so i am excited for that el canal we
are wadanka and kaku
we're done with these and yeah i forgot
today was the fourth
advent
yeah
sunday
i didn't light a candle though because i
didn't have one of those um
do you guys do that too
like for
the season and the weeks before
christmas
here people get like um advent cans
like uh
like a circle thing where there's four
candles on it
and it's like made out of this this
stuff from a christmas tree
is that a thing that people do overseas
too
yeah like a ref ref yeah
you guys don't do that
it's it's very common in austria and
germany at least
[Music]
free [\h__\h]
oh
i see a lot of people don't do it but do
you guys just not do it or is it still
like you guys don't do it but other
people do it in america
[Music]
ah some people do it
like here even if you don't believe in
religion people still
do it like many many families still do
it just because it's pretty
it's kind of a tradition
but i didn't get one because i live
alone and it's like what the hell why
why what what for
cocoon
we're reading cookie baking super chips
from today now
[Music]
this has been the first week since
forever where you had all short streams
plus two days off so how it's been
missing long streams want to chat more
um
it it doesn't feel like a big difference
because on the two days off that i had i
was doing a lot of stuff
um
and
on the on the days even where i had
shorter streams
i
went to physical therapy i went to a
doctor's appointment etc
um and now like two times this week i
did a gorilla super chat reading so
honestly
[Music]
[Laughter]
there's not
not really any difference
at least not this week but we're gonna
try again
we're gonna try again to have another
week with two days off sometime
yeah
my head hurts
love you can't have such an inspiration
thank you
as a viewer it feels a lot lighter yeah
i can see that i'm glad that for you
guys it feels lighter
def loop gonna be probably in january
i don't think i want to squeeze it in
this month anymore um
sorry sorry
soon though
uh unknown thank you for the pinky
i like how you still
add the pink to your uh super chance to
make sure that i'll recognize it but
don't worry actually it's um marked as a
pinky on its own by now
so you don't have to you can add another
letter another word with one two three
four five six letters instead
if you want
i finally became a bucket please eat me
joining your membership is one of the
best decisions i've ever made but the
only regret i have is not joining sooner
i can't wait to be revived as a phoenix
chicken in a year yay congratulations
nice
why are you here with your o2 account
though are you shadow band or something
like that
thank you for staying here for one whole
year it's been a pleasure having you
you're such a sweet
sweet sweet sweet
chicken
i'm so glad to have you
um thank you for being here supporting
me and enjoying my streams i'm glad i
can be part of your everyday life
it's got it got bunked oh man emote bunk
oh man youtube you suck
you suck
i'll say it how it is
genie thank you next time a bit early
but wishing you a merry christmas and a
happy new year i hope everything you
hope to achieve in 2022 goes smoothly
and successfully thanks for everything
you've given us in 2021 so far looking
forward to 2022
thank you me too i'm excited too thank
you
please continue supporting me in the
following year as
hello
[Music]
we've been cuddling before the stream
i almost fell asleep for like 10 minutes
before the stream
well
yeah
yeah we'll
um
[Music]
actually i put aside some
cookies
oh
well that's an interesting reminder when
do you show me play button was
i i guess i was planning on showing you
guys but never did
[Laughter]
uh yeah um uh
yeah i put aside some cookies that i
made today for uh bff i'm gonna give it
to her tomorrow
[Music]
it's so exciting i never
gave someone food like that before
except for cali i gave her the chocolate
but but besides that
i've never really done it before
making food myself and giving it to
someone as like a
thank you or souvenir present
hope she doesn't mind the cat hairs
yeah i gotta warn her about that that
there might be one or two cat arrows on
it so she should look at the cookie
before she gets it
[Music]
where are you going to the playbook with
the ps5 and ri special merch well i mean
the thing is i couldn't wait i was too
excited i already unpacked the ps5 it's
like standing on my shelf already
i couldn't hold it back it looked so
fancy so
it's too late for that
man
well thank you hey kkk come here come
here
with it hi
oh he can't kick frankie with a red
super charm
nice to see you
hope you like my cookies thank you for
coming by and supporting reduction
alright thank you soon for the pinkie
hilton so today i celebrate one year of
membership oh you joined on the same day
as unknown
you're amazing giving myself and many
others so much joy and laughter i look
forward to the new years to come now if
you'll excuse me i'm being called to the
black to the to the back room you mean
the usual room
nah you mean you mean the back room to
work right yeah yeah yeah yeah
understandable you gotta work i'm glad
you take your work seriously
yes yes exemplary chicken
thank you
oh wait ah
[\h__\h] i gave you a kiss by accident but
but it's a pinky and one year of
membership so you know what you can have
it you can have it take it take it take
it
you don't have to give it back
thank you for staying here
for one whole year
i mean who knows maybe you were longer
than one year but you're just wearing
the member for that time before
but thank you so much
i'm glad that you did not get sick of me
after all this time i really am
thank you
please continue supporting takanashiki
wawa and kfp
i need you
anton m dankeshen tai chi thank you for
the red super chat tai chi
come here
as always you don't speak but i know
i know you love me i love you too bye
bye
[Music]
hope everything goes well with the
baking it's nice to be here for another
stream i'm gonna tuck in and hope i
don't get too hungry
i mean with me continuously yelling how
hungry i was um i'm sorry i probably
did not help you with your own hunger
no but come here you also get a hug
today
thank you for the red super chat
feelings hope you're doing well i wish
you happy holidays too please stay
healthy
have a great time merry early christmas
yeah
thank you for the support thanks for
being here
looking for the top thank you soon
gemma should like it let you take off
your gloves we all know your skin is
orange orange girl good thank you i was
um i was almost gonna buy uh pink gloves
by the way because they had a pink
option too but they didn't come in prime
so i went with black ones after all but
um
i was thinking what could also work is
just getting gloves in skin color but
but
uh i have yet to find
like throw away cooking gloves like that
in skin color so i guess
that doesn't
really exist but
it would help a bit more with the
immersion i guess and then i could stick
um
fake nails onto the gloves
because you know kiwa has her nails
painted in like a
pastel purple imagine me doing that
putting those fake nails stick on nails
onto my
far away cooking gloves
maybe next time
what's gross about that where's the
difference putting it on your real nails
and putting it on your gloves
where is the difference tell me
i'd be freaked out
and then green screen looks that would
be funny too
add some feathers no i don't have
feathers on my hands
they might get into the food they won't
fall into no
you guys don't understand nail glue is
really strong okay
you guys have no idea what you're
talking about
[Music]
nice guy gordon ramsay oh he was really
nice today
[Laughter]
you can make it 100 believe in you by
the way if any other gordon ramsay show
up in super chat or chat he is fake oh
[\h__\h] finally i got to read this i
couldn't read them today at all
couldn't look at them for even for a
second nice finally
it was very nice today nice how nice
thank you gordon ramsay
i almost don't recognize you
thank you red room thank you so nice
gordon ramsay duncan i understand you
baking in front of an audience is a
stressful thing
thank you yes it is it is really
stressful
it is kind of like anxiety inducing
thank you for understanding gordon
ramsay
oh my god i just want to sit down with
you and drink some hot chocolate while
watching some uh love romance movies
love romans roman's comedy come on what
am i trying to say
kenshin 491
[Music]
is
romantic comedy that's what i wanted to
say
albedo is not biggest fan dancing
[Music]
look crack thank you soon
i made gingerbread cookies yummy i want
to do that too
kent is done asking for science hey as
an expert on both subjects who's got
bigger booings kelly or ahmed the recent
offer reveals made us doubtful that's a
good question
that is a good question
i think it's
[Music]
let me can i put up two images and then
compare them
i need um
can i quickly find them uh
i'll i'll pray maureen did her mom
upload it on her twitter
down down down
no she didn't
she only posted screenshots okay then
let's use the screenshots
hey
jingle bells oh yeah jingle bells amelia
watson too
will i get some screenshots from her
bust area too
no
i need some screenshots from her bust
area
[Music]
jiggle bells
jiggle bells rude guys that's so rude
[Music]
i can't find
anything
what was her
[Music]
no no no
hey i'mma guess does she not have like a
specific
uh hashtag for
the outfit for real
let me see
oh my
i need some screenshots twitter
i need some screenshots
um scrolling scrolling but all of this
is fan art
there it is there it is
here it is the good stuff um
okay
oh damn
so on the left side we have kalaipimori
and on the right side we have amelia
watson
let's look at them closely
[Music]
oh that is a tough
tough thing to look at
i must say um it is it is a bit
um this deceiving
here because if you look at the
two types of dresses we will be able to
notice that uh caliber mori is in fact
wearing a strapless dress
um and we are not sure if she is even
wearing a bra underneath however for
amelia watson on her side we do see it's
just a dress with straps so
and also the fabric of the top looks
rather firm so it doesn't matter if
she's wearing uh a bra underneath or not
it could very well be that the dress
itself is already supporting the boba
alone and even there are dresses that
have built-in bras that push the boobies
up as well
but in any case even if there is no
padding in there um it is it is 100 sure
that thanks to the uh bubba holders
the boobies are being pushed upwards
rather than comparing it to mrs kalai
bimori where her boobies are kind of i
don't want to really say it that way but
they're kind of hanging low you know
uh which is a good thing it looks
beautiful but her apples
are looking surprisingly small today
indeed uh compared to amelia's apples
which are definitely not apples anymore
if i look at them the impression that i
get is
melons um
yeah i think we're all really shocked
about that
and i i must i must come to the
conclusion unfortunately
uh i will for this one for this outfit
specifically i will rule
uh
it could possibly be
that amelia watson's
boobs are bigger than killer maurice
bobs
[Music]
however
however it is important to note that for
example
talents like aqua senpai
have already received
um
enlargements of her
upper areas
before if you look at her
outfits you will also see a
uh change
of size in bubba
um so it could be very well that this
has happened this might have been the
case with amelia watson
not that she in general has bigger boobs
but that just for this specific outfit
she might have bigger boobs because
it could be that her mama
just really wanted big boobs on her
daughter
and couldn't take it anymore and just
did what had to be done
yes
this is something that only
perhaps only nabi mama can tell us but
there's also a chance that maybe we're
being a big bamboozled right here it
could be that it is not amelia watson
who received the enlargement it could be
that caliber mori is the one who
received the
smallification
you know
i mean look at that that's not how i
know them
that's not how i remember them
they still look big but when standing
next to this lady here
i am not so sure anymore
i don't know
i will report that we are all together
as a group
as a flock of birds have been indeed
bamboozled
yes enough of this
this was my report on holo mips boobs
thank you everybody have a good day
just kidding we're not done yet
just kidding
almost we're almost there
[Music]
bamboo balled one might say yes
thank you for your work dancer you're
welcome it's it's a tough job but
someone has to do it um thank you for
inside thank you thank you for listening
in uh we must spread awareness about
this kind of stuff
yes because leaving everyone in the dark
is just not fair
yeah
because these ladies these ladies they
always talk around the pudding they
never get into the pudding which i don't
think is okay
yeah you gotta you gotta be clear
this comes from whole lives new number
one detective takanasi kiana
[Music]
the truth must be revealed yes
it's been fun watching you back before i
go to work and all i can say from one
beggar to another the cookies look great
you're doing an awesome job thank you
say libertas thank you nice guy gordon
ramsay duncan
viva viva
thank
you counting chickens thank you for the
red super chat
all i want for christmas is for you to
get a camera and a tripod i have cameras
i have many cameras
but and i also have many tripods but
they just don't work the way i need them
to work it's it's difficult okay
but yeah as you guys know i bought a new
tripod let's try to make it work with
that one
thank you dough counting chickens i'll
try to improve it so that you won't be
so nervous and i won't be so nervous
either next time thank you
lord edward
for kakarot dancing for the red super
chat hi tensor my friend yaha from the
3000 people discord group wants to make
cookies potential me and our mutual
friends i hope you can encourage her by
the way attention you remember yaha hope
to see more of the next cooking stream
thank you why the hell not my cookies go
make some cookies you could use the
recipe that i posted on twitter i uh if
you guys checked my twitter
uh where i posted the photos of the
finished cookies and the replies i did
post a recipe
and if that recipe is not good enough
for you there are i saw that there are
other english language recipes as well
of the vanilla kefir
and so yeah please check them out and
give it a try i think it's not that
difficult i looked at the ingredients
for the
um for the for the dough
and it's really really not difficult
apparently in some countries it's a
little bit difficult to get the vanilla
sugar but you can make that one yourself
as well
so
yeah you all should give it a try
really simple cookies that are so yummy
thank you guys thank you for the super
chats in the chats
thank you
and
and for kakaya so here's the case if i
didn't give you one yet
thank you
funds for tripod thank you soon and
securely thank you for the red super
chat as well
i just want to say i love your cooking
streams they have such a unique and
funny feel with your comment commentary
it's hard to put into a super chat but i
think dealing with everything and trying
to do a good job brings out your best
rants and chats it has a natural and
homey feel oh thank you i'm glad you
guys like them then it means it's worth
the effort
and worth the stress
it's stressful every goddamn time i hope
i can
like figure out a way to make it less
stressful for myself eventually because
i want to do more of these
and not only cooking streams but like
um or maybe origami streams or analog
drawing streams like traditional drawing
streams i wanted to do something with
acrylic you guys know this thing called
um acrylic
pour technique
[Music]
where you um
put like a lot of acrylic color into a
cup
i think like there's different ways to
do it and then you pour it over the
canvas it's a huge [\h__\h] mess
uh but i want to try that for example
because you get some really cool stuff
out of that um
[Music]
do you think you'd ever do a whole live
card backpack opening on stream uh well
if it were a card game that i was
interested in yes
or
maybe it doesn't have to be cards i
guess it could be like anything
like collectible to open up but
yeah
it first of all it would take a while to
be sent over to my place so by that time
if it's something new then the hype
maybe already died
and that's kind of sad too
i only have knowledge in acrylics for
model painting and not normal painting
uh-huh
i mean like painting like figures oh
you remember those monthly snack packs
um oh my god yes i actually
where is it i um
i
i did have some issues with that and
then finally
i think
maybe
for this month
i think it was this month it finally
worked
and but i still haven't received it
you know what thank you for reminding me
i do want to know where that is
hmm
it should it should be here but not but
oh wait wait my phone is about that wait
one second
do
[Music]
connected my phone to the to the charger
shonkers was laying right there and i
had to give her some quick cuddles i
want to go back to her asap so let me
finish these super chats
[Music]
thank you thanks for such a great stream
and was so fun and unique it may have
been a bit scuffed but that just added
to the stream these dreams are always a
blast thank you
and yeah um
my cooking streams are always kind of
scuffed too
other people just do it so much better
than me
um
but i guess the the scuffness of my
cooking streams
adds to the charm right right right
canopy
[Music]
it's so different from usual
nice guy gordon ramsay
fukushima
clint
oh you're baking sugar cookies in the
kitchen while watching me
noise mate
have a bloody good day mate thank you
boomerang
[Music]
we're getting to the end guys
sure
how how much do you guys want to bet on
people making a clip out of that boob uh
evaluation
how much you want to bet
[Music]
on
you make it hard to be sad i'm a little
upset that was my entire personal
personality trait a couple years ago
thank you so much i love your streams oh
you're welcome
you gotta you gotta accept the happiness
take it take it
[Music]
mr cat's big stun
okay quick quick
[Music]
oh uh
penguin with a picked captaincy and star
dragon dancer don't worry about it thank
you
so looks brave thank you soon what's in
thank you see be crowded action
oh congratulations on graduating from
college yeah
wow
looking for the top donkey
rooster banjo dancing
[Music]
i want some waffles
phil weasel thank you soon meg tron's
duncan
[Music]
i have to say the sparks literally give
me some courage i hope you have some
nice stream in the end of 2021. thank
you
really
oh
come
on
[Music]
australia got uh cancelled oh
so we'll have to try your food
recommendation enough oh you're the one
who was asking for that oh damn it got
canceled after all [\h__\h]
but hey um skiing season in austria
honestly i thought you were going pretty
early anyway um
it goes on for quite a bit longer so
um uh january february
march even
thank you come sanita for the membership
yeah so even there's still a chance if
you if you are able to still come in
later months then
i think you have higher chances um
mr matt thank you maggie is fantastic
[Music]
have you thought about buying white
latex gloves then coloring them however
with paint then over the latex gloves
you could wear food grade transparent
gloves
that's all i can think of why is why the
hell so complicated
why make it so complicated
dell star thank you for the right super
chat
hi attention i quit my job in november
and i am taking a vacation from working
so many years with no break oh hence my
little activity
oh my super chats will return in
february merry christmas henshaw may i
get an anal kiss on your lap like old
times eh
wait so you're saying that you were not
active
for a while because you worked so much
but now you're taking a vacation but you
won't be active either because
you're on a vacation you don't want to
watch me on your vacation or you just
mean no super chats during the vacation
because you don't have a job
is that what you mean i hope you will
still watch my streams oh what the [\h__\h]
is going on what's with all these super
chats all at once
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh i'm trying to end it here
well okay delta come here
come here
i don't know why you dare to call me
hancho again but
off you go go
[Music]
happy birthday
well happy birthday to you
[Music]
hey hey hey hey hey
it's not gonna answer that one
because there is no answer they're both
the same
ziti donkey shoes and dragon six thank
you swag
i'm not sure about that putting channel
down
and now
stop it stop it stop it stop it i will
refresh
i will refresh
oh my god
ever
thank you for a red one and a pinky
hello my empyrean boss i likely be
vlogging this week since i'm flying home
for christmas oh that's perfectly
understandable just wanted to wish you
and chat a merry christmas and happy
holidays in advance oh
i also wanted to give you give a gift to
broken give the kids to them please oh
okay
well thank you ginger ranger i wish you
happy holidays safe travel and a great
time with your family
and okay chad come here
[Music]
broken kisses for you mom
oh cute so cute
cute aren't you cute
thank you for being so generous ginger
angel
thank you
see you after christmas then dan kishan
thank you for the red super chat
you wrote an empty super chat with no
words but come here
[Music]
gig is that how i say your name
thank you for the pinky
love me tantro simple as i love you all
yes
thank you for
loving me back
thank you for all the love and support
[Music]
three six five dc video challenge down
the stream skydiving
and last but not least mental jenny
duncan thanks for the pinky uh i hope
you get better soon but yes there is
more more time with me indeed let's go
yeah please get well soon take care of
yourself but yeah i hope it's i hope
it's not too bad but uh hopefully you
can
take some time to watch
vods that you missed out on from
takanashiki1
look at the positives yeah
okay then thank you guys for watching
the super chat reading stream i'll make
the schedule now and then i will upload
it on twitter and then
uh tomorrow
on my channel there is no stream but
there will be the vr chat collab which
will actually be the day after tomorrow
for me because it's after midnight but
still it's kind of tomorrow um the vr
chat collab and yeah the the next stream
on my channel will be on tuesday so i'll
see you guys there thank you guys for
watching have a good night
[Music]
bye-bye
bye bye
[Music]
did i not say it
i cannot leave without saying that i'll
be nothing
[Music]
bye bye
take care of yourselves everybody
[Music]
jingle bells