[Music]
so
welcome
everybody
can you hear me can you hear me hello
hello i have fingers now too
yo
what's up hello everybody
[Music]
kick it again
welcome everybody
once again
at the kfp dance school
yes we are back it was uh it was quick
but today
um it's an urgent dance lesson why
because on the weekend we have the link
your wish live third third yes third
festival here look at these numbers
first and
of course we have all of myth here
yay um and that uh with that i will
bring in everybody did i say
in case i didn't say it so um oh we have
the colors here i should actually i
guess in this case this background i
should be standing like here
and then i will start by calling in
emilia watson
from the middle
[Laughter]
here here yes
yay
hi i can't hear you hello
hi you can hear me
yes i can hi
it's it's been it's been a few days
welcome back on the dance floor oh hi hi
thank you yeah i'm ready i remember i
don't i don't have a full both of them
yeah i guess so
welcome back welcome back
uh today thank
and never dance don't worry i will not
test you about the last dance i taught
you
okay i don't remember it good
that's normal okay uh my cat left the
room i think yes then we call a devil
person who has been here last time as
well
perfect perfect
oh okay
i see
you got to stand here good
here
on the blue side
yay hey welcome back
are you motivated to learn another dance
[Music]
so you have seen these uh these models
already but today is more or less the
first time we reveal the other ones uh
pre-two uh did a really really good job
at bringing them out really fast so
thank you thank you
thank you yes
actually the one from inna you may have
seen already somewhere on the internet
on twitter so let's do inna first
welcome new student nina
yes
come on come on come on come on
[Music]
perfect color match she knows where to
go
perfectly coordinated come a bit more to
the front either
cute
i can't look at her guys look at her
cute cute you have your wings and you
have a ponytail ponytail ready to dance
of course
yeah i'm ready how do you like your
uniform how do you like yourself
beautiful
stay back looking good you seem to be
from a different school than me and
uh the other two actually judging from
the ribbon and from the end from the uh
yeah
and last but not least uh we have
collided
[Music]
wow
very hype right now okay let me get rid
of this [\h__\h] hold on okay one second
guys okay okay yeah put them back into
your bag
the gun and the wine glass
whole live oh my god i look so angry too
let me fix that because this isn't me
this isn't me okay there we go hi
everyone
it's your boy
boy rory callipe from whole life
english myth i can move my fingers too
we all can today we all can uh
[Music]
a sailor uniform though you have more of
a western one oh yeah you went i think
you and ena are from the same
we're all seniors and gouda is the
junior
oh my gosh it's fitting it fits
perfectly she has that cute
yeah
all right and today today we'll be
teaching you uh another song that's not
gonna be not gonna happen last time yeah
last time i talked to you uh
[Music]
wonderful i mean we saw some great moves
on the dance floor but this time then
the song that we'll be teaching was
chosen by my students it's
one that everyone knows probably
don't know the choreography yet
can we i don't you don't i don't know i
don't know you don't know you think i
know how to dance
oh well that's good
maybe maybe you can
okay
well in that case it might be a video
that i used to watch
it might be a bit easier for you then
yeah that's that's a good thing probably
that one in overwatch
yeah there was like a viral video on
youtube where like they taught everyone
in a jail to to dance to it it was
really cool what
learn the anime bangs okay well can we
change the
thingy to the purple one the background
the purple background
that we had last time
oh yes yes
yes yes
okay i got it
wait do i purple background
please cute cute cute kid
isn't that okay yeah should we swap
since you're the dance leader yes indeed
here we go
um and also like
let's get our new students uh
[Music]
right and left side exactly
okay so
a dance that we all know by heart
probably or have at least seen a few
times before uh maybe we can start by
playing the full song once and see if
you can
chime in with me and then we'll start
from the bottom to the top again okay so
one time full dance please
if you want cali you can already
join i think it starts like this
yes i can do the point part that's about
it oh okay
but this is just to get you uh
familiarized with the song and the dance
yes ma'am
[\h__\h] i think i need to turn it louder
it's very quiet yes
uh
was that was that needed to be um
adjusted individually let me see
oh god oh god this makes me so dizzy hey
guys it's your boy
okay
[Music]
oh
okay yeah
[Music]
okay
can everybody hear the music properly
yes yeah
okay
well then we don't have to play the full
song anymore i guess we can do start
from the intro
um
thank you thank you
listen you guys already know what time
it is check out my hat
accessory time what can i say
accessory time ladies
okay focus focus
okay okay focus on focus up let's focus
up
uh it starts from a pose like this
and then you run
okay i'll teach you this slowly
wait i'm having a brain freeze
it ends there
anyway yes it starts from this pose
everybody okay
it starts pretty fast you only stand
like this for like a second
and then you hear that that rumble noise
that goes like
right you remember that probably boom
[Music]
after that
you get ready to run right and then you
uh supposedly you spread your legs like
with a little jump
uh
and then and then you pull your arms
from the back and uh slowly
bring them to the front to meet in the
middle okay
okay ah make them please all right yes
make them kids yeah make them cheese
wait wait wait can you give me one
second girls
can you give me one yeah something in
your eye yes that's why i'm thinking
that's exactly what i'm working
on
one second one second i need to check
really quickly because i'm nervous and i
forgot to power
up okay take your time
just one
second floating
floating do we have some flowers
no problem
am i floating you don't look amazing
that's floaty to me
that's not that big a deal
it doesn't stand out that much it's okay
oh you know if i pull if i put my
trackers down a bit i mean if i fix my
legs just a bit like this
[Music]
i remember
okay until then it was correct indeed do
you remember
yes the last night
so after the little running part we will
uh spread our legs
we bring the hands to the front inna
okay we burn the legs to the front and
then we um do some while you're doing
that you should feel the the beat a
little bit with your right leg okay
so as if you're
tapping it to the beat
ignore my fingers by the way i'm just
changing them randomly you can do
whatever you want with the fingers okay
and then uh
the the stepping once they meet in the
middle the stepping becomes a little bit
stronger
and then you throw
one hand
up in the air the right hand
shut them up there okay okay
uh
okay you put it on here
as if you're grabbing a star from the
from the sky and you put it in your bag
okay put it in the bag and grab another
one and then give it to the person right
next to you
okay
so
thank you
and then you do the same on the left
side you grab one from the sky
and put it into a back and then you grab
another one and you give it to the
person left next to you even if there is
no one there the other way
[Music]
uh
yeah yeah kind of you just uh bring the
hand back to its original pose kind of
okay okay okay
okay okay
and then you do this pose
with your left hand on your hip and the
right hand stretch to the side and we do
uh one right step
to the right side yes
it's the meme yes exactly
one to the left
one two left yeah and then uh
yeah only one time each and then you um
kind of like do a circle like this but
only to the middle only until they're
straight while you're doing this you
walk to the side
oh my by the way do you have an idea why
um every now and then while i'm dancing
uh
the the screen in my goggles
is like
disappearing
only for like a second it happens
the lighthouse doesn't see it first what
briefly it has just i'm literally like
there's nothing else here at least i'm
not glitching anymore all right that's
fine i'll i'll get used to it okay so
you while you're bringing it up to the
middle you go to the right side with
little tiny baby steps okay
like
well if you don't want to move too much
you can just do it on the spot you don't
really have to go to the right side okay
let's do it just on the spot
little baby steps yeah sure
okay
uh and then this is by the way the intro
is almost done once you're done here
you um spread your legs and at the same
time you um punch the sky so
like this and the hand the left hand
again is on the hip it's very often
always on the hip in this dance okay so
it's in the sky
then
you like a clock counterclockwise to the
left
and then you pull it in
and while you're pulling it in yeah you
uh
angle your foot a little bit like this
and then you let it go mm-hmm
okay okay
now
let's start from the top just to
remember everything okay wow it's really
my my bloggers are really really acting
weird right now
um oh
okay you start
are you okay
you know
oh my god she descended into hell are
you today the one who's gonna be
glitching out not me this time huh
you're the one that's gonna fly into
this it's right of passage
are you are you talking enough
i can't hear you shy
okay
how long were you
uh we start out with this post right
uh the hello captain pose oh are you
turning on the music okay gotcha no i
thought
uh like the captain pose and then you do
the run
okay
[Music]
okay pretty short intro
punch the sky to the left
uh bring it in and let it go
exactly
and let it go okay exactly okay let's do
it one time with the music
let's talk about the music once i'll
drink something
really quickly would you say
would you like to say what did you say
yeah i'm ready ready ready ready
[Music]
god i love the idol poses they're so
cute yes very cute
let's dance
there's a little bit of a countdown my
feet are so uneven hold on
you guys mind if i recalibrate myself
real quick do it do it okay
yeah now we're good
all right oh just kidding we are not
good
isn't that your default pose okay
kidding the cute legs crossed of course
yeah yeah yeah
are you right though
now we're good
all right you're doing it you're doing
this move
let's go
[Music]
because i know that part yeah this one
is it kind of flows automatically i
think punch the sky to the left bring it
in what i have issues with is the
stars
oh this way up what part are you unsure
about down
it's this part you're grabbing for the
stars reach through this door abs up
down
up down and then give it to the other
one
yeah up down up to the side got it
always always prioritize
yourself give the star to yourself first
and then give it to the other person
okay up and down up to the side so you
can't swap these arms that are folded
ah
do you always keep this one up
yes by default i usually put the arm on
the hip in the stance it's mostly like
that but
yeah it should be on they don't swap it
you don't go
[Music]
up down up to the right
yeah yeah yes you got it you got it and
then you do
this step to the right i can skip
and this part to the left
two steps exactly and then
[Music]
the little baby steps to the side and
then punch the sky to the left right
and down
okay i think i can try it again with
music sorry i'm kind of bad at
explaining today
no worries
oh god let me get these wires out of the
[\h__\h] way it's all fine
it's happening what's happening
okay let's do this [\h__\h]
make them meet in the middle
and start
down the sides down to the side
that's okay i think i kind of figured it
out a little bit more
this part is so fast yes it is fast yeah
is that faster
but i wonder
yeah do you guys want to sync up
[Music]
it probably doesn't uh
no not really well and those are still
just learning but
um
hard to tell probably because we just
suck
there was an attempt all right you can
tell us if we suck we know
oh they're saying uh callie do a jojo
pose
close what do you got what do you got
oh
it's kind of hard
joe tarot like this
you gotta extend your backwards
somebody else's
oh yeah i think i'm throwing up my back
when i do this wait i mean
can i get the serious expression first
sorry i hate to derail class a little
bit but just
i'm very friendly is
yeah it's like a back stretch
oh
it's kind of hard can you do the wall
you should do it as well
everyone's doing something else now
okay
[Music]
we don't know the dance so well just yet
probably yeah i think it's because we
just kind of suck right now
you know no no positive thinking we
don't suck we are on the way
when i say we suck it's okay
but that's like it's okay to suck being
sucking is not a negative thing for
necessarily i mean
look at it
precisely
okay
yes okay now let's play the music again
we'll just we'll just bonk it into our
heads hammer it in there as often as
possible
okay and you're good if you have
questions feel free to ask me at any
time
bye
you'll keep hand focused
[Music]
are spread but while you're um taking
the stars you can move your upper body a
little bit with it so when you go up and
down you move your upper body a little
bit and when you bring it to the side
you kind of lean to the to the right of
your hips maybe
yeah a little bit with the hips i see
a little bit with all right got it you
can tilt your head a little bit i guess
yeah
okay gotcha i usually do it like that
and then to the left the same thing
any other questions from my dear
students
oh actually
the last part yeah
the last part
oh
yes pretty much you punch the sky
yeah like while you like kind of jump
and bring your legs into position and
then you bring it to the left
and then when you bring it to the right
you kind of lock it in by by adjusting
your legs as well tip them like this a
little bit yeah
and then you let it go you let it go and
then
just like a rainbow let it go like a
rainbow
by the way when we do when we do this
step
this is extra homework if you want to um
if you look closely to the choreography
you're supposed to like shake your head
a little bit like this from side to side
like oh
it's a bit difficult to do
not not like this yeah but like
like this
you don't really have to do it unless
you remember it unless you have some
extra space in your brain
uh by the way all right with my
microphone okay okay
um
let's do it with music one more time
let's hammer in hammer time
i'm ready
hammer time
summer time
yeah one
two
three get ready girls four
five
six fine
hair in my mouth ah
wait a little bit feel the beats
[Music]
oh my god i'm not seeing the screen oh
sorry i [\h__\h] up
i [\h__\h] up i forgot up down
and upside
left outside
my screen keeps from disappearing for it
it's way ahead maybe
five minutes to adjust it
yes
i guess i can just
try and match kiara
yeah
if you try to match kiara then it's
gonna be delayed for her should i do
it's better to do it with the music
especially with this song yeah it's easy
to do with the music should i do uh
should i should i add some extra
milliseconds to mine okay
okay okay uh we'll have to test one by
one i think that might be best oh that's
annoying
i i'll put it to uh i'll put it to 300.
[Music]
everybody can like come along to their
song okay
okay
sure
no dancing unless you want one
two count with it count three
four four
yeah
very delayed
[Music]
maybe kiara you should keep yours lower
and then okay
wait if the delay is high hmm well then
i have to think about the math
not math but
if i hear them later shouldn't i make my
delay bigger or mathisfun.com
probably
but i i would think sometimes
chad that sounds like a math question
that's hard dreams
[Music]
oh they say yes
no yes yes i don't know uh
wait um i think about it map day i'll
just say math is hard they're about as
troubled as we are
yeah sounds about right
i mean that as a disc or anything you
guys are great it's just
[Laughter]
square root of 55 i don't know what that
even means yo
[Music]
that you can figure out your grocery
list and [\h__\h]
come on now
the only thing you really need in life
to be able to pounce yeah you start to
do them should we count again don't come
after me i do my taxes
pretty much i think so yeah what stood
out to me was callie and gooda being uh
like one two seconds late do one second
i guess one second
they were maybe maybe your delay should
be
your your delay should be at zero and
then
um
obviously you know and i would add a
delay
oh if we're now we're synced up with you
at 300 then maybe we should add a 300
delay so you know come over here
um
i'm sorry maybe we can make up our own
dance
trust me i feel sorry and i put it back
to zero
[Music]
a.m did you even sleep
all right we're going to try didn't
sleep did you think i didn't sleep what
how much two hours
[Music]
the most important part is that we're
synced up with kiara because
no matter how yeah the music and we're
in time with the music then we'll be in
time i think
somewhere gotcha
yeah i mean i'll just i'll do my best
don't worry too much about me if it's
synced up for you guys i'll just follow
your lead so
okay should we try i can go with the
flow okay listen
i can go with the
flow i can go with the flow
oh
yes stir that soup
are you flossing this one hold on yes
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
wobble your head and bring it to the
middle up left bring it down
i didn't see you guys uh following that
lower my
latency
there are more steps than i thought yes
yes well if i'm behind now don't wait
i'm so confused this is going to take a
while
[Music]
have you guys seen like those videos of
like um especially in japan of like
hundreds of people all dancing this song
like a mob like a flash mob yeah yeah
yeah yeah
they're so fun yes we can be part of
that we could be dead but we have to
learn this dance first
so it'll be a while
should we start again yes let's start
okay let's try again do your best to
follow
me with the choreo do your best fight oh
fighter
oh three okay
i'll just do what you do
three
four four
five five
six
seven
bring it to the middle
get the stars
wobble to the side level to the side
and yay yay yay
okay
um
when she starts nazanaza we're already
going into the next uh move which is
this
did you
see it's still going on at that moment
just see you guys now
i think i was way behind so maybe kiara
should be yeah she should be on a pretty
big delay because um okay if ours is
like at zero then
okay yeah just so you guys know mine is
super super delayed it's not that i'm a
terrible dancer i put it up to like
920 free [\h__\h] nobody [\h__\h] knows
okay
923 milliseconds i actually i'm a [\h__\h]
dancer let's try again but maybe the
rest of us should start at zero and
whoever is
yeah everybody else should be like on
zero maybe
um and gouda were always a little bit
uh later i think
than you girls oh so the issue is now
i'm behind
and i'm behind camera quite a bit like
the music goes but the bodies
okay okay so i need to change my sink
too huh
well like we could just do it like
however wait just leave it at zero
yeah all right zero
okay that's fine i'm fine with just
following your moves dude
okay
my dude let's do the intro again three
positions all right
five
six
seven seven
you
feel the beat take the stars
wobble wobble
one more wobble
baby steps oh wait first
okay mine is way ahead of kiara's
actually
yours is way ahead like mine is like a
full second ahead of kiara's yeah like
how how you guys see it is not like it
what's important is how it appears for
kiara i guess so that's why it's
important that we follow along to the
music with the moves because even though
you look out of sync for everybody else
it should hopefully be in sync for kiara
oh i see
brain hurt
i see
so wait so when you say you are
one second behind me you mean behind
my moves or behind the mute
i followed i followed the music okay the
music is one second ahead of you
okay
well
let's try to don't worry um go yeah if
you can try to follow the music uh then
that would be perfect but of course you
want to see
the choreography being danced to follow
along i understand my dad
when we do um countdown and it directly
goes into the
then we instantly start this right
uh yeah
you um make a big jump spread your legs
and then bring the arms from the side
together
right right after the countdown like as
soon as the countdown ends we're like
this during the countdown and when the
drums start we do like as soon as they
start we start
oh
what do you mean you start then i'm just
trying to make sure
yeah like when
that you're doing the countdown it goes
eight and then it goes
yeah
okay i'm not asking for moves and just
asking for like sink sinks oh like a
chat that'd be a
one more time
[Music]
oh
that's what i mean
i feel like uh
i'm confused i feel like everyone was a
bit too fast
no it's it's
um it doesn't that's what i mean once
once the music starts it's like one more
second until you do this you start out
with this post
um
like that
i think that's what yeah i was doing
this at the
part three
two four
five so we wait six oh you have to
happen you're in sync
[Music]
it i'm getting it um when kelly was
counting she was she was in sync i
noticed that
so it's looking good it's looking good
okay
count it down every single time oh wait
never mind
five
six five
now you're one second delayed again
take the stars take the stars wobble
wobble
wobble are you okay you know you keep
switching
wait i think i'm like a whole second
ahead and it's so confusing yeah can we
go over the moves again yeah
it's okay it's okay we'll go
we have this pace we're gonna be here
all night baby
okay okay try and make some progress
then so you start out with a cool pose
right ina
you're cool
yeah
and it goes like
you got that right
little
little baby marathon
and then and then you jump
to bring your legs to the uh to spread
them apart and when you do that you also
take your
arms and then bring them to the middle
and once they're in the middle you start
stepping stronger to
uh feel the beat okay
that's it you can just um follow
the beat and also follow how long i'm
doing that
in case we're in sync that is and then
after that
you do the
it should be
ah you do the stars exactly
you take one from the top bring it into
your basket you take another one and you
give it to the person to the side and
while you do it you can be a bit more
bouncy
okay
and then you do the same
cut it on the left side
to the side
to the left
okay
you know okay you're good you're good
okay should i do it slower i just don't
know where it lines up with the music
[Music]
it sounds like it sounds like this
what do you mean not delayed
it helps to hear you so there's still
this egg this
um
that's later after the that's later than
right
what do you mean later
later than what but this thing
[Music]
yeah that's why i was confused i was
like where do i do those
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait uh let me see what i'm forgetting
ah
yeah i think i just
skipped something
okay so we start from here
[Music]
wait can you play one more time
i'm brilliant without the music i'm lost
oh yes
yes yes that was it yeah but can you
play it again can you play it again
sorry
i need to hear the music every once in a
while
three
one don't forget to drink water
everybody
four okay i didn't bring any so much
water
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] it's down first okay
very confused at the moment
oh god where's my bounce one second one
second
i have some uh brain problems apparently
but yes after after what happened after
you take the stars
uh actually this move went on for too
long after you take the stars we do this
uh earlier we do the side step yes yes
how come i forgot that that completely
left my mind okay
so it actually goes like so we only do
one take the stars move i know you take
the uh two two times on each side
okay
but it's uh this this part it doesn't go
on for as long as uh i thought it was uh
yes
so we decide from here
[Music]
first you punch the sky
then do you bring it you bring it down
to the left as if you're like a clock
yeah you know your stuff about clocks
and you bring it into the middle nope
and then you bring it down
okay yeah okay got it okay and
we will hum it one more time and then we
play the music and then we just go to
the verse [\h__\h] it
okay okay so we start in this pose again
everybody puts your thinking caps on
[Music]
okay now we can play with the music yes
please yes please
yes
music music really makes the world go
around
music you lose control
[Music]
take the stars
wobble to the side
punch
yes
okay yeah
okay i got it i think
you guys are doing it
very well yes it still looks decent on
my side but i at least see you guys
doing the moves properly so that's good
okay so
and now uh the next part hopefully is a
bit easier because it's not as fast
um can you play the verse one once
okay the verse video because i got each
part separated this time at least
that we don't have to listen to the
whole song again
[Music]
um last time but
you're in this short amount of time it's
normal to not remember it
green you say
okay look at it look at me six so you
see how it continues
oh wow
[Music]
and then you wave your hands
okay so it's until that point where she
goes like prune to the bridge
um maybe some familiar moves here uh it
starts from nozzle nozzle uh in this
position
uh kind of lean uh to the left side with
your leg
uh angled
yeah
um it's
left right uh
yeah left right bounce bounce left
bounce bounce
uh you bounce
twice okay
uh nazo nazo
you bring in the hand that waves
up and down
every time you wave your hand up you
lift your your knee a little bit to the
upper side as well like uh together as
if they're connected like a puppet okay
and then you lean to the other side and
you do the same thing
uh to the left side
my legs are kind of [\h__\h] up same arm
yes the same arm actually yeah
you do it two times on both sides and
after that
we will start clapping on the top right
so back do four claps
top right top left
top uh bottom right bottom left hahaha
and then we
roll our hands like a whirlwind yeah
yeah yeah yeah
uh gotcha
we stand on one leg on the left leg
can we balance are we balanced queens or
what who can stand the longest on one
leg
wait let's do that okay
everybody stand on both legs holy [\h__\h]
you have some balance enough wow
and then
stand like this for as long as possible
go
how's it how's it going is everyone
ready for
all right
i'm good i'm good i'm good i'm good i'm
good i'm good i'm fine i'm fine
you need to lift your leg a bit more
angle like this
okay okay i'm fine
you don't seem so fine
it almost
[Music]
you know the secret i cheated i put my
foot up on the chair
damn
it's so easy for all of us to cheat you
can't really do a competition like this
come on now at least you're honest about
it
you have here sorry it wasn't up there
it was in the middle both arms in the
middle straightened out and then you
jump on your left leg a few hops
i think it's like free okay it should be
like free hops i think
okay
could be four
no cause that's just left
and i think it would make you a little
bit dizzy
no cheating we kind of do the same thing
uh one more time we start again with the
left leg uh to the left side mm-hmm
[Music]
wait i think i'm kind of off here
well um
we will figure out the timing
um
you do it again
the the bounce bounce
and then uh yeah
and then you clap again so it basically
repeats itself
until this point
uh you don't do the bounce again
instead
you um shake the left hand a little bit
we don't really have
automatic finger recognition so let's
just whatever do whatever you want with
your hands and one on this side one on
this side okay
and then she goes boom
okay
so you roll it and instead of jumping
again like this you shake
shake on the other side and then
okay
let's uh
play
yeah oh should it should i um
do it with humming once
yeah i can't drink water i can't drink
water one second i'm getting really
really husky
[Music]
so
offense to that but you're so it's okay
i think i got it yeah sorry the legs i
need to start from here
[Music]
sorry it was actually it starts out at
the right side i think
yeah okay one one step on the right side
and then bounce two times on the left
buns two times on the right
nope
um [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] can you play the music i think i'll
figure it out okay i think i'll figure
it out once the music comes
it is all confusing when i try to
explain it you can do it
yes
[Music]
i cut it too early
is
[Music]
i cut it too early so it's kind of
difficult to start in there but
it's okay we'll figure it out
no worries
okay yeah it does
kind of
start in this position but you
immediately
go
and switch to the other side
[Music]
okay okay okay i think i can explain it
now i think i can explain it
sorry for being so chaotic today
um
no worries
you you do like
left right
uh
[Music]
look exactly at what my legs are doing
in this moment okay i'll just i'll just
start from here because it's the same
um
[Music]
you
once you're done with this or once
you're done with the
oops you uh jump into the stance but
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's bouncing
two times but
yeah left you you first start here and
switch the right side
without the bouncing and then once
you're on the left side again
you start the bouncing bub
and you should end up on the right side
when you do the hand on the right side
two times up and down up and down and up
and down up and down
okay
since we're not in sync anyway okay in
the end it all doesn't even matter
um
yes um
uh
i already kind of did teach you all the
moves of the verse
so we just need to hammer it into the
brain again
and inna really don't worry kelly as
well you not supposed to really remember
these moves in such a short amount of
time
it's all okay it's okay yeah
just can't have a play yes
before the big concert we're just uh
yeah hanging out a little bit dancing
vibing so let's play the music one more
time shall we and after we play it one
more time gouda gets to get some uh
water and i get to get a straw
[Music]
up
and up and down
[Music]
um
i need to get some water yeah little
little break time who doesn't need a
break can chill
as well
i'll be here be
[Music]
my outfit's all warped
one second
now i got this me
i got this man
the model's arms are like
shorter than my actual arms i think
it's okay that's fine
oh my god kiara's in like a yoga pose
whoa you know just slid away
these are getting creepy here
goomba
what's going on i'm scared
i'm scared oh my god watson turned into
like an scp
oh my lord what is happening in this
town
hey goomba
how do i let's see
oh that's a long hold and then i can get
my wow face on
you guys like my wow face
you guys acquainted with my wow face yet
yo what's up i don't think they've been
acquainted with my wow face what are you
talking about
what are you talking don't worry about
it let me get my gun i'm back
dude what the [\h__\h]
yeah it's my gun
my gun disappeared son of a [\h__\h] hold
on a second i'll be right back i'm good
i took it probably
holy [\h__\h] it's so dry in my room i feel
like
i'm in a [\h__\h] desert or something
everything is just sand oh my god
winter time do be like that
how's it going everybody
has disappeared with the other stage so
i got
the size is kind of wrong it's perfect
it's supposed to be your wealthy wealthy
model size i think
it's
bigger
but you know what it's cute it's
pocket-sized dude it's a it's a
possibility
my scythe is bigger than this if my
scythe is bigger than this it's just
this isn't you know one of those moments
so
it's kind of small right now but it's
getting out give me a minute it'll get
bigger
it'll get bigger you use it you use it
to get rid of the kusa just wait a
minute
get rid of that in a minute how do you
even use this side kelly how do you use
the scythe
well first of all you have to put one
leg forward hold on a second you have to
put one leg
one leg forward okay one one back and
then you you're supposed to use your leg
muscles to actually swing the side are
we doing a bend you need your hands to
be like the perfect
a band yeah
is no a finger triggered mustache that's
pretty pretty high-tech
okay
what is all of this
20 22 glasses huh
[Music]
there we go
oh it's a boom that's funny
yo i brought a drink as well
oh i'm alive doesn't that look delicious
yummy
[Music]
oh it looks like orange chocolate
citrus lemon
yeah i made that for the halloween party
what this one
i made it myself yeah
oh
what's in it yeah for my halloween
cocktail party
well if you like it it's like a
milkshake i'll make you a real one when
we actually meet up except without the
alcohol you know
it's really good it's super yummy it's
really damn good this is very tasty
is that a boom mic
okay why you look like you're working
with a camera team guru
probably
okay
is everybody well arrested
oh yes sensei
if
holy [\h__\h] you're so flexible kelly
you're
what can i say
did the screen switch because of
technical difficulties
you don't want to see her flexible body
i want to see her flexible body show us
the truth show us how flexible you are
i lost all my flexibility how about a
splint can you guys do splints
uh sure yes
oh no i dare you um
[Music]
thank you look
oh i actually wanted to do one specific
dance with you girls how about macarena
yeah
huh
[Music]
[Laughter]
right
you sing
[Music]
five
[Laughter]
which was like
okay guys i'm a little tired we're gonna
do that
again don't worry we're already in the
bridge actually again we're already at
the bridge
now
that is an okay sign i think or
something like that
oh
okay
oh sorry
hey
oh my god let me just say hello to
everyone really quick hi everyone who
are here i can move my fingers too watch
this
[Music]
hey there might be a delicacy
that might be a delicacy
[Music]
uh
in the original they dancing with three
people and they kind of switch positions
there but we're just gonna stay in
position okay
so
yeah
that's when they switch position we're
just going to do some side steps okay
and then
this is where everyone gets in sync
again
you start with a big idle step to the
right side
so right and left
once you do that once you're in that
first step
[Music]
this is before you kind of end your your
last step here you already start uh
a swirl like this you kind of like
um
yeah
you i don't know how to explain this
uh
it's kind of like
you're just like one hand is following
the other kind of yeah yeah yeah yeah
kind of like a like
like a whirlpool yeah like a whirlpool
making
yeah and once you're done with that
you're gonna go from the bottom and also
go with your hips down a little bit and
with your upper body
uh and then you kind of um
this should be normally this should be a
full open hand like a paper rock
scissors papers paper rock scissors
paper i can't do that unfortunately so
i'm just going to do a fist and maki
it's a long long long bear and while
she's singing that you go all the way up
to the front exactly
and yeah this is a really short bridge
this is how you enter into the chorus
she says
right i think we all know that phrase
[Music]
oh now this is really fast
um
you go
there
both hands up in the air and then once
you bring it down
yeah
uh up
middle to the shoulders
to the side
and then to the middle
okay up middle side middle and then you
kind of do like a face palm you look to
the side to the right side you kind of
do a face palm
yes i need to recalibrate it with masks
okay calibrate calibrate cali calioprate
this one is really fast so you gotta
really think fast you go up down right
uh middle up down right middle face palm
okay
up down right middle face
up down right middle face bone
up down right middle face bone can you
do that up down right middle face ball
up down right middle finger exactly
[Music]
okay so let's start from the bridge
again
[Music]
we just do a few side steps and then we
enter
[Music]
to the outside
middle face
it's really fast got it we gotta try it
what the music wants to adjust it to the
fast music up middle outside middle okay
face palm okay it's hard to remember me
dance time oh this is the bridge did you
change the europe last time
[Music]
it's i think it's starting soon
she restarted it
well sure
[Music]
ina yes you do this one
are you sure about it
and then there
from the bring it from the bottom lower
your upper body and bring it back to the
top yeah two
three
[Music]
three times
the face problem already um
happens after she's done singing so it's
kind of offbeat
okay so this is on ah
um
no
[Music]
it's really really quick is everyone
able to do it
you're good yep you're good
okay i can do it okay
um
uh okay that means we're already at the
chorus
or do we wanna do you guys wanna
remember the the previous parts one more
time by starting from two weeks from the
beginning yeah let's get a refresher try
to try to
full url
as the background always moved yes
yeah but this one is new it's um it's a
reference to the dreaming
music video it's a purple version of it
with with different uh writing in the
background yeah
it's cute very cute
[Music]
oh yeah from the beginning from the
beginning try to remember what we were
doing
okay
remember running
running
[Music]
up
my cable keeps on disconnecting
[Music]
foreign
nice
[Music]
so that means
we are
going to do the chorus now
uh
okay so
sorry my body was disassembling again
and we're gonna start without the music
where's i'm waited let me go i mean
you're good
i'm just having to get the music just
putting in the bridge and even though
we're not doing it quite yet okay okay
yeah the chorus should be the next one
okay i'll go go go
okay everybody here okay so
we continue from the face palm move
uh
and then
you uh change uh you bring your legs
from this position to this okay you
should be here at the face palm and then
you switch to this
and while you do that you bring your
right hand to the front and keep your
left hand on your hip
and now you uh let me change my finger i
have the right one actually this one
kind of ah this one actually this one
this is the finger you uh swirl turn the
finger around like you're pointing at
someone you're like you you you you you
yeah
i do you
i do
oh yeah and then you switch to the other
side this is just
you kind of um
shake it out
and then
you're you're kind of swiping a
windshield
uh and then
while you're doing that you bring it to
the right side
and then we do the finger again
uh
you do this move you bring it from the
right side to the middle and while you
do that
you step with your right foot with your
foot on the ground okay so it's like tap
tap tap tap tap okay tap while you do
that okay
um
only the right foot okay you can
actually lift it up pretty high so that
your knee gets lifted every time as well
okay
that's where we land and then she sings
something something that's where you do
like a little uh
um
this should be fists i have fists okay
uh you still do the step with your
you still do a step with your right leg
like this
uh
what was it again
let me try it
yeah i know the melody i forgot to move
one second
[Music]
take your time sensei
that's where we start the idol step
again we go to the right
gotcha and you bring it to the top
once you're at the top you bring it down
to your chest
and then she sings [\h__\h] no jana
usually this should be a paper pepper
hand but do whatever you want
it's not impossible
and now smash away all the things that
they say are impossible when you say
it's possible i can be on stage with my
senpai [\h__\h] you for saying that i will
do what i want let's make those dreams
come true [\h__\h] this hater [\h__\h] that
hater [\h__\h] this and [\h__\h] that
okay
i got a little bit too passionate
yes
you hear the sounds pretty clearly and
when you listen to the song um you uh
have to really make it hit
each sound properly
you can take one step to the front with
the right leg
uh and you smash a [\h__\h] window smash
that window or throw a baseball
throw that baseball
by uh lifting your left leg so you take
one step to the front of the right leg
and then you uh throw that baseball
yeah you got it got it okay okay you who
who here knows how to play baseball
does anyone you do i played softball yes
back in the day i played softball damn
wait what softball what softball
what is software
like this it's like baseball but it's
like for uh ladies oh
it's a lady's team what's the difference
is the ball not so hard
why is the difference i don't know
actually i mean yeah i think it i think
the ball is a little bit different
wait don't you throw softballs like
under
huh
oh you can do it on your hand i think
yeah wow
i think
instead of like this you throw it like
this like bowling
yeah you look like the ball is bigger
they say the softer and bigger
the ball is accurate basically
i don't want to smack your leg
okay
cool i [\h__\h] up my calibration sorry i
didn't really do many sports when i was
younger i just did uh
um
in lane skating that's all i did
or the subway sports are okay
okay okay okay
uh we were at throwing a baseball
uh but let's go again from the top
uh the first part of the chorus so i saw
baba
aloo
ha uh
[Music]
then you bring it from the right right
side to the to the front while tapping
your foot
and then
you go to fist here if you can yeah
[Music]
throw you already go
into the next part of the
of the chorus the second part uh okay
oh this is difficult this is a bit
difficult because it's not very clear in
the reference video of the choreography
but it kind of um
uh you go like um your hands just like
this to the bottom and then once up to
the top and then
you kind of uh turn it around yes
exactly
like this
and then you go back to the top
exactly exactly good job good job good
job and then you do this move
shake your head with your arms yeah yeah
cute good good good it's like are you
[\h__\h] crazy or what yep
except are you [\h__\h] crazy yeah
if you have if you have uh
uh
something like these fingers
then it's like you're um like are you
crazy you're saying that's to someone
yeah but it's actually with the fists
yeah local local
and then
we bring the hands to the front as if
we're giving someone a gift okay
and then we sway from side to side
can we play the music once a minute
[Music]
you're welcome here's my here's my
business card
hi miss you dozers
[Music]
uh
that's my favorite part of the dance
yeah it's cute it's fun doing this move
it's cute
[Music]
how long does it go on
so we were um
we were about to give someone a business
card
yeah
after giving someone the business card
that person gives you a business card
back
so you bring it take it bring it to your
heart act as if you're looking at it not
really you don't really care who that
person is okay just take that damn card
and bring it to your heart twice so that
they are sure that you really looked at
it okay
like this
and
you're kind of uh leaning to the right
side with your head and with your hip
while you're going now
no sniffing the card
it smells like pennies
after that move you
take your pointy finger
take your pointy finger find the finger
uh
i think yeah it was like this yeah you
just say no no no no no no no no no no
no
[Music]
uh this should be open hands no no no no
no
no no no no no yeah no no no no no
what the hell is wrong with you
what the hell is wrong with you did i
stream today
what's your name simulation ice cream
alden ring today or elven ring that's
what inna is thinking about is
i'm thinking ring but i'm also torn
between elder and it could be elden ring
perhaps maybe just maybe
i don't know i think i think elden
ring's probably better to play
i think yeah
i'm in elderly moods kelly and ina are
currently addicted to ellen ring so
there's no other choices
i'm just trying to play
who's your wife
can i ask you your wife is
me too oh my god no wayna
[Music]
after saying no no no nothing else it
must be ellen ring ellen ring
she sings
[Music]
with your right hand and your right foot
you step and while you're doing that you
kind of um
how to describe this movement huh kelly
tell me
yeah this is a swimming move yeah yeah
as if you're swimming
yeah so you do that once with the right
side
and then you do you keep on switching
one two three four four times okay
[Music]
yeah that's where you um
kind of almost get on your knees
but while we're actually dancing we
probably won't go that far because it's
faster but just in spirit think that
you're going on your knees on the left
knee uh kind of uh
oh my god
that's actually where uh you do a turn
but i have a cable on my headset i don't
know about you girls but i'm not going
to do the turn so we should do something
else you just maybe pose yeah
pose
first does the turn and then you and
then you pose you say
it's over is done we're done
done and then she sings oh okay
[Music]
oh god my brain
let me look let me look
yeah your t posing basically
[Music]
wait i think i
oh
[Music]
i think
i think i may have mixed one move up
that one i don't know where i was doing
that but that doesn't belong there uh it
goes it belongs to okinawa
uh
can we play the music once i'm or i'm
gonna
forget sure let's go for it i haven't
done this so you gotta remember too i
haven't done this dance in like 10
[\h__\h] years or so so
my brain is looking foggy
the chorus chorus yes
[Music]
here is your business card
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
it seems like today
i am just a hot [\h__\h] mess um
but what you think's all keep in mind oh
okay it says big
means big a big dream big dream while
you're doing that
while you're doing that that's when you
go
[Music]
you cross your arms in front of your
chest
then you switch to the side
you just kind of bring them out
you may you may
you like it don't you it's what you're
saying
exactly
that's easy enough and that's when we go
to the outro
and we can add that now i think we will
be able to remember
somewhat
it's just idle step for a while and then
she goes sidestep with the wobble again
sidestep with the wobble again
and then this move that we learned in
the intro
and this
is basically the intro as the outro it's
the same moves
she just goes
for quite a while
[Music]
punch left
b you get
big shoes apparently oh [\h__\h] i can't i'm
calibrating that's okay
i may have to do some smaller moves so i
don't bump into my furniture because i
live in a very small place
the underworld do be like that right
you do be like that there are lots of
[\h__\h] in the underworld so you
know everybody's got small houses yeah
everybody needs some space
but there ain't no space in the world
stretch stretch stretch stretch
stretch
we actually um kind of learned it until
the end of the song but let's play the
chorus again until the outro um and then
we're done then we can try to do the
whole song
the spirit that comes
oh
[Music]
thank you for the business
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
punch left
yeah
that's where it ends that's where it
ends let's let's um i think we can do it
a few times but it's always a little bit
if we do it on the green screen then
somebody can edit it yeah yeah yeah
let's do that yeah nice
that's so bad that's a good idea
okay uh but wait uh wait wait wait a
second
um
green screen hurts my apples
okay okay okay very bright
switching to green screen let me put my
drink away then
drink behind the green screen
okay
i'm are you switching to green screen
i think she's doing it
let me check i think then there's one
problem
you just press the button i'm just
putting in the full song right now
[\h__\h] gun
where is the green screen
i'm so upset about my gun
i don't know where the green screen is
huh
hmm
thank you so much
you want to dance with your gun that's
dangerous this is good you're gonna let
it go go on fine
no it's super mowing
yeah but okay
[Music]
swirls
um
[Music]
business cards
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
for being a terrible teacher today
i'm so sorry no
i'm so sorry about that that was a blast
kiara be nice to yourself i'm morning
you'll be
that's a [\h__\h] water gun cali
it's a water gun what's water going to
do to me
i can't move anymore it's not even
filled with water if you've got a gun
guess what i have myself
we've done this dance before kiara let's
go
then i have a funny idea this camera
looks broken to me it doesn't look
broken to you though huh oh there it
goes hold on if you zoom out you should
be able to zoom on it i want i want to
do something i want to do a start with
our with our legs this one has a
leveling
[Music]
i don't know why my legs can't go
straight though
but we can do we can do a star with that
if everyone sits like that in a circle
i hope it don't make you go out of here
kelly can you do them uh do that to
actually sit oh you can sit down yes
i know you do you know how to sleep on
the floor
so
i met people for a star
on the ground
yeah cali
connects uh ame with ina is this
[Music]
let's put a bottle in the middle and
then turn the bottle and and give it to
each other's choo choose i don't
oh my god
okay
[Music]
oh my god you call it epidermis i call
it identity
what's happening to your family i
learned something new chilling
ice cream skin but it's not very
accurate
i thought you were just wearing like
what is happening
skin color this is yeah
[Music]
though your face i just want to hold it
forever
oh my gosh
speaking as a bird
yeah as a bro but that's fine we're just
bros just bros being friends hey listen
what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you dude
what's wrong with you man this is normal
you're the one making it weird
you're the one making it
oh wow this is kind of wild for me
can i do a heart this is kind of wild
thank you my gun
i got a gun
pow pow
plums hold on this is not the right
expression
can you move one meter to the right so
people see the bottle
yes ma'am
oh there's one i get to the left or the
right
holy [\h__\h]
hello uh-oh hello
is this thing
yeah
i mean i don't think
i hear your voice normally if that's
what you mean oh
oh yeah
kelly is that
is that a mic oh [\h__\h]
it's my gun
i don't say so cool i don't say so
i don't speak japanese i don't know what
that means
[Laughter]
my tracking is wrong oh you're doing
selfie camera
i want to be the cameraman
you want to be a camera man
only if you're also on the camera
did we did we give
[Music]
so yeah my hand isn't showing because i
think it's because of that yeah there we
go
oh hi
hi
[Music]
hello
hello hello
[Music]
hi wait wait thank you wait
wait
oh
okay
yeah yeah
love
cute you look so adorable
what the hell
give me that
[Music]
[Laughter]
she stole
is
[Music]
is almost
too close
cute
are we going to take super cute selfies
oh yeah
[Music]
oh my gosh my gun
my gun hi ladies
hello
hi
goodness gracious need to stop being
about their motivation for the weekend
how about today we ask inaudible
food
poses while they do it oh i love them
sure i can do that
you know how are you feeling totally
stabbed towards them really come from
the ground since it's
one two for you how many days today is
uh today's what today's wednesday i
think today is wednesday today is the
day yes you're on a saturday yeah
how are you feeling
hello
um
i'll do my best
okay very memorable i think um
i'm not used to the thick stage alone oh
yeah
big stage it's gonna be you see stage
but you you deserve it we all deserve a
big big stage to showcase our our
idleness oh yeah yeah
yeah
everyone works so hard it's finally wait
finally time it's happening
yeah what about you it's exciting
on day two on day two right with me
yeah
indeed i mean i'm really excited about
it just because i mean uh doing 3d stuff
is kind of like it's a really big thing
for me because i plan to do a lot of
concerts and like really big things in
3d and so it's just it's really exciting
that everybody finally gets to see
finally gets to see us all in 3d and i'm
really glad that it could be together
because one of my biggest fears is that
it was going to be like
oh callie you you got to be 3d now like
we need you to be 3d but then you guys
weren't gonna get to show yours and i
was just like really scared about that
so
now that we all get to be revealed
together i feel so much better and and
now knowing that we can like be like do
like three cool like 3d stuff and stuff
like that it's just really exciting and
i can't wait it's like the start of a
whole new a whole new adventure you know
[Music]
yeah excited
i'm excited the possibilities are
opening up before our eyes i'm hyped so
let's
yeah to make a great first impression
yes
i think indeed it will be a chance for
us to also
get closer to the japanese audience
because there will be so many uh
japanese viewers in the in the real
audience but then there's also of course
the online international audience but
yeah i hope we can make a good
impression and and hype up the crowd
when we perform on stage i wanna i
always wanted to go like
and then hear the people go like oh
and i wanna hear i wanna see their hands
with the lightsabers
[Music]
oh my god dream come true that would be
so nice
who's gonna cry me me i'm gonna cry
i think it's best to hold it i think
it's all gonna happen so fast that i
won't even be able to really process
what's going on and maybe i'll cry
afterwards but not not during it no no
no no no not during it
don't want to mess up something so
important with crying no no no no no no
yeah
good performance and then we cry yeah
yeah mm-hmm
crying can come later
afterwards
yes although although my my viewers they
all said oh i'm gonna cry when i see you
on stage yeah you guys are probably
gonna cry
that's okay so are the chumps
dead beats you better cry i'll beat you
up what yeah
you'll be
that was that was twice i like this
can i say something like this isn't that
just this is corny as [\h__\h] but like
sitting here
actually feels like we're
together yeah
actually beside me right now it feels
pretty close to that but but if it were
really together i would i would know
that you smell like roses you smell like
the ocean you smell like lemon you smell
like
i'm not sure about inna what does these
actually smell like old spices but emma
knows what inna smells like though
violet
cuyahoga
it's something you pick up
subconsciously you'll be like oh yeah
you know smells like
violet violence like violence
so i associate the smell of soap she
gave me oh she gave you silly yeah
i gotta prepare presents for you guys
when we meet i'm gonna pick the best
[Music]
you can make good desserts you guys are
coming to my house
guys
it's a party party
i can make really good chocolate chip
cookies
yeah let's all cook together that's what
i really want to do get a nice place
where we got a big kitchen and we can
all just have a cooking party
yeah
yeah yeah
this sounds nice
oh
nice there we go we should do that thing
where we go we get behind each other and
do that yeah
okay
yeah yeah
we can do
this now
[Music]
choo choo
yeah go real deep there go real deep
yeah okay
we've gotta
[Laughter]
it's like and everybody follows you yeah
something like that
blend that do whatever and we'll follow
you i guess
you gotta do this uh isn't it like
with the right hand oh yeah add the
right hand with our heads
this
um
probably mostly k-pop videos where they
stand in one line and they play the song
and uh someone in the front dances and
then they go back to the back and then
the person who who's second dances a
little bit and then they go to the back
so we can play hide-and-go-guide and
then just do freestyle freestyle dance
okay
and every every 10 seconds or so the
they switch the back you know what i
mean
that sounds okay yeah let's do it let's
play how do you guys
yeah yeah with music yeah and then
just freeze time in front freestyle or
dance to choreo however you prefer
okay
three
four ina come to the middle
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
breakdown
yeah okay well okay with that i think
that was a beautiful ending dance
oh
thank everybody for watching today you
know we have a concert on the weekend
you can watch it online or in person but
tickets are often gone so pretty much
definitely 100 gone so please watch us
online if you want to that's a shame
um i think i think some of us will be
doing a watch long i'll be doing a watch
long of day one i'll be looking at
inaugura and ame
on the first day
and i think
and me we're definitely doing a members
only watch along on sunday too right is
anyone for doing one you also doing one
yeah i'm doing a members only for for
day two
but it's a little bit later it's like
it's the day after so it's like a little
bit
yeah it's like after kiara's i think by
a couple hours so you can experience it
together with us if you want
or you can experience it alone
you can experience it two times or three
times or five four whatever
and yeah and
thank you everybody for watching this
was taka nashikara from whole life
english and
murray calliope from whole live english
and
miami
[Music]
come to the middle and put your hands in
the middle i always wanted to do this
everybody put your hands in the middle
okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yes yes yes yes um
i see you i see you as our leader you
streamed before yeah do you want to say
something like let's do our best
like that
um yeah it's already been over a year
and almost a half i think and and now
we're gonna keep going strong and things
will be a little bit different from now
on because you know we'll have a sort of
evolved form where you guys are going to
see more of us than you've ever seen
before um so looking forward to it we're
still all trying our best and to make
you guys happy and to do what makes us
happy and that makes us all happy yeah
thank you everybody for watching and
there we go thank you
[Music]
and in german we say auf wiedersehen
[Applause]
oh
you