[Music]
do
can't get
[Music]
time
oh yeah let's act let's just ask that
this is the first stream on my channel
since my vacation
it's like
not really but let's just act because
this was this stream was supposed to
come first
well here we are
[Music]
excuse me what sorry you got destroyed
by guard yesterday excuse me i destroyed
him okay
he's a
as far as i know
he's a very very experienced shadowverse
player
who definitely knows what he's doing
probably played it for what how long
years
and i actually as a newcomer
managed to defeat him
one of the three times okay
so i will say i destroyed him
i think i think if if i
um
and to be honest my deck
was quite uh at a disadvantage against
him like no matter how often i would
practice with my coach oh my god are we
going into shadow very uh topic tangent
right away
yeah yeah he even he even wrote it
himself that i killed him
in
wait immediate immediate tension
uh well yeah i was i was gonna say
that when i was practicing with my coach
momma
um she would like look at my
hand obviously because i would
screenshare but at the same time she
would play
the deck that giggle place against me
and obviously would try her best
to like
navigate both of us
and
so like she would do the best she could
do
like not trying to let let me win
and
would also navigate me perfectly
and then still
still i would lose like pretty much
almost every time
it's just
yeah not really like i don't know the
deck that he was playing is very very
difficult to beat at least with my
dick
so i'm i'm quite
impressed by myself i'm satisfied and
happy that i got him at least once
yeah
love the voice hacking session thank you
that was fun
that was actually
i i was like oh i'm gonna make every
line in german so where i wrote uh ahead
of time i wrote down
like every line in german
but then it started
and i realized
[Music]
they they're the the coaches are
probably
like gonna find it funny in the first
two
expressions but then afterwards they're
gonna be like well i don't i don't know
what the hell you're saying so
can't give you a point for that so
while the others were saying their voice
lines i quickly
uh changed up my voice lines to add more
english to it and and yeah
maybe some more humor as well because i
noticed that
you gotta you gotta throw out some
some savageness and some meme
otherwise you don't get points
so i tried to
integrate some stuff like that but i'm
not the kind of person who can think of
stuff like that
at all
yeah the only thing i could think of was
guess i'll die
but other than that i couldn't think of
anything
so yeah
yeah
i i i i did my i did my best
yeah and the pictionary
[Laughter]
pationary went really bad
but i think i think it's okay
you did great thank you
uh well anyway i didn't want to do it i
didn't want to talk about shadow verse
right away but
as you can see from my
beautiful straw hat
and my
here my [\h__\h] let me put it on top of
junkers
[Music]
foreign
as you can see i'm i came back from my
vacation
[Laughter]
uh
but i still brought some
some vacation vibes with me i feel like
this outfit is so [\h__\h] perfect
because there's a swimsuit underneath
and a straw hat and sunglasses if i
wanna
uh but yeah uh we're gonna mostly talk
about the vacation
and then also i guess talk about the
streams that have happened yesterday and
so on
like the
usaki and summer festival
and the
shadowfish tournament
seven
seven hours shallower tournament did you
guys watch
it did you guys watch it it was not on
my channel but i told you guys several
times and i showed you the link on
twitter and i i gave you the link on the
youtube community board as well a lot of
you guys are saying yes but i know a lot
of you guys were not there evil
but i practiced really hard and i
thought like it was really really really
really really
interesting and cool and entertaining
and actually today after i woke up i
spent like two hours
watching um
here we go we're talking about channel
voice again
i spent two hours watching
um my uh the matches where i was in
and because i was really curious what
the coaches were saying and about my
turns and and my
uh uh
opponent's turns and um
and when
at what which times they would
uh
like
unmute us and and listen in because i i
did not know i did not know when they
were listening in so i actually talked a
lot to myself even on the coach muted
turns because i was like what if they
turn uh tune in to the coach mini turns
but they actually did not
tune into the coach music turns even
once
uh yeah i wasn't i wasn't sure if they
were so i was just talking just in case
i was like talking to myself a little
bit it was kind of awkward but i think i
think momo was listen like she was muted
to me but i was also low-key like hoping
that she hears what i'm saying i think
she was able to hear it
so i just wanted to
um also let her know
like what i'm feeling
during these coaching unit turns
and i did
oh man especially in that last round i
[\h__\h] up a bunch of times and the
coaches didn't even
didn't even know that
some of the things i did were
unintentional and i actually wanted to
do something else partially
oh my god the best example
like okay so this was a seven hour
thingy okay and for me it started at a
decent time
uh like uh 9 p.m
uh and it ended at an undecent time
half past 4 am
and which was
okay
because
uh
wait a second yeah because i stayed up
so long and ruined my sleep schedule for
the reddit shitpost review anyway
so i was i was kind of ready with i
wasn't really feeling that tired um
although it is exhausting to be like 100
focused for seven hours and trying to do
my best in the tournament that was quite
exhausting but
the one thing that was obviously a bit
more of a problem was that you know
my my neck
i was
i was still uh in some pain and i was
taking painkillers i i got prescribed
we're gonna talk about this later but i
got prescribed seven different
no not two different painkillers and i'm
taking seven
of them each
no
totally total
number is seven per day
and there's two swords
and yeah anyway so so so
uh
during the tournament see we didn't
think it was not really planned to have
it be seven hours uh so that was kind of
unexpected so i didn't really account
for eating food in between but i ended
up uh being forced to because i was
feeling really hungry so before my last
match i made myself some pizza and
quickly devoured it so that gave me back
some energy but i was still
like it was still getting really [\h__\h]
late and i was under the influence of a
lot of painkillers and i started getting
uh quite the headache later on so
in that last match against kelly
i was not feeling very well and i could
not focus anymore obviously kelly
probably definitely also was not feeling
well because she uh was running on very
little sleep and it was a really awkward
starting time for her
uh
the whole tournament started for her at
4 00 am
so yeah uh both of us were a bit [\h__\h]
in the head i think
um
but yeah
i was i was not feeling so well so the
things i did were so stupid
and i watched the archive of it and it
was not even so noticeable apparently
but i [\h__\h] up a bunch of times and
every time when my coach would uh be
able to unmute herself and get into the
call with me i was like instantly they
you never got that because
they they um unmuted us very late always
but i was always like
like
immediately when it was my turn i was
yelling
i'm so
at least at least you know i
i knew that i did things that i
shouldn't have done
ah it was uh
it was very funny
every [\h__\h] turn i messed something up
that that even though i won
that was not how i wanted to
do it but i was i was losing my
concentration i was i was [\h__\h] done
and my um my neck hurts her head and my
uh
head hurts and my
concentration was not there anymore uh
thank you painkillers i guess um
yeah so
for example let me tell you one example
[Music]
please you guys need to watch the
archive if you haven't but um
her
ted
shut up
um i know hurts it hurt is correct but i
wanted to say herded because that sounds
better
because it makes it more clear that i'm
talking about the past
and i don't like uh
saying hurt in
in past tense because it's stupid anyway
anyway it doesn't matter
hurts ted
oh yeah
you have to watch the archive if you
haven't because um
i was laughing
when i woke up and i was watching that
arcade
i was so entertained because
um you see i was playing this phoenix
deck
and
um
there's a phoenix card in my deck
which if you play it and you evolve it
you
um
are you um play an amulet and and that
basically gives you the effect that
every card you play you you draw every
card you draw afterwards will be half
cost so that is the special most special
thing about the whole phoenix deck is
that there is a phoenix card which helps
the cost of everything
not only for me but also for the
opponent but you can even play a second
phoenix and then it halves the half of
it so that's absolutely
incredible
um
so
you would you would normally
only play the phoenix
after you were able to evolve because in
check overs there's this evolving thing
and that you cannot do from the start
you can't you can do it after the uh
third go for return or so i don't know
at a certain point
so i hope i always wait for that and
then play the phoenix and evolve my
phoenix immediately in the first round
where i can evolve
and i'm 100 aware of that
strategy
and i did it
like that all along
now sometimes sometimes
you can like if you feel like it
uh in some situations
it's okay to play the phoenix without an
evolve before they evolve
anyway just to have something on the
board
and
yeah just to be there i guess
and i did have two in my hand yes that's
correct so i did have like an uh like an
excess of phoenixes that i didn't need i
didn't need so many rather lane usually
you can do a whole game with only one
phoenix you don't necessarily have to
double the uh half the half
one phoenix does
already have cost
so that's enough generally
so
having two phoenix's in my hand right
away in the beginning
i was waiting to evolve one after
the evolving got activated and my coach
was aware of that and we talked about it
and then coach says bye bye i say bye
bye
and coach
muted turn starts for me
and they were not listening in at that
moment but they were like oh she has two
phoenix's in there in her hand i
wouldn't i wouldn't uh even uh mind if
she played one of those phoenixes
without an evolve on her board uh just
to be a little bit aggressive and have
something on the board because i i don't
think i had anything else
is mama here
normal here
i don't think i had anything else that
would actually like make damage and be a
follower i only had like ramping stuff
mama
hey hey hey
mama probably hurt me when i was uh wait
where are you momo
where the hell are you
where is she i can't find her
mama
oh i don't see you wait are you you're
not a member right uh are you mama
oh
i want a module
i can see you easier is mumble a mem
not a member okay let me look at the
non-green names
[Music]
okay now you're easier to see now i'm
looking forward to what you have to say
when we talk about channels
so so so so so let me tell you okay i'm
continuing uh where was that oh yeah
momo heard me i think moma you heard me
when even when you were muted right when
i was like freaking out
so i spot i mean
the painkillers might have clouded my
memory but as far as i remember
i
uh you couldn't hear me oh yeah i
thought so i thought so as far as i can
remember
when i played the first phoenix and all
the all the uh
all the um
uh what do you call them again the
people who the commentators they were
like oh i like that she's very
aggressive though i don't think that's
bad that's really good yeah she has
another phoenix anyway yeah i like the
strategy uh kiara so they were really
hyped up about it and thought it was on
purpose but to be honest that was not
imperfect
because
my brain you know i told you i lost my
concentration and i was like even though
it was what the second round or
something only or the third round i did
i did not have an evolve yet
the vote would be two turns later i
think at that point and uh my brain was
like oh i already have the above so
let's play the phoenix and develop the
phoenix and i played the phoenix and
then that moment i was like oh
wait oh i don't oh
my mom
[Laughter]
and then i started panicking laughing at
myself because that was uh stupid but
apparently it was not that stupid after
all because then momo was on the call
again and she was like it's okay it's
okay that's actually not not a problem
like it's not a big deal
and the commentators were like were like
praising me for being so so aggressive
yeah it looked intentional
no that was only one of the mistakes
that i did uh in that last match
i [\h__\h] up a few times i don't even
remember other times i think so there
was another incident that
the commentators were questioning and
then later apologized for it but i think
i really did make a mistake or at least
i did not do
what i wanted to do and maybe maybe what
i wanted to do was the wrong thing
and i ended up doing the right thing i
don't know but in any case i don't think
i did what i wanted to do
uh with the fusion where where the
commentators were like oh did you just
fuse the wrong thing
it was the few thing that was hard to
work yeah yeah i did do something wrong
there right but later on the
commentators were like oh we apologize
of course she knew what she was doing
and infused the right thing
yeah i think i feel the wrong card
because i was being stupid again
i mean after seven like six hours being
on painkillers and already being way
past midnight come on come on give me a
break i was like
[Applause]
i was like [\h__\h] up so many times it
was so stupid the whole match was so
ridiculous and then i ran out of cards
like i never had many cards to begin
with in that match because of that
[\h__\h] fusion i wanted to get cards out
of the fusion obviously but i fused it
with the wrong card and then i didn't
draw any cards this probably sounds
really um like confusing to people who
don't know shadow version who didn't
watch the stream but
stay with me
um
so i was going really bad
but but i love how the commentators
did not know
this they didn't know this like i was
out
i was like
you you mainly only saw the the camera
of me right and not you didn't hear the
voice and i also was reading the
comments afterwards and then the
comments were also like oh kiana's
vibing ken is so happy kids excited and
actually
i was just laughing at myself and half
crying and like what the [\h__\h] did i do
and apologizing to momo the whole time
even when she uh was muted i was just
passing i was not vibing i was just
laughing at myself for being so stupid
and then and then yeah basically just
panic mode all the [\h__\h] time
uh
but they thought they thought i was just
being happy and confident no
no no no no no
so yeah we realized that we were
definitely having an issue with cards
and um
you know the playing the phoenix card in
the beginning was still like
wasn't what i wanted to do but it's
definitely something you can do in that
situation but the fusion really [\h__\h]
me over so i didn't have cards and kelly
had a lot of cards and she she had good
cards
she had damn good cards
i think
as far as i can tell and as far as i
remember the commentators commented on
it
yeah
i'm such a mood i know
they were wrong so wrong yes they were
you guys too though you guys thought you
know i did the phoenix on purpose you
thought i was having fun i was not
having fun
my legit thought you were gonna lose me
too
[Laughter]
we were me and momo were just like
panicking
um
i wish i wish there was a separate
recording of uh the whole thing with our
voices on the whole time that would have
been fun
everyone's brain was gone by that point
yeah yeah yeah
especially yours i guess because you
probably paid you didn't only pay
attention to what i was doing you paid
attention to what the opponent was doing
all the time
and counting shadows and counting
paradigms or whatever the [\h__\h] that was
i still don't really know what the how
the [\h__\h] giggling stack works i have i
have no idea and you know it one it was
so [\h__\h] complicated i did not even
want to think about it i i did not want
to think about it i did not want to
learn what the hell his deck is and how
it was no it was not worth my time
i just wanted to survive
and deal with whatever is in front of me
[Music]
so oh yeah what was i saying oh yeah so
we were running out of cards and then we
were really [\h__\h]
uh but
but
somehow
i was surviving
by living off of the top of my deck
and
getting exactly the only cards
that would have worked and the only
cards that i needed to win because i got
those like
it was just so [\h__\h] perfect you guys
have to watch the archive if you didn't
watch it look up shadowverse official
channel on youtube
uh open up the stream the seven hour
stream go into the comments there is a
comment with all the time uh time
stamps and go to the very bottom because
that match was the very last one against
cali we had three matches against cali
and the last one is the is the most
chaotic one especially now if you know
the backstory if you know my side of the
story
if you know that i i was just [\h__\h] up
and did not know what i was doing
but it's even funnier
at the moment oh my god man
also yeah you know how
how
oh wait was that the last match or was
that another a different one where i was
like i had leaf
no
yeah i think that was a different
one against cali
like i don't even know anymore but there
was a moment where i had lethal with
gandagoza
and the commentators were like yeah yeah
this is over this is over but i was on a
non-coach call and on coach turn and and
and
and my brain was already um
melted cheese
and you know when you ganda gilda has
eight attack and and whoever my opponent
was had 10 health points left but if you
evolve kanda goes out was that the was
that the girl killed probably yeah
actually yeah uh if you evolve ganagoza
he get goes from eight attack to ten
attack
and
i used gandagoza a million times because
it's so [\h__\h] easy to use and i love
gandagoza
he was rocking my deck
um
and
so
i was thinking i i saw that i had
gandagoza but i was like but if i evolve
him i only get up to nine oh that was
against kelly okay okay okay the second
one against count
i guess so maybe uh whatever
it was some match where where the
opponent had ten half points left and i
thought that if i evolved ganagoza it
would only have nine not ten attack that
it would go from eight to nine and not
from eight to ten
uh
because my brain was already like
yeah
melted
so i was thinking and thinking and
thinking while the commentators were
like yeah yeah yeah yeah she knows she
has gotten the ghost or she knows she
just has to use him for the lethal but
then after a while they were like wait
why
why didn't she play it yet oh yeah
what's happening why is she still
thinking why is she not doing anything
and yeah in reality
i needed a moment to realize that
he does get up to 10 and that i have to
play him immediately otherwise the time
is [\h__\h] up and i'm i'm [\h__\h]
but yeah i realized in the last moment
and i i threw him out there i evolved
him and i i i killed the opponent and
then momo got back into the call and we
were both like
and i was like mama i'm so sorry and she
was like i was so scared i was so scared
[Music]
dad actually that was on stream because
they unmuted us for the moment
so
you can listen to that that was also
very funny
oh
man
oh man
it was it was very
funny
the fuck-ups were so funny like in
against giggup i was still um
focused
i still
i still have like a
like a oh
i knew what was going on but in the in
the end i did not know what was going on
[Music]
but i took this whole thing now tell us
how you broken okay okay wait wait let
me just finish the shadows dog i took
this whole thing
so serious i didn't want to take it that
seriously
but i took it so serious i'm quite the
emotional type of person you know when
we had that take two
um match
[Music]
uh
where you build your deck at the spot
with random cards thrown at you
and well first of all i want to say
because that was not on stream you were
not able to see our point of view of
building the deck
but
me and momo were really struggling
because the choices that we got
were uh bloodcraft havencraft and
portalcraft maybe
i'm not sure what the third one was but
it was all it was all choices that are
not
desirable for take to uh shallow crab
okay that were not desirable for take
two and fey took havencraft um
and anyway
even even havencraft is maybe not the
most desirable option for take two the
easiest would have been like a forest
forest or
what was the other one
uh
swordcraft those are the ones that you
want to get because they're easy okay
and we practice at least a little bit
with with forest crafts and also have
more experience with forest crafts i
would have hoped for forest crafts
oh portal and roon are also really good
i guess so but i would have no idea how
to [\h__\h] use them they sound very
complicated so we had those choices
bloodcraft shadowcraft havencraft
and
momo said we should go for blood crabs
because that's still like strong and
manageable and she knows how to play
bloodcraft
so i trusted her i mean the other
choices were not good evil
but i was so nervous because i had no
[\h__\h] idea how to play
uh and i'm not not at that level of
experience yet where i can play just
whatever
and just understand it anyway i don't
have that much experience yet
so we we started building the deck you
know it would have been fine if we would
have at least had good cards for our
[\h__\h] dick
but
momo and me were really struggling to
build the deck
because all the cards that got thrown at
us were mostly [\h__\h] there was only one
good card that we got one good card
which is also the one that i played at
the very end and totally [\h__\h] up
because i ran out of time and i was in
an unmuted uh a coach mutant
wait that was yeah faye got quite
good cars her deck ended up being pretty
good and our deck was just a huge mess
absolutely unplayable and the cars that
i was drawing were also [\h__\h] and we got
to a point where you know
we were already
losing
somehow
and um
i was scared and i had what three cards
in my hand
and and moment was like okay next turn
play this and then this
and i'm like okay
but then the next turn
which was the losing turn for me
basically the next turn
i got
the only good card in my deck the best
card
i forgot his name what was his name no
more
and i was like [\h__\h] momo told me that
this card is super good and it looks
super good because i i said in the
description and it can attack twice and
it has bane and whatever so many things
yeah that was his name
and i was like [\h__\h] i feel like
momo would want me to play that card
because she didn't know that card was
gonna come
she told me to play two certain cards
but but
with hazan
i'm sure she would tell me to play hazan
but i was i was not sure i was like
i didn't want to lose
[Music]
so i ended up actually playing
i guess the right thing i played one of
the cards that she told me to play and i
played hassan and then i evolved him and
i wanted to attack i wasn't sure yet if
that was really like gonna work out but
i was like okay whatever we're gonna do
it feels like the right thing to do but
then i evolved him and the moment
because those [\h__\h] animations take so
[\h__\h] much time
he was like doing this evolve uh uh
animation
that blocked me from from clicking on
the kill
from doing the the attack animation
so time ran out
and that's how i lost it i could have i
guess somehow turned it around if i
would have attacked
hazaan has bane and drain and can attack
twice it was the perfect answer to the
board
my instructors were actually not great
because i messed up misread one oh
really
oh
no it's okay honestly we had such a
shitty [\h__\h] dick but i was so
i was so frustrated because i really
wanted to win this like and i didn't
want to be like i wanted to win like
something and
and then because of [\h__\h] time like i
was already so so bad and
nervous and pressured i just
[Music]
i start crying
i'm glad they muted me on stream
because i was crying
i was
i was legit crying
um
yeah i got i got too worked up about it
i was so frustrated [\h__\h] take two i hate
texture i never want to play it again
i hate it
i hate it so much
but then right after that we had the
voice acting thing so
i tried to get myself back together
and uh yeah
[Music]
do my best at the voice acting thing
i i wiped off my tears and then went
ahead with it
yeah
at least the voice acting thing went
somewhat somewhat well
yeah
um
oh man but i'm really glad that
i was able to win some matches
and honestly it was like playing
shadowverse
was so much fun
not only in the tournament but more i
guess it was more fun in
the practice like here in here and there
like on my vacation
um
i was practicing with my coach and also
on my own
and i was just like really having a lot
of fun
it was a nice hobby that i picked up
there
and
yeah
i i really
i really just um
had a lot of fun with it even though you
know tournament
it was
it the tournament ended up being way
more serious and way more stressful than
i thought it would be
like the whole organization and all that
was effing good like they did a great
job and everything went smoothly uh
mostly and i i i and the staff were nice
and the commentators were nice and uh my
coach was nice the opponents were nice
everything was great but
just the fact that it's a tournament
brings so much pressure with it
and especially when there's someone in
there like
who's like really strong
and i know that he knows what he's doing
it gave me this pressure of needing to
be able to
get on his level but how can i get on
his level in such a short time right
yeah that was uh
quite a challenge um but hey i killed
him once
i did kill him once yeah
[Music]
and i was the only one in the whole
tournament who was able to beat him once
callie was up against him in take two
but not
what
not in a normal
match
and faye was against him in a normal
match and yeah they both uh
got wrecked by kikuk
honestly from for my part as well when i
won i would i would say that that was
also like just our i mean the whole
thing is just rng
like me winning against kelly in that
last match it was also just r d all of
this is mostly rng
me winning against gig was not really
skill
it was just rng
yeah it's mostly rng i still i still
don't understand what heart of cards
means
and i i learned what the top of the top
deck means but what does heart of cards
mean
it's from yugioh
oh
what does it mean
[Music]
it
it means you got the card that you need
in the next
turn
getting the right card in the right
moment ah
trusting in the heart of the cards is
believing in your top deck ah
okay okay okay i'll go
well well well well so yeah
that was channelers
that was shadowverse if you missed it
watch the archive
you can you can if you want only watch
the parts where me and cali are in but
the others were also really
entertaining i think and interesting
wow wow what an experience but i'm so
glad i was able to be in there together
with cali
um because it was a whole arc like it
was a whole season
tournament arc for real though me and
kelly were uh you know doing shadow
verse related things for a while now
and now it feels like there's like a
proper ending of this season
and it gives you this feeling of
accomplishment and finishing something
off it's like kind of satisfying
yes yes yes
[Music]
so
i think
i have my memo
i have a memo
uh with some random things that happened
during my vacation that i felt like
that i felt like oh i want to talk talk
about with you guys actually it's not
that much
and it's really a lot of small random
things too oh yeah i just want to say
though one more thing about shadowverse
tournament
faye one of the four opponents was faye
uh a voice actress a cute voice actress
who does a lot of english voices for
animes and games and and and she
did the english voice for petra from
fire alarm free houses which i played a
long time ago on my channel remember
and uh
i was playing it in japanese
but i fell in love with petra
in that game and i was so [\h__\h] pissed
off when i was not able to romance hair
and and back then that's already like
what half a year ago
and and back then i was like getting
really frustrated over it and that
that kind of created a little
interaction between me and faye like
half a year ago where she was like on
twitter replying to me that she is so
sorry and she would totally romance me
if like or she would let petra romance
me if she could or something like that
so that was already a really funny
incident back then but besides that i
never really had any interactions or or
or like contact with her and then when i
saw when i realized
that she is one of the participants for
the tournament i thought that was so
[\h__\h] random
and then in the beginning i didn't even
understand why i later on realized oh
she's a voice actress for one of the for
two leaders that are in the game
so she has a connection with the game
and it was fate it was faint it was
indeed faint
it's just so [\h__\h] funny when i
realized that i was i thought it was
hilarious it was absolutely hilarious
um
but
i thought that we wouldn't get that much
interaction anyway
during the tournament but i was wrong
because during the minigames we got a
lot of interaction and
i did not expect her
to
be
[Music]
so
how to say
into me
i i was very surprised because right
away from the beginning
she was sending me those signals and i
was like what's going on
what
what what
and i was feeling so flattered and
wow
so i was getting pretty excited
and and and
the more
you know it was not a one-time thing it
was throughout the whole tournament like
we had this minigame where we would draw
cards of the game uh with paint in 60
seconds and the coach would
guess which card we're drawing and
while the while the commentators were
explaining the game
uh fake was drawing me on paint and i
saw
it she was like really putting a lot of
effort into it it looked really good and
i was like what what what's going on
wait why is she drawing me what
did what
i'm getting signals here
the whole time she was like flirting
with me and i was
oh i liked it
i did not expect it
but it made me really happy
[Laughter]
yeah
now that
it's nice to you know for once be the
one that's being
how to say
what's the word
what's the word for that
[Music]
symptom pursued that's what yeah that's
what i wanted to say
[Music]
sued yeah
yeah
that was nice recorded yes
why
huh
i just thought something about english
language but those both of the work both
of those words have something to do
with law
suing something and being in the court
that's
that's a weird connection
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
i thought there were no japanese people
right now because it's so like an
awkward time but
they they are here so let me speak a bit
more japanese
so
well well well
you know
the whole neck thing
is overshadowing the fact that not only
the end of my vacation was [\h__\h] but also
the beginning because i was uh not able
to board my flight and had to go to my
vacation one day later do you guys
remember that
um
so
you know i wasn't that bothered by that
i was not so bothered by that because to
be honest i thought that
no
four nights is enough anyway
it's actually my my room my ex roommate
who wanted to go a little bit longer
so i just went with it
but
having the end ruined as well
leaves quite the sour taste
uh i did not like throughout the whole
uh
vacation until the end
the whole missing the first day thing
was not not a big deal to me at all i
forgot about it and i was just enjoying
um the vacation in the moment
so that was it was really okay
it was really fun especially because
if i would have boarded that first
flight
i would have been
oh yeah i didn't even tell you where i
was going
so yeah
[Music]
let me tell you bye
i want no i was going on irastoya to
bring a flag
for you to make it like more
tata tan
they don't have those flags
brazil
no
i went to greece
[Music]
it was my first time in greece ever as a
european
um traveling inside of europe has always
been very easy and at the moment at the
moment it is super easy to travel from
australia to
uh greece as long as you you know do a
little test or if you have a vaccination
that also makes it really easy but as
long as you do
a test and the result is negative then
it's like super easy
and in greece
um
yeah it's also like fine like you wear
masks here and there but uh
it's like pretty chill and yep so
i went to race but it's my first time up
until now
i visited many many countries in europe
like italy and
germany and croatia and
so on and so on but never went to greece
which is actually quite surprising to
myself as well because europeans
[Music]
like
if you grow up in europe or at least
like in germany or australia
going to greece with your family for a
cheap vacation at some point
it's just normal
like
i feel like everyone has done that
before
yeah spain as well yeah spain and
and italy
but uh actually italy is quite expensive
some for some reason but spain and uh
greece are like the cheap uh
vacation destinations in europe
cheap but you can still get something
really good for
your money i guess
[Music]
so i
i went to
spain before on my own but not to greece
this is the first time i was looking
forward to it i was really excited
because one thing i do know about greece
is
not only that the beaches are beautiful
but also that the people in greece
are
so
goddamn kind and sweet
honestly
i knew that from before because
i um had a lot of
greek colleagues before
at work
and they all came to australia for work
and
and and uh we're pretty new there so
it's not like they were born in
australia or whatever but
but um
i had a lot of great colleagues and they
were so nice and sweet they were the
best colleagues ever they were so sweet
so so so sweet i love them
[Music]
and the other thing that was really
easy about greece is that they all speak
english
at least in those places where
um
where there is a lot of tourists
but that's basically everywhere in
greece
i'm so excited for your birthday me tell
me too oh my god
been to super saiyan here uh
really nice people yes
right
yes
and like when i went to spain i had the
issue that
barely anyone spoke english
but in greece
everyone speaks english it's
fascinating
it was easy even without knowing any
greek but i always knew a few greek
words because of my great colleagues in
work before i i knew like for example um
kalimera is good morning
yasu is like hey what's up
hola is like how are you and at the same
time the answer that you are good if
harry stone is thank you
uh and so on so i already knew
a lot of words
[Music]
cause i'm talking so [\h__\h] much let me
take a
cough drop thingy ah
travel time to grace was like move the
plane
three hours
um
[Music]
oh yeah and we went to we went to uh so
grace has a lot of islands
and we originally originally wanted to
go to other islands but
um
there was no good uh flight connection
flight
at all
like really really long
connections like 10 hours
it was ridiculous
so
we had to give up on those other islands
so we actually went to how do i even
pronounce this in english
cre creta
[Music]
in german it's kreta
yeah that's why i went
yeah
it's quite a popular destination
[Music]
we wanted to go to santorini first as
well
because like
if you go to santorini normally
you know it's really famous for those
white blue houses on them
on a hill
that's what it's really famous for
um
and if normally
normally if we would go there
besides like not not in the time of a
pandemic
then it would be absolutely
overloaded with terrace and you would
not be able to take any of those you
know nice pictures of that beautiful
scenery which is the reason why you're
going there to begin with right
so our idea was
if you ever go to santorini
once in your life you have to go now
like now it's already too late probably
to be honest because there was more
tourists than expected in
krita as well
uh so i guess in santorini it would have
been the same but
still much less than usually
and i guess it would have been it would
have been great but we actually didn't
really find any hotels that we liked
surprisingly so we were like uh whatever
whatever we don't we're not going to
santorini we don't need santorini
so he went somewhere else
[Music]
yeah
eh
[Music]
you went to minos palace oh no i did not
so uh we did not do much sightseeing
because we didn't really want to do
sightseeing anyway like we wouldn't just
just be at the beach and relax and chill
so that's what we did most of the time
but we went to like
other beaches as well
and uh we traveled
uh because
has like a decent size that you can
travel through quite easily
um and even fairly cheap even with a
taxi
but we took a bus once
and also a little shippy
yeah
so it's easy to travel through
this island so we did we did a little
bit of that
uh
yeah and and yeah so
and where was i
originally i wanted to say something
before i told you guys that we went to
greek greece
i was the sand there
[Music]
it was coarse
and rough and irritating
and it [\h__\h] got everywhere
[\h__\h] the sand
[\h__\h] the sand i told you guys to kill
the sand did you kill the sound
[Music]
did you kill it yes there was an attempt
oh
that doesn't sound like you did the job
oh my homies ain't sent in me too
[\h__\h] hate sand
and the sand herded me hurt
me go again hurts me
yeah
[Music]
it hurt me
[\h__\h] sand
it was so hot too
all right so let me tell you some random
things
well where should i start some of these
things are so random they're not even
worth mentioning
i sliced up my feet with tiny ass stones
in the sand i did i was we were at one
beach at one point that was sand beach
but it had like
it was a bit more of a rough sand
and uh i was running when you know when
i was making a kfp uh picture
that kfb sign in the sand
it was normal sand and i was running
around
uh quickly picking up those sticks and
putting them in place
and it was so hot so that i had to run
you know i couldn't just walk normally i
was burning my feet off obviously i i'm
feeling so that doesn't matter blah blah
blah blah blah
um
[Music]
youtube we're back okay
so yeah i was making kfc science i was
struggling and i was running and at some
point uh because
the sand was not not as fine as on other
beaches although it was beautiful but it
was this this particular sand was not so
fine
so
i sliced up
my feet but like really
like it didn't bleed
it was just like a tiny tiny tiny slice
two slices
but
the thing is it was such a tiny slice
that that it would constantly fill up
with sand
and when if i would wash it out it'll
fill up it with sand again because if
you walk in the sand
obviously
you will always have
sand on your feet like if you wash it in
the ocean but then walk back
then you're already
you already have sand on your feet again
unless there's a shower or something but
the that wasn't like an island that uh
had no showers and no shops and whatever
like it was absolutely like how do you
call that
it was natural
okay no nothing there to wash my wash my
feet off
so yeah
that hurt
it's like a yeah like it's like a paper
cut uh through sand
yeah
uninhabited yes yes yes that's why what
i wanted to say
no i had flip-flops i had sandals you
know that the top
what was that the weird word oh
funks fungs
fungs
uh but obviously they
did the andrea gotta protect you from
sand
[Music]
um
yeah we call them we call them
flip-flops in german language
there are thongs called titties around
here is that true
you know since it's called farms already
i i don't i would believe you if you say
that they're called that somewhere else
it
well that was a lie
so that was a lie
i would i wouldn't doubt it though but
it's not true
oh it's called flip-flops in english too
okay
i see
okay so that was one random thing that
happened
ah
oh
actually
there was one thing you know how i
actually ended up not streaming during
my vacation because i
lost one day anyway and i had other
things prepared like the sound of it
which is almost at one million views
yeah yeah
stream
it's so close i didn't expect it to do
that well thank you but the video was
amazing wasn't it
[Music]
thank you yuna for working so hard on it
yeah
it's very close to 1 million
and i'm really happy about that thank
you guys for receiving it so well um
it was um
it was quite hard to sing but
actually uh
surprisingly
some people were like
saying that
my pitch must have been edited because
there's no way i can sing that pitch so
well and i mean it was difficult but
no it was not edited i mean there's a
mix going through it obviously but
i can sing in that
pitch i can
although that is really insanely
high do you want to hear it
i will prove it
[Music]
uh
jenna are you awake
i saw fukuki senpai singing the song in
the karaoke stream
today
i wonder if i can sing it too
or if i have to do that in an
archived one
i wonder if it's a
what her stream was
uh her stream was was archived wasn't it
[Music]
there you go yeah
oh it's really exhausting to sing though
[Music]
foreign
do i have
the
karaoke
[Applause]
[Music]
um
well i mean my throat is not
at its best right now but
yeah but will it really would it really
be fine
i'm actually worried
i feel like maybe not uh i feel like uh
gotta do uh like i i i would have to
choose a specific
a specific
uh
instrumental
that that we're allowed to use but
but let me do just the chorus in
in
oh
just the chorus
in in acapella sorry my my brain is uh
partially
shutting itself off
i know you don't hear it
[Music]
foreign
it's really hard to breathe
[Laughter]
[Music]
crazy
why am i singing the whole thing now
[Music]
yum yum
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
i can sing it better but you i think you
got the gist you got the gist that i can
hit the key okay
moto m
okay
no more no more doubting me
it's a really [\h__\h] fast song too
though so yeah that's something that i
prepared for the street for the vacation
so that uh you guys would uh be fine
without me for a little time but
i know you were lonely because i was
[Music]
we believed in you thank you we didn't
miss a lot thank you i miss you too we
missed you so much i missed you too
i missed you so much i missed you too
yeah i'm glad you went to the vacation
well me generally as well but yeah okay
okay so
okay i can i can tell you those small
things later i guess but i guess you
already want to hear
what the [\h__\h] happened to my neck
so
you know how i always crack my neck
because
um
okay do you want to hear a tangent first
so
i started i've always been wondering
because this is
a complicated topic okay okay listen
listen
i it's not like i have been doing the
cracking for my whole life
i started doing it at a certain point
but
i suddenly felt like doing it because i
had suddenly pain
and like i don't know tension tension i
guess
in that area
and but i was never really sure
what exactly caused it
but i do think
there might be one cause one reason
because
looking back on it now the timeline kind
of matches up and it kind of makes sense
um
so i've been cracking my neck
like like this for
because of the pain in my
between my neck and my shoulder left
shoulder
uh for a long time now it's been like
how long
four or five years
and
like it's been without a break
continuously okay so
actually
during that time
i was in
some sort of school
and
um in that school
there was a
pe class
uh physical education
and
there was one day where they called in
some something special
for us to have a special pe class
and that was boxing
they
um
did like a special
boxing class i guess
and we all had to participate
and you know i got no arms
you know i have my little arms i'm not
very strong
and there were like really big big
boxing people there
telling us how to box and they had these
things on their arms that we should hit
you know
and
and then we were like you know doing
that the whole time
and i was i was really weak and really
exhausted
but
i was instructed to keep on going and
hit stronger and so on so at some point
i
kind of injured myself
in the in that boxing
class
i i remember that
because it really hurts afterwards and
it hurt for a while
and i think
this is what caused the common year
of the following years of me cracking my
neck
all the [\h__\h] time because i still
feel
some
pain
and tension or whatever
i think in the same spot
so i think that might be
uh
connected
because before that i did not crack my
neck at all and i did not feel like
cracking my neck and i did not feel that
pain
yeah
um
after after that by the way i was just
like you know the the the the people
those coaches or whatever they did not
really take me seriously when i was like
[\h__\h] i really heard something there
they just will keep on going keep on
going
i don't really remember if i really did
keep on going but i think i kept on
going for like a little tiny bit and
then i was like nah i'm dead i can't i
can't i hurt myself
so
so that's um the reason like probably
maybe not for sure but probably the
reason why i keep on doing that and i
always thought that there's still
something
it's not normal it's not just me having
uh sore muscles or whatever
it's like for real something is [\h__\h]
broken there
and it never got fixed
i don't know i don't know how it does
not heal itself on its own for five
years but whatever apparently it's just
something that
was not able to heal
um
so
which day was it friday
no saturday
saturday morning
i wake up
in my vacation my last day i woke up at
9 30 in the morning because at 10 am i
would have
my second
of two massages that i booked for
this vacation in the hotel
and i was really looking forward to it
because the first one already was like
really really nice
and i was looking forward to it because
also
um
afterwards i would fly back home
and uh
i just wanted to know
get get uh
some more relaxation done because on the
on the day before
uh
i
we we walked a lot and my shoulders were
getting sore again
because
of uh
you know
doing something something so i wanted
that massage i really wanted that
massage i was looking forward to it and
i paid money for it
so i woke up
30 minutes before the massage
and i
i of course as always feel tense in my
body
as always
not that i was like sleeping in the
wrong position or whatever or slept on
my neck funny or whatever
no
the thing that i did afterwards was the
problem
i started you know doing my cracking
exercises
[Music]
and i
i i put my my hand my right hand
above my head
to to like stretch it over like this
and i tried to crack
but
it seems like something went wrong
because like i did that and immediately
instantly like it came out of nowhere
like it shut through me like that
and i could not move my eye
i could not move anyone i could not move
my neck
i was like i was like in a baby position
my roommate my ex-roommate was still
sleeping
and i was just like there
and i actually was really hard to
breathe i was trying to you know stay
alive because it was really really
painful i could not breathe well
and i was i thought i was dying
i thought i was dying
and i noticed i met i i [\h__\h] up
because this is not normal
i noticed
something went really wrong
[Music]
um
and i stayed in that position for a few
minutes because i could not move
and i was just like really trying hard
to breathe and [\h__\h] and my my room
ex-roommate she woke up and she was like
here are you okay and i'm like no no
and i could barely
stand up and walk
because i was just like
i was like how to say
[Music]
i i don't know i was really struggling
with staying alive
um
that was really bad
it was really painful
it was so painful
but i was like i was waking up 30
minutes early because i wanted to go to
breakfast and i was like i got to get
the breakfast because
while i'm at my massage at 10 a.m the
breakfast will close at 10 30 or
something so i have to get it now no
matter how much pain i am
i have to
so
i walked over to the restaurant
alone my
room
ex-roommate she stayed in the room a bit
longer
uh
because she didn't need to hurry up so i
walked over to the restaurant alone
and trying to trying to look look normal
you know it was really busy you know i
think
around 10 a.m the
breakfast
restaurant is really busy
so
i woke over there and and and the staff
was like super kind super happy
super energetic and they're like good
morning kiana what's up
how are you and i'm like
i tried to keep my [\h__\h] together because
i didn't want to make a drama out of it
and i tried to i wanted to eat breakfast
but i didn't i was in so much pain i
didn't feel like eating food to be
honest so i just took a few slices of
watermelon
i i sat down and i was
trying to eat it
but i was suffering and then
super nice waiter
came by and asked me if i want coffee or
something or orange juice and i said
orange juice please
and i looked at him and he probably
noticed that i was
dying
he was like are you okay
and i'm like
no
no no
and the moment i said no
i couldn't stop anymore i started to cry
in the in the breakfast restaurant of
a
like a boutique hotel tourist area you
know you know where everyone else was
like
living their bestest life
going on on vacation as a couple looking
super sexy and tan and everyone's just
you know at the beach at the pool being
sexy and you know
just just enjoying their time and i'm
there crying alone in the breakfast
lobby
suffering and i asked could could you
bring me um
could because my i thought maybe i
should ice it
i asked if if he could bring me ice
in a
in a in a bag
and he was like yesterday of course of
course
and immediately he ran away and he came
back and brought it to me and he was
really worried all the staff was so kind
of worried to me that was so sweet
um
i was really so sweet but i also had a
sunburn
oh no no never mind i don't know i'm a
phoenix i don't have something
so no it did not hurt at all to put that
ice on my neck it did not hurt
uh disregard that
no no
[Music]
anyway i was i was icing my shoulder but
i guess it was so honestly that really
might have been a reason but it was so
[\h__\h] cold like it was also painful i
could that keep it on my shoulder the
whole time on my shoulder slash neck
and i was trying to eat at the same time
but i was really suffering and at some
point
the
the the waiter comes by again sees me
suffering again still
and and he's like can we do something
for you are you okay okay should we look
like call you a doctor should we
you can take a taxi to them to the
doctor or
to the hospital or whatever and i'm like
i don't know what to do i have a massage
in five minutes i want
i really didn't know what to do i could
not move my neck and my head at all
and i was thinking you know the the
whole hospital thing yeah sounds good
but
we had a flight coming up and i don't
have a insurance overseas so i would
want to go to the hospital after coming
back i mean the flight was coming up
anyway so whatever
but
she did bring me some painkillers which
was super nice oh my god because i had
no pain guys
i took the i took the pain colors and
then i went uh
i finished my breakfast i didn't eat
much anyway
no i went to
i wanted to go back to my room or like
actually i wanted to go to the spa and
tell them because it was already 10 a.m
i wanted to tell them
i [\h__\h] up
i cannot do the massage because i can
literally
not enjoy it
while i'm suffering from insane pain
okay
and i thought they would understand and
you know they were really nice and all
and they were they continuously even
though i told them i'm checking out
and going on a flight in a in like two
hours
i continuously told them
but they continuously offered me to
do the massage on another day or like in
the evening or whatever
when i feel better i'm like no i can't
no i cannot
but i feel like they
were um
they were aware of me leaving but they
offered that anyway just because i did
not want to offer a refund
because i did ask them if they could
you know refund me because i i paid for
two massages and one of them i can
obviously
not go to right now and they saw me i
was standing in the lobby crying
and the hotel manager and the
receptionist and the spa lady they were
all in front of me and talking to me and
trying to help me you know they were
also telling me to go to go to the
hospital or whatever they can they can
call me a taxi blah blah blah
but they saw me suffering it was
obviously impossible for me to take the
massage
but they they said no
no we can't refund you can't take the
massage later though and i'm like yeah
but as i told you already
i don't have time to take it later
i am
going on a flight back home it's my last
day
yeah
so
that was that that was wasted
i was raising money unfortunately
yeah
no refund no refund unfortunately
uh no massage i i don't care about you
know i was more mad about not getting
the massage
than not getting a refund i did not care
much about the refund
i wanted the massage i'm looking forward
to it
oh because
i've already had sore muscles from the
day before and and you know it would
have been a really nice oil massage
really nice thing they could they call
it the crate crate massage yeah with
olive oil uh-huh
well well i was i was getting all
excited for it again what a nice finish
to my vacation you know
that
[Music]
i want the massage
i want the massage back
anyway
so
uh i still had like because i didn't
take the massage i still had time
i was laying in in
in our room's bed for another two hours
playing shadowers
and roommates chan was watching me play
shadow verse because she was like oh she
actually obviously is not a phoenix so
she had a really bad sunburn and she was
like she can't go outside
into the pool or the
beach anyway because she was burnt to
death
so she was just chilling with me waiting
for me
um while i was
absolutely
unable to
[Music]
move yeah
and
then we packed
then we went to the airport
then we flew home
and the whole time
i was still in a lot of pain it did not
improve
it was not improving so i was sure that
once i would arrive in australia i would
go to the hospital
even though i was scared of it
even though
i felt very very nervous about it
[Music]
yeah
we flew back home
uh i arrived and and roommate tom
actually originally wanted to go
straight back to her own home
but ended up ended up going
uh together to my home together with me
where my best friend was waiting for me
uh because she was taking care of my
cats and um
she actually also had food ready for me
so sweet so i was welcomed with some
food and um
yeah it was nice it was nice and then we
ate a little bit and i got ready for
going to the hospital
i was so nervous
so we looked up which hospitals were
gonna do
and then i
i took an uh i took an uber
and actually
rmt came together with me
and we first went to
an emergency
ambulance
place of the hospital
and we waited around there
until finally a doctor talked to me
and i explained what i did and how
stupid i am and he was like yeah no we
can't help you here you have to go to
the accident unfair on fire house i
don't know what's that exactly called in
english
uh
accident you know the people who break
their legs that's that's uh where they
go
um yeah because there's apparently a
difference between the emergency
place where our first went to and then
the accident place which is i guess also
a truck yeah yeah it was called trauma
center something like that in german as
well
that's what that's where they sent me
urgent care
ah that might have been the first place
i don't know i don't know whatever it
doesn't matter i was i was told to go
somewhere else
so yeah the trauma center
so rmt followed me
and i went there but there they actually
told me i can't go in
with her i have to go alone
so
that's when i said goodbye to r t i
couldn't because you know of uh the
thing
they wouldn't let visitors like people
in there unless their family
so i had to go alone
yeah
[Music]
and i was really scared and i waited
there up there alone but it actually i
didn't have uh it didn't take that long
so it started out like i registered and
then i uh
after a while i got called to the
doctors and there were like three
doctors in there and it looked like
scrubs i felt like i was in the middle
of an episode of scrubs
that got me excited um and then those
three doctors like one of them was
typing in the pc and the other one was
just sitting next to him and then the
other one was obviously like the
the the doctor cox of the this hospital
and he was like
talking really fast but like he asked me
well what did he do what was wrong and i
explained it
and then what he said was
all right you probably have a pinched
nerf
and you go to the
x-ray
and you'll get called
and i'm like okay i guess so then i left
the room
but i already was like
did he take me seriously i wasn't sure
i wasn't sure but okay
i was waiting for my x-ray
and uh
i went in there i did the x-ray they
were really nice really fast and i went
outside again and then i waited another
hour
and
meanwhile i was um just chilling on
twitter because i had nothing else to do
and then i went back into the doctor's
place again and he was like okay so
he was talking so fast i could barely
barely like register what he was saying
uh let me drink water
i could barely register what he was
saying but i think what he basically
said was
he he never mentioned the pinched nerf
again because i guess that was not what
it was
he said
so you have a sprained
heist vehicle
[Music]
whatever
the spine
neck spine
something blah blah
vertebrae
yeah
it's something like that
uh
and then he said something else what was
that
[Music]
he said
who's talking so fast
he didn't even explain it
[Music]
i asked for clarification but he was
talking so fast
yeah he said something about the muscle
being torn he said
[Music]
no
i did get a piece of paper with the
latin
latin word for that spring
blah blah
[Music]
so i think that translates to
spring and torn
but he also told me that okay so he said
it will take two to three weeks to heal
the only thing uh
he
prescribed me was uh two different
painkillers with
uh
which i have to take seven off per day
or like i can i don't i guess i don't
have to if i feel better but yeah
you know is drawing me oh my god for my
birthday huh
and
yeah uh wait wait wait don't don't don't
get me out of my topic okay
i'm i'm so easy to like get uh
sidetracked
uh
oh yeah you guys shouldn't tell me about
that anyway although i mean it's kind of
to be expected inna always draws us for
birthdays
oh yeah okay the seventh day thank you
and and then he didn't say anything else
he just gave me the piece of paper he
was like bye-bye two to four weeks good
luck and i was like um am i supposed to
like
do something like maybe
maybe
rest
and he was like yeah yeah
just rest and uh
like he didn't take any time for me he
was just trying to get rid of me
and and he was like he also said uh
he said i should either either cool it
or put something hot on it like warm it
either one is fine
which doesn't clear up the mystery that
i always have in these situations which
one is better
cooling it or warming it i always ask
myself that and now that i'm finally in
front of the doctor he's like both are
fine
he's like whatever feels better
um so i i actually separately bought
some like heating thingies
uh to like put on my neck and shoulder
um yeah
uh oh my god my my fruit uh
felt dry
yeah i mean in the house but in a
hospital i don't really expect them to
take a lot of time for me so
it seems normal to me and i gotta be
real i mean it's free i did not pay any
money
for any of that except for the
medication later on in the in the
pharmacy
uh
but yeah i understand that in the
hospital they don't take much time for
you
and
that's all good
um but he said that
um
i'm not
he might have meant that if after two to
three weeks you still don't feel better
you should go to the oil fill of awful
what's it called again
uh to the orville guy but he might have
also meant
anyway wait two to three weeks and go to
go there anyway
orthopedic yes
uh because
now again because he was talking so fast
and he was talking so giving me some
little information i am not 100 sure
about this thing
but
the moment i came in and he was looking
at the x-rays
he said something like
i am in a
shoots
position
or something like that i think he said
that about my spine
now
yeah i think he said something like that
like
i don't know what that means
but
i don't i don't i don't know if he met
like right now or like in general maybe
maybe my spine has been in that position
for five years and that's why i i feel
so uncomfortable
i don't know
but yeah because i don't understand
anything what he told me uh
i am going yeah like a defense
whatever i don't know
i will go to that doctor obviously i
will go to a proper doctor
who actually takes time for me ah you
not message me
[Laughter]
[Music]
i see okay yeah yeah she was not really
drawing the thing that i thought she was
drawing
[Music]
so yeah okay oh yeah yeah i need to tell
you how i'm feeling now
so
uh
yesterday i already felt
much better than the day before
like
um
uh before like on the first day
i was not able to move my head at all i
could not move it to the front or to the
back or to the right or to the left and
everything was impossible
and then
uh yesterday it already was um
pretty
pretty improved like
uh if i want to do that movement that i
did before like i can go i can go this
far
but
if i want to you know stretch it even
further
then that's that's impossible i really
i really noticed that there is a huge
pain there don't you dare shut up
and then to the right side i feel
yeah i feel so it's hard to explain but
i feel some pain there obviously too and
yeah uh to go to the front it's okay
to the back i can't really
i don't want to um
but it's much better than before
much better than yesterday it's healing
fast maybe like at least the the other
movements but the one that [\h__\h] up
everything that one is still
um very very very painful
um
and lying in the bed uh it's also quite
painful
and
now i did not get a neck brace
unfortunately
but i can sit here and stream and feel
normal
it's okay
i feel i feel all right right now
[Music]
um
are you on painkillers right now yes but
i'm not on seven painkillers i feel like
it's not exactly necessary i'm not the
type of person who
like even in general when i have like a
fever when i have a cold or whatever or
if i have some headache
i
always try to
go through it without medication
and um
so right now i'm trying trying to not
take as many
as i was prescribed because i mean he
also said like if you don't have to take
them
if you feel like you don't need them
um but yeah i feel like also my
my tolerance of pain
is the
especially in the shoulder and neck area
is much much higher than others
because i was
um tolerating pain for years now without
taking any medication against it
you know what i mean
so
a certain amount of pain is normal to me
i'm just used to it
and
so yeah i'm not taking that many but i
do
like for example during the tournament
around the end
um even though i was taking painkillers
i had like headache uh in the last match
like with cali
in those last three matches
i had quite some headache and um
and my neck after i mean after seven
hours i was like
not feeling comfortable
anymore
yeah which is also why um
this week i am not playing yakuza
um
you know i i would probably be able to
survive it and it probably wouldn't be
that much of a big deal but i don't
wanna
i don't i don't wanna risk it i don't
wanna force myself to
go through a long long rpg stream it's
just a bit unfortunate because
we are so close to the end and i wanted
to finish it right away after my
vacation so that we can move on to
something new
but we will do it next week
by next week i think i'll be fine
uh
i'll because like i feel so much
improvement
already
i guess i guess this this thing like the
the the center of the pain
will be painful for a few weeks i guess
but like all the other movements are
okay-ish
so i have confidence in it recovering
fairly soon
[Music]
um
yeah that was the next story
[Music]
and yeah i'll i'll i'll go i'll go to
the orthopedic
of course
once
once uh
like i don't think it makes sense to go
right now
i will go like after two or three weeks
as a follow-up mm-hmm
don't worry okay
uh
also why the [\h__\h] is it so hot in my
room now
oh
i have air conditioning but it's not
really working
it's so hot so exhausted it makes me
feel weak
hot sleep
it's not not comfortable
[Music]
but i wanted to talk more so
i just remembered something because i
was looking at my memo
you know when i was laying in the hotel
room playing shadowers and not being
able to go to the massage
my roommate was like
packing things
and
like from like out of we had like a
terrace
with a pool
that was really nice that was cool and
and she left over the night she left a
bottle of water outside
and then by by
10 am or like 10 30
she she you know because she was
cleaning up she was she took it from
outside she took it inside she was like
oh [\h__\h] out of this this bottle is
really [\h__\h] hot
and i was like oh wait that's perfect
give it to me because i needed something
to heat up my my neck at that point i
was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] cooling it i want to
heat it now so i took the neck and you
know i was like really not able to move
much and and
lying on the pillows was really
uncomfortable for me so i put the bottle
the hot ass but it was really [\h__\h]
hot
i put it like under my neck
and it was the perfect
um
support for my neck and at the same time
it was like
perfectly the perfect um
hotness to heat up my
neck
so it had like a double effect big brain
yeah
[Music]
so i was chilling with that hot bottle
for
one hour playing shadowers in the bed
galaxy brain
right
uh i need i need more i need some water
brb will you wait for me
[Music]
will you wait me to put anything
i wanna put some ice cubes into it too
okay
[Music]
eh
a ice cubes out of the tree
yeah i don't have a i don't have an ice
cube this disposal
i have to
you know fill up those plastic trees
all right so
thank you guys for the well wishes
and for the for the sweet sweet messages
and not only here on youtube but also on
twitter you guys have been so sweet
thank you thank you
thank you
but i'm doing okay i can definitely
stream
there's no problem and i'm doing short
stream this week short streams this week
anyway
i know
um
oh yeah this weekend
uh
i'll be with the other girls
on anime expo
today saturday sunday it's a online
convention
we'll be
there for i think about one hour per day
and you can buy tickets online i think i
think they're like five dollars
[Music]
have my ticket oh
well prepared
yes yes
probably something like that yes
um
i don't know much about what we're gonna
do and like how it's gonna work but
yeah i suppose it's just gonna get
streamed if you have a ticket you'll be
able to see it
i think so
yeah
i hope you guys will be there to support
us
because we'll all be there
yeah
no problem if you can't afford it if you
can't watch it that's okay too
and though
i'll be busy on that weekend but i'm
still squeezing in a mario kart stream
so even if you can't if you're not
watching the anime the axl string
you can still
see me on youtube
yes
a little bit of mario kart
[Music]
and then next week oh my god it will be
my birthday
and it's so soon it's so soon oh my god
nice
i have
quite a few exciting things for you
so
i'm i'm hyped up and i
i will by the way i will be doing a
call in
where
anyone can call in not only whole live
english members they may call whoever
wants to call me is allowed to call me
the totsumati
mas
and that one will be at a time which is
uh
before
midnight japanese standard time
so they should be able to
call in yeah
and then i'll be doing like karaoke as
well
and then
there will be something else and then
also there will be
a full member hello english
collaboration on my channel because i
wanted to you know have something like
because if it's my birthday obviously i
want to have something like a birthday
party right
so i asked the girls if they would join
me on a little
collaboration together i don't know what
we're gonna play at maybe jackbox games
or something like that because that was
that we can play that with five people
and that seems fitting
but i'm not sure yet to be honest
but yeah so we have a few things planned
for my birthday
and the merchandise i'm so excited to
show it to you
[Music]
guys
um
[Music]
look forward to it
i'm excited i'm so excited i will i hope
this week will be over fast
hopefully and oh yeah so
i also wanted to kind of talk about the
other things that will happen
like the streams like besides shadow
versus we talked about shadows in the
beginning but i also wanted to talk
about
like the [\h__\h] post review of cocoa
senpai
and
the
second
summer festival
and
no i think that's it
[Music]
yeah
did you like it did you enjoy it the the
reddit [\h__\h] postman review i think it
was great i think
i mean i was very i was quite nervous
but i think we got along well and it was
fun and there were lots of funny memes
uh sometimes i did not know what to say
because uh it was quite sensitive
some moments were pretty nearby
well was we're staying up till 5am thank
you
yeah for me it was like really late the
starting time and the ending time was
also [\h__\h] late so i totally ruined my
sleep schedule through that oh yeah
because on my vacation on my vacation
every day
i woke up before 10 am
it's incredible
it's incredible and i did not take any
naps during the day
not even on the beach
gasps incredible
i would usually sleep by
at the latest 1am i think
during my vacation
i was living a healthy lifestyle
yeah although i have to say the sun
was quite exhausting i think that was a
big factor
the sun was
um making me feel very tired i think
yeah
unusual yeah sleeping at night what the
hell
what and i was i was glad i thought you
know this will be nice if i can continue
it but it will be immediately ruined
with the
shitpost meme review oh man well can't
help it
[Music]
back to the usual sleep schedule it's
really bad right now but the tournament
also made it worse again
ah
but i'll try to at least bring it back
to somewhat normal time because now i'm
like
sleeping at 6 00 am 7 am
i want to get it back to sleeping at 3
or 4 am at least
that would be nice
lost class can't fix it too yeah
[Music]
ah but like in the vacation like the
reason why i woke up so early was
because most of the days i had to
one of the days we went on that tour
where we got into a bus and went on a
trip so for that we had to get up like
at 7 00 am
and then another day
i had to also get up at 8 a.m or
something like that because i actually
oh yeah that was something i wanted to
mention before and i got on the tangent
i i had to record like something for
something
and in the middle of my vacation
so
even though i decided to not stream
anymore after all
during the vacation i had to bring my
laptop and my microphone and everything
anyway
but i brought my old laptop not the not
the new one because that one the old one
is a little bit
um
oh this is not so heavy
and i was too lazy to pick up uh to set
up the
the new laptop
so i just brought the
the small
lightweight lightweight
laptop with me
and i had to record something early in
the morning
yeah and then i was just staying awake
um
so most of the days it's because i had
something to do that's why i had to get
up so early and also because obviously
you wanna get that free breakfast right
why the [\h__\h] do they close breakfast at
10 30
on a vacation
who wants to get up at 7 00 am what the
hell
could you at least have the breakfast up
until 11 30 please
11 30 at least come on
some hotels do it though like at the
week on the weekends they often have
breakfast until 11 30 or 11 at least
but normally they always ended at 10 30.
so you really gotta get up early
frustrating love those places that have
all day breakfast
those are the best
yeah
all day breakfast no matter what time of
the day
if we about to offer the late birth no
can't be about to offer all day
breakfast
yeah
all day breakfast doesn't that sound
nice
[Music]
how was the food oh
so breakfast was actually the best hotel
breakfast i've ever had
um
like in most hotels
the for example the scrambled eggs are
[\h__\h]
because they make it with some kind of
mixture that's like not really egg
anymore anyway
and
it's just like
i
i i've seen it i've seen how that i mean
i've made it before myself so i know how
it works they have these these big big
boxes of that mixture and they put it
all in the oven
and
then they're like voila these are
scrambled eggs without even opening a
single egg
and it really doesn't taste that well it
does not taste like actual fresh
scrambled scrambled eggs yeah
so but here in in that in that
hotel though eggs were like the
scrambled eggs were actually scrambled
eggs and it was actually fresh and it
was really good
yeah
and then the besides the breakfast like
we
went to some restaurants in the evening
and they were really really good yeah
uh i mean one time i
uh you know how i'm not really good with
seafood i'm really picky but i don't
like to eat like
um grilled fish like if it's like a
normal fish
oh
and
so
my roommate wanted to eat seafood which
makes sense when you're in greece
every [\h__\h] restaurant has a [\h__\h] ton
of seafood
so we went to
one of those seafood restaurants and
i was like okay i'm gonna go get a
grilled fish but i wasn't i was not sure
which one to get
and some of them are really expensive
and and the top one it said
small fish
a zero and i was like oh that's cheap
and
a small fish one small fish that means i
could probably still eat a dessert
but i was wondering what fish is it if
it just says small fish
what burrito fish is it
but it didn't say so i guess it was
probably no special fish just some
random fish
and i kind of guess that that can't
possibly be that good but i was like
okay whatever so i i i ordered that and
i expected
a decent sized small fish
but
[Music]
what a raft was
about 50
tiny fishes on one plate
like a lot of a mountain of tiny fishes
that were so [\h__\h] tiny
and they all had their head attached to
them
and they were like oh
like fried
and i was like ew
i don't wanna eat that i know i know i'm
really picky i know it's stupid but i
want a normal fish and not tiny ass
fishes and
my my roommate was like oh that was our
yummy and she immediately took one of my
plates and she just ate the whole thing
i was like
did you just eat the head as well she's
like yeah yeah you can eat those like
with those small fishes you usually eat
the whole thing like like like a like a
fried potato and i'm like
i can't no you know disgusting
but you're really supposed to do that
yeah so i was like
[\h__\h] like i ordered the wrong thing
apparently
but i have no choice i have to eat this
so i tried it and to be honest it was
not like
disgusting it was edible
but i think
the whole time
i was already set to feel disgusted by
it
like my mind was already ratting it off
as disgusting
so i i tried my best to eat as much as i
could
but
like the heads
creeped me out
and they were like like inside they were
also like like partially really black
uh so dark it it creeped me out as well
relatable really thank god
thank god thank you
but it's so stupid because like it did
not really taste different
from an actual fish
i mean it tasted boring to be honest
uh
it was underwhelming i think a normal
fish fillet
grills would have been so much better
uh
those fishes were
honestly really like nah that barely
barely seasoned and stuff
yeah just a lot of tiny fishies
i i bought
i did try to eat as many as possible
but at some point i could not eat them
anymore and because they serve such huge
portions unbelievable they serve huge
portions
i could not eat anymore but it still
looked like i left over so much
and then i i was lucky
i was really [\h__\h] lucky because guess
what happened next
while i was
contemplating what to do how to make
this look like i ate more than i
actually did
no no cat no no
the electricity
of the restaurant
died we were outside but they had lights
everywhere but it died and it was pitch
black super dark
outside they could see nothing
and they weren't they didn't even put
like any candles on our tables evo
for the longest time there was no light
and the staff were literally just
waiting
for about 40 minutes or even one hour
for the electricity to come back
so i was like [\h__\h] yes
they don't see how much i did not eat
no no i did not toss it anyway no no no
no no no no no
i just i just like
left it there
and i don't think they really saw
that i left so much on my plate
i was really lucky
they had no electricity for a while
so they could not see
saved by the darkness yes indeed
[Music]
we went to a different restaurant and
that one was much better they had really
good food there
my my roommate extra mate as always she
ordered some really fancy stuff like
like some tatar
uh with some fish
i don't know i don't even remember but
she really likes seafood she ordered
some fancy things that i can't eat
and i i ate some
some salmon
uh
pasta
because i mean at least that's some kind
of fish right
[Music]
it was good
and then the
the dessert was really good too mmm that
dessert yummy
huh
yeah we ate we ate
a bunch of
food i feel like if we would have
looked a bit further we would we could
have found even better places
to eat at
but
it was it was really good nonetheless
best part of the vacation
[Music]
oh
it was all pretty much on the same level
to be honest
the massage yeah
that was like on the second day
that was really good
on that day i felt really relaxed
i can tell you the worst part
just kidding it's not the worst part
but
my sweet sweet ex-roommate
wanted to do some kind of water sports
with me
and i never did anything like that
before
and i wanted to do it to be honest but a
lot of it looked
dangerous and scary
so
we went for
the most basic water sport i guess that
is usually offered
in these places
which was
jet ski
you know the thing that goes like
like like a like a motorbike in the
water
uh-huh
because i was looking at it when other
people did it and i was just chilling on
the beach and i was like that looks like
so much fun that looks fairly easy
and
yeah
so it was like 20 minutes for 55 euro
which is like
50 bucks 60 bucks which i think is
pretty expensive
but you could write it together
uh so instead of taking two because i
never wrote it before but she did before
we just went on one together and i would
like squeeze onto her i would cling onto
her
no no not divine i mean i guess yeah
dividing by two because uh
we were
like
dividing it on our own
but i think that's hella expensive
though
yeah
so um
the one thing though on that day
the
the um
ocean was not as cold as the day before
the waves where the waves and the wind
were actually
a little bit strong
it was still totally fine
but
like if you go swimming it was still
totally fine but for jet skiing
it made it a little bit more difficult
sorry my my my throat is getting really
dry
so i told rmt that she would please go
easy on me
not go too fast please because i'm
really scared okay i am
a chicken when it comes to these rings
well in general i'm a phoenix okay shut
up
and she you know i have to say she was
quite nice she could have bullied me and
and
and did the exact opposite of what i
told her i mean she did try to speed up
every now and then
she was genuinely very fast but she
could have done it way worse she could
have she could have
she could have gone so fast that she
would eat me away into the ocean and i
would have been eaten by a shark called
gooda
but thankfully that didn't happen it was
really hard to stay on the jet ski
though
because
i kept on like bouncing up and down and
my my butt would lift itself up from the
jet ski i could barely hold on to rmt
could barely keep my butt on jet ski and
it was uh really slippery too because of
all the water
shooting around us
uh yeah
it was so scary i was constantly like
she was just driving you know she was
just vibing and chilling and i was
constantly screaming into her ear like
[Music]
i'm dying
yeah
that was me for 20 minutes
that's also me in a roller coaster
same thing
[Laughter]
yeah
so i would like to say that that was fun
but
it was fun and uh
at the same time terrifying
it was
it was it was terrifying and fun
yeah
but finally at least i i did some kind
of weather sports that was a nice
experience
um
yeah
i clinged onto
rmt
the whole time
she must have felt so annoyed by me
because i was screaming the whole time
thank you for
you know
doing this vacation with me
and then you know i felt really bad
on the last day as well because of the
whole neck thingy because i felt like i
was you know dragging the mood down by
having this happen to me
um
but she was really sweet
and and
and kind as well so it did not seem like
she had any problem with it or so and
that made me happy
what
what about us you've known rnt for a
minute and hold hair but not us what are
you talking about i know aren't you
longer than i know you guys and i hold
you guys too don't i
you know when i catch those chickens and
give them
what are you smoochies about
getting delusional
i think i still have like some stories
some small ones here and there
um
but i think
for now i'll leave it at that
and keep the rest for long rpgs
[Music]
and so anyway i am back
and tomorrow we will play
plug and play
which is a funny looking game
which seems to be fairly short
i remember good i played it in the very
beginning
back in today
i did not i did not look at the stream i
only saw like a clip of it i think
but it should be fun and it's a short
thingy and i was looking for short
things to do this week so that's one of
them oh
perfect game for bottom left potential i
don't know why you say that
pretty sure yeah about fun well then i
hope you will come
yeah i did have fun at the solo festival
i did i was just a bit frustrated that i
had to do it with
er
not moving chiara
but it was fun and a lot of interactions
with kelly and nancy
and so on so i was very happy
especially kelly she was so
she was so dead did it she was so
yeah
i don't know what was going on like you
know when the
there was this tunnel of love right and
i was like hey there's a title of love
and kelly's like let's go in there
together and i was like think i was not
trying to
i didn't want to change her mind you
know but to myself i was thinking
did she even hear what the name of that
tunnel is are you sure you want to go in
there with me are you sure callie is
that you
yeah i was so confused
i was so confused and elated she gave me
flowers oh and she was watching though
just watching the fireworks with me
[Music]
foreign
yeah
i was i was very very happy
[Music]
because that did not even come from my
side
at the moment when i was like looking
for a flower and like trying to figure
out again how to throw a flower at her
that's the moment when she throw her
through her flower at me and i was like
callie
i was still trying to figure it out
while we had the same part
oh man
a dead egg yeah i mean i i was panicking
i didn't have anything else in there
i gave her eggs
[Music]
which um
was supposed to have no particular
meaning but i know it's kind of funny
because it does end up having some
meaning
here have my eggs
full of love
please enjoy
can i offer you an egg in his trying
times
[Music]
ah funny
notice how she got close in the group
follow up
i mean
come on
no i think also um we did really great
uh at that shooting range i was so
surprised
how the hell did we get number one
i mean i i don't even know how i was
even able to
uh
hit the
the thing on the first try
i even got a bullseye but i didn't even
think i would hit the
the area that you were supposed to hit
in the first place i thought i would hit
the outside of it
because i did not really have
grasses i don't use the bowl in my
minecraft at all
barely
you guys
know
yeah i was so surprised
but happy
happy that i did it i'm so happy
like i feel like i
i
contributed to
the em team winning
and that that made me feel actually
useful
you know that reminds me of
back in school time in pe class i was
always the one getting chosen last for
the team
uh for like dodge dodgeball and stuff
like that
because i can't shoot
at all and i'm like bad at these kind of
things but then here in the summer
festival i i actually helped with it i
was good and people were like whoa kiana
cool amazing kakui and i was like
thank you
i did it
[Music]
but once i didn't suck
yeah
i was legit very excited about that more
excited than i should be mimi
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
what a nice combination of people i mean
this just once again
shows that
birds of a feather flock together
am i right or am i right
i am indeed right yes
kelly
kelly was a delinquent what does that
mean again oh yeah didn't she yeah
didn't she say she bullied people
like loki
like she was the kind of people who
would like tease people
didn't you say something like that
oh my god
hi key
she beat up she beat the bullies
when she was bullied too oh well
so in any case i guess she was just
very
[Music]
aggressive
like very active
[Music]
ruff ruffian ah
she fought back that's nice
thank you for the red super chat oh
thank you
you're back to rise back to glow back to
fly back to soar back to warlock truth
be told you feel on fire with your
passion flow is that some kind of
song lyrics
it sounds very
[Music]
interesting
thank you
[Music]
thank you soon i feel like i'm probably
not gonna read super chat today and i'm
probably quite behind on them
maybe who knows
i mean
maybe not even that much actually
because uh
i did the super chat reading on last
monday i mean i don't think i finished
but i was close to
right only yesterday and today
oh
oh maybe tomorrow though like i don't
know how how long is the plug and play i
wonder maybe one hour so we can read
some super chats after that
yes yes yes yes
okay i should not be that far behind
okay good good good good
i hope so
um
i'm feeling weirdly exhausted and a bit
hard to breathe at the moment so i hope
you guys can forgive me
um
[Music]
some sometime now
but i had a lot of fun catching up with
you guys we'll catch up in the following
days too
if that's okay with you
um
i also want to read more comments of you
guys today i was talking so much
continuously
but i want to talk more with you guys
uh i think actually maybe even on
wednesday because we're playing
fantastic fantasy style online which is
by the way a sponsored stream thank you
very much
and we might have some time to talk on
that day too and obviously during super
chat readings
hmm
thank you
thank you guys for the superchargers
i missed you guys all of you
it was it felt kind of weird to not
stream for such a long time
it felt weird but it also was nice
honestly i i enjoyed um
you know not having to stream i was
still alive on twitter and felt
like
the need to check up on my replies and
all that all the time i could not
turn my brain off
completely for like 25 4 hours a day but
that's okay i mean i needed that for my
own peace of mind and it was always nice
to check up on
what you guys were doing like
i i just get happiness out of
reading your guys's replies so i think
it's okay
yes
uh
but
yeah i mean i have to be honest so
the vacation did not go
how
it should have gone it even started
horrible by me missing one day
and it ended horribly
um
so
unfortunately it did leave quite the
sour taste
and
i mean i came back injured injured so
i guess i
am less
less relaxed now than i was before in
some way
which is really unfortunate
and i'm
i'm a bit sad about that now
um if it would have only been the first
day missing thing that would have been
fine but
you know the end was bad too
uh
so
i don't know so it's very unfortunate
that it goes that it went like this i
need another vacation sometime in
in in who knows october or
september
[Music]
yeah
yeah i want to remember the good
thoughts and ignore the bad parts i want
to do that but like the whole neck thing
is just like so
so present now present so pretty pretty
it's just there and like overshadows
everything else
and i'm so stupid like it's so stupid i
don't even understand how i can sprain
my neck just by doing this like normally
you do that while doing sports or while
i don't know having an actual accident
but here i go i do this and i'm [\h__\h]
broken
how do you do that
how do you even do that
i mean i was always broken before that
already
it's so stupid i feel so stupid
eh
too much balance
it's okay i would if i i wouldn't go
that far that it would hurt
don't worry
also like
it looks like i move that much but i
don't actually move that much let me
just tell you that
it's exaggerated the image that you see
is
is a quite a bit exaggerated
yeah
yes
bless cappy papa yes thank you cappy
papa for giving me energy
tv magic exactly
i am
i am bouncy but
probably not as bouncy as you think i am
[Music]
thank god because i couldn't and that
would be exhausting for eight hour
yakuza streams
anyway that that's low-key like breaking
the fourth wall or something like that
so
never mind
also by the way we have not mentioned it
but
can i just say
hello
to this cute chocolate kitty cat
animation down here
[Music]
the other one
is
smoothie and this one is
supposed to be junkies
and chocolate is so chunky that you can
put a glass
of whatever that is
a cocktail on here
and she does not care she is so sweet
[Music]
she's so cute she's so fluffy
i love the face it's like
like look at her face she's like having
the time of her life best time ever
so fluffy
cute
i love her oh
i will pet her forever i also like how
she's resting on like pillows
hmm
very cute
oh my god i can't
so fluffy and i like how
the tail
tail kind of kind of have you paid
attention to the tail it kind of like
turns into feathers oh
at the end
so cool and the ears too
feathers like mine
[Music]
it looks like feathers but it also looks
like flames
that's so
cool firefox for the cat
yeah the detail
so cute
in reality they don't really like being
on my lap or so but okay well now she's
on the table
but um
here
in on my stream
i can put her wherever i want
and she can't even be on my head
there we go
don't know position anymore
so
cute i'm so happy thank you i i feel a
bit bad because i actually
once i started talking about wanting
something like this a bunch of people
got to work and made it and and i have
not even i have not even showed all of
them yet
but it's not only jolly that made it
yeah although i think this this one from
jolly is actually uh commissioned right
so
uh i'm not mixing up things right
yes yes this one is commissioned by this
logaria
which is which is super super sweet
thank you so much for that
yeah a bunch of people made stuff like
this for me
ah i was so happy because it's so cool
to have like
being able to pet my kitty cats
um
on stream
and i'm so glad we gave them some kind
of you know
um
design so you guys
know what they look like
yeah i will i will try to always have
them here when i can
it's just so cute
i know
[Music]
foreign yes yes yes yes
i think i should probably
uh
slowly end it soon
um but i want to remind you guys
that
goodbye declaration
is almost at 1 million views by the way
sorry
i was
i thought it was quite funny that you
guys a bunch of you guys apparently got
bamboozled by the title
and we're like
it was actually a goodbye declaration
like a graduation
[Music]
so funny
so funny no i would not announce it like
that would i would i i don't know
but yeah
um please skip
check it out everyone who has seen it
has only had good things to say about it
uh
and i think it's actually like
i'm not the only one who
um likes the song more the more the more
often you listen to it
other people reported the same thing it
it is pretty addictive
[Music]
i would i would want you know a simple
video where it's just one piece of art
on the screen the whole time and then
just lyrics in the background and in the
foreground and all that you know the
other
um goodbye declaration uh
videos are basically that
and they seem to copy one another
so
i would i would have been fine with that
i just wanted something simple to throw
out there on my vacation
but she
i was certainly saying that she has too
much time on her hands but
as far as i know i think she is somewhat
busy but
yeah she did
i guess just
she told me she didn't want my music
video to be like everyone else's so she
put way more work into it than i asked
for
yeah
it is it's really good i love it so much
i i'm so proud of it
yeah
and a lot of people a lot of japanese
viewers have also been
saying that because they saw the other
good like goodbye declaration
covers of other girls
and they were like wow her music video
really stands out
i love her sound cover and it'll make me
so happy
yeah
okay
um so you guys know where it is it's on
my channel so after the stream ends go
there
get it up to 1 million i'm actually real
surprised it when it's already at 900k
uh almost almost 1 million i
i did not think it would do that well
because heart challenger was like going
for a really rough patch but i guess
that was really just because of the
shadow bamboozling
and nothing else
which is not fair but it is what it is
yeah so i was really scared of uploading
more music but
um goodbye declaration has been doing so
well
thank you
[Music]
so
we'll get it up to one million when
tomorrow hopefully let's go
one tip if you want a little bit to help
me you should put you should make a
playlist
and then put in another short clip in
between
and then loop that because you have to
have something in between you can't loop
the same song over and over again
youtube doesn't count that
but i also have a playlist on my channel
a public one the music playlist with all
of my original songs and all my covers
so you can also just loop that and
listen to takanashikiyada
how about that
yeah i think that's the best way to do
it
i know yeah there's also the heck
playlist and i'm glad you guys know it
and i wonder if there's still people out
there using it
um but
i think the music playlist is also
totally fine go ahead and use it and
listen to my music it'll make me very
happy
yeah i also listen to
my original songs on spotify and apple
music amazon music etc
uh in case you forgot about their
existence on there so you can
listen to it anytime you don't have to
listen to it on youtube
no i don't
like
i i really just want you guys to listen
to my music like
just because i want you guys to listen
to my music
not because of the views i mean the
views are phenomenal
but i legit want you guys
to want to listen to my music
i want you guys to enjoy my music and
like my music
so that i can also make more music
you understand
[Music]
um
youtube community board if you have not
seen it yet it's already on twitter
uh
i will upload it to the youtube
community board after the stream ends
all right
uh
so let's let's have a fun week
all right all right all right
[Music]
yeah
let's have a fun week
and
let's have it get over with
let's get over with it quickly because
uh i can't wait for next week
i can't wait
this week is cool and all but i can't
wait oh by the way
whole
talk coming back next week
yes guest has also been decided
yes yes
[Music]
um
yes
no i will not tell you yet
anything's nice to ally but i mean
there's not many people left from the
zeroth and first generation so
guess what it's one of uh the people who
are left from the zeroth and first
generation
oh
[Music]
yeah because i
got a lot of uh
the rest members of those generations
sorry my voice really hurt so i'll leave
you guys here okay
i also need to go to an idol meeting
really really urgently
so
thank you for welcoming me back
i'm i'm really glad to be back here
with you and with my kitty cats
[Music]
so
i'll see you tomorrow around the same
time
already
[Music]
and in german we say
alfredo
thank you for being here taking your
time to chill with me and listen to me
thank you
i love you wow i miss you thank you
bye bye
bye bye same goodbye declaration
see yah
[Music]
the