[Music]
do
[Applause]
ah
[Laughter]
oopsie
[Applause]
that was grass whoops
[Music]
is the fgm too loud
huh i'm gonna turn it down a little bit
oh sure
nice but yo
everyone good evening good morning
um i'm here today in full armor because
i felt it was kind of fitting
for this particular stream uh
wouldn't you agree with me
wow this stream today is sponsored
by sega thank you so much for sponsoring
this stream
uh i'm very excited to try out this game
because
it is quite up my ella
alley i would say my ally ally
ally right up my alley
um this is fantasy star online two
new genesis yo
a very recently released
game actually june 21st says really
recent
maybe you guys already saw it on enoch's
channel because
inna also did a little stream on it
i've also seen some other whole life
girls uh
playing it on their own and
and i only saw like little snippets of
it but
mostly i am going into it uh completely
blind yes and
obviously it's free to play had to pay
nothing just downloaded epic games
uh the application or like whatever
and then download the game it's really
easy yeah oh yeah football i saw fubuki
said by playing it and her character
looked like really really cute
it really impressed me um yeah you can
make some really adorable
chicks in this game how i was i was
you you caught my interest for wookie
senpai
[Music]
okay yeah so
this game is uh when i'm playing it on
pc
most likely i'm going to play with
keyboard because i just prefer it that
way but
you can play it on xbox one it's
a cross play is possible which means
that
if i understand it correctly you can
first of all play with other people that
are playing the game on the xbox number
one
and i think it also means that you can
play the same account
like if you created it on pc you can
also still play it on your xbox one if
you have that as well
right yeah pretty sure yeah also steam
[Music]
and that that that
that uh what's it called sorry wait what
was it called
you can get it on steam and what's that
and i mean this epic game store but also
wait
with a windows shop like what do you
call that jump
it's not what's it called again
i am microphone my micro first micro
microphone microsoft
sorry about that uh that was um
yeah an oopsie uh never mind
so there's a lot of ways to get it but i
just got it on epic games
and you can do that too very easily
sorry when i tap out
that's when the bgm cuts off don't mind
that please
yeah so again free to play
uh and yeah uh
i will start out with making a character
i tested out the game already so i
already made the character but we're
making a proper one together
but look into it a little bit more
closely
and there is four race choices there's a
human which is a
wait do you see everything yeah yeah uh
a human by the way this is the bt i'm
okay
is it too quiet now or or normal is it
bgmu
[Music]
yes yes stop telling me about symbol art
i am aware
regime is fine okie dokie
all right that sounds good
so human a humanoid race with a standard
appearance in body type
humans have a good overall balance of
abilities
and have no strengths or weaknesses oh
so depending on the race there's
actually already some like
different traits or like abilities
however these in-game abilities only
take effect when playing classic pso2
ah so in ngs it makes no difference but
in pso2 it does
is that how it is did i get that right
and there's new men
human and human that's funny
and not anymore ah and now it's just
cosmic
there we go we learned something already
i mean i like both both sound both
options
sound interesting to me um as long as
the
the race does not like
influence the ability so strong that you
obviously have a
a big um uh what what
naphtha what's it called again english
hello
you know what i mean disadvantage yeah i
came up with it before the chat told me
yeah as long as but but i think it's
generally interesting oh well it's not a
part of it anymore apparently
so a new man is a humanoid race known
for the long ears
so like an elf while the frame will
physically
they compensate for this with their
exceptional aptitude for techniques
oh however yeah yeah okay
and there's cass where the
mail version is like
a full um sentai
robot nice i
like it that's that's pretty dope
the grill is also not looking bad a
gundam
sorry that's what i meant gundam
[Laughter]
okay it says costs are a race with
bodies composed of
mechanical parts they make up for the
poor aptitude
of techniques with the durable physique
um she got those nice hips too
i gotta be real i i wanna recreate
myself
and i'm i i i was thinking about making
a cast
i'm i'm not sure like if the bot
i guess like the human body type would
be a bit closer to mine
but i don't like this one well the
crotch area looks a little bit yellow
okay and then we have this one it's cute
what is this
a dew man or a doi man
a humanoid brace with distinctive horns
on their head ah
and odd eyes oh they specialize in
offensive performance at their expense
of their defense
oh they look interesting
the girl looks cute but
i don't know either caster human but you
guys seem very
excited about uh cast as well
a human okay okay i was thinking about
pronouncing it in german
cast
cast wow why is castle popular because
of the
nice sexy bunny
all right i guess so uh tattoo obviously
hello
who do you think i am what do we have
here oh
well wait there's a small version too
like a
cute like more fragile looking version
oh
what interesting i love the hat
so this is just the base that i work
work around with
um interesting i
think we should start off with that base
uh create tactile
let's go so i've heard good things about
the character creation uh oh
oh wait that's like oh
that's like um like a like a puppet
like you look at those uh elbows like
you can see it's open there oh you're
like a robot
oh that's not really me but okay let's
roll with it
wait did i just uh trying to figure out
the camera
did i change oh there we go oh
oh oh interesting crotch area never mind
okay
okay okay so let's see what we can do
face base face
okay oh dear there's base phases you can
choose from and from what i understand
this is from um the old game and this
these are new um base choices
oh cute
i see oh but wait you can
do like more detailed outfits right
whoa the old ones look
like i wanted to say the old ones look
good too but
they do they do they do they do just
gonna click on the right ones
[Laughter]
oh they can have long big ears as well
oh
and then wait how do you do like details
here
okay wait want to scroll
like that oh obviously i don't want to
spend too much time but i love character
creation
oh so we can change the whiteness and
the jaw
oh that's pretty easy to change oh we
can do random
not so not so long oh
how do i look uh-huh
i wonder if we can make her look like me
uh huh
uh-huh and then oh
somewhere around here all right all
right all right
and you can edit later oh yeah i saw
inna was able to
edit it even like like later on but even
after you like played the game already
oh okay is that
is that am i missing something is that
everything in the face
oh you can do eyes and all that later on
okay now hairstyle ah
can we get a similar hairstyle to mine
oh oh my god
oh my god
no
she has a huge top hat we have to do
something about that but
uh i think that hairstyle might be the
closest
perfection
that's actually pretty hot i don't know
it's actually kind of hot
and then we don't have to spend so much
time on the
on the face and everything's okay the
creation we can we can play more of the
game
[Music]
well i am i like these options oh wow
this is so futuristic yeah
but i want to make something cute i love
that hair
[Music]
those are the old options but they look
great
yeah okay let's go with that
and then let's do this but my hair is
not that orange it actually has like a
slight
uh a reddish hill
reddish red reddish red rat reddish red
reddish shoe a bit more actually
and then a little bit a little bit
brighter what do you think guys
oh a bit more oil
[Music]
what about that oh screens on it
reddit radish red
[Music]
[Applause]
radish
yeah ah this hairstyle does not allow
like
different like ooh colors in there okay
that's okay
what is that uh-huh uh-huh
okay uh wait i i wanna change
the size of her upper head uh
huh uh alex or oh
maybe that's just uh how it is
[Music]
she has some headphones on too
interesting okay nick area let's go
ah ah
i see oh let's just go with a thin neck
but wait oh
wait wait wait wait we can change the
general size of the head but i want to
change this
top up part you can add ears
oh looks fine really
small head i think this is
okay
and oh we're already in the eyes this is
quite we're going quite fast we could
take more time but we're going in a nice
speed oh pretty
hello oh which are more like mine
i can't choose these
which option one two three
four which pupil
is or like iris is the closest to mine
what do you think huh
middle one three four
two four three
three four
two what
i think there's a lot of force
okay i agree i agree
and then the color is just feeling
purplish
but a bit brighter
yeah something like that maybe a bit
more
pinkish
and then uh somewhere here
i think wow cute girl hello
ah oh that's my that's that's this face
this is too big but
somewhere here and then oh
oh that's that's kind of cute you can
make her
how do you call this an english one
there sheila sheila
what do you call that in english
[Applause]
i think that's actually kind of cute but
we'll stay somewhere in the middle
what was the what was it called
crosstalk yeah that was what i meant
yeah yeah yeah all right and
the then of the eye oh well it's
definitely more like that
actually that's already pretty close
wow wow
no no no we don't need them to be that
big but it's interesting you can give
them some really big
animal eyes
maybe like here
somewhere here i don't think we changed
that much
oh and i think my eyes
are like a little bit like lower
most of the time so i'll do that
exactly oh the eyebrows are horrible
right now i
dislike these eyebrows very much
oh because they're painted on because
like she's like a like a puppet
like a doll oh
those are not that's not even real hair
is it
i see this is because this is not a
human
ah well i like those eyebrows
oh look how she's looking down on all of
you
she's like i i dislike you
you are disgusting
love that okay
we'll go with those and we can change
the color
to something orange oh yeah that works
with me
okay eyebrow thickness oh
oh we can make them a little bit more
visible that's good okay okay
oh we're gonna do that too nice all
right
let's go
okay
i thought i reset my eyes okay no no
those are the eyelashes oh
those are cute but they don't really
look like mine i think the
i think the first ones were only pretty
close maybe a little bit too
thick but those are
not thick enough maybe those
because those wouldn't you guys agree
those are a bit too
fake and then these ones are maybe a
nice in between
i think i like these
104 four four 104
four four four four four okay most
people say you guys
oh we can change the color of that okay
i don't want to do that no no no
no no but i mean we could ah actually my
eyes still have a little bit of a
grab on the side maybe like a little bit
yeah that makes it a little bit softer i
like that oh
cute marry me especially when you look
down me like that once if you look up oh
[Music]
well that scares me a little bit could
you look at me like that a little bit
cuter
huh um it's okay that's
not cute oh cute but scary as well
isn't that what we're into
all right nose i think her nose is
too small too thin it creeps me out a
little bit so
oh normal nose makes her so much cuter
okay i mean that's still a little bit
too perfect of a nose but
oh hello stop looking at me
stop being so cute ah can i
ah i can oh
oh noses are difficult
those are really difficult to make but i
think yeah yeah
and then what about this oh
long face oh
is she still cute is she still cute
where did i mess it up i think she's so
cute
oh what is easy at it ah no no no no no
face faces we already came so far okay
you can do fangs but takana sukiyana has
no fangs
so we're not gonna do that and
wow really plump lips oh there what
happened did you do the
the thing where you i don't know when
you put your mouth in a glass or
something like that
i saw that like ages ago that was
horrible horrible don't do that don't do
that
ah cute kind of
cute can we give her a little lip color
as well
just tongue
cute what the hell would she have her
tongue sticking out all the time
[Music]
um
okay i could do this forever let's stop
[Laughter]
uh i think the mouth uh we made it a
little bit wider i think that's good but
we could also
cute i like that kind of mouth i don't
know if you know what i mean
but um it's cute
it's like a w shape i mean it it always
is i guess but
it doesn't really look like my mouth
though
something like that is okay it's okay
it's okay
uh oh yeah ears cast headset
ah i can take it off oh well i have
normal ears
ah the hair confused me
oh
[Music]
and then we can even adjust it even more
as much as i like uh elf ears we gotta
be realistic here i don't have that
so unfortunately i wouldn't say that
where is that changing ah i guess i
don't have horns in this
unicorn where is the unicorn thingy at
it
doesn't show up
oh my god oh my god
unicorn
what i like those horns
i like it
i'll not put it on just so you know guys
you can put on horns that's really cool
you can be a super special unicorn yeah
oh my gosh it's already half fast i'm
gonna hurry up okay
let's put on this feather because
phoenix what's that
oh let's just put on this yeah yeah yeah
uh oppa
city opacity i know i know i know uh
ah you can put on another one no no no
no no that's okay
oh my god we gotta play the game how how
has it
been i've been hurrying up how has it
already been so much time okay
okay you know this is only supposed to
be one hour but we might add
like half an hour who knows
oh dear customized expressions oh there
ah that looks funny sad
oh oh oh my oh dear
uh wait i want to change it a little bit
um um
not that it really matters because we're
probably not gonna see it ever but
wait i want to change the eyebrows
[Music]
oh no no i want to angle them can i
angle them
very cool
oh you that's that's that's wow like i
oh
no no you're supposed to look sad okay
it's gonna take too much time i guess
sauce
[Music]
your sucks ice cream wink
yep
[Music]
no
wait let me try to fix this yeah
cute oh
saved it saved it oh i was killed that's
cuter than before i think
and unhappy wink
wait i can't can you do that
i i i will wink at you but i don't thank
you
don't misunderstand me anyway okay oh
yeah
let's leave it at that there's you can
you can change up all those expressions
that's pretty cool
okay uh do we like her is she cute
wait what about the bubba size i saw
inna was able to change it where do i
change the bubba size
oh yeah
oh wait that was only the head oh my god
okay speed run
i mean the boobs seem about right they
seem about right
uh but hey look look at what you can do
oh
wow nice body
wow damn
oh oh okay there's always time for a
little oh
nice sorry okay sega i am so sorry but
i mean can you blame me
uh oh dear i messed up her beautiful
body no
[Music]
aha cali
cali um but also kiana okay i'm
also pretty big you know shoulders
oh my god oh my god oh my god
okay i think there's so much to do
[Music]
i can change the color is it the clothes
cute i like that
can i wear that it's also cute
can i wear that
accessories ah oh wait
[Music]
there we go so much to do
stickers
what where does it go where did it go
where is the sticker where is the
sticker
i wonder where do i put it oh well okay
okay
okay hey outfit
oh
[Music]
i like that one
oh i love that one okay we're going with
that
oh we can change the color oh let's make
it look orangish wow
nice oh wait
[Music]
that's gonna take a million years to go
fruit
[Music]
motion
oh my god okay yeah you guys
you guys obviously see that there's many
things you can do
oh my god uh i think i'm done with that
why okay now we got the classes
we got the classes and there is hunter
a class geared towards close range
combat they axel at
engaging enemies in close quarters
boasting
high hp and defense they can hold their
own when operating solo oh sounds good
no no no no no i'm not done a fighter
a class geared towards ultra close range
combat
there are at their best when pressing
the enemy what they lack in defense is
made up for their devastating
pulverizing attacks
interesting but not really my thing
ranger a class geared towards medium
range combat they use ranged weapons to
engage enemies while maintaining
maintaining optimal distance they can
also support other players with a range
of special rounds
oh and then there's gunner
who uses two guns ah one big gun and one
two two small guns class gear towards
close range combat they
that exo excels at wielding ranged
weapons point blank
they make light work of enemies with a
great mobility and a relentless torrent
of
torrent of fools those two seem like
something that
tiara would choose but what will kiara
choose
force a class gear towards long-range
combat
i like honestly you know you look at me
and you see
a shield and a sword at
obviously close range but i prefer in
games i
normally like in mmorpgs and stuff i
usually prefer
long range you guys know me if you watch
my streams you know that
don't ya uh although i mean if it if
it's like other games that are not
mmorpgs
obviously the only choice you mostly get
is close
range combat so yeah i mean i do both
[Music]
um okay uh voice uh we already read this
did we no
they make use of techniques that assault
the enemy from a distance making use of
a variety of techniques they can exploit
exploit an enemy's elemental weakness oh
taster protector a class
geared towards close and long-range
combat oh that seems a bit more
difficult at least for beginners it also
supports other players for techniques
ah like a support role focused primarily
on ability enhancement and healing oh
they can stack any battle in their favor
oh that sounds
interesting yeah what do you guys think
i should go for
inna is that oh then we should not
choose that
because i want to play with inna
together
uh well if she's that then i should be
close
combat like hunter
yeah i think that would just go full
hunter to be honest
air force
gunner ranger gunner
is it easy excel is willing ranged
weapons point blank what does that mean
they make like work of enemies with the
green moon
yeah i mean we can try let me try it out
but hunter
[Music]
tk let's go
we got no time to lose we want to play
the game
oh my god hello wow
i played a little bit to test out the
game but i skipped all of the scenes
so i don't know what's happening system
check complete
status all systems go this gives me
flashbacks of a certain game and i don't
like it
sequence standby we're reaching target
coordinates in 10 seconds
confirm final landing trajectory error
adjustment
complete five
four three two
two one one let's go
[Music]
what's happening
oh
is that my hand no where's that cute
girl
hey who is that nice butt
this
it's pretty dope
i like your character design
no it's smoking sorry was that me
i fell from the sky like a like a star
[Music]
thingy
thank goodness it opened here take my
hand
you got a cute voice oh cute smile
shooting start yeah that's what i meant
i'll meet you right now that's
shooting you really startled us falling
out of the blue
does anything hurt are you okay
wait i feel like i could have done the
better creation
oh wow that's a really nice name
i'll make her i'll i'll recreate it
later so nice to meet you
and the proportion maybe looks a bit off
because we try to
try to speed through it i'll show you to
our town okay
we can talk more there okay i got a
little floaty thing that's also orange
nice
okay so i already know i can speed like
this and i can jump and i
i love the water texture wow
we're in some kind of vacation area here
oh
sorry i don't want to go there i want to
check out those beautiful trees wow they
were really pretty
okay no but we don't have time let's go
we gotta climb up this cliff okay
because we get a running start you can
jump really high here
oh yeah try i will try three two
one jump nice
nice cutscene again nice
what the hell what's going on
what's going on
wow a doll's unit
doll's doing here it does not look like
a cute dog
huh i should be able to handle something
like this
i'm
i will marry you here right now here and
now forever and ever
[Music]
i'll i'll help too all right focus on
defending yourself
sure wait i look so weird
i'll make my character again okay i'll
show you when i
created actually the first time i
created one
um
just to you know test out the game
ouch i can dodge oh but wait there's
almost dead
no
wow this is fun i like close count
combat after all
ouch i fell down the normal attack last
week and i'm
playing with the mouse and keyboard
because i kind of prefer
it at least for this game
oh character sound for free hey can you
change like everything
for the first five hours wow six
hours to re six hours
so this is what i had that bad feeling
about huh
i know manning you are right
online time only okay okay thanks who
are you
i look so i look so weird
i'm gone
[Music]
loud okay but we can talk about it when
we get back to town
oh aina manon are you done gathering the
rest assigned
oh that's right i almost forgot
this is so cool that it has full english
voicing damn
and they're good oh
yo i love my my swords like a charge
blade rasta sign works as a medical
medicinal medicine medicinal
agent or can i when can i meet him
it's a good idea to have some for when
you get hurt in battle
all right
it's over there
okay taking it yep
okay oh
yeah yeah i got another one and another
one is that all
all right that'll do that'll do we're
going back to town now
they're following me wow is that my team
[Music]
it's so pretty look at those pink trees
over there oh by the way i have the
graphics settings um on like
wait i'll show you because i don't know
what it's called
what wait it's actually
not here huh i have them on the on the
setting that's like not the most
best setting but the one below it just
in case i didn't want to
have any problems wait how do i
i thought i turned the thingy off the
friend request thingy let me try again
options interface
no gameplay
oh did it reset no framework
associations hide
huh
[Music]
i already turned off symbol art
is that not the right setting for it
oh well in the graphics menu and the
display thing i know i know
what do you mean
otherwise we'll just go with it
uh you have to hide the ones you already
have and it should be off
and rubber but you can decline it all
right okay we'll just ignore it
oh
well we need to cross here hmm but what
about you
hmm got any experience with gliding no
you gather photons the energy in your
body into your arms and your legs
oh you do that that sounds different
jump off from here
even if you screw it up it's just the
sea down there
go on give it a go
tough teacher
[Music]
oh my god okay let's go
uh what no
wait i'll wait
i can do this better there you go see i
can do it yeah i can swim no worries
what is it yeah
yeah honey
hello oh
fishing
[Music]
i love this like low-key raggy
feeling in the music don don't come to
our humble little alia town
hall i'm sure everybody here will give
you a warm welcome
you all are looking suspicious
suspiciously hot
[Music]
it gets effing everywhere i'm not gonna
swear this is the spotted stream
[Music]
oh look at that style yo
let's go to someone's house
are these are these npcs or players no
those npcs right
all right let's go up the stairs
follow me
and almost emotionally it is me this
is my place come on in i don't wanna i'm
a stranger danger i've been told not to
follow
men into whatever they're offering me to
follow them into
well like i said and there you are with
your spring licks oh
i'm the leader of this town okay this
here's aina
my daughter she's cute i'll be friends
over there
a pleasure first of all
you're probably wondering where in the
world you are
yes i am indeed wondering that could you
tell me
let's start with the planet we call this
one
alpha alpha and this is a town on that
planet
called aeliotown alientown it's a pretty
small place though as you can see
no mice north of here is alpha's largest
city
named central city what a name central
city is the seat of alpha's government
and economy
i'm sure you'll have the chance to visit
it at some point
and then willing in today's stream i
wonder
the ones you just fought were the
smaller class of them
that was supposed to be small okay let
me tell you us half ins have been at war
with these dolls
for a very long time how long you ask
well let's see count counting they say
it's been over 500 years
damn there you go
but we still don't understand very much
about them though i'm afraid
why do they attack us where do they come
from
we really have no idea about the only
thing we do know for sure is
the dolls are our sworn enemy
i guess you could say they're just one
big mystery to us these are certain
dominoes
like you meteor
[Music]
meteorin is what we call people like you
hmm
the folks who show up here on alpha from
space in those
i did indeed land like a meteor man in
here
is also a meteorite she dropped down on
that little island about half a year ago
she's so cute and now she lives with us
meteor dolls we don't know where either
of you come from
or even why you come here for some
reason
meteor and all seem to arrive here with
no memory of their past yeah that seems
to be a thing
with you know protagonists like man in
here
i am not surprised that i don't know
where i am who i am where
i came from few fragments of knowledge
left
man it is really smart hmm she knows so
much about machines
no she even helps me with my studies
is she studying that both the dolls and
meteor
probably come from the same place
but whether that's true or not i can say
with confidence that you meteorn are our
friends
you guys have been our allies for a long
time
of that there is no okay
if you trust me that's okay that's
enough of elections
wait he has no nipples i'll send
everything we just talked about
does he have that thing floating next to
you is a mag by the way
mac your mag that is so
cute what does it do that's another
unique thing about you meteor
but we'll go into more detail on that
later
sorry that's the thing i always pay
attention to when uh
when i play games and then there's a
topless guy in front of me
whether or not he has nipperino's or not
sorry i'm hungry by the way
let's get our grub on then why don't you
take a look around the town while we get
it ready
how how has it already been an hour okay
don't worry guys we're gonna play a
little bit longer than now
sega has sponsored this stream uh very
kindly
for an hour but i'll gladly do a little
bit more i bet everyone's eager to chat
with you don't be shy now they don't
bite
oh okay we got a girl over there
easy we can jump on top of the building
i like these fabrics they're really
pretty
[Music]
who is it someone on the beach huh okay
what's up what is up hey you're the
meteon from earlier right i'm real nice
to meet you
me i just finished getting the training
targets all sorted out
you can give them a go if you like oh
training
arc let's go oh
you know yes i actually know it's cute
isn't it
i know how to walk on let's go
you really had your eyes on the prize
well then how about the sights stop
strikeness try attacking while you dodge
uh-huh
again uh wait
here we go okay hey
yeah did i do well
i don't step oh
when i sit down there's no doubt your
true meat here
looking right to see how you perform in
the future thank you
okay quick next next one
it's so pretty here though like the
whole game
seems to have a really futuristic theme
obviously but like this area
is so natural i like it
it's very pretty you want to talk to me
how you doing how are you
doing how are you sfx
oh okay wait i'll turn it down wait one
second i can't turn it down right now
i'll teach you about all sorts of ways
to attack all right
uh one second oh wait
is that it hold on all right store up
your photos and your body and then let
it all
out do it right and you'll unleash more
powerful photon arts
charge it up and let it all out the
longer you charge up the better okay
wait a second can i
uh wait please don't kill me yet
oh wait the game doesn't stop okay oh
wait we gotta fight first sorry
loudest effects coming in hey
okay i healed myself with this uh weird
thingy
okay okay that one's dead okay
when you learn phones inside your body
you might not be able to use your photo
lights when that happens just wait a
while to let the photons build up again
if you're not the patient type you can
attack enemies without using photonics
i added the left click right so build up
your photos quicker too
next time i'm going to cover how to
switch between different attacks quickly
listen up and try to do as i say
oh wow
an open pallet with ships held down
but uh-huh is this different attacks
oh those are tags yo
hey come here
where are you dead week
what are we going
yeah did i do well great work thank you
whenever you wear a new folding arm be
sure to apply what you have learned here
to it
here you go just make sure you're making
ah you gave me some
food thank you hope you'll put
everything i've taught you
uh two good use out there are you okay
chill
are you trying to impress me no one can
impress me only i
impress myself
how are you doing how are you doing
sound uh sound effects
down down down down down oh voice maybe
oh i don't know
hey okay should be better now
[Music]
is it better it should be better oh
wait where are we going uh follow the
arrow
pretty close
oh welcome to the
plant fields
what is it this here is my field what's
gonna welcome you to take
any and as many vegetables as you like
but the truth is the enemy have been
coming and wrecking the place recently
oh damn
they're not that tough but they're
getting bolder heck i can feel them
peering out from the shadows of the
trees as we speak
i have a favor to ask of you could you
get rid of them for me it would be a
great chance to see what you're capable
of
capable of too oh we'll do
where are they i'm gonna give you a
little fighting as well i don't need
five things advice okay
i'll listen you've heard of weapon
actions haven't you they're special
skills that differ between weapons
uh use the right skills to get
the upper hand in battle
while you have a sword equipped press
the thing in the middle
the scrolling wheel to use the sword as
a shield
oh and reduce the damage you take
depending on your timing it may become a
perfect card oh there's perfect guard in
this game too
completely protecting you from the enemy
attack okay
[Music]
all right
wait it's coming at me okay you want me
to block
come at me can i do it again
oh hey okay can i kill him now
don't want to waste my time anymore no
and you lock on
oh yup oh okay i died before it could
throw that
rock at me nice i think i timed it at
least once
you got all of them i really can't thank
you enough
you're welcome i'm gonna send you a
mountain of veggies oh
least i can do to show my gratitude yata
why am i getting messages like that
is there no way to turn those off i
think
but but the the picture thingy is turned
off
i just remembered someone wanted to
speak with you
an ark's defender by the name of bosey
you should find him in front of the
fountain okay let's go
uh there okay i'm coming
don't whisper me please
[Music]
how are you doing oh cute
don't distract me right now
[Music]
hey settings yeah yeah it's okay
and what is up what is up my boy
it's you what's that you heard i was
looking for you yeah
were you not that's right i wanted to
give you a welcome gift
welcome gift although i wasn't quite
sure what would be good for you
oh i'm not sure either
how about the cat then i thought of
something awesome oh wait sorry i
skipped that i remember putting it in
putting it in an item container a while
ago but as for which one i can't picture
you want me to destroy them and look for
them
you want me to look for it okay can we
broken by attacking them allowing you to
obtain the items inside
contain this uh containers come in three
different varieties
uh green gold and red golden red
containers are rare in particular there
are
only a certain number of red containers
that can be found per
account oh and they contain valuable
items oh
interesting okay
[Music]
you can't find it you want me just to go
looking for it
i did i did just ah well there
presents guys presents
green that's not so special but okay
what do you give me
[Music]
well prim armor oh i'm so glad you could
find it
what you seriously can't tell what that
is well i guess it's armor it's
kept around for just such an occasion oh
i've kept it in top condition so i
shouldn't give you any problems
oh a gripping armor you can equip armor
by going to a grip armor
on the gear subpalette palette in the
main menu
uh-huh when you want to unequip a piece
of armor select remove
go ahead and equip it okay
[Music]
equip uh-huh uh-huh oh there we go
is that it good you're probably equipped
that was easy
if you get armor elsewhere make sure you
equip it remember that okay
okay okay remembering
explanations on features in pso2 and ngs
can be found by going
to help on their system in the main menu
then select the game guide okay
have it have you had a good look around
town already
if you have have you failed for now it's
probably best to head on back to
gadowa's place
okay i'm on my way i want to show you
guys a little bit more of the game
gotta hurry gotta hurry sorry this feels
like a speed run
uh i just i just wanna try to get as
much in as possible
negotiator what hello
hey you're back i bet you're tired see
he has voices why don't you take it easy
here for a while
uh-huh i love the visual i mean too
i love it too i think a rest sounds good
i'll go check on the preparations make
yourself at home okay
okay yeah one hour is like
so short it goes by so fast especially
with games you log into
when you're really into the game you
could play it for 10 hours a day and it
feels ready for refreshments
it's nothing special but we put a little
something together
it's a long-standing half and custom to
offer the warmest welcome we can to our
meteor
guests
[Music]
okay he seems nice
yeah he seems all right
[Laughter]
i like the npc designs they're pretty
sweet
looking we
[Music]
here's some for you help me out with the
character creation
but we'll keep saying if i help me
please she could do probably a better
job
okay looks
[Music]
that character is special yeah because
it's my character
that's okay here don't you think it's
okay she looks nice
you know i really love this place
i want to make damn sure no harm scary
fire
i would i would sit uh maybe one more
meter
back they're the warriors who do battle
with the dolls
both me and manon are full arcs
defenders
but aina over there is still an
apprentice the blue-haired girl
you know before i showed up to that
battle back there butterflies
looked like you were pretty evenly
matched
arcs could use more good fighters i for
one
think you'd make a great addition to the
rxt are you going to pay me
good luck i'm a phoenix yes i am what
did i say
see how you like it here because of the
fight
i'm afraid for them because they're so
close
i can just walk into the fire and then
come out with free dragons don't worry
no that was something else
the black hole
not good looks like the ones earlier
oh [\h__\h] that's a lot
oh my what
dad dad oh
dolph we're under attack whoa
are we strong enough oh my god
super and boss battle level
they're coming protect the town oh
yeah whatever we're fine
next one um elemental weakness seems
like you don't have a weapon of the
right element okay then why the hell are
you telling me that
yeah i'm too far away
who wants to who wants to fight
[Music]
what's that on the ground does that hurt
me too sound like an aoe oh my god
though uh the the battle system i like
it
pretty small i can probably do better
but
and where's that health bar am i being
blind i don't see the
health bar
there is no health bar yeah no i mean
the enemy's health bar oh we did it
they don't have one okay i know my
health but i wanted to know their health
bar
[Music]
do the enemies in this game generally
have no health bar
or only in this tutorial
only the box is from the urgent quest
what the hell is that oh yeah i forgot
the kick charge downtown
take these two and run to the northern
caves
what but dad look
we'll just get in the way here is what
he's saying
hey yeah
i know let's go
wait i i can't wait so emotional
come on no you too oh
go no that is trying the whole village
it what am i fighting that thing still
no i'm leaving right
okay go the cave is off the slope
oh my god yes
they're not going easy on me i only have
one health
health thingy left yeah oh
are the girls following me
all right tutorial village that is very
sad yeah
we did it we did it
we could help
woof
[Music]
right in the middle that's probably
gonna hurt him the
oh my god
what are you gonna do with those hands
huh it's not gonna do anything
bad ending
oh good you're back and are you okay
no my favorite news is that the mag's
body scan feature
isn't showing any injuries
what about what about the blue head girl
well
oh no
no
i still can't believe any of this i
can't believe it either how the hell did
we survive
whoa whoa whoa whoa where's where's
where's the war
i know i want to ask about gaga
pretty badly some arcs defenders from
central city came and
took her to the medical okay so she's
alive but what about betty
some arcs defenders from central city
were searching for him a little while
ago
okay they haven't found any survivors
yet
what no way
we got hit by that huge doll's attack
hmm it looks like we were unconscious
for a while
the dolls are gone now but it looks like
a leotown has been
completely oh no i guess we can't just
stay here forever we should
get going to central city too i guess so
[Music]
i guess we should go that is
very sad it has there been any lag uh
like like like fps loss
in the battle scene at least not like on
on the stream because i don't see it i
don't have any fps laws in the game
enemies are scratching and take them out
with a dash attack wait how how does it
work ah
okay did i do that wait i think i
need to go back
you killed them i don't know if i did it
some but not much okay
[Music]
you know what that little mag thingy
it looks like kotori the orange and then
the turquoise color
oh my god and it has these flaps
oh thank god there's some stuff here to
heal myself
apparently i was healed anyway though
after that cutscene
thank you whoever healed me
it looks like kotoni can i get rid of
that dash attack thingy pop-up do i need
to do it properly
you did it i don't want to see that
anymore
oh wow
wow we're in a tunnel now oh
it's so big oh
enemies has a tough exterior what did
you say diving attack
ah well with midair oh interesting
oh [\h__\h]
wait how do i oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice okay okay we killed that one do
they not drop
items take that we need that
we need it middle mouse eh i felt like
i tried sometimes it felt like it didn't
uh block it just attacked i feel like
maybe that was uh yeah i didn't press it
long enough i don't know
and how do i how do i
wait oh there's the other one oh my god
ah yeah i meant to sidestep
oh how was that oh there we go how do i
do it
um need to burn that into my brain
what okay i did something weird
oh there we go okay i changed the
the camera angle for some
real reason
[Music]
help oh thank you
she can revive me okay well then uh
i'm not scared anymore if that's the
case whatever then
wait you wanted me to do something right
yeah okay
did i do it
[Music]
sorry for dying there once let me get
those items
[Music]
oh very pretty okay
run quickly
phoenix be reviving yeah okay i die in
the game i did not revive
myself i got help reviving but yes
generally that is totally accurate
i cannot die oh are we gonna see the
the city once we're out of this dark
tunnel
whoa whoa i think i see something
oh there's also something in the sky
what is that
oh i sense a beautiful scenery
that's central city i thought so okay
let's go let's go okay
okay
[Music]
wow look
pretty they got some nice signs too
thank you
and those light up the road i guess is
that an
elk thingy and some
oh is that cute aborting me
wait you don't look so cute and close up
yeah disgusting i thought you were cute
from a distance
but getting closer to you to you was a
mistake
oh sh okay
uh the city is pretty close
noise let's see if we find dad again
here
i hope so you can't just have him die
there
[Music]
knock knock please let me in oh what's
that
you two are from aliotown isn't that
right that is correct
and you are my name's ran
i'm an operator for central city
that's pretty high-tech
that sounds scary crawford
please go through the gate there and
proceed to the tower
just ahead of you is that the moon
will escort okay
okay
[Music]
you can't be from a place that doesn't
exist anymore that's not true
that is not true but besides besides i
i'm not really from that place i am from
the sky
so that's kind of incorrect wow
so modern but where it was there's so
few people solo stuff that's where i can
change myself later on okay okay
you're looking cute okay i will remember
that
uh item lab enhancement technician
personal shop staff hey
dicka um
but that's so funny because in in german
that's
that has a different meaning that that's
that's a funny name to have
just from the point of view of a
german-speaking person
where is everyone am i not supposed to
see it already here
i guess not i guess it's still like only
me huh
wow
that way food stand
you're not probably don't have as good
food as a cafe but i can help you out
with that we can have a little bit of a
collaboration
maybe perhaps hey of me is worldwide so
i don't mind you know building a
franchise over there
[Music]
okay she's cute why does everyone accept
me look cute
[Music]
i really messed up but you can really
create really adorable characters okay
i'm crawford wow you are still sitting
here
i should have just put on you know one
of those helmets where you couldn't see
the face at all anymore
i mean they told me about well i heard
you had
difficulties to say the least oh yeah
i'm so glad the two of you managed to
survive
so very glad wait
what about aina she's being treated in
the medical bay
oh but don't worry i hear it's not
critical he's got a really dope kid
half a day since she was brought in she
should be starting to feel better soon
i hope
no what about the boy the big boy
oh
i'm totally fine don't push yourself
though
thank you crawford are you gonna love
the crowd
you came to check on me didn't you
that means a lot to me she's so cute and
what about my dad
yeah you don't know either okay oh his
face says no
i see
what kind of doll's unit could have been
too much for i mean you saw that
thing didn't you didn't really think
your dad could take up on that huh
but we believe it just might be another
doll species
named dark falls oh dark falls was the
cause of a near extinction level
catastrophe over all of alpha 100 years
ago too
apparently it was able to easily wipe
out the capital city of the time
if the dolls unit you encountered really
is dark falls
then that means there's absolutely no
time to lose
hmm we have to start preparing our
forces as soon as possible
and
and what and
well you three are the only ones who
have ever actually seen dark false
so i believe arx could really use your
help fighting it
i know it's a lot to ask after what you
just went through
but your aid would be invaluable
i'm i'm in yes
in fact i really want to fight dark
falls
i want to defeat it so nothing like that
ever happens again
i know and you two
[Music]
you're still new to this planet right if
you feel you need a little more time
no i'll certainly understand no no no
i told ya it's destiny that's why i fell
from the sky
i
all right i'll join in too yeah you
better
what choice do we have we're gonna die
if we don't fight we might die if we
fight
but we're also going to die if we don't
fight so let's fight
so easy decision now
one plus one is first we'll need your
help preparing for the next attack
and of course when dark falls actually
does show up
that's when we fight
[Music]
for the moment you should rest ran
our rooms ready for them yes i've
prepared three rooms
we can all stand in the same room i
don't run little caves
good i want you three to consider
yourselves citizens of central city from
now on
all right when you get a minute i'd like
you all to check your max
you should be registered as arcs
defenders now boom
your mags will also act as your room
keys
oh feel free to take a break anytime you
need to
and we can talk about all the rest
tomorrow
i sent your room locations to your max
now
i want you all to take it easy for the
rest of the day
will do thank you very much
hello what a sweet guy oh very good
looking guy
let's go take a look okay head to the
lounge
honestly i think after we arrive at the
lodgings that's where
where we're gonna end it because uh it's
already one and a half hours
uh but i think
we will play this at least one more time
in the other stream
um i don't think this will be a one time
only thing so look forward to the next
time and maybe we'll play it together
and perhaps with someone else as well
who knows
aina oh hmm yes
are you okay totally why do you ask how
the hell are you okay though
sorry i'm just not very good at reading
people
[Music]
oh don't be silly manon
it means a lot that you care
yeah but how are you okay
[Music]
how is that possible you need to look
out here you didn't even grief
we just have to beat the three of us
together
okay i'm such a mess
oh multiplayer will unlock once you
complete the prologue
story quest did i do that no in areas
where multiplayer is possible you can
communicate with other players and fight
in parties of
up to four people oh please mind your
manners
yeah did you hear that guys when playing
with other people and refrain from using
abusive language or causing trouble
understand everyone this is only gonna
work if you guys are gonna follow the
rules
i guess we're done with the tutorials
good morning thank you actually perfect
perfect way to stop it uh this fandom
make requests for you
big requests there are some basic skills
i need you to acquire
if you're going to fight these dolls oh
yeah teach me more we have a great
instructor at cocoon
our top flight training facility oh he
can teach you
everything you need to know head over
there when
you're fully prepared i am always fully
prepared
thank you i don't need that luck either
cocoons are a type of training facility
called trainia
that exists in every area or each cocoon
has its own clear conditions upon
achieving them
you will receive skill points
some coconuts can only be accessed once
you meet certain conditions
[Music]
i see very interesting okay guys
oh my god oh dear oh wow wow oh my god
hi kelly
oh okay i have been welcomed
what is this a little bonus for you a
little bonus for me thank you
yeah so there are godzilla elements in
this game and apparently there's a daily
free gotcha what do i do
salon thank you
and healthscape though i've been waiting
for you
everyone people waiting for me
what do i do kiana doesn't load in mine
well just wait for me
take some time
this is so nice there's a welcome comedy
nice
oh how do i get rid of this next looking
uh-huh oh my god
social distancing please okay wait so
how about the free gotcha
[Music]
where's jeffrey gotcha personal
no give me a room
with uh i don't know that cute blue
haired chick
can't so cute hello everyone
and we don't really have time today but
but but next time f11
okay oh what do you get from these
alex uniform clothes
yes you know one of my favorite things
and other refugees
is you know the kind of aesthetic
cosmetic things
that you can buy so i'm looking forward
to this very much
okay one one free
got this one one time for yourselves
daily what about the other ones how much
did they cost mm-hmm
let's do it everyone's looking so
hot already
what do we get we're going to scratch
screen scratch
[Music]
isn't that a male in the phone can i
even wear that
but i got a whole clothing item i know
ina
only got a little beard
[Laughter]
what what oh
heels i guess so
wait am i wearing it no no i'm not how
do i wear it
can i wear it
what how do i uh how do i wear it
[Music]
customized
loading oh they're dancing wait
oh you're doing that are you are you
[\h__\h] wearing a chicken head
are you doing that because of me
ah let me get out of this okay oh my god
oh my god let's take a look at these
people your outfit is cute i wanna zoom
it can i zoom into
like when i wanna do this thing just
change
it i wanna zoom in how do i zoom in
[Music]
you have to eat it one set
you're cute oh you're close like you
that one
i want that
a plus and minus
wait where is my plus and minus the
thing is i have japanese keyboard on
right now okay i don't know how it works
but
it cute stop moving you're cute wait
cute i don't want to look at you
stop moving stop moving you're cute
oh cute
[Music]
oh oh i like your dress too
diablo oh
and i don't know i'm looking forward to
these cos uh oh good costumes yeah
yep but there's a lot of people here
wow look at you wow
what is that big thing is that a
character oh
what nice weapon yo you look like really
high level
are you really high level
[Music]
cool i like this place i wanted to end
the stream though
ah well let me look around
[Music]
she had a cosplay on the stage
you're not you're not talking about that
stupid chicken are you
right let me look where where where
where where
wait whoa
where oh
[Music]
wait no did you actually mean that girl
i just saw this girl
oh you didn't mean to ah i was gonna be
mad because you thought you
meant that stop it stop that flapping
stop it but hey you do look like me how
the hell do i manage to look like you
so that they look like me wait
good job and tell me how to that looks
like a christmas outfit almost
yo i thought i thought i thought they
were trolling me and saying this looks
like me
oh i like your outfit too
[Music]
okay so guys have i misunderstood it or
is it
true that like if you had a character in
um
fantasy star online 2 not new genesis
that you can like kind of use that
character here or so is that true
but did i misunderstand something wait
are you answering me
is that yes oh that's why you guys are
already looking so fancy
is that your characters from the
previous game
most of us here doing that oh that's why
you guys look so fancy so maybe i can't
even get those outfits yet because
they're not in new genesis yet
oh you you look like kelly oh my god
she's rapping
she's gonna strive yo what the [\h__\h]
hey look at her
eh why am i saying that i thought i
can't see that
why is that different thing anyway that
was safe you guys are nice oh my god
that's so can you guys take the
picture together the kiara and the cali
yeah that's so cool hey it's gonna be
fun to play together with you guys
yo that's a sticker okay that's
something else huh
what i can get on top of you oh yeah now
you can fall off
yeah this is fun and that's so cool that
they
integrated that so like you don't have
to start all over from the beginning you
can use your previous character
that is so cool respect that they did
that
stop spamming those
[Laughter]
all right okay i'm quite impressed this
looks like fun
i definitely want to change the looks of
my characters and of my character and
then
we're going to play with uh uh inna and
maybe with you guys i made it with
someone else
maybe maybe there's gonna be one more
person who
uh oh my god they're spamming oh my god
can you turn those off
can you at least turn the pop-ups off
oh my okay they're just being excited
now so i'll forgive them
this time
holy [\h__\h] that looks so accurate how is
that possible
no don't die no what the hell hey
what is that pose yo
wait someone said there's a godad too
now i want to see the gura where is the
girl
i'm gonna come to the fountain whoever
is cosplaying good uh
please come to the bottom also i like
your looks you look dope you look dope
he needs to
yeah the character customization but how
did you do that like is that a
like an outfit that was being sold or
can you like furball
on change like the colors and [\h__\h]
good eyes here where
dokko oh i've seen that before
that's here where where is that oh hey
cute wait i wanted two men i wanna zoom
in properly
but i'm i'm too stupid to figure out how
that that's hella cute that's like a
mecca version of gouda
[Music]
tons of cosmetic items is so cool
oh my god i'm fascinated by this
oh you look cute too you got the virgin
killer sweater cute
it it did i miss something
group photo i don't know man you guys
can take one
i'm not gonna take one i okay i'll stay
i'll stand here in the front in the
middle and you guys can stand behind me
if you want to take one i look
ridiculous right now though i'm gonna
change my looks probably
there's pagoda too damn they stand
behind me i say
stand behind behind behind we need
everyone to stand behind on the stairs
you know
do you understand how to do a group uh i
i have already turned off symbol
you don't need to tell me that again you
guys understand how to do a group
picture
do you guys get it gonna stand behind me
oh i'm going to send a picture in the
front then
[Music]
welcome to take a little picture you're
welcome
emergency announcement we have confirmed
the presence of powerful dolls in the
vicinity of the alia region
all arcs defenders please prepare for
deployment
is that a general thing that happens
every now and then like a raid or
something
and we gotta like destroy it together
holy [\h__\h] those boobs
for high level oh nothing for me huh
wow that's so cool you guys don't you
guys have something better to do then
now
okay okay take the picture then wait
wait i'll pose okay posing
take it and then run and do your quest
do it do it okay i think everyone who
wanted one
got kiana won't load father stop me in
i want to get rid of that menu okay
there we go
just just photoshop me in your picture
later on same
well that's not my fault i think
oh that's oh
okay well yeah you'll get another chance
i'm sure of it
[\h__\h] chicken oh
ah ui off i say okay that's okay thanks
guys
that that was actually fun i love mmrpgs
like i
i used to play um mri refugees
like for my whole
teenage time and i was absolutely
addicted to
mma physiques i played so many and i
told you guys several times
uh kfb knows that i've been waiting
for another mmo rpg in like an
anime style but everything that comes
out recently
is on on smartphones and i just don't
want to play an mmrpg on a smartphone
you know me um so this is
i love that you know i always prefer
playing with a keyboard and a mouse
on a pc i mean okay controller is okay
too but generally when it comes to
mmorpgs i want to play like this
so so i am excited this is like destiny
i was waiting for this holy [\h__\h] finally
finally something has come
uh and ina seems to want to play this
uh every now and then as well even
outside of the sponsorship so
well i'm looking forward to that mm-hmm
anime style evermore begins are the best
is also it has those
cute outfits that i can buy so let's go
let's go okay i hope you guys had fun
unfortunately um i mean
i i don't know for sure but it seems
like it would you look
cute it seems like it's probably better
to not do a super chat reading today i
should separate it
separate it uh
one question though these these outfits
though do they oh you look funny
do they um bind on the character
like uh if you wear it once is it bound
to you and you can't
like um give it to someone else anymore
or can you like gift your outfits to me
how how does that work only if you
bounce twice
depends on the outfit oh because because
i want some of those outfits
if you have premium
not all outfits most are depends on the
item
or maybe some of you have some spare
ones
well he looks cool too you got a nice
coat that looks like bat wings yo
and she looks like a princess i love
that outfit
we can give you some okay not today
not today that's okay that's okay but
that already sounds very promising
pso2 to get old outfits oh
in a personal shop need some of that
premium
cash shop money
someone said there's a peculiar wait
where is piccolo i can't
where is
sorry i am just really curious this is
really interesting
um
can't be a boy hello can you change your
name or
or did you always have that name
um right here where is right here okay
is she up there
i don't know
[Music]
foreign
you show up as a bunch i show up as a
bunch of numbers
how is that possible interesting okay
wait where is big corner did you guys
see her
play already oh
i love that what the hell how is that
how can you look like that
that's so weird oh wait that's oh my god
help explosion
oh my god wait i want to see pecora
piglet come to the stairs please
to these stairs why you look you look
hot
[Music]
can't yeah i feel like you're there but
will you load for me is this the thing
is this just too many people right now
behind me oh i can see your text
damn show me a screenshot send them to
me on twitter i'm curious
i like your fishes
i could stay here forever eh
i want to be on the sofa too wait stay
stay down you're up this cute
wait wait you're cute you're all so cute
ghost rabbit pecora ghost pickle
ghost pickle you're not existing pickle
he'll say but i love this gouda
it's good as badass oh my god how the
hell will you do that
okay okay i should leave sorry i'm gonna
keep getting super
distracted okay i think you guys got the
gist
um this game free to play
go play it it's fun it has cross play
it's awesome graphics that
has a lot of customization options not
only like in the character creation but
also
um like generally as you can see you can
do so much holy [\h__\h]
and and and yeah you can easily move
between pso2 and ps
uh fantasy star online two new genesis
it's super easy
as they told us and yeah it's
it seems like a really fun game
i want to play more of it definitely
sorry that today we didn't make so much
progress uh
we'll we'll do that sometime hopefully
thank you you for sponsoring the stream
and yeah i'll see you guys the day after
tomorrow because i'm taking tomorrow
off and then the day after tomorrow we
have
uh we have some stream
which is uh
and then on the weekend we have ax so
exciting but honestly guys next week is
my maybe gonna be even more excited so
stay tuned for that i
am i'm super hyped uh for several many
many reasons
[Music]
i'm really excited uh you guys gotta
stay on top of everything
keep on watching takana turn on the
notification bell ding ding ding
yeah and check out this game definitely
and that is i guess the most important
message from the stream check out
fantasy style
online too new jerseys and you might
might get a chance to see me and ina
in in the game yeah 3d debut
there we go here it is
uh yeah thank you guys and i wish you
all a lovely day lovely evening
do the emergency guys now that there's
so many people there do it together come
on
i can't help you i'm low level i just
started this game
i can't help you here yeah
sorry no super chat rating that will be
uh the day oh
the day after maybe after mario kart to
be honest
all right adam german we say au
rieu
[Music]
see you
what's up
[Music]
do
you