[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
again
hi
good morning who's tired I'm tired
[Music]
hi hi
I'm tired
[Music]
yeah oh God I I'm like
I'm drinking the
um Red Bull from last night
[Music]
I didn't think I was gonna do that but
now I have stooped so low
[Music]
it's it's not been 24 hours since I
opened it
yeah it's really flat now but that's
okay it hasn't even been 24 hours since
I opened it so yeah it should be all
right
she'll be all right right now
finally I can catch a stream live where
are you from where are you watching from
that this is the one you'll you'll be
able to catch live
interesting I did not refrigerate it but
it's still pretty like cold I wouldn't
say it's warm I wouldn't say it's ice
cold either
but it's um
colder than
colder than room temperature
it's fine probably it doesn't taste it
I'm weird it just tastes a bit flat
bye
[Music]
-bye
um
what's colder than being cold I'm
some kind of like
[Music]
funny and so smart but then I realized
after this that stream what was that
stream afterwards I realized I messed up
uh the title it wasn't funny at all
because I kind of messed up the whole
joke
anyway do you see this shirt thingy it's
my pajama
but that's the one I was talking about
um the one I have in in common with uh
[Music]
it's my pajamas
yeah
you can see my pajamas that's okay
because you will see my arms a lot today
um so I need something you know to cover
it
[Music]
My Stream is running on my phone on my
bed
wait wait wait I'll be right back um
[Music]
so what are we doing today
Noah
well well well well well sell this
watch is I mean a lot of you guys
probably don't know this but this is
what you call an ironing board
let me um
just a little bit uh
all right let's see if I go back here
okay yeah that's okay that's all right
so this is an ironing board
I'm in Japan no I'm not in Japan
um
yeah yeah so so I don't think I've ever
used it before but I've had it since a
long time by the way am I loud enough
for you guys the microphone is kind of
far away
is it okay should I turn myself up or
the music down
you hear me fine
really
okay well then so this is my old ironing
board that I think I've never used
before although there's some dark spots
here
maybe I got a second hand oh
maybe it's from rmt
I feel like even the ironing board or
the iron I got from RMC and I was like
oh I already have one but then I and now
I think I have two irons that I never
use
IMT gave me one I'll be jam a little bit
louder okay okay no problem
[Music]
okay
there you go
yeah
um now I turned I went on to test it and
that worked
uh but I also don't know well with this
thing here I think it's too high close
but this keeps on it keeps on coming
back down
yeah it's on even I think I want to turn
it off I wait no 10 steps ah oh well I
mean okay I guess that's okay but uh how
do I put it in the water I have to put
in some water is it here I wonder
or that's a small opening
[Music]
because I pull it up or
foreign
[Music]
by the way I think
about this one second hand when I had no
money because there's a the person
there's a price sign on there but it
makes no sense because it's a 690 as if
it's 690 Euro
but I don't think this ever had the
value of 690 Euro
yeah anyway it should work uh so wait
did you tell me where to put the money
it does
it's just talking about money I'm going
to put the ladder is it here
that's a weird way to pour it in
[Music]
Spanish
maybe it's chilling but then that means
it's like like from the Ice Age
then that's like from the Ice Age yes
it's there okay well I do have like a
water container thingy over there
[Music]
heavy heavy what's up it doesn't spill
everywhere
[Music]
to put it in
this I can like get rid of it but it
feels like
wait it kind of extended
all right I'll try
we're in
Bakery
what's that oh it works like what it's
just pouring in water but
I don't know I just got so excited
oh
yeah baby
how much can I get in there
huh
are you going overflowed we didn't start
that coming everyone saw that coming uh
get it out of the side
wonderful
more
[Music]
exit
close why does it not close now
anymore
Mommy
what what is Dazzle
[Music]
it's like slightly open you see that
why is it slightly open usually you
unplug
let's save it oh I accept duct tape it
yeah worst case
are you guys all welcome to Backstreet
me today it's not my first time till
iron something I mean I just don't
generally do it because I'm too lazy
but there have been times in the past
where I've attempted it before but I
guess it's fine like you hold it like
this normally and it doesn't flow out so
I guess it's okay but I think it was
closed before
[Music]
it's not supposed to
did you hear the sizzling sound probably
not but
okay I just accidentally um I mean
that's what it's supposed to make it's
we're testing it
this is a test run it's supposed to make
a sizzling sound there's so many so many
hairs you heard it yeah it's like ASMR I
just got a ASMR mic for this
foreign
[Music]
don't be scared for me it'll be fine
so I have the
banana tea cups
[Music]
yeah wait what's the dial zone so the
water one is on zero
so I guess we're like
turning that to
[Music]
all right I turn it back to zero and now
I can't turn it around anymore it's a
really old iron oh my God
[Music]
[\h__\h]
but it's it's did you see do you see
that
foreign
[Music]
up
there's like a
oh there's a mechanism there
was rolling around over there here this
one I guess now
now I should be able to push it
[Music]
but honestly I still can't turn this
wheel oh wait no no okay okay you just
need the right grip so we do that maybe
on like
on one because it doesn't go any further
and then down here what's this song it's
on two there's like one two three and
we're on two I mean I guess it's a good
starting point right oh
[Music]
okay the water is
water is like
oh you see it
no you stand yeah
let's see
I'm getting I'm getting hot I'm getting
hot in here oh my
okay so I have a a couple of clothes
[Music]
um some I mean it's it's stuff that I
either don't wear outside or
I've
uh yeah
I guess that's it so don't worry about
that should be all right
um
and it's mostly white clothes for some
reason
I guess it's because it's like like
blouses are often white like white is
the choice for blouses often and those
get so wrinkly so I have some blouses
and I have
one skirt that I never wear I have some
pajama stuff
and I have some merch
[Music]
and yeah um also one thing I realized I
had to like bring out my old like summer
clothes and so on because
um
winter clothes my winter clothes are
like usually like you know things like
you don't have to iron like
sweaters and fluffy even fluffier
sweaters so
let's turn off the iron it's fine
wow we're gonna do it now we're gonna
get started so we're actually gonna
start with these
we're going to start with these they're
not that wrinkly but I guess they could
use like a little
a little
you know a little help
[Music]
not that bad
we won't see a big difference but
there's I have some stuff that's like
insanely wrinkly okay so basically
[Music]
I don't want to ruin this one though
example
[Music]
okay
all right
well then so I mean as I said I'm not
uh it's okay
not a hundred percent new but this
um okay some water is on there now
that's that's that's a good thing
so see how flat that looks beautiful
turn it around no right do we really
need to do that
the warm in there
there's my screaming concern you does it
worry you don't worry about it so I
think this is uh the other side
[Music]
uniform and
I feel like when I do that on top the
other layer is getting wrinkled
you know what I mean
how do you not do that
flat everywhere let's let's be flat
[Music]
never any process for real okay I see
some like
potatoes
here there's like some wrinkles there
can we get the look rid of those that
would be good
[Music]
sweet sweet steam I see you steaming but
you're steaming upwards shouldn't you be
steaming downwards on my clothes
foreign
[Music]
that's what I was saying now on the
other side I have like really strong
folds
[Music]
that helps me by the way
no Moody kid
it's a an impossible game is this like
hard mode can someone turn it on to easy
mode
that looks nicer that looks nicer
and the other side also a seed
shimmering through
I think I think
I think
[Music]
okay man I mean
in comparison you might not see all the
details
oh do you see it I mean I guess you see
it somewhat clearly yeah you can see
there right
I'm not bad wow
okay okay then I mean I'm kind of
already satisfied with that oh what did
I spy with my little eye
this this is no this is not acceptable
it's not acceptable
I mean I've seen my mom do the following
but I don't think it works here because
the the tip of the board is too big for
like this to really fit
because otherwise I would just pull it
over
but with shirts and so long we can do
that we can like pull it up like like
put clothes on the iron basically you
know what I mean game journalists
it works if it works it works
[Music]
oh oh this also this crease oh that's
bad that's a bad one a bad boy
[Music]
you're a bad boy aren't you what I do
with you
what do I do with you huh
get out of there you're not welcoming oh
it's got weaker it's got weaker the HP
is falling we broke their defenses
Now's the Time cast cast a Mystic art
casted
it's fainting
won't be here for much longer and the
world will finally be free
from the creases and the crisis at the
creases the creases the creases mostly
oh yeah I'm okay with that and now you
know what you do then is I guess you
fold it nicely I was just gonna throw it
to the side
turn it back around
crease decreased
wow looks okay
this was just you know cast object
how do you fold the sleeve like this
I mean where did I put this
there okay this one's a little bit dirty
for some reason probably because I did
cooking and stuff on it
wash it
washed this one before ironing it
okay okay I'll wash this one next time
now let me
let me bring in
one of the more difficult cases
um
it's already turned around but you might
see what it is
[Music]
I know
foreign
[Music]
super wrinkled I have even worse cases
though
but yeah you see the wrinkles nicely
yeah yeah all right so here we'll use
super secret technique don't tell this
anyone what I've heard or I've seen this
so we're gonna
search on
the board
[Music]
all right all right oh
nicely
all right one more time to the snap wow
now look just watch and learn how those
creases that's like I'm feeling this and
the advertising for TV like from the for
an ironing board so with this an ironing
Machine and Iron with the iron 6900
you will never be worried about your
wrinkled clubs ever again you will feel
like as if it's happening in your sleep
you won't even have to lift the finger
because Kiara comes with the iron and
she will I run all the clothes for you
[Music]
this is actually ironing my clothes here
actively and effectively efficiently
do this regularly this is kind of chill
I could do like that's the streams like
this and it's kind of satisfying because
look how beautiful this turns out don't
you want one of these of your own
don't you want one of these items yeah
it's telemarket sick
wow oh what's this what's this
you know just watch close your eyes for
a moment and then open them again it's
gone it's like magic
Magic
[Music]
I'm waiting for iron
um go on the online website and go to
the contact page
[Music]
it's probably the first step or or write
me a DM
if you want to get in touch with me I am
here to advertise your irons and unless
it's not better than mine if your iron
is [\h__\h] and I don't think I can
advertise it
being honest here
okay here comes the better side why do I
have to turn them around anyway though
I'm actually curious does anyone know
what you turn the t-shirts around for or
like anything new iron really why do you
turn it around
what's the purpose of that it's not
damage like the the print if it has a
print
wow what a deal
telemarketer we deserve oh just for Dad
okay so if it doesn't have a print it
doesn't really make sense but this one's
I've washed it so many times
so it's like really faint when you'll
see you'll see
that it's not dancing
and the the T-shirt I got from
like in terms of faintness all right so
let's get rid of this
[Music]
there might be some people who have the
same shirt
wow I do really
[Music]
I'm not even really using like
special techniques yet but it's going so
well
wow
gorgeous it's gorgeous although I would
like
a little bit more power I see some like
tiny tiny wrinkles so this t-shirt has
not been using their night cream
in the night before going to sleep
me neither so I will look like this
t-shirt
soon TM
I really like
it should like be on top of that a bit
more
otherwise I'll regrett ready spaghetti
in 20 years or so
I wonder if my mom is watching this
she must be so proud of me she'll be
like oh my girl's all grown up she's
finally ironing her clothes
to call her
[Music]
but I would say she already made that
realization that I'm all grown up
because that's an awesome like uh you
know I've been I haven't already grown
up since many years ago okay
I've been paying my own bills to my own
apartment since years
[Music]
and I've been cooking my meals recently
very very
[Music]
what's the word
I don't know how to describe it I would
say there's enough reason
to call me an adult I
[Music]
said
foreign
[Music]
those are some strong creases it's like
stuck forever or not
can we fix it
um yeah what was I saying the fact that
I don't drink alcohol although I was I
will proudly
say that that's that has nothing to do
with being adult but I guess but but but
first then you know when I am with
adults and they all order alcohol and
I'm the only one who's not ordering
alcohol I do feel a little bit like
less of an adult you know
not I mean
yeah that's just kind of how it feels
like them
isn't it I'm sure some people can relate
to that
and also that I don't have a driver's
license but I have decided to a while
ago probably already told you guys to
get myself a driver's license when
someday one day in the far future when
I'm done with Holo because then I have
time I don't think I want to like do it
now because that involves studying and
all that
and I I don't know I mean some people
say it's
that difficult but I that really depends
on the person right I know people who
have failed
their driver's license tests many times
and I know some people who got it on the
first try so and I guess it also depends
on like where you do it people told me
to
although I would say that's really
cheesing if people told me to
um take the test
uh on the countryside
even if I don't live on the countryside
I should go to the countryside
but that's like that's really cheesing
it though
oh yeah and then also whether or not
you're doing it for a manual car or an
automatic car but I mean I don't see
myself ever getting myself a manual car
but then again it's like it's one day
I'm being put in front of a manual car
and it's like oh I have to drive it now
then I'm a little bit [\h__\h] in my nose
but I mean how often is that gonna
happen
hello
and then the good thing is although I
also don't really see that happening
much more anymore if I'm never like on a
road trip with someone who has a manual
car then I can be like sorry I can't
help you out buddy I guess you gotta do
the whole trip because I can't drive a
manual car you wouldn't wanna
have me drive that I'm just gonna crash
it
no but I think
[Music]
manual cars
now that I think about it I'm not sure
but oh but I did and remember you know
when I was playing like GTA and I was
like falling in love with those classic
cars
uh they're like I assume mostly manual
but right you can like change it right
maybe it's only classic car on the
outside but inside it's like
cooler
muscle cars no I don't mean muscle cars
I don't you know I I wasn't falling for
the muscle cars
I was falling for those like old looking
cute cars that have like the the luggage
thing
um outside for example
and some even have like seats outside
facing backwards like the other side of
where you're driving like this
this seats are outside facing backwards
and you drive that way the vengeance is
yeah yeah that's what I mean yeah
[Music]
I want to get one of those but but I
guess it's obviously not gonna it can't
be my only car right
that was surprised like when I was
looking those up they're not that
expensive so
that impossible
all right the other sleeve
yeah I don't know
[Music]
um
so hot I think the steam is making the
room hotter than it actually is
[Music]
perfect but I'm happy with it
foreign
[Music]
and see the beauty
although this bothers me
this is like damn this makes me into a
perfectionist a little bit but yeah this
around the sleeve where it goes down
here because it was like on the side
when I was ironing the front and the
back was kind of ignored and neglected
I'm sorry
I'm very sorry
[Music]
there we go aren't we happy now getting
the special treatment that was already
done and I came back to save you there's
a lot of like like little fur balls on
this shirt by the way I don't know if
you like see them
well I don't really care about like
getting rid of the hair of my clothes
anymore and especially not
uh
pajama clothes yeah look at that
[Music]
um
it's better than before that's for sure
here's a little bit iffy but the
shoulders are difficult you know that's
pretty faded yeah
[Music]
so I think it's still very visible
sorry sorry sorry sorry all right here
let me fold you
um so folding is another oh oh God don't
look at those creases
they don't exist folding is never like
you know thing this shirt is so big but
I guess you know like this maybe like
this
I guess so
well you have to see the front
folding
hmm
[Music]
Elsa is too big to fold properly on this
ironing board
there we go
I mean I guess there's there's other
ways to follow things right you know
those things like
I saw advertisements for it in a long
long time ago where uh there's like
these folding tray thingies when you put
the shirt on top and you just like Whack
It Whack whack and then done
I mean cool but who buys these kind of
gadgets
[Music]
and five minutes after this is straight
I'm just gonna push what's inside
wow
wow all right all right all right
[Music]
there is our successful piece number one
okay now we'll go for
kind of
hopeless case perhaps this is a blouse
that I
have maybe worn once then I washed it
then it turned out like this
and then I was like well I guess I'm
never wearing this again because I will
not iron it either
[Music]
um the worst is the sleeves because
wow
that
um but I think we can fix that
can we fix it
[Music]
are you motivated well let's start with
the main part
foreign
[Music]
marvelous
Flawless oh yeah I'll take care of you
this is like therapy for the t-shirts
for the blouse
it's been in pain for so long it's been
neglected and ignored for so long
but I'm finally showing you how to take
care of yourself
oh
this will be like night and day you
won't recognize yourself after this
you'll be like thank you Dr kiwawa
thank you I can finally go outside again
I can finally love myself again
Maggie you've changed my life
I want to glow up yeah oh wow
wait ah you don't even see that part
I'll show you in a second oh my God I'm
trying to do it like a bunch of this
point right now so we can see a nice
before after but I would like some water
there can I like
by the way I wish I could like go
on request
like that let me turn that up if I can
oh yes I can okay some two now
give me some of that sweet sweet Steam
[Music]
um
okay I need some backseating
it's not button to steam I don't know it
just goes on its own like I guess try
pushing the button
I don't know
what's happening
Bright Water I don't have like a proper
sprayer
all right it's okay
I only have like a sprayer that goes
like it has like one hole so
try higher temperature all right are we
gonna go to the max
[Music]
it's cooking
oh yeah
I feel it's boiling
so satisfying
this reminds me of my childhood when my
mom was ironing clothes
it was always like kind of smell so nice
and then having the freshly ironed
clothes
[Music]
oh
like heaven Almost Heaven
that's Virginia
[Music]
I think if I want this part to become
better then I have to like go all over
it so just
a second okay better like this
second
appreciate
this difference oh
[Music]
oh
I have to look at that oh
[Music]
okay okay so let me turn this a little
bit over here
and I'll focus on this part now
and your world has opened up
maybe I can motivate some of you guys so
iron your clothes alongside me
[Music]
for household things I have to clean my
apartment today at least a little bit
it's been a [\h__\h] mess there's like
cat hairs everywhere
insane
wow
and immediately it's like a different
shirt
and now you'll think oh I can wear this
now finally
yes I can
white blouse there's like a million
white flowers out there I don't think
this is like the most recognizable face
[Music]
art flowers and
I did oh oh my God I can't believe this
part
you guys could see like a close-up
because this is
mind-breaking [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
I'm gonna try to get like up here
[Music]
like
I don't know
I'm a genius I was born for this I'm a
talent for ironing who would have known
although there's just this crazy oh what
is he's doing here
don't don't go away go away
[Music]
toasty
starch spray wow what what how what star
spray what how do I make that
I put in some flour and in the in the
water
[Music]
next level
as next up I'm not ready for that maybe
in the future okay backside
[Music]
okay close your eyes close your eyes for
five seconds or let me count
okay close in three two one
[Music]
okay opening in free
two
[Music]
you can see already it's already better
I'll make it even prettier
[Music]
proper spraying thing I've only liked on
that sprays one spot one dot it will
make just one Big Blob of water
[Music]
life went to your house
comments in the chat that are saying oh
okay wow house material oh
well
I come with this iron so feel free to
buy this iron for 99.99
[Music]
and you get a freaky Walla
with your purchase to iron your clothes
right in your home
[Music]
and I wanna I wanna check my mom was
writing to me
oh I have a WhatsApp message
she didn't write to me
she's saying I'm doing so well
I know I know I am
although I do think I'm taking a lot of
time but you know I'm just starting out
I'm I'm new to this
foreign
[Music]
okay I'll be right back
let me just uh get that spring thing in
maybe
[Music]
foreign
it looks like
it looks like they're
might still be some oil in it
[Music]
because if you remember I
I use this
[Music]
um as an oil sprayer for my airfryer
stream
and uh
[Music]
I see like little like oil drops in
there
I refilled it with water to use it for
my plants okay maybe not even afterwards
I was probably not the best I think
[Music]
I'm kind of happy with this all right um
let me see
oh yeah the side knees a little bit and
then we do the
way
arms
which
are gonna be really difficult
[Music]
but
I'll do my best
[Music]
that's why I approve myself to the whole
world and everyone will have a new image
of me they'll see me as the wife who
screamer
[Music]
thanks for the memberships
foreign
the real girlfriend experience streamer
a girlfriend I'm trying to be your wife
then yeah I don't think your girlfriend
is gonna be ironing your clothes
[Music]
okay let's see what we can do with this
I mean it's
extent it's supposed to look like this
because of you know there's like a
ribbon here that like pulls it together
so it's a little bit puffy
um
so I would like some backseating on this
from my mom ideally oh
[Music]
spread it out a little bit but then here
I definitely have the problem on the
other side
probably gonna mess it up oh yeah I mean
like stretch it stretch it
foreign
[Music]
okay okay
holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] I'm not even using the chips
I'm using the full surface
oh
foreign
what is that
[Music]
they also all wear like these kind of
white clothes in the Mamma Mia musical I
could I could perform there now what
about this part
I don't know if you can really iron this
I don't know if you can improve this
[Music]
foreign
thingy like like um like a it doesn't
look like an iron you know what I mean
cloves steamer but I also don't use that
one I bought them on thinking that if I
get that one it will surely be more
likely that I will higher my clothes
with the steamer just because it's
easier you don't have to bring out the
ironing board but no of course I never
used it it hasn't even been unpacked and
I've had it since a long time oh the
irony
had it since a long time but
wow so satisfying
I found joy in life again if you feel
like life has nothing to offer you
anymore and you're like
life is [\h__\h] miserable it's
depressing sorry irony here's a new
hobby you need a new hobby I'm in your
goddamn clothes for once son
hahaha
[Music]
no
foreign
[Music]
oh go away
so I'm scared it's like a game just like
in my gameplays yeah it's not perfect
but whatever
um this really bothers me it doesn't go
away
go away
with while I'm fixing that I'm making
problems elsewhere [\h__\h] it
Mommy
mommy your t-shirt from work is ready
oh
I I can tie your tie as well yeah yeah
oh look look whoa
I uh not ironed iron I mean Iron also
not for Facebook look the volume has
increased this is the deflated one this
is the
fresh one wow
again well at the same time I'm making
it unwearable by streaming it
ah thanks Mommy you're welcome
okay let me do the collar before I go
over to the because there's
[Music]
this
ah this is from the brand I always used
to order from
ah
on on Tower ball
[Music]
a long time ago I found this um this
brand that was just everything I wanted
in terms of clothes because I couldn't
really find
um the clothes I wanted in Austria
and and even during the time when I
lived in Japan
I think this was mostly while I was
living in Austria when I would visit
Japan the course I found there and I
felt like a little bit too much I wanted
something in between I found this brand
old taoba that I loved so much but it
was also kind of like a hint and miss
hmm But I trusted the bread but however
now it's like so not worth it Austria or
Europe I think specifically Austria
though in this case made it even more
difficult recently to order things from
anywhere outside the Schengen area I
guess
[Music]
um I haven't been really needing to
order things from overseas that much
anymore thankfully I used to do that a
lot though
I used to order
so many things from taobao
it's like a Chinese Amazon
or just so much from there
but now even if I wanted to now it would
be absolutely the worst experience ever
because they add
Ed yeah Europe in general but just a
while ago Austria I think added even
more to that
so oh yeah actually I saw my friends
posting how they got messaged from like
their AliExpress sellers
telling them that all those sellers stop
shipping to Austria now
Austria specifically
because this is the absolute
like worst [\h__\h] ever like they can't
they're making they're losing money by
sending things to Austria the sellers
and I guess also we as the buyers
[Music]
tumors
they don't shipped what the [\h__\h] is
Officer doing man I mean I don't really
need it anymore but there's so many
people who now don't even know where
they get all those things they need from
because there's something there's many
things that you don't even get here
yeah more things that are just 10 times
expensive here
so shitty it's so shitty
okay here we go that looks already
pretty good let's make it
apart a little bit
guys I would also say it's a little bit
like counterproductive it's like too
much it's like the people who decide
that
they never ordered something before from
overseas
I feel like the obviously some countries
are being like more
targeted
than others
wow
I'm making it more complicated it's
really shitty I'm suffering with my
friends I'm feeling with them like I
don't really
need that stuff anymore but my friend
um my best friend you know she saw I'm
I'm going to Japan she asked me to bring
something from from Japan
that she can't get anymore now from
Austria
I said okay but next up I'm going back
soon bring you something next time
[Music]
although eventually they want they might
want to like everyone's gonna ask me and
I'm gonna be like smuggling things
through no no no no no I can't do that I
don't want to end up in like a jail
well I've been watching like um
some videos on I guess especially like
uh in Japan when like people arrive at
the airport it's like a Japanese
um
document like online YouTube documentary
series like a news program but for
YouTube
where they stop uh people at the airport
who are like
smuggling food and they're mostly food
mostly food
through the airport for their luggage
and then the dogs you know they walk
around they smell it but even even
without the dog they even catch people
and I just wonder
ah the front iron
or maybe not
oh I touched it yeah it's it's a hot
area
um what was I saying
[Music]
so then yes sometimes you I mess up and
then you have to ah yeah but I mean a
certain amount of souvenirs is just fine
I'm not gonna like overdo it but I just
wonder like some people I saw in in
those videos they bring they bring
mountains so food like sausages and
cheese and freshly cooked food and
vegetables like mountains mountains
and and the whole suitcases are filled
with it and and you just ask yourself
are you [\h__\h]
what there's no way that you don't
really know that that's obviously not
allowed
[Music]
but what
what every time I see it I'm like how
can you act to be we know you're not
that stupid it's so obvious and the
signs are everywhere on the Japanese
airports like no meat no meat I don't
know about other airports
but on the Japanese ones it's written
there very obviously
[Music]
BRB
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
you've seen those before my um
my my pumpkin carving stream remember
okay
[Music]
I took off the gloves because I thought
that
if I open the door in my pajamas and
then like like this like
[Music]
who wears that at home what a weirdo
what's up
girl why does she wear clothes is there
any good explanation that I could have
why I would be wearing this
any any ideas
and there's one thing I stuck in there I
can't
I got a rash avoid summer but I'm inside
bad circulation
[Music]
laundry and but are there actually
people who wear
loves when they do their laundry like
gloves like this
hand condition oh yeah maybe I have like
uh some kind of skin disease that I'm
trying to contain I guess
and don't explain yeah confused them
just let them wander after they leave my
door what was that girl doing
what was she doing
action okay I have some some serious
business to do here I'm playing a game
that's called be coming Iron Man
I shall become Iron Man
all right I'm pretty satisfied that this
is like a million times better than it
used to be it's not perfectly some
creases are like what the [\h__\h]
what what
see those
what is it with you
how many times they have to tell you
you're not welcome here
off
foreign
most satisfying
weirdest but funniest from the concept
uh handcamp streams
love this like I look over there on the
camera and it looks so nice
satisfied
it's like the same amount of satisfying
or even more than peeling off a film of
something a plastic film of something
real
foreign
[Music]
did I not do the back why does it look
so wrinkly again
pretty sure I did the bed hmm
the Bamboozle like you iron something
and then your eye on the other side and
then the
ah and on the other side
the sprinkly again
but I don't mind I'll go over you as
many times as you want
come on come here
[Music]
is one second son even though this is a
girl's shirt
let's just imagine
just imagine
but if you close your eyes
[Music]
okay I will actually consider buying an
ASMR microphone for this
oh
so nice
because of the sizzling sound and the
steaming sound
oh yeah
okay
all right so now what's left to do is
some uh folding this back boy
what's that song again from red velvet
so I'm gonna do like maybe sideways you
can see more
um okay let me remember it's like um
half
off like this
um the arm is like I feel like this
foreign
[Music]
if I wear this again in summer I'll have
to iron it again
anyway so how about this I mean this is
probably not the best way but please use
a hanger no
where am I gonna hang it up I only have
my winter clothes out right now oh this
looks like [\h__\h]
the arms go in the back
in that case then
I don't know
I need to watch the falling tutorial
[Music]
torture no this is
this is really sad satisfying
period
how about this how about this and then
yeah what what like a pancake oh a
little bit lopsided but
oh
wow I mean that's not perfect I can't
waste my time any longer with this one
amazing
next one next one
interesting one
it's like also a pajama thingy
it's turned around now but it's
basically the same
it's just like a little
little t-shirt kind of a summer pajama
because
it's very airy it's very thin but you
see the wrinkles and yeah right I have
the same one in black too
much
[Music]
okay
are people gonna draw me in this and fan
art
[Music]
all right here we go it's very thin
fabric compared to what we just had
we're just working with oh wait I should
wow it already looks so different
foreign
again
only wearing that no wearing more than
that
so we go
[Music]
not yet it's too early
happy birthday almost divided
thank you for the rest of the chat
[Music]
I thought you were purchasing the Island
right now with the red super truck but I
guess not okay
but for your birthday I I offer you one
coupon
for ironing one Set uh of course
oh this is my little something
I might have told the story before tell
me if I told the story before it feels
familiar that I've told them before but
um I used to like work as a trainee
well when when I use back in the day
when I used to work as a trainee in a
hotel
uh it was a hotel where um
there were some like business guests
and then there was this like American
American dude
who was here for business I guess
um and
he
uh at one point I think I was working
for the reception at that point
but I was a trainee so I was kind of
like in like doing everything
and
um
he was gonna
ask for some laundry to be done and I
said it would take too long because yeah
our laundry people I guess they're like
done for the day so uh you need it like
sooner right blah blah blah and he he
asked me if I could do it and I'm like
oh
I'm I'm look at me I'm like a I'm a
teenager who's a trainee here you really
want to entrust this to me I'm not I'm
not like in charge of that but he's like
ah it's okay it doesn't have to be
perfect I I'll pay you some some you
know tip I'll give you some tip money
and if you try and I'm like uh
I might ruin your clothes though
you sure look at me don't remember when
you're close I don't really think I'm
good at especially because the suit
I think I think
um he probably only gave me the shirt
like I also ironed her pants
but you don't really
do you Island the top of the suit like
the jacket I'm not sure anymore it's too
long ago but I felt very nervous about
it and I didn't want to ruin it but I
did tell him like I might ruin I mean
I'm gonna try my best but I can't
promise too much
yeah not really right yeah if anything
like you bring it to a dry cleaner
um so yeah I warned him several times
and then he was still in like like
totally chill about it he's like oh well
sure I trust you I'm sure you can do it
so
um I did it and I did it like in the
back office I brought out the ironing
board
[Music]
kind of um
an empty day anyway there were not many
it wasn't there wasn't much going on
that's ironing it I didn't
but I also
really did him a favor
[Music]
all right I don't think it turned out
that well but I also didn't make it
worse
so I brought it back I got my tip and he
seemed amused
[Music]
foreign
maybe I got like 50 bucks or so from it
which for training for a trainee
that was incredible
I'm like oh bring it up I cannot
remember you close
if you need anything sir it wants to
know in a hotel once you know that
someone's like
um open to tipping
in a hotel I feel like you know
depending on which
um apartment you work you're less likely
to receive tips but yeah once you know
once you know you want to like be super
nice to that person
hmm
gosh
should I iron these like these marks too
these like paper thingies
annoying
[Music]
alrighty
I also need to do this
Flats
this one's really easy to iron because
the fabric is so thin and it doesn't eat
so easily go back to its original state
that's really nice it feels really
satisfying I should have started out
with this one
[Music]
you guys wear pajamas or do you sleep
naked
or does it depend on the on the season
because for me
in the summer usually it's naked
or like pants
um Into Summer
oh yeah yeah lots of similar people I
mean you know what Mew said by once said
you know what Mio senpa said you should
not even be wearing your panties
yeah uh what was her reasoning
I think it was more of like a spiritual
reasoning but
but one thing I can definitely say I
sleep so much better without socks than
I do with socks
so
don't recommend socks
this part is really [\h__\h] up oh it's
all like going inside do you see that
but it's supposed to like open its flaps
like this
okay I will have to use the tip for that
one for real
um
I have to kind of hold it open though
[Music]
yeah
over here oh
[Music]
gorgeous
gorgeous gorgeous gorgeous
[Music]
okay yeah that works really nicely
wow the straps are finally looking
normal again
foreign
[Music]
I hope those people in Fire Emblem are
not like dying while I'm doing this
they told me oh we need to move on
it's time for war and I'm like sorry
guys I
already have an appointment for like
ironing some stuff can you can you
please wait
mama you guys can go ahead I'm joining
one day later yeah yeah priorities
it's so much cuter cuter
Kawaii Saga
now Tana
[Music]
but they say Iron Man is a hero so
ironing my clothes I feel like that's
part of the job right part of the job
description
laughs
Phoenix
oh oh actually I guess I got some
practice recently from ironing because
of my iron beats stream remember
I got a tiny baby iron
[Music]
that might actually be useful for this
part but yeah
[Music]
let me know
you're told ah I'll be back OBS OBS
please
I was just talking to myself
hello and we're back okay wonderful
stuck
[Music]
to me while I'm doing the ironing
you better clean up your room
wait that's not life that's that's mommy
again I'm so confused
getting I'm getting mixed signals from
you guys
what do you want from me
[Music]
okay I'm happy with that
let me turn it around
[Music]
a little bit up here maybe the grills up
there are a little bit
messed up as well
[Music]
all right
yeah okay here we go this one I feel
like this is so cute
that like you could you don't don't even
have to wear it as a pajama I feel like
it's even cute enough to wear outside in
the summer maybe at the beach or so
stress
is the stream stopped again
are we good
[Music]
okay
yeah it's cute it's not a chance rest
but now you're saying I can probably put
this on the toddler and it will work as
a dress
so if I ever need to get rid of this
I guess I'll give it to a toddler but
for now it's mine
[Music]
correct one and my back
I have so many I have uh
some more dresses
yeah
[Music]
I got this apartment and then they for
free get like this
oh OBS OBS hello
let me iron
I was talking
full
[Music]
we're having a nice tea time hello
OBS not doing so well today or YouTube
I'm not sure which one it is
YouTube doesn't own an iron yeah
let me let me hear it let me iron let
tuce
I was just starting a new topic
all right we're gonna do this t-shirt
and this is lounge I guess it's also
blouse
right but um close these buttons first
do you think it will be easier if I keep
them open
maybe I should close them at least like
on the bottom one
[Music]
um
back seating moment
[Music]
uh close probably
the gloves on
[Music]
IRA
I'm only gonna close one because this is
really annoying
why
[Music]
why that's so difficult
foreign
[Music]
open open is fine
here we go all right I was just saying
before YouTube Broke My Stream again do
you remember those TV shows where
um I'm sure they have it all over the
world where
uh people would like I guess they would
sign up and with like they're not so
nice Apartments
and then tell them how they struggle
with it because they have five children
and no space for them and
and blah blah blah no money believable
blue and then they fixed their
apartments by like renovating everything
they get a whole new makeover
and then they get like the coolest the
fastest apartments or houses usually I
wouldn't I would say it's like smaller
houses or like just Apartments
yeah I would watch those and oh I was
always so satisfying too because you see
the difference of what could be what
will be
and what used to be
so nice
so nice we have a whole channel for that
ah
pimp my house yeah it's like paint my
car but it's for houses
[Music]
um I watched that when I was young and I
always I was I was like man I'm so
jealous why does that not happen to me
to us I want them to do such a cool
makeup I mean our apartment back then
where I was living with my mom was fine
but
they made in those in those makeovers
it's just next level
it was just so cool
I'm gonna pour some water
in my mouth
[Music]
what are you guys saying move that bus
it's not a tablecloth it's a blouse have
you never seen a blouse before probably
because all your blouses are shrinkled
wrinkled as [\h__\h] baby you should give
them to me so I can iron them
[Music]
they often use a bus
say that okay
I don't know about that
[Music]
oh no then you know
I didn't like watching this one because
it was so cringe
but German TV you know in Austria we
have the same Timmy as Germany
but they had some weird ass TV shows on
RTL too and I wonder if they had this
kind of
um
um Concept in other countries TV as well
there was one where you would switch
wives men would switch wives of their
family and live with another family's
wife for a while
but yeah why I'm swap
it was always so cringe because they
would choose the most [\h__\h] up families
and you would also always feel so sorry
often for the children because it's like
damn you grew up like this you live like
this
sorry
only like once in in maybe 10 or 15
families there would be like a decent
family
that's not like pure cringe
[Music]
you know what I'm gonna open up this
this button too
that's the point yeah I think like RTL
that that was the channel that had all
these cringe shows I think they realized
very much that what they were doing was
cringe but purposefully made all these
TV shows to be cringe because it's like
watching
oh people like watching people that are
like cringier than themselves so like
just weird and and then you made me feel
a bit better about yourself maybe I
don't know we're just I don't know what
it is what makes people watch that but I
didn't watch it
I I could not
I could not force myself to watch that
stuff
yeah but there were so many of those TV
shows
hmm
why
why you may wonder I also wondered why
hot garbage yeah
really garbage
what is that
[Music]
there we go
yeah that's why that's why that TV
channel has this kind of like reputation
here
[Music]
has that reputation that they only make
these [\h__\h] shows so it's like a meme
in the German speaking countries it's a
meme dance oh yeah you know RT L2 is the
shittiest TV channel
that we have
but I think that was also the one that
would occasionally Show anime like
those are Tales who were I was a long
time ago that I watched actual TV
they just have a
um a comparable TV channel that would
show [\h__\h] like that
[Music]
MTV is like a whole nother level
Spain is
[Music]
hi
what
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait
I I that's how you say it though
probably right probably even pronounce
it correctly
[Music]
oh man oh man putting myself in trouble
here
who said the player play play or reply
my chat stopped moving on the one I'm
actually looking at telefinco I
pronounce it
quickly
oh man tennis
[Music]
I pronounced it well but apparently not
correct
[Music]
so what is there one in an American TV
channel that does that stuff I only saw
the
single TLC
I think I heard about that before is it
also where they play like Dr Phil and so
on
elsewhere like oh God that's so
nostalgic about like people would
uh it was like an audience right and
then the main stage and then people
would come in one by one and talk about
their problems there was always like one
theme right
and they would come in and then but
they're all kind of [\h__\h] up it's
always like a [\h__\h] up topic like I
don't know what what was that
what about
those yeah
oh yeah an intervention shows
I have to I have to admit I think I
watched those two
um but those shows where they do like
pregnancy tests
yeah you are not the father and they're
like
I told you [\h__\h] I [\h__\h] told Dylan
and she's like having a an existential
crisis oh my
who is the fun
Beach
[Music]
so dramatic
it's not falling back on me
Lauren was a family bonding show back in
the day
[Music]
oh yeah I think I know which one you
mean
oh those Pregnancy Test shows and then
they
it takes so much time on purpose they're
like they have the test in their hands
and they're like for for all [\h__\h] 10
minutes they're like I'm now gonna
reveal
if you are the fighter or not
but before let's first talk to the child
but before let's talk again to the guy
oh no but before let's take care of the
lie detector test is that really this
[Music]
TV is so [\h__\h] up
the light attention
do you love her
have you slept with someone else
[Music]
oh man is is Jimmy
the child of so and so or someone else
oh man
but I was so young when I was watching
those
I don't think I could bear that [\h__\h] now
poor Jimmy he just wants a mom and the
dad man
I think
um
there was one show I was really into but
this is probably like 500 years ago
um
it was like kind of a smaller studio and
it was like always one person like
hidden behind some kind of like
hiding door that would you would you
would kind of see the silhouette
um of the person and then there was like
the the MC the moderator and then there
would be like one or two people who are
inquiring something but what was that
about
too many creases
no it was mostly like like scandalous
kind of stuff like again probably most
of the problems were about whether or
not that person was cheating on them or
not or
whatever hours for it no it wasn't blind
date no no no no no no no no no no no no
it wasn't something positive nice like
that
cheaters then oh did you guys have that
too
you guys have it too of course of course
you guys have it too it's like it works
everywhere huh
[Music]
okay one of these shows that I really
momentarily enjoyed and I was I was torn
between enjoying it and not enjoying it
and also being embarrassed for enjoying
it and feeling like I shouldn't be
enjoying this because this is crap is
Big Brother
ah so many of the candidates were so
shitty
oh oh yeah it's like a guilty pleasure I
guess so
yeah they're still doing a big brother
right
um and some of the Big Brother Seasons
they would have the setup where
um they have like a really really
luxurious apartment and then there's
like a fence and then there's the really
shitty apartment they have like cold
showers and they have shitty beds or
sleeping sleeping bags or whatever
shitline dad and it's cold and they just
have the worst [\h__\h] worst food as well
and then you know you have to get
popular
and and I think you also have to I think
the audience vote so you have to be
popular and then you will be moved to
the popular side uh
oh yeah
and also like uh always those couples
that was formed and then there would be
drama
[Music]
big brother but I was always thinking
since I've joined follow life then I was
like
a whole life
a big brother whole life Edition like a
it can be a parody it probably can be a
parody
big brother kind of thing
but I guess that's just like
living like living in in one house in
house but obviously we can't have like
camera streams on 24 7 but but it could
be like a skit you know like
I was thinking we should we should do uh
if we ever do like Ian hologram we
should do like a skit like that a big
part of skin and I also want to do like
a like a like a parody of like the
office for example
I want what do you call those what do
you call that category mockumentary I
want to do a mockumentary skit
hey
it would be so funny
nah
oh yeah Flavor of Love was the worst
[\h__\h] ever
I hated Flavor of Love with my guts
I was just ugh
so much cringe like you know all those
[Music]
99 of the participants you cannot tell
me that they really weren't in it for
the money and the fame my back
yeah
there's solid things
Public Enemy Number One
I'm the Public Enemy Number One oh no
oh man I'm making I'm getting oh God I
think that I feel like the FBI is coming
to shut me up they're one they want to
silence me ah
[\h__\h] hell man
I think I'm pretty done with this shirt
like the the puffy arms are so difficult
I need some help there
months besides that
is
[Music]
I mean the FBI shouldn't be targeting me
they should be targeting Big Brother Tel
Aviv television television programs
dance not me
that's the real evil
[Music]
but honestly like uh
after a while some people would be in
this big brother houses for so long like
you would wouldn't you feel like so
miserable
[Music]
they were really miserable
I watched like maybe one show oh but you
know what I was really enjoying
and not feeling like a guilty pleasure
about
it was called pop stars
there was this German TV program I think
I'm Pro post even
um called pop stars it's like in Germany
uh the more popular one was Deutschland
Superstar Germany looks for the
Superstar about pop stars did that one
show was looking for like usually one
solo artist but popsters was making
groups they don't like making like
pop groups and sometimes it would be
girls sometimes it would be boys
sometimes I think it would also be mixed
hmm
yeah and usually the groups that would
come out of it were always unsuccessful
there was just one group that was
successful
hmm yeah it's like a idol Survival show
um I don't think
oh yeah no
no successful one and then so many times
they had no success and then after many
years they finally managed to get one
good one again which was Mom Rose and I
was a big fan they were good but then
they just found it after a while too
but I was always streaming I was always
watching that I was like one day I won
the audition from pop stars and then I
want to be part of this group yeah I
want to be part of a pop group like now
you know never happened though
I'm I'm here
I can make music
I always looked after that and the
auditions are always the most fun part
to watch though but I think that's also
with
um
what are those shows the ones that are
like
Talent rather than
ah Again
YouTube sailing again sure
that's fine now
yeah like X Factor
[Music]
America's Got Talent yeah stuff like
that
I really like pop stars specifically
although I feel like the members they
chose usually I was really unhappy with
those choices oh I think we're out of
water by the way oh yeah I just know
this that's why it's not working so well
anymore okay
come on I'm okay with this shirt it
looks all right better number four I
mean look look at that
wow and it's just a normal ass blouse so
I can't even like
can't be in trouble wearing this I would
say it's
it's a special sleeves it's just a
normal blouse
hey
so let me fold this how do we fold this
I should probably button it but hmm
the one problem I see that you guys
probably don't see is that there are a
lot like really really tiny tiny tiny
tiny tiny tiny
[Music]
mini Cat hairs
I'm here
[Music]
oh well
I'll have to roll over it with the
hair remover what the [\h__\h] is that
[Music]
without water it really doesn't work
well anymore at home
okay
oh it feels so good it feels like the
clothes get bigger when you iron them
huh
feels like there's so much more surface
foreign
[Music]
okay I'm running I maybe got ironing
down more or less but folding the cloaks
maybe I was asking in the beginning of
the stream who who buys those kind of
folding gadgets maybe I need it
because that's the one problem that I
seem to have here but normally I would
hang this blouse anyway
I'm just folding it for now
and I had most of my like top clothes
the bottom side
either fold or actually I have like a
um like a comp compartment for hanging
up uh pants now too
um
not at all
I can't I can't fold this [\h__\h]
I mean it's probably here it looks it
looks acceptable
something's off but
it's okay
yay look at that wow
okay oh
I think with that I will unplug
the fire records no let me just turn it
off normally here
[Music]
there we go
um in in two hours or so yeah
oh not even completely two hours I have
ironed one two three four four things
okay that's probably a little bit too
much time but I was like talking a lot
and and I wasn't even using all the
tricks up my sleeve and there's there's
more more tricks up there
uh let me let me sit down for a sec
and nothing burned yeah I didn't even
need that much help from you guys
[Music]
it's so unusual
I was rolling around the microphone it's
so unusual for me to stream when the sun
is shining it's so bright what the [\h__\h]
ugh
I'm not used to this
the
afternoon sunshine damn
what is that bright orb in the sky
kind of fall down upon us
gosh I felt so hot let me take all these
gloves now
uh
[Music]
that's all
[\h__\h] what's up
good I'm gonna take a shower jump into
the pool
Pond or something
oh oh
boy hey I did some I did some productive
work through the stream again once again
[Music]
a thing that I would not do unless I was
streaming
and I think
of course really productive efficient
thing
I'm gonna do my dishes next no no
because I have a dishwasher why wouldn't
I do my dishes now that I have a
dishwasher
my older Apartments before before Holo
I may not have had a dishwasher
but I don't want to go back to that
lifestyle no thank you
no thank you
foreign
[Music]
like show you much because
it makes no sense like unless no camera
but that makes even less sense in my
opinion
no I like to show you the things that
I'm doing and if I can't show you then I
don't really think it's worth doing it
you know what I mean sorry was just
removing some
some hairs from my microphone
[Music]
oh yeah you couldn't even hear me well
if I did the vacuuming stream
and Broadway stream oh yeah that's
something I still have to do because I
have those embroidery sets
scrubbing the toilet
chat brushing stream I would do that but
my cats are you know I can't show them
on camera because they're they're too
famous you know doesn't it would it
would make all the paparazzis uh come
and try to find them and they wouldn't
be able to live a normal life anymore
[Music]
brushing huh
uh I don't know about Dad that's kind of
um
challenging it isn't it why is their
hairs on my my cup again
I don't want to drink the water
ah
okay I'll take a first candy then
there's no hairs on the fruit candy
that's for sure
um
turned it to zero
I have I have a lint roller and I have
one thing that's like way better than
the lens roller in terms of
um you know with lint rollers you have
to constantly buy new paper new sticky
paper and
there's one thing that I can really
recommend I don't know what they call it
though but if you have cats eventually
you will probably stumble upon it it's a
roller where
it's it's not sticky paper but it's just
and I need to okay give me one second
it's not sticky paper but uh
[Music]
it's just somehow
collect stuff the cat hair by just
rolling over but it's also just Fabrics
it's not velcro either
it's not gel either no nothing I guess
yeah like a static brush static roller
yeah probably
and then it collects it in the back
yeah yeah yeah
that one's um good because you don't
have to keep on buying new paper
and it works good for most it doesn't
hands on some Fabrics it doesn't work so
well
but for example on like a sofa
on my sofa it works perfect
so good
[Music]
so if you have I think it also works
with dogs if you have a dog or a cat or
cell and have that hair problem then I
recommend it to you
mmm perfect
all right guys I'm gonna read some super
chats but I can't stay for too long
because I have um I need to clean my
apartment and then later
someone's coming over to help me with
some stuff
hmm
music change okay let me unplug it now I
guess
[Music]
we are being I have to walk around the
whole thing
[Music]
here I am
it was a nice zatsu ironing stream
wasn't it
[Music]
good opportunity for some conversations
too
[Music]
um
you will write the content it's always
good thank you
um did I read the
[Music]
the ones before yesterday's Fire Emblem
stream
that's probably why I have to start
right the unarchived karaoke ones
just yeah start from Christmas sounds
like it's ages ago but though it's very
recent actually
actually Christmas was just very
recently
okay
[Music]
let me put up the thumbnail
oh I actually also have to
um yeah
I actually have to record some stuff
today too
so that management does not Bonk me
[Music]
so I might just read those ones and then
leave it at that we'll see how many they
are
[Music]
those are quite a bunch if I get done
with those that's already good
it was actually Christmas because I got
my own customers in the morning next day
oh nicer
oh my cat no more cat merch I'm a cat
merch
[Music]
I can read the days pretty quickly oh
you think so
all right I'll read the undercut ones
first
the game of Crete Duncan
and take a spunky thank you for the
pinky Merry Christmas Kiana 2022 is
finally over but what a year it's been
yeah
I'm glad I was able to spend a year with
you and kfps
are you so serious about it
and I'm excited to see what you'll do in
maybe we'll forecast you ladies will get
really cute new ideas
[Music]
but no you for you it's like you um
traveled back in time
assuming that it's Christmas but it's
actually really the 24th of 2022
[Music]
it was in 2020 free at the end of
January
[Music]
I mean it was supposed to be the
Christmas of 2022 but delayed
to 2023
then then we have two Christmases this
year
[Music]
yeah so
too had to clear that up but besides
that Merry Christmas to you today catch
monkey happy New Year
I wonder if you already sent one like
this
on the 24th of December we're still on
the 25th or so
just repeat it yourself or if this is
your first one and you always knew you
always knew this was gonna happen
[Music]
against monkey
that could thank you thank you soon
um Schneider thank you for the pinky
Duncan I can't believe I missed the
tales of arise but now yesterday because
of moving what
what at least there's now something to
watch during the next break
I guess so yeah finally karaoke again I
just hope mobile internet doesn't die
during it oh no
that reminds me
endless you know that recording I did
the other day
um someone was using their mobile
internet as well while doing that and
eventually ran out of it when we were
close to the end of the recording
and
uh
but there was no way of us like moving
it to another day so well you'll
eventually probably say it and then
understand what happened there
[Music]
oh man
you know it's Cali
[Music]
it could have been good at two though
because like
I called her several times even though I
told her
to not do it
I caught her several times using her
like uh
like I told her to get like one of those
those pocket Wi-Fi's in Japan that I use
when I travel in Japan but she just uses
her phone thingy and it's like really
expensive
and until like two days ago or so she
didn't even know
where the Wi-Fi router was in the place
where she's staying at
[Music]
when well she forcefully more or less
had to figure it out
because well without it things were not
working
[Music]
story like
go
wasn't there like some kind of story
that everybody clipped as well with
Buddha going to the like a big
big machine I think Ena maybe told the
story also do you know what I'm talking
about
what was that about
who remembers that story
[Music]
that's knowing about that
oh [\h__\h] I close the wrong tab
router here let me type that in no
that's not it
PC
[Music]
no that's not it
that's the story
she didn't know how to reset right or
something yeah it might have been that
reset louder
[Music]
no but it really reminded me of that
that really reminded me of that and
enough to help good out
ugh
finally finally she now can use the
Wi-Fi
[Music]
wasn't that her debut what's the latest
she needed help yeah really
[Music]
so long ago
technical support
[Music]
I think it was
ah whatever maybe someone will find it
for me afterwards ancient scriptures
two two and a half years ago they um was
it really that one I'm not sure about it
don't rely on that statement
okay now I accidentally closed the Super
Chat window give me a second
is Pearl School
ah Buddha can't reset the modem oh
[Music]
why doesn't that show up for me I typed
in the exact same thing and the clip
doesn't show up for me
[Music]
that's super weird is it like shadow
bunked
[Music]
delete it
EMS
type into Google
how to reset your mode into default
settings restart modem how to reset your
model video why can't I reset modem even
in holding more than 10 seconds
I just get normal troubleshooting for
the modems just normal to help
why isn't that
okay oh well whatever unless you guys
found it
was
oh well okay that makes sense too
um anyway thank you Schneider well I
think it's a good choice to keep that
one for when you need some kiwawa
content
if I'm gone for one or two days or so or
more and you can watch the finality of
tales of arise ah couple more days or
weeks or months
hurts it anymore at this point right
[Music]
oh joyous day right now I finally become
a full and proper kfp employee already
after a measly six months I can confirm
that you're kind determined and humorous
personality had a much needed and
positive influence on me
it definitely made a big contribution to
me being in a better place than before
and yet I hope I'll be able to stick
around for much much longer Viva La
Canada
also Mary post Christmas let's hope this
year's season will be even greater than
last year and less to season and all
yeah I think it's finally looking up
again
it took like what three years
but I think in most places
I don't know I don't keep up to date to
like daily cases but
your eyes oh it hurts your eyes really
you can switch to my office
[Music]
maybe you need to get used to to Bright
mode light mode
[Music]
what was I saying I forgot
all this time
I deceiving yeah yeah yeah
I think we can be hopeful
um things are like pretty much bad to
normal anyway right so
[Music]
for half a year but black people are you
here right now or are you let me show
your face show your face if you're here
Flappy Boy
[Music]
Flappy boy why are you sleeping right
now but you're in you're in my time zone
I think judging by the Euro donation
no no zombie boy what
[Music]
next time tell me
um tell me about have you found my
streaming because you say you say you've
been a member since half a year but
haven't you been watching for longer I
want to know like how how you found me I
don't know tell me more tell me more I'm
always curious to hear your guys's
origin stories
um thank you Flappy boy and yeah happy
New Year and merry Christmas to you too
thank you for the beautiful rainbow
Super Chat I don't go outside much so I
really don't see many rainbows but this
this is
the most beautiful rainbow I've ever
seen
thank you
[Music]
they're all right thank you Jay swagburg
thank you for the rights of a chat
thanks for another look at these streams
are always so much fun thanks for giving
me an excuse to procrastinate putting
away my Christmas tree for another week
you know what's a life hack you can't
have that problem uh that's a struggle
if you don't get a Christmas tree in the
first place but I do understand like
Christmas tree really adds to the whole
atmosphere without a Christmas tree can
you even say it's Christmas
hmm I didn't have one this year but a
lot I would like to have one but it just
doesn't really make much sense when you
live alone like
[Music]
um
it just doesn't make sense you know what
I mean no one's looking at it besides me
and it doesn't really
[Music]
I don't know I can't Flex my tree to
anyone
the only one who maybe would get quite
some joy out of it is the cats but last
time I had a Christmas tree
oh they don't really I didn't really
play much or at all with the tray like
my old family cat would have a blast
with Christmas trees like running around
below and
knocking things over but
um
my cats my current cats they don't
really seem to care
oh fake one works well yeah I might just
get a fake one again
I used to have
one in my
uh old old old old old apartment
um
many many years ago I don't know why
that one went I guess I threw it away
small iron one what iron you mean
plastic right
everything's iron in our minds now
they last forever yeah but unfortunately
I guess our fruit out one away was
pretty shitty though it was pretty low
quality
and now now it's about time you know
we're doing our course today choice of
course
[Music]
what I mean so maybe it's time for you
to get rid of those that Christmas tree
right
[Music]
I miss you kiwawa thank you hello if you
miss me you should you just have to come
to my streams
ah you guys not helping me the chores
like chocolate oh okay thank you
it feels like share okay okay
it's a choice day today
Tuesday
no it's Wednesday
[Music]
thank you
maybe Tuesday should be the chores day
[Music]
stream I miss you live singing hope this
has a free broadcast because I'm gonna
miss it ah shoot to my regular Camp do
this for five days can't wait to see you
again oh no regular Camp duties
what does that mean
interesting
[Music]
well I will rebroadcast it and when I
rebroadcast it I'll try to
um do it during a good sea time because
this time I think it was early morning
early early morning
um
[Music]
foreign
Hustle
rebroadcast yeah no problem guys user
account for your free Donkey shoot or
[Music]
um
hmm speaking them again thank you for a
recipe chat Merry Christmas Dental it's
great to get a late present from you I
mean on time of course that's what I'm
saying
my small cat has been crawling all over
me during the Stream
there's a Lego singing too really
[Music]
not crawling over me too
just recently there's so many people
around me are getting kittens and then I
watched this YouTube video of someone
who has two two adult cats and got a new
kitten
um like how how the first few days went
I watched a video on it again made me
feel like I wanted
[Music]
foreign
I don't
I probably shouldn't get another cat
[Music]
no they're so cute I'll have to go see
Cali's ketokato she has plenty I need to
go check them out
uh I'm excited
kitten action oh yeah
thank you spankenheim
please raise that kitten well
I guess it's not really a kitten it's
just a small cat
s
for the pinky it's always nice hearing
you thank you Mama
thank you that husband
the first time in a while I think for
karaoke stream I think so
it was nice it was fun
yeah thank you for coming by and
listening even though you know I know
the times are always kind of shitty but
it was aren't archived you have to watch
it it's on the archived
you have to start somewhere to have as
many cases yeah
[Music]
it can happen in an instant with a
finger snap
I can with one go I can adopt 20 cats
I'll just go to a shelter and get every
single cat in there
I'll just buy the whole shelter
foreign
[Music]
I recommend
uh Jeffy thank you thank you sir 956
thank you for the pinky you're killing
it for my first time really listening to
you singing a cutout stream oh I've
secretly subbed and become became a
fellow Cafe
oh yeah yeah thank you thank you I think
I can hear my fellow cronies looking for
me P.S he lifted my spirits after
dealing with a shitty day oh you're
welcome I'm glad I can do that it's
always nice when I can help someone
um have a better day
I'm just doing my thing but
it's great that it has an effect like
that thank you very much for stopping by
and listening to my karaoke I appreciate
it very much
thank you soon welcome to kfp
TV table training I know Fernandez
Jose
probably right
[Music]
um
for the rest of the chat Mary January
no if anything is Christmas
here's your present money and my undying
love but mostly money hey
hey please
the old one and awake your scary great
old ones
so Ina doesn't feel left out
what are those
Swank yet scary great old ones is that
really a thing
[Music]
that sounds more like a Halloween song
foreign tracks
[Music]
and don't worry you know you guys feel
left out
I sang the five onion rings song that's
her song
I feel like you know
everybody has that golden rings in their
hand so since Ina had that line it's
like her song
[Music]
deja vu it took me so long to read all
those Christmas and New Year super chats
and now I'm doing this to myself again
bringing myself back to that hell
voluntarily it was my choice I can't
complain
Tammy
[Music]
Community
Daisy thank you for the rest of the chat
I haven't been able to Super much over
the past year because of money stuff so
here's a belated super for related
Christmas thank you Daisy it's okay I
totally understand don't feel like
obligated or anything of course
thank you so much for thinking over me
and happy belated Christmas tree YouTube
I hope you're 29th of January was a
lovely one
for the membership thank you
Daisy here's a kiss for you
[Music]
if you want I can iron some of your
clothes too
Christmas you know
foreign
[Music]
before but it's the first time kind of
hibernating on stream and I just don't
do it very much maybe once in five years
[Music]
um
Jacob 47 out thanks for the pinky Kiana
cute oh that was quite the Assumption
quite a statement but
can anyone confirm what Jacob is saying
Jacob says Kiana cute is that true
true the fact it's true checks out
okay okay so Jacob not going to the
usual room for
[Music]
picking up things
that's my understanding
that will explain a lot
okay okay no no I'll let this one slide
so I won't let this one slide
Taco thanks for the pinky and you were
still pretty boss dazzling delightful
and divine oh thank you for the lovely
Christmas content thank you Doug Hood
yeah I ended up not doing it proper 3D
because
I know it's so exhausting and it takes a
lot of time to set up and
makes me very nervous
too another time though I'll do it again
sometime before the karaoke thing thank
you thank God for watching anyway I
appreciate it thank you
thank you for the pinky yeah you
definitely are the greatest gift to this
world we live in
oh come on
[Music]
that's too much
that's too much flattery
there's greater things like would you
say that I am greater than pizza or
greater than
kittens
more greater than
[Music]
I scream on the pool side in the summer
I don't know I wouldn't say I am
[Music]
the pool's gonna meet
your mid
[Music]
oh thank you thank you okay I think
that's kind of an exciting duration Jeff
you got your ticket you made like a real
ticket or or a streaming ticket Jeff
Jeff Jeff
memories
there's like barely any kfp got like a
real ticket so I need to know did you
get a real ticket or streaming ticket
I mean streaming ticket's fine too
tell me Jeff
I'm looking at the chat streaming oh
okay
that's fine too yeah barely anyone got a
real ticket
I'm so sad
well streaming will be fun too though
[Music]
um
yeah it will be fun too I mean you know
even if you got a real ticket that would
mean that you also have to spend even
more money for flight tickets for going
to Japan in the first place and all that
brutal yeah
they should like like
is already a huge venue and then it's
two days
that's already big but there's bigger
venues they can go even bigger maybe
next year because this is the second
year in a row that they're doing
makuhani
maybe next year they'll go for something
bigger who knows
I think the problem is just
uh
as far as I know like bigger in terms of
bigger venues
they don't they only have like the the
like concert Place venue
Tokyo Dome I don't think Tokyo Dawn
Budokan and so on come with
um like makuhani has with some space
where you can do an expo
you know
but then you might just want to maybe
separate it I guess
[Music]
because I think that's
so sorry
[Music]
um
there's I think one venue that would
really fit is the Budokan but they don't
have like an expo
suitable venue there I think they're all
like for concerts only
is very big though
but maybe maybe maybe
I guess you could also like increase the
days but I don't really like that either
because if they increase the days maybe
that means they're also split the
members even more
um I don't I don't want that
[Music]
or just do it like a
tour
to like those two days but
over the course of a month or two
but whatever I say it's not like I have
any say in it I just hope that they
consider making it bigger or more
accessible for everyone in in some way
next year
I would hope for it yeah
yeah there are virtual tickets yeah yeah
every time there's virtual tickets you
can get one streaming ticket
already online
one of the day one comes to take it so
bad oh you wanted like a a real one a
venue ticket well you can get a
streaming ticket for sure there are
Unlimited
[Music]
okay my great Junior
miserably happy
for the pinky thank you for the
fantastic Christmas concert Kiana it was
so much fun uh as usual you totally
rocked all the songs thank you
Rocking around the Christmas tree and
happy holidays
thank you Jim Tracy for listening in and
cheering thank you soon for using your
time for me I appreciate it very much
hope you had a lovely Christmas with
Meek
next is Valentine's Day
tie-dye TDP Danke Schoen looking for the
top 10 cushion and pets okay
[Music]
um it's almost
3 P.M now
[Music]
thank you I have to clean my apartment
it's so filthy
ah it's so filthy and I have to record
something really quick
[Music]
foreign
I bought a new cat transporter that's
what arrived I didn't buy the one that
you've seen everywhere on the
advertisement so the one with the big
window
it looks like a space
transporter no I bought like something
that's more made out of mesh but
um you can't even extend it and use it
for flights I mean I'm not planning to
bring them on a flight but the barriers
could do that and also like I saw people
using that to bring their cats to like
picnics and so on yeah
yeah an extendable
backpack and even when it's not extended
it looks pretty spacious
hmm
pretty useful you can have it as a
backpack or I think maybe also uh over
the shoulder or so
um
uh there was a stroller version but I
didn't find that one and I was like
maybe the cat really won't like it that
much anyway if she's like you know
because like if if I would use it as a
stroller and the cat sitting in there
won't it be like like rumbling and
over the stones and all that and like
I don't know I feel like they would feel
[Music]
proper like a baby stroller you know
then I don't think they would feel that
much but for that backpack that I saw
there was like a stroller version
[Music]
but that one looks really shaky like you
know like a suitcase kind of version
[Music]
so I think they would feel like the
vibrations the whole time and all that
but if it's a sturdy hydraulic one
like a baby stroller
that would surely be fine but I'm I'm
not really ready to buy that yet
I don't think it's quite necessary yet
on your back yeah album oh well for now
I bought one of those
um backpack Transporters I'll see how it
goes I'll see if jonkers likes it when
we go back to the vet
or if I'll just use the old one and go
on a an Uber we'll see
[Music]
yeah I wish I could easily take my cats
to Japan too
then I would just go anytime for long
long times
this would go for half a year or so to
get as much 3D stuff done as possible oh
well
last time
I went to the bed the day before
yesterday or so I took her in a
transporter but it was like so heavy
and it's hard to carry that one so I got
a different one
[Music]
it took three months for you cat to be
comfortable in it
[Music]
yeah I will test it before I'll see if
she wants to go in or not
how angry she gets when I put her in
[Music]
yeah okay so that's it for now and in
Germany we sell vena's in thank you for
watching me do some really normal things
it was a really mundane every day
chores yeah every day but more like once
in five years
it was fun it was very satisfying yeah
thank you guys
now you should do your chores too you
have the whole day ahead of you if
you're over that side of the globe
and if your day is more like ending then
good night and tomorrow's another day
thank you soon enjoy myself bye bye bye
bye
[Music]
Fire Emblem tomorrow
foreign
[Music]