thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
it's not pre-recorded and it just took a
while to get some other stuff set up
plus we're now both high quality oh God
right as I say that
high quality high quality
sort of thing
It's Like A Step Above some curtain
tracking stuff
anyways yeah I'm just leaning here
against the wall my arm is totally
working
oh hi yeah
uh yours is working better than mine is
it
oh I think well there's some Twisted
arms and stuff yeah
our hands like our hands aren't really
working but oh no here it goes oh there
might be some lag in the Stream I guess
today is just the Unlucky internet day
because it's been working fine in the
last two days for the stream like there
hasn't been any dropped frames from
internet lucky on the weekend yeah not
so much now even my face is lagging is
it yeah
well we're here and uh we can like turn
towards each other now and talk actually
talk to each other
[Music]
wait it's too far we're not actually
first when we were setting it up we were
like in the same program and I could
have hugged her but she said no we're
doing in a two separate programs yeah we
have to do it in two steps so we're kind
of we're together but we're kind of
separate so we can't actually like touch
or interact but here watch give us give
me a high five so they know
[Laughter]
no it's wrong don't get the wrong idea
no so close yet so far yeah oh so we did
um oh it's green again yay I did lower
the FPS of the stream to 30 so it's not
as smooth as yesterday's dancing stream
but I think it still looks good yeah
yeah it will it'll be fine what are we
gonna do today I'm in yeah so if you
guys see that thing over there or that
way oh
there I'm pointing too yeah over there
that's a a camera that's live feed and
we're gonna shoot it with uh we've got a
chicken camera no let's match it oh well
if we do I think it'd be fine I duct
taped it I duct taped it so it won't
move I'm just leaning again
the airsoft is not that strong oh okay
okay it's pretty sturdy yeah okay are we
gonna shoot and I'm gonna sing a little
bit Yeah together
oh my God broken yeah our hands are not
working very well but you'll be able to
see Kiara's gonna be the one mostly
shooting today oh really yeah because
I've already done it before and okay it
has protective eyewear
yes I I will shoot our dinner for
tonight
so we only have today we only have two
types of targets we got this uh the
white one in front that swings when you
shoot it
do the glasses like no I just tried
winking with the glasses it it did it's
uh it kind of works kind of work
and then we have the target behind which
the the red squares will actually turn
yellow when you hit it successfully but
we'll do that after we do the white one
so I usually have like this big rifle
that you can like [\h__\h] it like this
but
um I don't have that rifle today so we
only have a revolver Airsoft and a
Pistol Airsoft oh cowboy and policeman
yeah that's what I'll be today actually
it is
oh yeah we're lagging a little bit but
uh it doesn't look so bad but there
might be some frames skipping a bit
um it's not just skipping right now it's
loading
it's loading
guys are you are you hearing and seeing
us
Mosey
ah yeah it's just unlucky day for
internet it does it sometimes especially
when I use too much internet
that's why oh
okay choppy
oh no yeah
what's teapot teapot it's a code word we
use for when we disconnect from the
stream because sometimes that people
will like just type it in the chat when
it's not happening I think so anyways my
neck is getting all messed up
I'll just hide behind you
I gotta hide those legs
arms are missed
it's fine now it's looping it's really
bad and then stuttering a lot
um
struggling
internet why oh
Scottish stream maybe we should just
record a video
we could worst case
looping and out lagging crazing
uh
what about now what's his name
um my neck oh my God
did you uh recalibrate me since we're
waiting yes and do you know how no looks
we both walk us
on this side
[Music]
okay
so three two one uh wait unable to find
okay I'll highlights
thank you
unable to find thousand markers try this
again
oh I think they can see it now the
stream's working oh we thought it was
offline
all right go back no
[Music]
no
I'll sit here
[Music]
it's funny because she like kind of
drags me with her yeah oh yeah
this version doesn't have any uh yeah
physics yeah I'm gonna set it up so that
we can do only upper body tracking for
both of us no legs so both of us get uh
oh
we might may have gotten the same result
if we used
to mess up so much
I say that oh my mouth don't worry it's
just lagging okay but
is it working now guys are you here you
say say um let's just shoot stuff oh if
you hear us fun
we can show a guess
where are the croissants
[Music]
still got the magazine for this
there's a little square
should it be here or outside
I'll check it
[Laughter]
there it is
over there
you're gonna show it wait
hi it's a gun I have a gun I have a gun
I have a gun it's Airsoft oh yeah
Airsoft is really heavy for an air stop
though it's so heavy oh my God I'm
scared yeah it feels it feels Hefty can
it go like off on its own no it
shouldn't what if I drop it off sorry my
body's so messed up I don't know why
it's good yours yours looks good there
we go just just uh yeah just stay calm
mama just stay calm okay okay so I'll
show you we're just gonna get to it even
though it's kind of loading a little bit
I don't think it's that bad because it's
only they're still saying
only so I'm just like saying it okay I
like saying it too
I get you okay so the way this works
there's like this little circle thing
push it down sort of and get some of
these pallets in there oh I only got two
oh yeah
but he's not a natural
you guys know what we're talking about a
little ring thingy with the revolver
reloader whoa so you just put the
pellets in
if you have a real Revival do you also
have pedals like that you can get like a
not pellets but you do put bullets in it
instead but you can get like a little
reloader thing
like a ring like that yeah it's like a
little ring and you could just put it in
yeah
small teapot
it's very bad it's really bad there's
not really anything we could do about it
to be honest I mean I guess I could try
using my mobile hotspot but I'm pretty
sure it's also [\h__\h] it might be better
than this should I try
um
I don't trust that we could try again in
like two hours
dragon two hours reschedule another one
because we don't really have anything in
particular plant yeah we might do it
again later
all right well at least one shot yeah
wait here so you like I said you you
this is like training for a real gun you
just don't put your finger on the
trigger unless you're ready to shoot so
you hold it like this and then okay wrap
the bottom hand and the handle okay
she has the gun I have it again don't
worry guys I'm holding her in case the
revolvers too much
do I shoot the live targets or not with
both hands okay it's gonna backfire on
me look use the iron side all right
it will shoot where the where the white
dot is hopefully you gotta push hard
I'm scared
mwah
it didn't it didn't it didn't hit
anything no no that's too missed
um
did they even hear it I think it's
catching up they're saying worth a try
I don't care anyone more sure what are
you addicted now
um no I don't want to hit the target
okay I want to protect them ah there's
an attacker that was much higher was it
I wasn't looking should I go lower
yeah I think this one has a difference
it's really loud I'm so loud it's so
heavy too
what what yeah yesterday the day before
yesterday I kept on hitting the target
all right give me I'll show you yeah
you're showing me I'm not much of a
cobbler
so goalie
so good you gotta you can aim like close
one eye to aim it but I did usually when
you shoot you don't want to have one eye
open you just want to have uh both eyes
open but you can do it for now because
usually for a real gun though they say
you shouldn't aim you shouldn't you
shouldn't aim using one eye you should
have both eyes open but you can do it
while set while like lining it up
just to explain the iron sights this
little Gap should be lined up with this
stuff
okay okay you didn't tell me that
then then it should be a piece of cake
watch
it
wait my finger is too weak
watch this
oh [\h__\h] that's so happy far too I need
both feet can I use both fingers for the
trigger
and here I go and maybe I'm aiming for
Focus I'm gonna aim for the bottom one
you take a breath and hold it when then
shoot
pull the trigger away yeah
nice we got it hello let me check how
many bullets there's probably not even
that many bullets left now
did you guys see that's a croissant if
you saw that one
they're still reacting to you hitting
the target yeah yeah it's kind of slow
to catch up all right well we should
decide if we want to try again later
and I can try calling my ISP Forest case
we could just do a 2d stream I don't
think that will help it's not gonna
matter it's because my my laptop
is Wi-Fi I'm using two PCS before
anybody says anything but maybe the
internet is better later on it was a bit
fine yesterday yeah it's weird because
usually the internet is like worse on
the weekends than uh anything else
are you guys okay I mean you'll hear
just five minutes later but are you guys
okay with us maybe shutting their pants
and they're crying
losing my head look ahead let's check it
goes I'm looking for um
I'm nowhere
okay this actually look like
okay so hmm should we write it in the
chat
oh yeah but our plan is I guess I'll
just wait oh I shot the Wi-Fi
oh I'm getting closer