yes
oh no my btm is missing again
uh
chat
brace yourself this might be loud okay
brace yourself
three two one
oh my god i'm so sorry
[Music]
sorry chad
sorry it wasn't looping sorry
oopsie
[Music]
properties loop
good
that sounds like a god the god of gods
yeah my god is ancient
[Music]
yeah
ookie spooky for halloween god of god
what do you have to
say to me on this holy ghost night
my ancient wisdoms um let's see here's
my ancient wisdom i don't know how to
play minecraft but we're gonna try you
ain't that's a lie
you've become a lot better from what
i've heard and seen
eh
maybe
thanks though doing i'm doing my best
but you know
this is a game that oh man everyone's
really good
combo
oh they're saying hello to you everyone
in their own way so cute
it's not ohio though uh
no i said i said the regular one i i
decided not to be cringy for two seconds
it would have been cute because i'm sure
all of them would try to read it on
their stream and be like
i have so many i have so many melons
oh that's good all right well kelly um
today
we are what are we doing today we're
gonna get you some wings girl
[Laughter]
you want wings you want those
i like her elytra wings
electra yeah i keep seeing you know like
fly down from the sky like a wizard from
the future yeah and i'm like i want that
where are you right now i want that
um i'm hanging out in the main central
area um of like the the portal okay yes
okay one second stay there it's melon
farm yeah that's good take as many
melons as you can get
right now
here we go
because before we go to the end we we're
gonna do a little bit preparation
you betcha i'm ready yeah
and uh when i'm coming to you also with
my wings
you're not done yet go in here to the
the crafting table and then type in
mel melon yeah
melon and then the big one
to shift shift left click on it make as
many as possible
of the big ones oh
okay and then repeat that a couple times
what will they do
uh it will make you instead of
watermelon slices you will have a lot of
big watermelons and those we need for
trading in phoenix then
oh yeah i have 44.
44 okay make some more make some more
okay i mean yeah i'll just i'll tell
iris um i mean they're actually being
made a lot right now yeah yeah don't
worry about it i've taken millions of
melons out of here millions melania
and uh all of those chickens in my
inventory are vegan guys don't worry
about it don't worry about it i wanted
to give something back to sana
ah brb you do the melons and i do the
giving back to sana
gotcha
[Music]
all right guys check it check out all my
melons leave all these valuables yeah
check out cali's melons check out her
melons
hey
you said in face
i didn't say nothing madam
i i was talking about them chet what do
you say did you say it first you did say
it first oh don't
you know what chad's gonna say though
who made this area
sick onsen's so good i can't wait to
completely finish it we will finish it
at some point the spinning machine the
carnival
uh the carnival and the onsen
but even though it's not finished like
everyone was already super impressed by
it so
i'm happy they liked it i got all the
cool like stone rooms down in the dark
are you by the onsen now
i'm taking a rest i'm taking a lot oh i
will do too oh [\h__\h] okay sleep slip slip
okay good night nighty noodles good
night
uh
i was gonna say something
what was i gonna say i forgot
uh
so you got as many
melons as possible right
yes ma'am let me count how many i got um
64 64 44. i don't know how to do math
and and all of those are big melon
stacks right
yeah okay over 150 yeah we're gonna
one second i gotta give back the beds to
bales because i accidentally stole her
bed
okay
and i got lots of cooked rabbit by the
way oh um from senpai and she did
diamonds 60 diamonds yeah there's a lot
of diamonds yeah i remember didn't she
say something about being your sugar
mama
yeah yeah you learned that now with the
berries
don't make berries right you get stuck
in them
oh yeah where are you hannah didn't see
that coming i'm by the main fountain
okay um stay there yeah you're like uh
you're like an excited
excited little
mouse running around
yeah
can we eat it
okay
i have to tell you del cali the place
that we're going to today is pretty uh
dangerous um okay in many ways
uh so today you gotta be super focused
and careful and just do what i do focus
is my middle name okay i'm always super
focused guys follow me right chat i'm
the queen of focus let's go follow me
we're gonna go to phoenix then first and
trade your melons in for
uh emeralds and the emeralds are gonna
trade in for uh
uh
some armor for you
cool
that we have
in the barrels around here
yeah maybe in the back the front back
barrels
got it okay all good
um okay
oh rolling rolling rolling rolling
it's
angry
is it slow
yeah you got to go over the figure out
the red tracks in order to become
faster zuma move it
oh wow there we go by the way i didn't
even say cakey
yeah we kind of didn't we kind of just
jumped right in huh yes we should
introduce ourselves whoo
chris
who are you
kiara
kelly
um what do i do uh
i
i stream
and i make
something akin to music sometimes
something akin to me i've already seen
everything i need to see yeah it's like
i guess i do that my brain is pretty
dead we've been i've been doing a lot of
streams lately
um but feeling good feeling good i'm on
a i'm on a grind
yeah
are you coming yeah i see you oh
the cali train coming in
oh sorry
that was powerful
how much did that uh how much damage did
that do
i was only about a heart and a half of
this year ah yeah i wasn't even aiming
for you maybe if i would aim for you it
would do my
ah
let's go i gotta i gotta store away
these diamonds like a dragon oh should
we go to yeah that's important let's go
to your house first uh to store them
away
yup because i will lose these
i will lose these
a whole stack of diamonds that's just
pretty nice mmm
snappier very kindly gave them to me
[Music]
i know
you're so kind
i i arrived at your house before you
oh
it's because you could fly no i just ran
wow that makes sense like
throw my diamonds away
that's not new that's the only chest you
have that's so small no i've got a bunch
of chests it's just they're very
cluttered um
yeah what should i uh should i store
everything valuable away i wonder yes um
my diamonds board basically what we need
to bring is good armor and
good food which i've tried to take care
of before stream a little bit we might
be able to get some more
and i got golden carrots i will also
bring another chest and um i'll also
bring
us some shulker chests but we'll find
even more there what you could actually
bring with you is
um those two stacks of cobblestone in
your chest in that chest over there
okay there's two stacks and
actually
yeah
two stacks of that okay and
uh
wait what was i gonna say do you have
any
never mind okay that's fine
now
follow me
okay
lead the way should i get a pickaxe do i
need like tools ah yeah bring your tools
like a pickaxe and yeah
and the sword
okay and oh yeah
i will
give you a do you have a bow but
probably you don't really have a good
one probably i'd assume
i don't really use bows very often but i
can use them so okay i can use them i
just don't use them often ah and a
shield do you have a shield
no but i can make one i need iron dang
it let me go run to the iron farm real
quick okay i can make all this stuff i
just for some reason i didn't have it uh
already which is odd to me because i
usually have a gazillion pickaxes i have
more than i need usually so oh
oh i could i could give you uh
i could give you
um um uh pickaxes and stuff too or we
could get we could get decent ones in
phoenix down as well
thank you no worries i think oh my
goodness am i making all these new
advancements because um yeah because the
server connected yeah that means like
all
all of our advancements got reset but
the japanese ones didn't get reset
yeah
it's pretty wild here i'm going to make
it real quick huh okay so i swore my
crafting table where'd it go wait what
are you making right now
um i'm gonna make a pickaxe and a shield
no pickaxe you don't need to make
because we're gonna get a better one
than what you're probably making at
phoenix
but the shield yes yes needs the shield
okay let me find a crafting table that i
know we must have somewhere
[Music]
i have no clue where my crafting table
went what the oh yeah yeah
that's so weird
you think there'd be just one
all right maybe i can make a crafting
table should i
do i have
[Music]
should i give this one to cali
another infinity bowl would be nice
no it's okay don't give me your your
nice expensive things
we definitely need a good ball
i'm going to eat his house oh there it
is
[Music]
do i have the levels i maybe do
oh
maybe
should i put infinity on this one
power two punch one i'm breaking two
that's armor that sounds
lame
okay i made the shield
yeah
yeah okay okay
i'm gonna make you a
infinite bowl
well really the cool thing about that is
that you only need one arrow in your
inventory
and you can shoot forever
with that one
whoa
that sounds cool what do you want to
name it callie
um okay let me think let me think of
something super clever um
call it um
[Music]
um
e
what
yeah eat face what
h
e e space t h
e c even peculiar sempai agrees e e
e e t h okay what does that mean
it means no it means uh it's an ancient
language
oh
okay i will name it
yeah it's the language of the gods eth
arigato goes he
i think that's towards someone else no
not not towards me but you can dream
right
okay i blessed my senpai with the
ancient lady and i just saw you oh there
you are one second stay where y'all stay
where you are
i will give you eth
yeah
thank you there it is
thank you and uh l beautiful you only
need one but i'll give you a couple
arrows thank you how is something like
this allowed to exist yeah it's super
cool you just have to have the arrow
somewhere in your apartment it doesn't
need to be in the main task bar at all
just somewhere apartment in your
inventory
and uh the bull you know how to use a
bow in minecraft yeah okay like this
right yeah yes oh wow that is strong
nice oh
yeah
whoa
wow nice oh strong bow i'll give you
this stack of
fried chicken
for our journey so now let's go to
phoenix then wonderful okay let's take
the water the ice express to phoenix
done
yeah
right
that thing is super useful i've been
using it a lot yeah
just maybe try try to not lose it
okie dokie i won't whenever whenever
you're like building something i guess
you could just store it somewhere else
yeah you betcha all right
understood boss understood
there you go all right ride with me
okay oh i can get inside right yes right
click here let's go
oh your wings are really cool what
happened here that huge white thing down
there oh what is that who built that
it's super close to the little pico
doesn't find his house so i guess wait
you is your dog following you
oh hey we're done
why is it hurting what the [\h__\h] what
what
why
why are you little [\h__\h]
let me grab everything
i'm so confused
what did i
oh because you hit me
oh
wow
it's being protective
no get out of the
oh my god how sweet i guess oh wow i
picked up all your stuff by the way okay
hello
doggie can you please go away can i get
my dog to like not yeah you gotta go
back to your apartment and then make him
sit where your apartment is inside
otherwise he will follow you when he's
not sitting
all right come here poochie
oh goodness sorry that my i accidentally
sicked my dog
oh no problem
what the [\h__\h]
it came out of like a second dimension
like come out yeah yeah they they
actually uh teleport when you're too far
away
yeah if you don't make them sit down
they'll teleport you're weird
oh i was so i could have a whole group
of dogs just like attack uh my enemies
yeah
wow well i learned something new
so are you at your house right now
i'm going back okay
is this phoenix done oh [\h__\h] this is
phoenix then hold on oh you went the
wrong way
yeah can i just make the dog sit like
the dog isn't following me anymore by
the way oh
okay well you can just make him sit
there for now i guess
are you are you on the highway
no i i went down to phoenix stan oh okay
wait i'm coming
okie dokie i'm gonna chill with your
villagers hello
there's a big squidward noses i'm on my
way
ah oh the dog is uh
the dog is in he's coming after you no
no he's in the boat
okay oh a cookie boy
that was odd that was odd that he just
like sat down in the boat like all right
i own this [\h__\h] now that was very weird
he's lucky that i only have an arrow and
and a bow in nowhere right now
he can't beat it i don't even remember
taming that dog
i don't even remember
okay i have arrived in phoenix then
and
okay
you know what's my stuff
yes a lot a hot way
yeah
paper
uh your crafting table
pumpkin
um
here this is your bow
dream sparks bow oh i actually had both
yeah i had two bows in there
yeah fireworks then your armor your
diamond armor your shovel
your eggs and then uh you had a diamond
sword uh
usaken keybind sword
senpai and then
um
um but i think you had more hang on i
gave you the almost full stack and uh i
had a little bit left as well
okay gotcha that's fine that's funny
here um and then there's spider eye
something and then uh some boots and i
think oh yeah uh that's it thank you
no problem
i'm helpful in minecraft i think feel
good about myself why you're expensive
what's the matter with you i want to get
you also um feather falling boots if i
can find the right guy
holy [\h__\h] they're expensive is it
because they're tired
we should try to sleep let's go into
this house and okay uh
good night kick kick one of these out
well this one is oh we oh wow we got to
kind of share a yes yeah get off of here
you weird not not you needed the
villagers i got arrows arrows you got to
give me like one arrow oh yeah yeah yeah
the stack
is fine too there you go
here you go
well thank you
no problem
um
ready who
has who had the feather falling boots
no no no
no no no no no
but pickaxe you can't look for a good
pickaxe as well
efficiency too you know like all of them
by name and stuff uh some of them i give
some of them names so the really good
ones useful ones
nice
guys
[Music]
who's pants guy who's probably gone oh
no
there's a chance that my feather falling
boots guy
is
dead
oh it was like he was selling boots that
um make you take less damage when you
fall on the ground
yeah
and that is pretty good
uh oh that sounds like it would be
useful
yeah
there are so many villagers here i mean
they could be anywhere um
yeah yeah i'm still sorting out stuff
but wait you have watermelons right so
uh follow me ew
okay
let's go trade those watermelons so
basically where we just wear that's the
district that has like armor and tools
and all that and that district that you
see on that side the bright one that has
like like books like enchanting books
like this dude has for example loyalty
and silk touch and all that
and you see how they can't get out
they're not going to be able to go to
the other districts because i placed
this this trap door here
nice like we can go for everybody they
can't yeah it's really smart
so yeah here are the smart boys with all
the books and also uh this dude sells
like lapis lazuli and
glowstone and you can even here you know
how from zombies you get rotten flesh
and you never know what to do with it
you can trade them with him
emerald yeah neato cool right
no you really set up this place super
well yeah okay follow me the third
district is where you can uh trade your
watermelons
okay it's down this road to the right
do you remember this place actually
kelly
huh this is that village where we for
example jump from the window and into
into the water uh
oh a long time ago right yeah that's the
one that we kind of killed by visiting
them
yeah and we ransacked everything and
ruined their lives yeah i remember
exactly and i i uh revived and renovated
it so that's what it is now you became
the mayor yes i mean i gave i gave
someone
a villager to title so look in here uh
ask any of these actually you know what
i
didn't i get a
discount oh oh my god you i i actually i
personally have a disc discount with one
of these guys can you give me all your
stacks of watermelons i give you all the
emeralds i get from it
here you go
one
two
three no
because normally you get one emerald for
four
watermelons
but
i currently have a discount where it's
one ammo for one watermelon so it's way
cheaper
but i gotta wait a little bit because
they got a restack but i already got
wings
you're 12
emeralds there you go
one second
thanks respect please faster well i'll
go with him too
okay
this is a
use 12
more one for one i guess that's pretty a
buy i didn't realize that is does one
for one is you know you want to know how
i did that that discount
hit am i allowed to yeah i don't like
the i don't like the way it's a good
thing actually so um zombies came into
phoenixton village
and attacked my villagers during the
time when there was a lot of japanese
tourists on the server
for some reason they made it in and uh
they attacked some villagers and they
became into they turned into zombies
and then
uh
when the good thing is about that if you
cure them you can cure them with like a
potion and like a golden apple and all
that
and then they will give you super
special discounts but only to the person
who cured them
yeah this game is way deeper than i
thought uh that it was
it is
they're all like indebted to you they're
like it is like there's 12 more i i
threw them a little and he already
restocked twice today now i think they
only restocked twice per day so we gotta
wait until
night time actually but let's see
pretty realistic i suppose yeah but i
want to see if there's wasn't there
uh how many emeralds do we need
ah good question wait what was i gonna
get for you i wanted to get those birds
and
zen pants and boots
and yeah i guess all kinds of armor do
you don't have any armor at all right
now any diamond armor um no ma'am only a
diamond sword
all right oh god
a diamond sword is that does that have
any enchantments
let's see she's gonna get you this oh
that's sharpness
sharpness too oh that's at least
something
yeah
okay okay are these the black um
these are the black smiths
eye patches and [\h__\h]
and you know what how many do we have
right now emeralds
okay use this this one where i'm
standing here this dude
if you scroll down he's got a helmet
with protection free and breaking free
okay cool get that one for now
protection three hang on i'm trying to
access him please i'm sorry oh because i
was accessing so i'm sorry
what am i looking for the protection
free uh something something free from
like the the helmet the helmet or
protection to uh protection uh hold on
three helmet yeah yeah
ah this one should be good right should
we get this diamond chest plate for cali
what do you think
chad what do you think i'm breaking too
desperately wait who was that
last protection two i'm breaking two not
yes no do i have anything better blast
protection
uh probably gonna need more emeralds huh
yeah we're gonna get them we still have
a lot of watermelons no worries should i
do those ones
yes
is this better
fire production one on breaking two i'm
so excited me is anyone in you have a
special shield
yes i do
actually you know there's like only one
type of shield that you can craft
um which is the one that you're carrying
but you can
cheat no but you can decorate them
uh
like you can you can you can make like a
million different patterns you can
combine all those patterns and then they
look fancy and my mom she taught me how
to make this phoenix looking shield
so cool
wait how many do you have left emerald
[Music]
nine nine nine left
okay for now
ah wait oh that would have been good too
projector protection because they're
gonna get shot but all right we're just
gonna get one of these um
oh wait there's more
i feel like a lost little baby child
following around like my hero
the ten-year-old little boy who's like
falling
the master that's how you feel ah
i want it to be night i'll i'll check
with the i'll check with the watermelon
guy again
see if he's
do we have some more melons
i don't know we have enough we have and
actually i have a [\h__\h] ton of emeralds
at home i'm thinking of getting those
so that way a bit faster
okey-dokey
squier yes
you're squire no squire yeah i'm i'm
your squire
yeah i'm just here to be helpful
you already have electronics you're not
restocking yet i'm impatient i'll give
you these melons you can rough them up a
little bit maybe maybe it becomes night
before i come back but i'm gonna bring
some ammos you just have a talk with
them tell them to restock or we're gonna
kill them just kidding
they gotta be nice to the villagers tell
them tell them
tell them try to bribe them
yeah i'm trying to get um what am i
trying to get from them uh
you want to get those emeralds yeah
okay gotcha yeah it looks like it's out
of stock right now tell them to restock
restocker i'll punch you with the sword
i'll do it and i won't do that i don't
want to ruin phoenixton but
you're making me angry my panties
only we had oh wait those panties are
better aren't they
oh you know what uh hey what about this
one
oh wait i'll just give this one to cali
this chest plate because that's better i
think than what we have there but i'm
gonna repair it
oh can i repair it anyway
panties
you have 60 diamonds don't y'all
i do i'm i'm gonna give you a better
chest plate than than what the
those dudes have right now
can you like later give me one diamond
or two in exchange
i mean i have 60 of them so i can give
you a lot of them nice because i don't
have many and i'm repairing the armor
right now so that well you're giving me
a lot of free stuff so i mean yeah of
course yeah i'd be happy to do it
exchanges was all about
okay stunks
good so that's that's gonna be
that's gonna be mine
is it is it getting dark outside yeah
sun's starting to set a little bit oh
nice oh my level
oh [\h__\h] uh uh wait does the trading
giveaways
i need levels
you you you
you i'm out of levels
dropping another bear oh how do i get it
really quick trading gives levels okay
wipe your head uh maybe head um i think
i'm gonna bring some
iron iron yes iron iron lumber party
slumber are they gonna go are they going
to sleep
yeah they're sleeping right now but i'm
jumping all over the beds and having a
good time it's a slumber party
yeah yeah yeah pillow fight lads come on
they're sleeping with their diamonds oh
weird
men do yeah they don't have mirrors
i had armor with mending oh well
god fly oh
who's lava is lava floor
i love playing that as a child
yeah that's a fun game yeah especially
when you've got like couches and chairs
and like beds and stuff like that yeah
and then the room gets super messed up
afterwards
sleepy time
okay
i'm going to sleep on it oh
[\h__\h] it go into my elytra
no it can't be if it's full full exp if
it's full health then it will go into me
right
one second i'm gonna go to sleep in a
moment
okay okay okay okay okay let me talk to
you guys
wait i'm not getting exp
ah
give me exp
i wonder here
we can kind of save it last time it's
not giving
my ax
[Music]
good yeah i'm uh i'm um
i need some exp right now because i need
to repair um some diamond pants now i
ran out of iron
damn it do you you have some iron don't
you
i have 20 wait i have yeah i have a ton
of iron they're still out of stock
though for emeralds
ah yeah they take some time in the
morning uh when you do you want to come
up over to the blacksmith district
yes oh wait now
right chat you're right
this is where it is right i'm figuring
out the layout of phoenixton mm-hmm
this place i think
oh no this is where they live is this
the one that i wanted to repair hi
oh this is the ice for you right at your
face thank you
okay i have indeed received and also i
will give you now this diamond chest
plate
thank you these i'll give you the
diamond after the mission
yeah
no problem and now you're missing uh
boots right
boots okay
let's see what we can get we need some
more
oh wait no i have emeralds what the hell
boots boots so we have protection two
boots or
death straddle one unbreaking two what
do you think chat which one is
better
oh yeah maybe you can try buying them
don't kelly uh protection okay
protection two protection wait who had
that do you like the string
who had this dude okay
you gotta look at the guy
um
wait uh you you probably don't have
enough uh i only have nine year olds
yeah okay i'll give you i'll give you
some how much did he need
how much did you need where is he here
uh inside inside the in the corner
there is a dude called tetsuo he wants
20 20 emeralds
for
uh
the boots the boots i i throw you over
some more
thanks okay you're getting them okay and
then after the title you got the boots
yeah nice you can put them on yeah
you got the new shoes
okay now we're talking now okay and i
still have 10 emeralds left what should
i do should we store them uh wait we can
maybe buy
something else wait let's let's try to
go get some
decent food we might need some more what
do you think chef do we need more food
i got 29 cooked rabbits and 45 cooked
chickens that's actually quite a lot
yeah
hello
oh
quite a bit
where'd
oh we could get golden carrots
i'm gonna
i guess i'll go get some golden carrots
so fast more won't hurt
um golden carrots i'm gonna go get some
more
wet minting
oh you're here oh hey you can't um wait
i gave you the melons right
indeed did this dude
it doesn't look like it oh ah they
didn't the the one with the discount did
wait can you give me those back here
yeah
only one stack is enough for now
thank you
welcome did i did i pick it up
no wait i didn't i didn't pick it up
oh i re-picked it up and you throw them
right at your head
oh and the pickaxe oh yeah right we need
a good pickaxe for you
right cause you don't have a good one
right now
yeah i was just gonna make one out of
iron but i guess if we're going to the
end i really should have a good one oh
oh cheap
oh yo
[Music]
yo you're a cheap man i like it
oh man that's a lot of carrots i'm gonna
go grab some more
what a deal callie what are these i
will give you hmm
wait what i have 20. you wait how much
food do you have like which one i have
and uh let me list it out for you 45
cooked chickens 29 cooked rabbits
approximately one raw cod and 20
20 golden carrots and five melon slices
20 golden carrots okay let me add on to
that with 26 more golden carrots there
you go thank you all right
i think we're a tasty vegetable i think
you're good with food now
yeah you're sure
okay
and uh i give you the rest of the melons
because he's done for the day
cool can i eat these now the big blocks
you can't eat
you gotta like if you place the big
block the melon block and then destroy
it again it will like scatter in many uh
slices
oh cool
i'm gonna try
harvested melons yeah like a summer
festival yeah
okay okay okay and now and now and now
we're gonna get you the pickaxe and then
we go to the end okay okay okay i'm
ready just has taken more time than i
thought it would oopsie
and that's okay what's the best pickaxe
you guys can offer one i'd rather you
got no pickaxe you got
no pick i'm not i'm just gonna be here
smashing melons
yummy uh the what the melons were
probably not gonna bring with us though
because um
they have food but
we need food that fills up a lot uh asap
that's why we're bringing the better
food only so
you can you can keep it at home should i
give
efficiency to we can add on more things
later this is like for the end
for the end for now that's enough i
would
say hmm
we can add some stuff to it
yeah okay
okay pickaxe callie
here there you go thank you
thank you
and we'll treasure it and while we're at
it yeah while we're at it
you don't have a diamond axe do you
i don't okay
so with the watermelon emeralds you also
receive this
diamond pick a diamond axe thank you
wow i'm getting very lucky actually this
one is good too
now i ran out of emeralds oh no wait i
didn't
i'll give you a diamond shovel too
how can i pay you back for all these
things no you don't need to basically
you paid for it yourself oh [\h__\h] this
would have would this have been better
technically iris paid for them i guess
with all our melons
i'm getting confused wait i'll get this
one okay so and a shovel
there you go
however we don't need the shovel and uh
i think we don't even need the axe in
the end let's go back to our
headquarters
okay oh let me take dad
oh okay it sounded like i feel like i
sound like my uh mickey mouse for a
moment
yeah for a minute you did it was a
little confusing you gave me a shot
there
and
oh that's a great you know what i got
better boots uh
[Music]
but uh we gotta repair them
okay let me repair them
the other boots you can keep in case you
lose the boots that you currently have
which i wouldn't recommend because
they're really nice like feather falling
is
one of the best traits to have on boots
i would say
oh yeah wait so you take less fall
damage yeah yeah yeah so here they are
here they are new boots make sure to
swap them out
okay
i wait you can
i should have combined it oh wait sorry
give me both back
here i can combine both of those
traits and then you will have
super super nice boots what do you want
to call them you want to call them some
things
oh man okay let me think
um
[Music]
good question chet what do you guys have
any ideas
what should we call these these shiny
new boots
dead boots oh that sounds nice
b
these dead boots
gucci
drape jordan
death
that's kind of cool
um
air maurice i like that okay
please and more we see one in capsule or
any any specific language um yeah all
caps all kind of feel nice and
aggressive thanks chad for the
suggestions
air maurice
okay oh i can't wait to equip these air
maurice thank you so much there you go
protection
i can't believe that kiara got me those
brand new air morries i feel so lucky
thank you very expensive
i shall make it up to you i think now we
are armor-wise we are ready to go wise
we are ready to go material wise i'm
gonna take pick up a few more um
building blocks and then i would say
we're good wait ship ship boat
boat
oh
can i i mean has is it calmed down or is
it going to go
but it's in a boat right now hello dogo
um
you have permission to not be friendly
to this dog by the way
i just want to get him out of the boat
one second uh with that i'm actually
without hurting him
yeah i'd prefer that you not but wait i
want to break the boat
okay i didn't hurt him okay
thank goodness i think you need to right
click him again
right
and then he will portal himself into
your home
if we just leave him so get back into
the boat yeah he doesn't seem aggressive
so i think yeah yeah because i died once
he forgot who i am love that ah i will
make you remember who i am if you don't
move away
i can't believe that the dogs know where
the house is that's kind of cool i mean
they know wherever you are and always
we're just gonna go to your house and
then make him sit down and then and then
i'll leave him there yeah
okay
i should that's it okay okay it really
is night time
we're going to your place and then you
can give me
uh maybe maybe maybe because i ended up
preparing more so can you give me like
six diamonds or so yeah i can give you
as many as you need
i'm cool with that but yeah it's just
yeah i mean i guess you can go throw
them in your chest before we go on the
journey yeah yeah i really will
all right oh i'm just gonna take you
take them out of your chest and yeah
just take them
i'm going to take them i'll get in the
hood
let me put some other stuff back maybe
can you find other cool stuff in the end
you can find a lot of cool stuff trust
me captain really like what
uh we can find choker chests and like a
lot of we can find dragon heads
cool hola
i want a dragon head
wait um i threw out the cobblestone in
order to save your items last time
should i get like other rock or uh if
you don't have it anymore let me see i i
think i have more materials
over on my place because um it would be
i don't know can you make andesite into
stacks uh chat i don't remember was that
possible
sorry i made slabs and stuff
ooh slumps
oriented
[Music]
uh
yes you can okay you use it okay cool
you use it for getting around the end
yeah
uh so take that one stack that you have
of and the side
okay
[Music]
oh wait i haven't this one looks
it blends in so nicely because it's gray
for sure
all right all right all right okay i'll
take i take a couple of blocks of
cobblestone we probably have to go
pretty far
and because the nearest end cities
have already been pretty explored i
guess by
me and ina and gula and ame and i
already went back there once flying back
with my lighter i went pretty far
so
this time we're just gonna do the
original strategy again by not flying
but actually placing a lot of blocks
over the void
trying to not fall down you will see
what i mean when we get there let's
sleep for a moment
sure you said i don't need the shovel
right
uh yes you can put the shovel away and
i'm back
is it not like oh wait why did i think
it's nighttime
yes uh
the axe hmm actually you know what keep
keep the axe cause
if you fight one-on-one against someone
then
uh the axe does more damage like than
the sword actually
wait what yeah
only wanna wanda like cause the sword
does aoe damage while the axe does a
single target damage
wow you're very like um
quashy
with with minecraft
yeah
yeah you like know your [\h__\h] yeah i i uh
i got all my knowledge from the chat
you have a bucket in your
in your inventory
in that chest i saw maybe fill that up
with water and bring that along with you
yes ma'am and
i'll take i guess no i'll keep that in
here
and
let me see we don't need this we don't
need that
all right i got it open
um
i'm doing some last
second last minute
should we turn off shaders yeah
i was getting this suggestion turn off
shaders yeah
okay i'll turn them off i will i'll let
you use that pumpkin in case it helps
should i take a bed
uh
no no no you can't sleep in the end
right you'll blow up exactly we don't
need a bed we're just going to set our
spawn before we go into the bed into the
end
um
[Music]
uh i guess i'll take the
i'll take the fireworks
leave this oh yeah we used that last
time to fight the dragon yeah that was
one of our strategies we used a million
strategies if you even can call them
strategies
well we we won in the end so yeah i'm
gonna bring
those
two shulker boxes and we can make more
once we're there
yeah yeah kiara said she's gonna bring
an ender chest yeah
well i guess i'll leave that here i
don't need that i'm trying to clean out
my ender chest and my shoulder boxes
um anything else that's really cool
leave electric yeah i'm leaving my
i'm leaving my electron or maybe i'll
just put them to the end of twist okay
and then wait no diamonds uh the apples
no this and that and this sorry one
moment i'm almost you're all good almost
wonder what the cities are like
cities yeah they they look
interesting it's like high towers and
really slim towers and so the the thing
is that um they're filled with these
enemies called uh
what are they called the shulker enemies
celebrations not endermen uh enemies are
everywhere too but inside of the towers
we're gonna have issues with the the
shulkers yeah i guess they're just
called
shulkers um they look like the shulker
boxes and we got they they dropped the
shulker shells to make shulker boxes huh
um see i will i want those but they're
they are really really annoying to deal
with
um we gotta be careful there because if
they hit you you're sent flying like you
literally start floating
oh
so that's gonna be a bit troublesome
wait so should should i hit him with
arrows
yeah that's why we need that
bow and
yes okay i think
i think
i think i think we're
we're pretty much
i'm gonna turn off shaders right before
we go in guys yeah yeah you're going to
love it now
make it look good
let's see
yes okay
okay um
do i need uh do i need even more blocks
well kelly has a couple of blocks
i guess i can
know
diorite can be made into slabs too
and and the sun so i'll take done
i mean worst case we can just get the
end the end material it doesn't really
matter yeah you could probably use that
can you hit that with pickaxes or shovel
pig cat probably not shovel you guys
gotcha cause we're not bringing the
shovel that's right i remember now yeah
i don't think we needed that for
anything there
push
i mean come on that must be enough for
us
okay
wanna come over to my house
yeah
and there uh i have a stone cutter that
will be most efficient to cutting the
stuff
i guess it'll bring them away
okay
do you have a water bucket
so here yeah put in the the blocks that
you have
okay should i make the regular slabs
yeah
shift click on them to get uh as many as
possible all right 64.44 okay that's
about 100 or so
is that is that all the stone blocks or
whatever that you have yep okay i think
i think we'll be fine i'll take this
with me
oh what's this beautiful what
oh those that that's the material that
we also get in the in the end
in the cities because that's
end rot and they light up the room too
and they're really cool you can place
them also
like look look over here you can place
them straight you can make them look
like lamps
the end rod
yeah yeah they look like lightsabers
oh
my mama i put them all over this
apartment because she thought it looks
fancy
ready i want them for my own stand i'm
gonna do my best we're gonna get a lot
of those don't worry
okay cool okay sorry sorry that i took
so much time i'm kind of nervous that
we're forgetting something um i think
now
we're fine let me give you this pumpkin
head
yeah
i think it's like i personally don't
like using it but if you wear that then
the um enderman will not target you
oh
but oh my endless yeah but i don't
really like it because it like put it on
and you will see that you will see less
much less
oh i see i see yeah but you look funny
now yeah i do i look like a little
jacqueline
well but it's less protection as well
huh exactly but it's more about like we
got to be very careful with where we
where we are walking today
so
i feel like
um
it might be press f1 to get a better
view is that true
yeah ooh f1 no f5
oh f1 is something else yeah five is
like there's three different like angles
that you can play with in the game yeah
but i pressed f1 and now everything's
clear
yeah yeah yeah that's for like taking a
good picture i guess yeah yeah oh
you mean you don't see the ah
i think that's only with the shaders if
you turn the shaders off then it um
will not work i think that was a thing
right
right chad
only with the shaders on
which i guess you can keep the shaders
in the end we will see how it looks like
for you maybe it's too dark for you not
sure
oh
no it'll still work that's kind of
interesting but it turns off everything
so like i can't see what items i'm
holding etcetera and that's great yeah
all right it's nice i am worried i feel
like i want to wear the helmet just to
be safe yeah
yeah just if you feel like let's see if
they target you the enderman because you
look at them too often
then we will use the the the pumpkin
helmet if
if you can
stop targeting you yeah yeah they will
like you can look at them and they
ignore you but
we will see how you can control your
eyes
i'm really good at controlling my eyes
trust me they definitely don't dart all
over the place and go all over one
finger it'll be fine can you put your
bucket of water into your hot bar
oh yeah it's in there okay good because
if they happen to target you and start
attacking you
just put the water on the ground because
they don't go into water
okay so they don't like why am i going
up here wait don't go down go down
that we shouldn't really go up here i
guess
okay
so i'm gonna get one and don't worry
guys it's just well around it
i'm gonna walk around it
yeah
okay it took us one hour to prepare i'm
so sorry i hope we can find a city asap
no props um i'm here just directly right
as long as it takes chiara as long as it
takes okay okay
yeah i'm here for this i mean i guess
your sleep rhythm is [\h__\h] anyway right
so yeah pretty pretty burned yeah
got them at these these mountains
i should i guess i should have gone up
because it it ends somewhere and you can
just drop down into water i guess oh
well oh oh well
we're gonna go the safe route down here
we like some mountain climbing
you like mountain climbing laid yeah oh
yeah my legs are dropped strong now
where'd you go
oh i see you went down there
i didn't want to do it
let's go starting to get a bit dark i
hope we can get there in time oh yeah
[\h__\h] i didn't bring a bed damn it oh
oh well we have to arrive
before it turns into night then
okay let's go quick go go go go go go
oh i swim like you um you gotta try to
get under the water otherwise you can't
swim that fast
okay like point downwards to the ground
while
uh yeah going forward and then while
while you're in the water if you press
ctrl
then you're zooming through the water
yeah
cool yeah nice okey dokey
oh it's turning nice oh well we'll we're
gonna just have to protect them defend
everything off is that right
i'll fight anything yeah beat him up
following the path
uh jumping on some water helens in the
night time
uh-oh
ct oh wait are you guys making fun of
because i said ctrl and not control
i heard a creeper did it blow you up or
someone else i'm okay okay i definitely
felt like i felt i felt it hit me but
like it didn't hurt me okay good
i can't see [\h__\h]
oh wait why
it's very dark oh you still got the
shaders on maybe they make it
uh pretty dark huh
i turned mine off for today it felt a
little bit laggy
okey-dokey
i'll turn them off shortly then
ctrl
troll yeah
yeah
let's see is there anything else i
should warn you about oh you know it's
she playing minecraft
today at this time
why is she
why is she here
she's usually around
a similar time whoa whoa whoa don't fall
down did you fall down my whole shift
i'm okay
should i hold shift it's just i'm going
to go shift no no no just try to walk
straight
keep your
that that little cross in the middle
that you have just keep it on the middle
of the path and you should be fine yeah
is that a wolf
is that my wolf
no did you make it sit down
oh i i didn't
okay then we'll just have it follow us
until like the room uh where we jump
into the end and just have him sit there
yeah sounds good to me
wait a second
i didn't bring oh no this is still touch
okay fine fine do i have my other
pickaxe in the entities
i hope oh well
oh well
run run run run
run run rather
we can make it
yeah easy
i'm gonna take
that coal because i never have enough
coal
i never have enough coal oh there's a
lot of coal burlington
i see a dead beet over there oh oh be
careful ooh
and that's the creeper i think
that's an enderman oh okay run run run
run run run run
don't let go
all the
the spooky spooky uh skirlingtons and
endermen are coming out to play uh-uh
keep on running they're here i don't
know the moonlight is where you're like
oh that's a cool fight
is this the right direction
wasn't there one point on this path
where it splits into two paths
and i never know where to go before and
then like around that's a creeper
falling behind uh wait i'm gonna go into
the water for a moment and eat some food
uh can they follow us all right they
can't go into the way
[Music]
there's a little [\h__\h] going on
around here oh man
creepers everywhere literally all over
the place
now what the hell did you just come to
support
us nice
what is happening
it's like a mom bringing us the stuff
that we forgot and she just leaps
thank you
a freaking hero
oh
we were in a pickle there we were in a
picture
[Music]
away you demons
all right i think we're getting pretty
close
[Music]
oh no
on y'all
yeah easy clap
easy easy
patch
are you using the infinity bow now right
yeah
does it feel strong
it does
i like it a lot thanks for making it
powerful if i don't lose it
hold on to it
ah there it is i think i see it
in the distance i see the
tower the last time i went to the end
actually was literally the time that we
fought the ender dragon
oh yeah i play a lot of minecraft yeah
well what i'm excited about
uh
yeah that's gonna be really really nice
for you i think but you gotta get used
to flying i brought some fireworks
because the the wings only work if you
have fireworks with you
yeah are there limitations to playing
limitations um
what do you mean
like you can't just like jump in the air
and fly wherever you want right well
you can as long as you have fireworks
oh i see and i guess you can kind of fly
like if you jump down the high tower
with the
with the wings on
then you'll also kind of fly but it's
not that effective without the fireworks
are you by the really tall tower yes i
am i don't see you i don't see you
anymore slain by kada again
she was slain by
fried chicken
poison
[Laughter]
what is that if he is dangerous i think
they probably
oh hey i spy i think they probably put
the
like put the name kadaga on a weapon i
guess that's all there is to it i see
i get it okay so we have a rafter yeah
set your spawn point
i guess we can put the beds back into
this chest here
and
all right
what are you
what do you have in your inventory right
now
all right i'll tell you i have a diamond
pickaxe 45 cooked chickens i have a
pumpkin head i have um i don't need this
rock cod i'll put that away 46 um golden
carrots i have 64 stone flaps and plus
44 actually so it's over 100 then i've
got uh arrows i have a bow i have 18
watermelons i have 27 cooked rabbits
away in the chest we need space we need
as long as much space as possible okay
and i have a water bucket okay and i'll
put those here as well okay okay okay
we're ready to go
uh fill your health up one last time if
you don't have full health
yes ma'am and uh it's gonna be dangerous
kelly very dangerous boy okay i'll do my
best just be very careful if you're if
you're on a narrow path just um
press shift i'm trying to
not fall down how do i hold up the
shield
um
right
with the bow it doesn't work only if you
have like a one hand weapon
i understand okay oh i didn't bring my
other one
okay okay yeah okay okay all right i'm
ready i'm also very nervous whenever i
go to the end but let's do this let's do
this what did i not sit look at that
scary oh i didn't turn off my shaders
whoopsie doodle did i not set my spawn
did oh well it will just be it will just
be in the in the i will just be
respawned in the in the thing in the
theme
and come back
and why oh for the shaders
yeah no you can do it um if you press
escape and options oh okay and then
video settings
okay and then shaders
it's like on the left side and the
middle and then you click off exactly
and then it will take a moment to load
but then you can just get out of the
options
okay oh apparently i did okay chat made
me nervous i did set the stream thingy
um okay all right let's go uh be careful
yay careful careful careful careful how
do i make sure that the endermen don't
like i'm not looking at it no just just
try to look as much as you can on the
ground like lower your head but not too
much like just just keep it somewhat low
okay just mind your own business
okay
i always felt like i had to kind of keep
the cross hair away from them but they
seem to like it's like i'm looking at
them anyway no you can look at their
body you just can't have your your
little cross in the middle on their eyes
that will anger them oh i
i see let me hold on i'm gonna put the
pumpkin in my bar okay just to have it
ready you know i don't just kidding that
wouldn't work i need to actually equip
it um
oh well
i think like see see how like this out
here at the end of this like island
there's like nothing yeah right yeah um
that's like we're gonna build a lot of
paths over the nothingness
also be very careful when going up here
very careful okay
oh god gotcha
oh god no problem you guys a little
stairway wow yeah this is uh
by going into this portal we're gonna
port ourselves onto a different island
oh so uh how does it work again um
go here you guys just found this
uh yeah this was here like already this
thing this portal yeah okay look at what
i'm doing so i put this this this
trapdoor up right
and i jump here up here be very careful
again and then crouch
then push uh can you add it wait how how
does she do it when she's alone how does
this work again
um
when you're when you're crouching
i guess you wait you don't need to
crouch no no crouching uh you stand
under the trapdoor and then close it and
then you you i'm flying right now right
so now i i went into the other dimension
so what you're going to do is stand
under the trap door like first you have
to open it i guess open it
and then uh when you stand directly
under it you right click the trap door
to close it
okay
and now i think you're flying right
you're like kind of in the flying
am i probably i'm trying to crouch
shift to crouch right no no no crouching
no crouching just standing underneath it
uh normally the trap door oh i see i did
it i did i did it okay and now i go to
it yeah just go through that little
portal there you are
okay careful careful turn around and
then go a few steps
towards me
and
a little bit more a little bit more okay
try pressing try pressing shift
okay oh no you're not standing up yet oh
there you are okay okay okay okay
now all right we got this
going down these stairs shift oh boy
this is really quite terrifying it is
i'm really scared
i'm nervous we'll be fine we'll be fine
now we can go here into this little safe
house for a moment oh you guys need a
little safe house yeah together
ourselves
okay okay that's this looks pretty
yeah
there's nothing really really here um
now the question is which direction
should we go
uh is this the path that i created the
last time i was here is this my path
guys or is this inna's path
bring a map i don't know where are you
how are you i'm i'm i'm i'm here
i'm behind the house
oh
if we use my path again we will we will
uh at least
pass one ender city or two actually that
i have already been through but at least
the oh at least the paths are already
made and then
from there on
we will continue building maybe
okie dokie
okay
all right captain let's go let's go
onward
not getting
in trouble with the enderman wait what
iris
what about iris
i don't know is this really my path it
doesn't matter i guess we'll find we'll
find it in the city eventually okay
careful here even i will shift here
because i'm scared i'll rely i don't
know all right nice i can't do it yeah
i can do it okay well i'll hold shift
because i know how i am yeah okay
do you have shift on
toggle or
i don't know i think in minecraft it
turns it off to be honest because i
don't i never have issues with sticky
keys okay i think eh but are you
if you when you press shift do you like
have to keep on pressing or you only
toggle it once and then you're shifted
until you press it again
you keep on pressing it pretty yeah you
should change that maybe
oh um where was it again controls
was it in minecraft uh
yeah
okay
wait a second where was that
options controls accessibility ah
accessibility settings
on the bottom right
and then
sneak toggle i guess sneak toggle neat
toggle okay iris it's not my path oh
okay oh iris is watching too
oh okay
but what someone wrote to me something
about iris's stuff did you die in the
end and like left your stuff there
because
you you died
if we get too close then it will i guess
disappear i hope that won't happen
okay now when you use shift you don't
you only have to press it one step
yeah i don't have to hold it anymore
i'm glad i had no idea how to do that
before okay okay okay well you can scout
out the area while i'm slowly but surely
making my way oh yeah
i'm gonna drink some of my some of my uh
my gamer drink oh okay have a gamer
drink
i i'm not saying
i'm not sponsored by them so i'm not
gonna like talk about what they are but
um
i guess a friend of mine like had some
kind of
gamer drink sponsor and like they had
too much of it at their office and
they're like just taking cali oh and i'm
like okay
i've been drinking it
the gamer drink
it's uh
it's giving me a little bit of energy is
it bang it's ba no it's not bang
um i'd be acting a lot more suspicious
if it was bang i feel like if it's red
bull i feel like you could talk about it
because there was a whole live red bull
collaboration before
yeah that's right
yeah well i mean i still have two bang
in my fridge but i just won't drink them
yeah i know i'm really afraid i don't
even cause i see the enderman looking at
me too and i'm like oh boy
oh there you go
there you are
uh
where is the next path that i built
so you know in the
basically it's like a [\h__\h] ton of
islands in the end and there are uh
mostly not connected so we will have to
build the paths this is a path that i i
guess i built before
uh
oh while we're at it um
yep
is that how you do it
uh
um we're getting some coarse fruit you
see those little right purple trees
there
yes ma'am they're pretty i like them
with your eggs
uh destroyers i can break up them yeah
cause they drop
what that is is it fills up on your
health yes but we don't really use it as
food we use it as a way to stop floating
because once look look at look at me
look at me
oh where'd you got me behind you
oh yeah
zoom oh
you zoomed
you will always be teleported to like a
nearby uh
ground
oh really yeah so if you fall if you eat
it you're fine
yes nah i don't and what would happen if
if cali falls into the void and tries
her best to eat and eat the fruit as
soon as possible
i wonder if that could save her
yeah i guess it depends on how deep
everything is huh only if you do it
rapidly it will save you you won't be
fine yeah you probably won't be fine it
does not work okay no okay what a shame
try to not fall into the void but um
when we go to those towers the end
cities there will be a lot of mobs that
send us flying so if you fly too much if
you fly like up too high then you should
always eat a chorus fruit
um to get back to the ground
and you wait so you float like yeah in
the sky yeah yeah yeah yeah and you
can't really control where you're flying
to like it will send you higher and
higher
ah yeah
and it will wear off like you see like a
timer
and it will wear off eventually but uh
yeah okay it's uh oh
lots of things to discover here
yeah well so far it's mostly nothingness
but
yeah but it's just kind of like
interesting i don't know in the main
game i just didn't
expect to find this yeah
by the way it's uh infinite this this
place is infinite
wait really yeah so like new villages
will just keep spawning forever and ever
and ever yeah but they will be further
and further and further and it will be
more and more difficult to find them
wow stuff like the universe yeah you go
really fast ah that's the fastest way to
run it's like if you have if you have
full health
double use of front running then ctrl
plus jumping
so three but i didn't know that
but don't jump into the void you gotta
gotta be careful when you okay i'll be
careful
yeah leave it to me i didn't know
jumping was a factor yeah
it makes you even faster oh ina left
you nice words probably like we we
taught them
enough things they're fine they're fine
yeah
you know so pro
i haven't seen
a path of mine in a while
well yeah
i guess i kind of
will you remember the paths that you
made no i don't remember that's the
thing
um
i guess in the first place
i guess i could have like your own path
half over there
um i'm gonna make the path i don't get
out you're gonna shift behind me
okay very
carefully all right i am ready just to
get started so
scared i didn't do this for a while
one second
take your time
okay yes
i'm scared
i've done this before okay easy easy
easy easy easy
easy wow what a mess
aye aye captain
just don't press shift again
otherwise i will press
oh yeah that's right i'm fast talking to
yourself i was pressing shift i was
holding down shift and i was
jumping up and down doing a little dance
yeah
gotta get used to it
oh my goodness is super high risk
wow it is
wow
this is the end after all
anything yeah
okay the path is done
we're gonna make a lot more
build it
let's all right
i can help with the path if you want and
i think for now i mean i understand this
i'll be the builder
uh but i would like to be helpful uh
it's it's fighting i can fight
definitely
i think the building maybe you should
leave to me
okie dokie
i don't think i got to be able to build
over there
i think we're already definitely off
path i don't see anyone's anyone else's
path so that's interesting we can go in
a new direction
it's for us there's a myth though that
um
let's say you come to the end for the
first time
uh-huh and you
uh start building a path into let's say
south
the
like the end since it's infinite
it will
create
um
it will create it will like load in
and while it will create everything
while it's loading in like it's not
pre-created
what so
um every every area that you have not
like gone to yet has
not been created like the game didn't
decide yet what it would look like so um
that is not a myth that is a fact but
uh
let's say you go south
and the inner cities there's a myth that
the inner cities start spawning
only in that one direction
like from north to south or and but i
don't i don't know i i've seen a video
that explains that but
i don't know i don't know there's a lot
of stuff
about this game
i hear a scary sound
scary things
i mean if it can be proven then then
they should prove it
i'd like to see them prove it there's a
there's a lot of people who oh god
you got this you're fine
uh there's a lot of people who who say
that is it's true because they have
they have seen it and oh god
you're dude you're doing great no
this is taking up you have to toggle
yeah
yeah i'm fine i'm fun
keep your pinky really far away from the
shift it's so you should be fine it's
just it's just like you stand on on top
of a huge tower that's made out of a
glass you see everything
i've been a place like that a tower you
can you can stand on some grass and see
all the stuff there all right okay
are you afraid of heights
currently yes um
generally
oh my god i made it probably just
because the stakes are super high we are
holding a lot of really important things
and if they fall we lose them forever
exactly
okay careful there is a there is another
uh void here
oh
careful
uh
are my slabs gonna be enough for that
little gap
oh my god
i'm like standing in the nothingness
are you scared of heights i guess not
um it depends on the situation i guess
oh we could have enderpearled oh no yeah
if you throw and the pearls um you can
like teleport yourself as well
to the place where you throw the ender
pearl too
but that's pretty neat yeah that's like
oh well it's fine we're doing a hardcore
mode you know super extreme mode for
experts
yes
and getting those ender pearls would
have been quite some work as well so
yeah i do have four of them though just
for next time let's go a little bit left
here oh i found a portal
oh
but that will just bring us back to the
main island i guess huh oh okay well
just good to know that it's there kind
of like a checkpoint um
well i'm gonna take a screenshot of that
for sure i guess we can go over there
uh
okay i'm gonna make the same as the
overwhelm updates change how chunks load
the first time but that's still seed
based old chunks don't change yeah
i guess it's kind of like the same thing
for the over huh
oh boy
a lot of jumpy boys
only spawn on chunk cords that are
dividable by 20 like 20 40 60 800 is
that true
is that true
we
well i don't know i don't want to that
that's minecraft theory yeah i don't
want to pay attention to that major in
minecraft theory
special
okay we're gonna go straight oh
oh i looked at it oh did i
at least they don't do so much damage
some damage but it's not dead yet come
on over here
on
let's just get him
the good thing is like the others won't
attack you so oh nice shot
is it dead now
uh uh no not yet oh hi hi uh
oh it hurts itself by going into the
water that's good
give me an interesting position you
thought yourself said
there we go okay uh i want to take back
my water
my spawn source oh [\h__\h] there we go okay
i guess i looked at them at the end of
man huh
that's so weird sometimes i don't even
feel like i looked at them but i guess i
did
so
it's weird like that see
[Music]
i haven't ended chest with me chat look
of course this is not my first time
indeed very well i know what i'm doing
very well
yes mostly definitely more than me i
have no clue what the f word's going on
but i'm very grateful for the journey we
want to go to like a big island you know
because mostly the end cities are on
those big islands i'm gonna path
of oh wait i see a pav
did i make that puff before
are we like circling around to
stuff you've done maybe have i used that
material
i got an arrow or projectile can't hit
enderman okay gotcha so i'll use my
sword next time that's iris path
best avoid it should i not go there
okay let's go
oh
i mean i'm trying to go mostly straight
so
i guess we'll go maybe see little legs
little legs like spiders legs everywhere
and they're super modest
they're super models
looking very stylish today please don't
kill me
very stylish
girl yeah it's just another sign that
black is a very flattering color
it is though it goes with everything
that's why my whole closet it's the
color black
yeah i heard you say that why did i hear
you say that just recently
yeah i talk about it something oh uh in
a thing we can't really talk much about
oh ah
yeah
the secret thing i think i know okay
we'll probably learn about
next month next month oh really or
really okay they told me next month okay
look forward
i gotta go over to that island i think i
don't really have
a choice
because uh over there it doesn't it
doesn't look good to me we'll see we'll
see what's okay we're just gonna go you
want to do captain you're just going
further than iris
yes ma'am
[Music]
oh yeah outfits should maybe come
sometime soon too hopefully the new
outfit yeah yeah
i love we're told not much longer i love
kelly's new outfit so much thanks i'm
glad you like it
uh it's something i've wanted for a
while that kind of
looks so good it looks so good
yours is dope too though it's perfectly
fitting for you
i think our
our two new outfits for some reason even
though we didn't really um do it on
purpose
i think our outfits are kind of color
matching
oh yeah i think so as well they do have
like a similar thing going on i think
oh some people i saw someone in the chat
being surprised about what new outfit uh
it's been so long since we announced it
and nothing has been happening people
forget about it
i mean i don't blame them you know
things of course kind of you know
get a little messy sometimes yeah but
it's fine it's fine no worries guys
everything's all good in the
neighborhood and you'll be seeing them
shortly shortly yes on our one year
anniversary you know i've been around
for a while
they're yeah we've been ready they're
they
at that time i was ready
me too
we were i see another path we were
just
you know waiting for the right moment
yeah exactly and everyone's got to be
ready so
whose path is that
i was i still watching is just here
where are your legs my legs oh you lost
me i'm too fast
yeah you're very quick and these
long-legged boys i'm afraid of them here
here here
just don't look at them
actually that's not even
that's that's
that's uh i thought it was
never alone never stuff but it's not oh
iris i don't think i it's not never
wrack actually it looked like it was uh
the what's it called
i wonder who's that is
well it's a path for us let's walk over
it
carefully where are you oh uh oh god
uh
yeah
you running so quick
oh where did you go
i saw you before here ah here mojimo
straight straight straight
oh i see you hot hot hot hot hot oh
they're so scary you gotta go to where
it feels the hottest that's where the
phoenix is
okay i gotcha i'll i'll turn on my my
temperature receptors so i prefer the
cold you know i mean could i use granite
that's ahmed good as pep how the hell
did i get there
oh that's a smart idea to like code them
by different like types of blocks
be careful callie smart
be careful
uh oh yay did they they took quite some
time to find the understudy or no
because i don't want to go into a
direction that has absolutely no
understandings
you got good gear to deal with them okay
i'll try not to be so spooked by them
yeah yeah they don't do much damage
though than and the enderman yeah don't
don't panic no need to panic
all right sure i'll just be a little
cautious then
definitely be cautious
i don't see you anymore
i went too fast
are you too excited for yomicon yo oh
yeah
i really like doing panels where i can
see everyone yeah it's like exciting for
me so like see the fans they're my fave
i fought a fave a while ago
i thought that the panel that i did a
while i guess the one with you
was my last one and i was a little bit
sad about it that um uh that was the
last one but now i got a new one extra
i didn't know it would be that fun
it is fun because i feel so like it
feels like we're connecting with the
fans in a whole new way like seeing
their faces
yeah it's totally different when you can
actually see them and hearing their
voices and seeing their emotions when
they talk to us they all look very
nervous always though
they're cute i mean we're kind of
nervous too but in a different way i
think yeah you know
so don't worry guys we are also a bit
nervous yeah no but
it's it's all good we're overall it's
the it's like the excitement is number
one number one feeling
yeah and it's always fun to see
everyone's cosplays too
yeah people get so creative i love that
i love seeing all like the cali scythes
careful i'm gonna preach do a tiny
bridge all right
whoopsie okey-dokey
little bridge ah good i met the feet
compilation guy yeah so funny i saw that
oh that was funny that was pretty hard
it's like it's like a repeated meeting
there's like thousands and thousands of
viewers that we have right and then like
making a connection to people that we
know from chat or from super chats and
then they show up at those panels and
they're like hey i'm this and this
person
it's so funny
it is really neat to put it to put a
face to the name yeah oh i gotta eat
yeah eating is important
okay i see no more paths maybe we're on
our own path again i think so now this
must be like our our own way do we have
to find our way all the way back by the
way um no so what i was thinking is like
we're just gonna i have it in the chest
with me
so we're just gonna put everything in
our ender chest
and die and then yeah fall into the void
nice idea yeah okay careful it's um
oh my god i'm already like
running out of
do you still have slabs don't you don't
need to give them to me now 44 yeah i
have a bunch of them 44 over 100 over a
hundred oh no i have over a hundred yeah
okay
no worries i'll probably use this here
i'll probably have to use the the spongy
material that they have here eventually
because we're we need to we need to go
far i guess pretty far
yeah
sorry it's it's really like a luck face
whether or not the city spawn or not if
you run into one they can be very far
apart and then there's one problem
kelly i'm gonna tell you the sad sad
story of nina maya inaudible
oh no did ian get in trouble
well i mean no but
so you know after we killed the ender
dragon
um
both me and ina made a stream
reservation to
um go into the end and get those lighter
wings asap yeah and
i
my stream was scheduled uh on the same
day as hers but like about
eight
eight hours or so after her stream
schedule starts
so that would be a lot of time for
someone
like ina to get her elytra right
right eight hours it's more than enough
so she starts her stream
and
goes into the end really motivate she
prepares so well she prepared so well
she prepared like night vision potions
so that she can see in the dark
which we aren't even using
um
but yeah so she was super prepared she
had like motivation as well she was
super motivated
then she goes into the end and she she
first of all first of all it takes her a
million years to find an ender city
like hours
of bridging and
you know
she went over so many islands that
didn't have anything
and then
and then she finally finds one
and
it's it's bugged
in a way that
it's broken and it doesn't it has
everything except the wings
absolutely ridiculous
that sounds horrible
yeah what a shame i want to go watch
that now actually i i know that sounds
like sadistic and whatever but i want to
go watch that happen
it was
pretty sad
and uh i think
that's pretty much the story so that
took her hours and and
she kind of gave up and then i came
online
i started preparing and from the start
of
pr
from the start of going into the end to
until the i got the elytra
it only took me like
one to two hours
i was so lucky i immediately found an
inner city immediately found the the
wings because i want to do a different
direction than inna did
i found
it so quickly and i felt so sorry
because inna was like
trying to really just
yeah i'm always like
for some reason i'm always so lucky when
it comes to minecraft
well let's let's let's hope we get a
good roll with you today then yeah no i
hope so too so far it's not looking that
good but it's because we gotta go
further
than before because you got me i'm super
unlucky no no no no no no no no i put
all my luck into getting into holo
that's about it
no complaints yeah it's just because
it's already been explored a little bit
in the closest areas
i need to drink water
grab some now grab your you're getting
my brain after my bridge
first bridge then drink
okay
but you know has her wings now
so now she's good
yay
but i think she only has
one pair and then
didn't she go to the end and then got ro
roboco senpai a second pair of wings
because roboco senpai lost her wings
so inna was so nice to look for another
one that's so cool yeah what uh what a
chad she's such a hero i'm telling you
yeah
even though they're so precious she
got new ones for rokuko senpai
wow what a savior
that's really cool tina is never right
now well
she only has a little bit no
i have i got the first never right in
the server though
oh wait really yeah
wait maybe it's not loading in
is that already explored um
uh
uh wait it's maybe not downloading it
just don't don't be sad yet he knows the
city though uh wait do you see that what
spawned over there maybe your thingy is
is that
ah i'm not sure we will see we gotta get
a little bit closer i guess your your
chunk didn't load in over there yet but
i see it maybe not you will see it in a
moment
okey dokey oh wait lead the way captain
it might be do what i can it might be
broken though i'm not sure
oh
wait we'll see
no dragon head so far
render distance oh yeah it has either
been looted before
or it's broken
i did fly around the end uh oh i can see
kind of aimlessly before and looted two
cities in a really random place so it
might have even been myself
oh but i feel like i went like further
than this
all right well we can you can check it
out well that looks so looks looted that
looks very looted
yeah how can you tell um because like
you see um if you look up
there there's a ship right it looks like
a ship
yeah
now
uh on the edge of that ship there's
normally a dragon head
which oh um whoa but but there isn't
which means it has already been looted
because the courtesy is you take the
dragon head um if you've looted it oh i
see yeah gotcha well that's fine we'll
find another one yeah question is should
we go
from should we go over there and then go
straight from there um
uh yes please
okie dokie should we check it out then
sure i'm fine with that i don't know i
don't want to waste too much time on an
already looted place but i guess we want
to at least go over to that to the
island is that all you had
yeah okay wow i i do need to
um should we try and get more blocks
from here yeah
let's do that okay
i gotcha i can i can do that
[Music]
oh it's easier to do than i thought yeah
just mine everything that's in front of
you
gotcha
a few more blocks yeah i don't see a
bridge either but yeah that's why it
could be myself because i just flew onto
those islands rather than bridging
oh yeah you can fly now so i guess yeah
it's it's a bit dangerous so people
don't recommend it so i did it off
stream
because the chat will always go like
no kiana is dangerous don't fly in the
end
i see i can see how it might be risky
yeah it is because like it loads in so
slowly while you're flying so quickly
and you might bump into something and
die that's the thing yeah and fireworks
i mean i wonder how the flying thing
works with like control and stuff like
that is it hard to control where you're
flying it's pretty easy to control but
the thing is like most of the time when
you fly everything loads in slower than
you fly so
you might end up flying into a huge
mountain and it kills you
which
might have happened before
oh
i take that as it has happened before
i'm not sure did it
did it
did that i mean did i die i definitely
bumped into some mountains before but
did i die
hmm
getting lots of blocks for you
almost died there you go phoenix never
dies at least
maybe just the the past the past one but
oh boy that jumps that's me
i'll help you oh good job kelly good job
yeah thank you you did the water
immediately i'm proud of you yeah
thanks let's kill him yep here where'd
he go eyes he keeps on coming back why
is he usb come on closer come on oh we
angered the second one too i'm using the
wrong [\h__\h] oh boy okay that's fine we'll
get them
we'll get those free end up girls
yeah
i can
shut up there we go
[Music]
nice all right now this one wants to
play
it would actually be really nice if that
one drops a pearl for you because
uh all right i think you picked up the
other pearl i picked up one but you can
get 50. oh oh okay nice
and because with the ender pearl that's
another way to kind of save yourself
when you're floating let's say you're
like really up high floating and you're
like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i'm gonna die i'm gonna
fall then you just throw the end the
pearl onto like the ground and then it
will teleport you there and you're safe
oh wow that's extremely useful yeah yeah
it is but i'm usually like always too
too panicked to do that kind of stuff so
i usually try to
just
go with the flow
and just
land
wherever or try to
float against a wall and save me that
way
smart yeah it's dangerous
man this place is super dangerous i
didn't realize like how
kind of clutch this whole place out of
out of those little out of that tiny
mining session i got one two three four
five six seven eight eight stacks of
slabs okay that's pretty good for now
that is a lot you can always get some
more later yeah yeah there's more than
enough so
i worries me though if this place has
been looted i feel like maybe a lot of
places nearby have been looted too so
i'll probably have to keep going for a
while um
the thing is normally when people loot
uh
uh one of those cities they're usually
done they're like okay i'm going home
now i got my wings so i'm going home so
the hope that i have is that if we
continue walking the next city we see it
will not be looted
oh i see i see hopefully looted
looted yeah
apparently i say it in a lewd way
i mean i kind of felt like the way i was
saying it was not too far off either
it's just one of those words where it's
unavoidable yeah right
yeah there's no way to loot and ender
city come on
check yeah i mean well now you're
challenging the internet
i don't know about all that oh for the
night
or like a nice
lingerie on the ender city find we're
going to get those [\h__\h] posts come on
give me those [\h__\h] posts internet finds
away
you know the rules and so do i
oh
all right here we are the ones that
i loaded i feel like i put like a sign
of like block stairs this place has been
it's kind of
small it doesn't look
very exp oh okay oh well be careful
callie um see this is uh your first uh
what example oh what's this you can
always block them with your shield
because there we go look at me i'm
flying uh
oh
and then i eat the course fruit because
i'm up very high
and i go back to the ground but until it
stops hitting me
uh i will not stop floating that
those are the the shulker boxes there
are enemies like they will keep on
opening itself up
until we kill them
like so okay we have to shoot him with
the arrow
yeah oh [\h__\h] oh okay why did i throw
that pearl see now we got some some uh
chest
um i just wasted that ender pearl excuse
me oh [\h__\h] oh no that's that's okay
there's more than enough that we could
get here if we wanted
why does it look so
unluted
is it maybe not
the city at the end of the game
maybe it's just really broken or someone
um thing i did when i uh off stream
looted the the cities uh
one of them i looted completely and the
other one i just went in there to get
the wings so
uh
purple stones i'm taking them they're
nice right
yeah i love the purple it could have
been me just taking the wings and then
leaving
and leaving but what this place looks
familiar to you
it's been too long but you know what
else you can get here to end rods
because there are more than enough of
those end rods the fancy ones that you
wanted
oh yeah i hear them
okay well oh i mean if there's no dragon
head
is no way that there will be a
the electrons right oh god okay
okay it's been a while it's been a while
oh god this fire
what should i use to fight them um i
always use my arrow like even while i'm
flying i'm i fight them i'm just that
badass
that's sick that sounds awesome i got
sick emil
yeah
i see it's over here i found the rod
yeah be careful so that they like don't
fall down be careful to loot them
properly oh yeah
well that's cool that over there is
pretty neat
there's another ship over there oh oh
there is the ship
yeah yeah there's usually only one ship
like that um oh ah
i guess if it's there i'm gonna go there
no
are you flying be careful kelly i'm
trying
always try to like bring yourself to and
like an area that has a roof
like like uh i'm gonna fly here see how
it stops me there oh my god no it sends
me flying again but i'm just gonna go
here
and i'll fall a little bit but that's
okay
gotcha
okay really this morning okay i want to
where is that where's the choker that
was attacking us i want to kill it oh
well whoa look at this big dragon
fortress thing that's cool we'll peel
this
shulker yeah yeah over there i want to
help nice shot
nice shot
okay nice shot oh he did just kidding
he's already dead
there's another one up there yeah see
oops
oh was that too far
[Music]
ah got
it yay
there we go okay now you're really good
at aiming
now we're gonna make another path over
there because those uh ships are never
connected so we got a build over there
yeah i saw that i was really wanted to
go over there
but i'm guessing there's
usually that's where the wing would be
but i'm guessing there's no no wings
there
it's okay it's fine well we'll find
another one yeah
legolas
and legolas
yeah
hey
stairway
black
well we can
um
put this here put this right here i'm
gonna try to just
mine into it there you go
okay there's
what
oh there are wings the cali they're
wings really they're wings their wings
it's good that we went in here what the
hell it was suspicious that it was like
mostly
mostly just
wings
yeah i can fly
look at all this cool stuff in here
golden horse
whoa i want all this stuff
wait you should take that pickaxe
is that okay that's a really good
pickaxe
you can ignore the shovel we don't need
to shovel and now
you
left click
the wing
okay
and that's i picked it up but that's
yours now don't you don't fly with that
one yet because we have to enchant it to
be actually like good
cool good and here you take that take
that end rod did you pick that up
i think i got it oh my god we got the
wings
what nice
wow what the heck
what thank you kiara no problem i guess
it really just didn't have the dragon no
wait it does have the dragon hat it just
doesn't spawn on the other side
oh my god do you want the dragon head
i'll i'll get you one
i'll get you the dragon head i don't
know if you see it but
i do i barely see his little ears i'll
build carefully
around it
yeah wow i thought we're just gonna have
to look for even more ender cities here
wait be careful actually stay stay over
there i want you to stay in the safe
space because losing the lights right
now would be uh horrible yeah that would
suck that would really suck a lot uh we
will put it in the inner chest
and then we'll be fine
so uh wait how do i how do we take that
again
what's in the really big places
what do you mean do you the other houses
over there big tower over there yeah
that's got all those they're basically
filled up with treasures and uh those
those mobs so we're gonna
even though we already have the wings
we're gonna go for all of those two
we're gonna get you remember
though right yeah exactly oh okay we're
gonna get you some nice material okay
okay
come back here come back here okay and
take this dragon head it's yours now
it's yay i have a dragon you can put it
as a decoration or you can put it on
your own head
yes
[Music]
the phoenix look strikes again
thank you for the help i i love it i'm a
cool dragon now
wow okay one second we're gonna place
the energized here for a moment and
i'm gonna take the shulker boxes out and
you're gonna put um if you right click
this it will be empty because ever every
ender chest has its own player's
inventory
yeah that's right yeah exactly so you
put your
wings and maybe the pickaxe put that in
there as well and the other the other
super cool stuff that you picked up
actually actually wait a second sorry
take this shulker box that i'm throwing
at you
okay
did you pick it up
yeah i got it then place the shulker box
uh somewhere
open it up
and put those important materials in the
shulker chest
uh-huh and then the shoulder chest we
will place into the ender chest so we
have more space
whoa nice idea did you put it
yeah put the wings in as well
and the damage oh damn it yeah yeah good
stuff yeah i got yeah good stuff good
stuff
all right let's see what else i have two
pickaxes so
the new one the one with the
oh yeah the slick touch i would put that
one in yeah
okay now okay
you can have some of this stuff by the
way the chest plate was that in the
chest or
okay it's not the one i have you can
take some of that and maybe the dragon
head
yeah nice idea you should put the dragon
head back in
get me oh i put my helmet in mostly
doodle
wait all
right bug me my helmet and then i'll put
the head in the box okay okay
and then mine the chest again
okay
see
and then put that right into your inner
chest wow infinite inventory the thing
is with energists
um
you can only really mine them with a
slick touch pickaxe which i do have so
don't worry i will mind this
i will take it with us okay
gotcha because if you don't mind it with
a sick touch pickaxe it will fall apart
into like and the pearls and all that oh
that sucks yeah that does not sound fun
yeah
oh she will go back
this is so cool and we'll finish loading
this
yes i want to get all their treasure i
want all their treasures
you're not safe from takamoto it will
destroy you
yeah let's get them i'm feeling
confident i'm not going to hold shift
okay
nice i immediately started veering off
the path and i'm like never mind i'm
going to press shift
what what's that noise ah that might be
an enderman
it sounds like an enderman usually
they're not in my ear i think you heard
something else usually they're the end
the men shouldn't be in here only
sometimes they're in here
uh
no don't fall down
good job good job kelly don't panic you
did it no he might come back to him yeah
yeah definitely
a man's not giving up that easy oh you
died julie were a dad yo
i i'm gonna take care of the stupid ass
shulkers
you can try while you're floating i
think in here you're safe even if you
fall down
you can try to shoot them while you're
floating that's that's my technique
gotcha
i wish you
should
use this [\h__\h] easy
got it
yeah got em
the chest uh has boring contents but
okay we get a free ender chest here
okay heck yeah
where'd you go oh i'm trying to find you
these are really complicated
i'm already uh
done here already cleared it
i hope you do but i'm taking out uh some
some end rods for you
thanks the fancy lightsabers i think
we're
done i think we're done here
uh wait it doesn't doesn't it go even
higher it looks like it goes way higher
yeah should we just gotta do some mining
i think uh-oh there should be like
stairs yeah yeah yeah i'm sorry i didn't
mean to hit you oh sorry oh that was you
i thought it was an enemy
no i don't know what's going on
don't worry don't worry
oh oh boy
make a bridge i used the fruit and now
i'm in trouble hang on where are you
where are you i'm outside hold on
are you letting me a minute are you
completely like outside of the city
i have no idea but i'm gonna survive
oh no fight me
that's why i never actually use the
chorus fruit once i am in the city
because i don't want to be teleported
completely far away
it
doesn't teleport you to a close by
somewhat closer
close by yeah sure
well i'm gonna build the the bridge
while you're uh
outside the inside bridge
okay oh god
there he goes
all right
got him
got it
hello
hello shulker john how you doing
where on earth i am oh my god
let me down
let me down oh i'm just outside of the
place i can come back oh yeah you should
try to
um
come back inside
oh boy i'm being hunted
by whom
um i just heard a zooming noise oh
that's an enemy
yeah did you look at him again
no
however in the thick of battle thank god
you never know elena falling from a
highest place and not you all right
yeah you would think it might it might
be a boy here we are
i survived
congratulations
yes that's not something that normally
happens so
good news
all right
where did you go
there you go rachel i'm on my way back
okay
i've already uh oh boy um i'm already
climbing up the next tower thingy
all right
me though in that case oh i stopped
floating
okay are you gonna oh that's where that
is
i want to go back to you and find you
wait i'm gonna try to find you
you messed up well i'm on my way back to
cali
it's okay
i'll be all right are you down here
now i'm on the stone bridge stone bridge
ah the one from the
elytra the ship
yep that one down there okay okay okay
otto
i see you
callie carefully i gotta run
carefully open
up yeah extra care oh wait be careful
there's no there's a monster there but
let's just try to go over here
all right
he's got to keep it oh it's coming for
you it's coming for you take me instead
oh boy
oh no
no
no problem just takes a moment oh weird
how about work there we go
okay so now
i already started building some kind of
uh bridge there uh oh
actually uh it it attacked me um so i
floated up so let's go here
okay and here
and
yeah
so this is where this is where the the
ender chest was i already mined it and i
took some of the treasure but it wasn't
really anything good there
except some iron and the sharpness five
sword
okay so here we go
up
all right
what is y'all
mm-hmm right okay okay so this time
i already built the
the stairs so we can go up
okay right and i already killed a bunch
of shulkers but there's another one
all right you will die soon enough
friend okay let's go that way yeah i'll
get them okay
oopsies sorry
uh when you come over here oh nice okay
i'll get them be careful to not drop
them to the ground like stand right on
top of them when looting them yeah
gotcha
hello
oh okay got it i've still got it in me
chet
i've still yeah you're killing it
yeah
tiata the sniper yeah chiata
oh yeah ttr 14 yesterday was great
yay i hope you had a good time yeah but
we basically cleared another mission so
i wonder what's going to come next right
do you already have like a plan on where
to send us next
um guess you'll have to wait and see
yeah
are you ready to come inside because i'm
building the the staircase again well i
just killed uh one of the shulkers nice
they should be dropping shells uh with
the shells you can build more of the
shulker chests which is really really
cool check that out
all right hold on oh there's an ender
chest here oh
you found the treasure
yeah uh oh there's a lot of them in here
i oh i can imagine
like why can't i knock you i'm really
getting beat up
there we go i'm gonna come to save you
when i stop floating yeah
all good just just try to shoot them
while you're floating with your arrows
yeah it's when the boxes are open right
oh it also works when they're closed but
i guess i do it does more damage when um
they are open yeah drop shells where are
you if you're not here
doko
did you go to
i don't know i went to a different
building
a lot of them
i see i see where you are
there's like a huge floor going on there
yeah i'm coming
it i think some of them dropped some
shells so maybe you can pick those
okay
i'm on my way naruto
i'll be okay getting ready to fight on
site got my best friends by my side
it's really cool sakura they're
beautiful
i mean the lyrics are pretty simple i
guess
yeah pretty simple
yeah perfectly simple
there we go what's that
that's something nice did you
i got a sugar shell
nice and your chest here you can never
have enough of them oh wait i want to
see your look oh
that looked good that was a good
treasure
yeah they all saved half for you
okay it looks so nice i fell down
three that's three fruit that's much
better than three gold for each of us
and two diamonds for each one hell yeah
there's uh there's a cool diamond store
and if you want it you can have it
because that's a pickaxe i want to take
a look at it yeah yeah it's a nice
looking sword
i can help you i have any more oh um
arthropods five is like a pretty shitty
enchantment i mean
oh it's only helpful if you're gonna go
out to hunt specifically
spiders oh what the [\h__\h]
why would you ever hunt specifically i
guess i'll
maybe i'll go home
yes
wait uh you don't have the soft touch so
i have to mine it with my touch
gotcha
oh i guess so wait i'll put my chocolate
chest down put some stuff in
they make funny sounds
yeah
yeah i put i put some end rods in this
uh shulker chest you want to take them
you're
um on the bottom right there's another
they're trying so hard to attack us
let's see
through the windows i don't see us
on the upper above your head i put a oh
chocolate cheese nice sugar sugar chest
the minute no no no take that end rods
okay
because
thank you you said you like those
i do i can't wait to decorate my home
with you in the onset as well
yo
okay
killing it
i am gonna put that in
okay i will mind his chest
yeah and i guess we can keep ascending
the tower yeah
what
we can keep going up the tower yeah yes
yes yes
cool and keep on mining everything that
looks nice to you i could also get you
that purple glass actually if you want
that'd be really cool i really do like
that a lot
only works with silk patch
i i do feel like i hear that sometimes
in rap songs
oh all the time yeah
they do sound like uh some new some new
age like did you sneeze again i didn't
hear it
chad says blessings a little cali
no i don't think so oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yeah we gotta build
that
where did you come from
oh boy a new friend a new friend
oh well
i can't reach him now
oh nice nice just let me fall down here
yeah that's perfect oh he's under the
he's under the stairs
i built a little slab uh at the at the
uh thingy that you can
go up to using the floating oh yeah
floats upwards
yeah
oh i'm floating again there's more of
them
give them the last hit nice yeah nice we
got them oh teamwork must be more
yeah teamwork
there's another one
all right
eat the chicken or cooked rabbit
oh god i gotta eat too
that's high up in the tower did i forget
the diamonds
what do you mean did i forget the
diamond over there i'll look on my way
back then
we're pretty high up but i wonder how
much higher we get from here
ah from here on there shouldn't be
anything i think
oh really
there's it there's a shulker there
though that's kind of scary
uh oh let me get those introduced
even over there i wonder
so many branches oh we'll see so many
branches around yeah but this is
actually still like a smaller
uh understatement really much bigger
ones
where'd you go oh
i'm here i'm here i'm here i'm in bed
i'm back inside i went all the way
around to get the end rods oh
okay so that's all on this branch let's
go down again
okay
do it
careful careful oh worry chat
i've got the situation on the perfect
control
yeah you've been doing pretty good
boy where did you go where where where
sometimes they teleport
also did you forget your water you can
pick your water back up here i think you
should take it did i leave it yeah
oh there's a lot of water
oh nice
beautiful
tinted glass purple color for it is
really nice
i mean you can totally tint glass
yourself and i suppose it's pretty easy
but
why not take what we can get here
yeah of course if we can get it yeah
there's definitely a branch that we
haven't seen yet i'm gonna go left now
there's an engine man here
let's see
have we been here oh that was close
i'm alive though i'm alive
[Music]
stay alive stay alive staying alive
slowly but surely i'll just oh boy
it was an enderman just walking by
no he's just chilling
here but did i elude it
did you go into this
no it shouldn't be this is familiar it
shouldn't be
i still here and yes it all looks pretty
similar
yeah yeah they do they do look
uh
i've been sent flying
oh boy
are you able to come up okay
yep i'm here
oh oh wait
we've been here
have we yeah i was going to say this
really reminds me of where we were
before but um i'll take that in drugs
oh this is a
hello i'm going to fight you right here
oh
this is kind of weird
i'm so proud of you callie you're gaming
thanks you're okay
yeah i get them i'm getting them kill
them we're fighting them nice yeah okay
we're going down kelly we're
somewhere apparently um i think
that branch
oh there's two enemies be careful where
you're looking at
okay
i'm super hungry i guess here because i
said that i'm going left
did i really forget them
how
how is that possible
it's hard to remember like what branches
you've been to and whatnot i did forget
them okay sorry uh yeah yeah the stuff
that i left there for you sorry i
probably should have taken all of
no it's empty now we can go yeah uh so
we went left now i think right we
haven't really been to
yeah oh there's there's gotta be
probably no treasure but i wanna kill
all of these monsters because i want
those shulker chests
yes
[Applause]
dime monster
um
they sound like soundcloud rappers
no friends
soundcloud rappers
yeah they they sound a very certain way
oh that stuff
you guys
yeah
yeah i got yeah i got stuff for tonight
yeah wait i'll take the glass
from
i'm not here they're still able to get
in here somehow i don't know how
what kind of weird it must be placed
outside somewhere
okay
cali is
sound cloud rapper
i've actually i never used soundcloud
but uh i guess there's a lot of good
music on there too
i mean yeah for sure like like any place
really but i guess it's got a reputation
of having a certain sound that's uh more
common on it i guess but nothing beats
uh
stuff
audio stuff i love audio stock oh my
favorite place to be
they do have some bangers yeah have we
been on this one yes we have yeah sorry
i'm getting confused hey have we been i
think there's
one that we haven't been into
it's this one right to the left
no i see the windows are already
shattered so we have been there oh we've
been in all of them
but we haven't taken all of the rods yet
oh
well i mean i have plenty i think but
now oh 18 i guess i could always have
more but have we seen everything
wait is there something connected uh
more on the
ground level too yeah maybe
i'm done we're done it seems like we're
done
looks like we're done with this one it's
a rather small city but i think it's
perfect for like introducing you to
how these cities were wonderful world of
the end and you didn't die and you had
your your body under control and
everything wow i can't believe it you
killed the shulker chest you killed
enderman you didn't panic when they when
they attacked you
yay
you did so great
callie hey i did my best
i did my best you learned how to conquer
an ender city
you taught me how to do it though i bet
that guy dropped something
you taught me how to do it i appreciate
it
welcome
we got a lot of loot out of it too how
many chokers uh shells that you end up
getting
i have four four did you put some in the
in your ender chest as well oh i might
have yeah yeah yeah i feel like we
dropped how many do you need to make a
shocker chest two
so basically you put um you put a wait
actually i will teach you now how to
create one because they they are once
you start using them you never want to
use normal chests ever again
cool so i i brought it in different
colors yeah you can you can uh if you
have like paint a dye
which you can get out of flowers you can
paint them in any color
it's really cool so i brought some
i brought some wood actually just for
this
purpose
so uh
i will give you some planks here now out
of those planks you first of all make a
normal chest
gotcha a stinky normal chest
i got it okay i made it and then
after you make the chest you put the
chest in the middle of the crafting
table you see it and then put one
shulker shell above and one shoulder
shell
below that yeah and one danny yeah
which is purple by default but you can
always make it any color you can even
make them black callie looks really
fancy really
wow i can do that later
as well so if i have a purple one i can
make it black later uh yes or does it
need to be when i'm making it oh okay no
no you can do it later later later
cool that was perfect yeah wait how many
wait i didn't loot as many shulker
shells as i thought i did
only two no way i would maybe i picked
them up do you want this chestnut no i
mean i have i have a lot so i'm fine but
i feel like i just
dropped oh they
they they don't always drop them they
sometimes just die without dropping them
i guess we had a lot of those
oh yeah i like to see i see
this shulker oh wait wait
that's my other shocker
oh wait i got a lot never mind
yay
okay wait so um
what we're gonna do next is
we put um all our important belongings
into the shulker and the stroker into
the energies and then we jump into the
void um aye aye captain so you just made
a shulker chest
it did place it down put everything your
armor everywhere yeah
i can't put the shulker box into a
shulker box yeah that's that's exciting
yes yeah two two eggs
i get that that makes sense
i don't even need these anymore but okay
this and
this and this
and this and this
and
i guess this and this then i just
mine them
yeah have you put everything inside
yep okay then put both of them
into the
ender chest
i just break them by hitting them with
my hand uh oh yeah i guess wait i can
uh yeah with your hand i guess if you
have nothing left
okay as long as it doesn't like hurt my
box or anything no no no
all right and into the end of yes it
goes
okay very efficient this is yeah
so futuristic i feel like i've upgraded
from unga bonga caveman
um to now i can see the future with you
and ina
future travelers the matrix oh we're
gonna try out flying in a moment and
then we can okay end it but i want you
to try out flying
all right actually you know what we're
gonna
give it mending at least um okay
because the thing is with the elytra uh
it doesn't wait does it even without
enchantment it doesn't break i think it
doesn't break even if you use it all up
i think or does is it only with
unbreaking
chat help me
is it so much fun
it it won't break okay so it won't break
even if you use up all the
um health on it
but but the thing is it's like you need
to put manning on it in order to repair
it
and
um you need to put like unbreaking free
on it otherwise it will be used up so
quickly
wait a second i put my
oh
wait
i guess i can't
mine it but all the other ones are in
here so i'm good to go the
chests right
yeah
yeah there's one energetic in here all
right okay
we can we can go we can jump into the
void we're ready to so you're still
using the same electro that you found in
the beginning right
yeah i didn't lose it yet
cool but people like miko's enviro they
have already lost a couple of electrodes
oh no
because one thing that doesn't save them
i guess is
falling into lava
or falling in or like dying no i guess
dying somewhere in the middle of nowhere
and then not being able to pick it up
anymore pick it up a couple five she
lost seven eight she lost seven elijahs
that's so much
that's so many
wait should we like sign uh i guess it's
pretty obvious that we looted it i don't
think we need to sign
are you ready to jump
let's do it together this time we're
allowed to jump
yes it's free because it's what we want
two
before my eye oh if only
i watched you die before my eyes anyways
successful
and now we're looking too
are you kidding me wait what's the
matter with you what's the matter why
why would that well at least the ender
chest is safe yeah i mean
oh and i was like the gunpowder talk
yeah let's put it down
uh and set spawn again because i think
your spawn was that bad
and
we are going to
[Music]
just
go back um just take some food and your
weapons and everything out again
so that we can defend ourselves outside
take your armor and
food
[Music]
a rose
oh
wrong sword
shield on the armor
yeah you're so silly just put it on
you didn't need to do all that you big
dummy are you a big dog you're not a big
dummy
you're saying it's the kids okay i bully
myself every once in a while you don't
need to do that
not no
i know
let me give you don't you don't use it
yet but let me already give you some
fireworks here
thank you
cool oh i should get the elytra too
right yeah yeah uh no keep it in it
first because we're gonna go back and
then uh we're gonna enchant it
okay and then it will be really good but
the fireworks and the you know i'll put
the fireworks in the box too we put our
the beds that inna gave us into this
dress wait i guess we can take them
again and you can take your metal slices
if you wanna
oh
into that always your melon
give me that
all right and we go outside oh
normal sky beautiful
fresh air
i can't afford to have made a mistake
one second
no problem take your time
i'm so amazed we both didn't die i'm so
proud
i know i really definitely thought some
death was going to be in the cards for
us especially because i'm involved death
and i haven't had a relationship i am
deaf i really can't avoid it but that uh
that went way better than i thought it
was yeah but i gotta say a lot of it was
your very careful planning and also
being able to make bridges very well
yeah bridgemaster
yeah you're a british master but you're
the balance master you balanced on those
one block paths perfectly
i did by by pressing shift
yeah and now and now you also know how
to run super fast how to zoom like
standard yeah
yeah yeah i'm real quick now sonic real
quick
wait so
now everyone in with has a elytra i
think good on i'm the only one that
didn't have one yeah but i mean you
don't it's not like you really needed it
until now yeah i mean i play minecraft
sometimes but just not a lot this will
help me though i think yeah really good
for traveling i just uh yeah exactly i
just really wanted it for for like going
on adventures to far far away uh by all
means
[Laughter]
oh my gosh yeah right they only found
what you got to do huh yeah
yeah they know how to get one if they
want another one yeah sure absolutely
how long can you fly with one firework
by the way um so there's uh three
different strengths of fireworks the one
that i gave you is the one that i always
use it's the weakest one but
i think and most people would agree with
me that that one is good enough
um so with that one
you get like a small boost and then you
can just glide until you
completely lose the
power
you will see in a moment when we
enchanted i think i got a mending book
um that we can put on it and i'm
breaking um i don't think i have an
unbreaking book right now but
it will be fine as long as you have
mending on it for now but you you should
make it your goal to put unbreaking free
on it
as soon as possible where are you i'm
breaking through there you are i'm over
here and enchanted with unbreaking i
wanna do i have do i have one breaking
ah kimmy schmidt oh you're right kimmy
schmittas
i'm breaking
i'm breaking two ah how did i get on
breaking free
will
give me schmidt bro ah you need ah
we need exp to
uh
enchant yeah
yeah remember that one thing
exp huh
well you know what maybe i'll just give
you mine for now and then you can test
it out at least oh yeah
give the stream a feeling of uh
we have done it successfully
sure
and then
i will help you enchant your elytra uh
another time maybe
or we go to the exp final i mean yeah
sure thing well let's just go home once
and then see
yeah see how we feel gotta eat food
yeah it's important
ah well i guess you can combine
unbreaking two with unbreaking two to
get unbreaking three
which
sounds like my map is off but that's how
it works i guess
yeah two times unbreaking too in the
game only makes unbreaking free
wow
wow that's strange that's not how math
usually works kelly your shulker box
what color do you want it to be
oh i want black and i want
uh teal
teal oh teal yeah like a blue green yeah
i think i have a lot of dye at home
actually actually red let's do red easy
easy
black and red edgy colors you know what
i can teach you how to make red dye here
take this red flower
whoa okay i think that's the red flower
oh right that can to me yeah take um
okay i got it one enough yeah
i'm gonna get a couple
yeah i get a bunch of those
red ones we're gonna make dye out of it
sure yeah there it is if you put like
you don't even need the crafting table
if you put the red flower
into the crafting box in your inventory
one is enough actually kelly
oh okay put it in there
and then it should give you red dye
okay
yeah i got it
a lot of it
okay
thank you oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] wait go back
go back go back oh oh creeper
okay
got it
nice kelly
oh there was another creeper there i
guess one wind and dice
your bones yeah that's right you don't
like that mr bones do you yeah you only
know mr bones
there we go yeah sorry daddy sorry
that's cool we're almost home my
deadbeats are extra well-behaved these
are rambunctious ones that need
punishing
rose bush right
oh that rose bushes give two red dog
pranks
rose
nice
all right we're pretty much uh there
just gotta go through the water let's
ignore them and ignore that
skeleton
yeah you do skirlington
do you feel like you're not you guys
learn some
new minecraft skills today
yeah definitely there was a ton of stuff
that i didn't know you taught me thank
you teacher i'm happy i feel like it's
funny because like
normally i like have stuff under control
but whenever i play minecraft with with
people i always feel like a little baby
baby student
baby
learning with my teacher
it's fun
for enchanting with mending chat how
much exp do how much levels do i need
one one mending on an elytra how much
does that take two
let's
see need to jump
with fireworks you can make that with
gunpowder right mending needs to and
fireworks yeah i can teach you how to do
that too actually so
you need guys
but you also need uh paper
oh okay so paper i actually have a farm
for paper i will show you so for the
future if you need it take as many as
you want
thank you it's right now i will remember
kfp
nice i'm gonna remember okay
so wait i show you
let me show you i show you you're still
here yeah okay yep i'm following we are
back this is a jumping technique but you
are still so speedy hey uh if you're if
you're like if you didn't eat enough
food then you will not be able to run so
fast oh i see so this is where the paper
farm is basically i have two
you look inside and you see sugar cane
but out of sugar cane you can make paper
so this is basically a paper farm but
you can also make sugar out of it so
it's also a sugar firm
wow vickery yes i like it
so
whenever you need those but i already
gave you some fireworks for so far now
just for trying out very good
and
okay i will just give you my elijah now
because i want you to try out flying
yeah
i believe i can fly let's sleep first
though
yeah and we gotta get to an ender chest
well you can uh i'm placing i'm gonna
place a bed here for you there you go
thank yous sleepover that's where your
bed used to be kelly
they're still uh
they're still the little europa league
[Music]
a shiny prison
yeah with these bars like you've made a
shiny prison tiny prisons yeah why you
want to make a shiny prison
it just sounds like fun
i'm going down
you can go back up again
i'm going up you've got a secret little
basement in there oh my gosh
shiny smiley prison
the shiny smell
all right callie
the wings candles um uh-huh just uh
uh here for testing out
you gotta put them where your chest
plate is so you can't wear a chest plate
while you're wearing a lycra
i see oh wow that looks really like uh
there's something like seductive oh yeah
yeah yeah it mixes with the
with the shader
or optifine or something cape that you
have
oh really so should i turn on shaders no
no i don't know i don't know you already
have a special cape like normally if you
play normal basic ass minecraft you
don't have a special cave but you have
some special cookies
yeah and it mixes with the elijah
so wow you're gonna put the fireworks in
your taskbar
and i don't have them yet because i put
them in the ender chest oh well then let
me let me give you here more
oh thanks
on the task bar somewhere
and then you jump twice
first of all try jumping twice you will
you will feel some kind of difference
yeah whoa
yeah and then when you're on the second
jump you gotta uh
make the rocket go boom
give that a try maybe all right let's
try
yeah oh no you gotta aim kind of upwards
i guess oh i see i see okay gotcha okay
i can do this i can do this you can
i don't see anymore
see was that did you use uh one or like
when you're flying you can keep on like
letting the fireworks go off again so
you can fly longer cool try and do that
then try again
[Music]
whoa i'm flying around i'm flying to
ollie i'm going to the
express
yes ladies
amelia
tell me what's good you feel the freeze
there she is this is amazing
this is so cool the wind goes through
your hair
[Music]
yeah that was that was beautiful this is
so wonderful i'm having so much fun you
gotta be careful i'm on amelia's clothes
to not like um fly into a mountain for
example oh okay because as i said
sometimes they
load in slowly and you can't quite
prepare so always fly very high
on a high level
um and you can always if you're if you
land you gotta try to have a soft
landing by going uh
getting closer to the ground like slowly
not like i see not like a like straight
dive into the ground you just gotta try
to land like an airplane basically
imagine
you are an airplane oh a diving board
yes i'm an airplane and i need fuel and
if there's water around it's always safe
to just dive into the water if you need
to land
cool yeah
wow this is awesome
accomplished mission accomplished whoa
that looks amazing in someone's house
pink didn't i did i give you a mending
book before i think i saw some
enchantment books in your
in your chest
was that did i get you in the water oh
let me see it night i saw you
you see me slam dunk into the water yeah
yeah you have mending
wow you got mending in your chest
oh heck yeah so
what you're gonna do in the future
to make your own elytra work properly is
you're gonna take that mending book and
your elytra the unenchanted one and put
it put both of them into an anvil
and okay and then you while you do that
you can also name the
the lighting yeah i gotta i gotta think
of a good name i'll think of a good one
because mine are called hot wings so you
gotta top that off with one more
yeah well yeah that's right one that's
perfect for me i'm gonna do that
thank you so much
it's wonderful i love it
there she goes
there she goes i took some screenshots
of you flying
yay
i'm having a good time
let me go up to kiara and
oh i feel like i'm definitely gonna run
into something watson tennis racket
hello let me see if i can find another
ferris wheel oh it's much closer now
than i than i felt it was before yeah
you can go so quickly between phoenix
then and the spawn point and your
carnival and everything
uh-uh uh-oh uh-uh
did you hurt yourself in the water
i ran out of fireworks ah yeah yeah
that's see see that's why you need a lot
of fireworks like one stack is not gonna
last you very much
i understand oh i wanted to look here
uh
that was pretty close but you know what
we're safe we're good yeah i do not have
i'm breaking but i can probably get one
from phoenix then later on
all right
i'm gonna go back to you now okay where
are you
i'm here
that's a goat
you're goats
are they new animals they're new yeah
oh
i captured it
wow yeah nice
that's cute yeah goat it's too perfect
they're they're so adorable like they
can actually jump up um like several
blocks rather than other animals who can
only jump up one block yeah goats can
jump up many blocks
you ride them right yeah
oh
do you want to give me back my electro
no
[Laughter]
there you go i'm playing with you yeah
thank you for teaching me the ways of
the glorious lifetime it was nice
picking hot wings for a spin as well
that was fun hey
wait a second i want to turn on my
shaders for a screenshot of both of us
me too me too all right one sec
i'm gonna turn them on as well
let's see
video and
wait where's your electron now in the
inner chest
yep okay i'll go grab it yeah let's take
it together with the elijah's on
nice idea
that's good to me and where should we do
it i like how my my wings i don't know
have you noticed it kind of looks like
my cape looks like a phoenix too
oh
let me see
yeah it does have like that kind of glow
to it right like the pattern on it you
see the pattern do you see it yeah
yeah it's like a it's like wings like a
firebird yeah so cool yeah i don't know
how but thank you okay uh you need to
you need an and the chance right
that's right there's one at the
at the portal main area okay yeah
i see so how do the designs get chosen
for the elytra is it random normally it
has no design it's just like kind of
black
oh but you can add one on
not really like if you have a oh my gosh
it's so buggy what the hell oh my god
it's so laggy very laggy
it's usually not that laggy what the
hell
very often did they change something
it could have been
there has been a new update definitely
changed something
um but yeah so uh depending on what's
like if you use optifine or if you use
um some kind of shader they sometimes
give you some fancy patterns on your
cape
interesting okay okay let me read these
real quick
i that's what i needed for now i think
our render distance was too high
yeah
okay okay oh yeah good stuff
yeah yeah put that on that suits you
very well
thank you i think so too i love my hay
now let's while the sun is going down so
nicely let's take a screenshot here
yeah nice idea the sunset with the
perfect we should take it off our backs
maybe
ooh yeah let me get a couple photo of
artbacks a couple screenshots yeah
e all right yes i would take a
screenshot again uh f2 and maybe turn
off the interface with f1 first
okay
wait next idea
yeah peace
peace peace peace oh wait wait position
okay
yeah yeah yeah okay like this that's a
little too close
all right perfect perfect all
right cheese wait that's that's two okay
gotcha i'm gonna take a couple
cheese
you got that huge snoot now
i do have a big old snoot huh maybe you
can smell better now
yeah
extra extra sniffing senses
this has been amazing
[Music]
thank you kiara thank you for the
fantastic adventure that was so fun hey
i'm glad it went well
so much about minecraft i feel like if i
wasn't with someone who knew so much
about minecraft i'd be in big trouble oh
don't worry about that i can teach you
more we can go on another trip sometime
soon please now
with the wings we can fly together
go on a trip yeah yeah yeah yeah we can
go anywhere
down i can show you red cows if you want
i know especially i got the new place
that you found yeah we found me and ina
found a special island that has red cows
that give endless milk and there's like
mushrooms um growing on top of the cows
what the [\h__\h]
that sounds amazing minecraft is cool
it's just full of new surprises i have
never heard of
it is it do be like that damn so
thank you kelly for the collab today
thank you um to the audience for
watching and
sweating sweating and shivering together
with us
some clutch moments
there are some clutch moments for sure
but you know what uh it ended up being a
great adventure and i'm glad we went on
it together and i'm looking forward to
the next adventure that we have
heck yeah and thank you audience as well
for cheering us on and uh and
entertaining us with your quips and also
helping us yeah every once in a while we
appreciate the heck out of you thank you
i hope you had fun yeah i had fun
i hope the chat had fun we don't we all
have fun
of course you have any announcements you
want to make
no not not really i mean people
definitely no coming up i think uh yeah
i think my audience knows that song
cover coming up in okie dokie oh yeah
sounds good
all right all righty i mean i guess
that's it you've done it
[Music]
i'm excited i'm happy
yeah me too that was a blast even though
my frame rate is like 10.
the render distance go go escape and
then uh video settings and then on the
top right random distance maybe put it
down to like 10 chunks or something like
that
video settings render distance yeah
10 chunks yeah something like that
should make it much better
let me see
maybe that will be fine
yeah i think it's much better
a little better a little bit okay
and just make sure that the elytra you
enchanted before you use it you could
use it already but it's not really good
enchanted first okay okay okay okay okay
that sounds good i'll be extra careful i
will not misuse this fantastic gift i
have been given yeah
you will thanks guys
oh it's new i'm mori i hope you'll
remember me this is kiara she's phoenix
and minecraft
my craft expert
so thank you for coming on our journey
you guys and i guess we'll catch you on
the flip side yay what should we end on
yeah that's good
all right i'm gonna turn on all the
effects here we go ready
three
two
love you guys
[Music]
do
you