[Music]
foreign
baby
[Music]
I forgot to turn off DVR oh damn
can I turn that off still
oh yes I can
[Music]
thank you
I'm not playing without you
[Music]
preparing
I didn't do anything
[Music]
and wow
um
boom boom
I hopefully you will be a video a video
[Music]
I love it
boom boom
boom boom boom
wow
hi
[Music]
I want to make a bingo
Bingo Bingo Bingo it's not getting
bigger on your side guys just a massage
[Music]
just so much it's just for me because
everything is so small in my eyes
oh yeah that's about okay I mean I see
some gray there is it is that is that
um
do you know guys not like it you
probably don't like it let me fix it for
you anything for you
[Music]
okay have you got it and we got it oh I
think I got it
oh perfect
[Music]
guys how are you doing today will be
hopefully a short stream I can't
I can't stream too long
oh I didn't Loop oh that's fun
uh let me turn that down though
oh sure
can't go too long
hyper chat on baby someone's in a good
mood
[Music]
is a German word
that I that is actually so good great
top still no I don't see gray at the top
um I don't think there is one English
word that describes that
is being weird okay now it's fixed now
now it's working
[Music]
still a little bit loud really
foreign
in English is there also one word that
could describe it it's such a good word
it's like depends on how you see it
is how I would uh translate it but um in
in German it's one word see I was
good and
um farming some stuff there not really
farming I mean
chilling
now there's free Stacks in there no no
a matter of perspective yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah but see you English peeps you
don't have a real word for that
let's just say
missing Mason please return at base
house
it's amazing Mason where was he supposed
to be
Mason
uh Mason what do these words mean
what Mason
[Music]
yeah just trying to flex to you guys how
cool German can be guys all I'm thinking
of when playing this game right now
you know what I'm thinking of
[Music]
can you guess it
perhaps
how do you
yeah
[Music]
um
wait why is Chad so delayed did I not
wait
no YouTube stuff ah my dear Harvard
student YouTube Studio very slow on uh
hyper chat let me use the other one
[Laughter]
as I expected it to
[Music]
it has way more of a delay
yeah yeah is going to do Diablo stream
right
[Music]
I uh the pro I would do that too because
I got Early Access too
um who's behind the Diablo again what
company is that again they kindly gave
everybody who played The Early Access oh
yeah I have the latency wrong don't die
now I can't change that now I think
the DVR had changed though if you update
it shouldn't be possible anymore I think
[Music]
um Blazer yeah so so kind of them to
everybody who played The Early Access
they gave a uh that are like everybody
who played the beta as I did
and some others did too got Early Access
and the key and I wanted to but um I
don't have time also it starts at 1am I
think my time
yeah
yeah I was if it would have started a
couple hours before then I would have
done it today instead of Minecraft
[Music]
oh yeah Kyla is playing it and I think
both times of reservation
of her I think
yeah very nice
Blizzard's always been pretty nice
you know Cooperative with like streamers
very very nice
unfortunately I can't make use of this
niceness at the moment oh was it want me
to
maybe it was wami that I saw not botan
senpai
um you don't think it will work at the
start but the beta was fine
[Music]
what was wrong with the D2 Resurrected
didn't I play a details it Resurrected
wasn't it fine
I remember the color possibilities yeah
so I definitely want to play with
Kyla
let's play Diablo next week
[Music]
I already told her uh via DM like weeks
ago
um that we should play together
unfortunately I don't have time this
week actually maybe else on that next
week maybe end of next week I don't know
I don't have much time let's go
don't
um
immediately Max your level
desirable
for Co-Op to be around the same level I
would say yeah right
okay make second character for collab
purpose
problem solved
[Music]
ah
that's probably a good solution
um how do I play this game oh I didn't
tell you guys though what I was going to
say amtron will stop using uppercut okay
homework card
good
because we should do also with Kelly or
so yeah I got I've got Kelly interested
but I think she hasn't touched
the better she hasn't touched the
previous games ever I think
and corny
so she probably doesn't know anything at
all and then crony crony and I played
together before actually that was fun
that was fun but that was um Diablo I'm
getting confused Diablo II resurrected
that was that was the one that was the
one yeah I'm getting confused yeah for
people group
that's pretty good
pretty good group I would say good co-op
group
but yeah I don't know like if I start
playing should I play alone a little bit
and then you know level a little bit and
then the second stream could be co-oper
so I don't know honestly how we're gonna
do it
[Music]
um this is by the way this is acid
stream where's
um Phoenix then
[Music]
uh um ah that way
because I remember building this good
old times
good old times
[Music]
I can't sleep waiting for Diablo full
opening in five hours oh you want to be
there you want to be one of the first
ones let's fight the world boss together
oh hell yeah
oh yeah hell yeah is spitting hell yeah
okay so the stream is called clean up
wait I still didn't tell you
there's someone tell you what I was
gonna say that I am
playing Minecraft right now
I want to be as small as a cat
feels like
I'm really shitty version of tltk
I just want to play tltk Man
good night
oh it feels like you know Big World lots
of Green Mountains this and that it
feels like it's totk but in like really
low resolution low quality low budget
yeah that's what you thought because
yeah
tears of the Kingdom
oh man it just feels like a downgrade
right now I'm so sorry
it's the tltk brain brought
um
Kyla yeah she's resting until her next
stream which is in
four hours or so four and a half hours I
think
[Music]
tears of potential
um so yeah I haven't touched uh Phoenix
Sun in a long time
and I
I don't know how to efficiently clean up
though
like okay some I don't know how but some
of these guys they
uh got lost and they're in places where
they shouldn't be but most of most of I
think this should be you know pretty
obvious you see most of these like
blacksmiths
are in this area hi one night Ron how
you doing
this got lost who are you Kimmy Schmidt
why are you here because you're supposed
to be here
this is where the book people are
um
uh ready to love love is that how you
because yeah I need a way to kill some
of them I guess without
the Golems killing me back
so I don't think I've done this before
but I think it would help to make it
clearer
uh so should I get some lava is that how
we're gonna do it I actually even have a
bucket
uh why not
I'm not no I'm not gonna confine in my
people
that I've worked so hard to make a nice
living space for
nope because I I prefer it I prefer it
when it's like looking human Niche and
I build her bank nobody's gonna use
Phoenix anymore but apparently they
pull he used Phoenix then and I will
always be the third person so so maybe
it's okay we just need a little colon
yeah and then ideally
what we could also do
is get rid of this like make this flat
so it's easier to see that there's more
although oh no then I didn't I try to
cut it off completely has anyone even
left over there
foreign
[Music]
did they die or are they really on the
other side
waiters I don't remember bringing every
everybody of
tetsuo and Boots pants guy
[Music]
sometimes they're behind the house no
donate the cult wants to fall now does
she need more like uh jobless ones
I'm not gonna bring them over to her
that's a lot of work out
you realize a lot of work
they did no they don't die
the [\h__\h] tetsuo right and Boots pants
guy let's see if we can find them I feel
like they're gone
[Music]
let's not do this when I run
oh tattoo is here
boots pants guy
put put I don't remember calling someone
who's pants guy
oops excuse me move please boots pants
guy
[Music]
um
Aerosmith okay I was No One's Gonna find
you up here what do you have do you have
something useful
[Music]
a multi-shot cross boom
oh this one's not really like
useful anyway you see
it's okay if we can't find them right
yeah I must have you moved the Mason I
don't recall seeing tattoo outside the
village he's not outside the village
she's inside
here tetsuo but the boots pants guy
what the fence guy
I can't find boots fence guy
maybe he also got lost and is in a
different section
you buy sticks ah yeah that's what I got
him for huh because like I I thought
sticks were also an easy to
achieve in masses product yeah that's
probably it
I don't think he gave the gun oh
did I guys you have good memory and he
wasn't named what did the boots pants
guy have I guess some good prints and
some good foods is it him oh my God it
might be him
because he got feather falling why does
he not restock uh cause he doesn't
wasn't there an issue with giving him a
a workplace workstation
that might be him though
that's probably him right
I didn't name him huh
do I do it where
um
where do you like it's been a while when
you get name tags from
oopsie
I probably have maybe one more name
that might actually be him lucky lucky
guess
okay so what if if I make like a lava
pit I push them in there
hopefully they won't like accidentally
walk in themselves they don't do that
right I just have to be careful with who
I push in
actually has a good chest plate
wait no it's not him anymore
this one
is it good
I am a motherly instincts yeah okay
let's get some lava where is the closest
lava pit
[Music]
um just a little bit just a little I
think maybe there was some over here
maybe
[Music]
otherwise we can go
down here it's we haven't gone there
through this entrance in a while
man
nostalgic how do we do this again our
way down is down is with this one right
is it is it is it though yeah
I remember building this
with Ina or with while calling you know
or so
these stairs
um okay
lava lava lava lava
level
[Music]
put the ones with names on boats first
ah okay good idea
thank you
the Lost obsidian mine
I think I'll find some lava here
shouldn't be so difficult actually I'm
scared
I want a place
the light
bloom bloom light flower thingies
that's my instinct right now
[Music]
yeah she I think she may have helped me
with the elevator too I don't know
the days I'm sitting in this lava true
true way there I forgot that I forgot
that wait
oh
I am having an aha moment remember when
I was shook up the other day that
obsidian is a real thing and it's one of
the four stones or so in volcanoes
like dried love
oh
oh that makes so much sense now
where's the obsidian where do I have to
go for the obsidian
chicken do you understand what I just
realized
are you friend or Foe
oh
I would say I mean oh maybe he I don't
know
they all have eggs
mind blown actually mind blown that
makes like so much sense now like that
that in Minecraft
you pour water over lava and it becomes
obsidian
my God
[Music]
the realization
is endless where is the lava
let me he had an egg yeah but it's my
egg I'm supposed to be the caretaker
I'm not gonna give it to random green
strangers
you can't trust green strangers
and the name of the sword
I guess my 30-day trial is over but is
it 30 40 days in Game of 30 days IRL
because it hasn't been 30 days in game
I haven't played
Minecraft for 30 days since
where is uh where is this
no
what is this Stone again
but this one doesn't
come out of
Papa wait is it is the lava just
completely gone here has it all been
like obsidianized and now it's gone
three days in Minecraft forever how do
we know of active usage I would hope so
[Music]
let me get this stuff
yummy cool
[Music]
mmm yummy
ah
be me
that's it right no so there's some more
up here
maybe I'll be greeted by some lava while
I'm doing this
pickaxe is dying what's what pickaxe is
this
how to open inventory
here
it's just a normal but it has bending
not names though
who are you
I don't recognize you
don't eat the rocks
well I'm aware that I am not a Goron
and I am not a [\h__\h]
I'm never never Goran nor [\h__\h]
I get it oh my God amazing
[Music]
only a [\h__\h] or Goran would eat uh
stones
[Music]
why is there so much coal here and no
one ever felt like mining it
interesting
it's so dark though
[Music]
or is it reserved that someone Reserve
this
cone by any chance no right no it's a
mine now
you're lucky you're cute
we lost her well I'm lost why did you
lose me I'm lost
I need to find the co the the not called
the magma already I'm distracted but now
this is as distracted as I could be in
totk you know
I could be even more distracted there
and I would be so happy
oh
I opened a path to hell gold
there's gold I wasn't looking for gold
but oopsie that's that's not the right
thing
and blue stuff
[Music]
was it was that the thing
wait um let's get rid of
uh wait wait ah [\h__\h] okay let me place
this one torch
foreign
[Music]
looks like fried chicken too
happy come here
come to me come to kiwawa Papa
I'm Minecrafting guys I'm Minecrafting
Hallelujah
[Music]
a Minecrafting
this is not what that came to do
no laugh is that silly is a real Stone
I guess I should just see everything in
Minecraft and and assume that it exists
in real life even never right
you can't you can't call me a fool
because I fought obsidian or partially
thought obsidian wasn't real when
there's stuff like neverad which is also
not real right
[Music]
I'm not gonna find the accent if I do
this
[Music]
don't look kfb
okay
more cold than I left around okay
[Music]
um um
is that yay [\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off
I found lava I don't think it's like the
one source but
I found it and that's important that's
the only important thing
never ride is not real
don't [\h__\h] me
[Music]
nah
yeah just beat them is pokemon-ish isn't
it I called it old Pokemon Sony vgm
got it from audio stock
audio stock is goat
okay there's quite a bit of lava around
here what is that or an ink sack
foreign
[Music]
even though like last time you know I
was looking for diamonds remember and I
found oh
nothing and I was gonna say I'm already
like finding a lot more things of value
holy
[\h__\h]
that is a beautiful Diamond vein
oh my God
how long was I looking for diamonds last
time
where am I
I meant uh
[Music]
am I what am I at 11 where was I looking
last time way lower right like somewhere
minus
I have a shock of true
[Music]
I was struggling so much to find
diamonds and suddenly I they're just
being gifted it is it's always when
you're not looking for them
right how do I already have also so much
of that oh my God
let me
ah
[Music]
let me put some stuff in
why do I have uh wait I thought it was
gold golden apple
oh
what is that what's that what what was
that red stuff wasn't that Redstone oh
my god I've never collected Redstone
before I think
why am I even so excited I don't know
stack your chicken yeah yeah okay but
problem is I only have one bucket but
that's enough right
okay
don't burn yourself kiwawa wow
get up is this gold no that's Iron Man
okay let's go back up can we find our
way back
do you think I'll find my way back
this stream is fruitful so far so far
yes it's good because
it's not going to be a long stream so I
hope I can make
at least a little bit of like progress
or something that looks like progress
I think I didn't really have much coal
anymore at home so this is good
um also
nice five hours no no for real no no no
no no no no no
I I want to practice some more dancing I
already did dance practice today I did
dance practice and then I went swimming
for a little bit actually to cool off
because it's really [\h__\h] hot
and I don't have a [\h__\h] AC where's
the exit
maybe here
[Music]
I just see diamonds you know what did
you see diamonds near the water I think
it's an ink sack
yeah you think you mean this thing
that's that's just the ink sack
I don't think there was anything else
[Music]
swimming yeah I just went swimming a
little not really like for a purpose of
workout because the workout was already
the dancing and I was I was quite
exhausted
already but you know what you know like
actually I keep I kept on saying I know
I kept on saying the recent days that oh
I need I need time because I need to
learn this choreo
um I said that a couple times then I
never really
did it because I also had like
recordings to do and I just didn't find
the time yet so I think yesterday
yeah yesterday was kind of the first
time
for me to attempt I hope this is the way
attempt learning those new choreo which
is for in case some people are not
caught up up to date
[Music]
um I'm currently
making an EP album whatever you want to
call it
and
I want to make an MV
for at least one
of those songs at least like a pretty
Envy
in the end I guess I'll be
making choreo or uh commissioning a
quarter for all of the songs but right
now I just need it for this one
and
um
what I'm saying
wanna get does this lead up
I'm gonna take this
oh
[Music]
I found the accent yeah nice
sick okay which way
[Music]
this way I think is that
no maybe not
because I didn't see the store
um as I was saying oh yeah yeah Sal
I'm working on that and I've been doing
a lot of recording for Dad and uh yeah
finally yesterday I had time to start
learning choreo
and my God it it's already immediately
seemed very is it here
very overwhelming
it's it's a fast song
fast energetic song
wrong place
you said
I can still reach it I think yeah this
is there is there uh not wrong place
m fast energetic song and therefore the
choreography is also fast and energetic
and uh
I I haven't been really stretching my
body so I feel
uh already muscle soreness and stiffness
very yeah boy
nearby it's very complex too yeah but I
asked I asked my choreographer Kiana
to
at least keep the choruses always the
same because in some songs sometimes you
want to like switch up the last chorus a
little bit for example
only having the last chorus be a little
bit different or so I said no please no
please no I'm already overwhelmed let's
let's just keep it the same so I have
less to learn
yeah and then I just yesterday
I was sweating buckets and I was
hammering the choreo into my head
hammering it so hard you know is there
boats anywhere we have to build them
I use both before here
I remember it
[Music]
um
there's one boat
might need a couple more
let me see
gonna be great yeah I I think so I think
so I I just hope it won't look too messy
because of the lack of practice practice
a bit more today but you know
um
it's
it's difficult
very difficult two boats
and then
yesterday after I feel like I got pretty
far with like roughly learning the
choreo
[Music]
but
um I'll wait who's more
[Music]
I still felt like everything was looking
messy and I wasn't feeling confident in
remembering everything and then I I have
this
it feels like every time
um when I learned a new choreo
it's really interesting how
[Music]
um
the day after like you sleep over it for
one night
and then you wake up and you try it
again and it feels like you know it
better than what you like where you
ended it where you left it at the night
before
it's really interesting it's just like
overnight it was like naturally
registering the details in your brain
and suddenly you know it's
like pretty decently
um yeah yeah yeah sleeping on the muscle
memory it's it's really helpful yeah
sleeping over it I've had this happen
several times I was hoping for it to
happen this time as well and I did it
did hmm that's why you need to sleep
yeah also like not only when when
learning something like that I guess it
also works with like learning a language
I I feel like sleeping over what I
learned in Korean classes also helped me
um
yeah
so then I jumped into practicing a
little bit today and I was like I I hope
I remember this and I turned it on for
the first time and and I immediately
immediately clicks
and that just feels so good I'm like oh
thank God I really don't have much time
to learn this thank God thank God my
brain is not
you know [\h__\h] me over
thank you brain you're the best
you're the best I love you
[Music]
good job brain
yeah okay sure why not
um
but then today
I just I didn't practice that much yet I
practiced for a little bit then I went
swimming
um because I oh those are different ones
because I felt like I I just I was over
I was overheating I was sweating I
didn't wanna
and I felt like I was already doing like
pretty well in terms of memorizing it
anyway so no need to like torture myself
yeah yeah
[Music]
worst case the good thing is for the
music video they'll be Cuts anyway so
unless I really really want a
um
a like seamless dance
uh dance cut you know what I mean
like a dance version
without cuts
it would be nice it would be nice but
there's no need for it and for the Envy
there's Cuts so I can like focus on each
part I can like take the chorus only
[Music]
okay we got them in the book
what kind of swimsuit were you wearing
yeah I just I just randomly grabbed one
of my swimsuits out of my swimsuit
drawer I actually have quite how many
swimsuits do you guys have huh
I have quite a lot oh can we speak nice
why not okay I mean let me pushed this
one in here damn nice okay that was
someone
I think
one zero four four oh wow that's
actually a lot zero four two zero one
one one zero two oh I probably have like
six or so
[Music]
um
that other one isn't even the gold belt
do I even want him
who are you
what do you have
power five who went in there
okay as long as you guys have a job I
guess whatever
[Music]
okay
yeah
cute ones I have one that's kind of not
I have two that's kind of sporty and one
of them is you know the one that um
jenma bought for [\h__\h]
and I brought home even though design
wise it's really not that cute
it's really not dead nice but
[Music]
so freaking Gemma swimsuits oh man
people without context I feel so sorry
for you you need to watch my streams
more often if you want context
um
let's get this one in he's not the other
guy I want
can we get can we make this work
oh yes maybe yes
[Music]
where'd you go
you know I was just wearing you know a
light pink
[Applause]
um swimsuit that has a big v-cut why
you know clothes of like a really big
v-cut
before I felt like oh
only with badonkadonks like Cali or so
or crony
[Music]
that can look good but I feel like at
least with swimsuits even even I can
look good in them I have picked anyway
yeah yeah yeah I do I don't want to I do
I do it where did that guy go
foreign
[Music]
damn it
you look on anything boss thank you
so crowded wait wait where are you going
oh
okay two golden ones
this one also needs uh also he doesn't
even belong here he should go over there
maybe I can drive him over there later
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
uh where are you guys going what what
did he just get himself a job why does
he Sparkle
what if you Sparkle
what about here what's going on here
that's that's a dude
who are you
yeah you're nothing I'm I'm at this one
this one
even though I mean is this one even
worth
fighting for
[Music]
I would say no
and this one this one yeah
this toolsmith
um
don't lose don't lose him yes yes yes
that was easy
new employees Sparkle I see it guys when
you also become new employees
who are you where are you going
why how did they even come over here but
in the first place I don't understand
what there we go
power five okay nice I think we got like
a lot of the important ones
in place now
um let me see if I find anyone else
that's like really important what are
you guys doing yeah they probably know
they probably know what's about to go
down and they're trying to escape
one night run
um can we get everyone oh
no
come come back here
um
would you mind
walking over here
wait yes yo perfect perfect
um
let's just
[Music]
get in you're important I need you to
get in the boat this is like Titanic
you're one of the important ones
you have plot armor please get in why
can't he not get what's the problem
what's the problem
[\h__\h] off out there stay out
can can he no no no no no
[Music]
[Laughter]
is it the position of the bed maybe
and the I mean the boat position of the
boat get in
would you please please please
what the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] off [\h__\h] up [\h__\h] off
[Music]
now what now
[\h__\h] out okay let me just Purge a
couple of them that will make it easier
right but let's sleep first
[Music]
today is the Great Purge
it was going so well
man
[Music]
okay good morning
just you know what would be best if you
guys stay in there
um
because there's like the one night run I
don't want him to accidentally stumble
into the lava
uh yes under any circumstance
also I feel like are they actually
walking through I don't know they
shouldn't be able to right
only I can but they can't right
at least if I do this they definitely
can't
[Music]
okay
quick check
I mean bricks are nice but you guys
aren't really special
what about him
I'm breaking silver sword no one cares
no one needs that but if I don't want
them to make more babies again should I
get rid of some of the Bands
it's
[Music]
not even annual maybe biannual
I'm not gonna Purge you guys no I
couldn't do such a cruel thing now I
just need to figure out how to place
this
ideally
just hear a puddle of lava
what's the verdict judge Kiana
hey
no I've never watched The Purge movie
can I put this here even though it's
just a half block
[Music]
yes will it overflow please don't
overflow
it's not okay
isn't it feeling hot to you
[Laughter]
it has begun yeah
and I carry no consequences this is the
perfect crime
holy [\h__\h]
oh
nice nice nice nice hey you hey you I
want to show you something I want to
show you something it's it's
um something really cool hey where you
going where you going where are you
going let me show you let me show you I
found this super cool thing yeah yeah
just look at me my beautiful face
don't get distracted don't get
distracted
hey hey maybe I should vote him too he's
really yeah
he got it got himself a job oh because
was was one of the guys were jobless huh
he got himself a job thinking that he
can escape me
no you're wrong you're wrong in so many
ways what are you doing stop working
he thought that will save him well it
might it might let me remove those those
were from the guys who just died huh
done
scared of breaking us I'm not taking
away someone else's job right
the job will not save you no no follow
me I have a different job for you
come here over here over here
maybe I should place it here
so that they would be more interest and
they would stay close that's a good idea
get your job here free job here
yeah yeah yeah
yes yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
bound to happen it was bound to happen
but you are destined for the same thing
just much worse
wait maybe I should prepare
what the [\h__\h] why is it not ending
there you go maybe I should prepare a
water bottle too okay
[Music]
get in get in why are they so squeamy
Young
okay ah
squirmy I mean I think that's the word
squirmy
yes
yes running yeah yeah spread the fire
a nice nice nice hi who are you ah
you're not important
who are you
this one it wasn't even necessary to get
them into the boats to be honest like
they're they're good at staying clear
from it but I guess
if I have so many of them running around
it's like easy to
push the wrong person around okay hi
guys do you not want a job it's a job
opening right now it pays really well
[Music]
trust me oh yeah oh you're going for it
you're going for it no no not there
that's not no no no that's not it that's
not it my friend
I wish I could leash them
no no no no no
uh if I have bread in my hand will they
follow me
just wall them in and pour lava on top
oh
kiwaba always must make things much more
a little difficult does it work with
tough
[Music]
does it work [\h__\h] hell
it's difficult though they move around
so much
this is actually
[Laughter]
wait a second wait a second
there's this wood dough there am I gonna
be okay
[Music]
oh
um oh
how do I where do I put it careful
put them in a boat
these people
there's not space for all enough boats
um
[Music]
Dazzle burn pick it up quick
maybe a water bucket in addition would
be good but
[\h__\h]
um
huh what was that oh
they're still capable of like jumping
over there
oh
sorry
I hope he was just a pumpkin pie man it
was just a pumpkin pie man
here they can jump over it's okay these
ones are protected in there
and these ones well
[Music]
well
[Laughter]
[Music]
that was beautiful and you you're
telling me the Golems are not gonna take
revenge on me really are you sure
that seemed very obvious
obviously done by me with evil
intentions
[Music]
um
let's see what's upstairs
why are you sparkling
the ones tried to take you with him
impossible they're not capable of such a
thing honestly can I not just like place
it anywhere
[Music]
wait I'll get them I'll get them to stop
moving
[Music]
how are they how are they able to climb
everything
[Music]
[Laughter]
I didn't do anything I didn't do
anything I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry
as long as I don't kill them am I okay
and as long as the Golem doesn't see it
I'm scared I'm scared
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry
trapdoors to help
um that's okay
uh am I fine no but I don't think anyone
saw it but I don't know if that's uh
important oh God oh God good good good
good huh
um
[Music]
one like run no I can't kill you get out
of there get out of there now
[Music]
was that him
nah he's still in there
get out get out not you why not run get
out of there
get out of the park Corner
get out of the secret no no no
please you're so important to me I can't
have you dying like this
oh
I think he's gone
I think he's gone I don't see a name tag
it might be a different one let me check
uh journey man okay okay free people at
once guys
uh should I do it from the other side
again it was kind of easier oh [\h__\h] I'm
stuck
I'm stuck
[Laughter]
oh
yay oh it's so beautiful at sunset or
like night time isn't it
that was a slow death
oh that was beautiful tetsu gets to
watch all of that I hope he knows that
I'm so proud of him I would never do
this to him
see how beautiful this the Phoenix Sun
is at night
with a nice
a nice Shader especially you see how
beautiful the the floor is shimmering
me so shiny
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
No Escape my friend I wish the fire
would spread to him can I
um
[Music]
oh okay that works wonderful
don't run into me
crazy Burning Man
[Music]
Times Like These that remind me why I
both Revere and fear you what does that
other word mean I don't even know
I'm doing it a bit more like risky you
don't have a job right
but it's it's okay come come one more
step over here
that way I can very accurately kill
guys don't don't mind him don't mind him
he's he's just feeling a little bit
overheated oh he
buys
how'd you do that
wow this guy got some stem he might be a
phoenix
I respect okay
he might just be a phoenix
[Music]
he was left with one HP
I think he was this one was okay it was
just normal one right
[Music]
okay dead good looking good
um maybe I should get like more and more
and more
name tags because some of them are
possibly a bit unclear what does he have
nothing what might oh cause his job is
too too low
uh the one about the beds actually
should I get rid of some beds
still
to make sure they don't make more babies
let me sleep in this one actually the
people don't seem to be able to sleep in
this one it's always empty
[Music]
we're parenting villagers let's go
what are you doing here
[Music]
[\h__\h] is it the wrong one no right
yeah no that's the one I wanted to kill
yup yup yup very accurate Alyssa who's
wearing what they're for
they need for but I don't want them to
breed at the moment that's why I'm
purging them
what did you open did you not read the
title you shoot the oil
[Music]
does he know that he's in danger when
he's close to me hi guys
[Music]
I'm playing with fire today
playing with fire
[Music]
okay I'm good I'm good I'm a phoenix
guys I can withstand this easily
it's not like so little of them have
names it's just you have to get really
close this is Silky boy
say hi to Silky boy
okay I'll get rid of
um this bed
[Music]
um
Buzz Lightyear
okay these don't have names do you guys
have a meaningful job foreign fire
aspect
Riptide fires but no one's gonna wait
for ripped Riptide is even on one is
good is it not
Riptide I should keep right the other
one maybe not so much let me turn on the
light in my room
one second I'm kind of Tangled with my
headphones
[Music]
um
where did I how did I tangle so much
see the delay in the answer Riptide good
okay yeah if they would make the names
visible from like a little bit closer
that would actually help what if I place
it like like here is it is the bed gonna
burn
I was scared of Riptide to die but
hmm
horns free now I don't think we need
phones free
[Music]
I can't really place it there well
anyway okay you can live you can live
you on the other hand
[Music]
how do I do to you
Frost Walker though
fun
but I don't know
not really interesting
let's see if he dies properly
or somehow these are kind of oh
sometimes they survive with one HP which
is actually kind of like inspiring silky
boy reap tag oh
respiration I've got a Riptide freed and
I don't need oh somebody got a new job
mm-hmm
if I've got a whipped at free I don't
need a Riptide one looks at you
and I don't need a Riptide one
it's a Riptide one
[Music]
is it gone oh thank God oh [\h__\h] I wasn't
able to pick it up anymore ah oh no I
was it's in my bucket but it's kind of
too late but I killed two
one star or two birds with one stone
yeah
[Music]
just don't make new babies okay guys
you're looking pretty clean right now
I appreciate that I'm gonna get rid of
this bed
I'm hoping that
we're just places here
hoping that
Maybe
um this is a good amount let me count
should I count we have one two three
four five six seven
eight nine ten eleven eleven beds this
looks like more than 11 people
so they shouldn't be making babies right
okay and then we come back and maybe
make some more names hi what are you
guys doing here
[Music]
what I'm doing what I'm trying to do
with the floor I just just repairing you
know there's some some little breaks on
in the floor that could make people
oh
slip
stumble you know you know how it is
who are you
no one okay
Tombstone oh I guess you could see it as
a tombstone yeah visually remove all the
bad cilia down and put down the exact
number you need them do they even need
beds though to actively effectively work
the only the only thing that really
needs is a workstation right
or do they need a bed
oh
yeah aren't you did you didn't I see you
die a moment ago
honestly what the [\h__\h]
I'm going crazy
wow instead kill who are you
no one why are you stuck in there you
know what I'll I'll relieve you release
you from your pain
I don't know how it
I can't place it here
here doesn't seem to be I enough no uh
he's stuck I need beds to restock okay
um
[Music]
wow wow
Shawn Mendes I guess maybe all of them
though not all of them but
and how
far
[Applause]
are you he's important oh [\h__\h] who was
that
that I'm not sure if he had a name tag
because I was pretty close to him and I
ah it's getting too cocky but uh silky
boys here are you tired is here Buzz
Lightyear is here
uh
Poseidons is there
wait the Sparkle is it restocking
because even the ones who already had a
job are sparkling are they restocked no
it wouldn't make like a sound it was a
matter of time
so it's okay if I think um
the outcome wasn't too bad
it's it's you know
it's okay it's okay
I wasn't able to pick it up man
that's so scary
silk touch you got silk touch too oh
actually okay you can live
aqua affinity
I don't think anyone needs a book for
that I think every everyone is Affinity
to Aqua
wow okay I think they're fine I think
they're okay should I count them it's
kind of difficult to count them oh oh
God one two three four
five last
uh wait wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
one two
[Applause]
[Music]
one two three one two three one two
three four five six seven
[Music]
um
seven
it's about seven I think it's about one
two three four five six oh seven eight
nine ten ten okay okay a seven seems
kind of low ten it's around ten one two
three four
five six seven eight nine ten eleven
twelve
twelve beds
maybe maybe I miscounted but I think
it's safe to at least get rid of one
more bed what do you think
[Music]
oh
no I don't want to do a villager trading
haul how many times
[Music]
you mean the wall Guy the one guy
doesn't need a bed
he doesn't need a bed he's stuck there
forever I don't think I can
maybe if I pour from
here oh
I don't want to leave it for too long
no it doesn't affect him
in there
hmm he's legit stuck okay
now count again well again what
why oh they're now sleeping oh oh look
at this
before I felt like even the night they
weren't they weren't properly sleeping
okay one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten eleven
okay hey I'll make you a bed
[Music]
hey
perfect number you know what I feel like
I want to place a door here
uh
uh or like trap doors sounds help maybe
so that they just stay in there
I'm not gonna
give them like a one space cell I don't
like that but
I feel like a trapdoor or something
would be okay
[Music]
do I have any
here
even with a trapdoor though when you
walk through
they might Escape though huh
what should I do
any idea
was that was there a better way maybe a
button outside
and metal doors
button inside button outside
that's a button right
too much and it'll be hard to find the
one you need
not actually plenty of space in there
I think that's plenty isn't that what
I've been using over there
[Music]
trap doors are the right hand
too many inches
that's not that small small
carpeted fence where did that door go
out here
anyway it's free rain it's more free
changing what fauna does
okay us
they're still sleeping so I can renovate
in peace
um I just hope that this is not
someone's workplace actively
[Music]
I'm thinking
just doing something like this
can I I can't why
because half slap Maybe
yeah nice
button
where can I put the button here
no
[Music]
um
uh Wildfire plus here
it doesn't it doesn't connect
it doesn't connect though
wait I'll put the button here
ah it also doesn't connect
foreign
[Music]
what
ah
slap in front of the door okay
you mean uh
door opening slab with do I need iron
for those or I can also just do a
metal one right a wooden one but it
would look nicer maybe with a Batman one
but I don't have iron right now do I
have iron
iron
no iron
with the slab in front put the slab in
front
ah you didn't mean that I thought you
were talking about
pressure plates put those
[Music]
in front
or white slab and the button
wait but where do I put the door now
wait do I still keep the others
[Music]
okay I mean it looks kind of weird but
it works
do I need this uh this is kind of the
way
[Music]
and I think I have the perfect spot for
this
[Music]
here
Construction in the middle of the night
I'm so sorry
ah wait they're supposed to be like a
little bit inside
okay
[Music]
um and then like this
and then I might as well do something
like this looks nicer maybe
oh no does it
but I think it's not too little space in
here
oh let me clean this too while we're
actually
wouldn't be nice if this was like one
more spot over there but then this one's
not
nothing symmetrical here I guess
[Music]
good enough for now yeah as long as I'm
not making any more new employees which
I'm not planning to I could even Purge a
few more
[Music]
but as long as this amount of people I
think it's okay
and they they can't open this right
we can't right click on buttons I think
might as well put them on the the fence
walls what
what no what I don't know what you mean
but no
no no no no
can I make this
cleaner too while I'm here
[Music]
why is it like this is there a reason
my mommy is probably watching the Stream
and probably happy that I'm finally
working on phoenixson again
[Music]
to see healthy with this
remember
do you remember
[Music]
yeah I can do this
uh
the shape what what's the shape shape of
what I'm in love with the shape of you
oh beautiful why didn't I do this like
earlier
looks looks nice oh
[Music]
God damn it I just realized
I don't know if I have enough but I'll
try
[Music]
at least just roll for now
nice models are playing Minecraft yeah
she told me that recently she felt like
a little bit motivated again
this house by the way no one's using it
right now or is it oh yeah all right I
think I
kind of evicted them
it's just decoration now maybe we should
put a sign or so Aerosmith ah one night
run once lived here ah good times good
times
maybe I could make it my place in case I
need
or we might get an Airbnb
[Music]
does your mom like the tea at the case
rooms oh I don't know she hasn't
mentioned it
I'm not sure if she's watching my totk
streams
she watches a lot of my streams there's
certain streams that she
doesn't wouldn't watch I don't know what
it was but
[Music]
um
certain types of streams she doesn't
enjoy as much but most of the time
she seems to be watching like
almost anything really
where's the other one
[Music]
did you see that
that's a lesson to you
a lesson to be very careful around this
area oh yeah this this is like this
place is cursed
this place is slightly cursed in case
you haven't noticed she doesn't seem big
on the vagina pictures oh yeah yeah she
probably
wasn't watching like
fries who knows though actually I don't
know maybe she did
um oh
the Dawn is Breaking it's early morning
the taxi is waiting blowing us on
already
um so
boat what they don't do that is this
boat bugged out
and also he's been sleeping like for
years
do you want to get up maybe
no he just wants to sleep oh now he got
up
already I'm so alone so I could die
oh Fire Emblem maybe two yeah but I'm
usually quite surprised when
you know I find out she watched certain
streams like
that's a long-ass stream you watch that
damn
okay wait so I think I'm pretty
satisfied with the cleanup uh over there
and here I actually also like cleaned up
most
you're you're kind of useless
you know what that means wait wait wait
wait
wait wait wait wait wait
wait you're trying to
find safety with the cool people it does
it won't work it won't work this this is
perfect thank you
[Music]
ah
mm-hmm
okay let's count some beds shall we
one two three four five six seven eight
[Music]
oh and then there were a couple there
were a couple more over there
[Music]
uh nine ten eleven twelve beds
one two three four
five six
six seven eight nine ten eleven
oh uh
ah 12 perfect because this one's
supposed to be purged anyway
[Music]
um I want to hurt them
oh perfect so and then we should have
the perfect amount oh you got a job okay
wait what now your heart directness ah
he's trying to go undercover he's trying
to be a chameleon
wait wait stop running around
stop running around
[Music]
I think it will save you to stay close
to one I'd run huh
[Music]
yay
die while looking into my eyes
[Music]
I want to look into your eyes when you
squim oh it's a live one HP left huh
[Music]
okay nice nice
who are you
[Music]
um
okay okay okay
it's time to get some emmers didn't I
like take a lot of emeralds
from someone
didn't I take some for Kyla and then I
put them somewhere
somewhere because I'm going to buy name
tags
hold on my homie changed me possibly
yeah
we're looking here
or from fauna maybe I don't know
from fauna
sheesh oh yeah right she has like a
million emeros
um where did I put them probably in my
precious
chest let me check out my brushes
I've been taking this road in a while
wait I have my own boat
please
and honestly even just so that I feel
like I made Phoenix Sun already
a lot better
but you know what I would actually like
to do because like even when I put down
smaller signs or when I try to make it
visually like obvious
what kind of people you can find where
people visitors seem to struggle
with finding what they're looking for
so ideally instead of using small signs
I feel like I have to make like big
signs you know self-made signs
and write like blacksmith and Cole and
then
um enchantments and books Etc
you just need to fix up the farming
error yeah yeah but I feel the farming
area never really had so many over oh no
over what to say overpopulation
tough there
[Music]
Charisma right one sign at the entrance
be enough will they look at it
oh
oh no
[Music]
um should I leave something here
and the lamp is lately maybe
[Music]
um
and I see nothing else really
the Apple okay I'm going back and we're
gonna get some name tags name some
people and maybe look at the farming
area
no they will not that's what I'm
thinking
that's what I was thinking you know
they won't read the smaller signs anyway
okay
you guys know
what let me tell you something
uh last week
[Music]
oh
two
of my acquaintances
that are I would say around my age
either maybe a year younger or a year
older maybe well I think pretty much
around my age got married
actually I mean
one of the couples I was acquaintanced
with both and the other couple more with
only one person
two and even on the same day not not to
each other there was one that was at two
that I knew that got married and the
other one was
yeah I kind of I guess got to know the
the husband but I wouldn't really say
that that was my acquaintance
[Music]
on the same day yeah so like my social
media
I was looking at so many
stories
and pictures and all that of the the
wedding ceremonies and all that
and yeah I was like damn man
these people are making progress in
their life huh
good for them I hope they're happy
they looked really happy
and pretty in their dresses
yeah
they say May and June is wedding season
oh yeah yeah
they do don't they June bride hey do
that they have some name things for me
thank you
yeah
there's more thank you
guys do more thank you
level up baby others uh can I can you
wait there's a name tag like a lot uh
end level kind of thing
wait who needs to level up
do you need to level up yeah but you
don't have name tests
um
[Music]
because I don't
now they're all already max level aren't
they
[Music]
revive you can't imagine no no not in
particular I just wanted to mention like
that that was a crazy coincidence oh and
the thing is like
I wasn't invited to either
because I'm literally I can really
realistically only call myself
acquaintance not friend
kind of sad I know some other
acquaintances who were invited to the
acquaintances wedding
um but I was not one of them
you know it's okay okay I I didn't
really like feel like I I I was like
supposed to be there or so I didn't feel
like it was
insulting or anything or sad that I
wasn't invited no no no that's why I'm
saying we're not really friends we're
more like acquaintances because we don't
like talk much or so
but the thing is I would have liked to
be there in fear right if they would
have invited me I think I would have
gone because I don't know it's nice
wedding I mean
[Music]
no
I I wanna I wanna
be at a wedding
today and all that you know oh okay I'm
out of emeralds okay let me name some of
you guys wait I need an I need an anvil
right
I think there's an anvil in the
um blacksmith Village
you look at an important role at BFFs in
our room yo I'm waiting I'm waiting I
sometimes I ask them when are you guys
gonna get married
come on come on and they are actually
like
um I feel like when I ask
uh RBF I have I have cup like a best
friend
um whose boyfriend also you know because
they're really nice we're we're friends
too so but the the boyfriend
um sometimes I ask when are you gonna
propose to her when are you gonna
propose her and it always seems like you
know
they probably would already if they had
like the financials and all that for it
I'm not being that friend the thing is
like they're so perfect for each other
and they're so sweet and I love being
with them they're the best couple I know
and and and and they're just they
they're so functioning and they've been
together for a couple years I I was like
um my BFF you know when she had
different boyfriends uh that's when I
got to know her many years ago and uh I
didn't really like her old boyfriend and
thankfully soon after they broke up and
and BFF still to this day you know she
she talked we talk about it how it's so
good that she's got him now and and ah
it's such a pleasure to watch them and
be with them to be the third wheel
around them and makes me so happy
because they don't really make me feel
like the third wheel
no shipping real people but they're
already shipped there's no shipping them
they're already shipped
yeah
um
no no no no they're also like yeah yeah
I mean yeah would be nice but you know
you know
you want to be the cupid
[Music]
no I'm not the cupid they did that
themselves I'm so happy for them what
names do we need anyway uh
uh what names do we need you don't have
a name
you are the boots pants guy maybe you'll
just be the boots boots Penske
oh I can't type oh Japanese keyboard or
what
oh
I can't type what's happening
any idea why I can't type
it's not caps lock
[Music]
okay no
I can attack
[Music]
help
oh he's got feather falling free boots
pants
pants who's the bands guy that's good I
like that
no I I already ah
thank you
[Music]
how do I
what's pants guy
feather falling free can I really type
so much wow okay
[Music]
um
puts pants guy Fed Up only free
even without the feather falling I think
like he's got decent stuff like overall
if you lose all of your armor and you
just need some fresh armor just go to
him he's a boots best guy
who's got a name what about you guys you
don't have names do you have anything ah
[Music]
you lied to me he's not the feather
falling guy
how do I rename him do I need to spot to
put another tag on him on top of this
one or
he wasn't the one he's got
um
I don't know if there's anything worth
mentioning
I I would say he's the put pants guy
it doesn't have feather falling wasted
um
[Music]
and feather falling
not even a real name I just want to make
it obvious
for visitors
what he has
um Poots pants guy
has been renamed and the right one is
just checking again feather falling
although unstocked there we go
um decent
decent
um mining tools guy
he's the decent mining tools guy
how do you just take one I always forget
decent mining tools guy
named
hopefully with this in the stock markets
the Phoenix Student stocks will rise
again
who do we have here a librarian sells
power five who's in the wrong place
obviously
maybe eventually I'll be able to move
them
because the other guy next to him is
useless isn't he didn't have a job maybe
he can go to civil drop I don't care
anymore I don't want to purge anymore
I've already purged plenty
that's all and
you also in the wrong place
I don't know if I want to name the
farmer because the farmers all have the
same stuff
um
okay Power
[Music]
because he's got the power
or do we have a joke the name and Power
anything more interesting power
five oh man
we shall make it clear I guess
Canada why Canada
because
Farm are you trying to make a Japanese
pun I don't believe you guys are
that well knowledge
and maybe I'll approach the farmer oh
it's dead
um because farming is kind of you if you
if you give them something you give him
Kana and he'll be like Oh Canada
[Music]
because it's money get it wait where's
your your power five
and wait you actually
wait you also have decent mining tools
decent mining tools guy number two ah
but okay I am
I need the iron to build a
um
um an animal right
I'm gonna buy one here I think I think I
need to go home once
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
you think they can read that
on first attempt decent mining tools to
two Ls what's the hey Chad what's this
and Mining to LS what's that mean hmm oh
I don't know I guess I'll go somewhere
else
um
raw iron I have to [\h__\h] smelt that
[\h__\h] what
up here
do I have
very cold too
I think so
answering my own questions as usual
[Music]
wolves
ah what else
um I mean I have one here so I can use
my own as well
[Music]
um
we show decent mining to us
that's right wrong it's a small tools
why not
uh anything else we may have needed
maybe in the book area do you guys
remember anyone without a name that had
something nice the riptide
there was a rip tag one on the riptide
free and the riptide free had the name I
think the riptide one didn't oh and
there was another silk touch guy
maybe we can make silk touch number two
for the silk touch guy
no more
silky there was a silky boy how about a
silky girl he was a silky boy and she
was a silky girl
can I make it any more obvious
that they sound so touch you should buy
it give me all your beautiful emeralds
they were selling silk touch everybody
wants it
you need it to mine obsidian or was it
never right I don't remember it's even
one I just don't know yeah
sir silkington the third Beautiful
beautiful of what I've already cause
chat is so slow today I made the setting
wrong I'm sorry
that is so slow
you know guys what I cooked yesterday
the Caribbean Caribbean Steel
[Music]
but without the pancakes
changed bgm what about the pancakes but
it was pretty decent
the street was pretty decent I'm gonna
eat it again today
it had
um black beans
um
uh bell peppers and a lot of like one
whole big uh sweet potato that basically
makes up most of the stew uh Tomatoes
but the tomatoes basically dissolved so
much and you don't see them anymore when
you look into the soup
and I think that's
it for the main ingredients and yeah I
made it with um coconut milk
uh and some some spices
um
yeah yeah sorry sorry candle you're
you're good I think for now for now
how's my iron doing
beautiful 14 ow do you have any more I
don't need so many do I
an ambulance make an anvil
um
blocks of iron
[\h__\h] iron
do what did I run out of iron I mean no
problem because we have iron sources but
did I
did I really run out of iron
it's
done got some tattoos some iron I would
I win
uh
here block of iron
free right
one two
three
I'll make a backup maybe what am I doing
[Music]
um
no we already have Island Farms I always
use Enos because it's closed anyway
two anvils
we go back
[Music]
good night good night bye bye
let's go
and we name a couple more people
and then we look at
uh
[Music]
the farming area but you guys have to
when someone asks oh where should I I
need silk touch where do I get singles
can you guys tell them Phoenix and go to
Phoenix and it has recently been you
know cleaned up a little bit
so it should be easy to find what you're
looking for
how do you make these ones again do I
have any more
and then wait what is this
um
deep slate break slab
Stone
I have I have
I don't know anything about the game huh
after so many Minecraft streams that you
watch you still feel like you don't know
anything
are you paying attention
basalt
deep slant please
I got no more tips at least not here
um
you don't want anybody else
hey really
really is that so
[Music]
maybe at home I have some more deep
fried
I'll put one more here
okay uh
wait
uh wait
when I run and
hmm
meh
[Music]
I don't think that's anything special is
it
I don't know
[Music]
um
same
TBH really just an iron
okay
sell
your iron gets hot emeralds
now
um time no okay let's not let's not make
false advertisements
you're the right person
yeah
okay okay
sell iron to him please thank you
um
[Music]
building tools building tools you're the
building tools guy
[Music]
um
Bob the building tools guy
okay
there's a fisherman I don't know what
you're doing there
named named named and not named not
names wait ah
your decent
mall but the tool is in your name
how smart I wonder who thought of that
okay they're all named I think pretty
much just except the Fisher or what
about you guys tetsuo and yeah farmer I
don't know what to do with the farmer
actually went upstairs
there was Aerosmith right
and and the Golem yeah we don't we don't
talk about what's going on upstairs
we're gonna talk about that does he sell
quartz does he sell quartz blocks uh
probably not
no maybe in the future maybe if I trade
some stuff with him
I always like bricks bricks are nice I
should build something with bricks
okay
yeah some farmers were named yeah the
melon Lord
okay what do we need here you
you are just a glowstone gun
[Music]
oh God they move so much
we need an aqua Senpai what do we call
the aqua what's what's the fan name of
Aqua senpai's fans
huh
secret vendor yeah that one was secret
don't tell anyone
uh Chat is dead
no idea crew
okay he's the Acura crew I mean we need
one Aqua crew we need
um that's you we need
Spider-Man
[Music]
write it down guys because we have to go
elsewhere
Spider-Man
uh Aqua crew
um
random [\h__\h] guy we'll find the name
okay let's get that for now because my
brain is gonna overload
crew
I don't think anyone will buy the cool
Affinity but you know
Spider-Man
that's what that was Ryan
and the random [\h__\h] guy what we call the
random [\h__\h] guy
random you little [\h__\h]
Ram um
random [\h__\h] guys
you guys don't have good ideas either
today
can that be more original
exactly that
um
random [\h__\h] guy okay you guys are very
happy with my names today huh the ones
that I come up with
okay now we're just gonna give it to the
right people among all that mingling
you know accidentally give it to the
wrong guy
um
yeah wait we'll get a name for you
eventually too you wait spider guys uh
oh okay that's good that's good
[Music]
um
Spider Guy Spider Guy Spider Guy Spider
Guy
Spider Guy
lay down now you can lay down that's
okay
Aqua guy really wants to sleep probably
because Aqua Santa is not streaming
right now
[Music]
okay nice and we had the random [\h__\h] guy
maybe is it you no you're [\h__\h] sorry
because I don't because I don't are you
no
it's you
no you're Shawn Mendes you don't see the
names when they sleep do they do you
who are you
yeah it's definitely a random [\h__\h] guy
[Music]
okay
we can't we could call him zombie lover
[Music]
Buzz Lightyear
okay we need another random like a
lesser random [\h__\h] guy oh it's silky
girl wait where's silky girl silky girl
here
girl
so good silky girl
foreign
[Music]
might be inside each other right now
it's hard to tell
but that's Destiny that's just destiny
not what it was Buzz Lightyear
huh wasn't there a silky girl
I wish it was elsewhere
wait so what did we say we needed
another random [\h__\h] Guy and
um the zombie lover I think there might
be two zombie lovers
[Music]
and random [\h__\h] got two
it was confusing
ah
okay two zombie lovers
and one more random [\h__\h] guy
I'm running out of exp though
okay
this is is Silky girl here
is it you no that's Kimmy Schmidt
um you don't know
did I like manifest her in my brain or
[\h__\h] did I kill her
maybe I killed her
name is
okay because I only have two name tags
left
okay
uh needs some EX
he wasn't uh fauna's fancy fish farm
kind of close
from here
I think so
um because this is like uh now wait I
don't know
I didn't
[Music]
know it is
directional East
where's East where does it say uh South
East
yeah that's where all the Isis
[Music]
oh sure
makes sense ah what's that
what the [\h__\h] is that
something new
funny turn to friend it's pretty fancy
to me
ah since like the village
yeah fauna's fancy Village
that kills the Phoenix in stocks
Ah that's Kyla's thing
oh
okay
in circular motions
I did it nice landing
[Music]
um hmm
okay that was a fancy fish killer oh
backup swords and
um
I just do I have to take off something
I kind of want to meant this
oh
on the way
can I take off this
nice landing thank you they're not
they're not they're not spawning fauna
there they are there they are
faces oh yeah it's mending
it to be mending
I just wear my levels wear my exp ah
they're not going to me because I'm
mending okay
okay
wait
foreign
do I have to take off these things
no right as long as they're like fully
mended now it will come to me I think
will it
food
oh
I don't want to waste summer with shorts
on
fireworks [\h__\h]
if they have mending it's fine I wanna
get expedo ah 19 oh
suddenly 19 29 oh
oh wow okay
well that's plenty
that's actually plenty
okay
uh now we can go back
uh if we put our wings back on
[Music]
that
[\h__\h]
[Music]
is it like some laser there shooting at
me
[Music]
I guess I haven't killed them properly
yes I AFK base gunpowder Farm after last
stream and in the beginning of today's
theme you saw I was still standing there
and uh you saw free Stacks in there
because I took like free Stacks I think
uh all right
I
took free Stacks it was empty and then I
stayed there wait wait wait wait wait
wait where uh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h]
uh
um
[\h__\h]
thank you
can the gliding at least bring me on to
land
that I recognize if
where am I where am I
am I not where am I
oh
where am I
[Music]
oh my God
oh
[Music]
um
time
of the day to wakey wakey and burn the
Nikki Naki
oh my God I'm so scared ah
might as well yeah Put on Full Armor
where do I go
I I went East so does that mean I I have
to go north now right
West I mean where's that means
[Music]
this way this way
laughs
this way
is it this way
I hope it's this way weast
wheezed okay
we used really
[Music]
why
how everyone's going so smoothly and now
I'm lost
God damn it
but only because I ran out of fireworks
otherwise I would have been fine I would
have found my way
wait
[Music]
okay
550 minus 493 something damn
um
this is then I think the right direction
I think
because one is going down
they're both going down that's what I
want right
check Shockers oh maybe I do have more
why
no
yay
good job remembering
that I had that oh my God
[Music]
okay but why am I seeing
this [\h__\h] again
please tell me I'm going the right way
now
um I took those coordinates so correct I
left the shortcut
[Music]
and with that my fireworks are
officially wasted uh what
there right
right
they were animals I think
yeah I'm going I'm going back I'm going
back guys
I'm going back I'm going to
quit
[Music]
I think it was
it should have been somewhere here
[Music]
was it here
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] no no wrong way again no
no say wrong way
I feel like it was over here no maybe
not
wrong Highland
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I had some good stuff in
there I minded though didn't I why
didn't well my [\h__\h] inventory didn't
pick it up
no it's not gone yet can you
[\h__\h]
add when people are like after 30
seconds is gone and then after five
minutes I reach it and it's still there
every time near snow there was a big
Cliff there's big Cliffs everywhere
huh
I don't know where it is
[Music]
what about here
what did you guys see
what did you guys see what what did the
surroundings look like
yeah I know yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
it's not gone yet
I might lose it yes but
wait don't I still have DVR like you
didn't you guys say still DVR can you
guys not go back and check there was an
iceberg really
but I wasn't on ice
[\h__\h]
ah
I don't know it all looks
wrong
eh
886 4009 886 1409
[Music]
886. really
that far back didn't I only fly for like
five seconds
1277 ah
000.
okay and 900 900 900.
with 900 on that or X
I'm on the fireworks
[Music]
okay but I'm really almost there
1277 900 900 900 900 900 900
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
no it's not hopeless I'm going the right
way now
did you guys know the coordinates
please don't kill me please don't kill
me
I heard it jump into the ladder
laughs
my phone hit me oh wait
then
it could be
my boat oh I have a boat
900 900 900 watts 1200
906 or
[Music]
2012 74.
74.
[Music]
I feel like I have more control
like this
how did I get so far
how did I get so far and at the same
time
what
and uh
uh 900
somewhere here it should be
was I like what what did it look like
yeah it doesn't do this one if the chunk
isn't even loaded I know that and you
guys should know that too by now
[Music]
I think I was like at least standing
around animals though
uh 77 77
.
how can I be lowered
[Music]
over here huh
F free and B
hey was I on a cliff like this
try near the tree
oh this this looks more like it
are we showing hitboxes still how does
this work
there's animals
yeah I heard animals yeah yeah
I don't see it
it was a bit flattered right
I think so too
[\h__\h]
there are red flowers
[Music]
I mean now now the chunk is loaded so
now it's kind of yummy
has set nine seven
it should be
like here
a weird looking Club 77 need to go
nowhere
[Music]
animal probably
want an animal
ah
[Music]
funk
I can't see it
and now we're gonna get visited by a
enemies now I went exactly to the place
that you told me but I don't know how it
can be lower than like 90 when I go
there
but
probably gone now
oh man
two I'm not like I'm pretty much
pretty much I'm pretty much there
[Music]
77 1077 is like here
but then I should be way lower
um I did not go there so many people
told me that one
oh anime hi did you see my shulker box
can we just be nice to each other for a
second
and you tell me oh God where my shulka
boxes
it's gone it's gone
why is definitely 77
now being scary
[Music]
please let's be nice
no no I had to have stuff inside
[Music]
foreign
I can't fly I don't have fireworks
anymore
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
oh man so sad I just went out to get
some experience
why
why I don't there were so many
miraculous finds you know in my life in
Minecraft until now I almost want to
believe that it's still somewhere there
I do have a bad [\h__\h] hell
oh
[Music]
um
what do you think guys
should I still look
[Music]
maybe I shouldn't look where the where
the coordinates said it would be
maybe it's somewhere else
maybe someone picked it up this looks so
familiar these flowers
no zombie meat
the flowers look familiar this looks
wait this looks familiar
stuff looks familiar
but not really the coordinates
oh
doesn't this look so familiar though
I went to soccer box Heaven no
oh
[Music]
let me just try to go there one more
time okay one more time
1277.
and what although there were people who
said this it wasn't there
maybe it fell down here
and looked everywhere here this is where
I was
I was looking at a broken Hill this
thing
that was lower though I was
I was I I think I was relatively flat I
don't mean there were animals
I have one more but that's not the good
one
the other one had nicer stuff in it I
think
[Music]
oh hi have you found my sugar box
I don't even want to know what was
inside but I feel like
I saw a lot of valuable things in there
there was I know at least I was lapis
lazuli and there was a lot of coal
wasn't there
just as it was under a tree
well there's many trees
and I think I would have seen it by now
if it was around there with the hitboxes
on
[Music]
um
I had two
I had two shulker boxes
an interesting one and a not so
interesting one
[Music]
oh man
now there was a bit more than that I
just don't remember what it was inside
thousand
seven
yeah it was probably here
2014 a thousand years it should have
been here
okay it's gone it's gone and I am in the
middle of nowhere without fireworks
foreign
[Music]
why did this happen
why why why huh
this is so sad I don't wanna I read and
I haven't had a Zen loss in a million
years
and I normally don't lose things like
that so this is like quite
devastating for me
[Music]
sucks
Maybe
maybe I must request I take a screenshot
of the shulker box and I send a request
to those guilds and I asked them to give
me all of that
another 10 loss but it sure feels like a
big loss
[Music]
my neck hurts so much from muscle pain
and generally always hurting
fork okay we're going with a boat now
[Music]
place the boat
okay where is where is Phoenix done
[Music]
no I mind it and then I ran away
thinking that I picked it up
just yeah maybe it was mostly cool the
diamonds I put away though right
right
[Music]
wait did I put the diamonds away
West
uh head towards it
what normally you guys tell me proper
coordinates now you're just telling me
to go to zero zero
foreign
guys
you should know me by now even when I
play Minecraft for the first time in a
long time
always pretty good at not dying
I'm just bad at directions
where do I go
I [\h__\h] hate this kind of place
[Music]
it's hard to navigate
someone pick me up
Liz
do I have to go west
[Music]
help I'm directionally challenged
I think
now I'm going north because I have no
other choice oh my God there's so many
polar bears please don't kill me please
well that's cool this look kind of like
an art to go through
okay
now I'm wasting
my numbers go down okay numbers are
going down numbers are going down
down
yeah that looks like
could be our land yeah
should I keep on going in the water
stream directional challenges
ah
[Music]
yeah I'll become one with the polar
bears polar bears polar bears
well now the water is ending I have to
walk
thank God I am somewhat of Azora
myself
tltk brain rot
and can go up water stream I think I can
right
foreign
yeah yeah
but uh yeah yeah
I'm wearing my Zora armor right now
whoa
oh
[Music]
let me
that's it
get rid of that get rid of that okay
[\h__\h] it that just go here
oh where am I why did I how did I get so
lost just by going to fauna's fancy fish
farm
what the [\h__\h]
fauna
you have to make up for this
[Music]
somebody tell fauna to pick me up
she has to she's it's her fault
it's her fault entirely her fault
Ed
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] where am I
don't recognize this place at all
[Music]
it's hard to say
it
[Music]
hello animals
I need to take a bath
uh
hopefully that will help with the pain
I already showered yesterday but I got
the pool smell on me and I need I don't
want to try I think I need a bath
for the pain to go away although I feel
like you know they tell you we'll take a
bath when you're feeling sore but I feel
like it barely helps
that's it
if this angers the saplings well
foreign
[Music]
who can take a joke right
maybe I shall sleep
I tend to almost cook myself in the back
yeah I can't do that
and I no can't make it too hot no no no
[\h__\h] didn't let me bro
Liz I just want to go home
where is home
[Music]
the [\h__\h] is shooting me
it's morning well there's lava
[Music]
be careful
be careful mama don't jump into the lava
these are my coordinates going down
partially partially
foreign
why am I so far
I was doing things so efficiently
I I hate myself
[Music]
oh my God
I hate being lost it just feels so
helpless
so lost and so helpless
and so directionally challenged
I want a rage quit I wish I could just
teleport to her [\h__\h] shrine
should play tltk
wow beautiful roses
wow
[Music]
I want to play tltk
and temporarily displacement
I'm basically there okay
I better be I better be well that looks
like I can
um it looks like
fruit that I can pick up and cook with
until 2K
[Music]
but if I'm going to zero when where is
zero that's like for a long time we had
nothing built there but now there might
be some council stuff right
um
[Music]
I wanna I wanna put on a speed boost
potion
uh
I wanna play tutk
all the kinds of stuff is there yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
let's focus on that
let's get that down
[Music]
today was anniversary
today and tomorrow
is it today and tomorrow do they have
like two days where they like spread on
on two days
[Music]
of the first gen first gen right
second run first Christian Christian
I think it's question
right yeah question
oh that looks very familiar to me
gen one yeah
and I was maybe you guys saw if you
didn't then time to watch the Vaude but
I was in agisan by 3D birthday live it's
the first time that I was invited guys
the first time it was about time so I'm
like so happy so grateful when that when
when I get senpai
first sent me the request
I was so happy I was like I'll do
anything else no
even though I'm I feel like I built up
like a dancer image I just didn't get
invited until now
but
let me tell you there's more to come
there is another birthday live
soon
not my own but a birthday life that I
will be in
[Music]
and then
I got another invitation for one
that I I want to be in but I still have
to figure out like if I can fly to Japan
for it
um because my schedule is already
looking pretty crazy at this point
um so that's already free oh wait um
okay I'm gonna tell any names but I can
tell you those free including today
plus I think one more
3D yeah yeah so that should be like four
where are we where are we
there's a light Tower here
please
tell me where to go because I'm like I'm
supposedly there already oh wait I see
nice Landmark nice nice nice oh we've
made it
it's been an unnecessarily long journey
but we made it
I come to find this house good but can I
walk over your house
because I need to go to the other side
sorry fauna you'll hear some trampling
sounds
bands bands bands bands
cute she's kind of cute cozy Place
reminds me of Hobbits
Hobbit houses
[Music]
yum yeah I'm very happy I'm very very
very happy to finally be a little bit in
demand I'm thinking it's about time
yeah
um
so keep an eye out guys
I mean I will always tell you guys I
can't tell you beforehand but I will
always tell you guys afterwards hey this
happened
and this happened
so keep an eye out oh well why wait why
are we here
I think I'll take one stack of gunpowder
I think I'm allowed to take it because I
was also like standing there to farm it
you know
oh
where I just did this exp thing to do
like two more name tags though right so
we'll make two more name tags and then
we'll call it a day maybe
we'll name those bastards
uh
this one I think
[Music]
okay
no not saying that all is happening in
June some things are
uh you know a little bit further ahead
[Music]
yeah yeah
I'm taking that not so very much
thank you sure bells for the gunpowder
Iris made a also one really
why why do we have double is it also on
the server does Iris farm work better
if it works better then that's a good
argument
but I am a supporter of
also for Phoenix Suns
it's already there why must we replace
it with something
more technologically modern ah
as in a new server
really
please clean up your inventory for once
is that what's upsetting you
my inventory
foreign
thing after another we're cleaning up
Phoenix Sun at the moment it may not
look like it but
yeah and that's how Minecraft
inventories look like
to really build something in The
Preserve yeah yeah I saw a clip of uh
senpai
uh walking around that area and trying
to build something there and her chat
told her no no no no this is Ian they're
building something there or like
planning to and she was like well how
long ago was it like recently like I'm
in within one month recently or a year
ago
uh like was it reserved a million years
ago and no one's done anything but I
mean
reason it was it was a it could it could
be considered pretty reason I would say
and the chat also told her that and and
then you know she's she found the stop
sign and then she backed off and she
went elsewhere
yeah but yeah we should maybe start at
least like building the the base
just getting rid of trees or whatever
and just building the base the ground
to show how much space we need at least
but not gonna lie I was kind of scared
about the thought of having pecula
Senpai in our neighborhood
she always picks a fight with people
that are in her neighborhood
even even with the ones that were there
first
[Music]
yeah
no but yeah I also agree like if
something has been reserved for a year
and nothing has been done with it then
go ahead go ahead and have fun with it
of course
but this was pretty recent so
[Music]
but I don't know how much space we wanna
take up um so anyway
uh two more name tags right the
zombreigns
ah
I went so yeah well changing this one
because I can't find silky girl anymore
um some raids
some raids he said some raid
and another random [\h__\h] guy right the
the Lesser
lesser random
right
I think that's what we needed
pickle versus stunk please no please
have mercy
get off my lawn picker
all that traveling for this yeah I
cannot [\h__\h] believe it either
[Music]
happen in the morning what ah
um I'll tell you perhaps in a couple
days
all right
[Music]
it was a what the [\h__\h] kind of morning
not in my backyard pickles
[Music]
what an adventure it was not supposed to
be any Adventures today you jealous
don't be jealous once I started doing it
once I like my body learned how to do it
properly
I can't stop doing it anymore and
honestly that's it's just making it
worse
it was better when I did not have the
desire and and the skill to do it
cracking my neck
because now it feels like I Unleashed
something some kind of need to
constantly do it you know
that's not very good either
[Music]
um
over there right
with the pickle first thing English
right
like certain cute voices they only
really sound right in English in
Japanese right
in English it just feels wrong
okay maybe I can turn off these boxes
again
and unnamed people the core you're
unnamed you have your
you're uh
some rain and you are ah [\h__\h] no I
needed two time rates
what about the other random [\h__\h] guy
ah you're the random [\h__\h] guy I need one
more zomb read
the Lesser one
more one more time braid and then
basically it's done but I mean honestly
that one is so insignificant and I feel
like we don't have to name him
I should just stop doing it my neck is
back to not popping really I feel like
I'm doing it a little bit less so like
like compared to uh two years ago or one
year ago yeah
I think so my cracks have changed a
little bit
um
can I
sell uh maybe some iron
but it's 20 emeralds for one tag right
that's pretty expensive
and where were the tags
you have a techno
hole you say no I have no more coal
if only I had still some coal
yeah it was cracking way more and then
it annoyed me that everybody was always
telling me still cracking so I tried to
do it a little bit less doing stream but
I was still doing it very much so
outside of streams
a lot a lot of it I can't find the ninja
wait was it
was it the ah man this I was over here
confusion
[Music]
20.
well I don't know what I even what I
could even use whatever that one name
tag whatever
it doesn't matter
but thank you for the membership welcome
in terms of farming I mean this area
isn't that popular like mostly people
don't really
care for exchanging with Farmers I feel
like
so
not a big need here I would say where
are the important ones though
Tic Tac and cheese attack
take
well didn't I make like some kind of
song or a cell what is my Lord ah I
think last time I was here I already
also saw that he was lost and
um
I think my Lord is gone
last time I checked he was just gone
maybe I need to make a new mailord
some people would come for mail arts and
really have you seen that where is he
though
[Music]
you're not my Lord
you can help
you're not my Lord and he's gone
but this is not the first time I've
noticed that oh he's gone he could be
there
no one's here either
they had access to this area but no
no one is here
[Music]
I don't think so
I feel like I would have seen it there's
one in there I went oh wait no there's
two
should I jump in
how
[Music]
um
you're you have no job but there was one
in there with a job this one
[Music]
uh-huh
is that something the name it would
would it say the name up here
there are melons but you can't sell him
slices
wait there's one more that one that one
come over here dude thanks come over
here
I know you're trying
[\h__\h] I don't think there's a door here
uh
whoa whoa whoa is it him no he's also
not buying and today just not buy slime
but no no name
no name on these guys
[Music]
um
go back in
who's Hotel go back in otherwise I'm
gonna snip snap your toes
hmm
don't mess around with me now okay
how will I get out I got out safely
yeah uh that's that's for another day
we'll deal with that another day another
time
um but not today
um okay
let me just put back some materials and
then I think oh good I'm kind of tired
to Folk
I'm gonna eat my dinner
bricks why not
okay
I caught up recently with super chat so
I'm not gonna read them today
I need to keep it short
I hope you enjoyed this
fun with Minecraft in Phoenix 10.
I think we made progress we cleaned up a
lot we got rid of all the unnecessary
dudes
and we caught them no I mean the one the
blacksmiths and all those those are in
boats now so
maybe I'll leave it like that for a
while
and the other ones are stuck in their
house
so I can't run away I can't make new
ones because beds are gone the beds are
like pretty
um
proportionalized
balanced and yeah
we gave them names the ones that we let
survive gave them some good names
so it's easy to understand what you get
for your emeralds so if anybody asks
where can I get this net let them know
let them know
[Applause]
always at Phoenix and the OJ
you just got here yeah you can watch the
um VOD if you want
thank you for coming by
thank you soon guys and in Germany and
oh if you missed it please watch my a
little part at Aki senpai's or watch the
whole thing at Aki senpai's uh
anniversary concert today
those are sexy drop when you can see my
butt
very very good scene
enjoy and Julie
kind of embarrassing
I do that every morning and my whole
back cracks like
several times
I do that drop exactly that drop
and he goes in my spine
[Music]
I will have that poster 24 7 when I get
older
I just won't be able to get back up
[Laughter]
concerts are always very good
her birthday one was like
um
musical themed again and this one was
she she said she just wanted it to be
you know
um like a typical typical
anniversary life with her own songs and
all that
um
[Music]
thank you guys for watching bye bye see
you soon see you tomorrow bro I have
something tomorrow
take care guys thank you Hunchback Joe
that's me
thank you bye bye
promote Phoenix Suns promote Phoenix 10
let people know
[Music]
foreign
oh
oh well if it isn't moving yeah
[Music]
she's enjoying the carpet that I
very for rolly cleaned
and ridden of all the cat hairs
[Music]
foreign