[Music]
it
me
intoxicating DJ
[Music]
dancing so
baby
[Music]
feel it rush through me
feel
R feel it me
[Music]
oh
honey night is
[Music]
it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
l
dancing sry about so emotion
[Music]
B
K
KY oh w w hurt myself I heard
myself
chat we're starting out in the office
because I am going
to I don't know it doesn't feel real oh
my God it felt more real before
before it was like
[Music]
happening that's weird that's so
weird
H okay
[Music]
um audio
stock oh that's not that's not that's
not the right vibe
um let me get
some
[Music]
BTM I don't really have many music files
that suit this
[Music]
situation oh what what is this
like oh that's fine
[Music]
okay man okay
uh okay uh well first of all Amit am
doesn't want us to be sad so I want to
try to not be
sad but how can I not be
sad um you know you know me I'm a I'm an
emotional
person I cannot not be sad I am sad by
default uh first of
all I don't
know um I'm sorry for like how you guys
feel like I don't know how many
teammates are in the chat right now but
even if you're not a teammate
[Music]
even like anybody leaving from me is I
think sad to
see and especially cuz we just had our
anniversary and I think people were like
oh let's go you know just like in a good
feeling when it comes to
myth
um what what my I I don't know what to
say um
to be honest when when we
decided on the
hashtag for the anniversary life I was
like I was like myth forever really like
I don't know like yeah myth forever but
like people don't know that Amma is
going to announce her like
departure so how is it mid forever like
I was kind of like personally like I'm
I'm I I don't know maybe I'm taking this
the the most dramatically uh out of all
of us like I'm like
yeah yeah like yeah like me too like I'm
like this is not me
forever but yeah m forever like okay
obviously um myth
oh don't be don't be like that don't be
like that um
um
I I was really dreading this I knew that
I knew it we all knew like right it had
to happen one day that somebody
leaves um and
I I I did I didn't ever expect for any
of us to stay that long in the beginning
I think we all didn't expect to stay
this long because like it was hard to
even like imagine how it was going to go
because there was nothing before us in
terms of
Ian
um and um so honestly 4
years is more than I expected and and
like more than I can ask from anyone one
to invest into this I guess because life
life goes on and maybe you want to do
other things four years is a long time
and and
um yeah like it's totally understandable
in my opinion if you want to do
something else at that point and I'll uh
100% like ever since ever since she
first told us which is a long time ago
at this point
I felt
like you know I kind of became quite an
amig Gosling a teammate number one
teammate number one amig
Gosling I'm a big fan of her not just uh
a gen mate um so when I heard it of
course I was like no no no
please but her reasonings that she told
me
um and everything it just made sense and
um I'll I'll accept and respect it and
um I I I guess I'll support
it uh
but H it's hard because and I don't want
this is one thing I want to make very
clear um going forward I don't want
anybody to ever
like like blame her or anything there's
no blame on her she it's her choice and
and somebody had to leave first and um
you
know
um don't don't blame her you
know what was I going to say I forgot
I'm like I'm
so scrambled I'm scrambled egg right now
um I don't know what I was going to say
I don't know anything
um yeah when I I was saying when I first
heard it I was shocked but I I of course
I understood
and
it's it's okay am but I think about the
future a lot I'm probably overthinking
everything a
lot I always
do
but I'm leaving is kind of the end of an
era
right
and oh it's the bgm double oh
[\h__\h] it's kind of
double
oops [\h__\h]
it's kind of the end of an era and um
I
I I feel
like that's something really hard for us
to then
overcome um so I'm I'm kind of scared of
the
future I I don't
know like cuz I want people to have fun
when they watch
us
and just you know I don't know be
lighthearted or
whatever and if we're
not
complete like surely time will
like make it better but m
[Music]
no don't do this to me I'm really
stressed
out [\h__\h]
oh you didn't hear that maybe I don't
know if you heard
that
um
um what was I I don't know um I just I
just hope that I I you know I'm a little
bit like torn because I I think the same
thing that you're saying that myth will
always be five and myth forever and you
know and that Amma is absolutely
Irreplaceable I think the same things
and then I think about the future like
for like future anniversaries like are
people like always going to be saying oh
if only am was here like oh this would
be better if Amma was here and then I
feel like how am I ever going to satisfy
people ever again no matter how how hard
uh I work you know like I'm torn between
these thoughts
[Music]
um so I think for now we can 100%
say nothing's the same without a because
it's
not
um we can say that um but at the same
time we can cope with like oh oh like
it's not like a usual graduation it's a
what what did they call it again
something uh and end of activities or
something like that it's like there's a
little there's a door that's closed but
it's not locked I
guess but that's you know it depends on
the company and on
am or like when and how they want to
open it again
so we'll see like hasn't been done
before so we'll
see but I knew about this for a long
time so it's been in the back of my mind
for a long time and it's also the reason
why um I
organized the myth one
[Music]
block because I I want wanted make more
projects together with all five of
us before we didn't have a chance for it
[Music]
anymore
and and also you know I love am but this
was also a reason why I called dips on
chiku
and it's also the reason why I didn't
want to participate in GTA this
week because I knew he was
coming and I'm sorry I can't not be
sad I guess it's ironic because no she's
participating in
GTA but I don't think I want I I it
didn't feel right to
me
no I I'm always like when there's
something like this happening and I'm
like looking at the waiting room of the
the
stream and then all the fans are like oh
God it can't be real and like no don't
don't worry like it's don't think of the
worst and the other fans are like no
panic panic and I'm I'm just thinking oh
my God I feel so bad for all the fans
cuz like the people who are in the
waiting room there waiting for something
they're like big fans of the person and
and I'm I feel bad for like the feelings
that they're about to
experience and it hurts me every time
I'm like I'm sorry guys I'm
sorry
[Music]
and I don't think anything can hit
harder for me than a myth
graduation and am especially hits hard
for
me because I
love and we she always helped me I went
back all the way in our Discord
conversations I went back all the way to
the very
beginning and like I scrolled back four
years and I looked at what what we
talked about in the beginning
and I
I I generally I was just asking her to
download vectors for me like 10 vectors
per
day but there was also a thing where
like three days or so after debut
I was like
absolutely devastated apparently for
some reason like I was sad and uh she
could hear it in in voice chat
and and she messaged me afterwards even
though like you know I told you before
for me and uh am and gura like me with
am and me with gura it took me such a
long time
to oh my nose is so wet to like get
closer to
them and
so um having Amy reach out to me in the
very beginning when I was like sounding
sounding sad
apparently um she asked me like oh
what's up what's wrong are you okay you
sounded sad and then I opened up my
heart to her
but back then I don't think we were
really like connected that much at all
yet so that was just like free days
after debut or so um but she reached out
to me and oh that was sweet and made me
cry when I read it
[Laughter]
again and I'm
a I'mma made so many things for us
happen and she helped me so much in the
beginning too
and she's so cute and she's
so talented and funny and I love her and
I don't want her to go but I have to
respect it and she's going and that's
okay
um I'm just grateful that she did
this for so long anyway
[Music]
and that she made my
into what it
is and you know this like because I knew
this shut up because I knew this
I was um like extra happy during like
New York cuz I
think that was the last time I was going
to see her
so I was so happy when we
could hang out just us two because I we
stayed a little bit longer than the
others well she said yeah we can still
meet up she said look I'm using my
t-shirt as a
tsue she said yeah I'll visit you
because she promised me before and she
never came but she did say like okay
I'll visit you in in Europe I will I
will I will I will visit you in in
Europe yeah you
better
um um man but that's
why I was like very very clingy towards
am in in New York and
I was so happy that we spent so much
time together and that's why I Tred to
be with v every step of the
way that's why all my tangents included
Amy all my tangents
include thank you for guiding me through
New
York thank you for everything we still
have a little bit of time not much I
wish it was
more um I kind of wanted to be on like
standby for any kind of collapse that's
why I didn't do a schedule this
week and also because on Sunday and I
had to keep the secret still um so that
you guys don't
think too dramatically um but on Sunday
the stream is a holot talk with Amy
because I wanted to do Holo talks with
the Ian members at some point anyway and
now is like the time limit is yeah I
it's time we're starting with
[Music]
am I'm sorry guys
I'm man
I hope you guys watch every single am a
stream otherwise I
will come to your home and arrest you
you guys got to watch every Amma stream
until she
leaves make sure to support her whatever
she does wherever she
goes she
deserves every single piece of Love
she's like the most
the most
helpful and
and how to
say openhearted person she's shy and she
will not like ask for collabs much and
she will not go out of her way to like
chitchat
much but she still I know that she
loves us and that
she I don't
know I just know that she's so
sweet why am I talking like she's
[Laughter]
dying I'm sorry am I can't be happy I'm
sorry
am she several times she was like I want
to make this a lighthearted thing I want
to leave with smiles and this and that
and I'm like I'm I can't promise you
that everybody's like okay gotcha and
I'm like I'm I'm not going to I'm not
going to promise you that I can't
promise you that I'm number one teammate
I'm number one arm
goling I need to get some toilet paper
[Music]
I couldn't sleep at all because I
like in the night cuz I kept on thinking
oh I got to wake up for this and and
then I dreamt about like something
related to like announcements and and
I'm and you know all that I dreamt about
it and I kept on waking up and I fell
back asleep and I woke up and dreamed
some [\h__\h] like that
again and then I was like no
oh it's 8:00
a.m. it's really
happening I just wanted to drag it out
as long as I could like this day coming
and
[Music]
okay I don't know um we'll still be
friends of course I hope
so I still I don't I what the [\h__\h] what
is that is that my snot
what
um
um I can't think anymore more I can't
think
anymore I love Amma and I hope you
all will watch every stream that she
does I'll be mad at you if you
don't she has like a lot of things
planned for the next week so support her
please um we're going to have the holot
talk collab and we're going to I'm going
to join some like other collabs that
like other collab that she planned and
then there will be another myth
collab
yeah I'm like usually like I cry a lot
behind the scenes and then when I stream
I I usually don't cry because like
I'm I there's like some blockage there
that makes me not able to feel things
anymore somehow a little bit sometimes
but okay I thought I was not going to
cry I thought I was going to be safe
because it's hard
to let let out emotions when you guys
are watching
me yeah I'm like dis
disassociating I don't know man it's
going
to but okay so I feel like even I feel
like a long long time
ago I don't know I feel like I suggested
something like
this because I I used to be a big fan of
an a Japanese idol
company
um hello project you know and there's
obviously always graduations there
too but there's
group morning Muslim especially but they
did it with all groups um where in
morning musima they they kept on
graduating older members and then they
put in new members so that the group
lives on forever and
ever and
uh I have so snot in my
throat um but it was always so cool to
see in
concerts sometimes the older graduated
memb who were already like 40 or
something and with kids and everything
they would sometimes show up for like
big reunion concerts and stuff not
always but sometimes and uh I remember
like sometime last year I feel like I
brought this up I was like hey um would
be kind of cool if we could do this
right
like
flum would be cool if we can do this
like like fans will be so happy to see
someone again
and and um it it would be just so hyped
to to have graduated members come back
for some special moment and then and
then combine them with the newer ones
who maybe haven't even met each other
yet you know and then you see how the
Legacy goes on and gets carried on and
and then you see songs old songs
performed by new
members um who who weren't in the
original lineup and then they sing it
together with the old members who were
in the original lineup and stuff like
that it's it's just uh really really
special
and that's how I hope that they want to
do
it I don't know what they're really
thinking um I wouldn't expect her to
show up in every single concert or so
you know or anywhere at all don't have
any don't don't think you know I'm not
going to make promises I'm not I'm not
the one who decides it um but I feel
like that would be
cool yeah I don't know I don't know I
can't I met with her kids you mean
they're dogs and
cats yeah
so I feel like at times like these maybe
kfp gets worried about me um I will say
that
I I don't have any um graduation plans
as of now um I'm I have a lot of
frustrations penned up that make me
think about it a lot but I I
I'm I'm definitely staying
because I still want to do a lot of
things and um accomplish a lot of things
and fight for like things that I am I
feel I deserve um so don't worry about
me but it is a nice reminder that you
should always cherish the time with your
or um
ories as I have been cherishing it with
Amit in the
past yeah however long it was since she
told
us
you always always feel think like neosi
might be gone the next day
right yeah and
I'm so
proud that I was able to stand and work
and walk
alongside of
Amit together since the beginning of
Hall live English that's a crazy thing
to say isn't it before us there was
nothing and we created this Branch
together and back then like we didn't
have many resources we didn't have much
knowled knowled we didn't have
anything but together we made it
work like I got technical help from
her we all helped each other in some
ways Kelly helped also like I remember
she made my uh she animated my opening
loading
screen um Amma made my Stinger my
chicken Stinger Fried Chicken
Stinger like she made the animation for
it
um ana oh hi Ana hi
ana
um yeah and I feel like I barely gave
anything contributed anything but I'm a
did say in that text that I
read uh from the four years back she was
like oh
but you're always saving our ass in
collaborations so hey I can
talk at least
something um so myth was strong be
because of the combination of people
that we were and we
had
and we couldn't be where we are right
now without am and without you know any
of
us all of you you created myth all of
all of you all of us created myth well
you guys too I
[Music]
guess and because I cried so much here
today hopefully I won't cry as much on
the last
day can't promise I'm I can't promise I
literally love
you can't promise I'm I can't no no also
letting out feelings is is a good thing
and a nice thing and you
know it's makes the bondes
stronger and the connections
tighter well thank you guys for
following our journey and am's
journey myth might like change a little
bit
[Music]
but we're still going to try our best
going forward to make things fun and
entertaining for
you
yeah and now hopefully I will not get a
blue screen of death because why is it
suddenly making windows noises when it
didn't
before we're going to play
b
b we're going to play it um otherwise
I'm going to be really mad I'm going to
morb oh man I'm sorry for I'm sorry for
crying I'm sorry and I I don't even want
to drag the mood down but this is day
one okay what can I do what can I do
like this is still fresh the wound is
fresh I had a lot time to process it
beforehand but it's different when it
actually
happens don't apologize I'm it's like
towards you guys but also a lot of my
apologies are towards
am I'm sorry
am oh man okay please there's a let me
just say there's a risk of cuz yesterday
I tried playing and then blue screen of
death twice so
there's a risk of that I suppose but
let's cross our
fingers at least I changed my don't know
I don't know if I sound any different oh
wait I was supposed to change to
here I don't know if I sound any
different but uh I should sound like I
sounded in
Japan hey window sounds so far are ch
chilling out okay
cool can I understand things better than
yesterday yesterday we we got uh like
two dialogue Pages through the tutorial
like two two blob blobs two dialogue
blobs what is what is this what does
this button do again here no
[Music]
I it's like when I do anything when I
touch my my my desk okay I'm I'm just
not going to touch things it should be
fine um I was just like uh trying out
things right now
[Music]
um what was I saying yeah we didn't get
really far in a tutorial yesterday at
all like just two
texts uh but my brain was kind kind of
fried yesterday as as
well we'll
see is this is
It's I still don't 100%
know
uh a
wait oh yeah yeah yeah yeah this way I
can this is the way this is the way this
is the armit way of separating
audio this is the armit way one thing I
will try is when Amy is is you know not
there to go the Amy way anymore I shall
continue her Legacy with the am way I
shall do my best I have like you know
kiata way is kind of similar to Amway
sometimes I I have similarities to it so
I will Embrace her spirit and do things
the I'm away stubbornly
the I'm
way okay uh let's let's do this uh I
[Music]
guess uh W wait where's the tutorial I
thought you were going to give me the
tuto tutorial I reset
everything
them I think I'm going to restart the
game one more time
uh wait
uh app
dat why I literally deleted everything
again right
before uh
properties keep game sa no that's that's
that's
off okay deleting the steam Cloud
deleting the safe or I'll just delete
like the whole can I delete the the
whole
thing oh
that
a let's see give me the tutorial please
cuz I don't know how to play this game
no okay there he is okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay yipp no even making a new
profile didn't give me the tutorial
again it's okay I got it
yeah okay Joker Joker hello there my
name we're going to we're going to play
this game now and have fun okay I cried
enough cried enough let's have fun help
me play this game guys hello there my
name is Jingo I'm here to help you learn
how to
play oh wait ch
[Music]
why are you
dead there you go
[Music]
okay your goal is to earn tips to defeat
the enemy
blind which doesn't mean you have to
close your eyes don't worry this here is
a small blind you only need to score 300
chips to beat
it why so serious
chut select a small blind to start the
round
okay score at least 300 small blind
[Music]
selector you earn chips by playing poker
hands each poker hand earns a base
amount of chips multiplied by some Mt
which stands for
multiplier yeah uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh
that's a multiplayer that's the base
amount okay okay okay I'm already I'm
already functioning more than
yesterday I
think see your poker hands in the Run
info area along with other info about
your current
run and run info okay so here it shows
me combinations that I could have and
how much oh how
much uh
coins chips it gives me and the
multiplier okay and now I don't know how
to play poker so I don't know any of
these by heart so I don't really know
how this will go but they say that this
is easy even if you don't play poker we
see think of it like yti yeah yeah yeah
yeah I I understand like I already saw
that similarity like oh okay you want me
to get certain combinations like in
yatsi and the better it is the more
money I'll get um but in Yi it
was I think it was yeah giving like
suggestions on what I can make depending
on what I had on my
hand uh I hope it will do that here no
Dave the ah cuz I reset it it's gone
okay we can do it if I like uh start a
new game cuz I love Dave the
DI exactly like yti okay good cards also
earn you some chips hover over to
see
where where huh that s like up to five
cards Oh you mean
here select up to five cards and play
and press play hand uh select up to five
what just randomly I don't know which
ones but having a joker is always good
right uh
what I don't do I really have to look
here each time okay uh 10 98 do I have a
10 98 no oh but it can can it also be
like uh okay I don't have it though like
any number that goes in the like
45 456 for example
right as of now there's nothing
good wait
uh Cher Cher Cher King King
King uh Ace King
1054 ah because they share the same suit
five cards in a row consecutive ranks 10
9 8 7 oh okay jok uh-huh uh-huh well I'm
Speed Learning this for three cards with
the same rank they may be played with
two other unscored cards ah same same
number mixed with whatever else you
got uh pairs of cards with different
ranks may be played with one other ah
aha pairs like okay just the number uh
the other thing doesn't have to be the
same okay two of them one pair is one
yeah one pair of cards that they the
same
number and if the plate hand is not any
of the above hands only the highest
ranked card
scores okay but I just put whatever in
there okay
um but does it make sense to put just
all all the best ones in there all the
highest chips
ones play
hand oh oh oh that's not bad I just
don't get a multiplier because I didn't
make an actual
hand okay you can also discard you can
also discard up to five selected cards
to try and make even stronger hands oh
when I discard do I get a new card
discard if I discard discard oh I had a
pair of nines oh well whatever it
doesn't matter when we have a pair of
sevens eight sevens we can do a 8
five can we we do a
four four kinds of like numbers
consecutive oh wait and then the Joker
wait a second we can have the Joker be
the four and then wait I don't need to
discard anything what are you talking
wait I can discard the
seven right careful you only have a
limited number of hands in discards per
round that's
okay yeah Didn't I that ain't a joker
what do you mean that's not a joker
that's a jack
what but it says J
what
what okay I guess a joker will look like
this and or variations of this cuz I saw
variations of that what the [\h__\h] is a
jack oh Jack is what you call the the
the the Clover the
[Music]
Clover wait wait wa we have an
ace that looks like the heart kind of
and then we have a heart that is a heart
a the Spade is the four edgy one right
and then the four free covered Leaf is
the
jack [\h__\h] we're starting from zero
here Jack is the lowest face card okay
wait wait wa Ace is is a no joker is
number one right what what do you mean
not at all what Jack is the rank not
what
M no that's Club what's Club what did I
say what heart Spade club diamond heart
Spain isn't that what I said club club
oh what that what's oh oh Jack can be
paired with any of those hard Spade club
Diamond it just gives it a different
value
no yes
no
[\h__\h] uh Jack is always the same no I
mean like can it be paired with any of
these
icons yeah that's what I mean okay okay
okay uh okay okay and it will always be
an 11
okay aha oh so wait if I have a number a
consecutive number like if that's the
lowest and that's a what did you guys
say it's a 11 okay so if I have a 10 is
there a
10 in
numbers God now I'm confusing
myself yeah it does it just say 10 or is
it also a face
card but can I I do you know like up go
up with these face
cards it just say okay so I can do like
you know eight 7 8 9 10 and then the
Jack and then no yeah the Jack and
there's a king there's a
king there's a queen and a king and an
ace what wait what what face cards are
there
Queen and then King Jack queen king a
[Music]
joker H okay so Jack is 11 Queen is
12 King is 13 and Joker is anything you
want it to be right okay wait let me let
me let me let me
um uh wait there's Ace too Ace has a
number two I forgot not about that let
me pin this thank you
kite Mama
Mia Jokers are not in my
deck oh where the hell do they come from
then when do I get a joker
[Music]
then Ace can be either one or
14 that's like a joker then that's a
joker what
[Music]
I buy them okay so you're saying it's
not in my deck right now but later on
maybe oh W You'll Play You Learn okay
okay okay I just needed a this a
starting start starting
understanding Jokers are separate from
your deck Jers are special in this game
yeah I can tell there's like so many
different
ones
a Jokers are abilities and modifiers oh
cool okay so Ace is kind of my Joker in
my mind because I thought a joker can
just replace anything so the ace will be
the number of my
dreams um
right
what I am the
Joker Ace is only one or 140 oh it's not
one 1214 it's one or for a [\h__\h] okay so
even the first or the last
number okay ah okay
uh earn 300 chips before you run you run
out of hands to win this round good luck
okay 300 chips before I run out of
cards how many
cards view de uhhuh sort hand rank oh I
can sort it by Rank and suit what's suit
what's rank
uh is is the number the rank and the
pictures the suit I have free hands what
do you mean I have free hands I can do
free things with
this okay okay I think so what uh this
is not a joker this is not a joker it's
a Jack and a jack was an 11 but we don't
have a nine oh wait let's get rid of the
seven
I can do uh how many cards I need five
eight eight 7
six five so a four would be nice or a
nine would be nice so I can get rid of
the three and the
two for what I want to make
right I can do pairs too I guess yeah I
could just go with this hand probably oh
maybe I don't no I could get go with
seven like two pairs if I get a
different pair
going keep pairs keep pairs
okay let's discard those what did we get
oh we have enough a pair but we we don't
have a we didn't get a
four wait we got a
10 but not an wait you an 11 we don't no
nine and no four what why
I guess for now we'll just make two
pairs where is that on
the that's pretty
low throw in a oh okay so I can throw in
anything right but I would throw in the
one that gives me the highest chips
though at
[Music]
least a low car yeah no yeah oh it
doesn't get scored oh [\h__\h] would I keep
it
would I keep the jack for the next round
apparently yeah but I got a new one king
king Joker
10885 two pairs again no three pairs
three
pairs oh wait is it a pair because it
has a different icon he's a joker what
do you mean this a joker it's not a
Joker Jack not Joker did I say joker
sorry I mean Jack I know I
know it's still pair okay
um wait
uh five cards in a row with all cards
are in the same suit four cards are the
same rank they may be played with uh-huh
uh-huh a three of a kind and a pair uhuh
uh-huh uhhuh H what maybe
I
if wait do we have a we have a 12 wait
is King no king is
13 so we have a 13 13 11
10 I don't want to do stupid pairs
again Queen is 12 yeah yeah yeah yeah
yes I got it I got
it my pair of five are not doing
anything oh I guess so because I if I
were to go with pairs I would choose 88
and
KK smart okay then
let's get rid of the both
fives toss toss it toss it wait the
discards are for the whole oh no okay
wait what did we get another oh a
que ah but no I don't have a nine but uh
the consecutive and in free is that is
that a
thing no that's we have a
kind
Fork I don't want to discard again
because then I can't discard
anymore I guess we do peirs
again and then we keep uh the queen and
this for later so the pairs and then the
the lowest one because it doesn't get
counted is that the smartest
[Music]
play I will play
this I got to play the hands the cards
them dealt yeah okay um play
hand how far did we get oh that's that's
that looks good that looks
good oh we're almost at 300 okay okay
cool cool cool cool cool cool cool I'm
playing cards
now uh oh we got two
Ace Ace was 1 or
14 or was is said something else or it's
a nine no what this is
11 what what is AC is what okay don't
confuse me ac is one or 14 almost a
straight wa what's a
straight uh the consecutive ones okay so
we have a let's say
14 or one are you thinking about this
being a 14 and then we're missing the 13
but we have the 12 the 11 the T
oh then let's throw
out hoping for a
king right we're hoping for a king and
we throw out the six should we keep the
second Ace just in case we got to do
pairs again I need an eight oh a king or
eight okay should I keep the
seven throw out yeah that's what I was
thinking should I throw out the
ace keep Aces okay this card is seven
throw the seven what about the
six keep the a okay okay okay
okay we got a not wait what did we get
no not [\h__\h] pears
again okay I guess we're playing pears
again I mean we will get to the 300 no
that's boring I paired I I paired pairs
twice H
thce
bro okay though
cool yay
yipp I'm learning let's go I did it so
what did I get what free bucks o that's
nothing
cash is is cashing out my only option I
can't continue like
this o niely done and now that you flush
with cash flush with cash I wouldn't
call free seven bucks flush with cash
you can buy some new cards from the shop
can I buy a joker
card try buying this handsome devil o
Joker the real Joker to you're so
cheap you're so cheap this is one of the
150 Jokers you can add to your run every
Joker does something different ahuh what
does this one do plus four multiplyer oh
okay cool cool cool
cool this one adds yum
mhm be picky you can only carry five
Joker cards at a
time uh you mean five
Joker but also the like any other like
this Empress card for example would also
be one of the five right
now buy the other card from what does
this do enhances two selected
cards to multiplyer
cards what do you mean would they what
well we'll see it in action eventually
hopefully they're consumables ah okay
and what about those are those in within
the five cards that I can bring or are
they it's about to tell you okay this
terrot card it is a consumable this one
will enhance your playing cards hold on
to
it you can carry up to two consumable
cards a few at a time oh only
two okay I like these shiny booster
packs I used to play some card games so
opening booster packs was
fun I want to play something
again I mostly it was magic the
Gathering and I I I've tried a million
times to get magic gin
perms for us to play but the Publishers
just don't reply to the emails I
[Music]
guess they just will not
reply I wish I wish I want to get back
into
it
h Wizards oh are they difficult
[Applause]
oh
man that sucks we be so cool to play it
[Music]
online maybe try to add them we're not
really supposed to do that that's not
like that's not
our preferred way of doing business
we're not supposed to like you know
pressure them or
anything it's not like like proper
business
ways you
know we we got it it's not it's the
cover way it's not the am no that adding
them would perhaps be the Amway but if I
do that I'm going to be bonked by the
company
yeah please check your emails
Wizards wizards of the
something please check your emails thank
[Music]
you although it's been a while ago I
wonder if they just don't didn't see it
or if they just don't feel like replying
or so I wonder what's the issue they
probably just didn't really see it maybe
they have no one can you guys apply for
like working in the company and then
like apply for a position that handles
the
emails got to keep on trying yeah it's
just so like H the process of like
requesting something again it it used to
be simpler we we used to just go to our
managers and be like hey can you send
them a follow-up email can you send them
a followup email can you send them a
follow-up email but now I have to
reapply each [\h__\h] time in our our
system like the whole application oh
well maybe one day if you save up enough
you can buy a voucher vouchers passively
upgrade your run passively permanently
gain plus one hand per
round uh wait if a voucher then like I
use it once and it only us get works for
that run and then the voucher is gone
forever or does do I get the chance to
use the voucher in the next run too or
it's just like once activated it will be
for everyone or
it's permanent it's for the whole run
yeah but also what what about the future
runs oh I guess ah it's is it like
slightest SP where whatever I buy is
only for that run
and would that would make sense right so
whenever I start a new run I also have
to buy new
Jokers
ah I have to buy new Jokers
too okay makes
sense makes sense
I I want to play SL of fire again too
one of these days permanently gained
plus one hand per round well I don't
have money for this
anyway vouchers are restuck after you
defeat the boss blind M the boss blind
okay which is just a higher amount of uh
coins I guess and check out both of the
booster packs in every shop they're full
of good is I think wor it buffoon pack
well I like how Fredy they are and so
shiny oh my God I want to open I can I
can like imagine how it feels to open
them even though this is just the
graphic I can imagine how it feels oh my
[Music]
God I can I can like sense the texture
of it the plastic the fin plastic but oh
I can smell it I can smell it ah they
are worth
it okay okay okay imagine the
smell okay let's move on to the next
round
okay next round oh we have to choose a
big
blind bro I barely made the small blind
okay we choose to skip it to get a tag
each tag has a unique effect what
tag well I don't what's I don't know
what you want me to do that or what but
keep an eye on the bus blight it has an
ability you'll need to plan around
discard two random cards per hand
played this what okay I don't understand
this yet but maybe in the future if you
beat it then the ant goes up and all
blinds become
harder oh for that run
okay beat ant eight to win now choose
your path wait what does skipping do
what did you what do you mean what does
skipping do
a fre blinds is one floor
mhm
and don't skip H that skips the tutorial
what did he say about ah here skip
garbage tag gives $1 per unused discard
this
round does anybody ever go for
this would that would that mean uh I
don't have to reach
450 if I H it's like when I feel like oh
I can't reach it but I still want to
keep on going it's pretty bad
right most skips are bad okay you
skipped at five but that means no money
ah
okay okay okay okay no choose your path
okay
select when you get more cards remember
you can rearrange them J trigger in
order from left to
right Joker's trigger in order from left
to right ah what what does that
mean and make sure that you use your
consumables let's just do again enhances
to select the cards to mul cards
uh wait shut up I want to look at them
uhuh uhhuh okay they don't have
multipliers now so if I let's say I have
two pairs and then I'd have a throwaway
card if I put the multiplier on the
throwaway card then it will suddenly be
useful that's a good way to use it
right no
oh oh no it only works on scor card [\h__\h]
okay but then I can just use it on a
pair
okay okay select up to two cards in your
hand and press use on the taret cards to
enhance them oh okay well we'll probably
use one of the
Jacks
oh okay
yay the are these lines new the squiggly
lines I think they're new I'll
squiggle I could have done too oh
[\h__\h] it should have forced me to choose
to whatever okay uh the Joker wait The
Joker I can use it anytime oh oh what
did they mean by like you know the
positioning of the Joker
wait if I put in a
joker and I have to choose five cards
would one of the five cards be the
Joker Joker is a passive Joker is
automatic Joker is automatic you said
that
twice uh that'll make more sense when
you get
more it only matters if you have
multiple Jokers ah oh okay I see cuz
they're passive they meant like up here
they activate from left to right
or from the outside to the I don't know
what they said but probably left to
right so if there were five Jokers the
left one would be used first
uh-huh uh-huh oh
oh but is the joker now going to be used
on every hand I play or automatically on
the first one I
play every hand I play oh
wow
okay okay okay
let's make something we have two pairs
surprise surprise but we also have 54
free too 5 4 3 2 that's four numbers I
could throw away the
seven or I could just do two pairs again
I don't
know we have free clubs we can go for a
Flash oh free clubs which ones are clubs
again [\h__\h]
uh clubs which the club is the Clover
because it starts with C right okay okay
free flush
oh can we do a FL a free threee of those
and then a pair or so let's see what's a
flush five cards a chair the same suit
okay why would you throw in those other
good cards there it's just not doesn't
feel right no no wait never never never
mind what wait he has this one has five
of the
same that is you meant three of a
kind drop the three and the
two but then we can't do
5432 64 five for wait if
[Music]
we it's hard it's so
difficult uh flashes are the easier hand
to get
mhm we can just play a
pair but that's so
boring discard any non clubs discard any
non clovers you
say I I guess that's a fun thing to do
wait but that's so
many are you
sure gone for the big Club
yeah that's
crazy that's wait that's uh discarding
that's
crazy
haha I think we got one it doesn't have
to be consecutive right we can do this
this this this
this oh
hey okay
wow I got a straight does it matter in
what order I put them up wa what
oh as as soon as I reach the blind it it
immediately stops it oh interesting I
didn't think it I thought it would keep
on going but yeah what would be the
point yeah I should rearrange them oh I
get a bonus if it's like arranged
nicely I get a bonus for using less
hands oh I see I see I see I see I
see bonus gold for hand get you money
uhhuh bonus for finish quick
oh cool cash out only seven bucks so low
and I have nine bucks should I really
you're
anus you're
anus anus
start anus
start my what now you
anus and what the sun
uh your anus nness if you read this
backwards it's nus so oh it's like you
can say uranous
[Music]
what okay what does it do do these are
the cards that uh how the the the the
the the things that I use up mhm
converts up to free selected heart cards
two hearts
oh uh level up two
pair two
pairs you mean two pairs so four cards
what plus one multiply 20 CH what what
what does what what does this
[Music]
mean two pairs become
stronger if I had two pairs right two
pair the two ah no you mean the two pair
ah now I understand the two pair thing
itself gets more reward if I make two
pairs I
see and
I don't know that they're both nice
let's just go for the
anus buy and
use I don't know if I want to use it
right away are we still I guess yeah no
just buy for now maybe or is buy and use
H buy and use
okay you what
now what's this ah per the game oh
should no I have no more
money I think we're fine next
round should I go next round should I
buy the sun
too could buy a pack I guess
so choose uh one of up to three tet
cards to be used
immediately choose one of up to five oh
let's do a four
Arcana Arana
pack gotcha well okay we have creates a
random Joker card
cool enhances one select the card into a
steel card steel card multiply 1.5 while
this card stays in hand
uh-huh judgment is it this one which
which is this this is good yeah right
cuz I get a free Joker okay use which
one which one which
one R it's just
red it's just red man I wanted to see a
funny one that's bad this Joker gains
plus fre multiply when any booster pack
is skipped oh oh I see
okay that's the worst Joker in the
game a well
okay oh well it is what it is uh next
round I'm fine with it just being next
round wait so my my thing it's active
now what did I activate I don't even
know anymore well I have to do the 600
already okay okay we got to we got to
get like a lucky thing again discard r
two random cards what what did you just
say well we have uh ooh king queen and
Jack and that whoa whoa whoa
whoa this is pretty not good wait oh we
could do something with the hearts you
say because we got four heart
cards can could go for a straight too
right
buffer oh I think that's on
YouTube oh yeah it seems to be
location discard non hearts
Okay click
suit
okay uh what did that do did that sort
by the icons right okay so let's let's
do
that oh but ah this one still had the
multiplier now I'm like not using it
that's so
sad it is what it is right we just need
one more Heart Card we're definitely
going to get that it's fine you can use
it later oh does that start stay in
there you can hold
it I can keep it if I want I mean what's
the point if we're probably getting a
heart so we're just going to play it
right so I don't know yeah it reshuffles
after every blun okay
discard I think one two three we got
one and now should I sort by r no I
guess it's sorted by rank already as
well so throwing it in like this is
fine yay flush almost a straight FL is a
straight flush when it goes by order as
well oh what what's a straight flush is
there a
here aha aha yeah yeah that's what it is
that's what it is I see how it
is go
yippe why did they throw away those
cards and kept this
one plus four
multiplier
5004 my other flush was better
huh H because it discards two at random
it's the boss effect ah but it only
discards it after I put out my hand huh
okay what do we have uh
oh Ace Ace was one or 14 right we have 1
Two Three
or the White Queen
was 12
11 try going for
diamond the diamond diamond oh we could
we
could could also go for hearts again
have same
amount but I guess it would
no I don't
know at two pair wi so we can discard
non
twos
true we don't need much more
so flashes are good to go for beginners
because they're easy and score
relatively well
mhm more diamonds left in
deck H I guess ah because discard it
means I'm not getting those again huh so
this is what I could still
get so all hands and all discarded cards
will not come
back uh what are we I don't know what
I'm looking for we have like a decent
amount of everything
still hover over the deck for a quick
view ah oh that's I don't know that
looks very complicated to me right now
uh I don't know what to do all right
let's do a stupid pair let's just oh
wait I can't even um what do way what
should I throw
[Music]
away go for diamonds yeah okay I okay
now diamonds are these ones right okay
[Music]
so like this
discard right discard
discard
whoa I got so many
diamonds uh
cool 98 would be nice if we had a
seven but okay that's that's all I need
35 * 4 that's at least 100 at least 30
yeah you're
doneo I have defeated you with my cards
also we're getting another multiplayer
we didn't even take that into account
wow okay I see this is fun
mhm this is good cash out but so we had
one boss blind but we keep on going wow
we got two jokers here to byy oh do you
always get Jokers to buy if you defeated
a boss PL is that the thing this Joker
gains plus one multiplier per
consecutive hand played Without scoring
a face card oh that sounds complicated
this Jer gains 0.25 multiply for each
card sold resets when boss plan is
defeated
sold I can sell cards I guess out of my
deck
uh both bad yeah I don't know sounds
complicated oh oh I could sell the Red
Joker you can sell Jokers and
consumables ah only those cars ah makes
sense makes
sense chat is bad if it thinks bus is
bad The Wheels on the BS Go Round and
Round sell the red and go next yeah but
should I if we're selling one should we
buy this one
first by bu is good bus is good sell red
jok or buy voucher app gain plus one
discard each round
uh save your money bus is okay for
[Music]
specific bus just means you pay 10 and
under cards to keep 10 and under cards
to keep increasing B what you didn't
really phrase that much
easier one mistaken boss wreck you oh
[\h__\h] okay that sounds difficult for
beginners what does this say this took
against plus one multiply per
consecutive hand played Without scoring
a face card do you mean consecutive
hand uh but I cannot play one of the
face
cards like if I play a face card with a
consecutive I will not get the
multiplayer
a okay it doesn't give me any minus if I
play a face
card I'll just
um I'm going to buy a pack cuz it's fun
to open packs I'm going to get the
orange
one W this one's
gold this one's bonus
who Gold Card
W yeah bonus Ace is good oh eh but it's
gold it's gold skip it for red
card
oh oh wait this means I have to buy the
booster and then skip
it I thought that meant just don't buy
it at all
oh I really just wanted a
card $3 if this card is held in hand at
the end of round yeah cool okay H 30
extra
chips all right let's get the scoop
let's do what the C tells us to
do so yeah whatever this this next round
I
guess we committed to it we start small
again
Yim uh we have oo wo wo wo wo o o we
have pears do we we have pears we have
apples we have oranges a Full
House
house fre yeah I knew
that Full House baby
[Music]
every w Wait what small blind is 800 now
oh it went up oh [\h__\h] I thought we were
already
done Nostalgia yeah I used to watch that
a little bit at uh the new show I didn't
watch because the new show is [\h__\h] the
the the first one is uh was cute though
when I was so young flush of heart flush
flush
flush oh okay yeah yeah yeah why did I
already forget that brain empty
oh uh yeah okay
those hi so many hearts doy doy doggy
doggy oh so much
money we did it in two turns it'll get
more and more difficult to do something
in one turn bro do does the game
consider that that you know it's not
that easy anymore but still reward me
for doing it with two turns please
J Cool Bean a bean why is it a bean why
is it a bean what
why plus five hand size reduces by one
every
round
bean
bean plus 12 multiple if played hand
contains a straight wow plus
12 a [\h__\h] Bean by pack and Skip hm
how much money do I have 11 only
11 Venus all right this Joker won't work
for
waa me is okay get it and save money for
a couple rounds with it
Advantage Plus back just bu one everyone
I don't know save
[Music]
money but it's just so triggering if you
buy a pack and then you see what's
inside at least don't even show
me and then you know if if you see
what's inside you have to skip it that's
so triggering just don't show
me I want to look wa there's a coin on
it
why plus 10 chips two times multiply one
in four chance to destroy card okay wa
foiled card foil that's plus
50 that's a good King those cards are
amazing yeah this one also has a thing
on a
seal
worth King gives six
gold oh red SE let's go let gold oh you
guys like all these
cards
H Red Seal place
[Music]
twice what re trigger this card one
time nine is great nine is good what's
nine oh oh this
[Music]
one e we're not supposed to pick Annie
we were going to
skiper it's okay it doesn't go back on
the multiplier right
so 89 chips on single hand
[Music]
yeah okay eh they're both nice which one
say say foil or say gold foil
gold why is your face on the Joker card
what foil gold foil foil foil gold foil
foil foil foil I think there's more
foil
selecto
okay
bye-bye big blind 1,200
okay okay okay okay okay o uh we didn't
get our foil card that's so sad we have
we we could do uh the thing with the
three and the
two right the thing that I did before
what was
that this one the no no uh wait
what oh is this does this mean I have
that in my hand right now when it's blue
I I feel like I have more than that like
this one Full
House choose the
straight straight straight five cards in
a row do I have five cards in a row wait
wa w Wait we do wait we have four cards
in a row here right cuz this is
14 13 12
11 a 10 would be
nice okay so we throw some cards out
here
hope I'm doing this
right what 10 yeah that's what we need
right
straight 1 2 3 4 5
yippee World straight inbound almost
stra what's Royal oh because I'm doing a
straight with king and queen oh is that
a
thing W it's burning wait we already did
it wait we already did it yippe
so close to Royal Flush
why
why Royal is highest from a huh straight
Royal Flush is flush plus straight with
a single suit 10 J q k a what was I
missing same ah ah I was just missing
them to all be the same
icon ah I
[Music]
see CH C wa what is this Mega jumo
W
no plus two chips for each remaining
card in deck uhhuh would be currently
chips uh earn $4 at the end of round a
golden Joker SP elro
cards sell the
red really should I sell the red trucker
now the heart of
cards no not yet okay let's buy this
first spectral why why a spectral why do
we want
that open
well pretty cards wait what why are they
showing me my
hand oh because I use it on the cards H
I can only choose one right destroy one
random card in your hand add two random
enhanced Aces to your hand add foil
graphic or poly Chrome effect to one
selected card in hand I can choose two
oh
whoa add polychrome to a random Joker I
don't even have oh no wa I don't r i oh
it would be one of
these Ouija board converts all cards in
hand to a single random rank minus one
hand
size what you guys have to help me
choose I think this one sounds really
good this is this confused my brain so I
cannot judge Luigi
good IGI good hex and Luigi Aura and
Luigi grim and Luigi well great that's
like everything I'm I'm getting that we
like Luigi I hate
Luigi the Green
Man s Jimbo and hex what Jimbo where is
Jimbo ah this guy what what Jimbo what's
Jimbo what about Mario Mario I HTE Mario
too I only like the princesses
now Jimbo The Joker Jimbo is the plain
Joker ah yeah cuz he's talking to me his
name was
Jimbo weigi and Skip for red card ah if
I I guess if I even just Skip One I
still get a
multiplier that's cool
M yeah or
skipping not worth it forcing one rank
can be good for four a kind build
forcing one
rank
where conin hand s isn't that oh wait
now now my brain registered
it convert all cards in hand oh wait all
cards in this current hand but that
doesn't mean I'll immediately or is this
my starting hand for the next
[Music]
round is this my starting
hand no okay
uh I don't know I'm going
to well I'm going to do this because it
sounds fancy but we have to choose
anyway do we want foil holographic or
polychrome maybe poly Chrome no wait
plus 10 multiplier Plus times 1.5 what's
better wait what's
better it plus
10 wait + 10times
1.5 oh it's random oh [\h__\h]
okay and okay what do we want to use it
on I have to choose the
[Music]
card maybe on the
ace yeah Ace always usually Ace
oh use what is that ah it was the
foil okay well it looks
nice and then destroy one random card in
your hand at two random enhan should we
do gri it's fun add polyr to a random
Joker desty
Jokers we should only do this if we want
to destroy this one because would be
kind of stupid
if although I mean I don't know not
necessarily it could be on this one too
Ouiji Ouiji okay convert all
okay which
one I don't care it's all what oh it's
ah I all became
sevens wait did the ace become a Seven
did the ace become a Seven Lucky
Seven the ace became with seven so it's
Ace anymore it's not an the ace
anymore
what well you guys said it's better to
put it on an ace now it's a
seven
okay next
round one 1,600 all diamond cards are
debuffed I don't wait diamond diamond oh
diamond diamond the edgy
one 127 we got so many now we play
sevens I guess we do have a lot of Sev
should have bought the golden oh [\h__\h]
okay let's
go
oh oh
okay it's debuff but it doesn't mean I
can't use it right scores no chips and
all the abilities are disable well then
I guess we'll just get rid of those in
any case fish for
sevens should I just throw out the
debuff ones or all of the nonsense
sevens well for five
sevens all non
servants come on come on Lucky
s
folk should have just gone again keep
fishing keep
digging everything that's not seven
four of a kind keep fishing keep keep
going can we get much
sevener God gave you four discards for a
reason wow that's so
inspiring oh this also looks so nice but
we're going to use 7 s s s seven
surprise 120 *
12 Lucky Seven
[Music]
my lucky
stri my lucky strike I don't know what a
Lucky Strike is but this feels like a
Lucky
Strike it are we first trying like is
this my first hand is already doing it
oh my God it's burning it's burning it's
burning wo wo wo oh
W oh it's a cigarette right forgot I
knew that I knew
that
wow seven is
good I only got n bucks for that you
suck oh what is
this oh what is these what are these
[Music]
M we should go for DNA DNA what's DNA
DNA what does it say DNA this is because
it looks like okay if firstand of round
has only one
card what why would it only have one
card add a permanent copy to deck and
draw it to hand what I make more
sevens play one card it gets
copy
oh what
what play your best card permanent copy
permanent
copy I guess we'll just see it in action
okay let's just let's just do it and see
it in
action play single seven to make more
permanent what what does permanent mean
like will it always be in my
hand spectral you want the spectral pack
[Music]
again
okay sigil and medium convert all cards
in hand to Rand to single random suit
suit was not the number right add a
purple seal to one select a card in your
hand creates T card when
discarded medium sigil medium sigil suit
is the icon M okay
okay purple the
six purple seals are amazing
medium on the free medium medium and non
seven ah ah okay because I would discard
it if it's not a seven probably purple
the six white the six white the six it
could be any card right medium and non
seven okay all
right purple to six white the six purple
to three I agree more with purple the
free I'll go with the
free I Believe In The
Free okay next round let's go we're back
to small blind but small blind is 2,000
now
baby yeah B wait why is it h why are we
back to small blind did we just have a
boss blind or could I have
what how come we're back to small BL
don't forget DNA what do you
mean oh oh
[\h__\h] it first hard of so I have to now
dig for seven zent to free so like I
discard o this is actually a good hand
though like all of this is good I I'll
play a single
seven it Oh I thought I would need to
play the find the free and play the
free play angle
seven oh oh wait that's DNA I I was
looking at something else that was the
other thing okay okay okay here uh I
play a single
seven I play
one
seven yeah
okay that's
crazy
oh is it but I just added a seven
basically I just added seven into my
deck
right and now we want to
discard these cards and look for more
sevens and the free I forgot why we're
looking for the free but
um I guess because if we discard the
free we get a a fancy thing
okay play seven and
King I could
yeah I mean I could play
this no just search for sevens okay
we'll see how that
goes not worth it this SC for okay okay
okay if you think that's the W hello 777
we just need one more
Steven one more so pretty too bad I'm
never going to use it cuz now I'm always
using uh
sevens keep
digging the seven Hi
mcra God gave you four discards for okay
okay I already heard that okay all right
all
[Music]
right my lucky strike want in a million
my lucky strike
got me
[Music]
got
wo
wo so
go what only five bucks
wao my chat
[Music]
died I might get outpaced what you you
mean
outpaced negative what's negative
negative oh I mean
this two chips for each remaining card
in
deck
oh okay
negative plus one Joker oh I can get six
Joker for each remaining discard oh no
no no no
no okay
bye how wait I don't have the money sell
red card now
okay
goodbye
goodbye deck unlocked what do you what
what like you mean like the Dave the
diver stuff huh okay I have no money so
that's all I can
[Music]
do go
next
goodbye a goodbye yeah oh you who's a
goodbye oh you did such a
goodbye
ah man so many pairs but all we want is
sevens I'm sorry this is like boring now
but when we get sevens we're so happy
we're so happy aren't we such Happy
People
77777 okay more seven please one more
please the Polie okay okay okay
okay well this is very easy for a
beginner because I don't have to look at
the this info anymore because I'm just
looking for the same thing what DNA oh I
forgot it oh no oh wait can I still do
it I forgot it can I still do
it I just play another seven like one
single seven then we have to look for
another seven
okay oh should I played Seven of Hearts
what one two oh I get it
back
[Music]
sexy my lucky strike one in a million my
lucky strike
oh oh oh oh let's go let's
go cash
out wow what is this it looks funny
looks like Piko one and two chance to
create a tarot card when any booster
pack is up no
Venus Venus level up threee of a kind
plus two multiply on two you tell me
which one's good skip to save money yeah
we got to we got to save
money Hallucination is weird where do
you see this name of Hallucination is
this
hallucination okay skip how to how to
okay I'm I'm I welcome that because
we're always low on money the head all
heart cards are debuffed uh-oh oh [\h__\h]
oh we have a bunch of heart
sevens oh oh sad oh
well
yeah okay we got some sevens I have to
play another seven right I what if we
play this one then we copy the four
seven okay okay yeah I get it I get it I
get it copy the funny seven copy the
cool I get it I get it you can just say
foil by now I understand what foil means
ining
oh wo wo wo wow already 790 just by
playing one oh wait okay so we got rid
of this this this this
right yeah wa so many good cards though
if we weren't looking for
sevens I'm so scared to accidentally
press play hand one to oh wow wow wow
wow
I just have so many sevens man seven oh
but do I discard this too no right I'll
keep it
right keep I would keep it I think free
cards is high enough
chance to get another seven yeah
[Music]
yeah I play or should I discard and look
for a better seven okay but I get reward
for Less
discards
play random Italy
noises you can discard seven replay all
five it's fine okay we do we already
reach 4,000 Maybe
maybe let's see echola
seven I can't do math you do it for
me by Lucky Strike One In A Million by
Lucky
Strike let's
go let's go oh BN after your anus and
Venus now we have
saturnus what Saturn
your wait if you rearrange this your a
it's almost never
mind uh level up straight uh Plus threee
Mt and uhuh this looks cute Joker
retrigger all played cards in final
hand final hand of round wa so I could
get another seven like like isn't this
like if I play a
777777 and then it will give me 7777
again you don't even look at this you
guys don't even care the paintbrush is
good
okay for more
sevens retrigger means they count
multiple times for scoring ah okay okay
okay I mean it doesn't sound bad at all
though but now we have no oh actually we
do have enough money
but final hand of ah how would you know
it's my final
hand oh only the fourth hand so if I end
it with the second hand it does never
work
okay should we just go let's go
back to small blind now it's
5,000 5,000 still reachable oh God now
the sale
seven Mama Mia that hurts my
brain just throw all I can't throw more
but I'm stabbing less no I should have
drunk seven up not Coca-Cola what the
[\h__\h] I drank a few seven ups when I was
in Italia I don't know why but I didn't
know what else to order because they
were serving alcohol and I was like um I
don't drink alcohol can you give me
something else
o no seven heaven soon it's
coming could play the Full House yeah
could I'll play single seven oopsie okay
here seven
make foral 7 before playing single 7even
oh oh okay yeah funny seven yeah would
have been
nice okay get out of here get out of
here we want the sevens I am
py I'm
scared
what seven doco now I have to play
something here okay we have pairs though
we have
pears yeah my luck ran out what the
hell this is why we want more sevens
okay I have two more this oh I do oh so
oh okay
[Music]
um uh H should I keep the tents just in
case for a pair
no maybe not keep the hearts oh
interesting no discard all
okay what uh oops uh yeah yeah sure
uh All In Everything Must Go sail sail
big yard sail big yard sail I didn't
accidentally discard seven right I don't
think so okay we have three sevens oh my
God
why are you leaving me to rot in hell I
want to go to seven heaven not
to smell hell I don't
know not looking good buz no it looks
good it's coming now it was just making
me wait a little bit but this is this is
the final is the final
[Music]
Discord y y y
yep
[Music]
yep yep ah we can do this it's a full
house that will
do play the non
Sev oh you want me to play a [\h__\h]
hand before oh you want me to just play
as like a pair so that I get oh
okay I mean
okay
mhm interesting oh I don't have to yeah
right I don't have to play five cards I
can just play however many I
[Music]
want it's just a discard I guess
so I don't know how far prob we would
have gotten with the full house but oh
wao whoo whoa
W should I discard this one should I
discard this
card before I play my
sevens can't disc oh because oh okay
true wait does it matter we have hearts
and we have some
clovers
um should I like does it matter if I
play them like
this does matter okay let's
go my luck
is one in a million my lucky stke give
me the money w we still don't have 5,000
but we still got a bunch of
sevens
mhm but no more discards so we could
play we could play like three sevens and
then a a full house yeah I was thinking
the same oh my God just like me we're
we're same brain wave let's
go yippee okay how
much looks good looks very good oh we
barely made it w okay I thought it would
be a bit more than that that's tough
that's
tough oh a little bit of YouTube
Shenanigans I see I
see well I thought you would would be
able to gain much more money but we're
kind of effed oh played cards with heart
suit give plus free multiplier oops
sorry and the
hermit Kermit hermit hermit first
doubles money oh the money I have right
now it doesn't cost
money oh no it does I'm stupid free
bucks to get in total 18 bucks or does
it double the money I have after using
the free
bucks oh it seems so after okay that's
still better than before I guess wow so
go
math and do we want one of these or I'd
buy the heart Joker yeah I mean why
not buffoon pack Joker booster buffoon
first okay choose one of up to two oh
okay it's cheaper
too than the
Joker wow pretty this this this is like
in Austria this J gains plus free tips
per discarded Club Card suit changes
every
round this yeah okay plus and multiply
if play hand contains a
flush not great but Castle is better
Castle's good castle castle okay we want
to discard Club well I'm just going to
discard everything that's not a seven
anyway so you know we could still get
this
one play cards with heart suit gift plus
free should I
buy heart Joker for sa to get that too
okay bye now we have a full Joker roer
uh plus one though actually it looks
full but we can still get one more in in
the
future okay
big blind let's effing go this is this
the last one here the club or does it
just continue forever cuz I feel like
didn't it say like
free or
so oh I'm only halfway a 4 out eight oh
God that's so difficult I guess it can't
be too easy to go until the end it was
so difficult and slay as fire too we
started with so many sevens
all right get out of here wait I got to
play a seven I got to play a seven I got
to play a seven here this one the funny
seven okay okay it's not a funny seven
it's a full seven okay I'm sophisticated
enough to understand that
now let's
go yeah yeah we get it we get it 800 for
nothing wonderful uh discard discard
discards and we got an upgrade what what
do gain plus free chips per discard
to
changes okay wait when are you giving
them to me I don't know 77 if we get a
new seven I don't think we got a new
seven that's kind of messed
up need speed up animation no no it's
okay discard all non seven okay discard
discard
discard huh where are my sevens where
lucky
sens it's here it's here it has
arrived
yippe so that I was thinking about
discarding first but I I feel like we
got to discard uh anyway so I want to
just wait until you know this moment to
discard more
I don't want to discard you know too
early you know what I mean I don't maybe
I could have maybe maybe I should have
who
knows wait what are we club club is what
the clovers right so
maybe this one
[Music]
instead save the
eights in case we don't get sevens are
you is that what you're saying why are
you so negative why are you so negative
it scares me we're going to get us we're
going to get sevens again don't worry
about
it go away thank you ah do s
ah do we have another discard no we
don't well we have a couple of
pairs yeah okay this is the reality guys
oh actually we'll probably make it with
that won't we should I oh I can't
discard H and and the H
uh oh oh oh you think you think we'll
need to go one more
hand all
right wait should I played one of these
shitty cards a [\h__\h] a damn it because
then it would be replaced with something
sorry I thought oh there's no
need ah he so close did you guys do the
math or what oh 777
oh we H this card [\h__\h] see if I would
have played one more card maybe we would
have one more
seven oh wait we can have two seven
pairs does that become something oh it's
four of a kind is that better than two
pairs I guess that's just
logic mhm okay well that's anyway the
end so I just play these
for bo bo
Bonk oh
Bonk w w not doesn't deserve it it
wasn't oh n
f I'm starting to feel that I can do
anything
guys but yeah that doesn't that doesn't
deserve the song wa what is
that
W this Joker gains time 0.25 multiply
every time a playing card is added to
your deck and we can have one more Joker
this one every time a plane card I guess
that's really good because we wait what
added to my deck though a playing card
or DNA it's amazing with DNA
because yeah because of the copy so it
just adds it once though probably once
per
turn I mean once per um copying so once
per run once per once per
blind okay oh that's exactly the money I
have wonderful our last
Joker let's go to the club to the club
everybody the introverts oh ew oh no oh
oh but we already have a [\h__\h] 75 wao
whoo wo
wo well just first I do this uh but uh I
want to play a foil one is it
okay
no yes no
yes and not ah because I see why you
guys are split because if we play a for
one then at least in the future blinds
we will have more foil ones but for the
sake of this
score we would get more a little bit
more of a push of score if I play this
one now is that what you're
saying cuz this will not give me
anything to my
score okay I think I agree with
that I
think oh it will not copy because it's
debuffed oh because that's an ability
oh okay if that's true then anyway we
got to do
it
okay how much do we get just for that
1,240 all
right
now H that's free cards that don't get
an effect but that's okay I don't need
effects right should I just play this
now
no five of a kind gaming
what yeah
seven
W my luck is like one in a
million my luck is already
7,000 oh my God not a single seven in my
hand I look at this hand with disgust
definitely dropping that one I guess
just drop
anything should I just drop or should I
keep the
Kings what suit is
Castle
heart only got one Heart In
Hand always just got the lowest ranks
first okay
7 seven Ace
Ace
sheesh five five I got so many
pairs we we discard some
more should I
discard should I discard the ace discard
Aces fives and King well okay so
everything
discard Kings discard
okay come
on wa it doesn't give me the 50 chips
right it doesn't matter I just got to
play a seven
w
w oh let's
go good good very good oh no man why are
you so hanging why are you hanging did
somebody play Hangman with you that's so
mean [\h__\h] is this does nothing 10 butt n
there's no way it does nothing is that a
troll or like what does it do he's just
hanging he just hanging helps deck
fixing okay let's read destroys up to
two second oh cool level up straight FL
Plus for mold and 40 chips
cool get rid of non
Sev
okay oh when do I get to do
that in my hand in my first hand
[Music]
later whenever I want okay I think
that's all I want to
buy because I think I want to save
money oh buy Celestial
pack okay I
could no I can't I don't have
money
next 11,000 we can do it we can so do it
we can't do it guys like for me slatest
fire was so difficult to ever reach the
end is is this game also really
difficult to reach the
end I I is there a chance I do it first
try who's Hang Man now okay hang man
now does it
uhhuh fre and
eight why fre and eight fre and six I do
threee and
six destroy the tents what this Castle
what this
Castle heart heart heart heart heart
heart heart heart heart heart
heart an ant8 isn't that bad once you
know what you're
doing it can be really hard certainly at
higher levels but low levels with a bit
of luck but low what do you mean lower
levels is there something Beyond eight
not on white steak this game at start is
easier than SP I'd say at the final
Stakes it can get more
steak steak not six can be useful
because it can be turned into seven with
a different tarot ah is it like plus
one value or
so I'll just do this then uh
use what the what just happened
what just
happened there God what what do I get
give me more give me something
what oh they just yeah ah now my deck is
just smaller I thought it would replace
it with
something okay are we playing something
right okay we're playing okay okay okay
uh
goodbye
goodbye m
maybe I should have kept one of those I
don't know
n oh I'm not going to discard my seven
Hearts no
oh a [\h__\h] D I forgot
about
uh well I don't know how about the
hearts
yeah then we get more
Hearts apparently it's good if I get the
same like a higher chance of getting
like right now it wants me to discard
Hearts but in the future may you know
maybe I'll be rewarded for having so
many of those wait a second should
[Music]
I I don't know if there's a point in
doing this I feel like there is
read The Joker no I understand
everything oh yeah
okay but I was hoping yeah play all the
hearts okay I was hoping to maybe get a
full hand of a full seven Hearts Full
Hearts but this is good too cuz the
chances of getting a full seven Hearts
hand now would be difficult Maybe
do we even have five seven ofarts I feel
like we do
one yeah we do uh wo 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 eight
we have
eight
oh I had a feeling wa we what wao that
happened so easy oo we unlocked the
Joker cool thank you your anus is so
back and devil enhance one like the card
into a gold card
cool uh well I don't have much money
should we buy a pack I don't
know Skip achievement unlock Celestial
pack devil Celestial Celestial we can
skip
CIO safe for in
you know what yeah I'll safe I'll
safe
16.5k
ooh this sounds
difficult but somehow we always
manage n barely any sevens in the
beginning
wait uh well I'll just the what's what's
heart heart heart heart heart heart and
disc
[Music]
card don't worry my first hand that I
will play will still be a seven but I'm
waiting to copy a better seven right
right disc
card
yeah oh there we go
copy copy that
o
o o o I wasn't actually saying O but it
sounded like
o I need one more seven
though so I discard once
again heart seven is better
now oh oh I guess so oh well
yippe let's
go seven seven seven seven seven seven
seven seven s seven s
seven who okay let's go two more hands
one more
discard ooh only one seven in
hand this one might not be a full seven
that we get I don't know well we still
have a lot in here but only one discard
discard the
hearts yeah should I discard the others
[Music]
too at least these
cards that's the maximum keep the fource
ah cuz it's a pair yeah just in case I
could do that
yeah maybe I prefer
that to yeah I'm playing for all sevens
but just in case like it's better to
discard these cards than this
card this
card
okay see now we didn't get a full hand
of seven so now we got to play I would
say this card
which is a full
house let's
go what do we get how much will it be
enough I don't think
so it would be nice if it's enough but I
don't I don't know I can't do math I'm
really bad at math it's
enough
yippe oh let's
go we have more than enough sevens in
our death but it's difficult with so
little discards is there any like card
that gives me more discards probably
right I would love a card that gives oh
what's this played cards with off rank
gift oh cool Mar level up four of a kind
no no why is it still this
[\h__\h] oh a TOD let's go a TOD that's good
a a let's go okay I buy for you
oh no oh [\h__\h] no
space What would
I bye Jimbo oh yeah it's our most basic
Joker oh no
Jimbo just because you're a basic be we
have to get rid of you I'm sorry that
hurts cell cancel no no no basic Jimbo
bye-bye okay I go next round I save
remaining money
or Celestial okay we did save last round
or save
more move I can move this oh move holog
hologram which one's hologram a this
one oh cuz the order matters
huh move Todd to the
left okay
multipli yeah makes sense multiply is
always to the
right that's the only multiplyer half
okay so should I buy one pack or
not
no
no the fish cards dra face down after
each hand
plate what how do I turn them
around How will I
know unless you discard they remain down
but how the [\h__\h] how do I know that I
have
sevens how would I know that I have
sevens so but in the beginning it's
still I can still see them
oh you don't oh what the
[\h__\h] sorting helps H okay holy [\h__\h]
you'll have to help me with that
y okay we start with
two
Sev Well for now we just
discard for now we just
discard keep the eight yeah somehow I
did it I don't know why I kept the eight
uh
heart I don't know why why do you say I
oh oh as like a hint or
so when the cards are turned or so so
that I know is that
why
ah but what if I get another eight then
that will [\h__\h] me up then I'm confused
well we'll play uh
un oh the hot
[\h__\h] the foil is just so shiny and you
always said use the funny one now you
don't say use the funny one anymore
this is fine
okay
um should I discard cards right
now I
rank I should I just play them okay but
how will I know ah How Will I Know How
will I know after this like how many
sevens I have I guess when they're
turned around I can at least still see
if they're like foil or something
right how many phone
cards will it show like will this be
good to look at oh no it won't show oh
[\h__\h] 17 gave you 5,000
what Oh you mean one five of sevens
mhm for Rank and sorting I'm not that
smart this will be the end of me if I
don't play on stream I will never
understand this
round okay so we got two eights here
four fours okay but this will stay this
will stay so that's a hint so only the
the five in the middle will be filled
up we just I mean yeah well let's
see I have won already what we don't get
to 22,000 what do you
mean I might just win it I my we do have
some nice new
cards what
[Music]
w million my lucky
St what I did not think we would get
this
much H hu let's [\h__\h] go
oh oh cute oh what the
[\h__\h] uncommon jok is each give oh
uncommon uncommon but we don't have
space
anywh minus one
ant minus one hand ooh ooh get baseball
cart not
with sell heart Joker and get
baseball not with you mean this one not
worth you mean this is not worth or this
is not
worth get baseball over Castle get
baseball got baseball baseball baseball
baseball baseball over Castle but it's
uncommon it would add to the counter
[Music]
uh
yeah that's why if anything I would sell
this it's better than hard one
though keep uncommon for baseball yeah
yeah right
[Music]
the other theas are too
good if you're going for flush five part
is
better NY Joker bye-bye oh no the horny
Joker oh
no bye-bye what is this one anyway play
face cards give oh we don't play face
cards we only play sevens in this
house du okay no pack
come baseball let's play baseball home
run home run with the Sev Celestial you
always want the
celestials oh should I rearrange these
by the
way
1.5 H I guess they're both multipliers
so it doesn't matter they're just at the
end that's fine okay uh what
what
what these aren not so nice are they
Pluto is not bad Pluto Pluto isn't Pluto
the one that's not a planet anymore why
are you in here with these huh you're
not in the same ballpark which is funny
cuz you're round like a ball and not
playing in the same ballpark my little
Pluto
boy it's a planet to me it's a
planet yeah honestly I mean
it's it very much looks like a planet I
mean it's so rude that it's not a planet
anymore what is it now a star like
that's looking more like a planet to me
I mean I know they all like and stars
are all in in right if you if they
weren't so far away they would look like
this too right um they're also round and
like balls but they're small right
but it's a DW it's a dwarf planet oh oh
yeah right what no what stars are like
this
what what does it do level up high card
high
card high
card what what's a high card plus one
mult and one the plus 10 what's a
high you play high card for
DNA um when you play 17 it's high
card oh
why I believe you but I I agree but I
also don't
understand yes next
round next round 20,000 30,000 40,000 y
okay here we go here we go we're looking
for oh so we could foil we could uh
double the foil or double the heart what
do you want this
time oh God the eye oh I didn't even
look at it
foil foil no more
Hearts heart don't matter anymore what
why okay because
of I don't know
why now that you're out of ah
because oh that's not why I was thinking
hards okay but sure
okay all
righty here we freaking go
[Music]
this card disc
card oh what are we what do we have Club
cards GRE club club
club club this is
Club
this go go go go go get rid of it all I
don't want to stay oh wow let's go let's
[\h__\h]
go woohoo
[Music]
one in the million ba my lucky
strike it's my theme song now it's my
winning
jingle yeah have a new
soundboard what what seven what how the
[\h__\h] did we get 76 F I didn't even
look how's this possible I can't do a
math I but I'm amazed I'm amazed okay
all right oh this is cute it's a smaller
smaller
Joker play cards with Spades to give
plus free when blind is selector create
two common
Jokers no I has no money not much money
and no space this is good you made
something I just a single seven what I
did oh I didn't look I didn't
what
amazing dream catches that's a cap up
group
right I don't need any change of yeah
these are working amazing for
me either by voucher or skip
[Music]
no I think for now we can uh save our
money because with how things are going
now we'll definitely pass the next round
knocking on wood but I mean we just got
76k so let's
go holy [\h__\h] man wa threee sevens from
the
start heart heart heart heart heart
heart heart heart heart yeah the windows
noise is because I knocked on my [\h__\h]
table can you believe it it wasn't doing
any Windows noises before I stream so I
was kind of freaked out by that oh free
Queen amazing but we don't need you I
don't need
you 17K holy [\h__\h] this is so good such a
good run is it
not is this a good run or not I feel
like oh my
god wow wow wow wow W I think that will
do the trick
I think this will do the trick guys I
think we're through it this
round holy
sh
w w w I don't even want to look one in a
million ba my lucky like holy [\h__\h] holy
h
w
oh 99k we almost broke 100k
oh they should put this game into the
casinos shot oh that that reminds me of
that anime shot
shot why does it remind me of that anime
wasn't there a character called
that Sher is good silver
oh JoJo what no not Jojo
some uh some magical like witches anime
girls anime that that what was it it had
a game
[Music]
too yeah little little witch
Academia what there a character called
that I haven't watched JoJo no no but
that reminds me did you guys see there's
like new cast members for the one piece
Netflix show they show them them
off and does this mean like they showed
a video of them doing a table read does
this mean the table read was very very
recently or could it also have been like
months ago and they're way further into
the production now because I feel like
man if they just did a table read now
it's going to take a long time still
feel like they would have done that ages
ago probably M probably the L okay okay
okay okay they did it ages ago but now
they're feeling like oh we're getting
close closer and closer to finishing
this thing so now we can show some
footage of the table read I guess okay
thank God thank God it's been so long
and you know when uh when it first aired
they were like on strike or whatever so
um you know how I fell deeply in love
with nami actress and I wrote to her on
Twitter I was hoping because she had way
lower followers I was hoping maybe
she'll reply to me but and then we were
like oh she's not replying because they
strike so I should try it again soon
maybe now they're not striking right
Emily red I'm going to strike on you I'm
going to try it
again Emily Rod my beloved I'm going to
shoot my
shot y okay so should we get
the lucky
Striker so we get the so we get this
card enhan this one select the card into
to a steal card 1.5 multip while this
card stays in hand stays in hand but
what if I play it the hand is that
okay I B skip we don't need
to
skip get it you can afford
it we good to skip Shar is okay skip for
okay wait do we actually get
interest it's the second time I see
someone say
that do we get interest skip for more
interest what we do
oh for every five we get more money when
do I get it do I get it
now no it's still
20 at the end of the round okay that
will be barely noticeable because I'm
just winning so much [\h__\h] money all
right 40,000 no problem but this says no
repeat hand types this
round oh so I can't do two sevens but
that's fine I might only need to do one
seven I mean one five of
sevens but can I do 1 seven to copy it
and then five sevens or is it also
repeat hand
timee that works
okay easy
[Music]
Yahoo
20 let's
[Music]
go what is this heart
[Laughter]
a burn burn burn baby burn burn burn I
want to see but
yeah this game is on
fire this game is sun fire
[Music]
this game is on
fire look at the interest
ah cash cash cash cash wait so one
interest per so I get the four bucks
back okay that's not that's not that
crazy four
bucks four wow oh wait actually no I I'm
thinking in you know in comparison to
the score but no no no we never get that
much money I'm thinking sometimes in my
brain it's like score equals money but
no no no okay that that that's fine then
that's
good that's important
popcorn what this roll boss bind one
time per ant temp ooh that might be
useful if we got a really [\h__\h] ant but
so far we've been able to overcome
everything I don't know if there's much
worse
[Music]
anties it it could be a r
saber
yeah yeah let's get
it
redeem director called redeemed oh
director got funny
name okay one hand size plus 20 mold
minus full mold per round play
what oh ah I see
oh go
[Music]
next popcorn only good really early mhm
yeah no let's go
next first hand is drawn face Ah that's
no not the big wait no wait what first
hand is dra isn't that's similar but
different firstand only the first hand
oh [\h__\h] oh
oh speed up I'm not I'm fine with it
though game speed or animation
speed sure a little
bit uh okay well anyway let's worry
about that later
should I be worried discard the first
hand we have plenty of sevens but what
if there's sevens in there but we
wouldn't know so okay yeah I guess that
makes sense
yeah that makes sense
um or what this car wait what the
firstand so if I wait wait wait okay
yeah if I play uh let's say we get to
that uh aunti whatever and and I play I
I don't see any of the cards in the
beginning
right but I'm what if I'm lucky and the
one like I choose just one card to play
and the one card I play is a seven then
maybe if I'm lucky it already
gets uh copied or should I not do
that just not worth the risk okay we'll
talk about it then I
guess we'll talk about it then what is
is this a diamond card okay well I don't
care I'm not really paying much
attention to that anyway how much will
it be
22,000 wo wo W wo W
wo we already have oh so many
sevens like relying on the sevens feels
like I'm playing a a very specific deck
like in slay the Spire when I I choose
to play one strategy one one way you
know what I mean this feels like same
kind of thing
go go go go go go go go feel like slots
yeah that's true as
well w w it's a ship deck oh yeah one
trick pony I know but it's fun holy [\h__\h]
we got over
100k oh oh reserved parking by law Joker
each face card held in hand has a one
and two chance to give $1 no converts up
to free select cards to go like honestly
paying with seven
is such a brain empty kind of way of
playing huh cuz I never have to think
about what I can create I just that's so
brain empty holy [\h__\h] the moon do I get
the
moon a [\h__\h] First Look for okay look
for hermit oh yeah I look for hermit
bye-bye looking for
hermit no I got Sun empress and haned
man destroy up what that's fine right I
can get get rid of non
sevens or I make sevens into multiplier
[Music]
cards
hman
okay uh yes let's do uh let's do the and
the Dan
maybe M oh
[Applause]
M yeah I I'll I'll do this one both is
fine right but I'll just do this do we
still want
the up this why would I want to use the
moon why would I want
clubs
[Music]
why W cuz my fold sevens are
clubs so I want other sevens to be clubs
too
but I already have so many hearts it
will be difficult to get clubs at this
point oh wow actually no holy [\h__\h] look
[Laughter]
at I I have a single Diamond seven so
that one maybe should be
converted holy [\h__\h] I have
25 Moon isn't
bad okay all right all right
oh I use it anytime right but in in the
game not
[Applause]
now
okay cesal pack
too I mean I could okay why not I have
money mice Earth Jupiter wow level up
Full
House four of a kind flush do I always
flush what's flush
where's flush I do straight I do no I do
flush do I do I flush do I do
flush for of a Kind eh as a safety if I
you mean if I ever don't get five Sevens
at this point I feel like I will always
get five
sevens but
okay wasn't such a good uh draw was
it 52,000 Let's It
Go
easy wait hey I could go in the first
hand but should I still copy should I
still
copy
okay what uh should I should I use this
no just should we just should we just
end it already should we end the
suffering should we
[Music]
Moon here's Moon okay uh hi
hi wait what am I doing no no no uh
sorry I misunderstood we're changing the
non these ones the
non-believers
into the clovers
save none on the sevens and none on the
sevens save it for the boss oh
okay then go away go back go back to
where you came from wa just play we just
[Music]
play I I don't even feel like singing
anymore because this is too easy
now w w w
one in a million my lucky
strike oh what is
that each played card with Spade suit
gives 1.5 multiplier wi for suit changes
I don't know what this means uh convert
up to free card no
Celestial that's a very good Joker too
random skiper skiper Okay C to
go what do you got for me wa wo that was
a big one oopsie Venus Saturn Earth you
anus
Neptune
Neptune level of straight flush straight
flush o do I ever do
that that's kind of unlucky again
huh Planet X Doo what does SP an X to
skiper skiper Should Skip should I skip
it what happens if I skip it do I get
anything nice just Venus Venus Venus
level up fre of a Kind we're not going
to use any of
this no Venus just in
case did I get a reward for
skipping wait how's this work again does
this go into here
I forgot does this go up
here what
this I just guess you was a
okay sure
okay I'm your Venus I'm your something
your
desire okay uh first hand is drawn face
down so we just play some
[\h__\h] and then we don't have to worry
about it anymore right but what if
I what should
I what what does this mean what do you
think this
means maybe that these are face
cards the two left could that
be oh discard the
corners sort by numbers
discard the whole
hand any amount discard front and
back okay I like this probably the lower
ones have
higher higher chances of not being a
seven I was going to say but I feel like
these are would that is this like
logical that these might be face
cards if they stay over
there no matter what I
do yeah should I do
this okay discard do do they turn do
they turn around now oh oh
interesting the this one's definitely a
seven right
oh this might be a 7
to but can't can't be
sure that was definitely a seven this
could be a seven
wa wait this is by no that's by that's
by that's by the icons right this is by
number discard once
more should I
discard these and one of these or just
these threee
discard
unknown left four
maybe four left
okay I mean we have so many sevens it'll
probably come
around yeah there we go but I play one
to copy
I wonder if this is a foiled one it
could be a foiled one because we haven't
seen a foiled seven now so the chances
of this being a foiled seven is pretty
yeah I would do it too yeah yeah oh if
this is the foiled one that would be
funny ah it's not okay the chances were
high
though yeah okay
okay hi hi hi hi no foil seven that's
kind of rare at this point
where we already have 20,000 just for
playing 17 that's so
crazy it's so easy guys life is so
easy oh wait oh I did I clar
it wait that was oh right that was a
boss fight it didn't feel like a boss
fight what what that was antil
climatic what do you mean one more round
one more like round of
eights like eight more of these oh no
one more one more and now is round
eight i h okay oh the Joker is so
sad create a tarot card if hand is
played with four dollars or less uh and
has just one to select a card into a
wild card weed I'm a wild
card can't be used as any I don't know
you tell me
[Music]
time for the final antt bomi and ant go
hand in hand
together Arana P which
one big
one look for hermit or Temperance or
can both oh okay why not both
okay
hermit whe for what does her do doubles
money oh you want me to double my money
one in four chance to add foil to a
random Jer creates up to two random
taret cards creates up to two random
Planet cards must have room select two
cards convert the left card and to the
right
card
uhhuh death is good
too the left card and to the right you
mean like if I choose a seven and a
three
the left card into the right
card uh should the seven be on the
[Music]
right wait what reorder
first oh wait select two cards convert
the left card into the right card drag
to rearrange drag here so I choose the
threee and seven and then the free turns
into a foil seven
[Music]
okay okay people say the other ones are
good too but we just went for that cuz
that's
fun and another
one fool creates the last tarrot or
plant card used during this turn the
fool
excluded fool you like the fool
wait use Moon
first should
I it's another death cre so lost
ah
oh
oh oh but this now I have to use it in
the
round I
[Music]
suppose
cool yeah using Moon first would have
just given me another Moon I
guess all right Crimson heart one R CH
oh I don't care I don't care I'll make
enough money anyway Yahoo let's go
select the
Blinder play the right or should I play
the death first doesn't
matter I'll just do
this DNA and then death okay death
doesn't matter okay okay w w w wow W 30k
guys
Fork should I do like
this mhm smart I get it I get it I
totally get it I get you should we use
this too convert up to free select the
cards to clubs clubs oh no no not yet
[Music]
okay this
C byebye suckers I'm going into the mid
blind goodbye goodbye goodbye goodbye
goodbye goodbye goodbye oh
oh
sh
sh one Joker what happened to you plus
20 mold of plate hand contains free fuel
cards
oh I do that a lot because I play one
foil uh seven a lot it's an early game
card okay someone got hungry must have
been the library girl the
Bako who eats paper and
books beginners and streamers luck
really you think I'm just lucky well you
know I got the Lucky
Sevens
w why all these [\h__\h] planets again
Mercury no Mercury [\h__\h] all of that I
don't like it level up high card maybe a
Pluto
[Music]
okay I I guess that's not so bad huh we
like that one
okay oh
next here we
go chat wants a a specific one you mean
the Planet X or whatever that was I'm a
proon I'm going for Max oh look at this
stting
[Music]
hand let's go wait I could convert these
Hearts how many was it three oh let's
convert them but I'm going to throw
these away
[Music]
first one two
three I get it I'm so good at this game
now oh I got a Jer we let's go wait a
sec oh oh oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh oh [\h__\h] maybe I should have
saved it from the
boss hly
fony oh I should have saved it for the
boss holy
[\h__\h] we'll get it again we'll get it
again one free
roll first
shop does it uh apply to this one
too Jesus macroni
H useless Skipper re the
shop I mean we're at the end we can
spend some money to roll
it sator and Joker adds the number of
times poker hand has been played this
run to
multiplayer oh could have bought
this that's a good one h that's a good
one poker hand what is
that got the packs check run
info adds the number of times poke hand
has been played this run to multiplayer
so what poker these are all poker hands
what do you mean I don't
understand you play five of a kind 18
times not worth DNA still better number
on to the
uhuh just choose the highest
one don't throw oh
okay not
oh why why is it FR why is it throwing
[Music]
cuz you need to sell something okay and
all of these are nice right I mean we
could get rid of the castle
but I think we're good to win
probably
[Applause]
uh but we could still I don't know
re roll one more
time B
wa you can go into depth with that
one let just going next I don't know
should
I buy the
packs pack for
seven that's the worst Joker this one or
the other one pack spend your cash
[Music]
skip
next Crimson heart sounds like something
herb would
say all right this is The Final
Countdown one random J disabled which
one the count
that's the one I think I care about the
least
maybe
[Music]
yippee what's this do oh cre tag card
when
discarded
hey which one shio enhances one selected
card into steal
card uh tell me when to use this guys
[Music]
uh on a non seven Ace into
steal but that would mean I I'm not
supposed to discard it
right let's discard
first no
yeah okay well we have five sevens so we
already won
cuz I'm going to play this now right is
there a point in still doing that
because I mean I guess kind of but not
really steal the ace okay ah and then I
play the
17 and then we're
already then we're already
good don't W don't
[Music]
DNA oh because the multiplier will give
me more if I play a
[Music]
full
uhuh
uhuh I mean I read this but it's
disabled so yeah the the the castle is
disabled but we have the DNA
what uh wait are you saying what what
are you saying what are you saying what
are we saying what what did you tell me
to not
do what did you tell me to not do oh
because what what are you telling me not
to
do I forgot what you're telling me not
to do don't
DNA why
not because like I mean it's it's
working
now so wouldn't I want to do it
now or or do you mean because disable
another
Joker wait does it add another Joker I
thought it was switches or does it with
every hand I send in it uh adds another
Joker that will be disa it's it switches
okay okay I should I just play a full s
come in hand
then yeah
okay are we already winning oh my
God I
win good thing I didn't bet against you
yeah cuz you would be betting against my
whole chat as well good choice that you
did it first try first run first
win
yay that was fun thank you for helping
me I mean I feel like if I wouldn't go
with this strategy it would be more
difficult because I have to think so
hard each time and getting the
same five of a kind is like pretty high
ranked anyway already right
so I feel like I would go for that Strat
all the time because it's just so
simple the tutorial seed is very
forgiving nah don't say that that will
make me feel less accomplished and my
achievements will mean
nothing is that
true is that true baseball club very
strong h
yeah I'm never going to get the same
setup I know but I feel like it's easy
to go for that like just start building
your sens or whichever card you
[Music]
want no you played well thank
you thank you thank
you honestly that was already 3 hours
and uh I think maybe we just Read Super
chats now cuz I really owe you to read
super chats cuz I didn't read super
chats yesterday I still have a lot of
anniversary super chats to read and so
on um so I probably should be reading
some I mean it's a great cut off
anyway a new Joker unlocked and another
Joker unlocked let's go cute oh these
are all the ones that we saw like uh
oops I skip one flowers flower flower
flower
flower W what's this pretty with this
WOW more
Jokers win R without playing fre of oh
wow uh W I don't know so so win a run
you it copies ability of Joker to the
right cool wait that's cool that sounds
pretty good if you have a really good
Joker to the right start run with the
crystal ball voucher and two copies of
the
fool magic deck on
oh oh flower thank you that was fun I'm
out of here I'm going to read Super Chat
and you're welcome to
stay stay at
Bay
flower that was fun but now I want to
place SL this
fire but slightest fire is so much more
difficult there's so much more to take
into account and think
[Music]
about SL the spes goed that is tool that
is
Tool playing like a total Ace let's go
let me bring in some music
[Music]
um here is there anything good I have a
lot of unnamed audio stock files any of
these good oh I like this
[Music]
one lucky strike on that audio stock
file I got a good
one all right all right all right do we
have a
note of what super chats to read I
think I roughly remember what I was told
yesterday H thank you GD what would I do
without you honestly you're the only one
keeping
track ah the yeah the off
collab okay
okay oh that one's so actually
surprisingly
muchos muchos
Grand wait I should change
location you know what let's go to the
office
[Music]
yippe quiet
yippy wow I like this
[Music]
music okay I should probably put up the
thumbnail so you know what I'm
reading wait this is a coincidence I'm
now using the mixer that she sold
[Music]
me the extra mixer she
had it's nice it's white you know in
Japan they set up this whole streaming
setup for me and they had a a black
Yamaha
ag8 uh which you know on First Look it
looks so complicated um then I never
really understood how to use it now I'm
finally starting to
understand um and then mint was like a I
got this one um too the same one as you
but I have it in white I have an extra
one because I bought two accidentally do
you want to have one not for free but
like you know I was like oh you know
what yeah and now I'm so glad because at
the time I just said yeah because I
don't like the
roadter um but now I don't see okay I
think the
roadter was not at fault but it was like
superficially adding more problems
because it's just annoying and I feel
like it added a little bit onto the U
USB connection Shenanigans yesterday I
don't know maybe it did maybe it
didn't but I feel like you
know and this one's pretty it's white so
now I'm thinking of I have a black desk
but I want to buy a white desk mat to
cover the whole thing I want to I want
to try making more things here
white but everything's black right now
so it's going to be quite a mission and
I want to buy I know I have this like
mechanical keyboard right that waya put
together but maybe I'll buy key caps for
it that I white I did get some keycaps
gifted
um which all look very nice but there's
this one that has like this Takami fan
art all all over the
keys but what was it I think it just had
absolutely no writing on it so I'm like
where how the [\h__\h] will I know what keys
I'm
[Music]
pushing but it looks
nice so I don't know maybe I can just
use accent of it but I don't
know I don't I don't I would think I
know it by heart because I usually don't
look much at my keyboard when I'm typing
but still for reassurance i' like to
have writing on them
[Music]
I'm probably just going to get new key
caps and then I wanted to be either like
whsh or
like big or yellowish or
so I found some cute ones already on
Amazon but maybe I should buy from a
specific shop that specifies in it I
don't know I need to figure out though
like as long as I buy the right like uh
amount of keys and it says mechanical
keyboard key caps will it always
[Music]
fit or do I have to buy very specific
ones yes they should sze should fish fit
okay cool cool cool cool then I think I
know what I will
[Music]
buy pretty Universal okay
unless they are low profile case or
something oh okay it didn't say they
were so probably they not
okay they have different angles at the
very top but they should fit the
switches no problem okay cool yeah I
guess some are kind of like upwards or
so for
example
mmhm most Keys have like a plus Shing
yeah I saw that it it showed that on the
back mhm
[Music]
okay let's read super Jacob 47 py Ray
red
da monkey dead you space wonderful
things for the rainbow wow hi Mama
today's my fourth birthday as a kfp and
the first time since 2021 you stream on
my birthday oh I always oh I
consistently did since then wow there's
some people who are so unlucky I never
stream on their
birthday for that alone thank you very
much you always make my day better with
such small things just hearing or seeing
you lift my mood bottle of joy you sorry
I probably today wasn't able to lift
your mood at least not in the
beginning I'm sorry your sweetness
kindness cuteness and your humor but
also your groundedness helpfulness and
hard work make sure that you're the
highlight of each day for me wow thank
you just the way you are makes you the
best or I could ask for you're the best
no you and there's the personal feel too
you make us feel like each of us matter
at least I do you
do it is obvious that you care about
every single one of us despite your own
problems you try to help us whenever you
can you
sweetheart I
try I do care I do care as I was like
talking about it today I also care about
the non kfp is like you know when you
know I want I want all the Phantoms to
be happy I don't want to see them
suffer I don't want to see them suffer
it brings my
heart even even about us lurkers of
course of course especially kfp lurkers
you know this makes you both so strong
and good uh a height of gold is what you
have very caring and during that all
makes you my tan oi I can't oi anyone
else cuz there's no one like you love
you so much wa thank you tan she very
welcome not a must but very
welcome thank you so much for being you
thank you for being the son of my world
thank you for allowing me to rely on you
thank you for being there for me could
you please sing for the
fast what what do you mean for the fast
you just mean happy birthday uh to you
you just want me to sing Happy Birthday
or something specific I don't is there
the
song yeah happy birthday of
course and I'll I'll uh even look up my
birthday song Here is it in here
[Music]
birthdays there it
is birthday
happy
birthday space
waterfall are you
listening happy birthday to you
[Music]
m in the
H happy birthday to
[Music]
you you are now
FY and and um and I don't know I can't
speak of word ah you're thank you so
much for all your support let's go happy
birthday to you happy birthday happy
birthday SP waterfall happy birthday to
you you are now on Dem
man and you are the
man over 30 is nice yo enjoy the rest of
your life hey happy birthday to you
happy birthday happy birthday in your
shoe happy birthday happy birthday in
your pants to happy birthday to you hey
we'll end it
there yipp
[Music]
congratulations
ypp what why are you
confused what's there to be confused
[Music]
about could you please sing for the fast
as so fast fast I thought you meant fast
like I was like what does that mean why
are you Speedy
so what oh fast as in
German but that's because you switch
between English and German and I don't
know where exactly you
switch assle
assho you're almost
[Music]
pry well then you can listen to the same
birthday song next year apply
perfectly congratulations and thank you
so much for the sweet words and the big
generous Super Chat mwah mwah mwah I
hope you celebrated well what did I well
I'm so stupid I was going to ask what
did I stream on your birthday uh
this
duh well that was fun because we sang so
you had a Koka party for your birthday
[Music]
yeah okay well done let's move on Golden
I thanks for your pinky I celebrated
another birthday my third birthday in
kfp a couple days ago I feel like a
really lucky chicken do you feel like a
Lucky 7 to or like a Lucky Strike
getting to see you perform during my
birthday week yeah I see how hard you're
working and I don't take that for
granted at all good luck with everything
yeah high high chance that I wouldn't
have streamed because like I was really
busy I was really busy while I was in
Japan especially during the end of it
because of my 3D recording
um yeah but oh my God I was looking at
the calendar planning out things and
then I
realized well you guys don't have the
date yet but let me just say I realized
oh my God it's so
soon yeah B and like the MV
[Music]
ah no wait I did kind of already tell
you I'm working on something I just you
know uh you already know but I just I
just like yap yap yap around it it's
giving me some concerns because
uh you know y like I lost a lot of time
with
[Music]
like fry model you know trying to make a
3D model and I lost so much time because
we switched
modelers no I'm really
[Music]
concerned no rush really no there's rush
because I'm I literally said something
time sensitive in the
recording so well we'll see hopefully it
will all work out Kano is pretty fast I
don't know if he can work with
placeholders but um that's the worst
case situation I don't think he really
started working on it
yet um but
[Music]
yeah I think in the end I'll work out
all works out
hopefully let's go thank you golden II
for the support and happy happy happy
happy
birthday your third one let's go golden
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your shoe happy birthday in your pants
too happy birthday to you you're welcome
D thank you to you thank you for still
being part of kfp and always celebrating
here like as if we're some kind of
McDonald's but we are a
kfp we do birthday parties too I
[Music]
guess golden uh Prince of Denmark thanks
for the red super chat oh I feel like I
haven't seen your super chat in a while
did I what another what's going on
another birthday Super Chat august 19
was my birthday oh and it was also the
day I received earned my two-year
membership bed I have nothing special to
ask for except that I hope to be able to
send another message at this time next
year I hope so too I think you will I
think think you will uh I think
yeah thank you so much oh my God bre
Super Chat yay your two year in the
membership badge I just added the fourth
year membership badge and the fifth year
membership badge um but it seems like a
few more days because membership didn't
start immediately with the beginning of
the channel so a few more days and we'll
see some golden
chickens not RGB we're going RGB for the
next year
M let's go yeah you're going to be shiny
golden crispy not crispy you'll look
like a
[Music]
statue you sad you lose your armor no it
will be refreshing it's really like
tight and heavy it would be so nice to
Let It
Go Ching of Liberty yeah thanks for the
memberships thank you so much
I don't want to be naked guys that's
your natural form chickens remember
you're not usually wearing cloes you
should feel like that's normal to
you yeah you'll be made out of gold
that's
amazing and don't worry when there's
armor necessary necessary you'll still
put on some armor if we go to
war but you'll be more powerful just by
being gold you'll be more strong and
[Music]
magical birthday suit
yeah would we be naked if we were
plucked yeah if you had no feathers
that's when I would consider you naked
don't say you're naked now cuz my cats
will feel embarrassed too they'll
realize oh that means we're naked
too but you're
not oh thank you so much Prince of
Denmark happy birthday to you happy
birthday in your shoe happy birthday in
your pants
too happy birthday to
you thank you you know somehow I feel so
refreshed after crying so much
today somehow I guess that was good I
feel really
refreshed I mean I'm still sad about it
very sad but it it it was it was nice to
let it out
once and like finally being able to talk
about it because like I couldn't explain
a lot of my actions and
feelings that I had uh the past months
right it's always nice when finally
something comes out that I haven't been
able to talk to you about cuz I always
share like
everything now you know so now I can
talk about it
yeah that's also I mean it's not like I
I was hinting at it I really felt like
the anniversary like my
anniversary um felt different this time
uh and I wasn't hinting at the
graduation and it wasn't also I also
don't think it was particular
necessarily because of the graduation
that I felt that way but I think it
played a part in why I felt like you
know the way I did what I I said like
hey uh anniversary this time doesn't
feel like my anniversary it feels like
our anniversary it always is our
anniversary but in the past I would
always like say oh it's my anniversary
but now I just feel like oh it's myth's
anniversary it's our accomplishments and
you
[Music]
know yeah yeah yeah
yeah well it will Happ have been the
last
anniversary with the five of us so at
least with all five as official
[Music]
members so that was special so you have
to cherish it
[Music]
no don't cry now no we've cried enough
my eyes are tired from
crying don't cry don't
cry don't
[Music]
cry a you're making me think again
[\h__\h] h
[Music]
H nah go away go away don't let's have
thought of trains not thought of
pains stop
[Music]
no thanks for the red chat let's go k
King glad to see you making friends new
friends than you yeah new friends I hear
mint is not a scary
ghost no she is
terrifying it's good to see you after
all your hard work and preparations for
the upcoming concert I hope you're
staying healthy and things are going
well for you enjoy time with friends
thank you I wish I had more time with
friends there was also more like off
collabs that I wanted to do but just no
time and more people I wanted to meet or
visit but no time like way way less time
than I expected expected to have
H and I think my next trip will also be
pretty darn
busy
[Music]
no well that'll be in my next Tri will
be in
November I'm just enjoying the time as
much as I can here in Austria not
traveling thank you oh my God never
right thank
you surely not as busy as a chaotic
summer yeah that should
be hopefully
[Music]
true I'm planning to come to see you at
jakat a that's
go I'm
excited there's going to be so many of
our uh World Tour concerts now in the
winter so but don't worry I I don't
think it will like have a big effect on
how much I stream uh don't worry about
it but I'm excited I'm freaking excited
woohoo
woohoo World Tour going
hard right World t
I wish we could go like everywhere and I
wish we could stream it so you guys can
watch yeah but you know they need some
kind of
exclusivity so that it makes sense for
people to go I mean I feel like they
will always fill up the venue even if it
was streamed right actually they could
just make more money but you know I
think it's also Logistics like setting
up a streaming thing it's not that easy
because you have to charge
people so you need need a payment system
and you you need a contract with one of
those streaming websites and ple blah
blue it's just uh not that simple to set
it
up and it depends on the venue really
like the convention if they feel like
they can handle that if they want to do
that thank you for the memberships o a
thank
[Music]
you um yeah uh where was I oh yeah so
much than you soon I hope I hope I hope
I can meet more friends again um I'm sad
I missed out on meeting matara again
because we were on a meet and I was
really trying kind of make it work but
yeah she came kind of
late uh to Japan little while after mint
after I already met mint and then those
last days I was really busy and also
burnt out as
[\h__\h] Samuel py the Jolly Ram Rancher D
Na and cotton thanks for the red of chat
T you look out there's a scary ghost
behind you quick get the vum C
I I uh this isn't what got me the idea I
had it like before the stream started uh
but thank you I did end up getting the
vacuum she didn't know either I just
told her like oh I have a funny idea for
the end and she's like oh what is it I'm
like I'm not going to tell you I'm not
going to tell you it will be a surprise
and she was like oh I wonder what it
is
ha surprise surprise thank you Nathan
mAh
I
[Music]
am for the pink Super Chat they love us
oh we do we do we love all of you thank
you for the support I Ami
mama I Ami mama I think always watches
mint's
streams
mint say her name say her
name she's so sweet they're so lovey doy
those two they're so TI
nice to
see Miss for the red super CH thank you
for the for thank you too for the K you
both are the best B you miss
this it's nice to see you Fri m
f glad you had
fun it was inevitable for you to have
fun K
stamp strike D cat fluffy Hoots d Sean
Reed D or red action you're welcome was
it a EU friendly stream really was
it oh yeah it's backwards so it was like
well friendly well yeah it was during
the daytime I guess dead Bob five thanks
for the pinky as a long time kfp every
interaction you two ever had especially
your collapse what mean has made me
smile deep down to my soul much love to
you both now and forever more and not
that you've known each other for years
obviously this is all theoretical yeah
I mean uh perhaps I knew
her um before but uh just you know the
first time we streamed
together yeah it
is but it doesn't mean that I didn't
know her from
before many many years
ago didn't she say on
stream that I'm her
ory didn't mate mint say that
I think she said
that before she went on a
break so I was already aware of
[Music]
her I'm pretty sure she said that or at
least she thought so at least it wasn't
in her brain at least she was thinking
it no I think she also s said it
[Music]
um she was in the hot to chat what you
remember that what a bunch of you guys
remember that what the hell
what how do you remember that sound like
she was
moded sound like she was
mod Murphy rainy Ro your name always
makes me want to watch Vikings too bad
I'm already done with it thank you for
the red super chat I'm so happy to
finally see a phoenix and a ghost
collabing I'll be powering up listening
to the two of you on my way to work
Nashi waa and Maid men forever isn't
that a cute
nickname it just wouldn't have looked as
aesthetically pleasing if I put have if
I would have put the takiar right anyway
thank you so much
roov so what you're also uh a made me
fan is that what you're
saying are you just happy for me being
tay with any of my friends H thank you
so much
[Music]
Mah Paul Paul Paul bunan thank you danan
your platonic love for us oo Dixon Lee
danan De thank you for the red of chat o
a new name but wait I see your name for
the first time but you are wearing
armor interesting what has motivated you
to send a super chat for the first time
seemingly wow thank you finally
me thank you thank you
too A
lurker thank you for saying hi and uh
donating so generously thank you you
don't seem to be in the chat now huh I'm
looking out for you feel free to like
UNL yourself in the chat every now and
then H I'd like to see you
thank you thank you Dex Nathan cotton
thanks for the red super chat listen
it's not my fault I unsubed and resub
for your first
re what did I ask you guys to do that
because I was my probably was like
Please Subscribe I'm new
[Music]
here it's actually surprising that my
account was like deactivated but it's
still at least thank God it counts all
the
subscriptions since before for that it
doesn't like reset it there thank
[Music]
god well well don't worry about it naan
thanks for the red super chat uh what
another one oh my God Tak Shar thanks
for the direct implication of one minut
phomi we now have enough evidence to
bring you in
me or her
you're now officially under arrest for
being too cute and refusing to
acknowledge it consistently take her
down boys wait which
one mayry both of us wait who are you
arresting I think you mean mint right
because you're saying thanks thanks to
the direct implication of
mint you probably mean mint but I think
we're both
guilty arrest me too arrest me too
Nathan oh you weren't always the cute
police your title announ is cute police
that's
new interesting new job huh then arrest
me too I want to be
arrested fluffy Hoots D jod Ian D J Ian
D ghost stalker d Honolulu D Sage gar
dun uh
MSN dun I am my team H don't have a beep
do
I
oh well I'll just say I AI
thank
um I want to replace some of these I
want the w w w
and I don't know something iconic we had
[Music]
before my R oh yeah
BS I don't have boms right
now a tur the third or turn one to three
tur three D thank you for the pinkies
sorry for kept you waiting bus but your
army is
here but what did I need it for I don't
you weren't called but you're always
welcome to just chill
around thank you so much what accidental
free kiss so it's just a pinky but hey
discount dead Bob five Dan destroyer of
humans than what's an Oshi jump It's
when okay when your Oshi is in a idle
group or so and your Oshi has a solo
line uh you know whenever you oi sing
solo you jump like
uh let's say let's say I'm singing in a
rhythm of I am singing like this and
you're jumping like
this hey like you you try to jump as
high as you can to stand out so that the
that your oh she sees you but it's like
kind of bothersome to the people around
you so in a lot of venues or so it's
like um
banned even if it's banned some people
still do it um like I feel like as long
as it's not like overdone as long as
it's just like one crazy person jumping
here and
there um then it's not too bothering so
it can be forgiven
[Music]
H but I don't know it's probably not a
good idea to bring that into like let's
not even get it started because like you
know they're already like trying to get
rid of it in Japan so let's not get it
started we already brought a lot of like
Japanese idol culture uh into the
Western World now yeah deure and mindful
jumping I cannot tell you how much I
overused that word those words in uh
Italy
me and Nissa like it was mostly me I
think initiating it because it was so
stuck in my brain we overused it so much
and I'm always like oh my God so demure
and then the is like so
[Music]
mindful no why why would we go back to
skibidi isn't this better than
skibby but I I used it so much on uh
that trip that somehow I guess I'm fine
now and there's nothing triggering it
right
now thank God y'all are so white well
yeah
[Music]
surprise here we go where were we dad
no that's not what were
uh ah here f d jdn d ghost stalker d the
gim D de five D mental JY d y FL thanks
for the red chat she is evil I agree
100% thank you for warning me don't
worry I had it under
control arm D Honolulu D destroy of
humans D go
Happ
material super luminal fluffy Hood wrong
rabbit H Sky strike warlock
dcii
[Music]
freak SW F from the
pinky the pinky not the binky last song
hype shange of fire five
wiper thanks for the and MTO makes my
whispy me heart happy
yay a that's sweet I'm glad I'm glad we
can combine worlds of
fans yeah have them
intertwine twist play some twister my
little
wisps and Cave peas
[Music]
spicy thank you so much step sing
St vuli dun AK sf2 dun strike wock
dun and then you declared to Hunter
thanks to Luigi no I was even I was
going to hunt her even without Luigi I'm
pretty
sure but all I want to hunt now is Luigi
like get rid of him
forever U speaking of did you see that
Mario and Luigi game I was wondering I
couldn't find any info in it but I was
wondering if that's uh online co-op or
if it's only couch Co-op or if it's not
Co-op at
all you like it my Oshi is hating on the
on the Arts stunnel but I think it's
fine it's it's different but fun it's
single player oh man okay whatever I'm
going to not play it then not playing
it not going to play it mm- it's like
pretty much like the battle system looks
like that other game
recently which is fine you know but I I
don't know I'm not
interested RPG game when not playing RPG
you know I prefer
jrpgs like the cute
ones the
girls I still need to play the DLC for
Tales of arise by the way one of these
days yeah to you it's a JPG when I think
of jrpgs I think of cute anime wuss
[Music]
yeah but I got to play the
arise you know got to play the DLC at
some point but that that will probably
take maximum two streams I would
[Music]
assume and yeah for now we're waiting
for um the new Zelda game I wonder how
long it will occupy My Stream
time um but uh
[Music]
H
uh
Echo release date it was 26
H I
mean yeah know I think I can start on
the
26th yeah should be fine
[Music]
what else is coming that I'm waiting
for visions of Mana I'm
interested
yeah but I don't know it seems like a
long game
[Music]
and I don't know if it's a you know you
know jeopardies are usually not good
streaming games I'm trying to be a
little bit more picky
nowadays we still have Fallout New Vegas
yeah duck detective my duck detective
perms didn't go through they ignored my
email for too long and I'm still waiting
for No Rest For The Wicked I thought
that would go through faster because of
aie but I realized it's just the same
developer not the same publisher so
they're also ignoring my
email that's also been like in the in
their email folder for a long time now
and I'm not getting anything back oh wow
wow Zippity
zap pretty sure someone else played dark
detective already are you
sure let me see if I type in h
alive duck
detective no I can't see
anything it's just a lot of subu
Clips I just see a lot of subu Clips I
don't think
there's anyone who played
[Music]
it but
uh at least I got I got perms for Plucky
Squire which was easy because devolver
digital is
nice so I might play Plucky Squire maybe
after
Zelda if there's nothing else to play
pretty good
game
[Music]
H really
creative yeah the vola digital Is goated
For Real they're so good they're so nice
any interest in asot I know asot is
really uh a good
game um but not exactly my favorite
genre but I know it's really good
because my OSI my my YouTuber OSI likes
it love it yeah and Sony okay you guys
are pointing it out I didn't even think
about that but yeah I guess Sony would
be an
issue I wouldn't get the references he
didn't get them either really mostly but
because he's more of a Nintendo guy but
he still had a lot of
[Music]
fun he was like oh this could be Super
Mario
Odyssey if they tried harder or if they
put out a new Super Mario
Odyssey did you see a new Yakuza
revealed
today no my mind was somewhere else
today there's a new Yakuza revealed like
a completely new
one what do I have to look
up Yakuza
maima Pirate game what pirate M what
where is this in the timeline Yakuza
pirate
What pirate Yakuza in
Hawaii
what this is like kind of different it's
like a spin-off
huh after eight but okay I don't really
know is that before the games I played I
guess like in between
somewhere wait the trailer is seven
minutes I'm going to watch this later oh
wait graphic wise wait ah I guess they
just reused the Hawaii world because we
already were in Hawaii it looks like
they're reusing it
[Music]
huh eight
was you
played I'm getting
hungry they actually mentioned the
events of Hawai in the
trailer it takes place after oh I played
infinite 12 and it plate is
after oh where the [\h__\h] is he a
pirate oh shut up I wonder how long it
is not as long as the main game I would
assume when is this coming out February
28th okay that's quite a while
still I think we'll play
[Music]
it h that's
fun uh where was I where was
I strike Wallock Danon Psy Danon ashes
Danon kuu CER thank you for the pinky
from Australia sending some love Wawa's
way before breaking Dimensions not only
did I get to see you hang out with your
cute ghost friend but you're going to be
in another Ian concert yeah of course I
hope you have an awesome time and I
can't wait to see if
congrats thank
you a thank you for the you know early
support message way before the concert
thank you so much that's so
sweet I appreciate it I hope you enjoyed
the concert to its fullest even if you
you know watched it in Australia from
home maybe one day you can be there in
person maybe next time strike warlock d
ghost stalker d thank you so
[Music]
much
oh what do you mean you what only going
to braking Dimensions day to because I'm
working crew on Saturday you
mean at the convention right until 10:
p.m. at Main stage but I might be one of
the crew letting you guys into sore or F
meal or face featuring M come say hi if
you see
me wait you're you're saying come say hi
if you see me to the others right you're
not saying that to me right you're
saying it to the people watching cuz I'm
not I don't
[Music]
even you mean anim
NC he hardworking aren't
you window shut the [\h__\h] up here zip it
zip
it what's wrong with it I'm probably
getting I'll have to check it out um a
lot of you guys were like oh your GPU
might be fried what do you think if it
was fried would I be able to play the
game or do anything at
[Music]
all no my is fine okay okay but that
picture was amazing wasn't
it very freaky how bad or loose I don't
know which one it would be like it's
kind of
ridiculous
H or could it be something inside the
case that's
like I don't know it's so annoying like
why is there always something wrong
and I was thinking though just like
resetting the whole PC would be good
once but then I have to back up
everything that's annoying
that's something I want to
[Music]
do happens when you move backwards no
like yesterday it was happening without
me touching or moving anything even I
was like literally nothing was moving
and it would still do it
constantly today it's a bit more like I
like yeah I smack the table and
something reacts
[Music]
or I move a little bit around but I'm
not sure like what why why would what
what would it
be
haunted imagine all the cat hair inside
it not actually honestly like last time
that RBF checked my
PC uh we were both surprised about how
little cat hair was inside and that was
like my first time cleaning it after a
year or
so
H it's surprising how little hair is in
there like
[Music]
inside or like on the on
the wherever um
yeah but yeah I could probably use a
little bit of
cleaning I do think it has good
ventilation or just like somehow there's
hair everywhere in my house but just
doesn't make it to my PC for some
[Music]
reason no it's really surprising how
little it
[Music]
is did you change the temp I didn't do
anything I did that marel I did that
already
[Music]
yeah it's okay I might have uh like I I
was talking to RBF and we were saying
like if it's urgent If Today doesn't
work out then he'll come over on Sunday
but if things work out and it looks fine
then he'll just come over sometime next
week whenever there's some time
[Music]
yeah well both tomorrow and the day
after tomorrow are not gaming
streams so less things less chance of
things going wrong I
[Music]
guess by the way I might I was thinking
like because I can only announce it so
late I was speaking um no need to really
ask you guys for questions I can
probably think of enough on my own um
but I mean there's still enough time I
really haven't prepared anything so I'm
probably going to ask for questions
anyway tomorrow I'm going to I haven't
really prepared anything I'm going to
make the thumbnail tomorrow and then
post it and then uh you guys can the
teammates especially can ask whatever
they want to
ask I you know cuz it's a it's the
second I think the second H talk where
or is it or is it the first where we are
aware no it's it's the second yeah cuz I
think the first one was Coco Senai where
we are aware of the person
leaving so you know we can use that to
our Advantage and
ask questions that make
sense uh with that in mind
[Music]
M talking a lot about accomplishments
basically do you need clips of funny
moments um so I was like I kind of
wanted your opinion too on this but I
guess you guys don't really care uh I
wasn't sure if I should translate to
Japanese
um for now I'm thinking I'm just not
going to I'm just going to talk in
English
only I think
how
cuz I don't
[Music]
know would it be too much to add Subs
later to the V
[Music]
yeah
yeah I could ask I could pay someone to
do it within the company I wonder how
much they charge like if it's a 2hour VA
honestly that might be a
[Music]
lot might be good to ask cover staff to
trans no the staff wouldn't do that but
maybe a volunteer in the chat will
[Music]
translate but then I was thinking if I'm
not translating then I will just use
like um
like clips from fans I'm I'm having one
custom
made uh but besides that I'm just going
to use clips from fans you know our
favorite uh am clipping channel that
also Clips Wawa whenever she mentions
uh well hopefully don't
mind
mhm
Kazuki you don't mind do
you cuz he has so many good
Clips but there so many so maybe if you
have some
recommendations of best am
Clips let me
[Music]
know okay let's finish the super chats I
have to cook after this yesterday I made
corn cobs and just Grill
sausages I was like what goes with corn
cops
M I'm just going to buy Grill
sausages it's like specific ones though
it's like uh sausages that are wrapped
in bacon one layer of bacon and then
inside is
cheese like a little bit of cheese not
too much I don't like it when they're
filled with too much
cheese now I could eat the same thing
today because I still have corn crops
and sausages or I cook something from
Hell
fresh did C make a minecra no I don't
think he
did I have
Bal what what happened with the one
block compilation c car what
[Music]
happened I was so happy when cie never
mind never mind never mind
just remembered something that wasn't on
stream but you will hear it
eventually
what yeah no C is a bit busy now
uh with doing a requested clip for me
and honestly like I'm I was so I asked
cow Carro a little bit and advance for a
clip you know I I told Cal hey you know
um cuz I've been saying that I would be
doing this for a while now that I would
be doing Ian holot talks at some point
anyway it was a long time coming so cow
car did not expect anything when I just
said you know I'm doing I'm doing whole
talk yeah uh I'm starting Ian H do so
can you help me with a clip I was like
okay but then then came the realization
I feel so bad cuz cow carat is I think
am my toy fan
like am was I think Ker's first oosi
first
oi
yeah I'm so sorry for putting you
through this and now I'm forcing you to
clip something so
painful I'm
sorry I'm
sorry I hope it doesn't hurt too much oh
my God I feel so bad oh I'm sorry oh man
oh man that's so sad the more I think
about
it comat the coner send him some
emotional support he's forced to clip
something of
am for
[Music]
me oh yeah is pudding
here pudding didn't know I didn't tell
pudding that I'm going to need a new
opening uh you know with
for whole talk cuz pudding was making
the openings and the usually I tell
pudding a little bit earlier cuz I
usually announce it like at the start of
the
week um pudding doesn't seem to be here
huh sorry
sorry you'll have to do some work for me
putting he doesn't know
yet will get ID talk to at some point
yeah of
course of course
Theo I mean I at least want to do the
first gen for sure 100% and then uh
we'll see I want to do myth 100% And
first ID gen
100% and maybe still go back and forth
to Japanese members
what about Ana no I hate
Anna sorry I got distracted again
um where was I here you know
murer random collusion thanks for the
red of chat thank you for connecting us
across the world kiar we got your back
always oh oh thank you that's so sweet I
guess I was talking about something
wholesome there about the concert huh
thank you so much mAh
I appreciate it very nice of you thank
you for having my back can you massage
it
though Hulu flaming pants D strike
warlock
dy I love your name thanks for the r
chat thank you both for the stream
please make sure that mint is properly
contained boss yep sorry she actually
escaped like immediately after I
captured her in the vacuum there was a
hole in my
vacuum it's like when you vac is spider
and it's just don't do it because it
won't stay inside I guess I hear so at
least I hear
[Music]
it thank you
vog py d g d d the g d and c
[Music]
d oh my
God after talk making Dimensions is a
lot Let's do let's do like a small one
let's do blue protocol
oopsie a
[\h__\h] let's do blue protocol for
[Music]
now oh man
rip rip blue
protocol h job7 Hello red than FR thanks
for the red super
chat oh oh that was a one year
anniversary to POV nice for says I miss
you times 10 kiaa thank you for all your
hard work thank you for an amazing Holan
concert and thank you for being our
amazing Phoenix KP appreciates you and
loves you ra hope you'll enjoy the last
breaths of
BP what do you mean last breaths huh I'm
sad W love thank
you a hope you enjoyed watching it from
home
oh look protocol I thought you meant
breaking P manions I guess is no
breaking
pensions a ping what's up yeah sorry I
announced within the stream at the
beginning of the stream because of um a
leaving I'm doing a Holo talk this
Sunday
night
uh so yeah I'm going to send you
the footage
tomorrow you're
[Music]
school I I'm sorry do you have time okay
okay okay I still don't know what to do
tomorrow by the way I don't know I
[Music]
just I still don't know what to
do no I mean
because tomorrow guys what are you what
are you saying slay Spire we have we
have the 2.0
reveal uh do another red
huh I don't know that's kind
of making it way bigger than it is
so but
interesting anyway I'm wait wait wait I
I I got
distracted but send me ideas in the KF
beh hash if you have any like gimmick
[Music]
ideas rare chance with r that's
true but like I don't
know I'll think about it though that's
one of the
options the singing September Durance
yeah I had that too and I would
unarchive it though I but some people
were like I think not happy with that
idea even doll I can read broadcast rebr
rebroadcast
it I can rebroadcast it plastic
searches
interesting
interesting but that might get some
people offended I don't know anyway FR
send me send me ideas at the kfb hashtag
uh fro uh thank you so much I'm back to
EU times baby let's go and I was in
Italia again don't you feel like I'm
like doing fan service just for
you I love you thanks for the red CH as
well hi hi to you too thank you for
saying hi so polite so very demure very
mindful you're in ity too right now
oh it was so cold when I was
there it was just like on one day it was
warm a little bit for a few hours
but just because we were standing in the
sun waiting in line for a
museum besides that it was really
[Music]
cold people still say that I still say
that therefore people still say that
you're liking Museum now generally yeah
like I mean I like
museums that are showcasing like
architecture uh like you know those kind
of basically like like the Doge Palace
that I went to the whole Palace was the
museum you know what I
mean rather than having a like
modern building where it just
showcases uh like statues and
paintings yeah just when the whole place
is a museum that's what I like cuz then
you look at the like ceiling and the
walls and everything and you know it
still comes with paintings that are also
really interesting those paintings are
sick man holy
[\h__\h] that's some Next Level paintings
there
bro so [\h__\h]
impressive really beautiful and it's
usually medieval stuff and I'm really
interested in that
[Music]
H you guys are starting to bring out
those pen lights immediately
[Music]
uh 41
guy C General
froggy
pixels thanks for piing it the reason
they decided to stop blue protocol is
that they decided orange blol would be a
better title
agreed ah but just for renaming it you
didn't have to shut down everything blue
protocol come
on Bruce
[Music]
Bru ma Tommy
H
[Music]
how
uh come
who is that
correct
come Jackson Jackson f d ghost be
d uh spanking hi thanks for the red
super chat I have been summoned have
you I don't recall what I said but I
guess you're always summoned you're as a
kfp you're summoned since the beginning
of every stream until the end of every
stream easy simple as that
spank
spanking come I don't know if it's
correct how I say your name I hope it's
okay h d z d Cruz D and py
[Music]
D okay okay okay
okay so okay one more thing I will
finish the polar Awards I think tomorrow
I started a bit more today
but didn't have enough time but tomorrow
I think I can finish them I don't really
I don't think I have much to do I want
to probably go out and
buy something for a birthday
gift uh for a friend just a
packaging but besides that just
preparing the 2.0 stream which isn't
really much gift from M I have a couple
of gifts from mad but no this is
different birthday
gift yeah cuz to on Sunday I'm going to
a birthday
party
um it's like kind of overlapping with
Hol talk that's
the difficult
thing yeah I'm going before whole talk
and who knows they're like Oh no you're
going to leave early no you can't leave
early cuz people my friends they just
there they they act like as if if I'm
not
[Music]
there the party just doesn't happen it's
not even my party and there are plenty
of other friends of the birthday
girl but they they act like I'm like
some kind of celebrity or
so they act like yeah I'm the life of
the
party they're like oh my God the party
is ruined because uh wow is leaving
early like what do you mean I'm staying
for like 3 hours or 4 hours maximum
that's
plenty they're like no this sucks oh my
God we should change the date I'm like
what the
hell there's like 20 people going to
this
party don't make such a big deal out of
it so now I'm being pressured into
going back after whole
talk even though it would be so late
like what are you talking about they're
like oh if she comes back then that will
be fine I'm
like
[Music]
H crazy people I'll consider it what
about chat with I'm after right well I
was thinking so too like I don't want to
stress myself so I said well no
guarantee like you
know I think holot talk will not be
longer than 2 hours especially without
translating probably more like 1.5 hours
or so without translating honestly I
don't know it might be just you know
pretty short
um honestly maybe I should translate but
just like a little bit more roughly than
what I usually like when I translate
from Japanese to English I try to catch
every
detail but maybe I'll just do a little
bit more of a rough vague translation
this
[Music]
time so that it goes a bit quicker and
it's not too
[Music]
disrupting you know
or I was just thinking like usually when
I
[Music]
translate hi
smoothie
hi she's such a
baby she's so
[Music]
soft so sweet
yeah
um I'm still thinking about it I could
possibly I'm thinking
maybe it's not too much to
[Music]
ask I have this idea not sure if I'm
going to do it but so let's say we bring
jenma into the call she's listening to
it live with no stream delay
and while I I will have this the
questions up in Japanese this time on
the screen cuz usually it's up in
English right and I say it out loud in
Japanese now it's it'll be the other way
around so that doesn't need translation
but like she'll listen to what AM says
and just write a like a a rough
translation up in
text and I'll just always put the text
on the screen
like live translation but on my screen
by a
[Music]
human H I think we could do
that I think she would be capable of
that but I wonder if njama might be too
busy for it maybe I got to ask PMA you
think PMA can do it I'm not too sure
about PMA if PMA can do
it if she would be so good at live
translating I'll ask what HMA thinks
about
it or maybe
HMA HMA could be good at it
too and you know
HMA oh you know
what I don't think HMA said this who
knows I don't know there's a chance HMA
didn't say this to am directly
but um I was uh I was talking
I think it was in New
York um there was this one night uh
where I had dinner cuz like everybody
else was
gone amen was also gone at this point so
it was just like me and some
managers was uh jenma HMA and another uh
like like staff like event staff
and and I was like you know cuz hma's
I'm a manager I was like how are you
feeling are you
okay and and HMA said something
like yeah I'm I'm I'm pretty sad because
you
know am always gave me like
motivation and inspired
me to work hard and like you know
something like that and said that you
know he really enjoyed so much working
with
her H Mama H Mama teammate what a
teammate he so
sweet I'm is the son of all of us yeah
and I thought it was so sweet because
like on if your if your talent is am of
course she gives you all this like Drive
I I think that's what Hemma said too
like she gives me like this
drive HMA was very involved in a lot of
am projects right helping a
lot and handling a lot
[Music]
so
yeah imagine seeing I'm and myth doing
things by themselves and then joining to
help
[Music]
them thank you
HMA HMA is also I think one of the
OG's when it comes to
management or at least almost
OG I think pretty much OG so there was
um uh what what did cie call her manager
again my mind is blank right
now uh J Chad yeah J Chad jenma and I
think kenma was also yeah yeah yeah
yeah and now we have like way
more oh enma forgot about
enma wait if enma was there maybe enma
wasn't h no no HMA might have not been
there from the very beginning because I
think anma was
um
uh
managing Ina GA
no what what no jenma was managing no oh
yeah at the beginning maybe HMA was
already around but not quite assigned
manager yet because in the beginning it
was two
managers oh no free
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah anma was
managing Ena jhat was managing me and CI
but I quickly switched to jenma soon
after and then JMA was managing guda and
Amit and partially
Ena and then yeah I switched to Jemma
andma eventually also like became less
of a manager and then JMA was handling
inaura and me and J chat was just the
Cali
yeah mhm and then HMA I guess came
in you know we started like slowly
getting more managers and HMA took over
am yeah and then jenma had only three at
[Music]
least yeah that was more
that constellation until we had a new
generation
[Music]
added
yeah crack Knuckles yeah cracked my
Knuckles is there enough managers for
all the talents now well right now I
think more or less yeah I mean you know
could always be more
[Music]
Justice only has one manager that's not
really
true but there's like as far as I know
they're still being like first taken
over by the experience managers and
after a while they're being uh handed
over to newer
managers I don't know if that already
happened it's not secret people talked
about this stuff
[Music]
before let them be pampered by veteran
after they can kind of manage themselves
manage becomes support no no no no no no
no I wouldn't say
so like they don't honestly they don't
really change in how much
they do for us over the
time but yeah I think we're good someone
recognize your care hoodie for the first
time today and said they all friend oh
my god let's
go
[Music]
yay I'm going to leave you
guys I'm going to leave you guys uh for
today I'll see you tomorrow for the 2.0
reveal if you have any ideas so please
help me out on G uh the kfp
hashtag and uh
yeah um sorry for being very emotional
but you know I think it's
understandable make sure to watch Amy
streams I think am is starting a stream
in one and a half
hours isn't she I think a talking
stream mhm so go watch her please if
you're still awake watch
Amy watch Amy
don't leave any regrets you
[Music]
know
yeah RoR I don't know if there's much of
a point if it's in 1.2 uh 1.5 hours but
you know what's up you know that it's
happening
yeah I
love man it feels so unreal
again ah [\h__\h] well maybe it's good if
it's unreal right now now I can continue
to cope and stay in my bubble pretend
like nothing's
[Music]
happening
yeah join my
[Music]
bubble ah before you EX
a ah cow carrot I'm
sorry I'm
[Music]
sorry okay let's sleep in this bubble
goodbye guys I'm going to go cook
something hate
cooking and en German we say do thanks
for
watching no don't go don't worry I'll be
back tomorrow
[Music]
n