[Music]
are we back
[Applause]
give me
one moment
[Music]
thank you
stretch into the void
[Music]
uh
hmm
[Music]
welcome back
okay
um
oh thank you thank you
thank you guys
and
we are el
we just ended
uh a two
and a half hour
long
that was unarchived so hello vodka
watches you are now watching the
archived part and here on the left side
you see what you actually missed
21 songs
which were all quite a lot of fun to
sing
you missed that but maybe you can find a
clip or two of it if you're lucky
give it a try
so we're now at
101 million two hundred forty seven
thousand seven hundred forty eight and
we started out with like five thousand
left to uh one point two five
and now we have
about uh two thousand
left did i do math correct
did i do it did i do it did i do it did
i do it please tell me i did it
i'm impressed
you know ever since i left school i
haven't really been actively
needing to do any math anymore so
uh yeah
i wouldn't be surprised if i wouldn't
have been able to do that
[Music]
okay
hold
we're still going
and uh
we will maybe i should make this a
smaller
smaller and then
we do a cut off because i want them to
still see this so i'll cut off
and continue here
okay
going where we're going to the milestone
yeah
no
no please don't unsubscribe that's
bullying
please do not do that
i would uh suffer
a vampire oh i was thinking perhaps we
can sing that but i mean if you want to
hear me saying vampire why not just go
to my channel and stream it
no
specific need for me to sing it we'll
see if we run out of songs then i might
sing it at the end
but i do have some
good songs prepared well let's start out
with something that you guys don't know
some hello project idol songs if that's
okay
oh i'll write it in romaji
this is from a group called kyoto
which is a very cute group
you guessed it you guessed it
yeah i'll start out when since people
are still coming back in i'll start out
with some rather unknown songs and then
later we'll get some songs that you guys
know
okay
i still have the
uh cough drop another a new one
in my mouth but this should be fine i
think this song will be fine thai job
let's go
oh wait
let's
go
[Music]
oh
kiss me
[Applause]
m
[Music]
[Applause]
please stay
please please please
[Music]
[Applause]
please please
[Music]
i
okay
[Music]
is
or a 20-second song
[Laughter]
yeah that was a
hello practice song from cute a group
called cute cult uh kiss me i statue is
a
i think one more
hello project on
and then we go
to the other stuff
almost there
hopefully
the next one is
i mean i don't know it from the anime
and i think i've sang it before by the
way but uh it is also the opening of an
anime oh
old one the childish one uh i think it's
called inazuma 11.
did anyone watch that here i think it's
kind of like a anime for
children
mostly or like yeah
very young teenagers
shining power i don't know it because of
the anime i just gotta say that
but maybe some of you guys know it
because of that thankfully
[Music]
it's anime format okay okay if you say
something yes it is anime for a hairy
big song old man yes
it is about soccer okay
my favorite idol group which doesn't
exist anymore
r.i.p so sad
so sad
by the way i made a tea and i'm waiting
for it to be drinkable
[Music]
right water i can at least drink some
water
[Music]
okay they didn't die
[Laughter]
they are all still very much alive
the group
they're not dead
let's go
signing signing
signing baby
wow wow
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
i
is
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
oh
m
[Music]
is
yeah
this song is so funny like because i was
i told you guys before that this is um
this my favorite idol group betty's
cobble they were making all kinds of
really weird
stupid songs like they they sounded
great but they had weird themes and
they have been singing in the song
constantly about
japanese bentos
singing really dramatically about
[Music]
the bento that you made for me
is two stories hi
[Music]
but the one i made is the best panto
yeah he keeps on singing stuff like that
oh and and is also singing in the chorus
about the struggle of when you make a
bento that the stuff that you put inside
is like
continuously always goes on one side
like when you move it like i guess when
you carry it to school or work then you
open it up and then you look inside and
it's like all messed up and stuff that's
what it's singing about
i don't know it's
it sounds so badass and cool and
dramatic but then
the lyrics are about [\h__\h] mental
struggles
such poetry wow such bento
[Music]
uh
enough of i um unless we run out of
songs later for now i'll leave you alone
with these uh
these
um
um idol songs
and
we'll sing
my cross
delta
i got two songs for you i have one
elsing now
i think this one i haven't ever sang
before so
you just gotta be good
enjoy
[Music]
i do
my
[Music]
you
m
foreign
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
my
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
me
my
[Applause]
[Music]
m
me
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
oh
[Music]
or you comments are way too nice i
[\h__\h] up like a million times because i
was nervous
[Music]
don't be so nice to me i'm [\h__\h] up so
many times
you know when you practice so many songs
in one day by the way this is the update
we are over 8 000.
when you practice so many songs in one
day it all starts like
mixing up in your brain and melting
together into one jelly jelly piece of
stuff
[Laughter]
maybe if you don't know the song well
then it wasn't that noticeable but i'm
so sorry that i butchered the song oh my
god
i gotta make up for it
okay i'll sing the second um
i'll sing the second delta song right
now because i gotta make up for this
holy [\h__\h]
that was pathetic
that was pathetic you want
this one is very powerful
my current nervous self if you ruin this
i'm going to
kill you
water
thank you for stopping thank you thank
you
thank you
i appreciate it thank you for all the
support
thank you
i'm gonna sing until the milestone i
will not give up no no no no doesn't
matter if it's past midnight in a little
moment
huh
i will do this
and i have the lyrics open somewhere i
think
no
oh god no there it is
there they are
okay
me still having the tab open with um
electro shocking devices on amazon
nice
don't ask quiet if you don't know why
well
don't bet it probably better not ask why
it all occurred yesterday in my super
chat reading
okay
okay i need my cool voice for this one
[Music]
[Applause]
forever
[Music]
um
forever
[Music]
i
[Applause]
jump
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
[Applause]
god
if it's already because i sang too much
today but i feel like i'm not really
nailing this as as i want to but as long
as you guys are happy and as long as
we're having fun let's go
no but that voice is actually damn
difficult for me to sing with
holy moly
it's like
like
constantly on the edge of falling apart
and breaking
you might have heard it a couple times
though when i was like
[Laughter]
it's it will be tough
all right update here there you go
update updates cool cnc livestock
25 songs so far
wow
what well let me drink some more tea
it's getting it's it's it's reaching a
good temperature thank you
for the rest of the day i appreciate it
glad you like my cross
yeah yeah yeah i had this uh in my
memory someone was really asking a lot
for makara's songs and i think also
specifically perhaps
well cued it so there you go i love
their songs so much hmm
okay
let's uh pull out some classics
and a tada
you all know this one
at least if you're cultured if you'll
know it then you're cultured i will
officially give you the title of being
cultured
as long as i still have power
i gotta sing this now
laughing again you black me a bladden
wait
yes
[Music]
me
foreign
uh
[Music]
i
um
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
i sang that one before i wasn't really
planning on it for today i wonder that
was okay to sing
during
archive streams as far as i remember but
still for now i'm holding off on it but
you could find it in one of my previous
art class streams
franza
eh
yeah please still stay
uh
fun
where was the
instrumental for that
starting to feel really hot in this room
no i don't know where it is right now
and
[Music]
hey
oh you want to hear me for treat i was
planning on doing that today
okay go go go get wait
kind of short
kind of short but why the hell not
kiana only version
myth
or treat
because halloween on my channel is still
not over
as you can see
from my loading screen
i think it makes it pretty obvious
myth or treat
[Music]
yo oh she's waiting in a closet tonight
no way to stop she's dead set on giving
you a fright trick-or-treat but now
we're all out of candy feeling just a
little sick this chainsaw ought to come
in handy
i got a fairy chest possessed so let's
experiment a bit a little dissection is
best drop it long thing is hiding behind
your screens it ain't a spooky halloween
without some mythical beans
chad is splashing
look at those red cheeks
[Music]
how cute
i'll fix that up drain all your
love that's what
you
see
make a
[Music]
oh
well the spooky scary side hungry
dinosaur just one tiny bite please spook
a bean with a song if you're brave and
sing along not your wife i am a pumpkin
ding dong
in the graveyard we will be if you're
looking
[Music]
spooky ladies that is what we're about
this is the first time i tried singing
the other members parts
thank god it's a fairly easy song oh man
yeah it's short isn't it maybe one day
who knows maybe 2022 halloween
full version
i i think that would be freaking dope
coulda know
[Music]
i think everyone already listened to it
before
my part
is a really cool part i saw you guys
reacting in the chat
yeah extended version one day i hope so
we gotta get cali drunk again but that
shouldn't be a problem
right
right your part is divine it really is i
think that the
word divine fits it so well
yeah thank you
for that awesome part
okay okay
and
next song will be old school k on
don't say lazy
but one moment
let's admit it it's
it's a classic
but
fairly
fairly old school
don't say lazy
i think i've sang this one before in a
stream actually
i've got like a million tabs open
so confusing
yeah i'll be
i'll be
i'll be here
i'll close a couple ones
oh my body
let's hurts
don't say lazy
11 years old oh that's actually fairly
not so old huh
i thought it was even older than that
i'm gonna sing with you ah everyone
chime in you're welcome to do so
much
love is a staple is a banger i love love
is this different i love all the keon
songs
i sang that one before it's a cute song
okay
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
crazy
is
[Music]
[Applause]
da
[Music]
um
thank y'all
it's the best girl who's your best girl
guys who's your favorite k own girl
i don't know if people who get into
anime nowadays
um still watch like km because it's a
classic i would hope so
i would hope so
you must lookie
gotta love moogie
with those pickle eyebrows
actually surprisingly not many yui's
what the hell
okay
that's unacceptable
we gotta
change something about this
39 please no uh
yo he's so cute
who could dislike you everyone loves you
really cute cute cute
baby
another classic let's go
and update on the sub count oh my god
we're getting pretty close now
we're almost at 1 000 left look at that
oh thank you guys for your support thank
you for your help i really really really
really really really appreciate this and
also um i hope i can
finish this sometime
uh in the next one hour perhaps that
would be great because i actually have
something to record tomorrow something
important and i have to it's not a song
you guys will see it
next week
um
it's uh something pre-recorded and it's
taking it will take up quite a bit of
time of my tomorrow day
and uh
i hope i don't get
to go to bed too late
and video oh no no no no no no no no no
something way longer the m videos take
barely any effort
thankfully
but there is going to be an m video for
the weekend i think because i'll be gone
in a different country
[Music]
actually let me just tell you for the
past 40 minutes i've been feeling
very short on breath again so
forgive me if i'm not singing these
songs perfectly anymore
um
there's gonna be different karaoke
streams where i will
try them again
or am i in this most of these songs that
i'm going to sing in the archived one
i've sang already before anyway i mean
not most of them a lot of them perhaps
yeah yeah
[Music]
thank you
i'm glad you like them
thank you you have thanks so much
already yeah
guys so far what was your favorite out
of all of these 29 or 28 because 29
didn't happen yet which one was your
favorite so far
don't say it because that wasn't even
good
ah all of me wow a lot of all of me's
i really thank you
i sang it better in practice
just saying 99 love balloons yeah that
was fun too the feels thank you i i
freaking loved singing that i want to
sing it again if i could
all of me and me for tweet thank you
call me baby
having to know ginger thank you i guess
the girl was the best thank you in
advice thank you
glad you liked it raise your glass that
was fun too where's your class
that was quite in the beginning thank
you for being here since the beginning
thank you thank you
pay phone that was also one of the
acoustic ones
um
you did so good in all of them thank you
can i borderline i sang that one before
i'm pretty sure
uh i could uh but i already i already
sang two
uh macras
dalton songs today so i think we're good
for today
subscribe to me mamie hey i just met you
i just thought it was so funny because
of people who are subscribing probably i
really just met
okay i'll go sing the next song now
must
[Music]
[Applause]
i
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
everybody behind your screens
oh
[Music]
foreign
because of me clapping
the cat hairs have been like flying
around in the air and entering my huge
teacup oh god
let me try to get them out with a clean
finger do you have a clean finger this
one is clean come on get them out get
them out
yeah okay i got something out i think
there's some more in there
okay this this that that's the
cat here
[Laughter]
okay i think we're good
i mean who knows people say that in in
your sleep in your lifetime
you probably are swallowing
a couple of spiders
or and flies and stuff while you're
sleeping right so
me swallowing cat hairs is like
inevitable and normal
it's a myth what really oh god i'm
relieved actually
oh really
oh thank god aussies only
is it a myth everywhere except for
australia
oh
once the tea has perfect room
temperature it just cools down so
quickly i wish i could put it in a time
capsule and make it stop
oh
[Music]
stop t now
put my twice friends out there
i love that melody so much tim
[Music]
that's so good
you're thinking of a thermos kiwa
exactly but the problem with the
firmness is then then
it cools down too slow
because i can't drink it when it's too
hot so
compared to normal cup i will wait
double the time in order to drink it
but then okay it stays in the right
temperature longer but it just takes
just so much better to struggle so what
you would know what what you would have
to do to make this to to to um
perfectionalize this
is
first put it into a normal cup
wait until it bridges the right
temperature and then put it into a
firmness cup
has anyone ever done that before does
that work
[Music]
just stop the kettle part way
no but then it has to be cooking water
in order to properly you know
get the tea out of it
anyway
yes yes this is of course totally first
world problems but
yeah this is just what what i gotta talk
about when there's nothing else to talk
about
and this is what we can relate with
right because we all got those first
world problems let's be real let's be
real
wherever not you see it as a problem or
not it's a you know depends on your
point of view
hacking heck packaging heck
you guys want me to sing a
whole life song
a whole lot english song
go
i should probably get the cali song out
of my system before uh i completely
forget it now let's just let me just say
i am not 100 nailing this one yet now i
wonder should i sing it with cali
or without she sent me a backing track
that has like her backing vocals in at
least so
i shouldn't get like completely lost but
i'm probably gonna get lost for a moment
here and there
should we do a duet really
okay until i nail it one day i'll nail
it perfectly and then i'll do it alone
all right all right if you guys wanna do
it okay okay
okay okay okay
i have chosen a song which uh
has a lot of non-wrap parts that i
really like
and i like the melody of it so much
yeah
freaking amazing
let's imagine oh you know what
yeah long title what the hell what
happened
is this too long
can
the obs text thingy not take anything
longer than that no way
why did it cut off
hello
i guess i'll make a new one
why did it cut off more than that though
got it i'll make a new one
ctrl
[Music]
wait um
what about where is it where is
[Applause]
let me try to
make that look like the other one
that is a
segue black regular
and then
sorry we gotta make this perfect
set did you remember that segue
black regular is the font name
[Music]
ooh don't know why it's this font in
particular
we will never know
let's make it a bit smaller holy [\h__\h]
too big
and then
outline
select color
i got this one copy paste it
i made it a bit bigger
and there we go
and now we just add it onto there and
act like it was always supposed to be
together
it's a bit too big
okay
okay skinny
okay okay one more step for my tea
before it gets too cold
okay
lyrics ready kelly up kelly not ready
one thing i wanted to pull out well
kelly p and g
uh
kelly everyone
ask for kelly
maybe we can get get her to come here
kelly
[Music]
carla o p
yeah you were you were you you were
yelling so loudly i guess i came
you were disturbing me in my sleep
but i heard you singing my song
so i'll help you out there because
you're pretty bad at rapping you know
yeah i know thank you
let's do this together okay
yeah yeah yeah
which
is funny because there's a line that
says
which means
right now next to you is a
deaf reaper
so
we are doing it according to the song
let's go
[Music]
three two one
nobody knows
[Music]
but you don't know me take my wits right
with me but they don't want me made me
feel like gone go in the street save it
for later instead i'll make a style
retreat and hit go live real high so fly
oh my no drive this guy talk about the
misfire leave it those mixed fights
waiting for cash i'll never call up
again running this off it's a passion
it's tough i never had a life to begin
with but now i've got
[Music]
nobody realizing they don't recognize me
fine by me it's agonizing disguising
life not broadcasting only someone
laughing rather it's the matter of
writing real casting faster than your
seat belts faster we need help leaving
that pressure already
[Music]
have a great night
it's right telling horror stories goes
my kind of warfare put back the curtain
for one hell of a show deadbeat swinging
now out of control transmission life
before you i rip in real time just don't
forget it mention that soul
[Music]
hey
now what is it i'm here right here
i don't know how connection is kind of
gone
kelly
[Music]
[Laughter]
well it was fun that must have actually
been my my best take so far i think it's
because kelly was with me
[Music]
i hope you guys like that one i
practiced it uh only today
um
yes
i actually in order to practice this
properly i was like slowing down
the video thank you youtube for that
function
i was slowing it down and listening to
it in a
one one
one one thingy slower like 0.75
and then i speed it up back again to the
normal speed and then it's like pretty
pretty
decent to remember
i hope that was okay see i really like
the part that sounds so
um
japanese
uh music-y
like the part that goes
on
[Music]
oh
that gives me the chills and it also
reminds me of that one whole live uh
song um
because i feel like this is some kind of
style that japanese music uses sometimes
uh whole i've had a song that had a
similar feel to it um the one with
fubuki senpai
and mio senpai and i think i am simply
uh
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes
i feel like they had similar melodies
with that song
so it reminds me of that and i
absolutely love it
yeah
i love that song
and i also like like the dismal of you
so much as far as telling her stories
goes my kind of one from back to girl
i love that part too
this song is so good and also the music
video art by mama leone is so good too
loves seeing mamaloni art
well done bus thank you i'm glad i
didn't absolutely butcher it so then
when callie sees it if she ever sees it
she won't need to completely
kill me i mean even if she rapes me you
know you know the drill you know what
happens
nice ventral when she look at what she
was moving on her own it wasn't me
that wasn't me
or don't spread rumors here
okay okay
okay uh i have one more whole life song
but i'll keep that one maybe four uh two
songs later or something like that
one more whole live english song
prepared oh and i just refreshed ah i'm
getting so close guys
look
uh
refresh
[Music]
eight hundred eight subs left
here
yeah almost there
hmm
i honestly didn't believe we would
like a part of me thought that i i
couldn't make it today unless i go for
like 10 hours which would be impossible
um
yeah but i'm glad i was able to do it
because like ever since uh the last
milestone 1 million
it's been um
yeah milestones have been
like the the pacing changed
uh and i don't know i really enjoyed
doing things like
cut orchestrians marathons it also gives
me an opportunity to like push myself
and
and motivate you guys i think it's a
good opportunity to
um yeah
get people to know me so
hell yeah and test my limits and test my
my
uh
you know how far i can go and stuff
motivation
thank you for the memberships and thank
you for all the super chats as well guys
thank you soon i appreciate it thank you
thank you we're not done yet
we're not done rolling girl please are
you the one who tweeted that at me
i was um practicing it a little bit but
uh
i i don't know if i can do it
um
not today
not today but i have it in my karaoke
one day i will sing this list okay
it's raining on twitter you have been
training for a while thank you guys for
using twitter
and this
[Music]
i love all supercell songs and i also
love all pakimo no katari songs
i think that one that one supercell song
is being sung so often so it's been a
little bit overused so i'm gonna go with
this one
sayonara memories i have sang this one
before too but yeah
i i've nailed it a million times so
yeah we don't need that again right now
unless we run out of songs
okay this is a beautiful song please
listen
[Music]
lyrics because it's so much easier
to sing
with those
not that i can't read japanese but
please give me a break this is really
difficult when there's some kanji where
you are not sure anymore
[Music]
oh
makes me happy
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
is
me
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
come on
um
[Music]
oh
here
it's almost 1am i hope i hope my
neighbors don't hear me
but
for the sake of my neighbors i hope you
reach
the milestones
[Laughter]
thank you that was um you know it's
really fun to sing songs that
require you to really give it your all
and i get this feeling with supercell
songs not very well i guess both of the
lads maybe not so much but with the
non-veloc songs
it's just like
you give it
all you got you can really show
um
like what your spectrum of your voices
neighbors be vibing as well i hope so
yeah
i love supercell songs i don't think
they do oh i said that before i think
i'm glad to see someone asking for um
morning muslim adult that makes me happy
that i'm not the only one
who likes hello project
thank you guys thank you guys thank you
also thank you for the pinky
hanaji
did you hear my energy color before you
the one who's asking for it i signed
that before in an un-archived stream
because i don't think i can stream that
in an archived one look up takadashi
kiara
there's 100 a clip out there and it's um
i think
out of all the songs i've ever sang
before i think that is one of my top
five nailed it songs
it's just so much fun
[Laughter]
yeah i would love to sing it again but
if i would sing that now um maybe my
neighbors would call the police
it's a very high tension and erotic song
yamata yamada
okay
one more refresh please please get
closer to it come on come on wow what
happened
that was a big jump did you guys like
the song so much what the hell
less than 500 away now i will say
however
usually when we do this kind of
marathons in her life
on the next day
it always seems like we we whoever does
this lost some sub numbers but it's
because youtube is checking it so i will
not the first time that happened it
freaked me out so much i thought people
just were like [\h__\h] around with me
and pranking me but apparently that's
not the case so i will not care just
just so you guys don't freak out when
that happens it happens it happens when
like when too many people
subscribed and youtube is like
let me think about that whether or not
you deserve it or not
love you sing still have sparks and now
me treat omit tree don't miss
and felt so wrong when i was reading it
that my brain first wanted to correct it
and automatically read myth or treat wow
brain is smart
thank you for listening to those thank
you
it's riddle myth
treadle myth
you tried i give you an a for effort
okay yes um
uh
one i think
uh we'll sing this one because i think
that one is perhaps kind of
kind to me
as it is not too difficult
not too energetic
hopefully
a macro song but not delta
i need something to
calm down a little bit
oh wait wrong
wrong
this is the new one
oh oh i wrote the other one into the
wrong field too oh okay sayonada
memories i didn't forget anything right
now now it's all there right did i sing
something in between
okay
no okay good
let's go
[Music]
oh yeah
uh
is
[Music]
m
foreign
[Music]
la
m
[Music]
oh
i think didn't sana sing this in her
debut stream
like a little bit of it
she definitely sang something
like universe related space related i
think she's saying this one right
yeah
when she's saying that i was happy i was
like good song joyce
[Laughter]
such a classic
yes
yes you did you did you don't remember
guys it's not been that long
you should maybe remember
some of it is she having her oh
come back stream tomorrow right
like today depending on your time zone
yeah yeah yeah just for for you guys to
remind me remind you guys
give her a warm welcome back
she has a uh well a comeback stream in
in uh
do i see this correctly does she have an
unarchived card okay and then like a
proper return stream as well
i think
i think perhaps
in 14 hours
yeah
i will be awake she's streaming at a
good time for me night soon
nice to however i think during the
karaoke i'll be busy recording the thing
that i said i will be recording
but i'll be there for the other stream i
think let's support sana sana was gone
for so long it was so lonely without her
counsel is i don't know kind of empty
without her
i mean everyone from council is grateful
i don't know santa has this this
um
this this bright personality is
something similar to
me maybe a little bit a little bit i
feel like um from our
uh personality where we have some
similarities
or am i crazy
kiwa energy
big energy
big personality
wait that sounds so rude normally when
you say that to people isn't that a way
to say uh
i don't know something rude
i like her personalities wait that means
something else
i like her personalities if you say that
in plural then you mean something else
[Music]
update
i kind of want to sing the last uh whole
life song that i prepared
as as the finishing song but maybe i'll
sing it now and then finish with sparks
or something like that
we are at 750 oh my god 250 left let's
go
let's go
let's
yeah i think um i'll be working on that
for another stream
it's definitely
a song that i wanted to sing in the
future
yeah
all right now i wonder what should i
sing
ah wait i found the karaoke that i used
before i'm pretty sure i used this one
before
pretty sure
okay
yeah
it should be okay to sing this okay
let's sing fanta
a classic it's such a cute song
very idol
it was
a
oops wrong thing again
number thirty a free
font
now i need a lyrics
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
yeah good job guys
foreign
[Music]
okay
m
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
refresh
holy [\h__\h] why is it going so fast okay
okay because you guys are i'm going so
bro i will now
sing the song that i've been keeping
from you
which hopefully will be the last one
reflect
by
okay give me a moment to find myself
and the lyrics and everything
like
you're probably not watching this but
i'm gonna sing your song
i love this song so much holy [\h__\h]
i've i've had it in my ear since it came
out it's so special it has like
all these different
uh
parts to it that are so unique
[Music]
absolute banger
uh
my brain is empty reflect
reflection
evil kiwawa
yeah i'm gonna try
where is my audio
uh
[Music]
um
okay are you guys ready
i want to take off my glasses for this
one so that i see better
wait
okay
and
well
while we're at a change a little bit
more
[Music]
yay my hat i love my hat
sammy told me
okay yes
i i however will not speak the greek
parts because i i don't know how to
pronounce it
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
a
um
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
know
and look at this so-called time of the
sea all in front if you see what i mean
return to what you know it ain't much i
know
it shows
uh
[Music]
is
just gonna leave me like it's nothing
going without me i don't know what
you're thinking return to the sea a
shark is all you'll ever be
[Music]
um
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] yeah i didn't make any mistakes
okay no i made a tiny one but no one
noticed no one oh yeah yeah yeah
i'm i'm satisfied i'm satisfied with
that oh
i didn't mess up i was so concentrated
i was so focused i didn't want to mess
up the song
oh my god i was so into it
look
chat
thank you
thank you guys
for going through this with me thank you
for watching this stream and giving my
channel a chance i hope i will not
disappoint you i'm working hard every
day to bring you funny content please
feel free to check out my streams in the
coming days yeah we have something
really exciting coming up on
friday
yeah got um
shin megami 10 say
five uh yes yes yes
yeah people are going crazy with that
yeah but we we always try to have fun at
kfp thank you for joining you're now all
officially chickens no first of all your
eggs um i will sit on you and try to
hatch you
yes yes thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank
[Music]
oh and it's not that late yet i can go
to sleep at a decent
okay-ish time it's 1 one am uh one uh 16
minutes after 1am here you deserve it
thank you i love you guys
i love you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
kfb i love you thank you so much
thank you
[Music]
thank you all
again
oh god
but my brain
is empty i'm actually exhausted can i uh
if you want an encore can i can i lead
you to
uh stream vampire
or stream sparks or whatever please i
can't today normally i love giving you
guys encoder but um
we i think we should leave it at this 34
uh songs
it's actually more than 34 songs because
i was singing all day before that
thank you for your understanding
understandable have a nice day
tomorrow is by the way minecraft but uh
i don't know maybe it will be moved by
one hour or something i'm not sure yet
depends on how the recording goes
tomorrow and how i feel how my voice
feels tomorrow
[Music]
today okay you are not gonna
you don't have permission to ask for a
ramstein song for at least one year
anymore
[Laughter]
you should be thankful that i sang sang
to hustle you guys
[Laughter]
that was
something i always wanted to avoid
[Music]
you
actually
um
yeah oh thank you
i don't know what i don't know uh what
what to say this is uh
wow
it's a crazy number it's a crazy number
i can't
believe it like honestly
that's a huge number when i when i first
joined whole life you all know i never
expected this so
that we could that we will go so far
it's like insane
thank you everyone you guys are the best
whole live english
best all my fans best thank you guys
thank you thank you thank you
and for all the new people
maybe i should explain
uh there's this room called the usual
room you don't want to go in there we
mentioned it a lot but it's a room where
chickens get re-educated my viewers are
chickens they get re-educated there
try to not anger me or i will have to
send you there
feel free to whenever you don't
understand some kind of insiders we
talked about this uh on a different
stream whenever you don't know when
whenever you don't understand something
feel free to ask the rest of the okay of
people i always want new people to feel
comfortable and not like oh my god what
is this i don't belong i don't
understand anything because after a
whole year of streaming we obviously
have our insiders and
and our little
uh
rituals but we're not a cult
oh yeah one important thing to mention
is maybe a hashtag roll cached like yolk
we came awoke woke
woke and yolk we came up with those
hashtags in the fire emblem stream
they sound like proper words but they
have actual
different meanings behind them hashtag
stands for watch only kiana every day
and hashtag yolk stands for you only
love kiara it's okay you can like
someone else it's okay it's okay to say
you need to understand we are a little
bit
[Laughter]
me
let me enter the youtube see we have
these crazy chickens every once in a
while who want to enter the usual room
but then when i bring them into the
usual room they're like oh my god
kiwanwa is so cruel
[Applause]
you guys have like split personalities
or something
hey you guys are super chats i'll read
them next time thank god we're called up
so it's not gonna be hopefully not too
much thank you thank you thank you thank
you for the sweet support don quixote
and you sweetheart you don't have to do
that but thank you infatuate
my chat broke again so i'm looking at
the obs screen only and it keeps on
stopping every once in a while it's too
much
too much
oh and by the way uh if you got my
merchandise um and got the email you
gotta check your emails if you bought my
merchandise for my birthday it's uh
being sent out right now
um i think they're checking whether or
not everyone's addresses are still
correct so
check the emails
you should have received an email and
japanese fans have already received it
it's looking really great you gotta go
on twitter i retweeted a couple ones
uh they look so good holy [\h__\h] the
tapestry from huki papa looks so good
and everything oh my the slippers look
so comfy
the pla the the placement the table mat
thingy i want that asap i need it for my
table i hope it comes to my place i
still don't have it
i still don't have it
ah
can't wait to get it yeah it looks
really good the quality of the slippers
looks so good about you know i hope it
fits your feet guys
if it doesn't maybe give it to
if you have a little sister or someone i
don't know
or a girlfriend or or
or a big sister or maybe maybe you have
a mother with small feet my mom has
small feet
eh
thank you yeah oh that the dog the date
of it being sent off is actually uh
earlier than it originally was told in
those emails so um yeah it i don't know
how long it will take but it will be
sent out in this month in the next
couple of days will be sent out overseas
as well not only in japan
all right then uh
i think
that's about it so now that i've
finished all of the songs what are your
favorites now
which one was your favorite now
midnight
let's see what they say what's what do
they say
congratulations thank you
congratulations
uncle no sorry i'm dead
all of me still own me i like fanta
thank you reflect thank you i'm glad i'm
glad it went well i didn't mess up too
much
grim reaper oh that one went well too
thank you
heroine cry for me hey
do hush reflect
chat go like
ah
youtube obs are you okay is this too
much for you
tomato
[Music]
okay
okay okay thank you guys i love you
please please uh
have a nice day have a good evening have
a good night and don't forget to check
out sana's uh revival stream
uh she's coming back today
so so please make sure to check out her
stream and give her
yeah let's check out her stream yeah
it's not happening now but in like 10 14
hours or something like that
and okay yeah at kfb we say at the very
end
a german word a german greeting to say
goodbye which is called alvitas in so
get your finger typing finger
fingers ready i don't have any anymore
because yesterday i cut off my hands
are you ready
and in german we say
auf wiedersehen
thank you
for your support
i love you guys
[Music]
see you tomorrow hopefully
hopefully hopefully
bye bye
bye bye bye bye bye love you thank you
hope you enjoyed the stream
see you
thank you
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
thank you kevin you guys are the best i
love you all so much good night have a
nice day enjoy yourselves
[Music]
you