DET
OG
OGtil
DET
H
Yeah ah yeah
Ami-san
Mina
-
san Hello America Hello everyone How are you? Please wait a little while My
wife
is super sleepy The BGM is
a little too loud Are you
okay? Maybe
How is the book going
?
How are you? [Music] How is it? It's so early in the morning
in America. What time is it now? Um, it's 7 o'clock now.
Calliope is 7
o'clock. Good, good, that's good.
Above all,
[Music]
Hey hey
Debby,
I'm sorry, Calliope's Japanese has
gotten really bad.  I haven't used it
yet, sorry. I want to
improve my English so I'd like to try streaming in Japanese. No English this time. Thank you for listening.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you. I can speak English,
but I'm doing this challenge, so I
'll reply in Japanese.
Hey, it's not Japanese, sorry. Hey, hey,
hey, it's not Japanese. Oh, wait, it's
not Japanese.
Well, today I want to try playing Totsumachi.
Well, this game is
called Clubhouse 51 in English.
I'm Calliope and I'm going to
play Clubhouse 51 on Disord.
Please join me.  I was
thinking, "What is Clubhouse 51?" I don't
know what it is in Japanese.
Certainly, everyone has
already taken it.
Calliope, well, well, well, it
can't
be helped. It's a game, a tournament. Yes, the Japanese names are
completely
different. I understand that it's a game and a tournament.
Calliope, Calliope, that's right, so wait a minute.
Well, let's
gamble in the clubhouse for now. Let's gamble while we wait. I want to
play Black Jack. How
about it
? For
now, please stop. No, no, wait a minute. I
made a character.
Wait a minute, I made a mistake. I made a mistake.  I'm
going to have a little baby.
Wait, that's not Calliope,
this doesn't look like a temporary bride, wait, wait,
my
figure connecting,
yeah, flying
machine, no, I don't need it, I don't need it, I don't need it
, ah,
OK, I want to gamble, Harim, is that okay? Do you
like Blackjack, Blackjack
?  Let's
play blackjack. Hey,
ham, beok, this is English,
really English, skip, oh, let's try 5 razz, oh,
okay, I understand, do you know the rules of blackjack
? Do you know? I've played it before, play 5,
Jesus knows too, I know, okay,
okay  Hey,
good, good, Calliope, I've gambled on a real song before, I'll do
my best,
no, it's no
-sen, so what
should I do?
[Music]
That's really inevitable, the
player is the king, so there's nothing we can do,
everyone, don't worry, don't worry, let's move on to the next one,
this time for sure  Calliope will win. Okay okay.
Um.
[Music]
Oh, I'm
not 20. I
really wish you'd stop.
No, oh, oh, it's okay, we'll definitely win this time.
Calliope is the reason,
30303030,
oh,
30 grass, not grass, not grass, everyone, see, it's
not funny,
double
down, please bust,
please bust
[applause]
Ah, I do
n't have 40, I don't have it, but see, it's
negative  I can be negative so
wow Black Jerk
congratulations
Muff
hit
stand stand
stand hey hey hey he
lost
nnn oh well then it's the last one so
calliope
is
Ruin
Ruin ya baby oh okke good feeling good feeling
yeah stand
da stand
power
biu we won
[music]
yeah 2  It's my turn now, I'm glad everyone, look,
Calliope, maybe,
not Black Jack,
Levia, I don't want to read it, I don't want to read it, hey
, shall we do it again? I'll be waiting, hey, my friend will definitely come to play, I believe, he'll definitely come to play, yeah, if he doesn't
come, well, oh well  I'm going to gamble. I'm
going to gamble until late into the night. I'm really looking forward to it.
Dando
Power. Wow, I was surprised. I was surprised.  I
was surprised, oh,
wait a minute, wait a minute, it's
gambling, gambling, gambling.
Thank you very much for coming.
Sorry, I'm intruding on your gambling time. I
'll stop, I'll stop, it's not
fun, it's not fun, thank you very much.
No no no I'm looking forward to it
No no no I'm looking forward to Kario senpai's game
Yay yay yay I'm looking forward to it I'll make a lobby
Thank you No no I'm waiting Oh By the way Kao
senpai is here Member
Love
Thank you I forgot I forgot but I
practiced a lot so it's cool It's
cool I'm happy  Thank
you very much, I did my best,
yeah, Kaka-chan is bling bang bang bang, yeah,
wait a minute, I'm not singing with the face I was singing with, oh, please
try it, please try it, yeah, I want to
sing, I want to sing, yeah,
plug and rap, yeah, what game should we play?  I'll
leave it to you. I'll leave it to you. I'll leave it to you. So,
what do you say in Japanese? Connect 4. Connect 4.
Yeah, I'm really good at it, Big Brey
, you're such a genius, you're
so bad at it, so you're so bad
at it, so you're
going to get eaten, let's go, you're going to get eaten,
let's go, big Calliope, calliope,
please give me the color red  Oh, red
is good, that's the image, that's the best,
next to me, yeah,
no, no, no, it's so messed
up, are you concentrating, yeah, Kinkade-chan, how are
you? Oh, I'm fine, good, Calliope is fine too, I'm fine, very fine, it's early in the morning, but oh  Early morning Calliope senpai Yes your
Japanese is very good thank you Not that at all
But ah no no
no no what will I do what will I do Calliope I'm
not stupid I'm not stupid I'm not stupid no no
scary scary scary
oh oh oh this is not good absolutely not good
no oh no  It's not that, it's
that,
stop it,
it's that  I'm
not stupid, I'm
not stupid, it's okay, it's okay,
senpai, it's
okay, it's okay, ah, hey, I'm not stupid, please stop, wow, you're stupid, yeah, yeah, just one more time,
one more time, it's okay, I won't lose, so I'll wrap the calliope, I
won't lose, Oori, come on, come on, come on,
come on  Come on,
throw it around, throw it around, Okroz is so cool, come on, throw it
around, I love it, I'm going to beat you up, I'm going to beat you up, I'm going to beat you up, I'm going to beat you up, I'm going to beat you up for sure, I'm going to beat you up this time, yeah, your
intonation is cute, I'll beat you up,
intonation, it's
weird but it's funny so it might be okay  Hey, I'm
going to make it pop,
oh,
yeah, what should I do? Hey, I see, Calliope is
going to block it here.
[music] Is
one okay? Is one okay
? Oh, I see, oh, I see, oh, oh, oh,
oh, I
made a mistake, no, I made a mistake  Oh yeah
yeah
[laughter]
Please don't be happy
[music]
Peepipio senpai
wow
[music]
Uh, hey hey, it's scary, scary, scary, scary, scary,
Calliope, you're scary, the Grim Reaper is scary, look, stop, stop, stop, look, you're
not concentrating right now, so you
might die, you might die, senpai is strong, yeah, you're
getting strong, no, no, make
a little mistake  I made a slight mistake
No no no
[Applause]
wn
Calliope
UN
Bobo stupid native
Uwaaa stupid stupid o Shall we play another game? It's a
frustrating draw, so um Akana de
Chan is um um um um 1 more hour to
stream Macto is different  Ah, I'll be playing Minecraft
from 11pm, so please enjoy it.
Thank you for playing a little bit.
Ah, I can play a little bit. Boxing is
fun. There
's no mercy. There's no mercy. Papan,
pa ...  I'm
going to give it my all, so I'll try my best. I
kinda forgot to control myself, so let me
take a quick look. I
see, I get it, I get it. Bring it on, I'm
really gonna beat you up this time, so
bring it on, I'm gonna make you mine
Grim Reaper punch, scary punch,
just a moment, garaga, guard,
guard, oooh, wow, hey, hey,
there's a UFO over there, over there,
stop the UFO,
wa,
wa, wa, wa, woah, yeah, of course, of course, let's do it
one more time,
uoo, there was one over there, yeah, it's too
good, listen  Where is Mashira-chan? Rap-chan, if you like,
sir, sir, sir,
where is the
UFO,
sussus Swiss UFO,
stop it, look, it
's a UFO, look, it's Hoshimachi Mizu, look, look, it's Mizu, it's Mizu-senpai, look, look, it's over
there, look, Suisui-chan, senpai is
n't here  No,
wait, wait, wait, ah, ah, ah,
[applause]
Yeah, congratulations,
that was a good match, a good match, thank you, the
match was fun, so fun, so fun, and it
was a draw, it was a draw, yeah, hehe, let's do it,
this is the one I love about Oo Calliope, it's so good
I mean, I'm good at it.
Well, I wonder, let's have a taping match. I
think I'm good,
but I might lose. If I think I'm good, I'll
definitely lose. So, I wonder if I can win.
No, I haven't started yet.
Wait a minute, I'll protect, I'll even protect
. Ah, no, ah, no, I
did it.  Oh, Calliope, you're so bad,
but you'll definitely win, it's difficult, Calliope, you're so bad, I'll
take you, so strong, so strong, I'm going to
beat you up ...
Wait, wait, no, no, no, it's
alright, it's
alright, I'm relaxed, relaxed, relaxed, no ...
Hand yeah, seriously, change it, go easy on me, go easy on me,
if I win, I'll watch it, if I
win, I'll watch it, if I win, I'll watch it, yeah, my, no,
this time, this time it's
blue, so not lucky, Calliope, it's
red, right, red, no, red is the lucky color, so
this is really evil, blue  It's
really hot, it's getting hot,
wait, wait, that's not what we said, it's a really
good match, a good match,
no, a good match, that's a good match, above all, are you holding back,
no stop, it's
decided, no, maybe it's not a match, Calliope
is so messed up  I'm clumsy, so I'm
clumsy, the tempo is also good
, wait, there's just one more point, that's right, ahhhhh, did I win, I won, yes,
I won
[music], it was a good game, it seems
like a good game,
thank you, thank you, yobe senpai, it
was fun, it was fun
Thank you for coming. Let's collaborate and
sing again. Of course, I
want to collaborate. Yes, I want to sing together. I want to sing.
Kade-chan's singing is really good, and
you're also really good at singing and rapping, so
thank you for the rap. Let's definitely sing together someday.
Of course, I want to. It was fun.
Yes, it was fun. Thank you for listening.
Thank you very much. Do your best.
Bye bye.  See you
soon Peace Bye Kanade-chan Kade-chan You're so cute Play with Stop I'm going to stop It was fun It was a good game Everyone was surprised It was so much fun Gambling I'm gambling Or maybe practice is good but I don't know if there's even a CPU  But um,
thank you Jajagal, it
was fun, it was really fun, it's
good, let's do it again,
wow, Calliope is a bit of a piece of junk,
everyone is really a piece of junk, no, that, that, it
can't be helped, I've been a piece of junk since I was born, so it won't
change  It might
not be a gamble, no, this time it's
, stop it,
stop it, this is the worst, hit
it, power, yeah, I'm going to do it, it's good, it's really good, big
money,
poop, in this house, there's water  There
is no water,
but there is a sink,
but I wonder if I can drink it. I
love water, so I can't help it. I'm going to go
shopping at a water bottle. The
store might be closed at the moment. Is it
Jini or
something? Stop it, stop it.
Water,
water ...  The taps are scary.
Yes, that's right. It
depends on the week. For example, Florida
might be undrinkable.
Texas might not be so bad. I
don't know, but I don't
think Texas is that bad.
Yes, that's right. So I don't
think there's a problem. And I think
California is fine too. I do
n't think the water tastes that bad.
Sometimes the water in Florida
has a strange, stoney taste. It's a
little weird.  I don't know if I'm wearing dirt,
but it definitely doesn't taste good.
Yes, it tastes like stone, so I know it. Calliope, wait a minute, I mean, when I was a kid, did I taste that? If it's
stone, it's a hit. Maybe
it's a stand. Have you
ever eaten stone?
No.  No, no, when I was an adult  I
never ate it as an adult, but when I was a child, I
licked it once, and
it
tasted like a stone.
Thank you for saying that, but my
Japanese has become really bad. I
haven't used it at all,
so
I'll stop. Stand licking, lol. Good
evening, good
evening, good evening. I'm fine.
Calliope. I just woke up in bed. I'm
really dying.  I wanted to play, but I'm
glad I was able to have a good game with money, so
I'm feeling good right now. I'm in a good mood.
Look, everyone is a blackjack master. I've
become a blackjack master. I'm
waiting for the next 5 rounds. The other
members  I'm waiting,
will they come? I'm waiting, I'm waiting, but the other members are
streaming now so I
don't know if they'll come or not but I hope
they do, I hope they do, that's good
No no no no no no no
Chan might not be awake at all
40 likes 4 likes
please stop 15 and 16 are the best the
worst
yeah then Calliope is secret
oh oh it's okay it's okay it's okay from now on
Calliope is
60 all in that
is to say
Oluesia
all
in yeah  I wonder if the GP members are shy. It's
okay. Calliope is also really shy, so it can't be helped. Holo members are shy, so it can't be helped, but we won. It's okay. I'll wait for Calliope. Yes, I'll wait.
Please listen to it after the live stream is over.
From now on  Calliope is concentrating on gambling
so it's fine, it's totally fine.
Now
[music]
It's blackjack, it's
blackjack, it's really crazy, so if you
gamble and get a blackjack,
then you'll get a little more bonus
chips, it's amazing, it's really crazy.  It's
a draw so I don't get any money I
don't get any money Oh, how kind
Clubhouse 51 Play Tournament Ame So
kind, what a kind world
100 100 yeah yeah
Yes, I've been to Las Vegas. Yes, yes, yes, yes, it was a little scary. I might not go back because it was so scary. I've
done it once, so I'm satisfied.
It's
enough. It's fine. I think
just once in my life is enough.
But if you like gambling, you've
only said it once in your life,
so maybe it's better to say it, or maybe it's scary,
or what? I think there are some really dangerous things about it,
but if you're with friends, it
's probably no problem at all.
But maybe I should study a little English a little bit. I
did a double-down.
Yes, if I'm with friends,
it's fun and safe. It's
pretty interesting. But maybe I should study a little English.
The reason is  There are a lot of suspicious people
around so be careful. I
did it, 410, and I became insanely rich.
Wow, that was great, everyone's faces.
Wow, that double down was super lucky. Wow, you're so strong, Wanile.  Well, I'll try
playing blackjack one more time, and then I'll try playing other games solo.
While I wait,
I'll wait.  I was
thinking maybe I should do it a little later, but I guess
Japanese people also
have a calm time after work, so I
thought I'd do it for that reason. Today
is Tuesday.  Good
evening, good
evening, I'm feeling calm and relaxed,
thank you, thank you, no, no, it's me too, yeah, have you eaten?
Calliope doesn't eat breakfast, she
doesn't eat, it
makes my stomach hurt like crazy, so if I eat breakfast,
yeah, chicken doria is good
Wow, chicken doria, maybe not American. No,
no, no, I want to go back to Japan soon. I really
want to go back to Japan. Japanese food is
really the best. American food isn't that bad depending on the place.
There are some delicious things.  I think that for example,
fried chicken, yeah, sandwiches, and
sandwiches are
the best, but I prefer Japanese rice.
Rice
dishes, cooking, cooking, that's right, rice dishes, for example, tonka and katsu are also delicious. It's
Ace, so I'll eat it.
Seungwoo-ji's
wow, he's so cute,
stop it, that's unlucky, Biji-chan is
cute, but I think the English
members can
be called Bib,
Biboo, who is Biju? I do
n't
know who Biji is, I know Bib, they're
friends, friends  Who's name is Beauty anymore?
But it's 10 so what
to do? Well well well
well Double down e
Baby Hehehehe It's
safe, I
won't miss it You say it often Aco 6's
Rusty Rusty's
That's right, I
won't miss it, it's
cool Rusty
Lastiaco I love sex It's coming soon
Everyone Elden Ring
Elden Ring
DLC is perfect H
Stop stop Oh no Ace so no
what to do because I'm scared
Stand is scary Yeah That's right Good
Stand was good but no
no that's that  It was really inevitable.
IW
misses it. It was really inevitable. I won. I won. I
won.
410 is better.
It's good, is
n't it? Gambling is fun, it's too fun, but it's a game, so it's not really funny, so it's okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay,
hey,
halim, what are you going to do? It's a solo,
piano,
wait,
[music],
Baradan Kao, it's good,
listen to this, you
know  I do
n't know, maybe I'm not good at it,
stop, I'm in charge,
shake shake,
oh
[Music],
freestyle, love ring, bonbon bonbin,
bonbon, that's not freestyle, but,
this is not a piano, but, ah, the
screen, I see,
yes, yes, yes, okay, okay, okay, the screen,
touch  I can't do it so I
can't really use it. What is this
? I'm going to do a face scene.
Fishing is good,
but the
boxing CPU is really difficult. I ca
n't do it. I'll win in normal or o. Good
morning. Good evening.
Everyone, how do you guard?  No, no
, no, it's a small fry, a small fry, a small fry, a
small fry, a useless useless, look, she's
blonde,
so a useless useless useless, oh no  It's
Dio, Dio, Dio.
[Music] It's
difficult, difficult, I made it even harder.
[Music] Look, ha ha, it's
hard mode. It's Dio.
Let's go. Dio, Dio, Dio. Excuse me,
but you'll
have to die. I'm going to get beaten. Guard, guard. I'm going to
win. I'm going to win.  I
did it,
excuse me, champion, but please, it's
useless, useless, useless,
Ang has become even more difficult,
Amazing, it's no good, so
powerful,
Pupo, please stop, oh, I'm Pupo, I'm
concentrating so much, so
wait, Kira, this Dio is,
Yay, amazing, yeah, amazing,
so
good, thank you, kyu kyu, next is
Impossible
[Music],
inbu yeah, do it, at the end
[Music]
[Music] Are you
studying or not, are you studying,
stop studying my punch, yay, it's
so messed up  This guy is smart.
One more time, one more time, one more time. No, it's
Ishiru, but is he
doing it?
This guy is so smart, you stop,
huh, I did it, I did it, but it's not good, so at the end,
Calliope didn't punch at all, so I
did it, I mean, I really did it, so I'm
sorry, it was fun
[Music]
Hmm  I did it.
Game game game game game game
game game
game Yeah I've never played shogi
but I wonder if it's fun
Majin Yeah I
have a friend who loves Majin but I don't know the rules at all
[Music]
Yeah Lear Yeah It's difficult
Yeah Game Game  Game Game
Game Rudo Oh, this
is the one in English, Sally. Sally is
a game that Kia likes. This
game, 5 in a
row, wait a minute, how do you do 5 in a row? I'd
like to practice a bit.
Thank you for the gift membership.  Thank you thank you gift
membership
Oh how do I do it?
5 is it 5 in a row
Oh I don't know so
Kamo-chan, did someone ask me?
Wait a minute, wait a minute, it's Takashi Chiara.
Chiara, hello, hello,
Japanese hello, nice, nice to hear  hand
Thank you for that. I'm Takakia from Hololive Japan.
Hololive Japan or Japan. I
like it. I'm already Japan
Japan. Yes, I'm not Japanese, but
well, I live in the Japanese Underworld. That's
right, so I'm Hololive
Japan.  Shoso I
love Japan so much that I became JP yeah I'm
going to make a Robo thank you
Kiwa yeah I think he's doing it alone
yeah I thought I'd help him thank you help me
yeah other members are streaming too I guess so
Right now, I think it's the busiest time. Yes,
certainly, certainly, it's a bit
late. It's been a while since I played this game.
Wait a bit. Yes, I'm waiting. Yes, I just
got home, so it's
a bit late.  I
went to the post office and
brought the post, post, post box, postbox, box home, but it was so heavy my arms
were like jelly, I
'm so tired, so tired, thank you for your hard work,
yay!  Online play with Ah
play with Friends If it's in Katakana,
it's good, I think it's good. No, it
's Japanese. Japan play with FriendI
play
withYesOh wait a minuteOh waitN
's Nintendo
SWITCH's subscription
has expiredOh no, I have to pay it now,
right? Well, I'll buy
it now, why did it expire? Take your time, it's
fine.  Who is that? I know, I know, I
know, it was a different account. I
see, are you okay, Kari-chan? Yes,
how are you? I mean, how are you? Well, maybe you're not really well, but yeah,
yeah, it can't be helped, you know,
this week  I'm not that tired, so I
think it's okay because I can stream to a certain extent.
But I said I won't push myself, I won't push myself, I won't push myself, but when I
looked at my schedule on Google Calendar, it was packed!
Hehehehe, I
love streaming, so really, really
I love the boring broadcasts,
but I also love my body,
so so so, so, so, so, I
love my knees, if I love them, I have to take care of them, I take care of them, I'm super
healthy, I'm eating super healthy food,
and I'm walking a little bit,  But I do
n't know how to say it in Japanese.
But um, what was it, I
know, but,
well, it's not Bobo, but she uses something
to walk, yes, that's right, a bit like
grandma, a cane, a
cane, yes, a cute grandma, a face, grandma, no,
no
But I have to walk, it's important,
my knees hurt, but sometimes,
when I sit, if I sit for a long time, my knees
hurt, so I don't push myself too hard, I
don't want to stream for a long time.  I don't think it's long.
Yes, this week's broadcast
may not be that long.
But I'll broadcast every day. That's right. Have fun.
Hey, my Nintendo subscription is
a little strange. No, that's
sad. Wait a minute, why, why,
why?  I wonder why I'm paying more. I
have an account, but it's kind of expensive. I
don't have any
money. I'm poor. No, it's
okay. I might not be able to play the game. If it's no good,
then it can't be helped.  No, there isn't.
Oh, Switch Online, oh,
nice, nice, please
Please, please, please, I was
just saved, saved, no,
thank you, thank you, thank you for coming, I
might come again later, I'll be waiting, bye ...
Well, this is... well, I guess we're
friends now, right? Let's
be friends,
let's be friends.
Wow, I'm looking
forward to it. When I saw the guy waiting to call in, his voice was so loud I wondered if I could go.  I was
worried, but it
was a different day. I'm glad, yeah, it's good
that your voice is fine now. I
can't use it. Get plenty of rest. I'm glad you're
feeling better. Wow, I'm glad. Yea, yeah,
yeah, I can play games.  Shall I
send the code together? Code:
Oh, that's okay. The lend code. I was
just talking to Kia-chan.
That's right. She was speaking in Japanese and it
was really funny. I don't know
why she speaks Japanese, but she can speak English. So
wait a minute. The
lend code.
Thank you.  Okay okay um really  It was a funny
story but what were you talking about? Calliope recently had that surgery, yeah, surgery, so she was talking about that and saying thank you for your hard work, thank you, don't push yourself too hard,
but you're not pushing yourself, I
see  Don't push yourself, you really shouldn't push yourself, you're fine, you're doing
fine, I'm glad you're doing well, my knee hurts a little, so I'm tired, that's why it
hurts, yeah, I had knee surgery,
so, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, o-o-
o-o-o  Don't move too much, do
n't walk too much, that's true
, I'm
not pushing myself too hard, I'm taking it easy
so there's no problem, I sent you a friend,
just wait a bit, yeah,
yeah  Let's get some water hmmm
reest okay I sent it
thank you
no no okay then I'll wait in the lobby I love
Gorilla Gorilla it
's Gorilla Gori Gori Gori okay I see I
love Donkey Kong
Donkey Kong it's Kimonkey this is Gorilla haha
thank you for taking care
Gorilla ah wait a minute okay my voice is a little
low
sorry okay oka-chan's voice was really loud
so I turned it down a little but ah it's okay now yeah
this feels good it feels good oh the volume is
big yeah that's right the song is a song  The song
is good, so the amount is certainly very good,
so it's amazing, so I'm
going to choose an online friend, Robi, yeah, this is it, yay, what
game will I play, I'm looking forward to it, what can I play, oh, it's here,
okay, I did it, what will I
do, okay, I did it, I came  Mashiyoshi has come
Okay let's play Eh What game
should we play? What should we play? I
can do it No, I'll leave it to you What game do you want to play? I'll leave it to you Yes Ha-chan
likes yachting the most
But oh, how many times have you played this
Round 1:
I'm not good at it. I've only played once.
But I understand the rules,
so I can do it. Okay. It's just
luck. It's definitely the management. It's really
unlucky. If that's the case, then it's the worst.  So let's do this, let's
do it. I want to do it.
But maybe I forgot a bit It's okay, let's
check, check, check Oh, yes, yes,
slowly, slowly, slowly, finally, oh OK, wow,
amazing, wow,
amazing, do I
have my 456? No, 456 is true, ah, I'm
worried, I'm worried, I don't know what to do
I'm having trouble deciding, I wonder, oh oh oh,
wait a minute, wait a
minute, Calliope is good, um, should I do 444, wait a minute, no, it's
strong, ah, 4 is really good, so I guess, yeah, 4
of 4, yeah, yeah, CC
C Okke, sure, then 4 fufufu ah 4 o'clock
OK, please wait wait this this You can
spin it 3 times 3 times yeah 3 times That's right this
Choose it Oh I didn't know It's okay
It's okay Yes it's okay Well, I'll do it next time  Noom, it was a
waste, noo,
pum, don't
worry, don't worry, don't worry, don't worry, don't worry, I wo
n't lose, I won't lose, I'm sorry, it's a pity, how
do you say that in English?
Course ah that was was
Estrait Good yeah
nice you're good senpai oh it's okay I won't
lose there's no way I won't lose I won't lose what will you do ah
good
666666 oh oh 6
and let's go
66 oh oh nice
go
Maga again 235 u the
worst ah
hacha  Let's
get 6, 111
,
3331123, 3, I
don't know,
but this is according to the rules, Calliope is a
bit clumsy, so it's
blue blue blue blue blue,
so I see, if you don't understand, please tell me, I should have
just made it 1, there's no problem
Okay, I'll definitely win. Yes, there's no problem. Do you
think you can beat me? No, no,
no, no. I think I'll win, but I don't want to. It's
only my second time. Good luck,
good luck, senpai.
[Music] You
can aim for a straight.  Start over from 12341234
and stop, but it's still S straight go go go
Keke No oh it's okay it's okay it's
okay Srey is feeling good it's okay uh huh huh oh Okay okay okay let's go well well
well
okay okay ha
yeah 5 ah 5555 ah
2344 if there is yeah yeah mae bibi
straight
yeah you're in trouble it's true you're in trouble you're in trouble you're
in trouble shinigami  It looks like a Grim Reaper. It looks
like a Grim Reaper.
2452 No, I'm
going to make it 5. I'm going to collect them. Super lucky. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, it's coming. It's so
good. Stop it.
[Laughs]
Please, I won't stop.
Oh, no, no, this is it.  Amazing,
okay, wow, oh my
Gally, amazing, good, really strong, senpai, woof,
woof, what should I do, woof, woof,
woof, woof, woof, woof, woof,
woof, go ...  Is that right? 50 points, 50 points, 50 points.
If it's all 1 then it's ok. Seriously?
Oh, I didn't know that. You can do
it, you can do it. Oh, I'll put out five of the same numbers. [Music] Karaki, yeah, it can't be helped, it can't be helped. I have Ewa, Eiwa, Kapi-chan has three aces. Ah, that's true. I see. What should we do?
Fufufufu 4455445
444544 Can we get a full house? Let's
aim for a full house.
What game did we
play? We played
boxing, boxing, that's right,
cann4.  I
don't know if that's true, but ah, the lining up, yeah, yeah, the lining up, ah, I see, I see, that's right, that and, um, air haki and stuff like that, oh, it was really fun, it was fun, it was fun, yeah, what should we do, no, this is really garbage, 1216, really, 66, 6666  It's gone too,
but yeah, but it might be a full house with Fudashi, yeah,
what should I do? No, it's
okay, give me 1234, wait a minute  I made a
mistake, ...  So then you have to choose again, I see, yeah, a
full house, a full house,
sure, then 55555566,
Hugo, stop
it, please, stop, please stop
, oh, it's the worst, no, it's really the worst, that's right, please stop it,
stop it, I think it's a choice, I think it's a
good choice this time  Let's
make a choice. It will also give us points. Right. I
don't know what to choose. 64 and 62.
Yes, that's right. Oh, it's scary, scary, scary. Senpai is strong.
Oh, it's 6.
6666. That's it. I don't want to take it. It's such a waste.
234 Yeah,
do your best, do your best
666666 Wow
[laughs]
Sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry  That
's right, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, congratulations, congratulations, super super lucky girl, yeah, that's right, no, Calliope, I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm
so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, that's right, congratulations, this is
Fai,
so Five has come again, there's still Five left
Sansao oh
Kan yeah
No no Seriously,
this is not good, this is not good, not good,
not good, yes, this is, this is the pseudo-reverse, is
it the pseudo-reverse? It seems to be the reverse, huh, but but but, by the way, Calliope-
chan might be a masochist, masochist  M or M, I'm an
M, M, yeah ...
There may be S, but yeah, I guess it's
M. I was attacked. Ah, that's right. It's
like a naughty, naughty story. Oh my, my heart is beating, my heart is beating, my heart is beating.  Is it a
full house again? But a full house
is no more. Yes, it's not there anymore. 4 is a lot. 44
4, nice, it's the same, it's the
same as Calliope. The same, the same, it
's 12. 3, I think about it. A
bonus, something like
63, oh  If you reach that level, you'll get a bonus of plus 35.
So you can also
save up a lot of the higher points to get a bonus.
Yes, yes, I see. So what's that? It was a bit weird. It was really weird.
So I'll do
it. Gochis, I'm sorry, but I'm going to have to wait a moment. Wow, what is
this? What is this? I don't have 33 yet, so I'll go with 3. Treat 3, that 4 is a mess. There's no more 4, there's no more. Right?  Choice Yeah
Okay ...
Ah it's arrived Ah there's nothing Ah Taba
[Music]
Taba Ah it hurts Ah it hurts hurts hurts My hand hurts Are you
okay
? Are you okay Oh what a shame It's a shame Oh
gogogogogogogo Nice go go go go Nice go go go
stubborn Even so Your luck is so
good  Senpai, right, right, right,
what should I do? With
this, I used up all my luck with Pe-chan,
and if I take it, that's right, it's quite
expensive, that's amazing, let's spin it, let's go, let's go, go, go
, oh, then that full house  Can we do
it? Come on, can we just have sex? Oh, oh ...  You
have a really amazing face but
oh, don't die, don't die, no, do
n't die, that's not good  I
'm alive lol I'm
alive I'm alive I'm alive I'm alive
Live
nice Okay I don't have to worry anymore It's
bad, it's bad Hacha is bad, Hacha is
bad, ah, hacha is bad, hey,
but I'm
also Seth
so
wow  Oh my goodness, why
didn't I choose it? 6 Oh no, no,
no, no, no, no, that's right, El,
when I did the slate, I really
made a mistake, no, it's okay, it's okay,
4th house, El, straight,
what is El, straight? 1234, yeah, El,
straight, El  Straight change
2456 I don't know but 23 Ah
Best rate El straight Straight
El straight 2345 Yes 2456
12345 Ah I see, you can go with 1 or 6
Ah oh oh oh this is good I can wait for both
Ah I did it but unfortunately it was 1  That was so
close! That was
amazing! Wow, that's so
amazing! It's 30 points!
Nono, this is really strong, it's a straight hit, it's
coming, no, no, it's no good, so be careful, you have to watch your back,
okay, 2222, oh that's right, there's still no 2, okay,
wow, oh my god, it's still going,
good, good  It's
scary, Bones,
Bones, seriously, why did you erase the B straight just now?
No way, if I get it, I can do it, I
see, full house is the strongest, right
? 4th house, this is tough, really,
really
tough, I'll shake it all up  What should I do?
Yes, I'm sure it's fine. It's
sparkling, sparkling, sparkling, and I'm here. Please,
please, please, please
, I just got here. Don't be ridiculous. I could
have done it if it was chopsticks.
[Music]
But...  That's not there, I'll
take it in one go, I wonder
if it'll come, I wonder if it'll really
come, I might have to wait a bit
, this is fun, it's
fun, no,
no, I'll do it again,
no  Let's do it
one more time. No, I'll lose, but it's
super fun. This is a showdown. Let's do it. Come
on, come on, come on. I can't do it, I can't do it. Oh, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, I'm dead. Let's go. Yes, I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm
dead. I'm dead.
[laughs]
This is bad, can I overkill? Oba kill, Oba
kill, yeah, I want to do Maga, I want to do it, it's here, I'm right
up to the last moment,
this is too extravagant with poison, hey,
hey,
hey, come on,
strike, no, the key is fun, if it's too strong, the opposite  It
was fun, wow, it was fun, senpai,
congratulations, wait, wait, I've
gone a little too far with this,
so I want to do Calliope-chan's favorite one,
wow, it's amazing, I
know Black Jack, Black Jack
Wow, I've heard something about it, I think I can
do it, I think I can do it, I really want to check it out just once,
but I confirmed the Ooroos Rules,
congratulations, that
was really fun, the best, the best, it was the best  It
was amazing, eh, I'm looking at the rules of the game, I'm
looking at it, I'm looking at it, is it Japanese? Yes, it
's Japanese, 21, ah, closer to 21, yeah, that's right, that's the
kind of game, that's the kind of
game, okay, Blackjack, it
's cool, ah, it's cool, the name is
cool  See, it's like Calliope-chan, that
's right, Okay,
so this is God's favorite game, this is the very limit, it
's a chicken race, it's the very
limit, but look, we're aiming for the very limit,
Okay, so let's go, this guy lost, wow, he lost, it seems he
lost, that
dealer got that 2121
Yeah, yeah, that player's number
was 20, so it was a little low, yeah, it
was lower than Deer's 21, so yeah, so that's
what it was, the dealer was strong, the
dealer, you matched the dealer's number,
yeah, that's right, yeah, so that's what it was, okay, okay, okay,
but Deer was heavy  We
have to stop. Oh,
that's
right. The rules of this game are
a little strange. I've played this before. It's strange
, it's strange. Let's go. Okay then.
Hey okay then Calliope is all
in.
Oh, all in. This is all in. Like this, like this,
do it in 10 units. All
in. That's right. All in. All right. Oh,
not bad, not bad, not bad,
low, low.  It's better to do it wait
wait wait is this a hint? The hint is low no
pull wait wait I'd better do the head again it's
good that person is 10 I see yeah it
's still a hit I want a bit more of this I can
do more it's amazing  Ah,
stand, stand, but what if there's a 20 person with 20 points? Ah, it's
definitely better to stand, you
can't beat a 20 person, Ah, but this,
because, right, you're using a lot of coins, right, yeah, nice,
nice, nice, yeah  Wow,
amazing, unah unah unah, hehe, this is also luck, isn't it
? Calliope
has stolen Calliope-chan's love again.
No, it's a real song, so I won't do this,
no, this time it's Olung.
Hey, why are you
going all in? Why is it all in? It's
negative. So it's 100. Is this all
in? Okay, okay,
it's a chance. It's gold.
If it was 11, I thought it would be better to double down.
But it
's Dao.  Double down
isn't so bad so it's fine, it's still fire, I
want a burst, what is a burst, that dealer,
that 12, that something passing by, that yeah
yeah something,
22021 or more, it's not good to do it tomorrow,
certainly, I'm going to stand  I guess it's true,
bust, look, for example, this one, fa, ao, just barely safe, yeah, just barely
safe, that's minus 200, um, it
's okay, there's no problem, it's sturdy, there's no problem,
chair, strong, lucky, lucky, F, e-word, I did
n't say f, but
f-f-q  [ __ ] you, I
didn't say it, I didn't say it, I didn't say it, oh wow,
I'm dead [laughing] oh wow, I'm going to die, Shinbakiol, it's
the best, [ __ ] boy, oh [ __ ]
Boy [ __ ] boy, that's a good word, isn't it? That
's
right, everyone is a Fukuboy, right? Okay,
no problem, all in, Minor
300, okay, okay, if you're going all in,
then you're going all in,
of course, let's go, let's go, me, money, mama, make
mama  I can't do it, but I'm
18 and I'm good at standing,
but I'm not sure if I'll attack or not,
but I'll leave it to you, I can't go, I
messed up, I'm going to hit zero, hit, hit, stand, yeah, this is already over, so I'll come back
Okekehaja is already in the negative, so
from now on it will be negative, final round,
final run, no all,
o-oi, I'll take it all back, if I do this 100,
100 will come back, if I
buy it, will everyone's come back,
everyone's who lost  Are you coming?
What
will you do? Oh, you're
strong.
Lucky wahi
, oh no, it's too close, stop it. Ah,
ah
Yay minus 400 Mice
400 What is this What was
that It was the worst I can't lie We
lost together We lost together That
was black jack That was black It
was fun Black was fun It was fun Hey
senpai Thank you for playing with me Kao-chan Ka-
chan-
chan  I want you to buy it. Ah, I want you to buy it. It's okay. The
other day, when I was playing alone, I
bought a lot of things. Yes, I bought a lot of things. I won a lot. I became rich. It's okay. I'm
glad I became rich. It's okay. I've been going out a
lot today.  You've
been doing it for about an hour and a half, right? Yes, I think you'll do it a little longer. I was
wondering who it was earlier, so I checked it out. I see, I see,
yes, if it's
someone who's not a compliment,  I'll stop for a bit. I see.
Okay, okay,
that's right. Thank you for coming. It was so much
fun. Thank you. I
had so much luck. Thank
you. No, thank you.  This time  Let's
talk in English, okay? Let's do an English stream, okay? Let's do an English stream, okay? See you later, see you later, bye bye bye bye bye Cha cha cha cha cha Cha bye
Maba, Maji Maji Maji Maji Maji Macha
That friend request was from Chiara Let's go
Chiara  Let's
go, that was a new account, so I was
n't friends with Kari-chan yet.
Yes, yes, I'll check it out. Please wait a moment. Yes, oh, that's a request.
Fuki, please be my friend. Oh, a llama, a pink llama,
right? Oh, that's right. No, it's not a llama, it's an
alpaca. Yes, an alpaca.  I want you to think of it as an alpaca.
Yes, alpacas are good, I
love them. Have you ever touched an alpaca, Kari-chan? Yes, yes, her
grandpa had a farm, so there
was a parka. There was one of mine. Yes, yes, there
was one.  That's amazing. I was
making some kind of wool. That's right. That's
right. That's
good.
That's right. It was really soft.  That's
nice. I went to an alpaca farm in Japan and a
baby alpaca spat that spit in my face. Oh
my god. Oh it's so cute. No, no, no, it stinks too much. That
alpaca's spit, sniff
sniff  Have you ever done it
? It stinks so badly. Seriously? I didn't even notice it. Once it's on my body, it
doesn't go away. The smell is
with me forever. Seriously? I
didn't know. It stinks. It stinks. Oh, I want to see you again, but I don't know much.
I want to ride an alpaca.
Humans can do it, but
adults can too. I think adults can
ride one too. It's in Minecraft too. It's a
great game.
Um, what should I do?
I don't know much about card games, other than Blackcha,
other than Bura Bura Kujaki, ok, what should
I do, tennis, I'm good at boxing, but that, that,
what was it called, that,
it's on the far left
But yeah, left left, um, right right right
right right right right, ...
So I'll try it. I
think I'd like to try it.
Yes, I think the Japanese members love it.
So this game is so
easy. Yes, Miko-senpai and Suba-senpai are
really good, so I like them. Ah, I see. Kari-
chan is  First, yeah,
okay, okay, what are you going to do? Bring it on, come back,
beaten up.
Hmm, I see, so that's how it is. Look at the Shogun's army,
Shogun. After the fallout, the Shogun is right, I'm watching,
where is Amazon Prime, the Shogun,
Disney Plus, ah, Disney Plus, ah  The power of the
likes is really good, it's really
high quality, it's a story about samurai,
yes, it's a story about samurai, it
has a bit of real Japanese history in it, but it's
not all true, seriously?
What should I do? I've seen Japan before.  I
wonder if Japanese people also watch it. I recommend that shogun.
People who like history
might be interested. I like it. It's
interesting. I mean, that
actor is really Japanese.  There are Japanese
actors. Yes, they are really Japanese.
Oh, that's really good. It's a really good thing. Oh, it's so beautiful. I'll
take a look at the beautiful elephants.
What should I
do? What should I do? Oh, it's so popular in Japan.  I
think people overseas might know about this drama.
It's on Disney Plus now, so I
think people overseas might know about it. I
think so. I'm a fan of Goss of Shima and stuff
like that.  I love games, so I
'd like to try playing a bit. Yes, it's good, I think we'd be a good match.
Yes, the history is interesting. Japanese is
really interesting.
Yes, it
's educational. Ah, really, it's like, Act's Japanese is native.
Of course.  Of course, yeah, oh no, I
won. Nekari-chan won. I
was talking a lot about it, so
congratulations.
Thank you.
Let's play darts, let's play Dois, let's play. Yeah,
sometimes, I
was watching a lot of movies on Netflix, and sometimes the
Japanese actors were speaking Japanese, and I
thought, "This person is not a native speaker," and
recently, for example,  Jiu and the others were like
that. I thought that would be the case,
but everyone was Japanese. The
main actor, Mr. Hajime, and the other actors all
said that they wouldn't do the job unless they were Japanese, so everyone was
Japanese.  Ah, I see, so you're
speaking Japanese properly, it's really good, I'll
check it out. Yes, really nice, nice,
yeah, this one, this one, I chose this one, this one,
this one, this one, this one, I'm
good at this one too  This is also good at it. Seriously? No, I
can't do it. Eka-chan, I've done
it before, but I'm not very good at it. No, it
's really easy, it's really easy, it's a piece of cake, it's a
kid's game, it's a kid's
game, a low-budget
game, yeah, the budget is low.  Games Yeah, back in the
day I did
n't have any money so yeah, what should I do? I think this is good. I
see, I see, I'm doing the same thing again.  I don't know, I want to stop, but I want to stop,
but even if I stop there, it
won't do anything, it's no problem, I don't
know, I
know, it's that, do you remember that box, it does
n't have to be yours  That's right, that's right, that's
right, that's right
, okay, okay, I get it, ohhhh, hmm, hmm,
hmm, I
see, now it's the preparation period, preparation, right?
And finally,
papa, papa, papa, papa, we'll finish it off, fight,
gagaomai,
ga, um, I think this is good.  What shall we do?
Well well well well well well well
[Music]
Who is it?
Sell it now, try playing it
now, try playing it I don't know yet, I don't know yet It's
a bit too early, no no no no,
Kari-chan
Maybe, but I don't know, Kari-chan is kind of blue, so it's super
Hetty, so yeah, I see, it's
not, but it's really
difficult to do while talking, it's really difficult, it
's not right ...
Please stop that, I'm watching anime now, I
'm watching anime, what anime are you watching, huh,
monster, monster, monster,
oh, 8, huh, I forgot a bit,
Japanese, it's really funny,
it's Kshiro  So, yeah, I know Bakumonogatari,
of course, I know, I've seen it, yes, I've seen
it, I've seen it, all of it, yeah, yeah, no, the new one, I have
n't seen it yet, yeah, the new one, it
hasn't been out for a while and it's finally coming out this summer,
yay, yay  I'll watch it, I'll watch it, I didn't
know you watched Chanba Monogatari that much, I really
like it, I do
n't mean I really love it, I just like it normally, I
think it's interesting, I love Araragi-kun, so Araragi-kun, Ragi-kun, Mami-san, that's
right, who  I like
it, but it
's not a lie, it's my butt, it's really
nice, it's really
nice, it's really cool, it's
a lot of people who like Senbahara, and Hanekawa is the same, so it's quite nice.  There are
n't many people who say they like Nako the most. I
think there aren't many. Actually, that's true, but her voice is also...  I
really
love it, yeah, I'm happy, yes, we have the
same diapers, right? That's right, when I was in high school, I watched
it a lot, I want to watch it,
and then there's the other
one that came out a lot later, I like it, I know,
that silver grey one, right?  Oh yeah,
wait a minute, that hair, yeah,
sorry, I can't concentrate for a second, please stop, talk, tell me when to press,
who do you like next? Yeah, I think I forgot, I
know, that's strong, that, that
hair color, yeah, I think it's really cute,
yeah  It seems she's saying "peace peace yeah
yeah" It's a voice that doesn't contain any emotion at all It's so
cute That's right It
's cute so no I'll stop Also
Kuji-chan is cute too I give up I give up
Snail Snail is
cute I'll do it I'll do it  It's the end
Oh wait wait I see Oh
let's
get started It's starting It's
really open It's
amazing It's
amazing It's stopped somewhere
But I can't seem to get it done. Let's go. I
spoke English. I just spoke English.
This game's broadcast failed.
Look, where is this safe place?
Where is this safe place? I don't know. It might be
over. It might be over.  It's
over,
but I've already won, I've already bought it,
wow, it can't be helped, I did it, it's good, it's dirty, I've already
finished, so the way he talks is really shitty,
so it's okay, there's no way,
no, this is also Kia at the end, seriously, oh,
good  It was a little different, no,
well, well, when I opened it, my face
was pink or red or blue,
so I made Kari-chan's pink color mine. Umm,
stop it, stop it, from now on, Kari-chan, you
don't have that pink hair,  It's turning blue. It
doesn't suit me. It
doesn't suit me. It suits me now. Okari-chan, yeah, I'm
getting ready for my live stream. Thank you for playing with me.
Thank you. I'm
tired, but it
can't be helped. It can't be helped. It
can't be helped.  I can't help it, my luck is pretty bad  It
was fun,
it ...  I'm glad everyone, I
had a lot of fun with all the different aspects of the game. Wow, Calliope, I'm super sleepy though.
Sleepy, sleepy,
sleepy, I wonder if I'll go to sleep again after the stream. Look,
everyone, that Calliope has some crazy
news, do you know? As you know,
Calliope has a new album, their
second major album, called Fantomime. I
want you to buy it.
There are a lot of great
songs, and I think it's the best Calliope has ever done.  It's the
best, I want it to be the best, look, the jacket art is
also amazing, Ray-san
did a great job, thank you as always,
and if you buy it this week, there
will be one with a signature on it, that
standard edition, that Calliope
website, Calliope Shop  If you
buy it on the website, you can buy that sign, the
standard standard one, I think, that you
can buy it, change it,
yes, I can
speak Japanese, I can't buy fortune telling after this week, I can't
do it next week, so I
think it would be better to win soon, that little
Calliope  It's a
small signature,
but I think it's nice. It's
not the main jacket, it
's the alternative jacket, right? This is it, um, this one.
Wait a minute, um, I
'll sign this one or this one. Yes, it's a small
signature, so it will be this week.  Please
buy it. Yes, please check it out.
And under this video, there is a
description section that says "Summary". Wait a minute, I
forgot what it says.  I
remembered it, I
remembered it, it's good, it's correct, I'm glad, my Japanese
has become really, really bad, but I'll
get better, so please check it out,
click on that URL, and buy it,
Calliope's new album, and that
really,
really good song  I'm in it, and I
wonder if I'm already wearing that anime song.
Yeah, I want it, so I'll take a look at it once.
[Music]
So, I
'd really appreciate it if you
could buy it, so please, I'm really
working hard on it, it's cool, thank you, it's
really cool, thank you,
everyone, thank you for your wonderful comments.  I
'm really grateful, thank you, really,
thank you, I'm really happy, so please look forward to it, I'm working
hard on Calliope, so I still
have to record it, so I'm
still working hard, it's a great
album, so everyone  I definitely
want you to check it out. So,
that's it. Today, I'm
going to do a live stream. I'm going to
sing in a relaxed, chill mood. It's just a warm
-up.
Yes, that's right. I haven't been singing much lately.  I'm going to
do some other work from now on.
Today was fun, wasn't it?
Thank you everyone for listening. Let's play again
. And please look forward to Kao too. Yes, that
was Mocha operation. Thank you everyone for your
hard work.  And then I'll go to Japan and
see you later.  Take
care of everyone Bye
Bye Take care Peace
Bye See you later
[Music]
Hey
Thank you That's good too Pa
[Music]
HH