[Music]
thank you
come on
[Music]
don't listen
good morning
[Music]
clowns
Jojo
[Music]
thank you
oh wow
hello
hello hello
[Music]
wanna introduce first yes
okay let's go
oh you got it hi more is here
I'm excited
oh sorry it's okay no problem
no problem more is here hi Jessica
[Music]
happy death Grim Reaper I'm here I need
to do my best for my team ID sports
festival let's go
yeah dude I don't know it's been a long
day oh Ralph Ralph oh wow
[Music]
hey gin one and I'm your feet not Lo-Fi
but you can't call me your Brio fee but
it's not love I am can I please
FYI I'm I think probably I'm not the
only uh I'm the only one who doesn't
open stream so you're free to watch from
whichever cool
[Music]
hi hello everyone my name is
wait um
the blackhead from whole life ID third
generation
remind yourself about your introduction
no I've never done any introduction in
my own stream
oh my God
[Music]
oh okay
[Laughter]
Indonesia generation one I am
part two in these guys I'm actually NPC
right now
you're doing it I can see your forehead
yes
next
[Music]
next hello I'm iron I have I have been
chosen as the produce team leaders
hi a good good day good morning good
evening everybody I am participating in
the soccer match and also in the
badminton with a teaming up with Kaila
so it's okay
is vital
s
[Music]
um
how about that
before we start I actually have a little
bit of uh
um
okay so uh before we start I have
something to announce that
Uma will not be here but but they are a
really diligent member so they already
practiced
um in the afternoon although there is no
stream and he also later on in uh one
hour from now uh hopefully sooner Senpai
will be able to join
[Music]
yay
what uh I think Muna here tonight will
help us as the market for several uh
some games nice PC okay
and also
okay so I will also explain about the
game first uh okay for each game okay
maybe it will be better if we go about
the teaming first
in particular team we have
um nine members including me and then
yeah
[Music]
many strong people are we so many pinks
we are strong
[Music]
one two three four five games
five games five games the first going to
be a a catch the four third floor
capture the four thank you uh and from
our team it's going to be uh Kyla me uh
yeah okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
will be me
um
[Music]
didn't you guys planning to change the
potato cigarettes
foreign
[Music]
Antonio
[Applause]
you're playing against the blue the big
the big blue yes so basically it's the
pink team against the blue team
[Music]
very strong and then there will be
badminton so badminton will be will have
two rounds basically
um
[Music]
and then last there will be soccer yeah
oh yes it's really fun
[Music]
[Laughter]
so okay so basically uh uh uh initially
it will be me but it's going to be
changed yeah
[Applause]
for soccer we'll be eovie
[Music]
and before before we start playing I
would like for everyone to go here
that's amazing
amazing
I would like to teach you
the colon response
okay okay okay okay
ready ready Captain I'm looking at the
let me look at those strips
I got the script I will I will read
everything first from the from the top
to bottom and then we'll practice after
that okay okay okay okay
so I will I will give example first
fight fight let's go
hey
[Music]
okay okay okay
to manage the delay I will I will uh
like uh it's okay to to take times to
answer so it will okay it's it's okay to
not be as fast as uh as how I did it
okay okay
um
[Music]
let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
what does it mean oh okay okay so
basically uh that one
is like the the storm
whatever okay like the strongest team
ever okay
is like uh whose team yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
cookies and that Aya is like
like yeah yeah
why why yeah it's like yeah yeah
Indonesia yeah yeah
let's go
all right
again I'm ready I'm ready okay ready
probably uh I wouldn't say it's probably
like most likely
um
enough kind of you're kind of gone
yes
okay okay
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
so uh which game do you want to try
first yeah
um
I'm ready for football
you're good yes
[Music]
change
people oh my God
these are that are copies of Muna and
Kaila they're fake
Sunday
[Music]
I feel like we should practice what we
will really be in the end okay so
basically who wants to be a keeper
because keeper is the only one position
sorry
okay what is this okay I'm just oh roll
okay I'm just gonna be standard too wait
okay I'm just gonna be I'm just gonna be
cool keeper okay minutes please oh
already already
we're good
so
[Music]
so there is uh like three items uh if
you are on basic there is like two shoes
green and yellow and if you're the
goalkeeper you will holding this
yay yeah
yeah this is for the goalkeeper so okay
uh for the goalkeeper
um if you want to get the balls you have
to click it so it's gonna be on hold so
yeah and
uh for the
basic one uh there's like two a green
and yellow the green is like a regular
cake and the yellow is the long cake
um and there is uh if you are on the uh
some special occasion that now you're
happy to kick to the gold
I forgot your name yes
it was like a final decisions kind of
thing so make sure 11 meter shooting gun
the eliminations the elimination
yes
there is there is like uh
you cannot use this one you can use the
yellow so you have to use the regular
the green one uh you mean the penalty
you mean where you stand in the corner
and then shoot or no no no no
in front of the goal in the center
ah where they line up so it is 11. yeah
sure thing okay yeah they line up and
they try to get a goal until yeah okay
okay
I
mean
thank you
[Music]
okay
oh
at least I can't be out of breath here
in this game
[Music]
oh
that was a good chick hey
hey no
no no no no no no no no
no
we're gonna get confused
okay
let's go
come on
title
are we allowed to go down there
I don't know because I don't know soccer
rules can we get to the goal can we like
possible is that allowed
okay
oh
no I cannot even think about it
[Laughter]
um
let's go yeah
yeah
it's gonna be like that
yes
oh
[Applause]
yeah
okay okay white team let's go
okay
somebody
else
[Music]
I like it
this is crazy
I will be the back Kiara will be ready
mmm okay
[Laughter]
no I have found my new Talent
oh
there is very good long kick apparently
like the pressure
okay okay
[Applause]
just take the ball I think
yes
oh yeah
[Music]
okay
no oh the fireworks are giving me lag
really
opened my door BRB
need to pause
ah
[Music]
oh no no no
let's go
[Music]
okay
it doesn't look like it are you on the
first game referee yeah yeah
you always have King a bit for like oh
two seconds
in the game
stop
I think
at the moment
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
sorry I'm back
sorry Amazon delivery Amazon
finished
this
game is only six minutes as requested by
risu
regular game will be on 20 minutes
[Applause]
I'm already doing so much better at this
than in Pokemon unite I'm excited
talking about
this morning so that hey natural Talent
okay
this again or moving again
[Music]
mode
the shooter now is free zoo like okay
with the green shoes okay
be prepared
[Music]
[Applause]
we got it who is this yes
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
okay I can't defend the goal right I
can't
you can't yeah
okay okay let's go okay
a second ago
[Music]
like that
let's go okay all right
I'll do this
card oh okay yeah me again oh my gosh
yes
[Music]
spectator mode
foreign
[Music]
that's what we needed
I'll try I'll try
okay hold it today
[Music]
I'm gonna hold the ball
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
ready ready ready
can't curve yeah try to curve the ball
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
this is is
um in the soccer are you in the soccer
game yeah I'm in a soccer game you
should be the goalie I don't want to be
oh okay yeah that's the only way I can
we can win all of us okay okay guys
more yes
I think I get a white again okay
wanna try it
okay I'm gonna be Striker you'll be
Striker I'll be good keeper
I'm the best soccer player in all of us
yeah because we suck in Austria we never
make it to championships or anything
Striker Striker okay
who
is this goalkeeper on red
huh oh okay should I keep her okay okay
thank you thank you
okay I think I I think I picked it
already I cannot change it oh can I wait
wait again okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
let's go I'm gonna make sure again
foreign
[Music]
are we going
there I was going
there
nice nice nice
wow
that's cute
yeah leave it to me
fun okay
no
[Music]
oh
nice nice oh Kyla's so strong
it's right
here
let me go back let me go back okay
no no no no no no no no
no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
[Laughter]
[Applause]
that's cool
come on come on let's go
no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
okay y'all are aggressive
got a B gotta be aggressive
nice yes
[Music]
oh
my God
okay okay
let's go
okay okay okay okay okay here we go
[Music]
yeah
okay oh so it's a cracked goalkeepers
continue yes
you must
[Music]
that was fun
no no
let freaking go wow
you guys are getting stronger oh yeah
[Music]
are you gonna be Penelope again dang
okay
laughs
absolutely Rick no no
thank you
okay
oh God oh my God everyone is getting
stronger okay
[Music]
gotcha all right all right let's go
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay I wasn't prepared
[Music]
thank you
Get Ready Get Ready Get ready ready
[Music]
come on
all right
yeah I touched
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
okay
guys
[Music]
what color are we gonna break let's go
red right okay
somebody
else
okay
can you guys give me a left-handed uh
bat please
everyone's good everyone's good um
okay everyone's good
one I think it's gonna be easier if you
press F5
[Music]
uh make sure you don't go uh don't look
up because when you look up it's gonna
be sword oh sure oh
yeah it's gonna be short it's it's gonna
stuck in your place it's not gonna be on
your open end please okay does that look
more straight
yeah it just looks strange focus on the
streets
[Music]
how do I know
good day
[Music]
okay
I see I see aim for the red
oh
my God
[Applause]
if you're not playing the game you can
fly don't worry about that
oh
[Music]
okay
I think I understand how long will this
game be in the actual uh tournament
20 minutes
[Music]
wow
I think yes
yes
I'm sorry this is difficult
we can practice more later okay
nice nice nice okay
this first person is better Chad they
said third person is better because you
see the shadow
oh really I didn't know that she said So
Right girls you said F5 for third person
is better
it depends on your preference actually
no no okay I'll try this one um okay I'm
trying F5 okay
[Music]
okay
does someone else
try it it's fine
I need to stay in um
[Music]
um
we need white one more
white one who is it no white white
okay okay okay
[Music]
let's go
yeah let's party
[Music]
let's go let's go
oh let's go okay okay
[Music]
thank you
okay
nice
[Music]
one Kayla when it's the tournament it's
on Sunday
right it was fun Sunday for me
that was pretty good yeah I can't
Saturday foreign
got it
it's nice nice please
um if they're shooting over to your side
for the first shot you should just let
it fall down to the ground
he's here
yeah very cool okay
let's go
oh
no you did it pretty far yeah
[Music]
where is it where is it okay
but I don't see the shadow but at least
I see the ball that's me okay nice look
s oh yes okay
okay let's go hit it hit it
on the ground for a second I'm sorry I'm
getting back to my side
it was it is
I'll be right I'll be right okay
just kidding I'll be left
it's fine it's fine just
follow just follow the Batman
oh
we shot you guys
bring it on let's go let's go
oh no oh
my God
[Music]
you guys win yeah
good badminton players
okay
let's go next game
Grace
[Music]
potato
ES
okay
yay but but fauna already practiced
right and so that's Empire is coming at
midnight oh isn't it now midnight none
for her I mean because soda already
practiced the other day so it's probably
she did okay
try okay
we can all try this one it's okay
yes because it's like three versus three
I don't need one
I'll join white the white okay I mean
two versus two is it good though why I
guess
[Music]
close your eyes
just one time okay
how does this
works
[Music]
it's so cute
oh no there's lava thank God I'm not
participating in this I'm never good in
these races
yeah there's no way
wait what
are you are you going the wrong way
Callie yeah
I went the wrong way oh wait no I was
pressing Ctrl
you'll be already in the second round
you passed me already but that was okay
because you were slow
honey
[Music]
what's the best route why am I so slimy
yeah so try it the best fruit
[Music]
how do you gotta reach the goal so fast
determination
[Music]
oh
my God okay the bounciness I can see how
yofi gets sick from this yes
we should
okay I'm gonna get sick from this too
being stuck in the bedroom
[Music]
wow
there's like no path through them
oh no I'm glad I'm not doing it again
[Music]
you can get through the cobwebs that's
about it
yes yes
I'm not in sync with my potato sack
do I have to do free laps
you can you can actually just just stand
there waiting for the other team to
finish it
okay
what am I flying
I don't know I'm done if everyone is
already gave up just tell me I can just
stop the game
yeah
this is really tough okay
okay okay
look at this okay the only one from our
team who's here right now who has to
practice this is Lisa right I'm gonna
finish okay okay I believe I believe
okay yes
there we go I finished
[Music]
it
[Applause]
may be making me sick but I have to say
it's a very cute original way to replace
a normal Marathon relay yeah
[Music]
let's go let's go
thank you
okay I need to practice this one
um
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
she stays up late
oh
[Music]
foreign
oh this one
I have no idea what's going on
obviously the Rope
it run okay run nice very nice uh
basically you need to like spam clay The
Crickets
unaware
we both didn't know what to do
oh I didn't join the team
um
you haven't joined yet hold on I'm going
down okay I'm going down
leave it to me
okay okay
piano
the whole architecture is insane I know
you know this okay Magic
[Music]
sneaky
strong arms no more noodle arms strong
arms
again again again again again
we have to win
let's go let's go
left side or right side either one is
okay okay
also tips from me you can actually pick
the furthest lever so you don't really
need to stay on the front lever okay
so you don't fall off so early I guess
okay
[Music]
if you want to focus more we can like uh
divide on different level left or right
yeah
okay and everyone needs a different
lever right yeah
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah
wait wait here we go
easy
[Music]
ah
um
[Laughter]
maybe I should be in the team well you
know okay well you know what happened
okay what actually I started doing
better when I changed fingers when I
change my fingers
[Laughter]
oh man
[Music]
this time I'm gonna try okay with the
other finger unless you guys never give
up practice until you make it okay yeah
basically uh you can actually I will not
lose this first stick with your
um pointy finger yeah yeah that's what
I'm gonna do put your finger I switched
Midway through so that the other one
gets a break but team the current team
red lineup is our homeban lineup our
real lineup so you girls gotta win
against team white go go go go go wow
I'm ready
you'll be
no I use my middle finger man it's good
yeah best finger Ichiban skin
[Music]
right seriously
Beauty
[Music]
also you can you can press shift so you
can you you barely move I think oh that
would be nice
I messed up
it's still moving I'm still moving even
holding shift yeah me too yeah it is
kind of but it's not like
but in small steps ah wait hold on
because it ah because I hit shift it
messed me up
okay
it's okay fine
it's fine
even more stats like who uh who did the
most pulls each member I want to see
exactly one one versus one
if we were using a game controller it
would be a different situation
on the button matching Queen like two
like space bar
no I mean I mean you can do it right
okay yeah even you can do it if you want
it okay
yeah
okay let's just try without Kyla okay
oh
yeah
okay
two versus two okay oh okay one more all
right
no without Kayla so yeah
[Music]
oh yeah and
um
um foreign
[Music]
I mean if you want to flunk versus one
it's okay though if you want to try I'm
gonna try white team okay
so white and Chihuahua white okay I'm
gonna play
let's go okay that's good that's good
[Music]
too okay
you're playing against Kobo you wanna
you wanna teach her a lesson right this
is so true
[Music]
yeah
oh yeah yeah we're gonna be against
Coldplay yeah imagine that and then you
will be so much stronger oh God okay
[Music]
all right traditional right
it's gonna teach you who's the Boss
thank you
[Music]
oh it's so close
to the the numbers then it takes so much
longer and now you guys have to hold out
longer
come on
[Music]
kind of lose it
we're leaving
[Music]
my finger
oh my God
team mommy already
ketchup but we're still leaning we're
still leaning okay okay
[Music]
oh my God
[Applause]
I don't know man my finger's giving out
one minute
[Laughter]
syndrome
[Music]
30 seconds
20 seconds
oh yeah okay okay okay okay like 15
seconds
yeah I don't know about this
we tried really hard
right guys
[Applause]
[Music]
your lives
I'm never doing this again
[Music]
already
yeah seems like we played them all looks
like it
one last one oh
the library
can I take a break because I'm not in
the game anyway
[Music]
hi everyone
maybe while we're taking break we can
try to
um the the yellow elephant
sorry Senpai is here but yeah yeah
[Music]
um
calendar
okay
um
[Music]
put it in here
so foreign
[Music]
foreign
okay
okay okay okay
um so
hello
[Music]
I am watching on the day who actually
gonna play me reasons and also there is
another thing as you can see
yeah
okay okay
okay that's up here I want to tell you
guys that be careful uh if you're on
your opinion land so as you can see this
is the center of the place
one that I am sitting right now is the
center place and this is the red uh
the Red Land and this is the white land
if you're white and you're going to Red
be careful uh if you met your opponent
because you if they get you you will go
into jail immediately
okay and it's also vice versa with the
others
okay your friend can help you to get out
of the jail okay please explain it in
Japanese okay
okay
[Music]
um
foreign
let's go
okay
damage
oh my God
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay okay
come on
[Music]
foreign
thank you
so much
[Music]
foreign
it's okay
Don't just run
so if you pick white you see that uh
White laser like to up to the sky yeah
yeah you need to go to the red one okay
okay I gotta go to Red okay yeah if
you're red you need to go try just try
to find a way
um
to the white and then if you see your
opponent just punch
easy
yeah all right I'm back in I'm back in
the game company Mass
[Music]
a who wants to go with red all right
guys
yes you you practice oh okay I practice
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
look at this okay
oh let's go
let's go
[Laughter]
[Music]
should we go together
okay maybe separate is better because we
have higher chances oh this is close
items
[Music]
oh oh
okay
can't you like remember
yep if you really if you if you can if
you want to remember you can do it I
mean I'm not in this but can the people
who are actually participating remember
yeah
maybe then you just gotta remember the
pattern and you win yeah but but there
are mobs right there are mobs I ran all
past all of them they didn't hit me once
yeah yeah
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
put one door somewhere
oh
I know where you're going okay
okay okay
we're gonna see we'll see we'll see okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
my best
worried but she wants to have a pink
team okay okay
finger
okay yes
nothing to ask first
[Music]
you're okay you're good yeah should we
practice the badminton again yeah
we are here right yes yes
okay we're gonna go to batam let's go
okay so three versus three
not two words only can play by two yeah
two who wants to play
I mean if you want to play treats it's
fine to scan actually yeah
and soccer then I think uh you can
actually lead this uh start game and the
stop game okay okay
thank you
okay okay
let's go Stato
Focus concentration okay
okay
yeah
should I stay more in the front yeah
[Music]
let's go let's go you don't expect it
okay I didn't I didn't think about that
one all right that was good
[Music]
oh dang
okay okay
[Music]
that was on fire
toy toy
ain't too much power
I'll go
oh yeah
[Applause]
Auto
[Music]
bah
because
you'll be minor
ity
in Japanese
okay let's go let's go
[Music]
you guys on fire hell yeah yeah let's go
let's go
this is fun I like badminton but it's
easier to uh
it is
okay okay okay there's no need to sweat
yeah I mean I still I was still sweating
[Music]
sweating potential
wow okay okay
[Music]
I'm gonna protect the front
so far
[Music]
oh my God
I'm not ready
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
nice it was fun it's good that's fun
practice again of course that was
already good much better than before
foreign
[Music]
hello
foreign
[Music]
I know hahaha
Korea
thank you thank you very much
thank you very much
[Music]
oinka
Orange
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]