every day
[Music]
is
take me away
[Music]
do you feel the music
i
[Music]
is
give me that
[Music]
is
me
[Music]
crazy
quick note that there is probably going
to be a director's cut released later on
so please look forward to that that will
probably have some fixes for some scuff
moments now enjoy
[Music]
your disguise never give me something
and don't think twice and i told you all
the things i would do but doesn't matter
when you chase off the pleasure you
can't have
[Music]
if you want it oh
my
tonight treat me like treat me like
ladylike
treat me like ladylike
oh yeah
[Music]
one
treat me like ladylike
[Music]
no
i'm alive still breathing stopped high
done grieving realized that to survive
someone's got to stand and fight and
i've tried to believe in only time steps
to bleeding i'm not waiting anymore i
know what i came here for
[Music]
i'm chasing and hunting and this time
i'm coming
[Music]
baby you don't even know me at all
i'm alive still kicking break the rules
rewrite the system and my story wasn't
done sharp a knife and cut the guns cut
the cord burn the witch and you'll
regret what you're missing and i'll take
it to the grave that's the price that
you pay
cause feelings are temporary
[Music]
[Applause]
me i'm chasing and hunting and this time
i'm coming
be the last one to love when you run
[Music]
baby you don't even know me at all
higher
[Music]
cause feelings are temporary
baby you don't even know me at all
[Music]
yes
thank you thank you thank you and well
welcome everybody first of all to my
concert uh i hope you enjoyed the first
two songs how was it how was it how was
it
thank you thank you thank you i hope i
already got you hyped up this is gonna
be a really fun show but a fun show also
needs some
special guests some people to talk to
maybe some call-ins some games and don't
worry i got you covered i have invited a
very special friend to play a very
special game together with and my friend
is none other than
my audience member
nadine
[Music]
[Laughter]
number one idol in my heart so i thought
that the following game would be very
fitting um so i fought out this game the
rules are the following first of all the
name is idol shiritori the normal
shiritori
works the following i say a japanese
word and they usually are built up in
syllables so the syllable that it ends
with ninety will have to think of
a
new word that starts with that syllable
and then we keep on connecting and
connecting until someone makes a mistake
or says a word that already has been
said but here is the twist we can only
use idle words or cute or girly words
feminine words so anything that's cutesy
and not only
yeah i think
us too we shouldn't have any issues with
that uh
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
uh
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
come on
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
what
good morning
is
[Music]
um
because i lost so we decided that
we both
we both win in the end yes well i may
have won twice and she may have won once
but in the end
we're odenz so all is good we love each
other uh world is beautiful world is
peace
[Music]
bye-bye
so let's go to the next song
[Music]
don't know what to do
don't forget what i said
out of your head life is only what you
make it you're gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know your name
[Music]
don't be afraid
[Applause]
[Music]
that's how we like
it everybody's gonna know your name
[Music]
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way so don't be afraid
[Music]
even when the flames
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
my name is perfection i
[Music]
make you a believer i'm so worldwide
worldwide holy virtual diva
but sometimes i do don't you think of
the things they told you there must be
more than this there must be more than
what you know too i wasn't made to feel
but lately i can't help it if there's no
way out of here i've got an idea
bring it all down i'll make it come
around i'll burn this hole
i'm sick of windows
[Music]
just kidding i don't feel pain
change your mind so quick you won't
believe
[Music]
is
am i ever gonna die
[Music]
all
do you think i right
none of this is
[Music]
as a digital girl
yeah yeah
wow
[Music]
hey come on
[Applause]
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
hey come on
me
[Music]
hey come on baby baby
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
one two three
[Music]
is
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
hey come on
[Music]
okay
m
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
my
is
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
all right everybody
how was that did you like the previous
songs it was
the bigaku from matsura aya and
kenyabino ohio from honeyworks yeah um
especially the the vega i was really
excited to perform for you guys because
it's a hello project song that probably
a lot of you guys don't know but did you
like it did you like it did you like it
it's pretty cool yeah
matsura is good
so
next up
we will have more guests more guests
more guests previously was an energy who
could possibly be my next guest what do
you think guys
well so it will be
none other than my beloved
[Music]
[Applause]
very happy thank you to for coming for
flying over here like the birds you are
yeah
well i'm already doing gestures but i
wonder
what are we doing with you guys what
could it be
charades or playing charades yeah yeah
the typical game that you have to play
when you're in 3d well i think
we have like a synergy
synergy
so whatever movement i do you will
understand right
yeah of course yes okay yes
okay actually
uh the words are provided by none other
than god who is somewhere behind the
scenes
so she will feed me with the words i
will
act them out and you guys will guess
them so shall we begin
yeah
yeah okay word number one
[Music]
almost
[Laughter]
snake
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
people
[Music]
[Laughter]
a juggling
[Music]
okay last word i think last word next
from last one last week last week right
okay last
chicken dance
chicken dance chicken
everybody wants to eat them
yes
i don't i don't
[Music]
no
um
[Music]
ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
you
me
yeah
[Laughter]
after such a winning streak i think i
lost
[Music]
it
this is
[Music]
[Applause]
but it's okay we're still there four out
of five
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you so much
uh turducken is best
yes
thank
thank you too very
[Music]
love you much
i'm tired of the same song
everyday like it's on repeat i need a
risky breakdown
[Music]
take me away like it's just the two of
us i'm ready
do you feel the music baby
[Music]
intoxicating dj klein
lately i'm dancing alone
so robotic so emotionless
but then
[Music]
something to keep me up all night
don't look away now it's just the two of
us i'm ready
do you feel the music baby
[Music]
the way
don't care who's watching us so
so new baby
don't need no drinks tonight
[Music]
crazy
wow
[Music]
tell me
i will live to keep on fighting
[Music]
don't break
foreign
[Music]
i've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray
could you tell me please
[Music]
tell me i can hear it clearly
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
i promise i will find you
uh for the first time ever performed
people died
once again my favorite night is uh new
very new my nearest single so i hope
you're
listening to a lot are you
of course okay if we always streaming
kiwamo songs thank you very much for
your support so
you thought that was done with collins
huh no no no no there's more there's
more there's more
[Music]
aren't we missing
certain myth members
yes we are of course we are so please
come and say hello to
guna and kelly
we wee
[Music]
you could say it's not my birthday but
it's my birthday
i get it you made a funny word joke
[Music]
attention looking so cute
finally finally like i can do my whole
i can show off my body 3d
like yeah the whole stream yeah
it's so detailed and beautiful oh thank
you
it's very nice
what's your favorite part
a tummy window
you can only see that in 3d
right and the little wings too are
precious
are you gonna pull out your sword are
you gonna get your sword out someday for
us oh that's a good question well maybe
another time maybe maybe at a 3d debut
stream which this is not
right
right right all right well girls we are
the same generation so one would assume
that you know a thing or two about me
right
yeah he's cool we've only met many times
yeah yeah yeah especially us yes yes but
have now met in real life thankfully yay
yeah
you have hopefully a lot of knowledge
about me and i will test that with
them
[Music]
i have five questions for you girls
and if you answer at least four of the
questions correctly
then i shall take you out to dinner
sometime
oh oh cool
she's gonna ask for a prize
of course it's a prize yes there's
always a prize at kfp
so are you ready for the first question
yes get it on by the way you can work
together if you want oh
what it is yeah let's do it yeah put the
two the two the two biggest brains in
the whole live myth together yeah this
should be no problem what are you
calling yourselves again the boneheads
no bone bros
[Laughter]
will solve all the questions
now we got this on luck it's just math
don't ask us about math no no no i don't
even know math either so
first question are you ready
yeah yeah
question number one
what does kfb stand for
kentucky fred phoenix
[Music]
did you say kiara kentucky no i i've
never heard of that place i said kiara
you guys misheard sorry that's your
ear's problem
i said kiara fred phoenix i i know kfc
i've eaten kfp before
i should almost give you a minus point
for that answer no no no no please don't
take away my my degree in qr algie
please
i'll give you that point that was easy
though it will get more difficult maybe
maybe maybe
all right next question i wrote it down
what is it
okay
question number two
yeah imagine some quiz lights quiz
quizzes
yeah
okay
what was
okay i a new rule i will uh only allow
correct answers if you had one if you
lock in one wrong answer that's a no
point
all right girl don't [\h__\h] this up yeah
all right like okay
okay so question number two what was
takanashikira's
second original single
heart challenger
i was gonna say that too
sorry goombas you need to give her some
time yeah to shine god needs to shine
okay girl the next one's yours i'll be
faster
i'm leaving the hard ones for gore
actually it's all part of my plan
[Music]
did you uh probably acoustically oh i
thought you said first no i thought it
wasn't something
sorry i can't yeah my mighty ass sounds
like an f
it's okay it's cute
not the three of my song was but that's
not the questions spikes yes okay good
dogs let
okay no that was not the third question
the third question is coming now can i
see it it was
uh okay okay now this one
let's see question number three
what's the name of
the mouse slash rat that i lived with in
japan
i feel like i've been told this before
oh [\h__\h]
if you know this oh no uh do you need to
phone a friend
okay casper
just recently uploaded a video a lore
video that explains the whole story
behind casper on my channel so if you
guys are curious you could go watch that
if you want to learn more about casper
mysterious yes casper the family yeah
yeah yeah first i hated him then i loved
him okay fourth question if you get this
one right then you already have a free
dinner with me
so thank you for carrying callie yeah
no you no you got this girl you
definitely got the next dude i don't
know if i do guys
okay question number four
how many
re-debuts
did takanashikiya have now think before
you s
yell it out loud
[Music]
wait what counts as a re-debut
well and not debut but debuts after the
re-debut
i do have a history refereedup there
hasn't been one in a while but there was
a time where
i had many reasons for many re-debuts
me
i might know this my brain wants to say
too but i don't know okay girl it's
brainstorm um
the next one was the german one right
right right right okay so i think it's
two you know what i think is two are you
sure yeah oh i think it's two dancers
okay well
i still have one more question though
your winner chicken dinner from the
chicken let's go i think we're four for
four so far yeah
but i guess my questions were a little
bit too easy so
now
the next question you will have to
answer correctly otherwise otherwise god
damn it
will
can we double down do we get dessert too
of course of course all right
excellent egg excellent last question
and how should we do this um
i want your separate answers
so
what happened wait don't change the
world okay i want no i just want to see
if you both get it right without hearing
the others answer first okay
i'll take off my headphones okay okay
okay ma'am um but wait no how do i give
you a sign that yoga should come back
whatever just bring it back in in 30
seconds okay okay do like throw up like
um some kind of weird like hand symbol
uh okay i'll do this do a little heart
yeah and then i'll come back all right
bye i'm taking over bye-bye
i actually have a feeling you'll get
this one right
really oh okay
spell out for me without thinking too
much you have to say it quickly
alf wiedersehen
go alph a uf
alf auf wiedersehen v
[Music]
all i heard was wrong
is it that hard of a question throw it
at me chiara now kelly kelly recently uh
had a lot of fun learning german with me
so you might [\h__\h] oh my gosh
the german question yes all right
buddy spell and you have to do it
quickly okay no thinking spell
my ending greeting alf bison
goes
hey
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] that's too hard of a question i
thought this was a chiara quiz not a
spelling bee
oh chicken
river dashie grazie mummy
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
i mean beep that out beep that out
whoever's editing this it's okay on my
channel it's allowed yeah okay
well you know what i said double down
but i'm still gonna treat you for dinner
[Music]
winner winner chicken dinner from the
chicken as in the chicken is the
dinner's from the chicken not the dinner
it doesn't mean that the dinner is um
a chicken it's it's from the chicken so
winner winner uh chicken i'll shut the
[\h__\h] up now thank you kiara happy
birthday thank you
wait okay what's the answer
you can't just leave us hanging oh yeah
okay it's a u s
space
w o e d e r s e h e n
alph auf wiedersehen
and i'm gonna start saying that from now
on auf wiedersehen since i just spelled
it out i will say to you girls
[Applause]
[Music]
all right on to the next songs go
all right guys no time for break here
comes
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
i
um
[Music]
with me
m
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
m
there's no one else in this world that i
would trade for you
[Music]
please
keep me
with me
[Music]
that was hard calendar
remember a while ago
at dokomi where i had backup dancers who
were doing the dancing for me and now
i learned it myself and performed it
myself yay that was fun i hope you
enjoyed that well you know if you look
at the time you might think oh it's
gonna be over soon and yep there is one
more song but before that let me say a
few words to you guys
yeah we're
getting close to the end and i wanted to
do something like this for a long time
as you probably know and i wanted to
show off my dance moves
for so long which is it's one of my i
guess most prominent skills and it has
been my dream since to start to show it
off to get into this 3d body finally be
free to do whatever i want yeah and the
day has finally come i hope you guys
enjoyed it so far
yeah
i want to definitely say a big thanks to
ami and inna and good
for helping so much with the recording
and the setup you know i'm gonna
basically build a whole studio for me to
record this in and i really really
really appreciate that and without her
it wouldn't have been possible at all
and also big thanks to kanaroo for
putting together all of this into a
proper concert and even creating this
beautiful stage here wow
look
isn't it nice
yeah thank you so much
future i really hope that i can do more
like this more often
and get more members to join me in 3d if
possible to dance together yeah
especially you know myth
with all of them i want to dance and
yeah have fun together and i think we're
getting there slowly but surely
by the way if you missed it the birthday
merchandise as announced it was
announced in the previous stream
and before this one the countdown stream
and it's linked in the description so
please go check it out
if you're interested
and yeah last but not least i want to
thank
kfp
you know how much i appreciate your
support and you believing in me
and trusting in me means the world to me
so thank you for giving me the strength
in this very very stressful period
leading up to this day
yeah
i think it was worth it yeah
so thank you for waiting for me and i
will continue working hard to give back
to you as much as i can please continue
supporting me and watch me grow into a
bigger bigger bigger bigger phoenix
yeah
now
there's one more person i want to thank
but i will do that with a song so please
listen to the last song
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
my
[Music]
is
me
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
oh
do
[Music]
you