waking up in shades of
blue I don't know where I am or how I
got to you try to reach out but I can't
move I'm like a broken instrument so out
of
to why won't they listen to me anyway I
want to be and I'm not going to say I'm
sorry just so you let me stay L whatever
you think of me leave it alone I don't
want to live in the shade of her
throne I keep
hearing of a Melody playing in my head
fragments of AAS they won't let me
forget someone that I used to be hanging
on the L silette I wonder when you look
at me who do you remember broken
memories I been together tell me
honestly do you recognize my voice
voice air so hard to bre the wall that
I'm facing is just too cold and too
lonely wishal feel to a feel of things
set back then I you still Fe oh I ever
want want to be accepted by you wish
that you and I still laugh and say that
something were will
why won't you listen to me anyway I'm
going to be and I'm not going to say I'm
sorry just to say face whatever you
think of me leave it alone I don't want
to live in the shade of her
throne oh I keep hearing pieces of a
Melody playing in my head fragments of a
past that won't let me forget someone
that I used to be hanging on the bre of
H is feel when I wonder when you look at
me who do you remember broken memories
time spent together tell me honestly do
you recognize my voice
voice it looks so off to me the picture
you paid the US I don't need to remember
let me be take me just as I am
everything
disappears I shout to heav say
[Music]
let me be take me just as I am
yeah let me be take me just as I am yeah
I keep
hearing little Melody playing in my hand
fragments of the past and they won't let
me forget someone that I used to be
hanging on a friend the blurry silouette
I wonder when you look at me who do you
remember broken memories how we spent
together tell me honestly do you think
that I could ever find a voice to call
my
[Music]
own bo bo
bo bo
[Music]