[Music]
oh
n oh
[Music]
he
yeah
[Music]
no e
oh
[Music]
yay hello wait did you
yay welcome
backen welcome to Eden
Eternal I got new fashion oh my good
gosh so pretty wait have you found this
sh well yeah yeah I've been I've been
hiding away though where are you don't
hide from m i I wonder where I am look
at pleas KP oh my God thank you for the
gifts you guys have been sending by the
way I collected them all out of my
mailbox yeah thanks for all the
gifts ah I look so cute I got a pop star
outfit and some other stuff I'm trying
to find you amongst the frogs and the
random actually I think I got some
things double too I think I got the the
sight double and the key the flame key I
got double I'll give it away a maybe
that's pretty cool yeah um and think was
some doubles too no doubles wait how do
I know which one I B right
there how how does one oh here's add I
have added you without your permission
without our
permission without the
permission where G I'm in the Middle
where are
you I see you sister sh that's you
you're the one you're the one with the
Grumpy Cat what yeah I so cute I am
sister shiori you must repent for your
where did you go I can't find you
anymore too many people here invite to
party show me your cat I am now in your
party yay I you were absolved from your
sins and I can't seem to activate
any I am absolved of my
sins Abol I'm absolved I'm
absolved three times I'm absorbed of my
[Music]
sins are you looking at the kitty cat
yeah all my attention is on the kitty
cat I'm lost again where's the beautiful
kitty cat oh I see
it it is so cute the
face it's
grumpy grumpy kitty so maybe you guys
have noticed that we're now not just
gigy and Wawa anymore but no she already
caught wind of us playing Eden Eternal
and you like it too I hear yeah I do
like it this is how I met some of like
my early friends
oh oh my God one remained don't typ over
us I'm going to sue
you okay sorry so Shion also took it to
took the the job a called herself to be
our healer right yes I will heal you
from your sins yay there are no sins I
am pure as it gets oh my God there's a
Phoenix Mountain above
us
you how expensive was
that girl oh my God that's a big Mount
oh my God I want
that that is a large large Mount that's
me oh wow that's pretty cool you know
sometimes people send me like tweets
every once in a while there's like a
phoenix sighting in the sky somehow have
you seen one of those before I don't
know what what is it fireworks or just
some cloud formations or whatever with
the sun setting and then they're like oh
my God I saw you oh my God you were seen
in like Mexico oh my God you were seeing
here and
there no no no no no that was not me I
don't think I've seen it I want to see
really every once in a while I want to
see a phoenix
hiding maybe maybe I'll fly you want to
see a phoenix setting I'll fly over to
you
yay so can you can you like do delivery
too when you go over yeah can you drop
off some food while you're here what I
would love some food I'll drop you I'll
drop you some K of tea some chicken
nuggets
yeah that would be
good okay so today we're going to grind
a little bit more but shielding is a
little bit uh below our level so I don't
know you you going to like join us on
our Quest off your XP except like the
dungeon depending if it let me go
through we can do the your main story
Quest so we have to watch story Quest
I'm
on they want me to do the ancient Water
waste but I have to do that so solo
which was like not a requirement but it
says solo but when we're in a party and
we join solo as well we're actually in
there together oh really oh that's
pretty that's Prett very convenient very
misleading but very nice well I got to
go to the ancient waterways I think
that's like in the swamp which I have
forgotten where cuz I can no longer
teleport oh yeah they take it away from
you I know want you to pay $1 for it or
something I know oh my God
$1 $1 for
one uh teleportation or for all
teleportations I think I think for all
of them I'm not sure no that's I mean
acceptable okay one request today wait
unlimited for a week
oh still cheap enough and one request uh
guys don't right click follow me you'll
always be like in my screen covering up
a lot so try to follow me manually okay
and give me some
space okay not not you girls I mean the
the
kfp
oh okay there's a lot of them I met a
kfp of yours earlier they're like oh
grinding off stream I
see it's probably cuz they added you and
they knew where you
were they're observing our actions okay
how do we get to my inventory how wait
wait in the swamp what's the swamp
region
called uh I don't I don't remember hold
up where's the portal I do not remember
anything I remember I think it's around
yeah around the corner outside yeah oh
you you're riding a huge
bunny yeah I think Rainbow Forest that
sounds like a place that would have a
marsh in it rainbow rainbow full Forest
okay
yeah I'm on my way I got to go find the
tassos channel tassos channel okay T
channel the top right of the map just
just right click the wait do you have
the quest
now I have the quest okay yeah just let
let it lead you automatically yeah I got
to defeat Juan and
Angela okay I with you am warping to you
what once I get to it no I have to go
walk to the air balloon and find my way
over I'm sorry to hear that I know why
don't I use my
legs wait I lost you oh it's just at the
top right um from the Rainbow Forest or
rainbow rainbow fall Forest oh there oh
okay so I just meet you guys there
Castle Channel it
exists okay going in a
Circle okay I think I where am I I'm
there uh are you hitting the outside
mobs
first oh I'm at the uh complete right
you're kind of close though complete
right if you press M and then look for
my big giant blue ball then you should
be able to find me big giant blue I see
it you're GI blue ball you got a blue
ball it's the biggest ball yeah I only
have one ball though cross from here you
must be doing well in no not my God it's
a
mountain oh no I'm doing
horrible yes the big ball keeps growing
and growing I know it's going to keep
growing until the end of
it oh look your alpaca it's all
Halloween yeah thank you I love
alpacas yeah it's so cute I collect
alpaca just wait for the CH know I'm on
my way I got lost cuz there's a mountain
can't believe there's a mountain look at
you let me look at sh shooting
yeah I wish I could look at you too but
there's this guy
the what did I tell you guys about
taking keeping some distance okay wow
beautiful wow you're so you're like a
Christmas angel
actually I'm what I'm a pop star okay I
like the angel you would put a top the
tree just like SP on top I love the
bunny the bunny thing is that oh you
paint with it it was gifted to me oh not
not that bunny the the bunny the bunny
is so large the bunny brush I know I
know the the bunny paintbrush right
actually was first released too now my
account is gone
though hey how long did you play back in
the
day um I assume maybe like a year from
like when it started like the release
oh no I don't I don't know about the
release part but I I remember I remember
like certain events and like World
bosses and
what like they have Halloween bosses and
everyone has to get together to kill it
and it takes a really really long
time nice so we're all experienced in
this game to an extent to to some extent
yeah nice all right uh do you need to
get into the dungeon
now uh is G here I'm here she's also on
an Al okay you're just you're just so
short I can't find you no she's actually
taller she's flying above me you're
sorry so
short I assume I assume I go here and
then and then you guys are good yeah
yeah yeah do we just walk in all right
oh there I I am in the solo experience
oh yeah it does work I didn't know that
yeah so large guys have same colored
Wings all right good luck
We'll Kill Them All For You I already
forgot what my buttons are for
Shing let's go accidentally typing in
chat let's let shielding Lee off of uh
our exp at least I hope pulling
everything oh she's pulling it all again
oh no she is one of those people I'm
pulling all of them not even she's not
maybe maybe you are that you're not even
a tank I know but she
she's got some
AOE I
know what a typical MMO
move of the
Healer we should let her die shooting no
no so that she will learn her
lesson I don't know I feel like you do
do they give charms I feel like they
might give safety charms don't touch it
don't touch you oh thank you thank you
at least someone has my back
don't worry I'm killing it so it can't
touch you in the future in in the future
thank you in the future I'm looking out
for your future interest oh thank you
can you also pay for my college tuition
then if you I can
try but you can't go very far okay I'll
miss you too much you have to stay
within the state I have to I have to
travel remotely I see yeah yeah you have
to commute from home or I won't pay for
your your college wow what a what a
typical pair
you have to stay
home are you getting good
exp oh I have no idea honestly am I
getting good XP someone keep an eye on
my my
percentage I'm still getting good this I
don't need that I I wish you could pass
instead of greeting yeah cuz it feels so
greedy yeah you can pass you just to the
X yeah oh yeah like I don't need the axe
cuz I'm doing certain things oh I am
going to
inventory oh we're done wow that was
fast good
job nice I got to talk to S Sid s s si
si s like a son of a well son of in a
[\h__\h] sun in Sun
in no what is he doing in there how do I
get to S actually oh there you go I have
to left
click I will
follow wait where did you
go oh I'm I'm outside I'm about to head
to H look for my big ass bunny yeah
there's so many shiny people but the
bunny definitely
helps yeah it's oh my God it has a cute
little animation that
hops such a large cute bunny I know it
also takes large poops I'm heading to S
did you get that like did you did you
buy that or did somebody give it to you
oh no no I me spend on an
MMO oh no it was it was gifted to me
although I did spend like once here
probably oh I was trying to get a
masquerade
outfit recently or in the past I no it
was like in the past I don't know if I
have it at the moment wa where did you
go but there's this really pretty I lost
you oh press M press M I'm heading back
to town really oh she went so far
already
oh I'm hopping away I don't know why
your your bunny disappeared from our
view yeah right it's a camouflage bunny
I was following the Bunny and the bunny
left us and now I don't know where I'm
going you and
spirit I'm trying to find your blue
ball just just press M it's in town oh
you got there so
fast I'm sorry it's just so fast
possibly
fast did you find
siib I did yeah it's a frog dude
oh after that I don't know what quest I
have like what what quest I should do I
can go to gos mountains are you guys
there are we I think so I remember being
gos Mountain oh yeah gos Mountain was
one before Beluga Bay mhm okay well I I
got to go head there now if you don't
mind unless you want to do your Beluga
stuff now we can go with you to okay I'm
going the Goss let's go a there the
teleportation gos Mountain wait what
thought it was we about to gos about to
guys gossip gossip about what gossip
gossip about did you see the new
MERS oh yeah people said one of them are
is like my sister it
why from the color SCH and the black one
I think it's a two-toned hair probably
oh oh they're so cute they are I was I
was so caught off guard cuz I I
literally did not see the announcement
oh the the announcement I it was the
same I didn't know when they were coming
I didn't even know that there were any
coming I didn't know that it was like
coming up at all because they posted
like like some GTA related thing right
after it and I saw the GTA related thing
but I didn't see that like
what but there was also the problem that
it's like it's in Japanese and then you
had to skim just to find the English
part yeah yeah I was I was shocked when
I saw that I was like what what what
what shouldn't I Beed Twitter then you
see it and you're like what's going on
yeah no I saw the I saw the the the
teaser yesterday with like uh the
regloss members and then said something
about flow and I'm like what that looks
like new members I have to admit Flo's a
a weird name to it's
interesting probably because their
lyrics will be flowing and they will be
glowing on the stage right bars bars
bars
bars maybe that's what it is yeah regos
felt a bit weird too at first maybe but
now it feels like normal oh and then
it's actually like devis it's devis
isn't it oh device instead of device I
thought they saw they call it as device
though it was something it's not device
yeah it was something not in I don't
know
it it's it has to be it's whatever you
want it to be honestly I I call it
devast I call it de my bad that's my bad
you don't have to call things the way
they're intended to call just like how I
it's a nickname yeah it is come on
De did you did you guys see to be like
David when I saw the the was it a tiger
tiger girl yeah she's wearing like uh
jogging pants sweater sweat
sweatpants uhhuh amazing and it gives me
like you want for yourself no no not for
myself myself but I I love the the chill
Vibe of wearing sweatpants for your oh
default form but yeah I was thinking oh
my God that style with next to ban sire
I don't know I feel like there's a good
Synergy there and also yeah she looks
really tall and she's blonde and her her
art style I feel like will have good
Synergy with Kyla so I want those two be
to be next to each
other and then she got the same kind of
eyes as Raa so I want her to be next to
L too
so much good
Synergy yeah tiger and lion perfect for
those two tiger lion and then big
cat good combinations why are we here
are you do you have a quest gy the H
these yeah I got to kill a bunch of
gorillas for no reason they are here the
Batwing gorillas I don't even remember
if I had a quest for that
I also don't remember wait how many
optional quests do you have these are
just like I think this one's required oh
holy crap it's so bright why is the Sun
so bright
here the sun came out yeah maybe I know
but that was way too fast for the sun
darn deserts oh good God the
bloom when are they debuts they're
tonight bro no on Sunday
no I think no no no on the ninth on the
nth n
oh that makes sense a weekend yeah you
always got to give them a few Twitter
only days where they're just chilling on
Twitter let them warm themselves up
translate what they have
said they have I don't know what what
have they been saying what kind of
people are they I need to investigate as
well something in Japanese probably that
I can understand yeah I'm was staring at
them but I can't read their tweets
there's one person bit of English they
said like I Google translated this like
I should reply
to hey I wonder if anybody can speak
English from them that one girl
apparently not
so I think Rica is like a a rare one
mhm I guess so yeah it's it's a rare
thing that's fine they can still learn
English or they can try their best with
passion
English well if you just make them Lear
Spanish
yeah we Spanish
speakers yeah bring them on actually is
it it must be really rare to have maybe
a Japanese person also speak Spanish
thinking about it cuz the vowel
pronunciations are really far
away what does this say is is this a a
pet or a player gorilla F who the heck
do I need to
kill how did you manage to look like
that
like
what there's this like big gorilla here
looks
like like not like the
other characters that I've
seen big
monkey monkey monkey I feel so weird
hearing the screams of the
gorillas wow you still oh you're there
now can
I click a how right that works ah you
can click on a point on the map and will
move you there did you know
that yeah oh my God quality of life amaz
it's been a
while yeah it has how convenient it's
okay it's okay I follow I it's also nice
that they lower the requirements for
when you need to like kill things I
think back then you had to kill 26 of
something oh yeah that I I I think I
remember that
suffering quite they have to adjust game
for the times you know yeah true the
Zoomer Times short attention span
exactly well how far did you get into
the game by the way like was there a
particular map you stopped uh I I just
remember I was like max level and all I
was doing was like raiding and and Guild
Wars and stuff like that PVP wow yeah I
was so addicted to all of these anime
MPGs and once a new one came out I just
switched to the new one and then I tried
to grind as hard as I
could I was a pro you abandon this one
huh this one but now we're bad well I
didn't abandon this one but you know
things happened it abandoned us yeah
yeah yeah honestly it did it freaking
did did you ever play maple
story are you asking me or we should
play maple story I have never played
maple story there really really big
event that's in two weeks and it's the
best time to start maple story you want
me to that
one it's a really big event what's the
what's the event though um it's like
their hyper burning event where uh for
until Level 250 you level basically
twice per level or like so it's like
plus two on top of the level so you go
in increments of Threes And then you
reach end game well not end game but mid
game faster are you going to Beluga Bay
right
now uh I have to turn in a quest but
I'll come back there so let me just turn
in everything I have cuz I cannot Auto
teleport okay
okay A little mashing of the keyboard G
are you doing quests no I'm just hitting
things while where I'm
standing maybe I'll try to are you guys
about to do a dungeon for your thing
I don't know I don't have any Quest
right now at all oh
really you can uh you can pick up your
quest or like some some side quest I
don't know what you guys
up no I'm waiting for you no no it's
okay it's okay cuz I'm doing like all
quests I can so I can level up faster oh
okay even the side quest the the small
on yeah yeah oh actually I found the
main quest that I didn't do yet aoda
too which Quest is that one m Roa 2
level 23 you H it's it is a it
is it it's something with a dungeon oh
yeah it's a dungeon Quest I do the
dungeon we can do that one too what the
heck why did I not do that one
yet there we go I am traveling across
the
land Isn't it nice I like traveling
across the land with my
Mount it's no until like everything
starts chasing you and then you die but
I don't think they do that healer so
squishy I know I'm squish
squish okay I'll wait by the dungeon I
suppose isn't that same map yeah it's uh
at the top right of the map
aoda why are you hitting me Oh I thought
that was a player that's an
NPC no no players can't hit you unless
you do I know what where did that come
from ah here there's another
person must kill level me up must kill
still not level I will come stand by the
dungeon
to okay
welcome on my way level how do I click
there uh are
you oh okay I had to aoda oh aod
at least I hope I assume I can did we
not go into this dungeon giggy last time
we missed it I'm not sure I think we
missed it for real maybe that's an
optional one H it does say main quest
but I don't think you even have to do
any of the main quest
anyway oh wow there's so much like Lion
King
here all right I am here do as you wish
I will try to join
uh are we going in I guess yeah Solo
solo do you have the quest right I don't
know uh I do not but I will run it I am
allowed to run okay oh I remember this I
got the quest in the city you remember
this I don't have the quest it's okay
though I'm just getting XP I think so
really so erona solo
yeah Solo solo okay wait is this is this
again H where I need to talk to someone
first wait wait wait wait I might have
to talk to someone outside first again
take your time take your time not like
last time I remember this place oh yeah
oh yeah vaguely I think there's poison
in here maybe vaguely remember or maybe
I'm lying no there's no poison here I
lied this was not the
dungeon oh GG's already starting put I
can my I canceled my cast no no it's
okay you're going I canel my I canel my
cast I'm back I'm back welcome
back all right go my tank I I'm
going the music in here is so cute what
the
heck by the way why do they want the
cleric leave the cleric yeah why are
they hitting you hey why why are you why
are you aggroing them sh what are you
doing wrong
I don't know maybe you're standing too
close no you're standing too close no no
you just don't hit hard enough they
thought you were
pathetic I'm not pathetic no this just
means we need one more person to join us
and be the tank for us a real
tank I like this song actually
M it sounds kind
of like nightmarish or Halloween is dude
why don't you like Halloween you should
like it I love
Halloween you AR growing them again
leave me
alone okay oh yeah she I wanted to say I
saw your nun outfit so cute oh yeah yeah
oh my God like it it was blinding my
eyes I I can't help it just
Sunshine it was beautiful
salvio your salvation has
come yes you will be absorbed of your
sins from Sister
Shori yes uhoh I'm not resolving that
sin
[Music]
though talk to [\h__\h] ah oh there's
dinosaurs what kind of quest is this the
NPC is behind
me oops oh crap you're far away well you
don't need healing right now anyway I
think
put this dinosaur here I don't
know is it gooy
B in her Halloween outfit actually a
cave Dragon they're
different my bad it's not a dinosaur
it's a dragon yeah those are
extinct I this is just a
dragon a dinosaur related
one day we will get a
dinosaur in
Hollow a real one that looks like a
dinosaur and is a dinosaur it talks like
one too
yeah oh I meant
[Laughter]
okay I meant a grill a grill no no we
are getting a
[Music]
dinosaur a real
dinosaur and then and then she'll let us
like ride her so she can be our Mount
too yeah yeah yeah and
she
arms I can't wait for her dance practice
she'll be so cute oh my God on the big
stage and then she's just she needs all
the space she can get and then she just
eats the whole audience because she's so
hungry oh my God I'm so excited
well technically she could eat your kfp
they look pretty edible
no they do look tasty yeah tasty if I
had to pick one to eat probably them
dark dragon jeto that sounds like a such
a Juno
name he's got a bow o nice why did he
not use
it uh I'm a cleric build oh crap no
leave me alone I'm too leave her alone
for this
die okay dang what is this thing under
theg ground that doesn't look very holy
for sister shiori touch it touch
it corruption
Arc you cannot corrupt what is already
corrupted I thought you were a sister I
am a sister it doesn't mean I lead a
holy
chap what kind of Chapel is this I who
knows for you guys yeah is the Pierce
guy outside no wait the Pierce guy why
is it leading me there no it's probably
just outside m not works
sometimes get me out here this the
fantasy setting and then there's just
like these meccas and these cars that go
the the desert yeah I mean the the the
one like it sha the the car doesn't
really fit in so well I think with the
mount I know it must have really good
Wheels though to be able to run or like
in these
true areas
true oh I got to kill more dinosaurs
now not the
dinosaurs oh sorry the dragons actually
these are
DRS okay I'm kill I'm sorry for anyone
named Drake my quest
I can't get on my Mount Pierce yeah you
have to do it from your inventory it's
finicky so
evil it's evil Eternal I don't evil
Eternal I don't want any of these I'll
take
this achieve and accomplish chenana hero
what
nice but I guess cuz I did the dungeon
here
nice okay m
shene are you doing a
quest yeah I got to kill this dude named
Maus what quest is that it's just uh one
of my main ones what you call it's not a
dungeon though the fifth clue of the
Lost Civilization
oo okay and then I probably have to run
the dungeon that we just
did perfect I'm just assuming right now
that I will eventually have to do it
again no
problem I'll get another little small
Quest if I I think I still have a
couple I'm going to go be a mage so I
can kill things are you switching to
Mage now it is kind of frustrating to
level like healer
classes yeah it is like I'm trying to
kill things fast yeah got to level all
these classes that's why you always got
to like
go around with a partner who brings you
through and fights everything for
you which could be us it could be us
we'll be that for
you I'm killing I'm killing Devils do
you need
this oh I I need a rock claw DRS now oh
I need those too again okay there you go
I'm also doing unquenched first
interesting ooh so thirsty
huh my first can never be
quenched I am born thirsty never never
ever that's nothing we can nothing we do
will quench The Thirst you have nothing
you can
do D what if I try really hard to quench
that
thirst I don't try harder that's
pathetic talk it's not what if is I
will I will okay I like the passion will
quench that
don't worry give it a try
then okay kind put my leg up on the wall
no what flips her
hair flips flips her
hair we're going to see some more weird
fan art
gigy I'm using the one where I'm
grabbing your ass I saw I saw it's
beautiful it's so beautiful beautiful
you mean yeah it's
beautiful and then there's just half
invisible non Shi in the background have
you seen the meme it's like I consent
and then there's like is there someone
you forgot to ask I think I did see that
before you're such a meme Lord let me
find it I'll send it to
you quest done what are these alpaka
tokens and why is this the first one I'm
getting the heck what does alpaka tokens
do collect 10 and trade them for an
alpaka mystery capsule oh you may have a
chance to win fabulous costumes oh there
fora
heyo what cash shop gotum no way you
could get that so
easily actually they were pretty lenient
with things uh at some
[Music]
point cuz they gave you free outfits I'm
pretty sure they just couldn't be died
ah ah yeah true true true I wouldn't
mind using my
money now that I am grown ass adult no
honestly just the payment option is
stopping me yeah it makes it so
difficult I remember when I was younger
um I think I also didn't have like
anything proper to pay so I went to the
store and bought the pay safe cards
aw with my little money I bought like 5
Euro Five Buck pay safe cards
and just got whatever I could
get there thank you thank
you uh gorilla
F good all I just one as a single
[Music]
player is it a
dungeon I think so Shale Cavern I'm
going to level up I'm going to level up
I'm going to level up are we going to
have to go to
yeah you can you guys can come we must
help our Tavern main on my way oh I
wonder if we can get a quest for that
too if we
already yeah probably I just spammed all
the quest
here wait let me finish this Quest if I
can just run over
there run geky run with your Spots I'm
running spotu
my SP and beautiful
Alpa uh so where's
shielding I'm a sh Cavern aha
oops okay let me just uh redo my hot
keys I just changed into like a Bard
here over here hot key but I don't have
any b b CL class
skills tornado AR that's it I got
nothing else how am I supposed to kill
things I have
arrived shieldings C
Cavern a maybe I can't be a b yet I got
a grind someone kill things for me I'm a
Bard okay okay okay okay okay uh I'm
killing thank you go faster faster I'm
killing as fast as I
can you call that fast that's pathetic
I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying
I want to unlock B classes so I can sing
and be annoying B so cute I need useful
for like hiding but they changed things
I think they changed it why so you could
spam this uh burn skill and it was
instant so what people would do is they
would spam it kite and everyone in the
party would help kill things I remember
doing that yeah it was so useful and
then people would get you to pay them so
they could do it for you really I don't
remember that and then they took it out
oh speed that's evil will you
accept huh except what you got proposed
to look at your top left or so oh no
what I do is I leave them
hanging El to propose what you just
leave it
open well yeah yeah because if I ask
that someone else might propose right oh
is that how it works that is true
I appreciate you thank you currently
being proposed to please wait until she
makes up her mindate you you're
[Music]
amazing okay I'm in the dungeon I'm
going okay I come
there let me let me switch to my cleric
as well I can't wait for Shaman I can
kind of be lazy as a
shaman chill
Cavern okay I'm here yay I
attack attack oh this what's this
one but it's cloth
armor I didn't expect this in the desert
I guess I should actually she rejected
me let's
go actually we do need a fourth player
to join us you know do you know why we
need a fourth player to join us cuz when
me and gigy Mary then sh will be like
alone and third Wheeling she needs a
fourth
wheel it's okay I can I can want to get
married why
why maybe they allow triangle marriages
here in this game I I don't know about
that love is beautiful we need to get
married all of us oops she only likes to
watch okay is that what if I just do
like the I make an alternate account I
never use it and I just propose to
myself well I think you have to be
online at the same time though well no
you can just make two accounts yeah but
you got to be online at the same time I
different locations I guess I don't
think you can send a proposal to someone
who's offline and then the other person
receives it when like uh got same
character and account I see yeah yeah
they're going to be like this isn't how
are you proposing to this offline person
are you sure you're proposing to a real
person can't do that supposed to a
bot you remember those Bots where like
uh you can buy for levels or something I
mean I don't I never saw like where you
can buy them but I saw them running
around and like Fly for Fun in the
beginner area running around do you know
Fly for Fun Dam it I've heard of it
that's the one we can fly I think yeah
on the skateboards on the snowboard
skateboards those were so fun that was
like my first anime RPG
trickster I also play trickster I never
I never I wanted to play it I never got
like too far though NE I was alone yeah
me too and I didn't understand
anything yeah say oh crap no please I'm
just a Healer I'm just don't worry don't
worry I'll take care of
him look at me look at me guy oh good
God why does he so into me wo
maybe it's cuz of your cat Want You O I
can use that yes take it take it g did
you just ran past the boss I feel like
you did that last time we were I didn't
see it I you did the same thing before
only K went for it didn't even see the
boss you have an illness that's called
boss blindness I think she she she's too
short to see
things it Blends
in yeah I did not call G gigg but maybe
I should call her giggity giggity ooh
ring what is this we got to talk to n it
has G healing take it
Che I will I will take
whatever oh I need to I need to enter
this dungeon in multiplayer mode not
solo mode what the heck but same thing
do that too we can do it too okay it's
pretty fast after
all yeah let me just get out of here
here but right now you you did it uh
like solo uh like I had to do solo okay
mhm we I'll do it h cuz yeah maybe you
can immediately accept the daily Quest
from the soul Guardian cuz the soul
Guardian gives you a daily quest to do
it in multiplayer
mode is my notice
or oh
yeah yeah the guy right there this sh C
the soul
Garden okay all right I accepted it well
a player let's go I'm going my crap
Y is multiplayer a little
harder higher up oh yeah it might be
they feel are they hurting more yeah
technically they should that's why uh
there you go makes sense
yeah they expect four people for this
yeah they're hurting
me well I hope you like
it I do and then I have a beautiful
angel who heals me right
after yeah damn it I should have been
healer now I missed the times of being a
Healer being you get all the compl yeah
I don't know it feel like it's not a
great ful work I think people are
ungrateful usually usually I feel like
people were grateful and I could just
feel like like a girl girl when needed
one cuz I never no one ever wanted to be
the healer I always wanted to be the
healer that's good I never wanted to
take the the sword into my hand and cut
people's throats and see their blood
dripping I didn't want to do that you
know I wanted something more peaceful
you want be like a paladin yeah no not
my kind of
thing if anything
ma than
magic this time this time I'm
Cutthroat this time I'm coming for
blood we
[Music]
kill I want to be damage
dealer I want to be op yeah I like DPS
too I like being a hunter I think mhm
mhm in this game or in like any kind of
game uh usually feel like being a gunner
in games oh
crap heal
me I am I
am it
hurts uh thank
you help why are they hurting so much
now this is
multiplayer it's not a walk in the park
anymore yeah I keep on hearing T what
you can get the the those sounds like
keep on sounding like World of Warcraft
um merlocks to
me you hear
it sometimes well that also sounded like
a
merock gremlin I think you're too
squishy Gigi no no no it's fine I have a
beautiful healer you can't be so cocky
anymore now I know not a tank take
everyone
okay she's still she's still running so
fast as if it depends on I see it I see
it I see the the boss now wow I see the
boss now why' they put him there he's
hiding maybe you will regret seeing it
soon he going to kill me
uh I know we're doing
good ow
is that like is that magic circle on the
ground from you girls or from the Enemy
No it's from them oh whenever you see
like those dark circles just assume it's
from them it's been a while oh they Dro
better items and more items lots of
stuff wow nothing that I
need goodbye oh wait oh what
okay mhm mhm Gigi just run
it it's
I'm
dying I'm
dinga there's a
Revival don't worry don't worry want to
go oh good God oh
[\h__\h] oh no don't wipe the party don't
wipe the party where's Kara I'm here I'm
I'm here behind you oh Jesus Christ no
don't die don't get even more mobs also
no what the heck no can revive in a
dungeon I forgot yeah I'm I'm somewhere
else I have to walk
back just run Kiara I'll heal you how
after I heal myself just run back to the
entrance okay I'm dying I'm dying I'm
dying run run run where's oh
y I'm on my way have you have you
learned your lesson lesson not learned
oh no K it's okay I'll I'll revive you
if you just want to chill on the ground
right there yeah but I don't know if you
can get here with old enemies oh Jesus
Christ I Jesus Christ I canot they're
coming after me they're coming after me
why are they coming after me um oh
because accidentally texting in chat
they ran to the last person left in the
dungeon who's still alive what'll it'll
be me once I get
there I I can use my Revival item oh
Jesus Christ don't use the Revival it
why not it doesn't revive you with the
dungeon
oh i r all the way back oh okay I'm in
the
cavern I I'm here I'm here I'm here too
I'm going back
in
don't that brat that shaky brat
so no no no please serves your rights to
die back here this instance young woman
there's a giant Guardian right here mhm
oh actually I think if you take too long
um mom's also respawn yeah oh I was like
why are they behind
us well no that's uh that's because
we're doing a multiplayer session I
think recruiting
tank for future
dungeons
lft owie girl girl owie
don't D him away so much ow
[Music]
owie shoting just have your he I need to
buff you constantly on
gigy always heal
her can't I can't heal you if you keep
running yeah same I can't attack you if
you keep
running you guys saw already have like a
a heal buff
anyway oh yeah those beautiful Buffs oh
oh yeah heart truth that's what gigy has
to learn close to
me no worries I I'm I'm not like her I I
believe in Kiara is
G oh she's so squishy I think you're too
squishy no I'm not I'm not
we need to put you on the leash ow ow ow
yeah or we just need to break your legs
how much HP do you have actually I only
have like a 100 more than you but maybe
maybe my defense is also no cuz you're
agroing all of them probably better it's
just cuz you're AGG gr them and they
constantly only hit you they hurt they
hurt so bad one at a time one at a time
what are we slow dungeon clearers see
this is what I mean by being a cleric is
ungrateful we have we have a cleric we
can take more yeah I I would use that
logic normally to yeah
yeah he doesn't even get to attack yeah
yeah kill him kill him he let's go let's
go nice nice button
mashing mhm
mhm mhm mhm there we
go y
o m crit magic uh more
magic
magic they're all like magic stuff oh
you destroy this you destroy this thing
maybe this one I don't
know what destroying this do what is
that I don't know but you can hit it are
you destroying our exit no oh what is
that Unchained incantation oh it's a
quest item ah you can summon something
ah one of those just okay I don't really
[Music]
care what's that talk to
pierce Yay good job oh I have so much
crap in my inventory
this dungeon really CH garbage maybe
I'll level a different class right now
because my my fief class is like maximum
exp but the other one's lagging behind
the main class is lagging behind yeah so
for whatever you wish how do you what's
the window again how to okay okay
um yeah I got a level B too
to 35 so I'm a I'mma become a bar
now okay
yeah earthshock
[Music]
tornado I guess we can both heal
gigy
yay I don't
know I deserve it
her please
revive okay okay what's
next what's next is I got to sell all my
[\h__\h] I got to my
inventory
yeah
here maybe now I'll need to use my Mana
pots what's my
strongest I need to use the guitars
right
what's my strongest guitar yeah you have
to
uh Marshall handmade sacred 8009
865 wow it's golden
too so much crap in my inventory
same this is
beautiful this is beautiful ah oh I have
the Legacy loot oh yeah uh shooing did
you find the Legacy things did you
figure out how to get those things the
the what I don't know what that is I
don't remember how I got that even I
think giggy explained it to me it's the
codes the code you can put a code in
your oh cash shop and then they give you
a bunch of items I forgot was Eden
500k yeah I did see it I didn't actually
input the code though uh you should put
the code in it gives you a bunch of
level 30 stuff oh wow but we're not even
level 30 at least I'm not oh you can
wear it mhm it's just like item level
30 oh okay I I shall look into it when I
can it's good stuff if you if you get it
too late then it might not be good
enough
anymore oh how do you how do you put the
code
in uh go to the cash shop or click
wherever the cash app is I don't even
know where it is oh yeah it is I and
then reward
code and it should be in the cash up
inventory once you put it
in it just opened up uh the site can't
be reached oh there it
is oh this what's the code again Eden
500k
okay yep
thank you oh I didn't wear a necklace
yet there we
go what's this the mission book son of
Eternity because it's not Halloween
anymore Eden Moon you can also redeem
apparently Global
pre-register Eden moon going to try
that I don't know what it does but it
gave something acquired
finished what's happening
oh I got a title Eternal Guardian
successfully
read it gives a portable bang and a
noble pass for one
day
what what the Eden 500k oh Eden Moon
Eden Moon there's also a
code oh oh this is so cute thank you for
the gifts everyone
thank you Eden Moon Eden Moon Yeah like
you know
Moon maybe you know how to spell Moon I
hope yeah wait sorry where do you put it
in uh I press I and then there's the the
code at the bottom it should do a popup
window and you can go from there Eden
Moon wow so many codes are there more
that we don't know
about um
though
yes why are the merchant so far come to
me oh portable bag
nice oh you're a you s dies
useless do that maybe this guy give me
your [\h__\h] M might use
this okay
one
day and I got General
Merchant more
more more more more charms more amulets
so many I need to put them in my so many
things are you girl keeping the treasure
map pieces
I haveing them yeah I don't know for
what though I just have them I threw
them out you can combine the treasure
maps I them out I don't want
them you hate treasure yeah well it's
really good treasure I doubt it yeah
wow
oo level requirement
30 perfume the scent lingers long after
wear leaves close your eyes and you'll
still smell the sweet fragrant perfume
wafting through the air what does it do
effect last 6 hours is this does this
make me irresistible will people run
after me more than they already do I
think you're already irresistible that's
why they're chasing yeah imagine the
smell what if you smells stinky and
people still like really like that
smell m well some people might see it as
stinky
anyway just because it's too
intense I have to get Shaman to level 30
for warlock oh oh Shaman is
fun can't wait to put totem
down okay I'm going to try to kill some
mobs here with B level
one let's see oh that's big damage on my
back what the heck look there's a
sapling what is not bad at all so cute
oh thank you for
the
EXP somehow I feel like I'm stronger
than I was with my
Thief what I've learned to skill vocal
bomb what class are you uh
Bard oh oh well Bard's not an attacker
they're buffers yeah but my attack is
stronger like I'm I'm clearing these
mobs faster than with my Thief somehow
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] did I just
summon oh strong already level eight
level 9 it goes fast oh this is a
special special
dinosaur or he was a special
dinosaur but he's no
longer he'll be in the history
books oh my God level 10 ooh thank you
for the XP this is so helpful I'm just
leveling myself okay I'm getting my
levels too don't get the wrong idea and
I'm getting potions from you you are
such a gracious host I I'm just trying
to you know provide for our
family yeah it's a family once
again we're always a family so
tit our beautiful family I think I can
go to Beluga Bay now
okay yeah I have one main quest there
oh e guitar
sounds there's also uh what is this let
me just finish the quest here so I don't
have to come back I hate
deserts yeah they're not
great looks just like a desert Rous
Pumas
have I want dessert really bad I'm
thinking about ordering some coffee
coffee oh
wait as a dessert is that more like a
drink yeah I want a sweet coffee and
then it's like a dessert you know uh why
did you get isn't tiam Su like yeah
that's a coffee dessert true get
yourself a nice tiis
Su I want a TI
Su I know you do then you should get a
tiam
su all right I want to level up my bar
to level me up everyone's leveling
up just grind
what does this one do oh I think this is
the oh that's a buff I
see don't don't attack my
healer I have attack attack I have a A
non- shieldy
Healer be care oh don't don't attack
them no be nice Stone to pum
Stone I need to get a dinar to attack oh
I like those I've I've never seen them
before I only hear the legends of the
dino
nuggies oh you need we'll make you
one really they're such fun shapes to
dip ah when you say you'll make me one
you just mean you're going to put them
yeah from the freezer I'll make you one
from the freezer okay I mean self-made
would probably not turn out so well yeah
they're genetically engineered to taste
so
good let me put my where is my Mount
here I'm going
to
perhaps uh look for a quest instead of
mindlessly killing
monsters maybe
okay um however I would also still
appreciate you mindlessly
killing I just think that there is a
benefit into my yeah there's a benefit
for all of us oh
really well I'm going to it helps the
family if you're not in Beluga Bay
family then you won't getp I will go to
Beluga Bay I will head there soon then
for I now have Quest oh okay I'm out of
quest in that
area Beluga Bay time I love Beluga Bay
Beluga where's the beluga
whale can you make your best whale
[Music]
[Laughter]
sound so
[Music]
[Laughter]
peaceful it's also kind of like a howl
actually yeah but also whale sound also
kind of more like cing cing money money
money money into the game credit card
swipe swipe swipe I don't think that's I
don't like those whales those aren't my
whales um where's my healer where's my
healer I heal
me my way I'm also healer where where
the heck did you go why are you so
far I move the
jellies I see I need to talk to
something some soul Guardian in here
always make sure to activate the
crystals the teleportation crystals
yes don't
forget uh-oh my poor healer is being
attacked what's the last game you spend
money
on Fire Emblem
Heroes you mean money as in not just
buying the game but buying something in
the game yeah money money might have
been might have not done that since AR
Knights I don't
know oh what you buy in Ark Knights
character W all the pretty all the
pretty
skins
a they really good skins gotcha
PS aren't they making like another game
yes I am awaiting it eagerly yeah
they're doing like a 3D Arc knights with
mostly like it's very different it's not
a tower defense system anymore but I'm
so excited looks so good the previews
look so good I need to play
it I want to play hey let's let's grind
day one together oh I am so in if we get
perms the oh hopefully they had like a
demo and uh I was like okay you know
what we don't have terms for the game
but I'm just going to try sign up for
the demo anyway um and I signed up as
takanasi Kara because the demo was like
for influencers you know uhhuh oh yeah
and so you had to put in like your
socials and so on and only not everybody
got approved they approved me and I was
like jenma does this mean I have perms
for the game this is like unusual like
this is not how we normally do it then I
was unsure so I never ended up playing
it cuz yeah I didn't really it wasn't
official terms but but I mean they kind
of approved me so yeah they went through
that list themselves yeah mhm I missed
my chance I guess cuz I was I wasn't too
confident about it but there there yeah
I've been waiting for the Ian
release
H I don't know how much longer it takes
I've been really wanting another gacha
to get into
yeah looking forward to all these games
do you really need another I need
another I don't think I want to play
Star rail there's too much
reading I liked it though I do like the
reading
you have to get alive it's just like I I
keep up but then I stop playing and then
there's more characters like who the
heck is this now yeah and then I feel
like since it's a strategy game they
keep power creeping the other
characters
a so people are like it's good to have
this character because it makes your
team better and now you're behind cuz
you stopped
playing no I just do do like my basic
characters I haven't spent money on that
one you haven't you're so good I I
guess I played it when it was released
and then I was like how can I turn down
the double $100 pack and then I bought
it do you always spend money on your
games yeah I love spending
money you are on pngs you're the most
ideal player that they're hoping
for I'm a really good consumer I fall
for marketing tactics really easily and
I'm aware of it yeah do you fall for
like fish scams too or like cck on this
for a coupon no I don't I I fall for
like targeted advertising when you're
like scrolling your Twitter and then
there's like an ad and then you see it
you're like hey maybe I do want
this G no those are usually like bad
quality weird weird weird stuff doesn't
make you have that's
question does it make you happy GG do
you like spending money on these things
I don't know sometimes it makes me happy
and then sometimes it doesn't make me
happy oh well it has to do with what I
get I see depends on your chance of Goa
yeah
my quest is called scrub a
dubdub oh me too I had that oh you
already had that someone help me I
agroed the big
crab H sorry I'm
busy both of the bars are
n
nah I do need to kill some Eagles soon
but that that can wait I iron claw
Eagles yeah I'm killing them now
I'm accepting everything first so I
don't have to like come back kill are
you getting my kills right
now um I cuz it's I guess
so automatic
questing no finger lifted get two more
Quest I have to kill a tide Rock Turtle
but I can't find
one all right I help kill Eagles
actually I'll kill the the shells stuff
do you have the Quest for biotechnology
H I can accept
it I have that one Quest so we can just
do it okay I I must go to accept it
though but first I must kill the the
Eagles what's the what it sucks that um
you always have to change your equipment
when you change certain classes oh well
at least you can always have the the
cloes on you just got to have the sets
like inserted into the slot oh there's a
a set stuff yeah just for the cloo
clothing not for the weapons oh that
sucks a little bit of a quality of
life thing gu so
H okay uh Iron Claw Eagles you shall be
mine that's probably why I never made
like alternate alternate accounts for
these things it's like this is my main I
don't really want to grind anymore yeah
I usually also never made any more
characters than my main except in World
of Warcraft because in World of Warcraft
after a certain level I was like cuz I
was still a tiny baby when I played
World of Warcraft I was like ah somehow
I can't get past level
42 and then I kept on making new
characters and another one and another
cuz I really loved the character
creation in world of Ro 2
to I don't know that wasn't even that
special but for me that was like another
way of playing
Sims oh the dress Warcraft no just yeah
the World of Warcraft character creation
was for me like playing
Sims oh I like the Sims I hope the next
one is a good game uh well Sims 5 is not
happening
anymore oh really yeah they announced
that they're they're canceling Sims 5
and just forever continuing to add
expansion packs to Sims 4 a say they're
focusing on it they're they're doing
something else they're making something
else but it's not Sims 5 yeah it sounds
like like some kind of
multiplayer they're making a movie but
the
community the community is a little bit
disappointed I also wanted the Sims 5
well there's a there's an Asian
equivalent I know what you mean called
though I I'm interested in playing that
too but that's to me that's just a
different game I I want Sims 5 also
that's
true but that one's interesting able to
be a witch in there oh yeah enoy
enoy yeah I need to play that I think
actually I think I did uh uh uh input
per
request for the foro I'm looking it
up it looks so good they just moved the
release to win
when you oh the graphics are so
realistic yeah it's like Korean is isn't
it like in terms of the models oh my
God gosh enoy I just want to make my
anime voice in
there 28th
March
o oh oh oh oh oh
I just I don't know I was reminded um
that
GTA is coming soon I thought it was like
5 years away or so but by now yeah had a
new GTA is like spring 2025 or what was
it that's so soon G that's crazy I I
feel like it's been in development so
long that wait what GTA 6 is it GTA 6
yeah
faster than the Y simulator but I feel
like just just a couple of months ago I
was like oh like looking at the
announcement and I'm like oh that's
going to take like 5 years
but hasn't it only been like it probably
took them a while I think they just it
like hushed up okay it's fall
2025 but that's still like like only
like a little bit less is it is it fall
or is it uh winter now what would you
say oh okay then it's a year unless
go they seem to be on track so I'm
excited it's going to be good it's going
to be my first trip to
Florida ooh it's going to suck have you
girls been to Florida before Oh only
once I just hear a lot of Florida news
what I I have been once the Florida news
Florida man oh
how is it just don't go like a hurricane
that's true it's very humid um yeah
that's about
it Beaches they have alligators it more
humid than
Japan I don't I want to say it Japan
just kind of actually I don't know just
assume it
sucks no offense anyone in
Florida oh I remember these
gos I'm killing now I have the punish
the Glutton Quest
now shielding you 25 you're like so
close to us now oh I guess so let's go
you're catching up I'm catching up
yippe man I ordered like a a home
grocery service and they didn't even
have most of the crap I wanted so I'm so
disappointed did does that mean you
still have to go and get it kind of they
only gave you basic stuff like I asked
for gits like the things that Wen Frozen
or or vegetables they they manag to get
me but everything else that's healthy
not so
much blop so lame I know useless I know
what's the point of paying more to get
delivered you're not going to give me
what I want yeah they didn't even
substitute for it I want a freaking
broccoli they
didn't broccoli where's my freaking
broccoli make your own
broccoli you could you like grow it
myself yeah grow it in winter go outside
rip out a tree and eat
it why you make things so
complicated yeah
probably Trappers
small here
the Yum Yum trees as you like to say
when you feed it to a cute
dog the Yum Yum treat yeah yum yum treat
yum yum
trees oh trees I I watched some some
samed dog videos and when they feed
their doggles their samed dog uh
broccoli then it's called the Yum Yum
Tree ooh I think
very
sophisticated cuz dog likes Yum Yum
Tree surprisingly I like yum yums I'm
like Yum Yum Tree me
too where the hell are the
Trappers there you are reminds me of
this this has well the word Yum Yum Tree
reminds me of this Tick Tock cat who
sucks on its paws and then the owner
calls it Paw Paw time and Records the
cat just sucking on its paw and it gets
like really anxious and mad if um the
owner doesn't like pick up its legs and
bring its paws to its mouth so they need
like an hour every day for the cat to
suck on its
PA cute baby that's so cute it sucks on
his paw so much the paws get all
swollen
a that's a bit
much should give it something else to
suck
on why will it my on this P when my when
my when my cats were still babies when I
first got them I guess I got them like a
little bit too early cuz they still
wanted to suck on something and so they
always suck on my fingers it actually
hurts a little
bit Bo was cute so I had to let them do
it I felt like they're mommy they just
sucked on each other I had to get them
to stop it was kind of what sucked where
no it's not cute I don't know what they
were sucking on so I had to make them
stop don't make it so L that's wholesome
it's cute they're they're boy cats I
didn't want them to get infected if
their mouth spinning like weird [\h__\h]
what do you mean what what do you mean
what am I mean what do you
mean you're making it so cursed
cheen it's the cutest
thing are I don't know I don't know were
they sucking each other's Paws no they
wer sucking each other's paws I I was
scared of what they were sucking was the
issue cuz they were looking for tee but
they're boy cats they don't have they
don't have the girl tee the girl oh so
they're just noming on each other I
think so they looking for milky but you
you did not get the proper milky from
that
you cursed cursed yes cursed cursed do
they no longer do that yeah they stopped
they stopped they grew out of that phase
thankfully I have stopped
it my preventative
measures what if we had cats but the
cats were
[Laughter]
freaky uh I I think if the cats and
shodi are freaky that's too much
somebody needs to be sto fre cat she
stopped them they're no longer freaky
well they're wholesome cats now
good I took them to church and
everything
from their
sins cats in
church can you
imagine cat's in church I used to make
my profile picture that it was like a a
cat with a nun outfit
a wait Shing you you're a cat owner
right yeah do you put your cat in
clothes uh no they don't like it good I
did not teach some young enough yeah no
they don't they don't want to be in
cloves
yeah they shouldn't be in cloes with
dogs I understand but cats leave them
alone leave them alone guys don't they
should be in cloth no no I will Force
One into a clothes no no
no
no I tried to give them a Kirby hat but
they always fight it m cuz they don't
want to be in
cloes that's true they need to cover
up this is a world where you have to
cover up or you'll be seen as they're
covered up they have they have fur on
them they're naked no I will show you
what's
naked isn't there that one naked cat
like the Egyptian one oh yeah okay that
one's
naked I think I think that cat it would
be cute if you would put a sweater on
that cat a self- knitted tiny sweater
that' be kind of cute but besides that
no no so you can only dress up one kind
of cat yes the furry
kind the furry the cat if the cat wants
to be dressed it okay like if you it
would dress
itself go to Amazon of
blacko dress
upct no but like if you do since it was
a kitten then it will probably accept it
and then whatever but if it doesn't seem
like it's enjoying it then don't do it
poor cat Man Poor
cat cats have a mind of their own and
they want to be naked Okay their mind is
telling them I feel like some cats you
know are so naughty that they deserve to
be punished and wear clothes gigy I'm
starting to hate
you you're such a bird person
I thought you going
call noing because of shaking head
emoji I said that because of you you're
not a cat person obviously you seem to
be a bird person Bird yeah it's a bird
obviously it goes bark bark bark
yeah I can tell barking bird MM I want a
cat but I'm afraid that I'm afraid too
I'm afraid too get a cat I want a cat no
no please stay away from the cats I will
take the cats I'll take all cats on your
radar what if I get a cat and then you
can come over and take it and this is
just my bait to get you to come over to
take my
cat uh that's a weird strategy
honestly what would it
work only under certain circumstances I
think
oh that I don't I hope you don't enforce
them okay but what if it's just to come
over to see my cat to see your cat I've
heard that kind of uh pickup line before
from con what oh who wants to come over
and see my cat yeah wellknown pickup
phrase um I us you get here and there's
no cat no I don't know I I know maybe
maybe there is a cat H yeah in my case
there would be a cat for
sure yes yes um who knows well if you
pay for the flight ticket I would come
over what happens to your ability to
just fly anywhere a phoenix I I thought
you're going to drive by I can't I can't
no no that's not why why not because
hook Papa put a belt on me and it says
in like handwritten on a piece of paper
to not on unleash the true powers of me
and she's offering to see she show you
her cat and you don't even have the
ability well you know nowadays we all
have phones if you really want to show
me your cat you can take a picture of
the so-called cat what if she doesn't
have a phone anymore it just died yeah I
don't have a
broken there there is no it's a broken
phone no that's impossible you have a
phone don't gasl light me you bird
person
like a flip phone user yeah
yeah photo taking capability no no flip
can also take pictures don't gasl
[Laughter]
me man I was I was uh thinking we were
going to do quests together today but uh
I I I need to stop what are you girls
doing it's done at this point I'm just
hit I'm doing a bunch of quest okay
you're hitting monsters G caught up now
though yeah yeah you're 25 now do the
dungeon that's here if you get there
what's the dungeon called I think it's a
level 27 main quest called Morty
Kora have we done that already I don't
think we have oh okay yeah when you get
there I guess we'll re
reunite yeah yeah I'm just hitting
monsters and leveling up my side classes
okay but the Morty Kora Quest I want
what level
would that be 27 oh okay so I'm I'm
probably doing the quests before that
right
now gosh why are there so many quests
feel like a lot of main quests I didn't
do it's it's I wish in the in the when
you press l in the quest log thingy
where you see all of your quests that
you can have I wish it would
say I guess it does I guess it
does when you click on it I it does say
man that title is too long I I just
collect all the quest I will have to
keep
grinding you're so thorough with it I
like it with the the quest stuff yeah
that's why I don't have to go back cuz
it going to be like oh kill birds kill
birds
again well you not you don't have to
do uh them even if they tell you to go
back you don't have to do any of them
it's more like the the XP stuff I need
it yeah I guess it's more efficient than
just killing
mobs
yeah so
[Music]
this what am I doing here
again what a pig came out of the
N bamboozle what am I doing here
[Music]
I think I have too many quests now that
they don't show up in like my easy Quest
tracker too many
quests yeah oh Ninja Turtles oh my God I
watched your 3D model yeah the yeah and
I saw your
your my wings mys my
wings your wings your
wings now it's so funny the the boob
Collision Collision
I when I saw crony having it with her
like official model I was like man I
wish my boobs would do that and now my
boobs do it it's
fun nice you can't relate gigy can you I
can't but I can watch
you what you pair so you can pretend at
least oh yeah I'll get a fake pair so I
can pretend maybe I don't know I find
joy in watching kiaha move her arm and
smack her chest around thank you you you
I was really locked
in oh my God stream oh my
God you're kind of a firsty firsty girl
it's it's fun to watch is it not fun no
one else having fun watching studying
she's St late that's why that's what I'm
here for to provide fun it's for
wholesome purposes of course yes yes
yeah now maybe maybe you can do the same
thing with other Bonnie Parts I don't
know oh what body parts does shei have
that can like a
whole yeah and her pigtails maybe but
it's not the same
huh yeah can you gr guess someone's just
going to let me have to let me use
theirs oh he don't you have like a
mascot that might have a a little bit of
yeah can can it
grow a pair of something chest I don't
know either balls or or
chesticles H I can I'll
ask okay what are you
asking the gods above okay and then
they'll let me know it can happen or not
is it is it the girl or is it a boy I I
hope it's a boy it'll be funnier that
way hope boy is a boy poo yeah there you
go oh yeah I had a feeling and then it
can bounce it's popo
[Laughter]
I you know pople in in German is just
ass oh my God it's going to be growing
in from its
backside yeah what is
thisa B is serious treasure
box where did I get that oh I killed
probably killed
something the area boss I guess I'm
assuming nice oh my God everyone kill
kill fast these tribal Wizards destroy
them
enforcer Must Destroy must
kill did you prefer the black or the
white outfit
gigy I think I really like the white one
I like the white one to actually it's
it's like pearles pearlescent now it
wasn't in the music video but now it is
it's really pretty thank you it is
really
pretty I like the way I don't know the
way it contrast with your body it's just
a really good
look I I agree honestly thank you wow
you girls would look good in it
too oh my God we can be backup dancers I
want to be the one that holds your ass
of course you want to be the one but you
know that backup
dancer H she's she's not getting paid
she's paying me just kidding actually
not true okay I suppose I can
too if I must I'll do it well you know
you're not just there for holding the
ass you have to learn the whole coroo
properly
okay oh no there's more behind it
there's more behind it train so hard
just for that moment not that
easy don't hold the ass isn't that heavy
no there more to it you can't holding
ass yeah it's probably a technique or
something I think that's what it is
you're not taking it seriously girls
I'll train I'll train for a year oh it
is serious we're just taking the
logistics of it yeah yeah what what are
you training on which ass are you
holding when you
train um I'll make one like a fake
one I see I'm going to need you to send
me a mold of your
asso have something realistic to use all
right I I'll try to figure out how to
take a a mold of my ass Christmas
present m
well there are you know op by mouse pads
I never made one but I was thinking of
uh like if anything maybe like an ass
mouse pad would that help be good yeah
that would help well I'm not going to do
it though I'll glue it to my wall a and
then you just stand at your wall 5 hours
per day holding yeah practicing how to
hold it chose the Coro of course oh
yeah no you should practice it with
something that can move around like
something more Dynamic like a like a
[Music]
person going to get it
ass I don't know hire
one hire someone to stand there so I can
grab yeah I'm try to find someone maybe
I'm like Tex or something I was say I
don't think
so that sounds dangerous well yeah
probably
it for the
training just get really flexible and
hold your own ass okay I will start
doing
yoga why won't you hold Shan's ass she
needs to come over do you think she'll
fly here
no I guess I have to find someone Phenix
though I also have to run my my Chapel
my church oh yeah un attend
oh I have the the quest now for the
dungeon I'll stop doing things I'll
clean out my
inventory what's the quest called um
it's called moror 2 main but it seems
like you have to do all of the other
main quests first for it I see I am
still not level 27 I am the young
one
ohing you're 26 let's
go yeah you must continue to kill things
so I can level up I'll things for
you thank
[Music]
you oh my God there's so many
quests
beautiful I have the daughter in the
Pirate Man
Quest
oh feel like I did that one to I need to
kill aul
enforcer kill him kill
[Music]
him maybe now that my B is already 24 I
can switch back to
Thief oh yeah right cuz it 27
class oh yeah I can get up to Next
Level I'm on the next level what is this
anyway huh
what is this doing oh I have people
hidden oh I leveled
up what what is this
button
slam Max Max Max Max oh crap this is a
big Elite
group the class skill CP are they when I
switch wait let me test okay no answered
my own
question Thief simulator
[Music]
2024 th simulator yay wait another one
no I mean I I think a new one came out
this year and I I played it I think it
was this year I only played the first
one how's the second one it's good it's
better yeah I had a better experience I
think was fun guess I will look into it
yeah go
thiefing where is he oh down there fief
Joel yeah I liked being a
thief I liked opening locks with my
lockpick you go to jail for that yeah
but so in the game in in fief Simulator
2 you actually do end up in a jail and
then you have to break out of it and
that was always like the most riveting
part of that game for me you just keep
going back to jail then to experience
that favorite memor
but it's huge and you can find so many
things there it's really
good oh
legitimately check it out so I can see
what the criminals are doing oh I wish
there was a multiplayer version of it oh
I can do a class now that's that's not
one of the basic classes I can be a
knight oo o i mean that's kind of you
have like a an outfit that's kind of
like a knight or a paladin but probably
That's Heavy Armor right wa what what
what weapon does the Knight use I
probably don't have
one or do I does it use
sword oh the heck
Isa Night level six how did I I just
switched
class I will grinding page what talking
to
me no okay you're grinding you're
leveling me oh my God level eight you
I'm grinding I'm grinding grind me more
you for the grind no
problem I have so many Quest I can now
turn
in let's go muchos
exper
atanos okay see see
Amigos who is ltia I don't see ltia
here much
exper I'm I'm working I'm working on it
I
[Music]
just alpaca coin Stones
Rising Marshall Grudge swamp what the
hell get out of my inventory
does a knight use a shield night CLA I'm
not dying right now I have one I have
one
yeah oh they didn't spawn oh I
[Music]
see I am I am somewhat of a knight
myself level 11 oh there te someone you
die oh you kill I
see I thought it was like an NPC
you always got to kill always think of
killing
first kill first ask questions later
exactly Lia hurry up and show
up oh contains witch dock let's kill
ITA boom boom boom
um
no oh thank you for the
help thank you thank you Max Max Max
Max Max Max okay what we thanks elegant
increases your evasion and your pee
healing party healing Focus
increases your double
healing yeah
each time you pee it heals your soul
uhhuh P attack p
attack I think like single single attack
compared to AOE a player maybe player
not party a personal oh
person okay there's a lot of Buffs
what's what where are the attacks
provoke in increases P attack Prov good
yeah probably yeah I can I can get the
wait this is a tank class isn't it I can
finally tank but you can heal yourself a
little oh yeah this is very much a tank
class yep y okay maybe if gii wanted to
be a
tank do you want to be a tank
now nah no okay I don't want to be a
tank either but tank tank aasi K I got
to be a
tank I'll I'll try to tank a little bit
today at least only today but my future
is double wielding blade dancer you know
yeah yeah yeah yeah want to be
cool you are
cool so wait what is this you're the
cooliest increases malice caused by
attacks malice caus so just more aggro
stuff I
guess is
this oh new her oh is this like oh he I
got the the mor toora thing now although
I I do need a little bit more XP before
like
27 okay can you not enter it early I I
don't know honestly I think you can as
long as you have the quest can we just
sink again we're see
we're that's C I really love that I'll
try to enter early then such a beautiful
moment oh perfect
SC the orange brain wave we should sink
up more often
gy okay it has to start with sinking
another thing up first what is
it oh our
period first we have to think that and
then we'll be completely in syn oh I
always skip my period though that's
going to be a problem you can only skip
it when you're like really stressed
there so Buton to are you really
stressed right now no no no I mean I'm
always stressed but uh no no skip it in
different ways don't you know the ways
oh way yes yeah I understand I just uh
what is this I just uh I just don't take
a break you know with the no breaks yeah
no break just keep on taking I don't
know I talked about this before in girls
talk I'm embarrassed talking about it
like
so but I guess well sh's viewers are
certainly used to this kind of talk I I
don't know about
they the GS I guess so huh this is just
girls talk yeah yeah um like you guys
probably compare sizes We compare
periods I guess no honestly I I never do
that
but but I don't know if that's common
when I meet a girl who doesn't know the
way then I like to share the way because
it's surprising how many girls are not
aware of the way I think I might know of
the way because someone has mentioned
this way yeah you just take you just
take it without taking a break you know
the the I I I I I swear I I I I
generally I I the real reason I've been
taking it it's for my acne
okay oh yeah cuz I actually I heard
about that method I've never taken that
thing before though M well I take it
from my acne for many years now and and
and so my doctor said I I don't have to
take the break if I don't want to like
every once in a while maybe it's good
cuz normally you take it for a few weeks
and you take a week break and then you
take it again and then you take a week
break and then the week break you get
you
know but um I I I don't want to you know
I don't want to I don't want to always
be bleeding so I say okay no I I'll
continue taking these are the hacks yeah
these are the live girl hacks yeah and
for the girls out there you can also
take if you really don't want to get it
because you have a trip coming up you
can't take it too to try and Dodge it oh
what take what oh you know the your ways
oh yeah yeah yeah to try and get it to
skip so you don't get it while you go on
vacation
exactly yeah yeah nothing ruins the day
more than getting it yeah also like when
I have like a lot of dance lessons and
stuff it's really
uncomfortable so I'd rather just no yeah
always skip it you know yeah anyway
anyway
anyway anyway I can go to the dungeon
which which one are we doing single
player the one at the
end okay the more I assume yes yeah all
right I am inside blue ball should oh
you're inside already yeah I'm inside oh
on my way
oh solo right yeah SOLO yeah I I did
solo Oh Oh Shi
in
hello we now oh no GG's the I'm
bar all
right here's a
buff all right who am I I guess I'm
focusing on Kiara unless I tank
everything watch this girl
[Laughter]
uh is there like a key on the keyboard
to Auto Select the next closest enemy a
tab is the best that you'll have I think
oh sick GG stop aggroing everything I
can heal myself now I can heal
myself who you taking my
bro why am I not moving got to pick up
the pace oh oh okay she's stressing me
race now yeah why is it a race you got
to pick up the pain I can't heal you
from Far don't worry don't worry I'm bar
just let her die just let her die you
can't heal yourself enough if you
keep oh my God do not
worry okay be be
happy I'm happy look I have the whole
thing the whole party here
let then I'm just going to Focus like we
are not my problem yeah let her
suffer we can't move
anymore not with I can't move with W ASD
anymore oh why must have pressed
something
weird oh maybe all tabed or something
yeah oh that's a big circle I'm not
exting this die
why do they all didn't they have more
voice lands for the enemies they all
make the same sounds they're all Merlin
I don't I don't remember them having
voices honestly that is a new thing I
like hearing the guitar sound that's
nice yeah here's a
song the song of GG's people
yes I suppose I'm too weak to be a tank
you're not weak
I'm not doing my job properly I'm
doubting my my abilities now yeah you're
doing great says the person pulling
everything yeah well I never I never
wanted to be a tank anyway you're hading
for us and I had to heal
you
no I've achieved night them knom night
Knighthood Knighthood
yeah level 20 night let's
go that probably opens up more paths for
me nighted yes uh-oh oh they're helping
us
cool aggro on
me I don't know what all of these things
do we did it good job good job oh that's
actually better but I don't want it I
don't really want it we did it
we did it and another dungeon off of our
Books
huz
hours imagine what if what if next Ian
REO takes part and eat an
eternal that would be fun it's kind of
hard to
control
no need isn't R into you Renee yeah yeah
Raina she started with Members Only only
and I I I thought you know that would be
cool we would have a four people team
but the only problem is that we would
have like so many different time zones
then like the time that we're playing
now for her is middle of the night so I
don't know if that's going to work
out that that even though it would be
nice I mean if she wants to join she's
always
welcome of course I really can't move
I'm locked in
you're locked in locked in
negative pressing
buttons try Rel logging okay I'll try
switching channel and coming
back man there's so many stats I can't
keep track of what's good and what's not
right got to offer her I did I did I did
tell her like oh wait oh my God you're
playing e Eternal too oh my god let's go
please join
us yeah I don't know what to do with my
class skills should I just max them all
or is there an actual yeah I've been
maxing them
all
okay I still I still can't move only
move
click so
strange I guess we're done in Bela Bay
are
we maybe there's a there's a multiplayer
version of the dungeon
is that the
daily uh do we unlock a daily for that
oh no it's a main yeah it's a main okay
let's do that architect
angle
Garrison oh so many quest game against
one of the
Pirates ah same
same okay we the same thing then yeah
are we doing Crusade against the Pirates
or multiplayer talk to Rafi to report
your maybe after that we do the dungeon
again
weird let's kill the pirate
daily and then Crusade against the
Pirates too who is hitting
me crab you must now become my food
it's
a never
mind oh oh I remember this place I used
to hang out here and just like hide in
somewhere in the Fortress I would try to
find places where they would not bother
me oh and I'll be like he they do not
care I am here
I oh now I can kill faster
see I have so many self Buffs but barely
any like
attacks oh yeah that's how B
Works he but I'm on night talking about
your night oh I think I'll switch back
to Fe may you got lock
more I got like a lot unlock but it's
just Buffs Buffs Buffs
Buffs I'll
switch travel to
even that doesn't work anymore I right
click oh it's left
click I thought it was right
click oh my God ever LaVine is in this
Camp
yeah afil she's a pirate
now suits her that makes sense makes
sense yeah with the punk rock Vibe kind
of fits
[Music]
can you girls believe it's already like
November and Christmas is soon and the
year is over soon that's crazy I I like
the end of the year stuff I hate the
beginning of the year though it's boring
boring yeah like there's something
interesting in January you get maybe
like what Valentine's in
February oh I don't
know I like the chill month yeah and the
beginning of the year feels like okay we
have a whole year ahead of us so much
time to do
thingses I have to tax immediately I
have to do taxes all the time doesn't
matter
when but yeah end of the year stresses
me out cuz it's like where the hell did
the time
go I thought I
had so don't like it don't like it
Max Max Max Max Max
Max
oh I don't want that anyway
okay
huh the vile shark
killer v shark
Mage where's the
killer oh oh my my V Mages are being
taken care of it seems
where are they ah
here I'm back I'm thiefing again yeah
welcome the wrong weapon though but
whatever I'm talking to abil oh my
God hey hey you like a new song called
skater
girl want to be a girlfriend no way no
way thank you need a new one oh defeat
defeat oh somebody's doing everything
for me kill
kill I'm back to talk to Abal
LaVine I need to kill a doctor and a
fighter
okay if I I I see them I'm killing giggy
has accepted your quest
Shing yeah I think we're
sharing okay did you get get
those uh I assume I am getting something
I need I need some theves to be killed
okay on my way I'm killing them I'm also
here punch pump Kow
K oh already finished collect Fort
blueprint from Gilbert
Gilbert Gil
gilberd feel like my game is so bugged
out I can't do things properly
anymore what's the the buggy part uh WD
doesn't work anymore and uh clicking on
the quest to move towards the thing
doesn't work
anymore sounds pretty
bugged wait now it works
okay move in the mini map one is no
longer bug now uh
no W wsd still doesn't work my keyboard
language no should be fine but let me
change to German no it still doesn't
work oh well I need to kill more doctors
you save lives I take it
away St
do STW
happened to you I just moved from the
map uh
what what do you mean move
in move from what do you
mean move in the
map you mean click on the map doesn't do
anything on
me that didn't do anything for me
ever it's okay I can
accept it's what you get for studying
medicine gigy Moody has sabotaged the
evil schemes of vile sharks saving
Beluga Harbor from these scurvy villains
huzzah what are you up to all on your
own she walking all the way
back I got to kill more thieves man
how much blood does uh do I have to
spill better now it seems I have reached
a a a place where the quest items
rewards are getting better than the
Legacy things so now I have to Fain and
actually exchange my armor
soon I think that I redeemed the Legacy
and then did not use
it yeah I told you it would be too late
if you wait too long
oh I got to go back to a
LaVine I do so much walking oh there's
another dungeon so much flying oh oh
it's probably the pirate one that one's
kind of long I think I remember that oh
yeah
yeah who is
Gilbert Gilbert Gilt what you got oh
shoot you're someone I got to
kill I don't even remember killing him
he died too fast I guess
the set bonus do I have a set bonus I'm
spamming number
two oh yeah it's giving me set bonus
then I'll keep it for a while
longer hi good times set bonuses man I
hate the manual Quest it's like I have
to combine something I have to leave
this map just to do it you can't just
teleport me there uh you have one of
those
now yeah I got to do like um combine
this with a formula to make a stone and
then you summon something and you kill
them and then you got to report someone
no that's a video
game okay I'm at the dungeon I shall
await you I will begin killing mobs near
here you know you can teleport everyone
as the the
Mage oh yeah oh yeah I remember turn
oh would you like me to teleport you
over here they make they make um the
portals don't
they do they make portals uh yeah yeah
they do oh yeah well they just teleport
everyone in general
m i
remember you remember you remember I
remember the
20 what do you remember the TW the TW
crazy I was crazy
once do you remember do you do you
should remember I don't remember I
remember we all remember I'm not dueling
you oh you have
mercy yes I don't want to kill your kfp
so I rejected their dual request cuz I I
can't kill them This Ss
good I would like to be teleported to
the dungeon when possibly
yes once once I
okay let me walk over
there I will bring you right to the
entrance thank you it's so finicky when
I try to get there and like the button
doesn't go like why can't I just auto
travel here no okay okay I'm summoning
you I'm summoning you all right make
sure to link your soul oh
God girl you link the wrong
one why would you do
that I I I did not want this I haven't
asked for
this okay okay let me let me walk back
okay I I'll you s don't ever try to be
don't ever try to be a mjor ever again
[Laughter]
I I'll I wait wait I I I can atone for
this
SKU why is I'm not walking back okay I
had that last second
[Laughter]
warning it just happened so quickly it
did it
did why did you do it it's a little
funny cuz mes are supposed to be smart
with her
not I just got so excited that I was
going to use it he uses one brain cell
for whatever class she chooses to use
yeah it's for only killing and nothing
else well a nice little trip into a
different climate but I'm already back
yeah what a nice trip why is this for
have a quest how do I get down
there uh you have to get for the whole
Camp kind of but H if you just click on
the quest talk to ulol or so then it
will oh make you move there anyway I
have I have so many quests here I have
to go to my
L stop stop stop stop okay okay don't
worry guys just just stay at Beluga Bay
Town I'll warp you I'll warp you there
I'll walk I'll I'll I'm in the dungeon
don't warp me it's it's the v shark main
dungeon right maybe you can't even yeah
yeah that's the dungeon maybe you can't
warp me anyway cuz I'm in here it's
leading me to somewhere else I don't
know where I'm going why is it leading
you I just watched you pass me I know
music it's oh it's taking me to Garrison
Captain straw maybe I got to talk to him
first Captain straw what do you want me
to do how you at
[Music]
I I need to stop taking quests okay just
take me there so I can kill
things okay okay okay don't worry I'm
going to link my soul and then I will
spawn you okay and then I will probably
have to do this at some point
[Music]
again okay okay it's okay you link you
won't you yeah are you ready are you
ready okay okay it's okay we did it we
did it we did it we did it are you in
front of the dungeon yeah get in here
now okay is this solo yeah single player
yeah but solo means something else in
our
books oh time to let Chi tank everything
together
wait you're now even taging as a mage
you crazy crazy land you can do
everything you set your mind to what is
Mages are
squishy yeah they
are uh uh whatever don't
want okay p p
p here we go oh
this I remember so
well oh there's like under like the free
rooms or so over there there's like um
different holes in the
wall it's a Pirate
Cave oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I remember
that honestly such nice memories coming
back to me I I miss the running this
dungeon a lot I think this is the first
five player dungeon actually really yeah
times I miss the time what your favorite
dungeon I don't know I'm I like the the
malice one and then the for the world I
like the the world of the witchery stuff
I don't remember those names I only
remember the visuals actual name but
there's malice Palace and then there's a
witch level I I know that um I think
like when you're in aen uh and then you
go up to that church building thingy
there's a like a raid or so dungeon that
you can teleport yourself to and I did
that so many times I think because the
equipment that you could get there was
really good uh and we wiped so many
times there too but that was that was a
good one it was like a palace looking
place with like big
white uh walls and water and I need to
get there we need to get there so we can
remind oh I think I know maybe what
you're talking about
yeah good
times what kind of witch ritual happen
yeah yeah yeah yeah it was like like
somewhere in the high
Lev region and it was it was a we'll be
getting there mhm we'll get there I mean
we're only level 28 now but we'll get
there yeah we're going to get there soon
we level so quickly do we do we yeah so
fast
old stuff what did we start off with
today wasn't it
25 but we leveled some classes up all of
us yeah that's something to be proud
of so one day when we're more high level
and and we need to do like Dungeons that
are like that aren't doable with just us
free then we we'll get some viewers to
help us high level people
yeah they're going to drag us through
the
dungeons make it easy for
us and we leeched at exp I still can't
believe we're going in without like a
tank technically it's okay it's solo
it's solo Charles true that's true if
you do this in multiplayer I think it
might be screwed yeah mhm might be rough
very
screwed oh many rings no just wonder
ring I don't care I don't know agility I
don't care I need to clean my inventory
at some
point oh wait leave dungeon why would we
leave dungeon I haven't done leaving I
haven't done the things that I need to
do I don't even know what I'm doing in
here where's ax Moss where is
Kar okay I guess we got to look for them
no yeah they're in the rooms on the
bottom of the
map I'm killing everything oh I think
it's if you like screw it up maybe I
don't know no no or if you can't do the
rest of the
dungeon I got another Quest no there's
way more mobs here still oh God do I
have a Healer
here yeah I'm here uh hold
up uh wait am I following GG where are
you I'm I'm at the bottom of the of the
map of the D sear are you not in the
dungeon anymore I'm St I'm in the
dungeon oh oh good God why did you guys
separate great I don't know man I went
towards the quest is
find okay you guys separated a little
I'm I think I'm K just run back to West
if you can I'm uh I'm fine uh I'm I'm
fine things have calmed down all
right a little
bit all right we should not get a split
up NPC
over I was almost at uh who do I choose
to save
situation oh I would have ran
away okay you're you're there um we're
like around here where uh you're near
this
section did you go past this person no
oh there you
are can't attack M Di
noise I can't wait for group healing I
think I have to be level 30 oh hell
yeah group healing we love it we love to
see
it okay here should be one of the
actual where is
he did you girls already defeat axe moss
and Kar no I we haven't been here maybe
she has to spawn if you do a certain
thing yeah where are they he should be
here right
here that's weird kills more Quest says
let's just kill some more yeah we just
have to kill the whole dungeon oh yeah
we have to we need to kill all the
humanid monsters to uh them okay in a
big circle what happened we killed we've
been here each other I must kill all the
humans in this dungeon oh no about here
to the left should have created frog
character all right I'm going to where
gigy is running isn't there something at
the pier that we didn't kill cuz there's
like a skull icon there I will
go what did we oh we can't go there
anyway
have to click everywhere oh here you go
there's this one guy uh really cuz of
that one guy no there's okay it's not
just one guy there's a few
more okay thank god oh it's not split up
almost got one
guide I want to be tanked now I can be
like you're tanking you're tanking I'm
tanking
Yoo
okay oh GG there's things down here
I feel like a babysitter there's things
down here oh there's there is there a
boss there oh yeah Kar don't don't hit
anything yet I'm healing Gigi over here
okay I'm I'm here you can just wait
there let's
go you shall
die rally the troops oh he's dying so
fast oh
no SP
now we can you should you should need on
that
what did you greed on it you should need
oh but I think you got it did you get it
the I got it the book if you want to be
book for cleric that's for
Illusionist
oh Maes are for cleric staffs are for
the Wizards and Illusionist is a
book has the other boss spawned
now no
should be in that room do something
again where are they well I'm going to
sort out my stuff so don't die while I'm
busy it's
okay it it's probably just like a few
mobs
somewhere totally
doable not
here are you looking too
are you looking this the mob I'm looking
I don't want to do this right
here where is
it that's a main quest a daily Quest
there's so much freaking Quest I should
not have taken so
much there's 200 free gotcha draws
what where how do I track this
one really 200 free gacha
draws is there any on the
ship
no there was an
event what do you mean in the in the few
days that we weren't playing there was a
200 free gacha draws
event oh wow is that why you guys get
got so I found the group I found the
group of enemies
yay all right I guess we head there
don't start the boss without me though
no you don't even have to go here
they're almost dead okay okay we still
have to find a boss oh right I I know
where it is oh yeah he spawned he's
finally spawned okay on my
[Music]
way at least he should be yeah he's here
think I know now why this
let's go why does the dungeon stayed in
my memory so much because in order to
finish it you really have to clear the
whole dungeon be very
thorough it's also a kind of a big
dungeon
yeah y we did it yay nice
yooo yeah I guess we can oh you can
teleport us out Chi now that we're done
I mean the x is right there too I think
we to talk to the guy in here oh okay
the Sol guard run towards
him oh yeah undercover v
shark who do we k i don't question for
you to kill Charles oh is that the guy
we
killed is it I don't know who's
Charles oh it is it's the guy we killed
up here so we're we're done then well
you guys are done we have to kill
Charles again cuz we didn't get the
credit for it is he there what he's not
here have to reset it and kill Charles
no all right teleport us that's so dumb
that's so dumb they should like no oh I
can't use it inside a dungeon you must
leave you can't what's the
point all right time to head back out do
we
reenter yeah how do we reset this
dungeon uh there's an option when you
click on yourself at the the top left I
think oh
reset
okay Dam
Shield you know you're way around this
game uh only only somewhat oh but it's
hold up who's this guy I need to talk to
someone okay I I I I couldn't reset it
because of uh still had players in it
I'm I already went in but I'm coming
back
out okay I need to talk to a Lavine
D has been
reset hello every why why why you do
what you have to talk to AB now oh
that's because I I didn't do things in
order oh now now I can do it again oh
let's go okay we only have to kill
Charles we could just do that and then
teleport out with the soul guard no you
got to kill everything else for me
okay we'll do it for you okay now I just
talk toil or whatever oh yeah he's
inside the
dungeon all right oh you haven't done
the
dungeon oh shoot I was about to go in
oopsies all right tank away oh you're
already okay so we should kill Charles
the last then if you have to do the
thing oh yeah for her you have to kill
everyone to summon him anyway no we
killed
him um he was just there m oh and then
we have to kill him for the
quest I don't even remember him what did
he look
like I thought he look like a bear oh
yeah here's here's
o ah kill the jelly fish to summon
Charles ah let's not kill the jellyfish
then kill them
last oh I'm
lagging EP I like how I can just chill a
little honestly when I'm like playing I
just stare at your health same same I
just always have the T look at my cast
bar and just yeah it's so chill follow
tank heal tank that's all you got to do
buff tank buff group oh that looks like
a fancy sword that does look like a good
one good that I got
it is it
good cute oh it's good better than the
Legacy
sword oh too low
[Music]
level it's so weird when the music just
stops stops I know where's the
music yeah where's my looping bgm you
need to Loop it
better oh another fancy
sword let me to GRE on that but this
one don't care I think it's not as good
as the other one that I got but now I
got both dual wielding one
day actually
I can do a wheel
too level 30 wasn't it I'll I'll turn
back into Bard for a little
bit okay
okay but I won't pretend that I'm a
Healer uh don't you have to be out of
combat oh yeah I already switched I
already switched I I got the the tiny
time window of not being in
comat yeah
g
kid once again you must
die your screams feel his blood lust
okay well got to catch
up not AAL
chart I will need on this then actually
what what is that
anyway trophy
SL okay
okay have we done have we done the two
guys before I to askas oh
okay where is he whoever that
is if that's the person that we were
trying to summon last time so hopefully
he's
summoned he would show on the map but he
doesn't show on the map so
he's not summoned
mhm okay I'll run around and
see all right these people my WD works
again hey nice I wonder what the issue
was though don't know
either maybe it was a trial I had to go
through the trial of losing your wda
yeah maybe it was the class change that
somehow changed
something learn skill Burning
metal oh
yeah hopefully Charles isn't here he's
not in here right he's not we got things
to kill got to kill the small ones
anyway
first uhoh something's after me I will
save you off of our
nun oh he just wants to confess
something well he can confess the [\h__\h]
off oh crap I am
stunned wow our healer is so
strong he spawn I see him oh yes indeed
oops you do he is he is here with
us oh I see I see
all the way around we go why do I keep
getting stuck on
this W needs to be the one to do what
awkward silence with the bgm keeping her
gu my bgm is
back I need to create town oh we can
create a guil town now cuz we're level
three okay well yeah you really
shouldn't have given me leader because
I'm not online as often as you
guys and I can't be bothered with that
[\h__\h]
but I shall be vice
leader giggy do you want to be leader
okay
n
n honored
but don't worry girl guys I will I will
transfer at the end of the
stream maybe always when I stream you
can transfer it back to me and when I'm
offline I'll transfer it back to you
guys oh but that requires some being
like active oh they're active every
single time too they are they
are okay they're
committed is it Charles
time child I got to talk to go first
okay yeah don't die easy easy I'm a bar
too there are a few addicted chickens
I've noticed I'm happy for you I'm happy
I could give this
to you yeah the gift of mmrpg addiction
Yi
PE okay she don't need this back noise
y your first am RPG oh my God
what I'm taking your
mmrpg uhoh uh that's kill it kill this P
me what
oh I'm killing what's the word again
thank you thank you okay I should do
more damage I don't know the right
weapon
virginity uh your mmrpg virginity you're
taking that from them yeah she already
did already did oh my
God unfortunately I can't take your gey
either what was your first uh MMO RPG
for GG maple story I see fre yours is
like um mine was probably World of
Warcraft if we don't count like what was
it Toontown or something like Toontown
doesn't count doesn't count Toontown
should count though should count I don't
know what the hell was going everyone
first I don't even know if I was playing
the game accurately
I don't think I was either I was too
young to understand what was going on
there was no other rounds pie yeah and
fishing and trolley I don't think I was
even doing any of that I don't remember
the trolley one I think I ran out of pie
so I summoned everyone on my friends
list that I didn't know to kill one
thing from
me yeah but World of Warcraft was
probably the the first proper one which
is a great one to start off
with and I played it with my whole
family my mommy my brother my sister
with you that's nice fun for the whole
family instead of playing uh board games
like
Monopoly you play yeah it's funny
because like whenever I would visit with
my brother we whenever we would visit my
father back in the day cuz it was like
separated families you know there we
would play actual board games then I
come back to my home and there we play
mmor
pgs the
contrast what is this who's Dominic he's
not in here is he when I click on it uh
I think might be outside of the dungeon
okay leaving this dungeon
yeah
leaving am I walking to
okay okay I'm also
out I can be on my Mountain
again I will go out then yeah sh it's
over it's over Shing it's over I will
have to do this again though oh because
yeah no what it's okay it's okay no it's
okay it's okay I have to reach level 29
anyway we can kill
Charles no it's okay I'll kill him I'll
kill him just okay maybe you can solo
Charles yeah I'll be able to do it it's
okay it'll be a trial of your strength I
got too much in my
stuff why can't I sell [\h__\h] why
not yeah that dungeon
H quite long dungeon it's not really
well
organized
[Music]
yeah delivering this
lender o an axe who uses an a probably
tank
Oh I thought you said i' I'll probably
tank no no no uh a yeah I think
so can probably just throw it
away I'm
sailing
sailing I'm sailing all my crap oh and I
have so much dies too and I don't know
what to do with them sharks I think I'm
pathing to the level 29
quest uh explore Wetlands yeah same
let's
go are we going to different
area I think so I'm excited which one is
it or have we been there
already I want to see a new
one what's the next area anyway Wetland
Wetlands I remember this area
frck oh I think that's the place I like
with the dungeon really got to go kill
things here
yeah oh there's my oh my god oh
oh core memories are being unlocked
again
a I remember just like like I I never
really had a a group early in this game
like running through all the areas
together with someone I soloed like
everything and it was kind of chill no
it was chill it's a different experience
mhm I think back then you had to party
up yeah until theyed solo mhm yeah and
then for the dung because I didn't I
didn't have anybody generally I would
just like type in the party chat looking
for group for this
dungeon and heal no one really wanted
you unless you were a Healer or a t DPS
yeah true there was an oversaturation of
certain classes for
sure
yeah tanks are really popular not so
many people play wants to be tank yeah
why I think it's because it's like it's
the attention on
you yeah anxiety is
real maybe it wasn't as cool as d d and
then for the Healer like everyone has to
rely on you but if you you can't heal
enough or if you're like too op it's
like well I'm
sorry are you guys don't attack my
enemies first okay
getting rid of all these unless your
name
isy yeah
yeah back
off okay I already did
[Music]
that
okay happy there's a happy
alpaka uh
NPC what do
you alpaca mystery capsule shop oh and
it has like dying head gear dying but
not I thought someone was dying no no oh
my God my inventory is so full yeahum B
yeah did you get expanded inventory yeah
quite a
bit qu
o oh
wow yeah
I need more food chest
more
uh stop asking
[Music]
me collect full water bottles
um I have so many Quest I I'm going to
leave like the old ones like this one
yeah the Legacy items can't be sold got
to delete
it take what a
waste I hate the ones oh they're walking
me
there I'll keep this one
claw oh people are saying you can
archive them oh yeah oh yeah yeah where
does it
go in an
archive it's like um like of course the
arch would
know where is the archive she is it your
trash can press B oh and then there's a
yellow icon that's called archive at
like below with all the other other
icons
ah oh ah
I yeah I have some memory of this
interesting okay I need to sounds
useless M Miss
n what is this cash up
items what are these the main quest n
those are not is this just like a set
lost
city but but oh no it is like something
like cash up items but need more alpaca
coins I only have 10 I can get the
copper mystery capsule I'll get
one I'm opening alpaka
gacha alaka
Goa I just got dye for color for for
coloring
wee a pack of gotta you'll be proud as a
peacock in this dashing shade of
lapis wa this is for
you but the the um clothing die for cash
up items and for non-cash up items is
different right this is for non-cat up
items as far as I know is it not I have
no idea I think so oh I think yeah one
of them a gacha one of them you can
choose the color I think mhm
what am I killing
here Lava Rock Devil
die what's with the CP meat up here we
just talk to streamer pay it no mind oh
they're at this region they like they
know us they're at this region yes we uh
yes yes we
are at a region watch shower
streams H
Live on
YouTube
yes uh M Small Indie streamer please
forgive please like And subscribe hit
that notification button did you see hit
the Bell button did you see one of the
new members her OSI Mark she has free oi
marks if I understand correctly and yeah
for like comment and sub cribe oret it's
so silly but it's so many it's funny but
it's like so many like there's too many
taken now we have to take like two oi
marks instead of one
nowadays must be rough I guess we got
kind of Lucky although mine mine bugs
out depending on the device mine splits
into an eyeball and a like a Yap icon
it's beautiful they're not wrong I guess
so I don't I don't want this maybe I
should archive it
then okay I'll do it later you it looks
you I guess I can archive it for you
you'll archive it for us
yeah okay I'm going to can I look at
your other archives too what else is in
there no you you got your own personal
archive I have a separate archive for
everyone oh so I I can't take a a little
Peak at another person allow well only
if they allow you I have to get their
consent of
course what is it it's a free country
I'll ask I suppose can I look at kiaha
can I look at your archive uh you can
watch my streams on YouTube if that's
what you
want okay but we don't call him archives
we call him waa on
demand waa on demands m w with W so in
demand
going man kayin thinks that the cleric
is so slow right it's rough just die
please just die already I just die it's
a rough
life okay yeah really those cars are
so the Car mounts not they're cool but
they don't match they don't they don't
fit into this world makes no sense to
me is your immersion being ruined
yeah
100% deliver Adventure progress report
okay I'm on
it I need to play this for members only
as well at some point because this is
such a great Community yeah it's really
fun I'm I'm so glad they allow members
to play
yeah really
nice
oops and we can grind in members only
after we're done watching all bakim
monari series seasons soon soon we can
do something else kfb soon after so many
months you will be released from your
suffering I feel that I'm like I can't
do anything until we watch all of Teen
Wolf it for real what what is that how
many seasons does that have um I only
watch Four
Seasons um and there are 12 episodes
each so it's not too bad how long is one
episode like 40 minutes oh okay that
that's that's also quite
the how many seasons are we watching
with monre series like nine I don't know
how many is it dedicated very dedicated
and then there's
movies and now there's a new season
that's where we're going towards
man I would struggle with my attention
span for these
things for the they have to watch it
watching anything that's like a really
long yeah well we are we're taking uh
breaks you know between each season and
so on like one week break but yeah one
of the it has like so much dialogue you
do actually really need to concentrate
to follow the story oh yeah so attention
span is necessary cannot have Zoomer
attention span it will be
rough rough rough rough rough
rough they Yap so much yeah have you
seen have you guys seen mon like any
season I've seen clips of it but I'm
aware it is a Yap anime mhm s like the
first
season Joi did you just [\h__\h] do that
that was my monster that was my mob you
killed it now I have to wait for the spa
you deserve jail absolutely use your
room no no children
years not in the presence of sister
she you deserve to confess your sins to
the
sister never had a year sentence maybe
one year we had one one year before but
yeah you get five years hell no I a
taking you are you have no choice ah
there he is okay the was relatively fast
I'll give you um one year
instead one year
sentence I guess she will not show up to
to see your your
cat never was planning on it no please
you Wen planning on coming to see my
cat now it's a guaranteed no what I
thought you were you really were
thinking about coming to see my cat
yours yours sure but um before I come to
see you you must show me proof that you
have a
cat what if she show Dr I don't have a
camera [\h__\h] stop ping if you're not
honest to me we cannot go anywhere with
this with this cat relationship you guys
have some really complicated
relationship asan what what quest are
you
doing um I am Expedition team fun story
four okay what does it require you to do
killing things like these flowers
killing I think the game wants me to do
the
dungeon already wow no maybe maybe soon
but I'm close to the
dungeon
[Music]
dang now I got to defeat a transformed
flower oh okay
flower flower I like the music here it's
pretty
calming yeah magical
mysterious
lower at level 30 you get the school
uniform I'm now wearing a school un free
cash
yeah if you look at your quest above it
where it says like you can pick up these
quests and then level 30 gives you a
quest to get that school uniform
you see
it above my quest you mean an
L um it's the bubble with the
exclamation point above your quest uh
tracker ah that one
self-improvement you okay you sound like
you're
cing I'm I'm fine I'm fine I'm totally
fine I just love cash up items too much
it's my
passion kill it kill it kill it kill it
kill
it okay I wish there was like a sort
setting for inventory maybe there is I
know where is it by
newest suffering oh G is here hello
suffering
oh okay yeah uh I
guess I'm going to near your backs where
where am I going
to
there how about Auto
trash are we getting the the school
outfit now oh my
God I like my yeah you get it so fast I
like my performance outfit but you know
got to got to change clothes every once
in a while
and go through them let's see is it
purple then it will match with my
alpaka
cute
cute cute very cute but I'll stay with
this
actually okay I'm going to go to Aven
cuz I have some weird territory War
Quest what okay
oh and what is that is that about the
guild war and I remember when everyone
was so elitist if they were in the the
biggest Guild or something oh yeah oh
yeah trust me I always
was elitist about it yeah and I was cool
cool Guild wow and then oh my God for
the smalls sometimes so when when
there's like let's say like free uh like
top guilds and you're in one of them and
then there's this absolute huge drama
when you decide to go to the different
you switch to different famous Guild and
your whole old Guild is like what the
[\h__\h] she's [\h__\h] abandoning us and
cheating on us but I'm just going there
why because they're winning in the Guild
Wars like when when when when your guild
isn't doing so well in the Guild Wars
anymore you got to do you you got to go
to the one you got to do what you got to
do to go to the one that's winning man
because the winning where loyalty [\h__\h]
got to win got a
win I want to go back for me I would
just say like I'm going to go Guild hop
in my other account see you
guys uh I got to defeat our acelino or
something oh oh it's not bar the the
dungeon actually yeah I have the dungeon
and chilling until you guys get
dungeon
okay the dungeon I feel kind of bad I'm
not paying attention to the story
something about being Children Of Eden
and eternal no no need we already talked
about this like there there's no need to
pay attention to the story in these kind
of games I don't think anybody expects
that hey I actually read the story from
Aura Kingdom and
forgot I was not reading that I to pay
attention Okay um what is a video say oh
I
see W lands mystery of the okay I'm
going to go get the dungeon quest to for
the
wetlands okay maybe we can do the
dungeon and then we can maybe call it a
day cuz you have another stream
G okay it doesn't we don't have if we
want to keep playing My Stream can be
pushed back no no no no it's okay
actually yeah yeah yeah I need to eat
we'll do the wetlands dungeon and then
we've done a good amount okay yeah yeah
yeah what's happening in here why are
you fighting in
here go Wetlands frog frogy wa must live
here Roy waa where are you girl you know
did you did you guys ever buy your own
merch you mean in general no in hold
look I I was forced to now buy a couple
of my own glasses because I only get one
sample right I think we all only get one
sample if we want one but I wanted a
couple more glasses cuz I really like
the glasses the first time I asked them
hey can you guys like send it to me like
maybe deducted from my payroll they were
like no cuz I thought maybe that way I
can um like go around paying certain
fees but no I had to buy it like a
normal customer so
boo it's also it's faster to buy it
yourself though because they take over a
year to give you your stuff it's not no
no no it's not going to be faster cuz
I'm ordering for Geek Jack and it takes
like long
time wait are you guys playing a brand
root Quest or something
else what I'm mean I'm it's a Branda
root Quest brand the
rout yeah were you a different dungeon
uh uh I just not in it yeah it's it's
called level 30 The Mystery of the magic
water source and oh is that wait that's
not the dungeon yet first maybe I got a
different main quest there's probably
two dungeons here
then I probably I think the other
regions also had more than one dungeon
right oh my God how did you get the
other
one uh I I just followed one of the main
stories oh they're right outside
what's going on in the world chat why
are you so many where do you come from I
love this why are you asking that you
name is like the dungeon if it's brand
the
root the will of the one called
W Tak started streaming it last week and
we just joined the game in state YouTube
streamer that's me that's me that's
her SK cat from Ohio what
what are you talking
about don't don't give me a bad
reputation with your skib
G all right well I'm I'm inside the
Branda root dungeon if that's what
you're
doing I'm trying I archived all my stuff
and I'm trying to find it oh that's the
pain that's the pain now yeah now I
can't where is it in the archive
well I I just archive things I don't do
it organized can you organize my archive
please
nope uh please I'm a Healer not an
organizer I I'm I'm not quite FR it
seems for the um dungeon I still need to
do uh it's time need to do one or two
more things
maybe lost my staff
almost
there bless you thank you we'll take a
look don't leave I oh well I lost my
staff it's fine oh no what happened did
you try to fortify it no I archived it
and I can't find it AR archive weapons
all the Legacy ones I think get archived
and then they go somewhere I can't find
the Legacy weapons you'll find better
weapons yeah
hopefully oh my god Ra ubu XD u m what
are you guys typing in the
chat they're embarrassing
you eat an eternal community viewers
reflect the
streamer no no I I I don't do that kind
of oo
stuff that's not
me that's me really ra ra ra XD ra
XD sometimes I say that as a joke I say
that I say that maybe I can't believe
you I think I say that more than uu
o is not
real it can't hurt you
yeah okay do I have the dungeon Quest
now maybe now I have it you do like your
other
costumes what is
this oh there's
certificates oh
level
31 okay I'm I have the dungeon
Quest yeah yipp
yeah ready
whenever I'm inside oh
okay
solo okay me too all right let's do this
[Music]
giggy will lead the way once again oh
running you're a Bart now too we're two
BS and one play you guys all healers I
lost my staff so I we're we're
unconventional healers my
St I'm not even using my he
SLS I'm using a sword and a shield even
though I'm b class right now whatever it
works or does yeah whatever works
I'm
buffing just that and you're
getting I'm buffing I'm buffing everyone
get buffed get buffed debuff the enemy
so hard that it explodes come on wait
what attacks do you even have don't you
have like the slowest attack technically
it I have fire and
Whirlwind yeah and rocks rocks the power
of Rock
[Music]
uhoh I think you're taking on too much
everyone's following you uhoh
[Laughter]
uhoh
uhoh I love it when you say that it is
so
calming not that all
disturbing it's okay it's okay we me now
don't worry don't worry don't worry we
got them we got them we got them we have
the AOE just kind of slow
I think you also attracted the boss yeah
I made eyes with him and I aggroed him I
see this is fine we did it it's so easy
yeah this is
fine really not a good combination of
classes but this is fine once they give
me a staff I can switch
maybe I have one lying
around I like how these look like
Christmas trees to
me just looks like Christmas treand Bush
they're Soul trees
yeah but they're shaped like a Christmas
tree should I get a Christmas tree this
here yes I want to see a
deated Christmas tree
maybe I'll put a real one into my
garden
ooh yeah but I won't like plant it just
put it there outside it will like stay
fresh longer when it's outside anyway
right cuz it's like cooler are we
already done yeah fast dungeon
what it's a it's a small dungeon it's
not the main one h
[Music]
nice
okay well
then we shall slowly prepare for the
end the end of it all yeah yeah
uninstalling Eden Eternal
what the
[\h__\h] uninstalling e
[Music]
Eternal what we care about the game what
are you
talking I care very much about the game
no no I'm kidding I'm kiding
no but yeah uh guys don't spam the world
chat too much okay not not with that was
funny but let's uh let's
behave oh you know I can turn off your
world
chat well at least like not this message
thing but the other world
chat I have been not reading the chat at
all forgot it was there I didn't read it
even mostly but yeah um let's not
Let's Not Disturb them too
[Music]
much all right well thank you
for thank you for the
gaming it's
fun yeah I love mindless
grinding
te I'm so glad I found more
likeminded people like
you and then I can teach you about maple
story soon right you can teach sh about
itbe I'm fing Eden now I can't find
another game okay may maybe next month
but did you girls see I saw something
interesting yesterday that Ragnarok
online is getting like they're they're
working on a new like oh on on two
projects yeah like a new Ragnar ROK
online free and also separately another
like game like
that so I don't know it might take ages
I just well Ragnarok 2 is a different
experience from the yeah it's completely
not Ragnarok I was fine with
it but yeah I saw that uh like in some
Japanese news yesterday I was like oh my
God oh my God oh my God exciting
oh not popular huh Rock online too why
Why didn't it become all 3D right that's
why I liked
it I prefer 3D
Fanatics like um I I will say like for
example like if we differentiate between
these kind of like what we're playing
right now 3D and then trickster online
which is 2D but like kind of top down
angle and then maple story is 2D but
it's like how do you describe
that
g um pixel side scroller yeah side
scrolling technically in terms of the
map so Sid scrolling not not really my
thing for like
MPGs if it's like trickster tail then
it's fine like I don't have a problem
with with uh uh I don't have a problem
with pixel and I don't have a problem
with 2D but like Sid scrolling
2D I don't
know yeah but it looks cute looks very
very cute and I know it's like a good
game cuz people love it so much for a
long time must be good
game yeah it has giggy's brain and heart
and soul and wallet and body bank
account
everything good for you paycheck has
that too
yeah my heart is somewhere else but
that's okay so yeah let's let's play
again sometime soon girlies yeah yeah
but also we can always play members only
but let's keep each other updated on
what level we are okay
okay and I'm is there a limit on when we
should stop leveling though no if you
feel like leveling a lot go for it go
for it we'll we'll catch up with you
yeah yeah yeah yeah who shall I give
lead yeah who is going to advance this
Guild for us so we don't have to
hopefully does not disband The Guild
once they highest
level
86 86 no but this person was all like
they didn't start with us they were
already uh high level before okay I was
like damn they grinding they have
experience but you better give me
promotion right away there you go don't
destroy the guild I trust
you I trust you the ultimate rage
quit destroys guilt explodes
guilt what me yes you you're most
experienced player among these
people so help them out yay I got I
became captain and vice leader yippee y
and now go make a town that will
surprise me next time I go
online yeah guil town I remember that
yeah thank you so much girls for playing
together
problem it was a blast once
again oh I got had a great time playing
got some stuff I think I already have
these but maybe a different color got
some cash up items again ooh this one's
cute must take
anyway I will I will send people to
whatever people there are in the streams
y can't wait to do bigger dungeons yay
more challenging ones yeah ones that
actually require a t yeah and with with
like good loot Epic Loot that will fight
over
loot okay I think I'll go read some
super chatos cuzz I'm far
behind have a good one I will also
wander off to rest
Goodbye byebye byebye by
[Music]
bye I see the meme
now the myth of consensual stream I
don't understand
this what does that mean
I don't understand the meme at
all at it why is Jesus
there sorry I want to Tab out the uh the
game lags beautifully it's a picture
show let's get out of
there ah I want to I want to grind some
more off
stream or members only but we're busy
with monad oh no oh because don't do
before marriage or
what consensual stream but what does
streaming mean in this
context guess I'll never
know oh we didn't ask Jesus oh Jesus has
to be asked
when it's before
marriage Jesus never answers like his
his phone is
busy his phone is busy constantly his
line is not
answering can't get Jesus okay ask me
instead his DMS are locked yeah he's a
busy guy very very
popular okay let's move to m
uh well you know what because we were in
a swamp just now we could go to my swamp
but I have to dress appropriately for
it there it is goodbye little bird on my
head yeah even the Super Chat reading
thing is prepared
beautiful okay oh I see I see how it is
W in the swamp yes it's my swamp now I'm
borrowing it it's okay I have frogy wa's
total
consent totally
totally yeah let's put on some BT M oh
oh wait is
that monitor and output
uh okay then I mute desktop
it was fun playing with you thank you it
was fun with you guys you guys have been
really playing a lot
huh whenever I'm not streaming or maybe
while I'm streaming when I'm too boring
for you guys well the yeah MPGs are
definitely something you can do on the
side easily like mindlessly like if it's
just like grinding dungeons not so much
maybe like proper dungeons but if it's
just like Quest thing through the game
and you just have to click something and
then the game leads you to it you can do
that very
easily while watching streams and still
somewhat paying attention
right like grinding guil Fame you guys
got to grind Guild Fame to yeah level it
up
huh what's the end game for that what do
we want with the
guild but yeah let's I I I um I am happy
that you guys are getting into it I
don't know if you guys are actually
playing uh planning to play more even if
one day we stop playing on stream uh I
don't know how long we're going to play
it honestly I I do want to get like to a
high level where we get to do high level
stuff that would be good for sure I want
to um relive all all the things I've
seen before I don't remember what the
max level was back
then maybe 70 or so and then past that I
won't really recognize things anymore
Maybe
I don't
know maybe it was already higher I can't
remember it's a long time ago well to
play at least every second day I'm
having fun currently so I'm so glad I'm
just I I really just wanted to get perms
for any of my beloved old anime mem pgs
and I would have been fine with anything
but in terms of anime mm RPGs that I
played that are still alive there's not
many out there um
so Eden Eternal was one of them but I'm
glad because that was one of my
favorites for sure I remembered one more
yesterday um was it yesterday I don't
know I was writing to shodi we were I
was uh leading her giving her some tips
to let her know what quest what level
and what quest she should go for
um uh to reach to catch up with us and
we also talk just generally about MMOs
and I told her all the games I played
before and then I remembered one that I
think I didn't tell you guys twin
Saga did I tell you twin Saga was also
one of those they all came
like kind of from the
same place felt like uh I feel like the
the order was like release order was
like maybe eat an
eternal and Dan twin Saga and then Ora
Kingdom or or Kingdom and then twin saga
no I think it was in and then twin Saga
cuz I remember people jumping uh off the
ship that is Eden Eternal and they were
like oh there's a new one out there
let's go play
[Music]
there Ora came out before twin yeah
could be and then they were jumping ship
from Ora
Kingdom Ora Kingdom's AR side was wasn't
my favorite to be honest I preferred the
the look of twin Saga and Eden Eternal
because Aura Kingdom was like kind of
too shiny I don't know something about
it yeah game hopping was very common and
they pumped out those games one after
another twin Saga I didn't play for too
long though I think no but wait twin
Saga was the one with the idol on right
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and oh that
that's so cool that was a good part that
was a cool part about twin Saga all of
these games had some small thing that um
made them stand out a little bit that
was oh was that Ora
Kingdom ah did they both have it wait
what what's the special thing about twin
Saga then hey I thought twin Saga
was let me type Idol
idolon oh um or Kingdom okay yeah or
Kingdom had the idol
on which is basically like pets that
fight for you but there's like all kinds
of different ones and they don't really
look like pets they're like people like
gods angels
whatever and then I think there were
some like pop popular
ones like more stronger
ones that people were trying to get I
think they were also like a little bit
paid to
win
maybe what was the special thing about
twin Saga
[Music]
go just said it's cute and they're small
cuz that was more chibi
style something about
it yeah there were some paid only
mhm ah the idol on fragments oh yeah
[\h__\h] yeah if you didn't want to like pay
to get them you had to collect the
fragments right but that was really
difficult cuz there's so many
[Music]
side with good or evil What in in Twin
Saga oh the idol on oh my
God H uh yeah I don't know I I don't
think I was feeling it that much the
whole idolon thing because it was such a
pain in the ass to get the cool
ones
uh yeah
no you didn't turn really good choice
because of the
[Music]
alpacas it's jumping in my
eye first time here finally Oh you mean
first time watching live
welcome but now we're on our way to read
some Super Chat
toes we drink more
[Music]
water um um wait let me Google Roar Rock
online
to uh oopsie
two
oh looks a different from my
[Music]
memory
H that does look very different I was
thinking of
oh is
it it's been too
long it with Ragnarok
2 um was that game by any chance like
kind of cursed with like its release
that it took so long and and maybe it
was abandoned once or so or am I
thinking of something
else does anybody
know yeah
[Music]
not many people can relate it seems talk
to
me abandon and relance okay cuz I feel
like I have this
memory
of
playing like an an anime m g that was
abandoned but then somebody like made up
like I don't maybe maybe I shouldn't
talk about
it abandoned before it was was even
really launched though I think I don't
know I don't know what these memories
are so many I just played too many of
these games and the memories are
mixing together blue protocol is sad
yeah blue protocol just took too long
blue blue protocol should have either
been a thing when MMO RPGs were still
very popular or it should have just like
taken less time and in development hell
and then it could have maybe kept up the
kept kept the hype and everything the
promotion hype and everything going it
just took too long so I guess like the
people that were waiting for maybe also
forgot about it and
yeah it's so sad I feel like it would
have been also a decent
Community play together game
if they would have at least released it
an Ian but they said they would and then
they never did and they just had the
Japanese server running and that was not
successful enough for them
to yeah launch the Ian server man
man if they would have launched it maybe
we could have kept it alive is what I'm
thinking should have just believed in in
kfp in the power of kfp the KF power of
the kfp people
[Music]
H yeah we we would keep it
alive I would have made other members
play it too other I members and ID
[Music]
members oh well and where do we have to
continue
reading let's get to Super
chats shall we
[Music]
show maybe a capella video soon finish
maybe maybe
[Music]
maybe w
sorry uh Seven Days to Die day five no
don't worry don't worry don't worry
don't worry I scrolled
[Music]
up GD GD is losing it G is like i' I'm
done with you I've lost my patience I I
say what you got to read and then you
don't read the
chat no come
on can't be that bad
right I usually pick it up I usually
do at least when it comes to me asking
what stream I got to
read I know there's other times when I
play games and I ask a question and then
I I look at the while I'm asking the
question I maybe I wait for like 2
seconds but of course there's a delay so
then I lose my patience so then I look
away and then I forget about it because
I get distracted by the game again and
then like 5 10 20 minutes maybe hours
later I ask the same question again and
I wait again and maybe that time I'll
wait long enough to actually get my
answer some I I would say i' I never do
that more than three times in a row
[Music]
like the same question in one stream
maximum three times the third time I'll
be like sorry sorry sorry I I know I
asked it many times I'll actually wait
for your answer
now and sometimes I get one guide that's
on
you okay this only has a few super chats
so we're done immediately ja 47 D gin D
Vagabond d o from Guam wow
nice fight knocker dun V faction
dun Dale Solstice dun rainard dun and
Richard G
D
okay next
one I already read the Treasure Mountain
H okay Mirage dance shot
version has fre super chats Mir Dance
Shop
version finally has 100K
views and four blood got 4 million views
and I think something else also reached
like some big milestone
recently don't know what it was another
song did you see the hoto R update well
I saw many updates but like I wanted to
get my and then it's like they really
shouldn't I don't know it's too hard to
get see what you want like bro it's too
hard I got to say
like
very so
so hurdle
high that
it
yeah kind of makes it impossible for me
unless I stream it like 10 times 5 hours
each which I'm not going to
[Music]
do hit 9 million oh my
god well jaob 47 G and space wonderful
prodction and
then uh day six of seven days to die
which is this one cute not the
bicycle that was a motor motor bike
they're keeping the service Alive by the
way for us or not really I don't know if
they're keeping the Servers Alive but
they said like whatever uh in any case
our characters will be safe that's what
they said
yipp check 47 D zip D jino thanks for
the pinky today makes my fifth birthday
with since your debut and once again
another stream on my birthday oh lucky
there's other people who I never stream
on their birthday it seems I always
appreciate keeping us entertaining
entertained and putting lots of effort
for us uh I think this might be my first
time I have requested this but can I get
a happy birthday song of course of
course your fifth birthday
wao did you never get a happy birthday
song
before happy birthday to you m
AIC in the happy birthday Jin I sang the
German version for
you
woohoo good job on getting older good
job on staying alive it's not a
given especially as a
chicken oh my God speaking of my mom was
here right for two nights and and you
know she yaps a lot and she yaps a lot
about her garden and everything and um
she currently doesn't have any animals
but she used to have chickens but she
wants chickens again but she first has
to build a cpop etc and everything takes
a long time but she was um I don't know
why she was talking about
chickens and then um I don't know why we
got there again but sheal she reminded
me that she
like killed the chicken before to eat it
and I don't know why but she told she
she proudly shared with me that she
killed a rabbit to kill it to eat
it
um but
like like not a random one out there not
a random one that she found in the G in
the park or so
but like I was like okay okay man
chickens are one thing and I know people
eat a lot of rabbits like there's
rabbits do and this and that but rabbit
rabbit goes another step further into
like cute pet territory more than a
chicken and so like she was explaining
to me how she does it and I'm like no no
no stop talking I don't want to hear the
details and she keeps on talking and
talking telling me how she like uh makes
them numb and all that oh
no
no it's so hard to listen
to and then she starts another tangent
about
how I don't know I think it was about
chickens how how like that's the way the
way she does it is better anyway
because you know chicken in like those
like uh like big big places where
they're being held they have you know
and she starts talking I already know
where she's going and I'm like don't
tell me I already know about that stuff
I already don't tell me this like
horrifying terrifying story of how
they're being kept and killed I don't
need to know that I already know it and
she's like oh no no and then she keeps
on yapping yapping and she gets to that
point anyway I'm like I knew you were
going to end up there and tell
me I know he and she's like ah oopsie
I'm like
[Music]
br oh well but yeah it's it's I
understand I I get it like of course
like she probably would give chickens a
better living condition than uh in like
how to say the big factories
but it's still hard to imagine like
doing it
yourself it's just uh
uh I can't think about it it's the act
of doing
[Music]
it poor poor animal I don't want to take
something's life with my own hands it's
different when you do it with your own
hands but then again you know I I
understand like especially for people
who have like huge farms being able to
live off of your
own like
cycle of life
like having cows and chickens and
whatever and then they make new babies
and then you know you know that's great
like being able to keep yourself alive
like that without having to rely on um
grocery stuff overpriced probably too
and mistreated and
whatever surely that's great
and
yeah but then you
also have a connection with
them you hunt deer cuz otherwise they
overpopulate and crash the
[Music]
ecosystem yeah well but yeah if you
raise those animals then you have a
connection with that my mom even said
she was kind of sad when she had to
end the chicken's life cuz she would
just sit there in the coupe and talk to
them for hours and watch them for
[Music]
hours
yeah sad isn't that sad
[Music]
well yeah I I I I think it's cool to
have chickens just so like get daily
eggs man that's nice eggs eggs eggs eggs
why did I stop reading super chats oh
because of the Super Chat
why why why did I get
there anyway spank andham thanks for the
red super
chat uh saying my cat my girl cat used
to crawl into bed and warm up her eyes
cold paws on my
back you know you know when when I led
my Kos into the garden and then they
come back inside I always make sure to
hug them so that their cold fur is
getting warm again and then their paws I
have to squeeze and massage them and
hold them to make them warm again and
they don't mind they don't they let me
do all of that they're so
[Music]
cute but the Paw the paws oh
yeah I love them love them so much thank
you for giving me another opportunity to
talk about my cat's spanheim you're the
best today I had a really cute moment
where I was going to walk away from my
desk and go into a different room but I
noticed that both of my cats were on my
guest bed which is like next to my table
basically and I noticed they were like
curled up there and they were looking at
me like like Mommy are you leaving are
you going to a different room we are so
cozy here and I was like oh man they're
they're positioned in a way that if I
lay down I could probably hug both like
I could I could pet both this is perfect
so I laid
down and
I I I lay down with like chunky wonky
right in front of my head and um me
petting her with my right arm and and
smoothie on around my knees and me
petting her with my left
arm and then chunky wonky she she
sometimes she's so cuddly and cute but
she likes to be in her box if I lay down
next to her without her being in her box
she will often move away to a different
spot that's still close to me but she's
like
uneasy but this time she stayed and then
after a few seconds she like her head
was lifted but she like lowered it again
and then I felt her like her head kind
of touching my forehead and I'm like oh
my God this is so peaceful I will
die and then she got more and more
relaxed and she kind of stretched her
paw a little bit and her paw was
basically touching my
[Music]
eye it was a good cuddly moment it
didn't last very long but
[Music]
yeah I'm so happy I was I was thinking
like after all these
years how many years do I have my cats
probably like six seven years at this
point it's surprising it doesn't feel
like that long but it's a lot of time by
now and even after all these
years every time I see
them and I see them a lot every time I
see them I'm still like head over heels
for them still and I'm still like squeal
in and
squeaking and so lydy and
like you're so beautiful I love you
so
so I was
thinking I got to say a little bit of a
GF thing
okay prepare
yourself imagine if I could invest this
kind of love and energy into someone I
would be maybe I would be like that too
a human would I though actually maybe
not but imagine let's just say I would
wow wow I would never get sick of you
every morning every every hour of the
day I would be like oh my God I love you
so much you're so cute you're so
beautiful maybe not quite like that but
even after years wouldn't that be
ideal but that's too clingy maybe okay
but at least wouldn't it be nice to have
someone appreciate you and show you that
they still love you every single day I
think I would generally appreciate that
of course not to the extent of the way I
treat my
cats that's a bit too much and yeah I
don't like clingy either I don't like
clingy at all but but having your
significant other tell you and and
remind
you I think that's important to me and I
think maybe even if you say oh I don't
need that I think it still feels
[Music]
good cuz maybe sometimes you have times
where you doubt
it there's certainly a lot of insecure
people out there who do need
that verble reminder
[Music]
yeah so
this but maybe I will never love one as
much as I love my
[Music]
cats which is just that doesn't mean
that I can't love someone else but the
level of Love is just different probably
like my cats are just on a different
level like those are my my
children yeah I will protect them with
my
[Music]
life you probably love a baby similarly
yeah I wonder but they don't have fur
[Music]
so I don't think I would want to cuddle
with them as
much like I can honestly stay I don't
think I would love my cats and and this
is this is shallow of course but I
wouldn't love my cats as much if they
didn't have
hair I I wouldn't have gotten them in
the first
place
so
that's
valid really
really yeah biolog yeah yeah surely like
it would be a different Bond even if it
doesn't have hair a human baby would be
different I guess yeah stinky
baby they're
[Music]
stinky I'm happy with my cats for now
surely baby monkey why would I get a
baby monkey if I can just have my cats
then if I'm if it's in if it's between a
baby monkey and a human baby and a cat
no if it's between a baby monkey and a
and a cat I would take the
[Music]
cat would you like us if we didn't have
feathers um
sure
sure would you like yourself if you
didn't have feathers though let's answer
that question
[Music]
first I got a point right the the the
feathers is what makes you so great
you're so fluffy
and M
[Music]
hug and without the feathers you can't
even attempt to
fly you need your feathers would you
love me without my feathers I mean
that's just too too like I probably
wouldn't change so
much you guys change more drastically
dramatically no hey
one
[Music]
what why do you why don't you
have why don't you
have why don't you have my oi Mark in
your Twitter
anyway are you embarrassed to be
a
[Music]
fan I mean it's always always been like
that I guess
[Music]
but you forgot to put what do you mean
what do you mean you can't forget
it and then like 90% of what you retweet
is to Senpai
anyway which is fine you can have more
than one but where's the wa content
[Music]
just just saying I
think cuz you watch all my streams so
you surely like
me I don't understand you're such at it
yeah I know it's been like this for
years I like to yeah I'm not saying to
not retweet or
so but why can't we go hand in hand me
and
[Music]
to okay
I I'll move on from that it doesn't
bother me at all
head
holding just a little bit of
an
an you
know uh super chatos
[Music]
how do I read your name you donate in
dollars is it
subtle was
it we donate doll but satle right
satle and write it a English message but
Japanese name satle satle d
Elie py Cody Co D Nathan coton thanks
for the red
chat you said you want money to gamble
with Tanto with gamble with
Tanto did I say
so oh oh uh in real life huh yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah one day gambling with
whole life girls somewhere out there
just just don't worry don't worry we can
control ourselves we're fine just like a
you know every
there's so many people who just go on
like a onetime fun Las Vegas trip or
so who knows maybe one of the
members I I will end up married with
them although I don't think I can happen
with me cuz I don't drink so it would
have to be very
consciously can't happen accidentally
like in the TV shows cuz you're drunk
and then you wake up and you realize
you're married and you're like what the
[\h__\h]
guess that won't happen with me might
might be someone who do you think in Ian
let's say all of Ian goes on a Las Vegas
trip
and they get drunk except the ones who
don't drink narissa doesn't drink guys
so I don't think it will happen with
her Iris gets very drunk I suppose beta
you think those two would have a
situation like
that Cece and G oh yeah oh yeah might
happen I can see
it
uh
nice
nice yeah those two are likely but okay
to be honest I don't think any of this
is likely but if if anything then those
two would be most likely Maybe
I just figured Nissa would get married
regardless of the alcohol perhaps yeah
neriss and
[Music]
shine but Shin doesn't drink alcohol
either even even even if narissa would
do it without alcohol would sh do it
without
alcohol I think
not Shing is a tease
enough of
that uh where was I yeah thank you
Nathan
na instead of gambling in Vegas you
should host a whole life casino type
stream where you all play different
games together and see who wins the most
points at the end of the night all
different games you mean as in like
casino type
games that's that's sounds very
complicated would need different povs
from everybody
different games would need like some
kind of I'm surely there's a casino
Simulator game out there oh
100%
H I don't want to play that as a big
collab I would just want to play that
alone I just want to play that
alone you know what could work
well like playing like Casino simulator
and like sitting at the slot machine
endlessly
while reading super
chats that kind of has good Synergy I
[Music]
think like in a Yakuza game I don't know
but speaking of Yakuza games um the
tiger girl from the new
members she gives me Yakuza Vibes too
like I I want her to play Yakuza game I
wonder if she likes yaku Yakuza games
cuz have those sweatpants with that sick
jacket
it but for real what did you think about
my Synergy suggestions I want her cuz
like they're both tall and and blonde
and somehow their eyes somehow give me a
similar Vibe I want Kyla and her to do a
collab I don't know how they would
communicate but
still and then her and ban Senai they
also have like a similar body type and
it's a lion and a tiger
and they're both like on the cool side
lookwise and then I was thinking there's
the the gray-haired girl she would have
visual Synergy with
Zeta oh yeah the kiky girl that name is
so
cute but it seems like when some it's
like when somebody had a stroke writing
out Ki
I saw the post um of like trying to
figure out how you would get
a a couple name going between
us but yeah everybody looks really cute
really really cute there's another blue
kusogaki once again very
curious about that girl if she will
be you know living moving up to the Blue
kusogaki
[Music]
Legacy and yes yes you girl you guys
have spammed me on Twitter of course I'm
aware you guys don't need to spam me on
Twitter like did you see did you see did
you see that there's a there's a a girl
that's drawn by the rise artist of
course I saw because that's the first
thing I noticed and the first thing that
I reacted to H because okay so here's
the thing um whole live artists like
somebody who drew some like one of
us they cannot be commissioned from
anybody besides the girl who is drawn by
them so if I wanted like merch or
anything drawn by that artist I can't so
I have a problem now because actually uh
that artist I I you know cuz I've been
like getting different artists for my
outfits each
time
and before this happened I requested
that artist but at the time it just
didn't work out with the schedule so I
was like okay no problem I'll try again
another time because probably their art
style like they probably more interested
in like drawing cuz I think this was
like for like fever night probably I was
like ah maybe that's not even their
thing anyway like maybe I should get
them for you know an outfit that works
better for what they usually draw and
now it's impossible
that was like my
inner now it's
impossible I missed it I missed my
chance it's so
over I'm so sad but at the same time you
know it's nice to see the artist being
picked up by Hol and made into a
mama yeah it's nice to
see yeah I'll I'll find you know there's
there's so many artists out there I'll
I'll find others I still have others
that I'm interested
in to
commission so yeah but that's just a one
one
funny uh
anecdote I was like no way cuz I checked
out every artist first I was like oh
does this Arty look familiar to oh this
one looks familiar to me oh my
God I wonder I wonder if she
likes uh arar
[Music]
games more Tales of artists I mean there
aren't that
many what about no I like no's art too
very
pretty hopefully she does you should ask
her um well well well give it some time
maybe May I'm very curious to their
debuts you know it's always nice to see
if there's overlapping interests in
terms of games and so on and music and
so
on so it's this
huh uh Prime Time JC what am I doing on
Sunday a members only wait [\h__\h] wait are
we overlapping at all cuz I was going to
start members
only oh [\h__\h] wait there might be some
overlap
uh cuz I started 400
p.m. my time
that's no up don't they start at like
8:00 p.m. and then they have well I
might not be overlapping with their
debut but they have like don't they have
like a k relay right after the
de but with that there's no rule that I
don't uh that I can't overlap with that
so it's fine but uh oh it's a cover
relay oh I see I
see so okay I'm not overlapping with
their debuts okay
[Music]
is it oh yeah is it 8 hours time
difference right now to Japan from me to
Japan so it's they I think they start at
noon for
[Music]
me and they're doing only half hour
debuts times have changed it's become a
norm to do shorter debuts
no no I know there's people who prefer
that but at least do it like 40 minutes
or
45 and the debuts are zooming it's so
tight like 30 minutes 30
minutes you like it short well one day
it will be 15 minutes yeah we're we're
taking less less
time fre minutes is really short I mean
some people can make deal with that too
but then there's others like big yappers
who have a lot to share in their debut
they might need more time but okay it's
I mean I guess it's like less pressure
when you know ahead of time that you
only have 30 minutes then you'll only
prepare stuff for 30 minutes and
then I guess it's going to work
[Music]
out okay well I'll be awake for it I'll
be
watching thankfully those are at a very
watchable time for
[Music]
me that came I I should have known like
I I should have been aware but I I swear
like on the very same day when they
posted the internal
notification that we were getting new
kis on the very same
day they posted another completely
unrelated long ass notification and
nowadays they're really long because
they post like an extremely
long uh text in Japanese and then right
below they post the same text extremely
long in English and I saw like I I
usually I wake up uh and I'm in bed and
I take my phone and the first thing I
check is like all dimensions and I see
that the unrelated thing that's like not
so important cuz I wasn't part of the
GTA
thing I was like wasn't even it wasn't
even
uh like during the GTA project no no no
no don't don't think you're the wrong it
was something something about like GTA
blah blah blah so I see that and I'm
like whatever I'm not even that doesn't
even relate to
me and I ignore it and above that was
the notification
[\h__\h] I had no
idea I was so caught off guard just like
you guys for the first time ever I'm as
caught off guard as you you guys
were can relate to you
[Music]
now what it's Saturday oh [\h__\h]
right ah 9th not
10th
oh
oh that that's literally like during the
jakata concert
[Music]
bro like literally in the middle of
it
[Music]
well yeah I'll excuse myself from the
world tour concert
Jaa I'm sure everybody will
understand I'll excuse myself I'll uh go
watch the deut okay you understand yeah
yeah no I'll watch the I'll watch the v
i us I'll but the thing is if it's not
live I'll just skim through it I'll just
skim to the the slides that say their
interests and
everything oh
well oh well well as long as you stay
for Atlanta I don't
mind as long as nobody debuts during
Atlanta
a why overlap
why okay back to Super Chat reading
where was
[Music]
I
here okay uh J SW sent right chat than 7
days to d zombie preparation and future
Casino trip funds if there's anything
left over thank
you future Casino trip must happen it
must become real it must be
true thank you I'm looking forward to it
already Elsie La d tanaz d the steel D
sa 11 D GD D and Jackson f d thank you
guys for appreciating the Clementine
Clementine Clementine
family what a good
family good
memories okay next is the finale
I'm catching up guys I'm catching
up dog Hood thanks for the pinky donates
to Wawa in my sleep oh oh yeah fry me
just like that Wawa so golden brown and
crispy that's what you dream about
that's a
nightmare poor you you must be so
stressed
out thank you Doug Hood I hope your
dreams get better even though they're
probably good for you you you like it
huh you like
it oh sorry freak kiss
accidentally take 47 D you got Mike D
Cruz D Prince of Denmark D chocolate and
Sonia thingss for two pinkies while
today I had the pleasure of finding out
that you were already streaming when I
got off work I got to listen to you Yap
like it was a podcast while I was
driving back home oh
nice on most days I would be listening
to your music in the car instead so I
didn't get to put Mirage on repeat
today uh I was here to support you T
even when stuck in traffic
doll how long do you drive around happy
to have such an awesome ooshi thank
you
Yi
[Music]
yippe you are you in your car A Lot 1
hour oh okay that's not too bad but am I
always streaming during that one
hour sheesh
[Music]
blast it you need subwoofers to play my
stuff no not always
huh it was an afteron for me which is
rare oh because of Seven Days to Die
being at a unusual time afternoon
[Music]
I guess because we ended up uh
continuously like starting these streams
earlier and earlier because Europe gang
was
[Music]
suffering makes sense
well for
once yeah little bit of compromise thank
you so much for
watching hope you enjoyed the ark
Christopher Wells D and the steel D and
the steel D Nathan cotton thanks for the
pinky I've really enjoyed this
blacksmith wa Arc you must have really
enjoyed this week of zombie game always
ajy to see tenture having fun thank you
I did enjoy it uh I I really had a good
time it wasn't as scary as I thought it
would be at all and yeah the only bad
thing was the time zone but you know
it's just like it was a one time thing
and once in a long time thing
so can adjust to it and then go back to
normal not a big deal but sure of course
I also would prefer it at different
times but there's still an um like not
enough European members I guess to
really push hard for that and even even
with these current European members it's
like CeCe seems to just stay awake for
anything really no matter how often
noever no matter how
late t a collab at 4:00 a.m. 5: a.m.
she's in
it yeah I think
um herb is a little bit more like
protective of her sleep and all that a
little bit more but she'll still also
wake up for
things at weird
times so
yeah with with such openness to Crazy
time slots
uh still makes it hard
to trying to assert dominance in the
European time slots but you know when I
organize something it's usually at a
decent time time for me so just got to
keep on organizing things
myself now that streams in Japan times
most time she can call yeah yeah like
living in Japan it's or Far
East makes it pretty comfortable to do
na Prime
Time yeah
[Music]
you should organize a European only
stream um but then it's like who do you
mean you're people who live in Europe or
people who are
[Music]
European but sure surely one day for
sure Sur she yeah well sh yeah and and
with with with speaking of we having to
organize things to be in the European
times and look look how we started at
700 p.m. my time today uh and I dragged
two and a girls into
it hey hey W about doing Europe European
viewers a favor
here I'm dragging them into this they
already stream kind of early generally
those two early for their time zone but
I made them stream even
earlier thankfully they're very open to
it and
very very okay with
it I'm glad I'm
glad so you know every now and then I
might be able to do that but not always
[Music]
11:00 a.m. 1 p.m. used time yeah I mean
on the workday for you guys to watch it
is a little bit o maybe sorry but well
you guys are used to it you guys are
used to it there viewers maybe not so
much ground is
collab um I don't know grounded collab I
don't know at what time we would do it
it depends where uh
bi boo would
be at the time where that would take
place right cuz biboo was going to bio
would be part of the group right cuz
she's the
child
um but I'm hoping to get the grounded
collab going
for the end of the
year I'm I'm I'm
[Music]
hoping how long I wonder how long does
it take when if we wanted to finish it
grounded there is like a goal there as
far as I know so there's a game length
it's not like endless
[Music]
a tryle ah has there something been
announc I only saw a tweet
from uh
hure uh like hinting at an
[Music]
update hasn't been
announced ooh well then I must play it
it 15th
[Music]
November 15th let me put it in my
schedule
[Music]
okay okay it's in my
schedule oh I'm
excited oh let's go let's
go want to check the trailer oh there a
trailer reaction okay
okay is it on YouTube
look
cure 23 hours no that's something else
six days ago which one is there a very
new
one there's one from six days ago oh I
guess that
one okay
oh you didn't hear
it okay I won't show you but have I seen
this
wait was P not in the game yet somehow
it feels like she was but okay third gen
update okay okay
[Music]
okay
cute new
music
[Music]
you w oh
oh did she just throw a bicycle wait
four fourth
gen
oh wow two gens or even
more well that's what is this beach
place maybe that already
existed wow
oh the music is
fun looks
difficult but I've done pretty well last
time I played it right oh oh gambo gambo
slots there's a [\h__\h] slot
machine oh there's carts wait is
this what cart game is that an
roulette course what course runny h
[Music]
o God gains oh it's a
triathlon oh it's a Coliseum no you
fight as the
mascots oh this is a p p brain or a
different P
[Music]
song yeah
okay two
gens two gens
cute
wow okay I have to play of
course it's been a while got to bet get
back into the
groove O
Okay math problems to solve in the game
what the [\h__\h] why would they do that why
do they hate
me why
why math problems
why need a warmup stream n I'll play
maybe like an hour off stream to get
back into it
but no warmup
stream bit of cash to spending me true
we need some
[Music]
cash okay where was I um
here yeah Mo d h steel d h d Max the
first D just another okay Jim Tracy
[Music]
D Jim Tracy
D random collusion thanks for the red
super chat thanks for sticking with it
wa love to see the whole family having
fun together always hope you have a good
rest after thank
you it was a very special event for me
cuz I felt very involved and um immersed
and
yeah I I definitely felt like I had to
be online every day because if I miss a
day then you know the girlies would be
the ones who were online every day would
be like ahead of me and I have to catch
up and then I'm just not not that
involved anymore got to be there every
day yeah also as the armor like I took
up that part the job so I had to be on
top of it
[Music]
but I likeed that
feeling being
very
uh involved
and yeah
crucial family car yeah we'll definitely
get a car going next time for sure we're
close I'm getting there already have car
parts
anyway yeah
you sound so happy get to get presents
well it wasn't really presents it was it
was offerings to make things for them so
really it was me in the end presenting
presents to
them yeah but around the end we really
ran out of like materials here and there
even like the basic
materials and that was rough rough
trying to I'm was trying to make things
for everybody but ah the [\h__\h] hods
the Searing kits and all that the
glue Ian REO two in seven days toight no
no no
no oh where was
I oh yeah hope you have a good rest
after thank you so much random collusion
I rested a lot took me a while to get
back to my sleep schedule I think but
we're good now recently I've been always
getting up before like 12:00 which may
seem late to you anyway but I think
there were times where I wouldn't get up
before 2:00 p.m. so currently I'm doing
pretty
decently and I always fall asleep so
fast man I don't want to fall asleep so
fast I want to watch things on the
[Music]
TV get that sunlight yeah I'm still
getting some sunlight
by the I tried that stupid sad lamp as a
makeup table lamp cuz it was like kind
of too dark there anyway but the light
is so [\h__\h] like as a as a lamp for
lighting up your face it's so [\h__\h] it's
so harsh and [\h__\h] and not spreading
enough over my face it's like [\h__\h]
yeah it's a sad lamp don't like
it I don't know what to do with it maybe
I can still I think I already threw away
the box that it came in so I don't know
if I can still send it back I don't want
it I don't believe in I don't know why I
bought it in the first
place I think when I was still like just
thinking about it in theory it I still
thought okay like there must be
something about this lamp that it does
besides just being very bright
but then in
Practical
prac
I the moment I turn it on I'm like wait
that's just light what is that going to
do for me and may maybe okay maybe it
does do something but it when my brain
doesn't take part in the belief system
then it won't do anything for me I have
to believe for it to work probably have
to believe in it just like you know any
kind of what do you call
[Music]
it
plant yeah placebo effect I don't know
if there's more behind it than a placebo
effect if it works like that then that's
great but it won't work for me cuz I
don't believe it has a bit of UV a bit
of UV helps your body make vitamin D H I
see I see cuz like yeah when you're out
in the
sun yeah so yeah okay that makes sense
right that makes sense but I just feel
dumb when I'm sitting in front of this
bright
lamp it doesn't feel like anything's
happening and of course it wouldn't be
something that would be so
obvious I can't feel vitamin D Creation
in my body I can't s
that maybe it is happening but I just
feel dumb in the process of it I'd
rather just take my vitamin D
pills just keep using it n i don't I
feel just stupid just makes me feel
stupid Mo
maxing and
Mo just turn it on when you
stream no it's kind of
uncomfortably
bright I feel
[Music]
dumb walking my dog every morning oh
yeah I'm sure that that's good but at
some point in the winter morning it will
be [\h__\h] dark outside depending on
what you see as morning but that's
depressing I used to get so depressed
when I was still going to school like
winter versus Summer
when you go to school in summer or like
spring summer it was bright outside and
then in winter it's so [\h__\h] dark when
I go to school it's like so
depressing like I shouldn't be out here
I should be in
bed I hated that always had to get up
quite early for most of the schools that
I went to cuz I I it took me a while to
get there and I always had to do my
makeup because I felt so ugly had to do
my makeup every day install my bangs
every day before so always needed like
an hour so I usually woke up at like
6 was it extra dark thanks for
[Music]
depressing
yeah school could never hurt you again
thank God thank God sometimes I dream
about like having to go to school or
having to learn for a test or so having
a test up coming or so terrifying [\h__\h] I
wake up and I'm so glad that I don't go
through that
[Music]
anymore I don't envy any students out
there unless they're doing good and
they're enjoying school for whatever
reason good for you good for you I did
not have that
experience I mean surely there's also
some things that I would miss about
school just
like the youthfulness the fact that I
still had
youth then I was
young and then I still had my whole life
ahead of me cuz now I don't cuz now I'm
70 years
[Music]
old still a baby
no 7 years old baby to
you wow
that's I mean that's good to
[Music]
hear but
yeah generally I don't want to go back
to that time I was doing bad at
school at least seemingly in the things
that
mattered and I was always
unpopular always felt uncomfortable
[Music]
H yeah my only
Escape was playing mm RPGs with no break
in my summer
break it was really an escape for
me I mean I would play them throughout
the year but even more so during summer
breaks
yeah sure you guys can relate just to
playing any kind kind of game as your
escape from the
reality
[Music]
yeah School
s it's just also like the moral my moral
was so [\h__\h] because I was doing well in
je in school generally but like there
were certain things that I could never
do well in and it was just like math and
maybe like physics or so but that was it
okay in my first school I was doing
really badly at Latin too but that
didn't matter matter anyway later on but
yeah math made me cry same same
[Music]
you probably didn't have good teachers
no I think I did I had good teachers but
like somewhere in the beginning I must
have gotten lost and then never able to
catch up and then the pressure and just
the already the feeling of being a loser
and not understanding
things would always be a blockage for
me I was never able to to get past that
I guess and then I would repeat a year
and have a different teacher and they
teach things differently and but in a
way I would be motivated and try to take
that as an opportunity to relearn things
but no didn't work out either feel even
more
stupid
fu yeah it just made me feel like [\h__\h]
school made me feel like
[\h__\h] did you do art in class what do you
mean in art class or in any other class
I the saddest thing is just that
I I I was so proud and so happy that I
got into art school because that was
really a big achievement and not
everybody got into that school you had
to take a test and everything I was so
proud to get into that because the
school that I was in before so the art
school started from high school onwards
and I in in my junior high school right
before that I was in a really shitty
school and and like had a really bad
reputation but I I made it into like a
real upgrade of a
[Music]
school and I get into the super cool
school that I aspire to be in that I
could really Flex that I got into it and
then it doesn't [\h__\h] matter that I do
well and everything else because there's
like like those curriculums that by
Austrian School law you have to pass
them otherwise you're [\h__\h] and those
are just like math and
English and German I think those are
like there there's main curriculums that
no matter what Focus the school has you
have to pass the the basic school
curriculums no I mean not it makes sense
cuz you can't if you're still in high
school you should still
be able to do those most basic things
right but it [\h__\h] me
over [\h__\h] me
over surprised English is part of
that well that's the reason why I speak
English so well cuz we take it very
seriously here we have good good
education on English language here
and I think that's important
that's um would kind of suck if we
didn't put so much value on
that yeah I think most European
countries put a lot of importance on
that a lot of weight it makes you feel
better I think you're smart you speak
multiple languages and can travel abroad
without help yeah I had to
adapt and become mature very early on in
my life and I think I grew a lot in
terms of maturity early
on overcame many
challenges somehow made my way to get to
this point uh
thankfully school doesn't matter to me
my the way I did in school doesn't
matter to me
now thankful
but I mean even even though I did badly
at school even without Holo I would have
been fine because I ended up you know
going to Hotel school and getting the
hotel School degree or whatever you
would call it in English and I was set
up just fine I I would have been fine
getting jobs just fine getting jobs in
hotels would have been easy and if I
wanted to be
[Music]
more I don't know know how to say if I
wanted cuz I
I I was just like working part-time
before um Holo because I still wanted to
do other things on the side and if I
wanted to I could have gone full-time
and I could have you know probably tried
to get promoted and this and that but I
wasn't even that motivated at that time
I was like I I don't
know I don't feel like wanting to get
promoted I don't feel like working
towards
that cuz yeah but I could have been fine
if I if I if I came back after that one
year working holiday during Corona in
Japan if I would have come back without
uh whole life job in my pockets in my
bags I would have just gone back to
working in a
hotel and it wouldn't have been great
but I would have been
fine but
definitely I'm glad that things turned
out this
way I don't know why I'm yapping about
such things right now man I'm
hungry I'm so
hungry
yeah that would have been a sad return
it was a sad return nonetheless because
I never got to do what I wanted to do
during the working holiday and that was
a once in a lifetime thing so it was
definitely sad nonetheless but it it it
had a
good Band-Aid on top of it like hey at
least you get this not what you expected
but now you have a sick job that is
going really well that's changing your
life
so I mean going really well I say I was
still suffering
but mentally you guys know I wasn't
doing
well it was harsh but it was still
lifechanging and it was still going well
in terms
of
well
yeah depends on how you look at
[Music]
it but I've
endured similar hardships throughout my
life from Liv from my Liv yeah yeah
lives many times and um in the
end I
am too stubborn to give up when times
are difficult I must endure to
see a positive ending
[Music]
even if it looks
impossible even if it looks
difficult
uh I don't know what I would have
studied if I ever went to University it
would have been difficult for me to get
there in the first place cuz I just
wasn't smart enough but I don't
know I wanted to do art stuff but uh I
don't think I would have even if I would
have continued in that path I don't
think I would have gone to University
for it I would have just finished my art
school and that would have probably been
plenty on my
resume
to continue with that and get a proper
like graphic design whatever
[Music]
job you don't have to be smart to study
at a
university well I mean you got to get
through high
school at
least but I will say maybe it is more
difficult in some countries than it is
in
others to get for high
school might be easier in other
countries than where I was I don't
[Music]
know so I'll give myself credit there
maybe
[Music]
maybe you going have to be smart to get
through high school what what what what
was I failing what would you
say nah I know it was like like I feel
like anybody can learn anything um but
it's really just like yeah the
pressure and students like when you
already don't feel comfortable in school
it will
also kind of block your brain from
learning it's all kinds of factors going
into
[Music]
it maybe I should have been
homeschooled but I don't I don't think
my mom would
have wanted or even considered that it's
homeschool that I don't even know
anybody I don't think it's that common
here
homeschooling I think it's way more
common in like
America
yeah I don't know a single
person who got homeschooled and I I
never even heard about anything like
that maybe that's a very American
[Music]
thing h
but I do feel like a one-on-one setting
Focus maybe that would have helped
[Music]
me but
well it's not all that simple and easy
anyway let's get out of this topic I'm
sick of it I'm
just sick of it this is depressing what
a depressing
[Music]
topic um thank you random collusion
Jackson thank you for the pinky one of
the greatest collabs and so much of that
was thanks to you keeping wahah wahah
well thank you for watching it for
watching my streams on this series a
full
week of for me late night streams but I
hope I hope you guys enjoyed it it was
the same game I hope you guys didn't get
sick of it saying I'm over and over
but I think it was mostly about the
interaction and the the bonding not just
for me but for you guys
too so yeah thank you so much for
supporting me through it Eden Exile dun
and G
dun there it goes there it
[Music]
goes oh
oh Super Mario Party Jambo that doesn't
even feel that long ago at all but it's
actually kind
of kind
[Music]
of is that really so long
ago
well not that long ago maybe three two
three weeks
jacob7 D oh you watch L of the Rings
let's go
Angel the gaming storm
tan and py
d uh un arched Cal
rebroadcast
has no super JS
uhuh and and there's Gua Zelda
[Music]
wrong one what the [\h__\h] no right one
huh oh I took a break because of uh
seven days to
die7 d r d hul d there's so many l wait
why is there so many different ones CR d
j d d spe d m d AR d
why is there so many different lemon
sticker super
chats didn't know there was such a
variation now d py d py d KR 555 wizard
thank you
D and yumix thanks for the pinky I would
like to report that Carey Manila was a
success we had over 80 new new recruits
and trained them the ways of Ky new you
mean like completely new fans like you
made them into fans
Cy Philippines is now ready to serve and
support you
Mahal from your loyal chickens a bunny a
bunny Ariel me and un thank you so much
what do you mean like they were fans but
you Ro playing and saying you recruited
them to the to the
branch in any case sounds awesome yeah I
saw saw you guys doing a good job thank
you so much good job
working hard for
kfp yeah I wish I could have been there
thank
[Music]
you you don't feel confident you mean in
my smartness I don't think I'm
stupid but yeah I just I I maybe you
know if I started I I think I just
started off with the wrong foot so to
say and then is just over if it can't
keep up but I did well in in a lot of
other things besides
math so I don't think I'm stupid
[Music]
yeah I wouldn't even say I'm Street
Smart I'm just
[Music]
um I think I'm fine
tacal Templar Blair thanks for the
pinky you always find a way to make even
the smallest moments feel special for us
twins ah you hold a special place in our
hearts you're truly precious and we're
so grateful for you to seeing you brings
a smile to our faces no matter the day
one or
[Music]
two ah ah I was looking for another
Super CH from you but it came from Dante
I suppose this is this is 21 two your
streams help make any bad day brigher
your energy and positivity are
infectious and I enjoy spending time
watching you I appreciate how much you
love your fans and the hard work you do
you top guest thank you I do really
appreciate you guys thank you for
noticing and thank you for appreciating
me
back got twins watching
me thank you so much for the support I
hope you're enjoying my streams for a
long
time can Bond over it wow titty titty
very
[Music]
titty every de D every de D
ah take I put seven d back in d space
wonderful than H ACD thank you for the
pinky super chat before I pass out and
you probably saw you meix a Super Chat
already but I just want to say that our
KP money event wouldn't be a success if
it weren't for your love and dedication
so from me Ariel y make a bunny and all
Filipino C be we love you w thank
you thank you so much I think I kind of
like promoted it after it was over so I
wish I could have like maybe promoted it
earlier so that you guys maybe would
have been you know even more successful
but I hope I hope it went well and thank
you so much for setting it up I'm really
honored honestly to see something like
that organized completely by you guys on
your
own yeah for
me and you you really did a great job it
looked really nice I'm sure everybody
who was there enjoyed it I'm honored and
flattered thank
you every every
every
the tan reminds me
bro I saw something yesterday bro bro
bro
[Music]
I can't I can't I
can't I can't I I no I can't I can't I
can't remember when I pointed out that I
saw Tanaka in a different completely
unrelated non vtuber stream
chat and I don't know if I mentioned
back then what it actually was but it
was like some Australian trying to uh
get the record of like staying awake for
I don't know how many days weeks it
was and then today I go through my
Twitter timeline and I see some
something some
tweet uh
about some
streamer on solitary confinement to make
a record of being in longest solitary
confinement and I I'm like huh
and I see it's the same [\h__\h]
person
bro I can't even and I just like look at
like 2 seconds I skim
through one or two videos watch like 5
seconds in total or so
[Music]
but I I
I don't
understand
[Music]
people yeah like what n
nah
nah n no mm- [\h__\h] content
goblins coming right d the D thank
you andise D boo 723
[Music]
thank you D and
Z yeah what what what
no no no no no no I just clicked on it
to confirm if it was the same person
because that that kind of thing like it
felt familiar like I was like no way is
is this the same oh my God it's the same
guy
why try to break records that don't hurt
yourself and your brain maybe try if you
must break records on
stream okay but you can't do that right
because you need something controversial
anyway anyway
whatever going to read um try nine super
chats really quickly because it's just a
[Music]
five Angry Eyebrows wow
schoolly can I said a record for most
Watchers on exactly like do something
like
that do like brain rot yourself watch
watch one video
200 million times on stream that will
probably damage your brain too
but Jacob for the7 D GD D Elie laugh D
Cruz D and Kevin the couch potato thank
you D welcome to the
community if you're still
here there we go um I think I'll stop
there cuz it's almost midnight and you
know I'm
Cinderella but also I'm
hungry and I'm out of water so
but we caught up next is the the blue
orange Mario Party
from 22nd October we're not that far
it's really just a few more oh tomorrow
I can catch up more no not
tomorrow tomorrow I'm not
streaming the the the the sday
[Music]
yeah well then uh ouch my hand why did I
do that why did why did I sit on my hand
like
that oh
no
seems some problemos all right you good
yeah yeah yeah the whole day okay so my
I think my pinch nerve is kind of mostly
gone but today like I noticed after a
little while after I woke up I noticed
that I don't know how to describe it but
my neck
was so
tense like weirdly tense that even the
slightest motion felt like it
could result in I don't know the biggest
cramp in my neck ever you know what I
mean like it was weird and that was
going on for hours and I took a hot
shower hoping that would make it
better is it gone
now might be
[Music]
gone it was so
weird it felt so messed up
[Music]
sorry for my
yapping
today G I don't know man I just
[Music]
I'm I can't with
myself sleeping in weird disposition no
I don't know man I
[Music]
hi
baby
[Music]
hi no come
back that was chunky ly actually she did
a stretch oh what are you looking at she
looks like Mona
Lisa
wow think you just woke up it's okay you
I'm going to go give her a big hug
now
yeah my my my fairy god
C I can't I
can't my cats en be s in I got to go
[Music]
l