[Music]
to
oh
[Music]
two
my
[Music]
to
n
[Music]
oh oh
to
[Music]
oh
to
[Music]
pap
n
[Music]
hello merry chm marry marry Among Us
Among
Us I marry among Among
Us love
about welcome everybody to the uh
Christmas or Holo Ian holiday Among Us
stream we have gathered here today with
so many lovely cute girls and we're
going to have fun choking and stabbing
each other right yeah kind of
fun let's go awesome well we're gonna um
do it without proximity chat by the way
guys uh because you know we have some
first timers here I think it's Advent
girls's first time among using here
right first timers that's going to be
fun not s yeah we'll find out how they
act when when they're impostor we can't
tell yet like for others maybe we
already know a tell but for these
newbies we don't know what is their tell
maybe that's maybe you could tell us
would you be so kind when your
introduction to tell me what your tell
is please nah you got to find that out
who that information is classified going
to need a little cash money up front
first I'll try well okay then let's with
introductions let's start with the only
one who's a real astronaut here Amy uh
hello Amia wson number one astronaut
detective yeah I like Among Us so I'm
excited to play Let's go yeah let's
go out because maybe there's some new
viewers at this point who don't
understand why is am able to wear her
own clothes in the game and why am I
wearing P's cloves and is wearing man's
clothes oh
am do you want to explain H yes we have
H we had a collab with Among Us where
you could get a few uh Hol live outfits
and items in the Among Us shop but I
don't think it's available anymore it's
kind of a limited to
thing time too bad if you missed out me
and W are P right
now I thought this was a keyboard slam
you guys are actually you guys are in a
room okay oh yeah wow okay I thought you
to SL the
keyboard keyboard slam I know that's
what it looks like code looking like a
slam oh you're giving them hints you
G and slam welcome to the slam jam
please join thank Jam am fertiliz who is
CM spam I don't know is all right I
somehow they figured it out took all
the all right oh you have Stam color too
yeah yummy had a Spam color that was
amazing nice box oh while
we're uh you know bullying her for her
name Cy please introduce yourself so we
know that's
really oh yeah if you insist me it's me
Mory Kip H life English is hardworking
Shinigami uh I'm in a place with very
terrible internet so I can't stream my
POV but I'm very excited to be here with
all of these lovely ladies as the
sheriff completing my tasks and making
sure that we win the let's go yes he
wouldn't kill anybody she is now known
as spam calm spam
I I guess it's more now but yeah I'm so
happy you're joining even though you
can't like stream properly thank you so
much the dead beats they trained me well
I wanted to show off my new skills that
the dead beats
have members fairly recently indeed got
a lot out she's good at the game
oh you just ask us how do you kill
people in this game
okay I guess I didn't help at all that
you played it recently it was
unhelpful well okay moving on to fun
where is she where is she I can't find
her I'm in hiding you can't vote me as
the impostor if I'm hiding
right there is from Hol live English
promise hello hello I'm here does it
feel does it feel like normal now like
it still feels weird to me to hear that
introduction
promise yeah I think so fresh still it
is it is still pretty fresh but I like
it I think it's boat yeah the boat got
boats I feel like everyone's been
traumatized by boats
recently what's with this current Trend
in the whole life English of watching
school days what's going
on I wanted to do since last year we
finally got it yeah it was pretty good
about the
tree the tree yes the tree want to know
more like it there's a staircase did you
know there's a
staircase I
know I have no idea what these girls are
talking about good I'm so confused I
wish I didn't it's too cursed we're that
everybody is having fun school days and
all that fun a jolly season it is great
piece of Cinema yeah all right Iris our
number one Christmas lover hello yes
you're number one Christmas lover here
hiis it's Iris from H live English
promise you're number
oneill people uh I love this game but I
I I really suck at being imposter but
yeah so so yosu yeah but I'll do my best
are you really bad at it I don't
remember I I was horrible at imposter
last time I played this I screwed up
soing she gets imposter maybe you just
need a better mate to work with cuz
you're dumb d m oh
sh shut is this were you the this on my
face bit of a poopy
head what you're talking about the lobby
will fall apart it's no problem but
let's take our time okay okay yeah by
the way have you guys speaking of Iris
have you guys all seen the yesterday and
today's episodes of the Holo Ian Advent
calendar cuz Iris was very involved in
them I was very involved in them yes
just and they were both in
3D in space y so Iris why did you do it
uh oh it's cuz you know we needed some
light to bring up the Christmas spirit
you know MH what better light than
actual fire right yeah oh that makes
sense and you know it was my whole plan
so that I I could become the Christmas
tree in order to become the Christmas
tree you needed to burn the actual
Christmas tree first
true burning Christmas trees that's kind
of it is the master plan it's pretty lit
yes very
lit it was
fire indeed fire fire light the fire
fire fire light the fire fire light the
fire fire fire fire y uh everybody's uh
joining in again in the lobby I think
I'm coming I got my name I freed Comm
spam he doesn't exist
anymore real no more com spam I'm sad is
it going to hide the code if I have
streamer mode on yeah I'm yes yes it's
for me it does it's hidden people self-
introduction please hi uh bomu I'm clu
sparkling Gem of Hall English Advent and
today I'm a space Rock but that doesn't
mean you're allowed to Stellar Stellar
me out of the ship so I am not sace I am
nice
wow okay good you give me
nice no no D that won't work here
doesn't work
here man a so you have to prove yourself
prove the truth you can't fool us people
you're
sus already you're already sus
[Music]
already I think I think it's
her pretty good guess it's it's
definitely okay let's move on to F moo
please I'm I who
your voice okay Mo
Coco sometimes I become a dragon
sometimes you know but as long as you
know I'm not chihuaha I'm not FAA
I'm there we go and together we make the
best crew mate you know
dogs not it's kind of unfair it's UNF
yeah if you're imposter it's two it's
two of you guys imp can cover your own
Mist we should vote them out right away
every time I think so
too well let's not do that but indeed as
a crew mate they might be very helpful
cuz it's two brains for one I guess I
guess who's who's on the keyboard who's
controlling contr I'm the legs you're
the
brains the finger oh yeah nice looking
forward to
team I'll be nice to see one one day
they will play separately but today is
not
today isn't this game on mobile it maybe
somebody could play on mobile
right
works I'm sure it connects right really
it doesn't work on this
side well okay and then
[Music]
now an imposter hi
darling devilish Diva
Raven I'm an impostor today because I'm
pretending to be M and I guess
[Music]
am oh my gosh fake it till you make it f
it you make it
we're we're a nice couple n aren how
ironic I should be running away from
you I don't want your child
narissa even if honeyworks made a song
about our child I don't
[Music]
it okay and
then
please this is
oron from English Pro what all life
English
promise um please don't arrest me I'm
going to be a very good egg for today uh
cuz even if I want to be an impostor I
never get it I almost ever get it so you
trust me I believe her I trust her 100%
TR yes I trust her 100% I trust everyone
100 what are the chances
that I look so kind pretty high none of
none of us will get imposter probably
yeah probably none of us that's it how
many how many imposters are we doing I
set it to
two
wey I don't know should I free I don't
know good is good
okay and I I have in case you're
interested uh two long tasks and five
short tasks uh as well as two common
tasks I don't remember what the com
tasks were that's
suspicious what you don't you don't
remember are
you oh yeah cuz imposters don't do
tasks well it's been to Long rolls or
something right like you can do stuff
now or
something like rolls rolls oh yeah
wasn't there something besides crew mate
now like um uh
like help the Imposter like the Spy or
something like that's
not
s yeah keep them on that's fun I don't
know how does that work though I don't
really know for that one at the
beginning so wa yeah there's four roles
there I don't know you girls can
probably see them in the settings uh on
the on the computer here there's a
scientist who can access a portable
vitals panel so they can check at any
point of time if there's somebody dead
so they always see the status of the
crew and then there's an engineer who
can use the vents even though they're
not an imposter but then you might be
sused and you have to be like I'm not
the Imposter I just vent because I can
oh that's pretty cool really and then
the guardian angel uh is the ghost of
the very first one of us that
dies oh is that how it works the first
person that dies yeah something like
that the
garden the ghost of the first Dead crew
mate they can temporarily shield and
protect other living crew mates guess if
you're the first one that dies you
become the guardian angel and then you
can protect somebody else so that they
don't die yeah if you do it properly and
well timed you'll be able to prevent
imposters from killing their victim
sounds amazing me throwing so that I can
become the guardian
angel
a already are yes no
the and then there's a shape shifter who
can who can change the appearance and
disguise themselves as other crew mates
why would you do that though that just
confuses everyone it just makes the
Imposter
orost harder to find too because then
you know the Imposter can say I'm the
engineer oh no I'm the shap you know
like please I promise I'm not a murderer
it doesn't say that only impostor but
why would would why would crewmate do
this I don't know would let's turn that
one off but I like the other ones yeah
should I should I keep them or should I
I think shter
is oh it is okay yeah just doesn't say
so so wait does only one impostor is
only one impostor The Shape Shifter is
that how it works uh I can set how many
there will be I can
say I can say we want two or I can say
we I want one or zero I can set it in
the
settings but if I do one then only one
of the uh imposters will be Shape
Shifter but only 50% chance the one will
be oh yeah I can I can make it higher
too that we have one for sure I feel
default is good right it's probably B
default okay okay default then let's
keep the rolls then let's go we're
[Music]
going before
we before before we go um can we have
the visual tasks off because if we have
it on it might be too easy visual tasks
off oh true
seconds very good okay and before start
I'm taka I organized this thing the
logos and the thumbnails are
commissioned by me
[Music]
so don't kill me because I I PID for
this okay don't kill me we right we M
right yeah CL your by byebye okay
bye-bye oh the silence is so
loud hello chat wait what did it say am
I in am I among
us and this is the new
map wow the fungle they got a vending
machine break
room the
trash
I don't know what I'm doing is it
working guys how do I do this is there a
button what
happened I'm stuck in the
trash what the
hell why do I look like
this did I get
infected
okay I'm clicking I'm clicking I'm
clicking I don't think I'm doing it
right wait so everybody has like
different roles and
stuff okay boo boo says yeah as as soon
as she turned
around
a she just had the look of
murder murderous intentions I could
sense
them
[Music]
no I miss
you you the only real astronaut you know
what that means we don't have a chance
of getting back to our own
Planet unbelievable so who saw Watson I
didn't see her at all I didn't see her I
didn't at all oh no I didn't see her she
was who who reported just now me I did
tell us did tell us about it where was
the body so I was going around
Communications um trying to figure out
the mushrooms I went on and I went down
uh the the little zipline and then in
the storage room Amy was
dead storage
room
saw we saw around the
Busom you
me wait so F was also in the storage
area no no we were at the mushrooms and
we were having problems with that and
crony Senpai was around and then crony
Senpai went down but Senpai was there
too yeah yeah mococo was chasing me
around confused I don't know what's
going on I have mushroom problems yeah I
had like a meat problem I don't know
like I suddenly turned into like a a
lighter pink and there was like a chunk
of me chasing
me and they CH into people or something
like that is that just an effect to
freak you out or does it do something I
don't know I think it I think the the
the mushroom like if you touch it or
something um it hides the the people so
you can just like kill them and run away
and they wouldn't be able to kill or
something like
that did why do you know that hot
yeah my skin got swapped as well yeah me
too the skin him a wizard you're not
getting any closer to for a moment and
then poof it was gone and the light was
back
on weird I I don't know what what goes
on in this map I don't know I feel like
I trusted crony Senpai and now I feel
like I don't trust crony
Senpai why are they blaming crony I will
say I passed by and I was actually
running away from crony cuz it felt like
she was chasing me
I where were you you you followed me
theine what do you mean know who
vot holy [\h__\h] wait who voted who vote
Kara who there there she
goes okay
100%'s hair is in the shape of an Among
Us fact that she had like her own
like oh oh oops oops
oops wait how do I do this
oh
oh okay I
see
nice another one I just had a dream
about fish last night
too not these weird mutant fish
though I can still do stuff I'm grilling
there's cooking in this
game I'm a Master
[Music]
Chef oh what is this how was this a task
isn't the task I guess maybe cuz we're
on an island with
[Music]
oh
wait
protate maybe I can still save them I'll
do it next time I got distracted by the
fish withb in the listen to this liar
listen to her I'm so
innocent yeah yeah yeah yeah I going to
believe it too they got to believe it
too next to the greenhouse when I was
passing I was moving to the laboratory
she's above the green
house I saw her walking around I didn't
see anyone near her I didn't see anyone
else I was Nissa when we went up to
Communications and that was the last
time I saw
her we didn't see anyone except senite
and I think she's good scared us I ran
away instantly cuz I will be honest I
don't trust anyone who voted for crony
in the last round what like the imposers
were trying to get her out
because Ved her
because there a double they can figure
it out the pieces the pieces are all
laid out tell us before huh the puzzle
pieces are all laid out we're going to
start yeah I'm about to kill her sheriff
sheriff did
it there's only there's only
three Among
Us oh that's true there's two imposters
still crony could have been an imposter
thoughest I don't
know doesn't say who I don't know but
I'm pretty sure it chose it if she
self-recorded because look at her look
at her um
her icon like it's all why why are you
so suspicious of her for no reason
you're right you're right I feel like
you wouldn't be this suspicious unless
you were the
impostor not I swear to God that I saw
like narissa pass by just 5 seconds ago
before her death if it was actually me I
wouldn't say that I didn't see though uh
no I was pass I passed by her when she
was going greenhouse and I I'm currently
at the meeting room I went the opposite
direction that's why I she was like
stuck on a that biu and Irish Senai are
suspicious I think so too I swear I'm
not what were you doing not I was
walking around I was in the LA the lab
wait where's my the lab and then Nissa
was on like thep 10 seconds I'm playing
be I don't have
enough oh my
God it's not me uhoh I
[Music]
wait who voted for Iris right now I
wasn't
looking we get
him
awes I thought we won yeah Tombstone
guys I told
you me you didn't even notice I was dead
guys literally I P me and bi killed me
immediately you were fast self report
good team you two that was pretty
funny nice one tombstones let's go
impressive I was surprised well you know
what we learned from because call was
pretty quiet s out the quiet quiet ones
the quiet fooled me Cy he fooled me
too I was just confused cuz like my
voting was super rushed I was like what
wa wait why am I suspicious all a
everyone just literally just the
Spider-Man everybody pointing at each
other no one in there it was peer
pressure peer pressure you don't have to
vote if you don't know I know I don't
have to
vote Iris out that was so weird I
thought it needed to be like majority
vote to even get anyone off people vot
was enough to kill
me only a little bit of us left
yeah cuz three people had already
[Music]
died we're strong at this we're good
pretty good doing our tasks I thought
you guys
[Music]
were I guess we're S no matter what
can't be
helped well that was a good first round
let's let's try to be you know we turn
an extended voting time oh
sure yeah yeah uh it's currently 90
seconds should we do
12 at least yeah at least 120 120 is the
max should be good wait Chad says
apparently we can vote or skip the vote
if you not confident like who it is you
don't have
to pretty
[Laughter]
confident certainty there pretty
confident voting out all
the
well now you now you know then you maybe
cannot trust your
confidence yeah true
enough all right then let's start
another
round even though this is really fun
here thank you crony for finding
this see you on the other side bye bye
see you guys
bye yay I'm an innocent crew mate now I
can do my
tasks H I think I'm going to do a
fishing one this time wait what is
[Music]
this
fossel oh maybe maybe right cuz we're
surviving on wait
lifting got to get my
repon
oop nice all right so so we saw Iris and
fauna now let's see if Iris still alive
somewhere maybe FAA killed her
already wait how do I get in
there I haven't gone to the other part
of the map oh
wait I'm
gaming oh man I wonder if you can only
fish when you're
dead uh all right let me see where's the
rest of the map
this way the last time I tried to go
this way I
died right here wait what is
this oh
zipline you can only fish if it's your
task oh I
see ah I didn't even see her what the
heck
shoot it die so
fast it's okay at least we could still
do our uh I guess I'll just do my tasks
[Music]
s this map has so many colors like I
didn't even notice that there was
somebody else in the vicinity you know
what I mean like in the old space map
the colors stand out really well but
this
one what the what a
huh fa
Iris bis
oh wait am I an angel again this time I
don't think so cuz I don't have wings
wait what is
this I
see somebody stinking up the place it's
me
again no not again come on yeah come
on again you sensing a pattern
here what all right I'll break it down
for you
did you hear Iris oh my God I did all my
tasks you guys could see me I think some
of you saw me watering things in the the
mushroom place I moved some storage
around roasted some marshmallows went up
to do my tasks in the communication room
and what do I find Watson dead middle of
the floor I didn't see anyone leave
though was anyone near Communications
recently where isun top you take a
little uh like a what is it a wi the
zipline zipline Callie sounds suspicious
but I don't even think it's her she just
it's like when you lie you give too many
details you know what I mean like too
many
details yeah I know there was there's
like oh oh okay these white white things
are okay yeah the line go up and down
but yeah I wasn't there yet um in the
bottom right um wait is anybody else a
lot of sh shifting I don't know who was
okay I'm the yeah there what happened
with is that the mushroom stuff working
on everybody everybody got a skin shift
right yeah
it's we don't know who is who and then
we can't prove like oh that person was
there or whatever but we all look
different like not like each other right
so it's not shape shifting yeah no it's
just the mushroom
power mushroom power that oh by the way
I just want say I haven't used it yet
but when by a mushroom it does it
okay I can vent but I'm not the The
Imposter they just saying I didn't use
it I wonder recently was anyone around
upper engine Lookout or
mining May tried to escape by going down
the
ladders playing I was walking that way
but I didn't see
anyone okay I've been down over in the
left area for the time task so I haven't
even gone over there yet actually don't
know if it's
F I saw her shape ship though isn't that
something passing by the greenhous I was
to go up but and then you didn't see
anybody run past well no I didn't hard
to tell still at least hard to
tell yeah but bble was kind of quiet
it's not her just saying actually passed
by me and didn't kill me
so so right now only confirmed
Iris I can tell you I've been doing
water with narissa and then I did the
marshmallow thing and she sh
I
asteroids and I haven't been up there
yet so I I do have up there I haven't
heard CR say
anything we'll see we'll EX for
that maybe it's Iris
yeah maybe don't don't go alone don't go
around alone guys go with a
buddy we don't need a
buddy am I sure it's IR oh yeah I guess
they could shape shift and then kill and
then wait so I'm I'm not the what is
this oh what does this do wait
what what is
this huh oh I see oh I can spectate
let's see what crony's up
to pretending to do her tasks
okay ah
she went invisible is it like a
smoke maybe she really is doing her
tasks she doesn't look like she's
looking for
someone searching for a um person to
kill
perhaps yeah yeah trying not to look
suspicious trying to follow but stay
behind oh the
con
wait a second okay just so definitely oh
wait huh who's
[Laughter]
that that's just a random thing random
huh oh it was F okay so it's Iris and
Fu
uhoh caught
right-handed
I she was innocent was the
only was a little bit suspicious though
was I passed her going down the ladders
from communication to the lower part she
passed me maybe went up the
communication where'd you find her so I
was going up the ladder to the
communication and I didn't really see
her body but um I saw the the vent which
is the plant kind of opening up in the
closing so they
vent wherever it is from
Communications oh does anyone know where
where the vents from Communications
connect they can go anywhere right yeah
she didn't see they they got away in
only usually I don't know got away with
it usually vents only connect to certain
other vents I should have checked and
then I could have told you but too bad
where's wait so the does it show oh it
doesn't show the vent on the map I think
crony is not self-reporting at least
because like I feel like I was I was
running around with her a little bit
alone she could saw you yeah yeah and
she didn't and then I saw cie running
around I think we were alone for a
little bit but she may have been on cool
down as well but she yeah she was coming
down from that a she was she was coming
down from that area yeah I told you I
crossed paths with her yeah okay but
yeah and Cory said someone vented hm
[Music]
H where were you a good question we at
the the beach we're just kind of going
around but we don't really I don't know
what's going on on the map here if you
hit tab it'll show you where you are oh
T yeah hit
T there's also the map icon on the top
we don't know what's going on we don't
know we wouldn't even know how to kill
if we were the Imposter it can't be us I
see a map but I don't understand it it
has a lot of marks on maybe this maybe I
believe them actually I believe them a
lot of marks is kind ofation
marks a lot of marks on it does it have
xes on it c c I'm curious they wouldn't
have exclamation marks question L of
marks I mean I don't see so many marks
on my map yeah what what does an
impostor see maybe does a previous
imposter want to tell us what they saw
like KY there's no exclamation points
that's for sure with circles on
I sabotage they slipped up they slipped
up on the
screen
marks burn burn them do you have
anything to say to defend yourself we
just doing my
tasks if you were doing your Tas there
wouldn't be so many marks on the screen
would
there
[Laughter]
do it I couldn't
[Music]
the wait it doesn't show if they were
impost I
thought guess
not wait so I'm not Guardian Angel
anymore even though I died first how
does this work chat I'm confused
whatever I'll just do my tasks I
guess
what
oh science
stuff nice hold on cuz I get
a wait what is this Arrow up here oh
it's it because the power went out or
something a do
egg um the heck is
this
I guess I can't do it as a ghost
probably
uh I can't
wait oh so you can spy on people with
this
interesting okay yeah I can't fix it I
don't think it's a ghost let's uh let's
see
Iris oh she's uh blending in right now
but following
there sheriff sheriff
keeping an eye on yeah Iris running away
with her tail between her
legs let's see where she
went major suspicious activity detective
detected can she see me cuz I'm a ghost
right or was that
only hey can I can I I guess
not no she can't see me
oh oh yeah that's right she could hear
me if it was proximity chat what the
heck is
this wait
what not cie who who is dead cie self
report I just saw her like yeah I saw
her too saw her too I feel like her body
right underneath the
the
ladder the the left
ladder the map and exactly where the
greenhouse like close to the greenhous
yeah wasn't just with me at around Iris
I think right yeah I saw everyone
Communications and I was getting some
stuff done there and uh also the lookout
and then I went down she moved
fast and then
died is there anyone around there
I'm in the lookout right now I'm in the
mining pit I was around I think when
everyone was
around um we all went to Communications
home yeah everyone like uh everyone
except uh who was it like R Rissa and
FAA uh I think they were around like
Communications and like Lookout and then
everyone else went to the other coms
yeah um I am sorry FAA but it seemed you
were being just you know a little very
cautious I don't know if you were
careful about being stack killed but you
moved away from the the radio like where
everyone was trying to fix it oh that's
well you needed to go do the other thing
right to fix it I was the first one
there in the radio and I tried to put in
the code but I think you have to put in
a second
code yeah also I had two tasks that I
did in Communications
wow I wented them cuz I was I was in
Lookout I was putting the code in I
think I was the first who arrived and
then nothing was happening so I I
thought I would go to the other one and
I saw cie was like doing the code at
that point as well so she was like she
already arrived and then I left her
alone there I was about to go up to the
other communication thingy but then
the it was already fixed so then I went
back and I saw I think I saw again or so
yeah but I didn't see fa and I didn't
see Iris at all I saw you Kiara I I saw
all of you guys I don't know I don't
know I saw all of you guys in
communication I was I was with fa alone
for a while and she didn't kill
me yeah I saw Marissa go down go down I
didn't I was going to the green house
down where are you right now um I am up
in the lookout because I got lost and I
was very
fired aren't we
all I'm a little suspicious of crony cuz
she didn't vote for Fu Moko
she running I don't know if I'm
suspicious enough to vote [\h__\h] yeah I
don't know I I I don't know either I'm
going to skip did they Spell's name and
maybe boob you're not allowed to say
boob skipping
[Music]
we good luck crew
mates all right I got to do my tasks
it's very
important what was that whatever not my
problem uh task task
task
Pizza what's this Roa marshmallow oh
amongus marshmallow
how is this a
task is this important for our
survival I'm feeding my
soul Sandy Pizza that don't sound too
bad can I get my pizza with a a little
bit of sand on
top all right all right all right wait
wait we I
finish [\h__\h] I mean what the freak
okay all right I to do the laboratory
one labor
laboratory something about an
egg he Pizza give you me pizza what do
you want what do you want for me the
pizza the pizza this pizza huh guys what
a how do I do this wait hold on let me
do this other task over here oh Kiara's
locked in can I get over
here oh not Kiara huh wait why are they
pretending to be me oh can I just fly
oh don't they know that I'm
dead I'm
mining oh I see
it oh this it's taking too
long does everybody know that they have
to finish their tasks wait I didn't
finish it oh there's one
more okay now the last task with the
pizza no dead bodies fine uh hello hello
hello I think no is trying to kill me ah
you so I can't believe you I was not I
checked everyone's vitals and I decided
to go back to the
and I saw her and I got a little scared
so I ran back but then she chilled so I
thought it was cool but then she hit the
emergency meeting button must my
surprise no the thing is there's a
little bit of a backstory I was running
around and there's a back
story I'm done with my task what do you
mean
backstory I was running around I was I
was you know I I I was running around
crony alone she didn't kill me I was
running around fauna alone she didn't
kill me and both of those I kind of
fought were USS and then I found you and
you kind of followed me and now I think
if it's not cron if it's not fa I even
follow you what do you mean I ran into
you and then I ran back to the meeting
area you are so fake K oh no I was also
around crony and she did not kill me
either among us could have and as I was
doing tasks I could have killed crony
too and I didn't which I would have if I
had the opportunity to if I was tell me
everybody tell me Iris uh and tell me
fauna what are the remaining tasks that
you have I'm done with tasks and I was
hanging out with Iris yeah I saw yeah B
sorry if you felt like I was chasing you
Iris kind scared I was kind of scared
you were like stick to me like little
time yeah I have I have a task to do at
the dock okay and then I have one at the
cafeteria do it and then we win task win
let's go guys we have to do it also I
think people who are done with the tasks
can um the
what I mean we have to do the tasks we
can't just wait in the meeing area no no
like people who are done with the Tas
can follow around can add on I do think
I do think Nissa is a little bit
suspicious Nissa you and me Let's Stay
Together if I'm ex I'm not staying with
you we're staying together now I'll
actually take along with you guys if
that's okay just to see
if okay I'll still safer ifon is there
wait then maybe you two are the
imposters no no I'm done with my tasks
as the thing I don't know want to kill
me I think everybody except me oh my God
I didn't kill you when you were
around Pizza what the heck oh you two
didn't kill each other because you're
both oh my God you come with me and IR
why youing it on the blue women yeah
let's just all stay together and we'll
see what the blue women do oh my God IR
does anyone else have no no I'm all done
oh yeah we should follow Iris we should
pressure follow IR let's follow Iris
yeah yeah you can totally follow me okay
nice hey who voted for me
me wait am I getting okay okay good you
better you little [\h__\h] love you k please
don't kill me okay Dad what do I do
about the
pizza
he wants a
pizza where's the
pizza is it the sand Pizza they're all
going
together
shoot
guys
food pizza click his
bowl oh
oh yay I saved the world
task win who was it it was my task
excuse me I was it was am's task oh yeah
but who was the Imposter to reveal
yourself imposter though Iris I wonder
who
was it
[Music]
was you know outed themselves so good
you put us on the
doing I'm sorry I was suspicious of you
fa I'm sorry I was suspicious of you
Iris didn't kill fa Iris why didn't you
kill me we were Al together for so long
I wanted to keep someone on my
side and because crony was susing Faun
in the beginning I was like maybe I
should keep her on my side and kill
crony
instead
and like I I saw that Iris was uh going
into the same room as uh narissa was so
I was kind of waiting outside the room
to see I saw I saw I was like oh no I
think she sus I was trying to kill I was
trying to kill you actually um I when
you were inside the lab I was I was
following you and I was going to kill
you but then I noticed you were moving
weirdly and you were like running away
and then Rissa came comes in right away
I was like oh never mind I can't kill
you
here gave up went back I think I was
playing a little bit too cautiously but
um so difficult there's only there's
only me that's why I saw I was I was
worried like it was still pretty good
yeah impressive yeah I can't I can't
believe you suspected
me all's well it ends well hopefully
when we're together alone in the males
nothing I won't kill you don't worry
that's reassuring
don't drown me in the ocean please miss
mly mly yeah
mly oh sorry I was stuck at let me just
I'm here
sorry um I don't want to like you know
make any hard rules because you know you
just kill whoever is conveniently there
but please do not kill Amy right away
next
round
go no no no we need our we there space
so now to yeah kill me first I love
being the
ghost no pressure yeah no
pressure okay we complete I changed one
thing I changed uh the votes uh you
can't see who voted that makes it really
hard for me to try to vote
someone oh boy let's go let's
go see you later bye
[Music]
I'm a detective through and
through a detective wooden
kill time to do my
tasks pump in some
iron wait that symbol looks like the
steam symbol doesn't it it's like a
muscle but looks like the steam thingy
nisso was in here maybe considering
killing me first thought thought about
it the
laboratory I really want to learn how to
do like uh you guys know the Dexter's uh
labor laboratory
thingy I want to learn how to do
Dexter's voice but um can't really think
of what it sounds like right
now you G it too much I can't do it I
can't do it I need to hear it I need to
hear
it and doing the
task drop ship oh this is like oh you
can go in oh I didn't see this you go
into the
ship the
classic bio waiting to kill me funo
waiting to kill me has enough time
passed why are they following
me leave me alone if People's going to
kill me again
[Music]
ah hello oh for a moment I thought you
were dead
again oh no
no all right rip hope is dead I just saw
her alive like less than 30 seconds ago
must have just happened I just found it
in the meeting room but I was up in the
drop ship if you look at the map and
then I went down and I found her body
there and biu was up there and fun was
up there and biu looked like she came
from down below so I'm a little
sus Australia are you because I knew no
one would kill you so I thought it'd be
safer with
you story but following the both of us
though so I'm kind of s of I was just
making sure no funny business was going
on who was I saw Iris alive like less
than 30 seconds before she was found
dead like I it fell like like 10 seconds
before so I'm I'm like What's Happening
that was a really fast yeah I only
passed by in that area was like bioo and
fauna and that's it I think in that area
specifically you see anyone like coming
from that
direction I saw I don't know for sure I
don't know the storage room and then I
was using the
zipline and like B wasn't taking the zip
line up with
me oh well B would you like to defend
yourself
why I was following am because I no one
was going to kill Amy so I thought Amy
was the safest B but am saw you didn't
she not following her but coming from a
different direction I was following Al
this entire time you follow you entire
time I was running away from you so I
didn't always see
you well I was following you the entire
you want to kill her why you follow her
this is inconclusive evidence one TK
I've done one task so far it was
asteroids I haven't done the rest
because asteroids I was following yeah
the asteroids the video didn't you do
asteroids in the last one to yeah I have
what is the asteroids
like I went straight to
Communications are we skip I
don't can I skip Oro out I feel like I
don't think I
don't I don't want to
die by the way Iris I don't know if you
know but you mut oh it's because she's
dead oh never
[Laughter]
mind but she is dead I just wanted to
make sure she joins the conversation you
know maybe tell us help us out here if I
die
or I go
byebye
people are we
voting I didn't even vote for I
voted I didn't vote for you people it
wasn't me oh thank you I just like
saying
byebye me byebye oh no oh we skipped it
we skipped
it all right continue my turn
masks wait can I get over
there oh I guess it's going to go all
the way around cuz I only been here as a
ghost soon I don't
know uh
puzzle
puzle
puzzle nice okay uh
five more tasks left I'm not going to
make it get away from me I
trer it's fa I watched her
kill I knew it but she's
dead she's dead the switch the maybe
there a shape shifter no that makes it
so much worse I went I know it's not bi
boo because I went down because I saw bi
boo pass us we were both waiting to get
into the kitchen because last round foko
and I were frying fish together right so
as I was waiting I went to get beoo
because I was like Advent together
strong and then when I came back it was
right in front of the kitchen it was
right in front of the kitchen is where
is where the death just happened and I
saw someone running up to the Splash
Zone so where was everybody and don't
lie wait you found which which of the
two
Boko I don't I don't know where I don't
know where but then I have something to
add I was just up at the very top of the
communications and there was crony and
there was FAA First there was fauna and
me and everything was cool then crony
joined I left and now fauna is dead can
you confirm then crony um after I was uh
doing the ladder task I went down to the
zip line again after that was done so I
didn't you saw K up there yeah I saw
Kiara and fauna up there and then after
I was done with the ladder I went down
the
zipline and I couldn't see anything else
aside from that maybe someone vent I'm
not really sure cuz it's kind of a short
time May
youed says I mean I
know I know I'm gonna give my alibi
really quick and I saw bioo and we were
alone and she didn't come after me or
anything but I was in the Splash Zone in
the beginning I collected shells and
then I left
okay where were you though at the time
of the
murder I went up St just happened I
reported it immediately yeah I I know I
went to spash Zone and I collected the
shells and then I saw bioo and she
didn't hurt me and then I went back to
storage okay and then crony FAA and
kiata were over in Communications yeah
so Watson where were you I was at the
laboratory I I am s of am because Iris
was around me
fa and Amy yeah I am too what and now so
now I'm Su you guys are just trying to
vote someone off no cuz the last the
last murder the everyone who was present
we know that it wasn't fa now and
obviously iris is dead so it's only you
or bio but I know where you're
forgetting that the first round I
reported the body and both bio and faer
were with me and none of them said that
they B even said that she was following
me the whole time but she didn't see me
kill anyone huh
trust me
me who are we voting for self report she
selfreported
[Laughter]
V yes oh my God imposter
gone byebye H say no I don't know kiar
is really suspicious right oh sorry okay
see you later
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h]
what is
this what is
this guys what am I doing what is
this am I doing it
[Music]
right
um what am I
doing oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h]
uh I
yeah wait so um where am I
going oh it's both of them it's both of
them Qui Qui Qui I got to
run hold on let me go back I got to
check
something oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] she's on cool down people's on cool
down cuz she just killed
Kiara
um no we I I wanted to check if anyone
and Reese is dead oh yeah I didn't I was
wondering too I I think Kiara is safe
yeah because we just did the emergency
thing together yeah and then I'mma
joined right when we finished I ran away
cuz both of you guys are I thought both
of you guys were the impostor and you
were going to kill me no
no I why do you think I really because
the first death was Iris and me FAA and
Iris were the ones that were closest to
each other
and yeah well that's and now I'm scared
I know it's not Kiara because Kiara
didn't kill me or anything so yeah okay
I still have three tasks left by the way
wa so why did why did you just call a
meeting because I was wondering if
because we're about to finish our tasks
and you don't want us to finish our
tasks cuz you're the Imposter it was too
quiet and I was scared if anyone was
going to die and I thought like might as
well chat and Kelly what were you doing
I went down to mushrooms mhm and what's
the last task you did the Sorting the
mushrooms into the jars and the crystals
okay KY has been quiet yeah I mean ask
me any questions you want but if you
talk too much you get sused out too so
just ask me any questions and I'll tell
you am what's the last task you did um I
don't remember I was in
the shoot I can't ask chat too because I
can't even look at chat um I know this
sounds suspicious but yeah I don't
remember I'm going I'm going to vote for
I think yeah you're the impostor you're
just you called the meeting because
we're so close to finishing our tasks
that you're
scared no [\h__\h] the I'm scared
of AR I mean I saw cie and she didn't
kill me and I was running away from you
guys cuz I thought you guys were going
to kill me so H that's my defense yeah
okay we voting okay oh you guys if you
guys vote for me you're wrong just so
you
know uhoh I'm I'm going to vote for
Kelly all
right okay
or I don't know she seems almost sus cuz
I saw you I saw kiar and biu together
and you guys didn't die so unless you're
both the
impostor no we're not uhhuh that's
exactly what an impostor would
say well you think everyone's impost if
there was two imposters alive we would
lose by now so there's oh okay that's
true so one of the previous was well
crony I guess was the one that got
knocked out right so wouldn't that be
yeah yeah I don't know I don't know I
don't know I say we just Skip and
continue doing our tasks unless you guys
are cuz if I was the Imposter I'd try to
vote one of you guys out right now and
then I'd probably
win so I'm going to skip you guys are
wrong regret your decision I love you
I'll miss you yeah
right no she's
burning are we winning please my
tasks right how many more oh sorry
sorry how many more people do I have to
kill oh it's not this it's not this it's
not this it's not
this ah they should have listened to me
see see
G that was wacky it wasn't me god well
played well
play that was wild I was
shap actually I turned into fa that's
her C she was quiet oh you turned into
fauna I see we thought C quiet to
but thought [\h__\h] I'm so sorry I'm how do
I ever redeem myself no it's too late
it's too
late I'm this I'm that can't even
believe me yeah I totally thought it was
on me
too oh my God I'm not a real am
goling I tried to protect her and now
I'm the one that killed
her you did this to yourself anymore
yeah I can't trust Sally I'm sorry I
can't believe I got impostor twice
believe me I won't get it again so good
at lying yeah I don't watching
professional Japanese Among Us players
recently yeah everybody's just the whole
time
practice I warned you guys and you
didn't listen to
[Music]
me damn it and I still didn't get
impostor single time
man maybe next time we still got more
time right yeah yeah there's a little
more time then let's go next round
oh I saw I saw by the way the ghosts uh
were going in their own channel did you
have fun yes yes recommend it it was fun
I don't know why crony was probably too
guilty
to dead voice CH oh wait there's a dead
voice chat I didn't even
know voice chat I was like why isn't she
joining I was like oh probably cuz she
feels guilty oh no I don't feel guilty
at
all
AB you don't feel any shame didn't crony
just randomly get voted off too cuz I
don't even remember like
everybody yeah
iar was ging
it Kara knew yeah cuz I told you yeah
yeah I told you to believe me see oh it
was actually good what I did thank God
she was right you were so right easy way
to tell Easy well to tell if if cie is
imposter she's quiet when she's
imposter
imp so I don't know bye you are the Imp
wait just kidding I unmuted to say that
in the
chat time to do my
tasks makeing the
marshmallow
are they going to actually sell a wait
what I did it maybe cuz I didn't eat it
yet okay I got to wait for the task
complete ice SAU
sauce um okay where to next I have so
many tasks over
here you guys can handle it
that frisbee
task this I don't like this one you have
to click like 200
times this is too
much ah my finger
hurts why do they make you click so
much what the
okay all
[Music]
right didn't I do
this what the heck is it bugged
oh
okay my nose
runny okay so I guess we have to go do
that
thingy
what's up
guys
uh oh what I didn't even see I didn't
even see I didn't even really see I
didn't wait I didn't even really see
wait she was just there wait wait what
happened was that wait no no no no it
wasn't me I was doing the test where
were you where were you when you press
it wait who pressed it wa I I pressed it
I was oh my God I was so in my tangent
oh my God I went up to the top right of
the communications and I was just Tangen
thing and doing a task and suddenly I
see a dead body but on the same spot I
think I saw at least one more person
maybe another I think so it's Kiara Iris
fuok and then I just came into the room
and I saw K I just came
inside I just went up the ladder all of
a sudden
I was
Communications
I the same time and then I was trying to
go in the way at the mushroom door but I
got rid of the mushrooms but uh killed
by
accident maybe it's just amaz by being
silly uhhuh wait
what wait I'mma you there right when I
reported right no I I just walked into
the room like after cie she was already
in there like alive and you guys were
all doing the power thing or whatever
and I was also starting to do the power
thing putting in the code but then you
guys finished it and then somebody
reported Call's body so I didn't even
see it wait so you're saying besides me
there was Cali and you yeah and there
were like two other people in the room
just went inside the communication Iris
was in it must have been
Iris all in there she was on the other
side of the mushroom wall so I don't
think they could kill her on the other
side of the mushroom wall but I don't
know yeah I just went up the ladder was
how it went went and then all of a
sudden there might there was one other
person in there but it was hard to see
cuz everybody was bunched up I think I
saw
purple yeah purple was Kell's dead body
no no purple's
be that purple we do have something to
report yeah who's dead we
heard okay you are the and the
mute we were thinking maybe being
good thing that
[Music]
we I heard that I thought you were
saying it to someone else now I'm in
place can we have someone who hasn't
talked talk please oh me me me yes so um
I was at communications I saw a bunch of
people there and I was trying to like uh
do my task and like I was still on the
task when it happened so I didn't really
see anything oh so you were also in
Communications yeah there were so many
people in there report okay wait you
were there even now when when I reported
you were still
there um yeah yeah oh so you were one of
the other people I saw then where I
wasn't sure who am I seeing oh [\h__\h] I
voted for
who well I remember this I will remember
this but oh shoot you
guys I was just doing it as a
joke oh
oops
oh all
right do you see what happened
was I think they might have accidentally
killed somebody or something like
that and
um cuz they were doing the mushroom door
and it opened and then somebody reported
like immediately oh it was
crony what wait wait what just
everyone
was there was like a crowd of people
Communications wait did you did
you my you four people
go yeah
wow see The Quiet Ones it's always the
quiet ones I knew hasn't said
anything of last round that's I asked
you to
talk innocent I'm sorry I thought you
guys killed someone by accident you were
opening the door I thought it was B too
B sounded
suing forsing Amit right because of her
statement but it wasn't in the end
I was just kidding I said it on
purpose being silly H the two imposters
would of course vote for Fu Moko because
that
was I set you guys up I'm
sorry oh my God this is what happened
okay next we have we
got you guys want to do a different
M don't give the blue
[Music]
people
n
again wait what does it even say when
you get impostor it's like oh your role
is impostor maybe I should say that next
time that's what I always do like in uh
in Gary's
Mod like when you're when you get murder
in the
murderer game mode in Garry's Mod
I always read it out even though I don't
have
it okay
okay well how come my tasks aren't
showing up oh I guess cuz the Cals are
got
sabotage that's that's a pretty good
play though to kill somebody like while
everybody's doing the task cuz then
who's okay next time we're in a room
with a lot of people I won't do the task
I'll just keep look at that way I'll
know for
sure all right iris is
safe
oh self
report I I ran up because of the
communications thing was down and she
was right there in Communications in
front of the the thingy was anybody else
I don't think it was I was at the other
was but I didn't see her body I was down
by the dock I was in the labs oh me um
oh yeah I just met crony in the labs
yeah Iris and I are in doing the other
task the power thing we didn't kill each
other so I think we're
[Music]
safe pushing up some Li what narissa Fu
where were you down by the dock I I
figured that you probably all were going
there and I wanted to keep doing my
tasks so I just went down and I was
doing a sand castle and then I was
checking since don't the don't the um I
passed I passed the text yeah they
disappear but if you pass them you can
still do them oh okay yeah so I was
checking manually okay or if you just
still like remember where they were
before it went down yeah well
MO
reactor reactor that's what what task
what were you doing at the reactor we
doing our task we're just trying
to doesn't want to use the map I don't
like the map I like finding the little
yellow mark on the the screen
is emphasizing the
yellow what I actually haven't done that
yet the yellow there's a yellow so cute
little Among
Us uh
no the marshmallows
[Music]
yeah so inconclusive but but what task
were you
doing yeah the marshmallows are nowhere
near the r yeah so what were you doing
that was yeah but what were you doing
today huh we were doing a bunch of in
the reactor what are you doing what were
you doing in the reactor yeah what were
you doing in the reactor kind of su
[Laughter]
I skipped vote for now I'll give you
guys the benefit of the
doubt please don't kill us wasn't
me all right I got to go check if nura
was right that there's sand castles at
the
dock let's see maybe she didn't think
anybody would go
check there's no sand castle
here
okay that little detail it's a little
too
sus caught in a lie should I call a
meeting maybe I shouldn't right
now pass
um I won't do it right now but I'll just
use it in the next meeting hopefully if
I don't
die
um I'm not going over there I have tasks
over here I'll
do at least as the impostor I mean as
the uh crew mate we won one
once try to stay away from
people maybe car is safe cuz she's not
chasing me
down what is this trash thing I keep
doing it but it's
not wait
what am I doing it wrong it's bugged I
click up and then a cuz there's no it
doesn't look like there's any type of
response
happening shake it shake it let's go
back up maybe we'll find a
body I'm going to watch we got narissa
bi
boo [\h__\h] I don't want to be down here oh
shoot
[Music]
all right so it's Nissa and Kiara huh it
was Kara it was
Kara don't believe her do you see I saw
people kill am I am medic I am medic I
can see people's vitals yeah and I can
see you kill am turn around I can see
people's VES I have three battery
charges every round to see how many
people are alive first time I I saw no
no no this is hard for me because I had
just I had just seen bio and but I did
not see kiata and I was going down and
she didn't follow me so she might have
realized she was alone with but uh bioo
also when she killed me self-reported
and then immediately literally I've got
the scientist and I have this is the
first time I played it so how would I
know that I have three charges of
scientist
to where is the body time in a while all
the body is up the
stairs okay I
[Music]
saw watch it you probably just looked up
some guide about those no I didn't this
is the first time I have whatever
scientist whatever I can check people
well I was I was so often alone with
others and I didn't kill them so why
would I know exactly why some VCH for me
cuz I think I was Al Alone Together
come
on I was alone with for a while but I
was not alone with Kiara yeah I saw
Kiara for like a split
second I several times alone and I saw
crony several times I think alone and I
saw n she saw me wanted to kill me yeah
it felt like um either Kiara or FAA was
going to kill me cuz like they were just
kind of walking around so I stuck around
one of them to make sure I didn't get
killed um it would kind of check out if
Kiara was nobody's in the dead DC guys
don't ask I believe nobody's in there
not even call Call's in here with
everybody else T all a pictures are
here
goodbye thanks
forever I I love you or
I'm than you forever
well somebody's not voting the accepted
that me out but I guess you you'll
stalling it's so sad I I was always with
you
guys I love
you goodbye goodbye I will go up like a
phoenix and I will rise like a phoenix
wait what I thought it' over now so
maybe somebody was shapeshifting as
foko maybe it was Kiara shape shifting
as
them e there's still one more was I
right then was it Nissa because of the
dock the saian castle at the dock it's
got to be among us
fish Among Us fish Among Us fish Among
Us
fish think
cute and now to grill the
fish so wait I think I can read chat now
I think it's fine oh oh oh oh
um what is that Guardian Angel thing it
only applies like the first time in the
lobby cuz I haven't seen it haven't seen
like those wings since
then
it's 60% CH oh okay it's oh okay it's
not guaranteed I
see how do I see my
tasks I guess I can't see them while
this thingy is
up oh Call's got she's the garden angel
a f is not dead yeah I don't know why I
thought they we voted them off but I
think it was a
tie
Pi the mushroom put the mushroom in the
lab
maybe wait what is
[Music]
this uh trying to remember where any of
the other tasks are cuz I can't do that
I can't do those
thingies I saved them I
did okay so now they just have to vote
out then I guess it would be
them if cie saw them do
[Laughter]
it
nice is this the last task maybe oh
second to last
task nice
okay
uming pit I didn't vote yeah yeah I I
skipped to vote I gave them the benefit
of the doubt but they were
guilty let's here let's hear what this
is all
about
hello oh no I just missed I I believe
it's F what why like when we were going
to when comms were down we were going up
I see I see like um many of us were
going up I think it was like I think I
saw fa beu um I also saw I was also with
crony and narissa alone none of us
killed each other um and we were all
going up to comms but then I see F
coming down from comms ignoring the fact
that comms is do the bottom one first
first right we just to do the tasks and
you know you at the Top If you were at
the top you would do the top one right
but we're just counting like we're focus
on our task you can't see the task on
the map when comms are down yeah you
can't see yeah you can't but if you
walk we did last
time just I earlier why I decided think
so call lying is more difficult when
there's two
people
that's how we play
among me me a task you did this time
what's what's a task you did what's a
task you
theen why did you you you come came back
down from comms even though com a
sabotage all the way back down to the
greenhouse the greenhouse is
pretty green greenhous is
pretty you got
a
who are the cutest puppies who
[Music]
areow Liars look at the Little Liars
oh cute Little
Liars just about bowing
[Laughter]
it
love byebye
[Music]
come on cast
your yeah don't don't um delay your
death it's yeah it's inev time to go
it's time to go excuse
me bye bye
[Music]
[Applause]
puppies
that was
funny was funny
round that was really good susing out
Iris that was
impressive from the reactor too even the
last round when when we almost voted
them out cuz they didn't know what they
were doing at the
reactor was that made me 80% sure and
then I saw them going down from comp oh
yeah what we crew me we'll do the ex
yes
pleas I'm so sorry it's
okay you were just trying to survive I
think I think out of this whole group of
people me and foku are like the worst
Liars so it was a good
combination my B you Bast my b
we were so bad it's hard to lie with two
people makes me
laugh I laugh
too see see I I had a good the good life
you know I did the marshmallows and then
she goes oh we did that last
time oh my god well I finally got
imposter do we don't want to do one more
round
yeah hide and seek CH the map yeah hide
and seek hide and seek
hiek hide andek sounds fun it's like
hideand-seek like how you'd really think
hide-and-seek I don't think we have to M
for hideand-seek wasn't there an actual
setting for hide and seek though there
there is there is the computer you might
have to make a new room though maybe um
if you can't change it in the settings
um on the computer yeah then you might
have to make a new room is it yeah no I
don't think you can change it
here okay then I'll make a new one
watch okay it's kind of like it's pretty
much like playing tag yeah
cute um any preferred
map let's do orig oh yeah
yeah
nice I'll send you the link in the group
uh the in the group okay there you yeah
this one's chaotic but really funny
thank you never done it before oh it's
fine and it's a short game too
so let's go
perfect man this is scary this one this
is like the only time I actually want to
be imposter hide and
seek I never want to be imposter ever
again same we don't have for this oh no
I don't think
so try not to give away your location on
accident I guess we can mute if we're
done uh we don't have to right die hide
and
seek I'm not yeah in this game hey
you wait we can we can hide in V oh is
there only
one oh is this like zombies like the
infection
[Music]
spread better run we can hide really
slow do tasks the timer goes down
quicker so slow you have 3 minutes to
hide three minutes to hide she's in the
med Bay
upper engine she's coming
for wait
what oh
man yeah she's GRE who knows what color
I might
[Music]
be everybody's clumping
together where is she right now make the
time go down quicker oh my
God
hi wait how does this
[Music]
work no do your best you can hear the
music come close to you when she's close
by that's
scary crony where's crony oh no CR she
coming for you R say
it
I don't understand
this oh that's fun that's so quick too
that was so short I want to be
[Music]
impost for both the impostor and the the
the the crew
mates can we increase the speed for both
crew mates I want to but also I I uh I
think I have to make a new Lobby because
I don't think I can change the amount of
uh
Seekers there's only one
one yeah I it's fine to leave it on one
we just need to speed up so we're all
running really
fast okay
maximum let's go this is how it should
be oh jeez oh
boy yumpy let's
go y
wait do I get to go that fast too I
think so
oh I'm going to be Unleashed for my C
that F
honestly okay oh God where do I go we
have to do tasks do your task there
tasks task God I don't see them I see
tasks but I don't know what I really
want to finish that
sorry it's all good
[Music]
why do I have
no I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared I
hear I hear the base we got to win we
got to win this I can't find you guys
what the heck where's everyone oh it's
so
[Music]
fast
why are you guys yelling I'm not even
near you
[Music]
Terri this like a horror game all of a
sudden on the
scre where did you guys
go you guys are so
fast what are you yelling for terrifying
screams here
you
guys is so much more louder and louder
yeah it's so CH
get shoot the moment you hear the guitar
Rift you're
like she
coming hold it
together
God my eyes are spinning 20 seconds 20
more
[Music]
seconds where's the last who's who's
last oh you're going to be even faster
in the final round I'm alive okay should
I do tasks no no don't do tasks what do
you mean you got to run for your
lifea hiding I need you to run around
like I headless
chicken wait there's more she get one
more minute come after me don't stand
still it's going to show your
location it shows do you guys know it
shows your location yeah there's a
there's a red dot uh that indicates
where the
crew I should I see dead bodies I see
dead bodies I see dead
people my
i f because you see me from the map she
get
closer how are you getting so
[Music]
Mast that
was I was about to get
it that was impressive Iris that was I
SC I just didn't really see her on the
screen that often so thank God everybody
was so fast
[Laughter]
that you guys are teleporting across the
map yeah the ghost couldn't even keep
[Music]
C nothing is who is it this time let's
go who is
[Music]
it today I think going to have fun
R does doing tasks do anything like we
put early task wi if we do if we finish
them all yeah and we could get lucky I
was being very proactive with the task
hide hide and seek you got to
hide why can't I oh
[Music]
no okay got to go got to go I was about
to get in the thing I'm sorry
I'm
sorry
ni oh no's on you guys on you guys damn
it I I do wonder if doing tasks is even
worth it I know right oh yeah instead of
just surving easy
bait oh my God go she ran past she ran
past
no no she run run run so fast she's on
the the left side of the map she's she's
going on she's going to the cafeteria
wait can we tell her okay I don't want I
it might be a little
unfair oh okay I felt that was the the
wrong direction okay you know what um
let's do our tasks sque we I'm too
scared to move around at this point die
whenever I use do tasks it's
just
in
4k she only has only three
left what is the danger me there ah come
on guys one more one more
minute such a good hiding spot though
she's going at a good Pace very good tce
oh 30 30 seconds right 35 seconds that
was amazing keep going keep going keep
she almost was a really good hiding spot
yeah that was hiding
spot I hear it so loud all the time oh
no whoops you guys are slippery it's
difficult when everybody's so
fast is there overtime she's in there
over there's one more it's so fast I
can't you got to
survive
let's go no pressure oh
man5
seconds just go just
[Music]
go getting
to the
wall got 10 seconds 10 seconds 10
seconds easy easy she won't get you she
won't she won't get you oh
[Music]
no
what you should have just St still
K you should have paid in a
corner one literally one second aill
like mat though that was that was
amazing that was the clutchest ever
what can't escape time at the end of the
day but was really slippery yeah really
slippery yeah oh my God that was
exciting exting I'm I'm pretty exhausted
from that but we can do another one if
you want I'm
more
actually you know wait wait oh no before
Oh I want to I speed so
fast yeah it's fast oh good okay never
mind you
wanted how do you kill the whole time um
there's a kill button so don't you worry
okay oh my God no way I don't want to be
it no the has awakened she has awakened
I'm coming for you nobody's using my
hiding spot
right that's a good idea don't use my
hiding spot going work that your no that
wasn't your hiding
spot holy sh he on a rampage there were
two only saw one
person
overlapped does the music get louder for
me too I feel like it does yeah I don't
know it get louder oh when you're near
someone really even for
imposter get out of there get out of
there you little
[\h__\h] what's going
[Music]
on
slippery
[\h__\h] where are they
my hiding
[Music]
spot she's checking the
corner oh no that's that's the
stack I still got time I still got
time oh I saw someone where is
she that hiding
spot oh that's
[Music]
that being
soly oh my God that was no no I haven't
found anyone in the cages you passed by
somebody
a someone's here no oh
[\h__\h]
H where are
you hello I'm all
alone no hints no oh what was that there
was some button popping up there the use
button
yes in
[Music]
time
my hiding spot I couldn't even see you
that's lame what the
heck even see you surprise well I saw
you that's all that
matters dang it ni turn around so
quick
AO oh one more one
more
run
no
no there's still one more
minute they're literally run
run run run run you can throw it through
a loop just run just
run go in a circle go in a
[Music]
circle pun pun pun P pun
wow
[Music]
do that was clutch again pretty clutch I
would say get into
the out foring after Mama M that was wow
that was fun that was fun that was merry
I'm too excited to say anything so let's
start with the with the goodbyes from
anybody but me
um please yeah this is really fun I'm
glad we could get together and have like
a little Christmas Among Us
celebration thank you
Tiara the perfect holiday SE holiday
game right for
real just red with boy and some blood
when I think of Christmas I think of
Among
Us Among Us
ornament it's pretty festive the colors
are want to play this makes me want to
play on Project
winter
my f yeah I know
[Music]
C wow I'm sorry you died so often my
fected but that's okay it was still fun
call what about you you had some good
good kills was fun it was nice getting
to dust off the old Scythe for once and
get back in the game for a little bit
that was nice happy
holiday yeah I had a great time with
everybody here everybody here is fun to
talk to fun to argue with in a fun way
really in a fun way yeah in a fun way I
guess that's about it we should argue
more often yeah let's do it let's do it
no no I can't maybe not yeah no we're
just stay TI but within among us we can
argue as much as we want we and then
outside of Among Us you know we're
different people among us changes us but
what happens in Among Us stays and Among
Us among
us all right and please please tell me
about your experience today science
Rules science science Bill science
science science Rules end statement than
great interesting interesting I don't
quite understand but I agree oh I don't
think Kiara knows about Bill it's all
right don't worry about
it don't worry about
it we'll tell you later we'll tell you
later
okay Mrs Mrs Santa Claus Mrs Christ yes
yeah no this was fun I'm glad I was able
to lie better this
time yeah you some good lying yeah we
need to learn from
IR that was yeah everyone everyone was
great I love how bad F was at L yeah oh
yeah you can tell you can tell it's
their first time you can tell it's first
time my first time it was the same as me
when I played for the first time so
worry first time was always like that
great I love it thank you very much that
was fun they were so lucky cuz like in
that one round they were about to be
voted off and I thought I was going to
be alone but then somehow somehow they
survived somehow they survived
right we couldn't save you k no it's
okay we couldn't save each other even if
we wanted
to well thank you Iris and then
people what about you I was happy to be
able to to kill people I wish I was able
to kill more people but I
will amount of people I was able to kill
this time that's the spirit thank you
for your service that's the spirit
that's the Christmas spirit let's go
let's
go that was some good reaping it was
solid solid reaping good job again I'm
so sorry P okay a
trail what stays in Among Us stays Among
Us don't worry exactly
yeah well we learn a lot of things today
we really good at lying right yeah that
was
it and uh we have fun we we yelled a bit
screamed a bit and we did a lot of
lying yeah but most importantly we had
[Music]
fun
true let's play
more when I saw I was imposter with f m
I knew I knew that you weren't going to
be good at
[Laughter]
lying to our
face sweet yeah it's all good it's
funny I had so much fun thank you so
much for putting it together kiaha
[Music]
I'm sad I had to be the impostor I don't
like it brings me no joy yeah were
greaters though Mur I know what you mean
no oh but you were so good though you
were good at it round was over right
away
me te blue women women are
scary blue women always say it it's the
blue people the the avatars I always say
it mhm
yes thank you you're welcome I'm glad
you had a good time let's continue this
in the Mal Dives yeah
peacefully the other Blue Woman
quason yeah it was a lot of fun I'm kind
of surprised that I actually got
impostor twice U because I never get
imposter yeah I never get these
roles yeah and thank you for organizing
this it was a lot of
fun among
us I guess you know there was all sorts
of drama but like we said earlier what
happens Among Us stays Among
Us good wow
beautiful well said Thank You
Quon well yeah that's pretty much it um
but Christmas is not over yet I think
there's still members that have like
special streams upcoming so check them
out everybody and I just want to make
one quick announcement about the whole
Ian Advent calendar some people may
already know but the last day the 25th
day will be delayed a little bit so uh a
few days uh the it's out of my hands out
of my power now but please check back on
it next week we'll all tweet about it
when it is finally up uh so stay tuned
stay excited and thank you for spending
Christmas with us viewers I say to you
viewers thank you for spending it with
us and thank you to the girls for
spending it also with us thank you for
getting together at this
time Christmas
chras H
every fun that was really great and I
hope everybody has a nice nice holiday
season some
cookies y Yum Yum Yum Yum okay I have
some protein milk in my
fridge very crisp leave for
Santa maybe Santa s will come to mil oh
protect your
milk yeah all right I don't think that's
G to make Iris like Santa
anymore already
does oh no Santa is is literally the
tree now okay I'm the tree but I'm not
yeah don't let Santa drink the protein
milk we can't let him get any stronger
than no muscles for Santa no don't give
him the power poison the
cookies wait isn't like in some
countries Santa drinks beer or people
give beer to Santa really sounds German
Santa gets drunk I don't know I think so
drunk Santa visiting kids homes I don't
know if that's oh no and then he drops
just makes it worse that doesn't really
sound like something I would want to
tell my children over yeah okay that I
think some people already gone like
foral go is gone already so let's go
[Music]
everybody happy holidays all a good
evening
[Music]
bye
oh