[Music]
he
w
[Music]
n
a
[Music]
he
K I'm coming hello she's here hello
hello you're here I'm here
[Music]
thank you thank
you that was a amazing loading screen
right made by chy thank you so much it's
so good hey hat welcome back thank you
thank you I miss
you I I miss you too I miss her life too
yeah welcome back we're so happy to have
you back but I heard hat has a memory
problem or memory problem
I don't think so I'll remember
everything why really I feel like you
have some gaps missing gaps yeah I I I
don't know and sometimes yeah it's okay
I will teach you with memes me teach me
memes oh
me yes okay okay
okay you still remember English thank
you yeah so actually we we only have a
short uh amount of time guys because I
have to get out of the studio after an
hour so it will be a short memory
refresher but you know um so hatama has
been gone for like eight months eight
months so I asked you guys uh what memes
you want me to introduce to hatama from
the past
[Music]
than I'm so excited
but so almost all of them were like
whole life English related because most
of the memes were from English speaking
fans you know so I can't help you much
with Japanese side memes
[Music]
I'm
let's guess yes yes yes yes
yes okay
okay let's check out the memes Y come on
come on memes we'll start right away
with this
one let's see so top left says can't
wait to collab of counselors when I come
back this is hot saying right huh and
there was Council and Iris our after
whole life English myth
oh after those Generations we had
counsel and Irish you know right yeah I
know I but now you're back at Council
and IR is gone huh they're
gone what grad
graduation what are
you so what six members
[Music]
graduated my brain
no confused I li it's it's it's a lie
it's a lie no graduation no
no actually actually counil and Iris
became one generation
Fusion ah what's name is it promise
promise promise
promise it's
[Music]
promise n the
[\h__\h] n
theck yeah so it's it's because well you
know Council already only was down to
four members and Iris was always
alone she was lonely maybe I don't know
there may be many reasons but now it's
whole life English promise promise
nice I wish promise nice nice nice oh
and also uh just maybe in end of
November in October November of October
all of Promise they have a 3D
debut conratulations
[Music]
congratulations nice yeah it was pretty
pretty funny pretty interesting and at
the end know after all
individual uh
freedy they had one big collab with
promise all of wow surprise very new new
jul new news
yes
promise nice nice nice yeah but that's a
big shock like first you have two
generations now it's
one no more Council no more
Irish Irish is no Irish Irish still
here I guess it was it shows the Irish
logo but actually it was
Project okay next let's go next next me
next what's
that ity
ity what is it okay so there's a meme uh
template where it's like if you don't
love me at my uh
[Music]
worst
if you don't love me at my worst then
you don't love deserve me at my
[Music]
best
I get
[Music]
it if you don't want me at my
normal then you don't deserve me at my
RTX on
money do you know what this is ex mared
what is
it recently there was whole life summer
oh whole life summer and there were two
theme songs two two theme
song one was
say the other one was not
say and my Senai was in the not say not
of course yeah and then they in the
middle of the
song There was a transformation
transformation
jumps into a pool and she comes out in
this
beautiful it's crazy that's crazy it's
so
[Music]
crazy everybody was so like what the
[\h__\h] is going on it's crazy I will show
you what's name is
it if you don't love me add my RTX Mar I
guess I don't know if she has official
name but English fans say this is RTX on
RTX huh because it's like RTX is like a
graphic um graphic card or looks like
more more
realistic yes yes yes RTX off RTX
on I want to be an atie EG you want to
look like the the right
side ah a little bit okay okay RTX on
let's go next time next time maybe oh do
you know Dead or Alive Dead or Alive
game no does it have a different
Japanese name Dead or
Alive
[Music]
really d o
a
oh it's just like that in
Japanese
it's oh okay I make it bigger let's
let's look from the top this is H life
English uh happening so for me and GA
and M and F and in we want in Minecraft
we wanted to kill the uh what is he
called not D who is it what was with the
river the wizard wizard W wi wizard
wizard so H but they say he's really
really strong really
difficult so we prepared so much for
months n
[Music]
get then home
the actual stream where we killed the
wizard we um we looked for a location
far away for an
[Music]
hour we looked for a space for one hour
or so but
then we start fighting three minutes
later three minutes later
dead we killed him in three
[Music]
minutes Overkill
Overkill we we really fought
oh we have to prepare so much we have to
be strong we have to fight we need we
need a potion and we need weapons and we
need
armor
it just ended immediately yeah so we
were like in a dream potion yeah we made
everything but it was so for nothing
n come
down what the hell too
[Music]
easy
next nice nice nice
oh okay let's start
[Music]
here this is just an example of where
girls CED girls cry H where boys cried
whole life English first concert
oh that also happened whole life English
first concert in uh July I think wow in
Los Angeles Los Angeles wow that's cool
yeah it was big big big event everybody
[Music]
cried the bo cry the men
CED cried at
stream scam what's happened let's look
at it bigger men cry do you think this
stream
[Laughter]
is what is he
[Music]
doing Jus J Jus
yes it's a game where cute
looking
private
parts private parts private
parts and you play private parts and and
you move around and you I don't know
what you
do move
around sausage P sausage P yeah and then
you can like cut SA part cut cut and do
all kinds of things with the sausage
yeah sausage cut yeah and fails playing
it and it became a big big topic
everybody was watching and suffering and
[Music]
laughing every yes no way she played she
played with the sausage and she cut the
sausage and she tore
[Music]
[Laughter]
Tor
oh me yes yes please read next Roma
gladiating yeah there was a you talk
[Music]
abouta I told it I told it and you said
no no no no graduation no gradu of
course
[Music]
but
univers I can't tell
you you B
no but it's like you
[Music]
know you have to graduate but
actually I never
graduate oh you have to graduate though
I want to go to the kindergarten oh oh
you can graduate kindergarten no no no I
want to go start again the kindergarten
okay okay I think it's it's fitting
place
for Place yeah I I saw I saw
kindergarten
okay nice we can clap
together okay for
Japanese I think I know
it I know it yes I check it what you do
oh she she knows okay so there's I don't
even know oh really I had I had my uh
viewers explain you can explain I think
now now I know a little bit so there's
Gable can at
yes
yes Finance okay you explain a finance
yeah there's a
finance uh there is some slot there I I
don't know not the slot maybe maybe they
uh give the some
money I think so I heard this horse
race yeah yeah I think this one is
different not not not one not horse
racing horse racing uh maybe they they
give the money everyone for everyone
like how do you say uh the KAS KAS and
ah they they Bor no they uh S no not s
uh uh what's the opposite of
Bor yeah money moneyy money money they
loan the money loan money loan to lots
of M members and then if uh if they if
that whole life member couldn't uh P pay
back Lo they go to the Neo Island and
they have to work right work at Neo
Island get a get a money yeah diamonds
but many could not get diamonds many
whole life very
bad so I heard that a lot of H life
members they steal
diamonds from other places
[Music]
because
theage
very problematic very problematic so
they were very
desperate
desperate if you know this then why is
mikoi naked why Miki naked because it's
her fetty fetty her fetish no is it
because she had no money so she had to
give her clothes really I don't know
that's why I don't know that's the only
thing I don't know well maybe maybe she
was reborn naked baby naked
baby I want to go ni Nick Island oh I
also never went let's go let's go let's
go but then maybe we have to work I
walk let's break the let's break the
island
okay
nice
next Maybe maybe I will get maybe they
will be angry at me for using this what
I'm risking
it really so there I guess there was a
Netflix documentary about uh a party
that never
[Music]
happened the greatest party that never
happened
[Music]
I don't know why I don't know this I
don't know this at all but so they make
it into a meme because H life summer H
life Summer Splash party Splash party
two two Day concert okay on uh on
streaming only not real life concert um
two
days but everybody was waiting everybody
was m
and it didn't
happen
canel it was cancelled because the
server re broke the
server the streaming server yeah broke
the Ser yeah yeah because normally we
use different streaming servers so many
people mhm but we used new server a new
server and it didn't work we were too
strong
[Music]
yeah so then we had to cancel cuz we
waited 1 hour or so but then next day
for free the whole concert on YouTube
really
yeah
[Music]
wow thank you thank you thank you
cover but thank you cover but second day
you pay money yes
yes so this is a meme because uh the
other party also never happened so okay
n good Pace good Pace good Pace yeah
okay this is a tweet yeah tweet funny
tweet let's look first at original tweet
from so original tweet V is uploading an
episode
of and this is with
K is her name but can you explain
C boy yes she put the open into
the and then uh whole life official
account translate translate please
[Music]
read nothing wrong new appla I'm just
doing UPS it is wrong to bur my face and
call
yeah so they did direct translation and
then K read my
what she was
angry what is me
[Music]
the I don't know
why it's a funny way of
saying
but is
like but whole life
official said it first they were just
translating it's not it's not yeah it's
not the Ian account
for have to I have
to
[Music]
actual genius not as genius
as
I'm one life no no no no no okay okay
[Music]
next oh okay okay let's look at this uh
like from the top so recently there was
a whole life Minecraft sports festival
oh sports festival yeah you participate
last year or so
maybe so H there was all new games new
games uh hold up hold up yeah you know I
know it
[Music]
[Applause]
I wow one
congratulations so there was one game
that
was let's say team of three people they
get a
[Music]
prompt
so first one was uh 149 CM or
shorter and so ah yeah so that is Canada
sire right but no capture no capture
Escape next is debute between 2019 and
2020 she escaped no capture nice she
escaped also
it mean
she she
[Music]
can't the next is has more than three
solo original
songs also call but she run run run
run good job good job and last one is
been busted
by she escaped
again okay
so next is when nobody chooses you to
protect or be
sexy come
on she couldn't be she wanted to be uh
captured but she was nobody thought of
[Music]
her they don't even consider
her and then
[Music]
next
she was brought in for say so people
somebody thought maybe she say
[Music]
from
so this was a very very sadads
[Music]
yeah too bad too bad someone cat you
catada yes
yes okay
[Music]
me okay in
2020 she
with what
you it's she oh
I thought I thought she she was already
already have
it maybe this is long time ago here she
realized oh I like rocky
pie and n n sun and this year h s is
she's
watching I think it's h yeah yeah yeah
she's watching and everybody show their
Rocky p a everybody
Rocky
happy so happy and oh actually this uh
the k k is not whole life summer I think
it's uh her own uh
Frey showcase I
think and she even said even though was
not
there this is for
[Music]
you she was very happy
a me I also have a pie me too oh really
me too but I can't
I
need
okay all right I have uh
Muki two two
[Music]
oh oh the new one yeah you showed in
your in your stream
recently I I oh I think it does not
change I mean I just
[Music]
I not not I can I can
ch I just I just K this
oh wow oh
luy there's some luy somewhere when I
change to this clothes um uh when I
change to this the
ghost uniform not uniform the costume
outfit uh my bo bo uh a little bit small
small I turn oh maybe no no you know
some
[Music]
brass why because I want to
beor it's nice if you can have
both so versatile oppai is very
versatile
okay
next actually we're so fast we can go
slow
slow very fast very fast okay oh
speaking
of this
is summer H life summer uh official
stream uh where Mizuki
revealed and uh this is from second F
song uh members I know second
[Music]
much many many big op member so we start
left
side Wi-Fi connection it's Wii
connection Wi-Fi connection
Senai bad connection ah bad connection
[Music]
Senai Senai Senai
a good
collection best connection
connection it's a big big
connection I guess this is the order of
more than just the Wi-Fi
connection but they're all big yeah
they're all big me very big big yes but
crony crony size is something
[Music]
else me too I want to I want to have big
opai too big opai what's what's opai are
you I don't know what you don't know I
don't know
what
k k
k k c how big is K C I don't even know
okay okay next
me next me I'm Miss oh okay this is
interesting uh how long ago maybe 1
month ago how um there's a game
everybody play sua game right you know
sua game everybody everybody was playing
this every day all of whole life was
playing SOA game too
many who would win 83 plus talents
playing s game or one Ark
player let's let's show this one first
because it's connected
so here we have
[Music]
explanation what for one month she
played Arc for around
270 Hours 27
yeah if you look at her
Channel like in the
archive
it's and all same thumbnail and all like
10 hour stream 12 hour
stream so who
win
that's crazy I never played Arc how I
play Arc before uh I play a bit a bit
little bit maybe maybe I should play it
too I don't
know maybe play
Senai
play play with Senai Senai nice nice
nice nice nice okay
next
this this is uh free memes free pictures
so this and
this what name
uh what's group name adult ADV not adult
ad ad not
adult life
adult they're not so
ad so this girl is narissa Nissa very
C second one is
Shi yeah yeah yeah and Nissa love
Shi but right after debut Shi take small
break so
like where is sh where is sh I want to
see my shy and here too she's like oh
where is Brazil here where is France
here where is
sh she drinks alcohol because she
miss so sad and then another one this is
uh do you know Lord of the Rings Lord of
the Rings okay this is Lord of the Rings
me only know name I only know name oh
okay okay this is Lord of the Rings me
combined with
life so it's me saying they taking to
eard she's
like what did you
say and I say guard guard guard guard
[Music]
okay
yeah yeah I explained it's difficult if
you don't know but yeah she's shocked
because she only
know is Sil coming back coming back yes
yes yes yes small break small break
no problem welcome back welcome back
short maybe maybe hatama can make
friends with h life Advent have you
talked with who I only
talk oh how what did you talk about
um like nice to meet you
[Music]
and I couldn't I couldn't uh I couldn't
realiz the H which one is
H in the beginning I
understand you can understand very very
fast I think because M has more Ganky
voice and has
more chill
voice
okay
[Music]
next oh what's that
IAM I think maybe not in Japan uh only
America maybe uh for McDonald's
mcdonaldd um there's a character mascot
that's called uh the Grimace Grimace
grimas oh I don't know also in
Europa not in
Europe what what about the Pi Pi Pi oh
oh
[Music]
but in America there is Grimace
but people don't like Grimace
apparently so sad right he's a big big
purple fluffy fluffy monster
monster but everybody always hate him
but for his
birthday they make milkshake milkshake
for grimace nice nice so it's a purple
purple
milkshake but and everybody buy it and
drink it and say happy birthday
Grimace gri but they say it's so bad
when you drink it you
die influencer influencer influ
[Music]
influencer influencer everybody was
making Tik Tok where they buy the drink
and they drink it and they die but that
makes that makes Grimace even more sad
what the
G because he was like oh nobody likes my
birthday
shame so sad yeah let's marry me
no he's he's cute I don't know why
people hate him I don't know why but uh
at this time at his birthday am gur me
everybody from myth we were in Japan in
Japan so we were everybody we were
talking and home life English Community
we were talking about Grim shake so yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah but I think it's probably not that
bad right I never I never try I never
try Grim no try I'm a I think I'm a try
and she died
[Laughter]
no okay
[Music]
next so did you know fle sleep in a bed
like this wow oh bunk bed bunk bed so
this is
a this is a mean because f f makes fun
[Music]
of this is is so she's sleeping and she
says mama there's a monster under my
[Music]
bed and she says it's the most hideous
thing I've ever seen kind of
like we're
[Music]
twins it's really funny Dynamic so
cute do you know you know back seating
back seating
mhm
Chu it's back seating back and uh with
they have one channel right one channel
and they always collab always coll so
always play the game
mostly the f is sitting right next to
her and she always say do this that ah
why and I know you did wrong come on
come
oning yeah
and please be nice to Mo nice
[Music]
to
Next Love
I love this meme
so remember peon pizza peoni pizza and
you have good good pepponi pizza pepponi
pizza is hat
Pokemon then K Pokemon
is corn cup Pizza corn cup Pizza I make
in pizza with on the crust I make a COR
no
I shaved it and I put on the cross on
the outside of the pizza everywhere so
you see have you never seen something
like this before right it's all corn
corn corn corn corn corn corn corn corn
corn cor corn Pizza you like corn corn I
like corn it's so good right corn Pizza
I make the best corn Pizza by
pizza so challeng challeng
B we battled the pizzas no chicken on it
uh no h I made I made corn and tuna tuna
tuna tuna
onion I made half Margarita I think
marar and half tuna half tuna but why is
my pizza level 50 and how my pizza level
[Music]
pizza but my pizza has so many more
ingredients I lose it's too much too
much but don't you don't you want to
try try it I want to try it I see very
good pizza I buy a pizza
oven very
good is maybe last meme oh it was this
one okay maybe I didn't have
enough I could have had
more no more thank you wait let's go on
Twitter maybe I find more okay let's go
on
Twitter I asked by the way I I asked you
guys for memes with the uh
hasham M yeah meme I had to sort out so
many because
copyright but did you did you learn from
today did you learn some new things I
Lear I learn so much so many actually
now they all use it for streaming has oh
what is
this what is this well let's try this
together cuz oh what's this what's this
a oh this maybe good one I found one
more
interesting where is it download so many
files yeah here here this go oh too
big too big didn't
[Music]
I didn't
I okay I put in
here
maybe me
[Music]
me now it has to
be last meme last M five six seven eight
n
why why why
why it's not so
big it's not so big it doesn't show
up man that's
okay
maybe I want to show this door it's
funny maybe it's
wrong ah it's saved
as J F I have cannot right
now different different
file come on it's not coming try screen
capture
[Music]
okay there is
no no what's the shortcut for screen
capture yes it's coming I make
screenshots yeah where did it
go screenshot I don't even know where
the screenshots go automatically I can't
help you let me find different one what
is this but it probably saves the same
way okay I will explain I cannot show it
but I will explain it was a meme about
uh GI
guesser and there was this was also uh
flavor of the month game me
everybody is like uh let's start from
from the bottom K is from
Indonesia but she is like where is
Indonesia she can't even find on the map
and then there's Iris and uh even though
she has a lover
and she has lover in Australia Australia
but she still can't find Australia on
the
map and then loo Senai looks at this
building and she should know right
because she's in Japan so but she says
this is Tokyo Tower but it's not Tokyo
Tower it's not Tokyo Tower really and
everybody is like really confident here
money Senai thinks she knows it and F
but also thinks ah this is Japan I know
I know but they're all wrong I think and
then auk Senai was on a whole another
level do you know oh yeah she's good
at she created the word I
[Music]
think so she always find the exact Z
meter without zero meter difference just
super exact
location
[Music]
she was streaming do you guess her every
day and she always find the exact
location so she
[Music]
is it's broken I broke I broke the my my
OBS sorry so what happened many things
happen but from now on with hat more
things happen
[Music]
Y is back wants what what kind of things
do you want to
do I want
cooking play game M
uh like h t game
[Music]
English CL English
CL please please I I want to study
English more and more but your English
so good English English very good
English no not how English is don't say
don't say your English is Taco because
it's very
[Music]
good
okay I'm proud of my English and maybe
we can do a cooking collab cooking I
also do many many cooking stream yay
nice nice and English stream yeah with
home
life me and promise promise yeah I I
want to CL with promise too yeah an
advent Advent not adult not adult okay
we learned many things sorry guys the
stream is so short because we have to
leave the
[Music]
studio yes
callam yes yes yes thank you for
youres and I want h o oh h
[Music]
okay okay okay b b come over
here okay thank you everybody for
watching and German we say
and in German we
[Music]
say
okay thank you thank you thank you guys
for watching thank
you I'm so
[Music]
happy oh oh wait one last
thing
[Music]
so
cute very very
o thank you it's a Christmas O Christmas
O Christmas Tree presents enjoy enjoy
I'm enjoy oh byebye byebye
[Music]
anding