[Music]
I you I want what I need do you
you
[Music]
[Applause]
with the everything
the I be theing queen of
[Music]
you see
you you
you me I you I don't even know what to
do
[Music]
don't even know what to do with
this could play a me around
[Music]
heart
I still wonder if I was made for you if
I could only be
[Music]
me I you I even know what to do with
this
[Music]
see you me everyone
keeping my
way I'm just I know bre me shake
[Music]
me
do around
[Music]
around
um
no I'm not still D I'm in the game but
um I just
watched like I'm almost at the finale of
Breaking Bad I
have like the last two episodes to go
minus the first 10 minutes of the second
to last
episode I saw the scene with with uh wal
Al White in the car from the
meme now I know what that's
about I'm
so disappointed in the
outcome
man
no no
[Music]
no I want to
cry why just like Just Like Jesse says
he can't keep on getting away with
it bro
[\h__\h] bastard I mean okay I will give
him the credit that he really tried to
call it off at least for the sake of
Hank like I don't know like for him it's
like okay family is off limits even
though Hank is not blood related he had
the same kind of rule for Jesse because
he felt like family to him but while he
would have never broken the his own
morals for Hank he was going to break
his own morals for Jesse even though
they're both not blood rated but okay
okay double
standards but I will give him credit for
that that he was going to you know like
not have this happen and even even oh my
God he really tried
okay those dudes yeah obviously big
spoiler
warning I'm going to talk about this
because cuz I have to talk about it now
I have to talk about it ah sorry my
microphone ah the the cable the
cable I have to talk it
out something I have this like little
bit of
a again
whatever but yeah
um what was I going to say those
dudes they seem to be able to like
follow orders quite well until that
point
Sorry but yeah why can't they follow
rules
then they always were like pretty good
at following orders I I would have
understood if they still came out
because the way he said like don't come
it's off on the phone sounded like he
could have also had a gun to his head
and being forced to say that at that
point so so you might still want to go
to see what's up
and like you know but that's not really
why they
came they wanted the money no no no no
no they they when they were on their way
they didn't know yet that there was
money there to gain in the
grounds afterwards yeah yeah they got
greedy for sure when once they knew but
they still came out without that
knowledge
let me let me mute my mic for a moment
and try to fix this cable
thing okay I don't think it gets better
than this but yeah it you won't hear it
when the game sound is
on ah
a [\h__\h] I'm so
pissed I
mean like he's still like thanks to
Netflix trailer spoilers that play
automatically when you hover over a show
I already know that it's going to get
caught eventually right but but still
like Hank should
be Hank should have been aive for that
Revenge
just keep watching well I can't keep
watching now can
I unless we turn this into a watchong I
have two episodes to go one of them I
already started a little
bit Ah don't spoil me
okay but you saying keep on watching
gives me hope now there's another funny
thing I want to say like yesterday okay
I was also staying up really late to try
to get through the season I was uh
watching a lot and at some point I was
like okay okay I could watch this
forever but it's already like 6:00 a.m.
I need to stop so then I switched to one
of my fall asleep shows TV shows um
which in this case was the office so I
switched from Breaking Bad to the
office
and the five fun as [\h__\h] to me I was
like what the [\h__\h]
um the scene that I stumbled into I
swear to God it was
exactly on this
scene now if you watched the office and
Breaking Bad this is too [\h__\h]
funny I was like wait wait wait wait
wait I've seen the office like five
times I I didn't realize he wasn't that
show he played a tiny role but no
way and that's the scene I stumble into
the moment I switch
scenes this is taken from my phone by
the way out of excitement that I just I
can't no
way no way no way
[Music]
I had to take some double
takes there is no way I I'm like okay
breaking bed I'm done for today I I will
break my bed I'll sleep now let's switch
to the office as a background noise the
first thing I see is Gail
Bier
no I can't believe it and then the other
thing I wanted to show you um so when
when Rika and ren were here we went to a
lot of museums right and one of the
museums was just uh like like a more
like a modern type of Museum where it's
really just art pieces on a wall on a
like a
simple wall non decorated and really
like modern looking simple style of
Museum and there was this one gallery
where it was all from one
artist I forgot his
name um I can probably look it up but I
forgot his name and he drew like all
kinds of really [\h__\h] up pieces of art
uh
like kind of weird there was this like
whole room where there was like 10
pieces of art from him where Pinocchio
was involved but it was like really
friller horror style than for raid uh
like I don't know this guy was obsessed
with all kinds of things and anyway he
also sometimes Drew
self-portraits okay this artist drew
some
self-portraits every now and then
and you tell
me you you tell me what you
see hm
cuz I see a [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
Heisenberg especially the right one or
like a mix of those two Mr White Mr
White Mr
White there were some more
self-portraits that looked less like Mr
White but these two I was like what the
[\h__\h] this
artist first I thought oh he drew Mr
White but then I read the description
and it said self-portraits from the
artist yeah that's the
artist I can't believe I'm so
[\h__\h] brain
roted artist name gron
[Music]
no so we're going to play a Path of
Exile
unfortunately I want to watch one but I
have to do my job now and then I'll go
back and watch the final
finale can't be
helped cannot be helped
it is what it
[Music]
is long no no no no no no you guys have
been waiting for this so I you ask and
you shall receive you know although some
of you guys have quite serious man been
asking
for um you know you know what I'm really
hoping for is like if they did not sorry
one more spoiler if they did not record
that V uh the the phone call from Jesse
with
Walter uh and that somehow if if that if
they recorded it if that doesn't somehow
reach the [\h__\h] Police
Department because he basically
committed uh admitted to
everything in that phone call if if they
didn't record that [\h__\h] then they're
[\h__\h]
dumb anyway here's effect so [\h__\h]
loud it
really Coca-Cola
hiccups well I guess I'll find
[Music]
out last swearing okay careful
wa it's just
loud side
mostly there we go yeah I'm already in
the game there was no
que so really
easy oh yeah
mhm they did say something in the
beginning like oh you need to update
your graphics driver or something like
that and I
didn't it still let me in even though it
said you have to do it otherwise we
won't let you in but I was still able to
go in so hopefully it's
okay I should have it's fine it's
fine cuz I didn't know how would I
quickly find out what my graphic card is
and how how what driver I
need like sometimes when things tell you
to do that they give you like a button
to automatically update it and find did
it doesn't for you it didn't seem like
it did like I where how do I I don't
know they should make it easier for me
they already made it really complicated
with the steam key I had to Google to
figure out what the [\h__\h] is going on how
what [\h__\h] complicated I buy game in
Steam I think it work if I open but
no anyway let me eat some more
but I figured it out without asking you
guys why why Ste game not
work even by Early Access
version what mean need
key I almost bought another
one on the website out of
confusion I'm so capable
[Music]
why make com why make confusion when can
make game
play
okay so I hope you like your position
wait I'm too big
where should I
be what's a where's a good placement for
me you probably know
already
here my do
really
really covered the whole screen
sure yeah don't M
really
okay so I did no research on this
game so I got to look through the
classes here now but I heard there's a
fire Sorcerers and that that might fit
me but I feel like that's basically what
I'm playing in
Diablo
so sorceress it would be a big you were
banished by your aara for EXP
experimenting with the elements would
arrogance has led you here and arrogance
keeps you on those Gallows speak your
peace don't mention the d
[Music]
word well she's hot though is also hot
but can I are they are they gender
locked which is interesting wit your
very own coven cast you out for your
forbidden Pursuits I'm trying to read
this you're twisted necromancy ends here
at the end of a n okay so let's
Necromancer speak your last I do not
fear death I am its Master darkness and
the dead are my weapons of war my
enemies will rot from the inside out as
my Army of cop stears from screaming
limp from limp
M gender locked
okay so my choices are in that case
between the ranger the witch and the
Sorcerer
sorceress you were baned by your aara
for experiment only three glasses for me
arrogance has I like them already like
these are all ranged it seems
sorceress you were baned by your that's
what her Ranger all I need is a single
well placed Arrow lurking among the
Shadows of the treal and have the eyes
of a hog put a bow in my hands and
they'll die trying to catch me filthy
Thief yep yep yep your guilt is clear
plead for Mercy if you must
[Music]
mhm okay one last bite hover over the
icons okay
oh m m okay looks like magic to
me woo woo
[Music]
mhm can slow
enemies shoot shoot while
moving
MH
sorceress you were banished by your
power for exper this feels a little bit
too familiar arrogance has led you here
and arrogance keeps you on those Gallows
it's just very fresh in my brain you
know but I could do like I guess I could
go for ice or electricity as it
[Laughter]
seems um foul witch send forth armies of
dead command them to do your bidding
purs see that sounds really fun too
necromancy ends here the end we got
minions and stuff SP of bone grow at
your command and a fast and deadly
Magic oh all so you choose between these
briefings or is it all like you know you
can do them all at once but wouldn't you
normally focus on like for her there's
like different elements here
sorceress you were banished by your aara
for experimenting with the ele wouldn't
you focus on once foul Witch cast you
out for your forbidden Pursuits your
Twisted necromancy ends here at the end
okay when I already heard it once you
don't need to introduce it
again so
extra heard it like too many
times just in case you for thank you I
guess so helpful you usually focus on
one but at the beginning you can contr
uh this looks fun
this with the spikes it looks fun stream
spikes don't know if it's particularly
strong
though this is cool I think I'm going to
go with a witch in any
case
yeah stream spikes and maybe go for
spikes or for this like chaos magic
stuff okay uh she's also pretty hot so
that's that's something we got going for
us
hell
yeah what do I
call
Wawa
wio wit Cho
wio actually it looks kind of cool wio
if you don't know what that's
from if you're not knowingly reading
that TT Al I have the Candi almond still
you want to hear the crunch
I'm going to Crunch into it I'm snacking
a lot because I only had breakfast I'm
sorry
[Music]
M [\h__\h]
yeah names would taken if you
[Music]
so I don't know
I don't
know no
[Music]
[Laughter]
so witberg
doesn't have a good
ring no nobody said Skyward I'm I
started typing those things in
[Music]
what who's that lady with the two hats
again manff or what what is
it that's a
[Music]
Mana probably can't even use
it
um heisen bb heisen bb
but it doesn't fit the character at all
but that's so good wait that's so
good or just like Heisenberg instead of
Heisenberg it doesn't fit the
[Music]
character Walter
witch instead of Walter
why solo cell fun what does that
mean I want to go with
this yo Mr
wit breaking bird ooh ooh
ooh means no training
no
weird ah so for no tring with others so
pure
solo names are unique so don't linger or
what will take you mean somebody will
now one of you guys will now make a
character called Walter witch you really
think that's going to happen I'm going
to go with it wait
what what
why with you little [\h__\h] shits why
would you do that I fought so hard about
this one I F I was so committed now I
why would you take it you little
[\h__\h] don't you have any any mercy and
respect for what I'm going through right
now no I don't like it I don't want it
anyway
I shall me
Heber no everybody else died where did I
go oh
[\h__\h] sasuga sasuga Heisenberg everybody
around me dies I Stay
Alive even with all the [\h__\h] I've
[Music]
done let's go
I will forever now be
[Music]
Heisenberg can't keep getting away with
it should I do a w
ASD in in in the other game I was doing
that
cuz it did end up being more comfortable
I will not join the dead today join the
dead
today I guess so Walter I guess so
unfortunately but you will in 6 months
right at the
latest okay are the first ones you're
alive yeah wounded man what's up are you
one of those junkies huh who like the
blue stuff a little bit too much
huh wait do I see everybody in my
from fart with extra re Reaper wait
what's going
on what is this
chat
oh DND D this player has DND mode
enabled so now people can't write to
me so World chat can I turn World chat
off
too maybe that's where I should put my
head
are we good now oh there's zombies over
there okay let's talk to him I'm glad to
see another living
Soul the mill clearfell about a
strange our men I was fixing to go after
him till that bloody thing got to me
first now all those who drowned in the
flooding suddenly they ain't so dead no
more I would appreciate it if you e oh
oh W wo wo
wo reach
clearfell find the
pillar the dead rise again oh I'm going
to like it here her voice is so
sassy rivered
wand okay left click here to open the
menu
inventory bro are you kidding
me are you kidding
me look at
this bro I'm going to have inventory
problems all too
[Music]
familiar is this like a thing
where they they openly publicly
acknowledge where they took inspiration
from or is there like just like the
monkey thing where you close your eyes
ears and
mouth oh yeah so I can say how obviously
this looks like Diablo
2 I can say
it is Blizzard angry
but don't say
four oh they
are oh oh
[\h__\h] well I I I I for one am currently
also playing Diablo 4 on my uh channel
so I am a neutral
party for now we'll see we'll
see okay oh wait that is still Harry
[Laughter]
Potter prophetic creation oh my God
Heisenberg going off going off with
those
insults she's not having
it
[Music]
Alejandro those are the spells that I
use
po
Amigos
wonderful there's so many
here they look so slimy
large
chest oh uh we get
scepter oh wait no two pops or is it a
dead end down
there okay yes dead end
drowned they're
drowns wait uh
I can carry
both wait whoa whoa whoa what what's
with
these H Grant skill level one skeletal
Warrior M wait wait wait wait the weapon
suddenly gives me warrior
[Music]
minions wait there's a chest here too
n
no the weapon gave me a
skill crazy now we're not alone
anymore can let them do all the dirty
work for
me until they disrespect me then they
shall
die e by
Ryon or self-made bomb I have a lot in
my
repertoire don't
you [\h__\h] around or you will find out
or lily of the
valley that's how it is my brain Rod is
very strong right now I will go right
back to Netflix after the stream is
over and then I will
cry and then I will watch uh better call
all unearth spell wait I got I get a
spell out of the ch best raes
spikes stream
spikes did she just watch Breaking yeah
I'm like right at the finale and then I
had to stop because I need to
[Music]
stream raise SP of BS from the earth in
front of you damaging enemies so so so
so so so so I take it darkness and then
I activ what
o left click the skill to pick it up oh
okay and now left click to bind the
skill wait where does this go I'll take
it and put it
here
okay we now have a skill let's cook
let's get cooking we're
cooking it's on cute Q E RTF oh that's
weird okay wait what
I just found my path to
power she's so sassy oh my
god of course I will watch it of course
I will what kind of question is
that should I gone the other way
first creation spikes how did they know
I wanted spikes
first it's a coincidence right or is it
like when you do when you play witch
then the first school is always
thato find right foot oh it's okay on Q
now for
now oh this also looks like a big area
damn it I wanted to go to a dead end
first oh level up my first taste of true
power you can actually use any skill of
any class oh it's guaranteed
use the spell on
corpses what the
[\h__\h] okay what that's
crazy on Earth I mean that makes sense
with the
name what how many can I have I got rid
of the other U maybe ah did they die or
did they despawn after there certain
amount of
time oh just happened I think some just
dis is it time oh it is it is
time oh there it
goes
cool I should probably look at my skill
points so I I already heard that this is
very oh God God
intimidating
what okay but this is because that's all
classes or what holy [\h__\h] is this
because this is all classes wait oh
no p and is there if this is passive
skills then what's the non-passive
skills the way I put the the unearth
into that other
thing here's a search bar H thank God
but I don't I wouldn't know what to
search
Jesus a star map yeah could or or it
could be honestly I don't know any city
that has a such a complicated subway
map type
summon that's not a skill tree that's a
skill ecos
system it doesn't really do anything
when
I H
what oh I can't look for
it
minion
[Music]
um is how does it
work they're glowing
oh uh-huh uh-huh uh huh
so minions and what about the
spikes should how do I [\h__\h] how do I
know where to
go projectile
evasion BL how do I know which one's
like my area I guess it is kind of like
up here
is Path of Exile more like path of
what the
[\h__\h] too many paths path
of
extreme many
paths more excessive
yeah
wa
wa so I'm guessing I can't skip right I
have to take the first one and then go
to the next ones
right or
not yeah
okay so we're taking this one you guys
also say it's easy to Res skill so it's
good to know what's clear fell what the
[\h__\h] did I just do let me out of here
no what oh that's my quest oh
I have the
Apex killed little scorpions or whatever
that
is
yeah stream
spikes oh little little whatever that is
porcupine crap that's so cute
some animals in this world may
eventually all go in extinct and we not
we won't see them anymore but if that
results in cute things like porcupine
and
crabs then why the hell not sounds like
fun where do I go
does the map tell me where this
is feel like
no wa I just thought I died bro while I
looked away for one second from the
porcupine
crap okay I
heal oh okay
checkpoint very good seems like we're
going in the right direction oh my God
oh the blow of
Miller the Miller I pursue she talks to
him Dodge space bar to avoid the attack
wo I actually tried to dodge to the left
side but
okay I guess
from some point of view now that might
have been to oh that's strong holy [\h__\h]
is this like Diablo but with
um elements
of souls like
games
a ah give me some more oh of those pets
ah need more pets need more ah more pets
ah too late they too too close
still
oh oh
he's
[Music]
getting
okay at least my minions are taking care
of the
minions I shall help to we're almost
done we're almost done we almost got
it
[Music]
oh is that a tutorial boss
wasn't too
bad wasn't too bad first try of course
of course can I wear these oh they even
have they even have unidentified things
and they also have items take up like
different shapes of slots no
[Applause]
way you can't do that
well done please come inside okay I I'm
coming you don't understand what
what it's not the same mhm sure [\h__\h]
gaslighting me how Walter White Gaslight
his wife for her whole [\h__\h] past one
year being Gaslight so hard that at some
point she she
just she just what she
basically like the way she like I don't
know I can't explain it like she was
like [\h__\h] him I need to get get my kids
to safety and then then she's
like I'm going to I'm going to let all
this mental abuse get to me now honestly
like I understand though like she's
she's mentally [\h__\h] up now but I'm
going to I'm going to be on my man's
side now somehow
weirdly
yeah this looks like me
is this another
[Music]
player it must
be
chicken oh what the hell wo stop let me
look at
you only level 15 and you look like Dad
damn son you got all those like oh those
kitty cats are those
from are those holy [\h__\h] are those from
the like extra stuff if you buy the more
expensive wao this one's also
shiny
Cosmetics purchase
Cosmetics yo those cats are
sick yo look at that one go that one has
like Victor at the end of Aran kind of
like things going on
visuals oh don't open shop it shows
spicy stuff to to Bo okay okay but I got
to check it up uh out at some
point oh is this also Cosmetics or is
that natural doesn't look very natural
to
me
wayo I click well at least this looks
different uh what am what am I doing
here what did I activate the Waypoint
if it's cool it's cosmetic yeah that
seems to be the
general
gist no welcome to the camp of the Lost
stranger we survive but we do not
live I am
unaa all this began the night count Gino
took his most loyal men into the
grillwood after he returned a Madness
grew in him I felt that something
happened out
there please I beg of you travel into
the forest and begin your
search there must be some clue as to
what took
place sure I fear this land will only
deepen unless we do
something maybe not cute girl surprised
she lived okay Heisenberg why you
gay seems a little bit gay to me that
comment well okay that's the only like
person I need to talk to in here I
think oh I can walk through here
cool can you turn off the people like so
that I don't see them cuz I feel like
they're breaking my immersion in this
game like look at the these cash job
whales here it's like not very
immersive you can't okay so I let them
continue to flex oh proc of the count of
Oram able-bodied men capable of
excavation must present themselves at
the Mana at once failure to do so will
constitute a
crime only in town
[Music]
okay that's solo cell phone not
available
uhhuh it looked available but okay top
right you can see icons yeah I I know I
see
renley oh yeah wait I was still supposed
to talk to the blacksmith which is you I
suppose sorry name I went to the lady
killed with the violence if what you did
out there in the river banks is any sign
another Refugee from the Count's Justice
I take it but I have no fear this place
is something of a Hideway for many of us
now and we can sorely use your skills in
these dark
times I'll smitth for you what I can if
you're willing to bend your violence
cook for me is what you're
saying well I am the best cook out here
I don't need your
help but I do need a partner I suppose
uh uncut skill
gem what okay I put it here there's a
Bas particular Dark Hour stalking us out
in the FY it moves unseen under the dirt
and attacks without warning we can't
leave the walls to find food and I've
been unable to corner and slay the Beast
myself now if you could Channel your
violence against this Devourer as Finn
calls it we'd be indebted to you okay
you'll give me another uncut support gem
okay oh let's sell oh
pretty oh my God this
job yeah uh I'll sell this I but should
I identify it first I see I see I see
with Scroll of wisdom next time with
Scroll of
wisdom hopefully he survives
all right uh so this looks like heavy
armor but does this matter in matter in
this game can I still should I wear it I
don't know doesn't really look like like
something I would be
wearing this
maybe doesn't look like I wouldn't
necessarily wear it doesn't matter as
long as you can wear
[Music]
it no okay I look like a stupid person
look at my helmet doesn't match the rest
of my outfit at
all yeah but no shield for me wait where
did he go I need to
sell he disappeared can I sell to you
welcome violence if I don't got it by
yourself wonderful you feeling lucky oh
you got one of those sticks
too not
bad use the uncut gem he's a devious one
I I
him oh what are we looking at
here what do I do what is this so what
happened
right active skills I choose from the
top oh we already have unearth thanks to
a
weapon contagion afflicts a single enemy
with a de that de this is the chaos
magic that I saw if the enemy dies will
affected by
[Music]
contas re reanimate
or detonating a corpse affected by
contagion will cause a minion or
explosion to spread contagion I don't
know sounds good select skill to play
video monsters that die while infected
with contagion will spread the infection
to nearby enemies no never mind don't
like it oh no skeletal snipers do high
damage but have low life they can be
commanded to fire an arrow of poison gas
the clouds explode if an ignite effect
or detonating skill is used on
them well at least they help me maybe
I'll get to although SK have skeleton
Warriors right now too right thanks to
much damage that's thanks to the weon
yourself or other minions in your army
right skeletal minions revive
automatically so long as no other
minions have died recently yeah I have
them already from the skeletal Warriors
have high defense but don't do much
damage do I get more
then yeah when I change my weapon which
which I will eventually for sure soon do
already
then could pick fire too
fire
wait
h ah over here stream Sparks and spikes
I could be a spark Spike mage
spark projectiles bounce off W I don't
really like
them this is like too
familiar N I don't know maybe I'll stay
in here let's let's add the
snipers nah N I should have the Warriors
for when I don't have them
anymore you know and now and now I put
them
okay and I guess I could uh increase the
amount of minions by by pressing oh I'm
using I'm using something for that
[Music]
it preserves it
so
okay so now I can only summon one cuz I
I have it on level
one
oops and how do I bring the skill over
here I did the same for that
one yeah just want I maybe I have to
like
accept it
first that's Auto oh
okay okay okay okay well then I
guess I will
[Music]
continue okay well I welcome anything
that's automat
IC
uh am I going to the right place I need
to travel through clearfell to get to
the grawood and I need to search
clearfell to find the mud burrow
entrance to slay the
devour so two things to do here a
beautiful
mother okay now I have three of
them good so it added one
and I still got my
scorpions W my skeletons that makes me
feel like they're also enemies
ooh could wear oh now I look like I'm
out of Elden
ring let's
go oh which direction should I go too
many directions
true
right
yeah have you guys seen the girls are
back in
Japan I miss
[Music]
them I missed
them lady were visiting
me for like 3 days or so which is really
short it originally was going to be a
little bit longer but then with like
flights and their
schedules which is kind
of ended up like that PA
creation yeah that's that's kind of
crazy if you think about it I wouldn't
fly to such a to a place that that's
that's that far away for just three days
if if I only have three days I'll like
travel within Europe but not over
continent those girls kind of crazy but
I hope they felt like it was worth it
they had the greatest time it seems like
they did I got another UNC I have
received reports of a number of villages
hiding at the clear fellure ow can't
read
PDR what the heck V ha what did I ever
do to you or that me from the future
you should make a bigger scorpion for
me short trip but very valuable it seems
like it
[Music]
you
checkpoint oh another one of them she's
definitely s go
inspired and those remind me of
Golems very many little
Golems ooh level up
power yes wake up my
darlings CH
nail I should put that in the spam
folder we got to ignore the chain mail
guys don't answer it don't even open
it very
sus game looks great so far yeah yes yes
indeed no lagginess or so
[Music]
either oh I hear a interesting
voice but my minions are a little bit
distracted we got to go up here come
come come come oh oh that's not who I'm
looking for oh oh
oh my God is there another side twist
for
her oh what was that oh she's Reviving
[Applause]
them oh my god
oh oh can't this she too
strong oh [\h__\h] spikes got ice
[Music]
spikes oh no oh
no oh my God oh my oh my oh my God oh my
God I'm out
here no that's like that's too crazy for
me that's too crazy holy
[\h__\h] oops also drank so many of my
potions when how I get them back oh
she's still she's
still her HP didn't already go back up
maybe maybe I can try again maybe I can
try again before she loads back
[Music]
up thank you for being so
lenient come on help me
guys why is the [\h__\h] map in my face
what did I
press no no no no no no no
no doie doie doie
doie no no no she can
shot you have died yay
bro she's strong but also I still had a
skill point that I could have
used uh spell damage and more minions
damage
yes okay good oh oops it what then oh
the checkpoint was right
[Music]
there wait we put that in here too we we
can add some
snipers should we try again should I try
again 25
16 uh
15 10 but more
Mana I think you can take her equip the
skillers
oh so this is also passive but I need to
add something here no oh wait I won't
get any because I need more
Spirit but maybe get rid of one of those
and get one of the one of those because
I already have Warriors
anyway thanks for the
rain yeah that's kind of crazy early on
so
powerful maybe I can get another level
up somewhere close by but my U my my
thing my exp my next level is still so
far
okay maybe I'll come back I I'll focus
on my quest
first find your red no not yet it it's
not time
yet just not time it you don't
understand it wasn't one HP her well me
too she
was
rough I want
to I want to keep leave a bit strong
first did they respawn or what's going
on where do I need to
go oh yeah that's a lot
of Uncharted Territory here
I need resp oh cuz I died oh yeah that's
Mak a
Dan look at all my pretty scorpions
[Music]
see with this kind of big army okay okay
I'll go in one more
time let's go let's
go spam spam my attacks
more ah
yeah but yeah yeah yeah it's already
looking a lot
better oh yeah oh
yeah W
what what suddenly so much easier just
needed to have have more confidence and
not panic
okay what portal back to town all right
okay good to
know yeah but I don't want to do it now
leave me
alone okay guess I'll do
it um but we got ah head of the winter
wolf grants 10% to cold
resistance cool oh it's a quest item oh
oh orb of
augmentation right click the green thing
for permanent cold
resist oh wait oh oh that's how that
works I thought I had to give it to
somebody whole more like Quest reward
oh Regal
Shard augment a magic item with a new
random modifier ahuh ha similar to
probably what I did in what I've been
doing in De
before I'll go back once and
[Music]
sell oh my God what's that that was kind
of cute the way it was turning in the
circle but it's also kind of [\h__\h] up
as Z
Chima feeling lucky oh wait I need to
identify
[Music]
first only that one
right
hello funky looking
creature I'm not sure what I'm going to
do with it but cheers these ones are
they empty I mean they look empty should
I just sell
this not sure what I'm going to do with
it I can f them at the well
and by killing so I keep this in
here
oh
[Music]
D what do I do with these should I put
them in my chest later one stat at a
time sell the extra
plas these one
what what's
extra stash those for now the little
[Music]
Stones wait where's my
chest stash a
here hey none of it's junk m not
bad okay I guess that's
fine try using the augment or on your
armor but it's fine I like what it
has okay moving
on where do we
go oh chest
wasd the I was running
[Music]
out she ate at class selection what
me what do you mean I ate I did well at
class selection
oh try I'm trying to kill my own
skeletons
again oh oh oh I guess I did eat is that
really what you mean oh
Oh I thought you meant I ate for
whatever reason oh wait the mud burrow
is here and a waypoint is here not good
that I went back down here a little bit
very
[Music]
good ooh The Descent into
Darkness I wouldn't have it any other
way
frean thing you shall also become one of
mine my
minions e e I'm poisoned
ah ew
maggots e e e e
game still reminds me
to take my flasks how
nice I already know how to do it they
don't understand I'm living a risky life
I like
to I like to risk it keep my HP as low
as possible at all
times one year older happy birthday k
YY
oh makes me feel alive I
guess feel like this is not the path to
go further in but I still want to
explore as as always actually never
mind wa wa this one's kind of different
I can't go
there
ah let's keep some distance I'm ranged
after all do not
forget okay okay okay okay what is this
oh
stinky stinky
stinky
haty do I really want to go into the Hat
battery I have a bad feeling oh oh
egg Oh I thought it would oh there we go
spawn at least some
enemies I don't no over
here new
staff volti staff that sounds like yeah
lightning level two lightning bolt
ah right now I'm doing Chaos
ball oh not but this one's for ah for
both wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait now I don't have my minions or at
least
uh some wait should I have at least
um if I unearth something I should have
something right we go sure we can go
with this for a while
it's
two-handed that's
[Music]
fine I I might go back to minions in a
minute oh level
up heisen BB is now level four
[Music]
heisen BP going
strong shouldn't I have one uh arrow
shooting minion
do at
least pretty sure I activated
it no spirit
why let me let
me I
stop Fu I hate all this poison
[\h__\h] your SE ah what's the scepter so
the spirit stuff is on the
[Music]
weapon
okay kind confusing I I'll switch back
cuz it's confusing
me let's put the boots
on squish
squish I like the the lightning attack
though it looked like it was striking
quite quite hard
did you guys like me watching what did
you guys like watching me play uh League
of Legends
yesterday you had
fun yeah me
too me too I had fun
uh but yeah Top Lane was a little bit
lonely I felt pretty
[Music]
lost lost but I think I picked it up
quite well
anyway I tried my best
oh my the the
[Music]
V that's hard to
say have a feeling B also has issues
saying that name
ow oh he he he's digging a lot digging
and
Diving no don't go
back the side
commit
ah Poison
Poison the tail woo
one of us one of us
[Music]
ah come
on come on come on where are you
oh oh no no no no
[Applause]
bro oh my god
oh leave me alone leave me
alone Sur I can handle
this oh finally
reviv taking all those long coffee
breaks come on
busy reading that book huh on the
toilet that's one book big mistake
Walter White big
mistake how could you miss that I'll
[\h__\h] stop whipping
me I need minions have
going do something
still something
guys is it is my thing my FL going to
load up again or
what oh it's loading
up die
I feel like I'm like having troubl
catching up like he makes
minions
[\h__\h]
ah but his minions kill my minions I try
to kill more of his minions to make more
of my minions but I'm slow with it no no
no okay let's just try to focus on him
then at least on my
side I don't know it might still it
might be too late at this point
one HP in the
dream where is he oh my my HP looking so
good no
no no
almost almost not
the the tail the tail the [\h__\h]
tail what do I shoot
here oh my God look at all these e
disgusting emge
I
one the maggot still stay alive okay
then let me clean up
oh oh I really thought I was going to
die I struggled through
it Mama Mia
oh God even I died in this fight hell
yeah W first
try rough not not a good try but you
know that looks like some decent
armor a decent bow but not for
me m 14 maximum life 8 to fire
resistance better than what I have but I
need to be level five for it and then
requires 10 strength oh okay that's
something I don't have I guess cuz it's
red any winning try is a good try you're
so nice you're so
positive oh yeah there're they're blue I
guess
[Music]
yeah okay wait I got 11 of these
what
11 did that just say 11 so I can have 11
skills level
oh level two
[Music]
okay which means that I can turn one of
these into level
two or jump right onto level two from
this one
but this is like connected to my weapon
or
what to the one weapon I'm wearing or no
not really right the other no the other
the other menu that I was looking at was
connected to my
[Music]
menu H to my to my weapon I'm confused
uh I don't know I
guess if I upgrade this it becomes more
damage and more bone
constructs cone length ah it's bigger
maybe and then it stays longer that
sounds good just try contag of f
skill
okay and then put it
here okay I'll put it up
here I'll put I'll put
the oops see I'll put under Earth over
here just going go how do I how do I
remove
this
there
okay all right we have one over
here uh more minion
life or more damage damage damage uh
maybe I'll give them a bit more life
they they're they're like really squishy
oh you want damage well too
bad too bad too
bad too late and too
bad always more damage well can't make
damage when you're dead all the time can
you oh you should have me
so basically am I not already done in
this little
[Music]
dungeon let me
[Applause]
through got something in
here port to town yeah but I also I I
mean I want to I just want to go out of
the dungeon because I still have
something to do here
I still have the travel for Clear fell
to the grawood
thing can I take the how do I take the
wayo to go
outside Oh you mean teleport to town and
then Waypoint to outside oh well I'm
already
here okay uh where is this other thing
to the gril wood did I already see the
gril
wood okay I'll use it fine
this thing is Reviving
[Music]
them oh there it is so
close so close oh this looks kind of
pretty entering the
grelwood the grillwood has turned foul I
think I prefer it this way
Ed wait
what is that just telling me to give my
quest back when that thing pops up down
there like hey your quest is done you
should go
back
yeah there ooh witches were dancing
around the table Once Upon A
timef I'm also witch and I'm also
dancing around right
[Music]
now bro what the [\h__\h] is it with these
werewolves die
already okay time to go back
for a
[Music]
moment hey take a pun you know you still
need take so much space
bro how do I get more strength just by
leveling up or can you put any points
into like strength and Agility and stuff
like that
yeah sure I'll take it off your
[Music]
hands uh on gear or by leveling
up passive skill tree
okay de I want to wear these things but
I'm waiting for level five and I'm
waiting for level uh for 10 strength
H might take a
while remember us when you're famous
he mate should have some strength stash
him yeah but now I guess I'll stash it
so it's not in the
way but level five is
soon I'll keep the boots with me
strength seems like it's still more
further
away what am I looking for here
something evil I
suppose
purify I don't like these werewolves at
all
so fast and so
clingy does the
contagion only make him sick or does it
also do some damage
upon thing I can't remember
[Applause]
damage overtime okay ooh there's a
Hut and a
checkpoint oh wait are you enemy sister
what the [\h__\h] in the room
curious oh shoot if I wasn't playing a
witch and I guess the comment here would
be different
what the [\h__\h] what what what what what
what what what are these PS to are
following me
freaky where is
she where is
she
disappear oh there
ah
hello made me you actually are riding in
my chat for
once have you been playing this game yet
we planning to play
it I just
started carried too long dear sister
[Music]
will you play it will you play
it
C that's a gold thank you maybe question
mark So I switch this
out does it
matter oh this is for life oh but I need
to fill
it oh well now they're both empty
great guess I could go back to the city
to fill it
is this
what no Quest is still unfulfilled so I
guess that was not what I needed to
do I got this
thing oh another new
looking thing
[Music]
menu what are these like passives
no support projectile
skills pick one for the skill you like
these are ones you equip to your
gems support your main skill
G modifi to my
[Music]
skills she didn't answer did she no she
has she didn't answer I haven't but I've
been watching you play looks fun you
should give it a try
too there's no Q
anymore at least that's something
supports any skill that hits enemies
giving a chance that uh to rer enemies
on hit what does that really mean
[Music]
wither pierc an
enemy I don't know which one to pick
they all seem
like
[Music]
fine
oh 5% increased chaos damage taken and
can be inflicted upon 10
times
okay oh wait okay now I understand h
and let's go to unearth supports any
skill that deals damage boosting its
physical damage at the expense of all
other damage types what more more damage
yeah support skills remove 100% of your
maximum life from a nearby minion on use
to deal 40% more
damage
what more duration okay that one's easy
remove
[Music]
Max brutality how about
that okay now it's in here
[Music]
n portals are free right right I can
come and go as I
[Music]
like I want to load up my
potions wow fancy
Shield
wow 29 19
okay I'll keep the current
chat feeling
lucky not bad oh I learned the new
skills
cprl makes the selling
faster wonderful damn that looks so
good but I don't need it later lat
off okay here we go
oh it does consume a scroll oh does it
consume a the same scroll that I used
for
identifying oh yeah I could have turned
in my quest
huh oops I'm still committed to this
other Quest
here still want to finish that one but I
don't know where to go
we need to find the evidence of the
counts
activities
Oh used to consume a
scroll oh it is free okay good good good
good good that's what I like to
hear bro bro what's this EP
G bro
okay nothing
special
a my senses are dling me up here oh new
enemies
joining the game so far yeah I think so
I mean the beginning of these kind of
games is always a bit rough when there's
so much
overwhelming
stuff and I have yet to feel anything of
the story really
but seems like it's a slow beginning in
terms of story and
[Music]
lore so I will will hold off on my
judgments
still am I going the right way there
were so many
paths my
knowled yeah we'll see if I laugh at
someone dying in this game oh I leveled
up new shoes oh
but no no no no no no scroll of wisdom I
take uh
Dam will you play with geky be KY if
they ask yeah if they ask but it's
complicated cuz it would be so many time
zones
CU then for somebody it will be like 456
a.m. or
so
and I'm not
really generally for like a long ongoing
collab I'd like to avoid that if it's
like a one time thing
cool purify
but for now I'm fine playing alone also
because I don't really know yet how
committed I want to be to this
game we'll see we'll
[Music]
[Applause]
see people that don't say don't time
zone yeah they did play at a different
like weird time slot or like my prime
time time slot yesterday but that's only
because that was when the game released
and they wanted to play it when right
when it released I don't know if they
they would always be so happily willing
to do that oh my God is that is that is
that what I'm looking
for nah no leave me alone if this is not
for the quest then leave me
alone
no
no what the heck is
that that's just a guy Wonder
fall there's so many random big bosses
huh this look kind of cool though I like
the arena that we're fighting in it
gives me no way to
escape emerg nothing emerges there we go
just keep on running in circles keep on
running in circles
ow ow that hit hard for
once my my Archer skeleton is
G nobody's even paying attention to him
which is I guess good
don't aggro don't hold the
aggro keep the aggro on me keep on dot
dot dot St taking damage uhoh that's not
I should not have done that not have
leted the attack to you sorry but he's
still standing strong y
oh I hope he's doing fine I am barely
getting
hit oh he's gone he will come
back here dots dot dots my
dots and oh he's going down he's going
down
wa there we go wow you look at that
wooho wa
[Music]
yippee I'll just upgrade
this yeah
and we continue walking our Path of
Exile I mean how are already committ
committed to this path I guess I could
also go up here but
no okay I'll go
here we'll take a while longer until I
reach up
higher ooh raw
destruction okay now where is my real
goal where what am I what am I looking
for where is it am I like completely off
is this the map though by the way like
what's the map how do I look at the big
map it's not M apparently
you for
map that's
crazy that's
crazy oh that's not really what I was
thinking
of it shows the monsters that I bought
already yeah this is not helpful I want
to look at this kind of map but in
bigger oh ah
yeah even bigger maybe like a full view
okay it cuts up here guess I'll check
the left
side maybe it's not that far north
actually oh what the [\h__\h] well well who
is this that adorns the Tree of Souls
oh wait that that's what I needed summon
[Music]
Uno what happened here I am the
aent wait one second let me clear the
[Applause]
werewolf I'm so weak
still this
shade is it still alive no probably not
perhaps it can give us the answers we
seek or it is sword has the power to
bind souls to the tree like this we must
free it somehow I wouldn't to release
that being from the Tree of Souls will
need more than simply cutting his rope
the ancient Grooms that imbue the
Count's blade created The Binding and
only ancient runes can break it there is
a battlefield not far from here that
runs red with rust where the weapons and
armor of countless asites still remain
we call it the red Veil you should
search the area there may still be power
in some of those centuries old relics
okay renley will know how to forge them
bring the runes to him and then perhaps
we shall find some answers
H I'll wait here the old Magics will
protect me okay good luck with that kind
of naive but
[Laughter]
okay uh so
this little side quest is quite big but
it also involves
renley find the entrance to the red Veil
there the red Veil for obelisks of rest
which contain Runes of power
H Runes of power instead of rings of
power
oh Runes of
power Reon two out now
I guess I'll teleport back again and
just give back the quest maybe at
least the one
Quest
or probably would be
[Music]
smart nothing
here yeah my skeletons they die so fast
that's why I wanted to give them some
help I have
the I'll continue looking for that
entrance
back paddling skills Heisenberg's back
paddling skills I don't know it I don't
I wouldn't say that they're good I would
say he's not good at back paddling he's
really good
at Deep
digging oh the Grim triangle that's
something else the Grim tangle not the
Grim
triangle that's not where I would need
to go
down doubling yeah also also his special
key and of
course gas light girl keep gatekeeping
what no gas girl girl boss
gatekeeping
and uh
[\h__\h]
H let me try again gas light girl boss
gatekeeping there you go there you go
got oh
medium now that one looks the same
size I got another one of
these h
supports any skill with an area effect
making a
larger 40%
duration and more damage over
time and less
duration of supported skills of damaging
elements less duration but more
damage all right I'll take it
[Music]
actually feel like I'm really not going
where I
should
[Applause]
infection
infection she's cute of the random
things she
says thanks for the 20 MERS ships yo
that's
[Music]
big okay I'm kind of circling my way
back oh
this the red Veil I found
it oo my instincts actually
are always
good so far blood bones and
death in abundance
oh look what we have
here in the red Veil I'm looking for
obelisks and
rust wait I see rust with arms is that
what you mean
oh God that's a lot of Enemy
yooo No it's probably not what they
mean you're looking for f i uh uh uh me
I know I know I know I know I know
let me go down
[Music]
here e what is that that just looks
like the JJ on four legs I'm sorry to
say I need to share my feelings with
you let me it
on you fought the same thing okay good
good then we have an
[Applause]
agreement yeah looking tight in my
inventory belt a Bel the
first ah ah God damn it my minion don't
do [\h__\h] can't even look at my inventory
for a moment in
peace all right chill everybody chill uh
no space
uh well I guess I'll be tele repor
in but I will wear it
at I think I need to buy some of those
Scrolls hope they're not too
expensive use your uncut support gem on
your minions my next one yeah what is
this iron
Rune Place into an empty Rune socket aha
I don't have one yet I think it would go
in like my
[Music]
armor yes you feeling
lucky uh I would like to buy a Scrolls
guys okay well rley rley let's give him
his quest oh finally took down the
Devourer you what incredible this is the
first real success on your ti to we can
breathe a bit easier now this won't
cover our debt to you thank you oh
support J okay
uh anything take your
fancy damn he sells no
Scrolls
why that will be
useful oh I need more dexterity for that
one
[\h__\h] whatever that will be
useful oh is that bigger no medium
lesser
unidentified should I identify this
before
selling might make good strap
I'll just sell
it you didn't take the gem from
him oh what the heck oh I thought
okay uh let's skip something to my
Warriors last guess uh minions from
supported skills Die 4 seconds after
their life is reduced to zero oh
cool Minions from supported skills deal
35% less damage but they have 50% more
maximum
life can't can't use it the Pearly
though uh explode when reduced to low
life dealing 15% of their maximum life
as we'll have a lot of explosions with
that cuz they're like dying so
fast uncheck show
recommended oh but I want I I'd prefer
to see only recommended I think this too
much like
what this populate oh my God yeah don't
don't tell me to do that n we don't need
that maybe if I'm a pro and I'm more
familiar with the
game um minion instability or the last
maybe the last gas nah I don't
know let's do let's do
explosions we can make him stronger one
way or another maybe in the
future for now they'll just do more
collateral damage then and you are you
not going to give me a new are these
side quests or questions just a shame
what happened to he tried to yeah okay
okay anybody who
sells the Scrolls what the
heck it's only Finn and renley right
maybe una hello these are just some odds
and ends of mine oh there we
go wait 25 gold for one it better be
worth this hopefully worth more how can
I help take a
look no wasn't
worth
damn wasn't worth till next time
well maybe later on it will even out
what else we have I've collected these
over time M what do you think what do
you think
oh she's
so I don't know goodbye soft
gentle well spoken what a lady look at
her
scepter yes these are just some odds and
ends of mine they are
a bit expensive but okay well so we have
a a rattling scepter with 100 spirits
and it gives me skeleton Warrior
minion uhhuh this gives me better oh
that that actually sounds good it gives
me an improved Warrior minion with also
more maximum
life this is too high level and this
more Warrior
minion level and allies and New
presentence Deal one to four additional
attack physical
damage and plus one to level of all
Minion skills
H apparently this one is better in terms
of level and
price that's really good it's the best
that's better than anything I've seen
huh plus one is really that good oh okay
I guess I'll buy it that one spoke to me
as well that's a lot of money
though not much money return turning
from this
one
okay goodbye bye how are you in two
places at once un explain that to
me so what what's the main
quest if he didn't give me a followup is
is the quest I took from una also a main
quest
thank you I played top very well thank
you I think I also didn't do that badly
mhm All Things Considered getting thrown
into cold water being in the alone
Lane the one time I did badly was
because I suddenly was in a different
Lane with real people for the first time
oh hey look at that
perhaps this is what we
need what the happening what's happening
what's
happening oh oh level up What's happen
happening I have it under
control woo impudent Undead
yeah yeah so is smurfing I learned that
word is smurfing when somebody who
actually is really experienced in the
game makes a lowlevel account to play
with lowl players even though he doesn't
belong there oh yeah I got smurfed there
my first time playing against real
people also in a in a lane that I wasn't
used
to oh what the heck already full
yeah and already I'm like getting
smurfed that's not the kind of Smurfs
that I'm used
to what the
heck way too common why do they do that
though why don't they just play with
people it's like it's like when you pick
when you pick a fight with people that
are like race smaller than
you or way younger than
you that's how is that fun to them
though how is it
fun cuz they hate
losing how does it makes no sense how is
it fun cuz we ended up just surrendering
what's the point
[Music]
they must feel so
cool
uh wait so is that all she needs no two
more my
inventory my
inventory if they really have to you
know make a strongly inspired game why
do they have to keep this inventory
can they un Inspire themselves when it
comes to that please thank
you I would certainly prefer it
it God them
inventory change it make my inventory
bigger or else
okay Spirits in a tree R feeling lucky
why are you chitchatting to me I'm just
here to sell some stuff
de all of these don't even need to be uh
identified except for no this one
neither
okay
okay fwell fine with
me perhaps
this is what we
need no time to waste
checkpoint where is the
other run of power
oh I already had that way
point uh over
there you hold two chapters you can
summon another
Archer oh I see H it's all right
need to limit my
power damn it so this up here maybe but
ah also down here I still have more path
to
go h
so how long ago was C of xile one I
never heard of this game series before I
think 10
years
13 took them a while
H that
voice he sounds like fun is it still
active was it also
online
one most successful beep clone n
[Applause]
yeah I mean I see
why I can tell
why ooo hiding in the woods
it's free oh
really n TI of the slaughter yet
teleporting is free junk so why not go
and make some
money that's the other one okay
[Music]
go go yeah sure I'll take it off your
end
mhm I'll wear
it oh wait those are identified okay
never mind ah they take a pun you know
you want yeah sure I'll take it off your
hands go make a legend or
two okay uh wait should I leave anything
else Iron
Room
yeah I'll put it
away perhaps oh membership thank
you oh they're still fighting
[Music]
here
uh great I'm already out of
these identifiers
again but is it at least better than
what I
have
Shi yeah
mhhm
okay I wonder if this connects it
probably does death and Decay
[Music]
map save your Scrolls for your own
weapons uh you mean don't scroll don't
identifi those items at all just sell
them un
unidentified unless it's something that
I might want to
use
okay for now at
least in this economy I guess I'm I need
to save the money and the Scrolls I see
[Music]
look at my little army never mind it's
disappearing
already frog
oh all
these I won't say it I won't say
it I need to be say
so ah today was man Senai concert did
you watch it
guys like
online I was sleep me too
true but it looks amazing from the
Snippets that I
saw so she did get that nun outfit in
freedy huh I had a
feeling I was wondering does cie also
get another outfit with her coming 3D
life cuz normally means get 3D life get
outfit in
3D and if yes like normally it's the
outfit that is on the
promotional graphic
I
wonder is she going to get that in
[Applause]
3 B confirmed it's the art well what do
you mean the art she confirmed it's the
art that is being turned into fry or
what you would know more than us no I
didn't ask I wanted to ask
though she made the 3.0 3D for the
concert but she wants a
new
oh uh-huh yeah but the the the
3.0 she used the 1 million wish for that
right
so that's kind
of
separate from the deal that you
get a new outfit with a concert IRL
concert where is the last
one feel like I looked at every corner
now how do
I oops how do I look at the top
part ah maybe up
here oh I hear it I think I hear it oh
there it is there's the third God damn
it it the
nuts oh what's going
on what the
heck R king previously it was just like
a Spam of enemies and now oh oh I I saw
that one coming good that I stood aside
ouch oh W
the oh oh oh okay well at least I can
turn those into minions if I kill
them if I kill
them woo
W that was
close
the more more oh no wo level
up
hey very loud and very no take those
with you take them to you grave with you
would be lonely without them no no no
she answered
me God damn it no space okay let's use
this o we got the second
roll okra or fried green tomatoes Fried
Green Tomatoes is that an Atlanta thing
o okra I think I had that in Japan
before I didn't like
it um can drop the white loot or I
teleport and sell it and then come
[Music]
back yeah the slimy stuff right the
fried green tomatoes that sounds good to
me I like tomatoes and I like fried
stuff and green tomatoes are fine too
I'm sure yet take a pun you know you
want
to m
H not
bad let's identify the
staff uh the staff is too handy hands
though right
Firebolt you feeling lucky not sure what
I'm going to do with it but Cheers
Cheers Cheers my
friend
wa wa this one's
golden I need to I need more of those
stupid ah
yes identification thingies I've
collected these over time would be cool
if she also had like a button like
identify everything in
inventory I think that was a thing in
Diablo
[Music]
too okay that was not worth it these are
just some odds and ends of my
[Music]
uhhuh uhhuh
uhhuh I will treasure it I'm I'm making
money wao 16 to
armor increased BL man of recovery rate
strength fire resistance lightning
resistance for damage cool cool cool
cool
cool awesome beautiful
okay and I'm going to put
[Music]
these let's see summons bomb throwing
Reviving skeletal arsonist that can
detonate other Minions on command w c is
all Targets in an area after a short
delay making them deal less damage
raises a ring of bone spikes around you
I like but around
me PS are destroyed when enemies touch
them damaging and pitting those enemies
fire is a projectile that applies a
powerful chaos damage over time
debuff essent strain is a projectile
that deals
C enemies hit by bone cage will be
pinned if they are no skeletal
arsonist INF feeble is a curse that
weakens enemies H what would you do
maybe spikes maybe bone
cage and I get I get another one though
[Music]
okay but don't I need more of these uh
Spirits I can't add another
one how get
[Music]
more so now we have 160% increased spell
damage minions deal 60% increased damage
and more intelligent intelligence
nice you get more spirit I would hope
so place your wand with another
scepter maybe if I get another receptor
like as a
drop oh yeah I need to put the hot key
this is what we need wa how do I open
that menu again
no
[Music]
ah pressing
buttons
g g
g okay bone
cage and these are just passive right
they happen on their
own
so okay now we're done
here we've done enough haven't
we oh B what is this topest charm that I
almost almost left
here whoa it goes in
here what does it do used when you take
lightning damage from a
hit
oh okay used automatically when
condition this med Can Only Hold charges
while in belt refill a dwells or by
killing
monsters so if I'm
hit by lightning
damage then I get 25% lightning
resistance
what
okay temporarily I guess but it doesn't
say how
[Music]
long sure why not
actually can I really not do
more here I can do another one
[Music]
here 40
seconds okay that's overall kind of lame
me getting hit first for that to
activate and then it's only for 4
seconds and then you have to recharge it
n okay
clear F
encampment too
rly for forging your wings look like
parrot Wings did you rip them out of a
parrot you little [\h__\h] just to flex f a
spikes but I would ask
what
take stick to the cars m
tired of the slaughter who knows what
price sure I'll take it off your
hands oh this one has a slot but it
requires 10 dexterity which I don't
have sure I'll take it off your hands
should I do remember us when you're
famous
eh save them
okay well at least here there's plenty
of
space
[Music]
Oh
okay uh even though una is here we'll
talk to her in a different
dimension plenty for now plenty of space
she says oh is what we need oh I see how
it is wait maybe I should have used a
waypoint
I'm like really
far
right is it better to go
here and
then wait how do I
teleport
[Music]
to oh
here oh right where I wanted to go
una what happened you have
let okay she said stab them stay safe if
you can like this bam good stream spikes
do as I command release this shade to my
stream spikes
emerge oh there's so many B I only
noticed the one body when I came here
first didn't realize there's so many and
of course they come to life ah don't
they oh oh oh oh
no speak to renley what is she doing
he's unconscious but he's breathing
though this
wound we should take him back to clear
he may be the only one who knows what
truly happened don't take a a spooky
person to clear fell are you crazy stay
safe can she's looking for trouble this
is the kind of woman that if you pick
her up she's just
trouble is that kind of
woman
H yep yeah yeah you know you know how it
is the wound only by a Count's hand can
this binding be released where is she I
know an old Tale one speaks of a ring we
might be able to recover buried three
centuries ago in our ancient graveyard
the Grim tangle the over is this also
main
quest stay safe I don't know how they
quest this is like gold so maybe that is
the main quest I heard you head him for
the village okay when I fled for my life
there was no time for me to grab all my
smithing tools if you do manage to reach
my Forge you should find them and bring
them here I'll set up a bench and we can
see about working on your equipment
uhhuh
okay Oham Village
maybe that's where I'm heading
anyway stick to the
cars I'm
eating I'm eating
roasted um sugared candied almonds from
the Christmas
Market that I had left
over R got really like
these she gets it
M okay we turn the entrance uh to the
Grim
tangle okay wait that's no that's
somewhere else perhaps this is what we
need
no that is
[Music]
wrong yeah that's what me and [\h__\h] were
talking about when she asked me in
German what I
like to buy at Christmas
Market I said I always
get the
almonds
always return to the
entrance oops oopsie the entrance
where was the
entrance to the Grim tank Grim t wait
the Grim tangle I already kind of saw
that
somewhere but this map is
uncovered I will beast on your
soul this is somewhere North upright
roughly thank you thank you thank you
you're
helpful good
chicken good chicken who's a good
chicken
you I
[Music]
also usually get children's
punch I usually get children's punch cuz
I don't drink
alcohol so the almonds and one of the
children's punches
and
recently I went to one that had um
marle with uh the breadcrumb stuff
M
here no way wa where am I supposed to
go no apricot uh dumplings basically oh
was I supposed to come here wait I
already fought
you wait did that just made her
disappear
no I'm not trying to fight you when I
was here before it looks like I never
discovered the map what's going
on does the map just uncover
itself or or
recover the map's
reset wait that's [\h__\h]
up that's [\h__\h]
up that's not good
me not likeing this
system no no no never heard before of a
game that does
that what Dia did that
really maybe like this backtracking is
kind of unusual I I don't think I
did I mean I didn't play Diablo 2 for
very long but I didn't do much back
working in Diablo I so maybe that's why
I didn't realize also I don't know
anymore I tried going that direction but
I didn't find it
there so I guess we'll have to check out
the whole map
again
yippee what about this ah there it
is the Grim
tangle guess I'll go in here
single player to there you go yeah I
mean I don't remember that
anyway the roots here have a mind of
their own oh I'll need to convince them
to part for me oh like Jesus if the FI
Spirits are still watching I believe
they will help us
[Music]
please oo pretty the old magic still the
oh sorry I'm not very well read on the
Bible or anything I guess for that
matter you
know the joke of me not reading things a
bit
annoying just because yesterday I played
another like type of like genre game
from that genre
people like she doesn't read she doesn't
read but bro
bro yeah I didn't read any uh 10 page
manual cuz I wasn't evening sense
one
about strategies and stuff but the
skills I was aware of what the skills
were
doing fers fers
well it wasn't necessary to read too
deeply into them they were prised very
kindly to people like me about the
manual thing was I'm not sure apparently
there's really a manual that they looked
at I don't know the details though
haven't seen it
I did watch a video I looked up like
beginner's guide I mean all of this was
very spontaneous I decided to join one
hour
before the collab before my stream
started and I looked up a video like
beginner's guide for Vi but the problem
was that it while it was a beginner's
guide for V it did uh require prior
knowledge about the game The General
like it used a lot of terms that I had
no idea what it was so it was beginner's
guide for Vi in case you already have a
lot of experience in the
game beginner guide for
Pros in case you're just like switching
your main or
something so I listened to the video and
I did not really
understand yeah I need a beginner's
beginnner gu a beginner's guide for
beginners not a beginner's guide for
froze this Druid has seen better days
what do you mean he looks fine
me oh wait I forgot about my new
skill what just
happened [\h__\h]
he let me let me attack
you
infection if I leave that Circle oh wow
it it still would take effect right when
he walks
into oh my God he
down go Warriors go Warriors of the bat
I'm guessing I should not
necessarily step into the
middle it disappears on its own
anyway ah
a wa I suddenly teleported into
it that move killed me too the first
time IG Stone there wow up up no what
what does it do what it
doy oh there we go okay
okay it was
manageable after
all
H which one should I
identify which one of these oh this one
this one or that one I
guess 25 45 maybe that
one oh um
could no I mean could could where what
do you
think thank
you yeah with my eyes
closed thank you thank you thank you
bless you
too should I wear it is it better I mean
f 54 armor yeah
I like like
this that's
better
gu
[Music]
h h
this shall go into one of
these
um maybe in here but I don't know will I
use it a lot I already forgot like right
away about its
existence
uh
uh these to are
different so wait is this one just the
one from my
weapon and this is the one from my
skill how do I know which one's
which
confusing indeed confusing
you can freely swap the support gems Z
around afterwards
mhmh okay then
uh energy Shield recharge begins IM and
is not interrupted by damage for two
seconds when stunned
while okay
what cost multiplier
[Music]
12% inflict bleeding hell yeah
exalted
orb left click a rare item to apply okay
no no no no
no
ha
mhm what the girl's favorite part of the
visits oh I don't know maybe they'll
tell us when they are
here uh when we have collab sorry brain
empty when we have collab with
them it will be on Tuesday Tuesday in
it wait un why did you guys spot switch
spots by Finn was here before now he
moved over here cuz he doesn't want to
be too close to you or what no because
you're taking up so much space with that
creepy ass guy the ring not the ring
bearer the the W the ring W I've collect
get out of here you insan
my collection me lady thank
you me
Lady
Think toxic lady stay safe if you
can she's
trouble
okay uh continue through the Grim
tangle sounds like km Tander
why is it
so what this light that I'm
seeing feels like it'll ran away from
[Music]
me
curious this light
[Applause]
[Music]
well my minions are definitely more
self-efficient now and more
helpful have to give them that credit
guess I'll go up
here you're not going
anywhere now they're doing their
work
right where are we damn I already walked
so much for this
thing but I reached the dead end let's
check out these connections
here
M
oh
nothing nothing
nothing wow so many enemies
suddenly and it's really hard to
teleport M from there the the real
enemy is it just
me like for anybody who played uh the
same
class having the same
issues
key it's for me too thank God it's
normal turn on enemy name plates a yeah
that might might be helpful
I mean you know I know that mine are
like glowing green and all
that my God I don't want to die on these
little little
bastards they're an HP bars oh HP bars
for them might be
good yeah 40 80 let's go
baby uh
HP
[Music]
interface hell
yeah show Al
names game
play show Monster resistance show mini
life bar above you ooh go above
enemies
[Music]
nice h ah
save you should have
me okay uh oh I guess it only shows the
ones that I started attacking already
that already took some
damage this is this helps this helps
this
helps
that's
[Music]
go big big
[Applause]
big quality of life
Improvement I like it oops what am I
doing
did I go the right way cuz there was
another path that looked quite
[Music]
enticing oh what is this Cemetery of the
eternals that's not really where it said
I should go but that sounds very
fancy I think it would say I have to
look for that if that's where I had to
go
right about Coca-Cola I'm so tired
good night if you're going to bed good
night thanks for going strong it is the
correct
path but what about the other path what
about the other path is that the Path of
Exile perhaps should I not go is it too
dangerous like this one that on
here hard to see
you that the thing roll the credits roll
the
credits okay no I'm glad this is giving
me a feeling of conclusion and closure
the fact now I know that there's there's
there that that one's a dead end I'm
happy on this
path
sorry slightly not amused here
another uncut support
gem did I already put one into no I
didn't how about ignition I already have
a feeling that's exactly what I
need ignition sounds
nice okay you agree
wonderful well this is just a white item
so whatever
poison resistance would be nice here and
level up I'm level eight
now oo okay so we could go like oh
attribute as in like for example
strength could go in so many
[Music]
directions but probably up right is the
usual recommend holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
oopsie holy [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] like what what
the the [\h__\h] is
this seek the end
point splits hard to
say hard to say really this is like icy
stuff
this is like fire and death not Fire and
Life uh
curses
electricity I don't [\h__\h]
know grip of evil that sounds fancy oh
minions who is supposed to like have an
over oversight over like overview of
where the [\h__\h] to
go
HST this is like you got to
think 152 steps
ahead up there you want me to go there
sure it's just a long way to go you know
Lord of Horrors oo
huhuh I feel like maybe maybe it's fun
to just like not look at what's really
far ahead and just look at the very
close ones you know look at it as a
really small tree and just like gotcha
let it lead you where it wants where you
know like destiny
Destiny
yeah yeah what do you think about
that just follow whatever
path the path of
Destiny Path of Exile is like looking at
this and thinking too much about
it in my opinion but yeah so wait sorry
answer to this is like uh
ah yeah and the answer received
H I don't
know no I'll go up whatever I don't need
it up up up
up
ah does it fit it does okay going back
[Music]
do I want to
identify what's
this kind of
weapon I got some staffs but we're not
really using Stu so I guess I'll just
sell everything without
identifying hello I like like to hold on
to bits and pie oh I like this
one yeah one drops
double first time build build usually
always requires
respect what the
heck is that coming out of your front or
your back I guess front what the wait ah
those are hands I didn't realize it at
first
e e you look disgusting you look
disgusting he you look disgusting
mate Mighty
disgusting where was where was I where
was I supposed to go I forgot the path
on you I'm walking
backwards he way
right disg
disgusting oh shit's
wrong oh yeah up there
Cemetery please wow I say I'm disgusting
Moonlight you are
disgusting and that's a fact
oh quickly my family has been
abducted I've heard that name
before
[Music]
where what the
f oh my oh my oh my God
I know I didn't have to go down here and
just talk to them to see
instead but you know get that bastard
Tyrant prer traven he's taking my family
hostage they're being held somewhere
beyond these Gates I never thought he
would stoop this
low I sent for
reinforcements but it's been so long
I must get through the gate the keys
where are the Blasted
keys I I believe those cowards took
them his Acoustics I don't take orders
didn't fit his environment you love
cemeteries but okay open the
[Applause]
gates okay I guess I need the keys for
that search the cemetery of the eternals
for the tomb of the consort and the
mousum search for the counts grave past
the memorial gate is that the memorial
gate up
there I'll just run around and we'll see
what
happens nothing in the chest
really
wa wraps let's
go guys very loud what's going on right
it was
noisy trying to
say a lot of words in a very loud volume
purify calm
down he was very
passionate I didn't laugh at
him just questions his
Acoustics I would never laugh at someone
in
distress after
all you know me kfp you know
me I love seeing whole lives play pee to
Y I wonder were there any Japanese
members playing it yet
I only saw people
in I'm sure someone like shisho votan
would love
it this ban would enjoy or maybe could
it too cuz she played Diablo very
empathetically
empathetically yeah
oh look at that the tomb of concert I
almost walked away from
it crony oh yeah crony 2o she also
played uh Diablo with me before in a
collab Diablo 2 uh resurrected though we
played Diablo 2
resurrected
together see crony like if I had a group
with like only my time zone and then
maybe like na time zone I think that's
would
work we played the
before but I don't know it's generally
like ah I don't know always trying to
figure out when to play
together if she wants someone
to play it with if you hear such words
coming out of her
mouth and you're in her stream chat by
any chance then let her know Wawa offers
her
Services she did say a while ago that
you know she wants to collab and then
she'll hit me up with a collab idea and
since hasn't followed up so
back in New
York she may have made such a
statement No you don't need to tell her
D I think she's aware I mean maybe
forgot
but why is this so
strong he stuck
you are weirdly
strong oppose me mini
boss rare enemy a rare enemy is doesn't
always show
up cofins
oh they're all so easy easily
killed this one's kind of cool H
Wings the color of the name shows the
Rarity yeah I noticed it was something
special but when you say rare are you
saying that it doesn't always show
up oh yeah she's sick again who knows
maybe she would be playing Poe now if
she wasn't s
probably remembers every now and then it
feels too awkward and guilty to bring it
up nah there's no reason to feel guilty
or awkward about
that I don't know sometimes you just
don't really have a inspiration of what
kind of game to invite someone someone
to collab with
four does that make sense is that
grammatically correct collab with four
sometimes you don't have an
idea of what to collab with for I don't
know man whatever you know what I mean
I like this dungeons
[Music]
design
cool that it's the
blackish
stones with all the Engravings and the
different sizes and
patterns and then the the fire makes
stuff look kind of golden
to
my weirdly speaking to
[Music]
me where the [\h__\h] do I
go I can
create So
Random uh I can do it's
better okay okay sure you
can feel like I have to go up but I'm
going down on
purpose surely will bring me more
experience W there we go
y oh wait this one's also kind of strong
oh I just realized oh
oh
don't I got stuck the [\h__\h] hers or
something made me get stuck where the No
No at the
beginning wait does that reset my level
up no right I I I'm at the beginning of
a level so I'm assuming oh does that
reset the items I picked up so far no
right Al just like everything the same
you just get reset in terms of like
where you are
the enemies seem dead
also this part was undiscovered so I'll
go check it
out oh way a checkpoint what the heck
what what
the oh you're also special BL
one so many of them later you use
exp okay but still you don't lose items
right so that's good
to
no none can
appr okay cool that the fact that I died
at least led me down here
yes I am
enjoying only items still on the ground
are lost oh oh
okay I think I'm pretty good at like
placing
the
um placing
the circle of spikes quite well
[Music]
oh that one that one's that one's
blue that one's also
blue wait is that the one I died to a
moment ago I think
I think
not
dead sport G ghetto
does you died to a yellow B right yeah
yeah it wasn't blue but it feel like I
feel like it was that location though
[Music]
H I guess I
could give this one
also how about this one cuz I can't give
it the other one for some
reason but I was thinking about that
skill
too ouch
Stone charm oh it goes there but this
one's white cannot be stunned use when
you become stunned but wait wait wait
for cannot be stunned for the next stun
or in the moment when I get stunned I I
think this might be almost more useful
right now than the toas
charm oh that one's also
white the moment I do get stunned oh
then I like it I like it
uh up here I guess what does a chest
though too much
clutter it's a scepter but it's a white
one well I'm going to go sell
[Music]
2.5 seconds
MH how can I help what would you like
[Music]
de till next
time oh this one has a
[Music]
slot but it's kind of
weak
so I think I
sell okay take a look at my take a p I'm
not sure what I'm going to do with it
but well not sure what I'm going to do
with
it but all right I'll take it
thanks get going now all right
then to
to see y
later having fun ear aren't we
you're not going
anywhere o
checkpoint
M looks like a big arena to fight
something
big oh oh oh oh what the
heck oh show me your power dear sister
look at you oh I want to look at you let
me let me appreciate
you
conquer dare you disturb
me yeah enter my circle [\h__\h] get in
here of the I love I call to you no
problem no
problem who is
thisen a b wait that's from
you let me go let me go what wait what
the [\h__\h] I couldn't get out of
there
n mirror
match excuse me
power dear sister I attack them I would
prefer to just not be inside of them
no qut and
right right
insolence
conquer your
focus right of the I'm so slow she
slowed me no
to me okay
[Music]
how oh
that
con rven I need
you should about to do that thing
again ah
intro
down quit and rat my I call to
you no do something ah the skills are
like I'm like trying to like press
skills and also always uh uh put Mouse
Clicks in between but the cool down
basically is just so
big from the mouse click I oh God I
rarely get to
my get to use the skill but it's okay it
kind of work right of the full
moon
all
death to
Meen I think I'm doing good too
oh oh she dead she
dead oh okay
so that didn't matter anymore at the end
but you had it coming
[Applause]
yippee we can look at her now she's like
still
there oh they they knew that I wanted to
look closer at her so they left her
corpse here but it's hard to see this
actually her pose reminds me of
something I saw in the museum too which
I think I'll I'll show my photos more of
my photos on
Tuesday Tuesday
well that was
fun now I wanted to see her head
properly anyway we got a key
right oh yeah that's looks like a
key thanks for the membership
welcome wait aren't you the one I I
called uh disgusting a moment ago
it seems I need to fulfill everybody's
wishes more
often I
can seems to be working quite
well where am I going with
this did I walk past it isn't it down
there how's you know I
remember no okay it wasn't
there up
here the way point I have oh yeah here
we are you defeated us in here hell yeah
I did the prer will be devastated he
gets what he deserves but let's find
Draven come back when you have Draven
key another
key what go back into the same Cemetery
that I just came
from why couldn't that Draven guy not
already be there when I was looking for
asenia previous ly it's a different
tomb okay Tomb Raider Wawa looks for
another one
then so different entrance
okay not
here then I
shall accept
it must be over here
why empty
I think it's up but I also want to check
down
here
maybe so chaotic
checkpoint up there feels like there's
either like random boss
there
oh this looks promising down here
too just going to run a little bit
through it
[Music]
I'm
confused n okay nothing here oh but a
nice
chest maybe not that
nice could have been nice could have
been
nicer I'm playing the five
don't say that don't say
that does the company that makes uh Path
of Exile also make any other games that
I might have heard
of versus like their their one big
baby no oh so they're one big
baby a
half of Exile is an only
child my beloved
Son you my dearest
daughter
thanks cool
story I shall uh bring these valuables
to the rest of your family the remaining
Co of your famili
which just happens to be me I'm a very
distant far far far
cousin of fifth grade or whatever our
Victory I ha destroy Beauty found
it Dreadful
Draven I love this like writing here
this graphic in combination with these
wow you know
one thing that um oh
nice that Ren was
extremely fascinated with was
pillars like
these and she saw that here we had like
pillars that were like a little bit tiny
bit thicker on the bottom and then
little bit like really minimally th her
up at the top and she was like so
fascinated when she saw it IRL she was
like oh in Japan we don't have these
kind of pillars really at least not the
real ones like maybe maybe fake ones but
these are like the OG's and then she
like would explain why these are so
great because like the fact that they
are thicker on the bottom makes okay I
don't take this I mean I realize now
while I'm talking about it maybe you
guys are going to laugh about it like
little 15-year-old boys but the fact
that it's a little bit thicker at the
bottom makes it look longer
so you know overall the the ceiling will
look uh you know further away which is a
good thing
you so it will have that kind of effect
the pillars will look longer and the T
the tendo the the tendo the ceiling will
will look uh further away yeah
spacious yeah course persective
M yeah
so
for I think
not she knows so
much didn't know she was so into pillars
girer yes
indeed r was so fascinated by you know
Japan also has like amaz amazingly
beautiful architecture every every
culture really does oh my God what
the just like
a a hag
Carnival hag
convention hag March
yeah yeah that has a lot of architecture
knowledge
too oh look at
that shouldn't I uh identify it so that
it sells for more money at least even
though I don't want it the other stuff I
don't I wouldn't identify
necessarily oop no
need
yes you should dis
Enchanted
enchant the shadow dude the shadow dude
to
identify don't sell blue yellow
disenchanted oh does it give me like
extra like parts and stuff can't talk to
the shadow
dude
mhm I see how it
is I I like to hold on another for my
collection thank
[Music]
you oh a ring wow didn't I I know I
picked that up but I forgot about it
[Music]
nice stay safe if you can
okay oh use an orb transmit the ring to
add a modifier to it trans the
ring interesting let's try that next
time when I'm there maybe
I can
create it's so
pretty really speaking to me oh okay we
got oh but what about the Forgotten
riches I need to return at
once is this the right
path oh yeah oh there's also Che here
[Music]
oh
hu whoa what's the what's the catch
you
[Music]
know okay nice no
catch well inventory pretty full already
again wait so anything that's blue or
and yellow or anything that's yellow and
above for identifying H for whatever I
just did
disenchanting no drop blue and white
blues and
up okay so both ways is fine I guess the
Cates you found the riches so you got to
fight the boss ah if I didn't then the
boss wouldn't be there oh I wouldn't
have to fight him
[Music]
that's fine uh we managed to kill the
one of them we'll manage to kill this
one too but let's get a points going
here chaos damage physical damage minion
damage
H I don't know if I'm actually like
besides the chaos Bol which might get
replaced at some point if I'm really
using that much chaos damage
so I'll go with the minion damage
baby silly
stuff well speaking of baby silly stuff
let's go fight fight
fight another hole in the ground
depraved
witch you are not long for this
world W
bro okay
elen elen
Lord I will end your meaningless life
bro friend he's so
mad your spirits
hunger friend your soul ow your meaning
must right ends
now friend your
soul your soul is mine
your
soul your meaningless life ends
now friend your
soul join me at your
request no no join join join will be
punished the soul is mine why join
meaningless life can't you fight alone
huh
coward your intrusion will be punished
I'm sorry sorry sorry
I'm I am your
master C
down Asia friend join
me I am here
your
soul the spirits
hunger you're intr to me a no I did I
wanted to do the the circle attack but I
really should keep my
distance
okay we ready
spaghetti depraved witch Bring It On you
are not long for this
world cut
down your soul is
mine R your
soul the spirits are
mine your soul is mine friend your
soul your me angless life ends
now repeating himself your soul your
soul is mine baming those czy R your
soultion R your
soul your soul is
mine C my beloved Asia ah no no get out
of I
am he baited me into his
territory Better Call
Saul
sorry sorry you misunderstanding I
didn't steal your
soul I perhaps you I was just I was just
looking for soul you know the lawyer I
didn't want to misunderstanding
misunderstanding please don't understand
we have different interests I don't want
you
soul I need a lawyer do you know a good
lawyer where do you know where soul
is
Soul C down
your soul is he's not
listening cut
down a stubborn man soul my beloved
asenia your soul is
mine friend your
the soul is mine C
down
will suc to the Empire Asia join me
again again that's your
[Music]
request you WIP again oh
God I command you
down it's only halfway through why did
you guys not warn me about the riches
why did you not warn me about the I
require your
Aid at your
request at your
request
fire ow ow
ow join will be punished at your request
I am your master C
down soul is
life R your
soul asinia your soul is
mine I'm here
my uh-oh
your soul is
mine Spirits are
mine intrusion will be punished okay
okay oh oh oh oh oh I am with you wife
time
again the Eternal Will Never Surrender
he was on his knees
cut
[Music]
down I tapped out of the
game right when I killed him my God I
accidentally tapped down I f up a stun
Meer
oh thank God tabed out for a moment
ah oh but the new wand
let's go that was quite oops sorry that
was quite
challenging oh we got to level up
too
yeah requirements not met what do you
mean do I need to go into other branches
a bit
more oh I didn't take the note what do
you mean oh I need to do this one first
oopsie
sure need to go sell
first
yeah my inventory is full
my inventory is
full my inventory is
full can't carry
anymore can't carry
[Music]
anymore uh oh no never mind I don't
think I want
to do anything on
these hello
I like to hold on to another for my
collection thank you wait we got a big
life flash wa
[Music]
is a couple more
things this beautiful weard
wand
comparison
uh
is oh wait it's comparing to the scepter
ah of course it's better than the wand
at
least so from level one chaos ball that
brings us to level four chaos bolt and
we get some MAA
back okay
okay okay I did not augment my ring in
the end no I guess I didn't horned Crown
oh it looks kind of
cool I think I'll identify that one too
[Music]
uhhuh yeah
sick all right time
to go wait oh there's a lady up here
oh is
thats she looks pretty
wife but wasn't she in in her own grave
why is she
there use the thing on your wand now
what
[Music]
thing what do you
mean where do I go
you did it augment
orb okay but I don't have it with me
right now do my eyes again deceive me
yes I have the keys open up at last it's
open prise the first ones y h he's so
excited what is
this Graves yeah Isabel surprise Graves
the graveyard Callum the family of count
Lan of aam my family this doesn't make
any sense don't cry they're dead those
bastard eternals I must make them pay oh
[\h__\h] I must oh he's moring he's moring
wait gu wait wait wait wait wait wait
why why why gu what why is this
aggression directed toward
me wait a second I just up the [\h__\h]
doors for you why did he randomly rage
so
hard what's wrong with him CH NE going
too strong or
what
C
my's
ow I looked at the chat too
much got in The Cross by well so now
that I have this knowledge maybe I
shouldn't walk in
there oh
well oh okay
shortcut oh he's so
mad he's so
mad
my what happened with one that one arm
man so much bigger than the other did
you hex tech it or did just Shimmer the
[\h__\h] out of
it the music is good
[Music]
[Applause]
I am so joosu at this
game keep on King him oh this is ice
cold death and
Decay what am I doing it's making
everything so icy I don't want to walk
there but now I have no choice
going I'm so
slow
[Music]
wa lots of boss fights in this game
plenty of boss
fights looks dangerous
oh I stuned that
[\h__\h] die die die die die die die
y your Dre is over old man yay
yay that's what you get o or of trans
mutation and his ring oh I can't wear it
so what how uh upgrades a normal item to
a magic item with one modifier so on the
wand Target is not normal
Rarity Oh you mean this this one on this
one
why turn gray to Blue
[Music]
yay unlucky
o I guess so physical damage to attacks
is not the
nicest but not on this one right I I'll
just sell this one it's so low
level
anyway uh
[Music]
in feeble is
a Essence drain is a projectile
that maybe un feeble
[Music]
L my oh
true be
contaging cuz it always went away so
fast okay so Travel toan Village and
bring count laugh Ling to
Uno got
[Music]
it w and feebles me and feeble what is
that
me like
[Music]
enchanting you found the ring this will
most certainly break make you weak give
me a
moment thank you for renewing your
membership oh hey I can't see go walk
[Music]
away I can't see go away oh he just
looks the same I thought he would look
different the hooded one hello
[Music]
oh should I use it on the charm
too perhaps to make that
blue he identifies for
free sorry I was I can't click on
him there we go how long has it
mean I was
hunted the C he stole something that is
beyond dangerous hun it will cause
sickness then
Madness it can still be contain this
what powers might I learn from
him don't interrupt them please find it
I I am still too enfeebled this will
only grow worse so if we are to heal
this land we must find the
seed beyond our clan Graves is the
hunting
ground cut through those to reach the
village please go as quickly as you can
and see what you can find Vibes I fear
much
time I was not
Bamboozled just now I just like I was
not surprised okay I I felt
the yeah refund passers oh and identify
but I don't have anything okay goodbye
good to know though I wait
here sorry good to have him good to have
him around I like to hold on to oh I
like this
one me like me like like like like like
like
[Music]
so what did we get uh 4% increased
charges okay stay safe
he's sa
D wait a [\h__\h] second I just realized
puto you were always around for the app
streams weren't you and now you're here
for for the Diablo streams H wait what
the [\h__\h] is that
there why did I turn that
on
how I won thanks oh there we go that's
better are you growing mushrooms behind
yourself how dirty must you
be every step
every step I
take all the shrooms I'll
bake they follow me
not very
secretly they're
everywhere get the MCA weon be missing
you goodbye it was nice knowing you all
right travel to oldan Village travel to
hunting grounds would you say that so
easily how how would
you how would you recommend me to
travel there ref I also forgot again
what the button was l no okay no you
you
[Music]
you okay I've been here I need to go
there okay
[Music]
but
how from where if from up
here yeah thanks for the nice greetings
guys oh my God I see it everybody
everybody's in a [\h__\h] Mo I see I can
tell oh oh my
God
[Music]
y
glal leave me
alone it's a dead
[Music]
end oh this one's little bit strong
horor
stench that's your socks after you worn
them for 5
days okay but like where the
water thanks for the membership
welcome what looks
like maybe down
here I feel like that's also just going
to be a dead
end back to the
way what I can p to
that the
[\h__\h] what the
I come
give me the [\h__\h] alone what the [\h__\h] is
this enemy
spam oh my
God what I can just go
here
what I thought i' never been there
before so I couldn't go there have I
been there no I
haven't huh life and death are well
balanced here
disgusting
oh oh
gorilla oh my God okay okay okay the the
enemy spam is annoying me a little
bit it's like in Diablo I can kind of
run away from it but
here not quite as you saw I got caught
in it and almost died
okay that's the good
path oh what the
[Music]
heck
Point like what this what is this what
is
this just gets worse the more I move
you
bro well at least I get a pill great
great great great
great Mama
Mia The Forbidden books don't mention
anything like
this I should ask
local a local you mean one of these
gorillas are going to give us any good
answer interact to begin the ritual is
it like an
event oh
yeah yeah more enemies B bring of the
MIP
easy summon
Finn why what do you want here wow uh
this is your business oh cuz you're a
local
you've been putting support gems on
other which is why you're strong oh okay
so more minion stuff now see I used to
frequent The clanless Enclave that makes
its home high in the trees near here
okay the locals call it
frethorne a little while back a group of
strangers arrived out of the Deep
Woods they made altars like this and
started whispering to the others about
their
religion that was when I decided to move
R and judging by the size of this one
things have gotten worse a lot
worse something's wrong hero something's
definitely off I thought I was imagining
The Whispers In the Shadows at night up
there thought I was just spooked by the
cultist they moved in but maybe
not though it is full of Scoundrels I
was mildly fond of a fair few of
him find frorn above the hunting grounds
above above what do you mean above we're
out in the open Where's the second level
to
this
mean oh what is that I am the
a wa
wait right so there was a gorilla and
she said I am the Apex but it sounded to
me like she was saying I am the
apis as in I am the
[Applause]
gorilla searing dominance towards the
[Music]
monkeys the apest ape of them all monkey
to ah all always jump here out of
nowhere czy
L did I pick up The Kill gem
oh I have so
many okay first level
one let's put one into the sniper but I
can only why is
why or could I do it
no well okay
then more area of effect oh hell yeah
[Music]
and then this
one will make our Warrior
stronger five free levels on the fourth
level no three levels yeah
and now the arsonist is already level
three the sniper do we even have snipers
right now you're not using snipers put
it in your ARS yeah yeah yeah
yeah uh unor
could put an un Earth I use uner a lot
une
Earth nice
okay can you AFF more summons uh what
button was it
again what
button oh no [\h__\h] almost options
right
multitasking uh let's see more arsonists
no could get another Warrior
[Music]
that was a little
five I see so I could also up DPS here
no I can't okay that's just the
menu m
mhm
okay what am I looking for need to go to
Olam Village and find the entrance to
the Village which one is this also
Village L Quest I to find bra
H map is
[Music]
big I think I'm
winning doing pretty well
oh level up I totally winning
actually definitely
winning I just I just feel very lost in
these
Woods I don't know where I am speaking
of lost in the woods did you see to say
s
by uh kind of like did like a I guess
like an official song
[Music]
cover and had a little voice line in the
upcoming Moana 2
movie I was really surprised to see that
because we can't even sing Disney songs
in Our Kind streams even the unarchived
ones maybe that will
change or maybe we can sing at least is
that one song or maybe not Maybe not
maybe
not yeah like it's on her Channel but it
seems to be like in collaboration with
Disney is the oldan farmlands does that
lead to the Village
too just want to look around a bit more
because I'm supposed to find the brab
person
too infection
M it does lead
okay oh yeah it Marvel belongs to Disney
too
huh
[Music]
man the boss of this area gives more
Spirit Y how nice
I would like to meet this boss can you
introduce
me we got some
[Applause]
connection take
you marel stuff as far as I know just
like interviews I've
seen like when the movie came out
no like a few interviews have been done
so
far
mhm where boss where
[Music]
I think I'm going to watch Wicked in the
theater next
week let's go
also next week is another world tour
concert so you
know streaming on the weekend is looking
[Music]
difficult but I'm sure you
understand so
considerate I I covered the whole
[\h__\h] map where is this boss up
here be there in
person a to the
yo K me already you guys have to keep on
reminding me who's going cuz I always
forget don't get your hopes up I think
got like like it I think I'll enjoy it I
love Ariana Granda
so what's there not to
enjoy yeah okay I didn't see the whole
map yet I I'll give you that it feels
like I already saw a lot of it though
sorry twice already love it twice wow I
never really go out of my way to watch
movies twice uh at least not like in
such close succession
[Music]
no where am I
pretty hungry
too
suffering are you guys hungry yet I'm
hungry what will I eat today yesterday I
warmed up another portion of my
Curry that I have in my
freezer pretty good stuff I'm glad I
still had that and I already ate all the
sausages that I had left over I ate them
yesterday for like uh
lunch you've been eating almonds too but
not the candied ones uhhuh I'm sure it's
not
Candi kind of feeling
Brey oh so Australian of
you but I I have so much beef in my
freezer now but I don't know what to do
with
it beef Fila I got the nice I was like
in the Super Market and I really didn't
have much time I I was like so stressed
out uh cuz this was the day before they
arrived and I was like still cleaning up
my whole house and still finishing up
some
things like uh putting up a lamp in the
bathroom where it was just a light bulb
still
and this and that fixing something in my
garden and washing laundry and blah blah
blah and you know also had to buy so so
so so many groceries
for
theet cuz you want a lot of variety
right and I was in the supermarket
calling my mom
frantically oh there we go and I was
like first of all for like the wine I
called her I sent her a million pictures
of the wine section I was like what the
[\h__\h] do I buy the girls said they want
to drink some wine so I want to buy a
red and a and a white one I I don't know
what to buy and then my mom starts going
on tangents about wine and like what it
depends on what you're eating what kind
of meat and I'm like I don't know we're
going to eat all kinds of
meat and I'm like Mommy I don't have
time just tell me what to buy I I I I
have to stop shopping in like 10 minutes
out I'm on a really tight schedule
please just tell me what to
buy yeah it worked out I mean I honestly
I can't judge if the wine was decent
they were all kind of like normal I was
in a discount Discounter Supermarket so
I just bought whatever looked the
priciest in it but they were all kind of
about the same but my mom said this
would be
fine so
the girls did drink like one glass and
now I have so much wine and I don't know
what to do with
it thank God I only bought one bottle of
each at
least for cooking yeah the white wine uh
actually recently I would have needed it
because one of my recipes said use white
wine for the chees
sauce and then and
I didn't have any it was fine without
the white one too but it would have been
nice to have
it and the red one I guess too but how
long after opening it how long is the uh
usable what's happening why are they so
green
what's going on here
anyway I just realized this whole time
probably this the the fighting sounds
are really [\h__\h] loud huh I just
looked at OBS I'm so sorry why didn't
you guys say anything
if just lowered the
volume it's fine really
what what did you say
I lowered it a bit but yeah so how long
tell me guys I could ask my mom again
but tell me guys I opened one 3 days ago
until when can I use for
cooking a few months of no they're like
uh normal like normal twist and
open not eternally they're open already
until it tastes like
vinegar
H okay three weeks really okay oh I'll
try to
use one next week at least but I mean I
I won't be using the whole bottle for my
cheese sauce just a little
Spritz
Katana too
bad I I don't know what the [\h__\h] is
going on I'm just randomly pressing my
mouse in this
battle but it's
working that was
easy don't whisper at me from the dark I
am the
Shadows beef
B that's sounds
fancy make free liters of cheese sauce I
do think I have like two servings of
those spinach noodles in my
fridge so I could make the cheese sauce
twice at
least give it to N I was thinking that
too and like let my friends drink it but
yeah I'll I'll try to use a little bit
for
cooking beef on your best
Ste beef Bono huh I'll think about
it I can't believe red wine sauce the
whole bloody place has gone mad wait be
wait I have remaining beef Stripes from
the filet in my freezer too find the
other alters and dispose of them okay
wait that's perfect beef B is a beef
stew I have remaining red wine and
remaining lots of
remaining uh beef filet Stripes already
cut in my
freezer they weren't originally stripes
they were cut for the sake of the
rocklet of
course it was one piece when I bought
it okay I'll look up I'll look up what
else I need
to buy for ingredients what I need maybe
I already have everything who
know
ah
W hallelujah hallelujah hallelu
Hallelujah Hallelujah
hallelu Hallelujah Hallelujah
hallelu
Hallelujah just wanted to flex my range
just now give
me oh that looks cool
[Music]
the Mana
flask what do you mean if it's
good what do you mean if it's good it's
the same what do you mean
Flex is
working now sing a Maria wait wait wait
wait wait uh I don't remember how it
goes I don't really know it so
well
maybe maybe if
I was a politician maybe then I would
know yes
M what have you
learned thanks
bro care to take a look at my none of
it's junk wait trust me go make a legend
or two where is UN
here something like that I don't know
how to ask it's
in yeah give me whatever Quest you got I
got
you I guarantee I got you oddson it's
beautiful I
accept she accepts my marriage
proposal got to hold it longer
[\h__\h] it's beautiful guess we're not
getting there
today it seems Shadows haunt us both
manif flask was enchanted
hello these are just some odds and ends
of mine gains oh 0.15 charges per
second uh okay exchange ah how much you
want 28 I take I hope it brings you good
fortune it seems Shadows haunt us
both it's b d and a in flat wordss
really how do you know I don't even know
what that means though like I can't
recreate something by its notes
unfortunately buy a better
wand
no no my wand is nice I just got it
recently just got it recently if I'm
buying on the thing I would buy I guess
a second scepter cuz you guys were
saying scepter scepter get a
scepter w what is that on the
ground oh it's holding my skeletons ah E
I don't like
it
[Music]
anyway
H I guess we're going to give an
attribute to
something like I feel like it makes
sense to give it to intelligence cuz of
my class but then again some of the
these are you know asked for for
some stuff here and
[Music]
there oh for
supports okay another good excuse all
right I'll take
it yeah I did need strength or dexterity
for one of the armor pieces that I was
holding aside the the dexterity one was
the more recent
[Music]
one ho
macaroni took you a while to respawn
buddies search for ritual altars I need
more how many more of the ominous
altars Mary had a little lamp in my head
right now I know it's not the right
thing but the only thing I can think of
of is Mary had a little lamb
e that's wrong
oh it's just like how I sing Oh Canada
Oh Canada some things are just I I feel
like destined for each
other even if you don't agree what the
[\h__\h]
[Applause]
here the map feels somehow more visible
I think because of the contrast
of what it's yeah here too this looks
like brighter and the background is
darker so it's way easier to
see
infection just saying
case the deaths are
listening you hate this map why so far I
think I like it more than the outside
with all
the all the different like veins of
uh what the
roots oh look at that I found something
what the [\h__\h] is that that's not the
ritual that I'm looking for uh I think
or is
it so this is where the darkness is
hiding let's
go open
up
hello do I come back
later are you not done prepping do I
need to open up the other ritual
altars
okay
okay I'm I'm going to come
back I thought it was something
completely
different oh my God oh my
God are they
like they run into something and then
they explode in their elev
what oh
yes oh
[Music]
no wait did all I forgot did all the
enemies respawn when I
die or like on the whole map or just the
ones I haven't fought yet just the ones
I haven't fought yet
right like in haven't fought yet as
in since the last
checkpoint what build are you playing
I'm not sure I guess I'm doing a minions
build because I love the Minion ride so
much makes
sense holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] sumon build okay see that's that
will be my go-to answer from now on then
thank you for uh giving me my
script
owge
SM sad
you got into Q there was no Q was really
uh quite I guess
exaggerated yesterday I mean even
yesterday once it was open people didn't
wait that long huh
huh I'm a witch yes
[Music]
people try not to freak out within five
hours of launch challenge
Impossible 2 hours before it stabilized
oh did they get kicked out a
lot
quickly sorry I was just
[Music]
it seems
shadows I'm giving everybody business I
know I could
sell over by her as well but I want to
split give everybody the pleasure to
talk to
me oh wait
oh oh I can wear the strength one now uh
uh it is still better than what I have
right
now
uh at least in terms of the armor
Strat sure I'll wear
it hello none of it's j deal later later
[Music]
beautiful wait when is Kampus talk again
isn't it like tomorrow or something I
just realized cuz these dudes reminded
me of Kampus or Nicola talk not comp
talk is it always the eighth uh or
seventh
yesterday
no I missed it yesterday a yesterday
yes
ah now then L and laddin avoided
trouble it would would have kind of been
funny if I could have shown them a
compus
l a that would have been
entertaining but they left quite
early yeah you know what I told you
about so we have this like slim
slender uh s Santa Claus called Nicolas
show up um on the 6th of December I
guess and he comes with these
campus they look really scary and they
come in like First Suits but like
really nothing to joke about scary type
of f suits and horns and
everything yeah
and the tradition is for them to run
around see cus for p p from what I know
are even worse on the compus bigger and
more
scary and they they run around and they
you know people gather around
them and they're like asking to be hit
and stuff to be thrown around so I don't
know don't ask me why humanity is a
mystery so they will go and like I don't
know I haven't experienced this in a
long time but they would like pick him
up and I don't know mess with them not
really punch them and stuff but I don't
know I I have
been from my childhood I have it in
memory that you want to stay away from
them because they're really scary and
you could possibly potentially get hurt
it's like something you maybe want to do
when you're a little bit older as a
child you should stay away
yeah they grab the bad children to scare
them they even come to school they let
them into school sometimes it's really
scary oh I feel like I don't not I don't
think necessarily the school allows it
sometimes they
just go in on their own I
think but it's tradition
so and then they run around a little bit
in the calls and this is just one memory
I it might not be so common I just have
this one memory everybody's in the
classroom
like I'm
scared oh no I want to go out I want to
go out I'm going to challenge them oh
look at
that was that the last one no there's
more
beautiful where could it be looking at
this
map there's probably more here
too but I'm also going to go up here see
how far it
goes could have been allowed by the
school and then they just pretend like
it wasn't on them like oh no who let the
dogs out
who let them
in but yeah there's like specific
chocolate also that they
sell during that time the Nicolas
chol and also um you get what was it
nuts yeah I add new
soda they give out uh which was uh what
what nuts was that
again
peanuts lots of peanuts going around for
what forever
reason I don't think children like
peanuts that much
but
sure lightning mirages when hit Mirage
he streams Mirage but not for much
longer got a nice w
on but I don't like
[Music]
it so in a situation like this I guess I
should put it into chaos bolt
already whatever I'll put it into
engrave I don't care
and then this
one why is there two Warrior SKS because
one comes from my skill and one from my
scepter y y yep yep
yep let's
upgrade
H chain will make it worse
oh no oh no oh no no no no where do how
do I get to that menu
again
ah
G oh up here huh how do
I how do I choose a different one
H it's a chain now I can't can I not
change it
[Music]
anymore what do you mean what do you
mean it makes it worse
though say it in simple words because
that doesn't look bad to me it's a neat
detail to have the mouse reflect on the
health and I presume the mono
orb the
mouse reflect
what do you
mean the [\h__\h] dark mold The
Psychotic just wandering around there on
his
own okay we have lifted his
psychosis now he's got a whole another
HP bar
look at my bomb thrower having The High
Ground smart
boy what a smart boy and look at the
Yellow Hat
yooo let me look at it in peace please
T ooh I need more
decks good that we started Skilling into
it at
least but it looks pretty good
no just need more
decks hopefully
soon oh here's another one of
these plus one minion is that what it
says oh yeah cool
that is good as far as I know so this
one I can't use on anything can I or I
guess I wait I put one into chain I can
put another one into wering
touch okay well
done look it gets reflected when near it
oh that Ah that's what you mean ah
[Music]
yeah how many decks do you have now
where can I
see I don't
know there's another attribute thing
here put it in decks oopsie
n maybe that's enough it's
not it is
not uh I need 20 deck I'm still missing
three okay okay but I could probably
just the I think the left side the left
path was
also for
attributes so instead of going up I
could just go take the left one and add
more decks even
whoa what the how much how much cash
outfits are there ooh what is that what
are you growing on the ground what kind
of STD do you have
sorry sorry sorry
sorry
greetings just try to make J work
oh no oh no oh no no no no my manners
sorry tired of the slaughter
yet
yes what the [\h__\h] is that is that your
baby what is that Goblin Gremlin
thing it's a baby with a bird head Hawk
head or owl
head it's kind of
weird oh my God it's got aggressions too
that it can't control sorry I was just
elsewhere baby ow
bear oh you think that's an owl bear but
where is all the
fur wait [\h__\h] second whoa should I
use
this or can I disenchant I I don't use
these things do I this is for a weapon
right a shield essentially you like cha
ball too much so you can
[Music]
stay safe so you're saying you're
telling me
[Music]
to
uh uh
uh you telling me to do
this but then there's nothing on my left
click
the wering touch is gone
[Music]
too how do I get uh no never mind
oh can I not use bone cage
anymore excuse me no
strength no I can't even put it in the
slot here it's not cuz I'm in
town I miss his strength no but is that
really the way to
go I mean it's pretty cool yeah I
guess also what about these
two I not I don't even have enough
strength for that
either sorry I was
just oh
[Music]
maybe I'll put it in my chest for now in
case I change my
mind increased Rarity of items
found it still
go has to
go Finn makes fun of my it's beautiful
it's beautiful
so what I do if I have one of this like
just sitting around now stay sa can keep
it for the
future thr away new stash
okay you could talk to the hood gu
respect passive put it into strength all
nah it's fine uh cuz I'm also still
trying
to spe into dexterity as
well the red support gem from the bone
cage why because it make gives it oh cuz
it makes it cost more
strength you are smart
cookie now pick it up bro pick it up
pick it pick it pick it up wait how do I
pick something
up when my left click is this crazy
attack oh now it worked weird I clicked
on it so many times
uh where were we another ritual
altar I
am where am
I ah there so I feel like should be
something down
there yeah putting a skill on left click
has
issues who told me to do that
I've got issues you've got them
[Music]
too
ooh oh this is pretty with all
the all the feather finger
thingies I used to have those kind of
things in my
[Music]
room made one myself also before
wait did I just oh there was nothing
down there okay well I guess I got to
explore this
part you're not ready yet are
you oh wait it kind of looks
ready okay now I'm absolutely spamming
it cuz I'm using it with the feeling
that I am just using my old skill
still well not bad huh we can't afford
spamming it I've never used a Mona flask
ever before either maybe from now on we
will I guess we can begin it that's the
last ritual I need to do okay confusion
Okay it definitely makes me use it
more is it good is it bad who
[Music]
knows oh yeah now I'm out of
Mana doing good damage though
oh what did you do to
me let me out what the
[\h__\h] what he's
insane W he changed his form he's a tree
what what look at this HP bar leave me
alone what he made me into a tree too
again I don't want to be
tree back
off what what do you what do you no
no no no how do I how do I make him not
do that do I have to like stun
him I guess if he takes too much time to
come over to me like if I'm really far
when I'm in that state maybe he can't
hurt
me he's got the mark on me
again oh let me
out ah there's so much weird stuff on
the ground you the
P I'm chilling
though I'm
chilling well go
binted oh no I'm too close uh-oh let me
go
yeah
[Applause]
Yoo cool cool cool cool cool cool
cool
what
what what is this
menu are you giving this to me am I
choosing
maybe I'll take
this spend tribute for
reward aha aha this takes
576 tributes is that like a
[Music]
lot I think that's a lot
yeah I know I have enough but like would
I want to save some more for whatever
reason oh the orbs are hella expensive I
thought they would be
[Music]
cheaper you can't save it
okay no I didn't do it we can do it
after the stream
maybe sure doesn't say carry over okay
don't you like these gloves
though because I'm working on the decks
I'll be able to wear them
soon I'm almost there I'm working on the
decks for the helmet as well
so I'll take
okay I could still take more if I had
even
more no I'm not trimming my
decks
I'm trying to grow
it
okay well uh talk to Finn it
is time to talk to fin
are we
all in
capslock you are
revealing your true
feelings what have you
learned go so the cultists really did
ever a king lurking out there in the
shadows MH shame I might have followed
him myself if he'd simply promised
decent meals
instead thank you hero it's not the
result I was hoping for but at least I
know the truth M clear Fells all I have
left
now if I was a drinking man it' be a
sobering
thought
oh well well I'll take this one even
though I would have liked to have that
earlier then only I had one my slot how
do I get one more slot
here where what is this
go right click to break the skull
release the energies within
oh o ooh
[Music]
o Grim remnants recover 17 energy Shield
50% chance to spawn a Remnant when an
enemy or revive oh like on its own
cool h no Reviving Min and Di
person should I go for a grim Feast get
raging Spirits what
where you should pick summon raging
Spirits
huh oh
here minions from this skill convert 70%
of physical damage to fire
damage and some other
stuff W make own choice oh my God what a
those Leaf Wings on fire those are sick
those look
sick who got turn turn around don't go
away let me look at you turn around
though oh
cool those are cool Oh
[Music]
Canada Oh
Canada uh what was I doing uh
how can I
be
yes these are just it's beautiful I
accept you can sell these but no these
ah these I can't sell okay bye
[Music]
uh put here wait for
decks wait why is this here now oh I
have
to put it in two where just any of
these wait where do
I where do I oh here
Feast on flesh but this is
passive I do have to activate it
huh okay we good we
good it's a skill not a
support what are you saying
[Music]
it's fine now right it it'll work
now what are those
fish you got your own little lamps
around
you they look really stinky
though I want to buy stuff from the cash
shop
now okay go to um
I wonder if it would have been faster
with
the can I go there no through
the portal that I had but uh did you buy
an EA pack or where you handing the key
I wasn't handing the key I bought it on
Steam oh no not this place
okay let me just please look at the
map but it's all gone now so I cannot
orientate myself
where do I
go the better he comes to 300 points
that you can buy stuff with you have at
least 300 coins oh maybe I do I I bought
the like Early Access thing from Steam
no extras though only the basic
[Music]
one I'm uh creating way more
minions by spamming that
obviously which is actually I guess good
I'm also keeping up with the Mana pretty
well this might not be such a bad
Strat the only annoying thing is I can't
pick up items well enough [\h__\h]
hell yeah I I know that's the one that
creates them but like up until now I
wasn't using it that much because
of the
key where I put it
on with all these extra minions
everything dies much faster H
hoay okay then I think I found my
calling and my
footing I hope I'm going the right way
to the farmland
and is this entrance to the Village
Quest do they also mean oam Village I
wonder I hope so because I already
looked through this whole
place if it's not that then I don't
know be other to path down yeah I had
that feeling too
might want to play with like maps of the
places you were in on the side like in a
different window oh hey look at
that no let me
in don't attack let me
in now look at the quests all go like B
Bam Bam Bam okay they didn't they
didn't not
quite this gives me seven days to die
Vibes oh my
God it's just exactly the
same me and
oh look at this
ous e oh my God stinky that's that must
be so
disgustingly
stinky They're All Dead with like
millions of flies over
them but hey one cannot complain about
the variety of uh environments
here in this
game pumpkins oh they look
nice look how nice the plague spreads
among
[Music]
them what are these things that I'm
collecting these little orbs
remnants from the Grim Feast they give
you
[Applause]
a that's why I didn't notice them before
how the hell did that chicken survive
for all of that the last standing
remaining
kfp you know why because you guys have
an invisible armor that guards you
against my attacks unless I want them to
hit you of course I could hit you if I
wanted to don't
misunderstand take it
quick clarification yeah because I know
otherwise you guys are going to be
a pick it up bro I need an auto pickup
like do you get something like that
later on something that picks up items
on its own or maybe it's that a cash
shop thing I'm fine with that
too a
no no I will not I will not swap where
my unearth is it's in the perfect
position it makes me it more I love it
it's just a tiny problem small small
problem you can buy a stash
tab I'll click you can organize it what
but that doesn't help me with my issue
does
[Music]
it what am I looking for
The Village
entrance um this scarecrow M on it its
own little bit
concerning oh I found something
interesting over there unas loot
box loot
box take it n it's so annoying
ah yeah maybe it's more efficient if I
click on the I
than on the name of the
[Music]
item
anyway look at that scared
chicken hugging the wall it's okay it's
wow are you playing jump King little
chicken it jumped up there so cute
must be so scared it's
reaching New
Heights completely new heights that it
was unaware
of do we need
help barel
t
t the girls
need found something what a desperately
boring
home but one thing I must say that
Diablo 4 at least I don't know if it's
same with Diablo 2 but is superior at is
like things being easily destroyed like
normally these things they should just
go
Kaboom but they don't
that's one
thing where I'll give Diablo the
win hot Take Ah I don't think so it's a
cold take if anything even though that
doesn't sound so positive but apparently
a hot take is not so
positive it's 11
pm. I'm
[Music]
thinking should I end soon because I
want
to
think hard about what to eat and perhaps
still have time to order
something before everything closes
am I
full the loot is
huge maybe maybe maybe also cuz I still
need to watch Breaking bed
yeah
um on Earth since I'm using it so much
why the hell not not
you think not I think
yes me naming myself Heisenberg in this
game is so unlike me me usually I'd want
like a cute name that matches the
character and
everything but the brain Rod was too
strong this time it overtook me okay so
I was going to go here and take the deck
thanks although there actually was one
up here too oops
all right I can cancel I'm going to take
here dicks what
this life
recoup
uh when you take damage from a hit
recoup causes you to recover an amount
of the stated
resource equal to a percentage of the
damage you took over 8 seconds okay I'm
not sure if I would want to go there
[Music]
anyway protects your life by taking
damage instead oh that's what I'm
charging right now the whole time
huh chaos damage removes twice as much
energy Shield damage and bleeding damage
from bleeding and poison bypasses energy
shield and removes directly okay
cool you know what this means we got
some more decks I can
wear uh
this Feast on flesh and this we got
three yellow items now no one two four
four yooo
exciting oh is it the
switcheroo oh oh cuz it's full oh [\h__\h] I
I thought it meant like since I still
had some options
there it's
good it is good huh should I replace it
with one of the others you guys said
ignition was good
too this also is good damn
it
h Well for now I will go maybe put on a
sniper can have one extra sniper
oh sniper
comeback uh no okay not yet uh
unfortunately but I'll put it on there
for
now
um
greetings
hey who knows what priz is I'm not sure
what I'm going to do with it but cheers
not sure what I'm going to do with it
[Music]
cherio what is this later oh adds a run
socket to a marshall
weapon not but so far I haven't really
been using these
[Music]
things you found my loot I think I shall
Begin by composing a song about you oh
no please don't in the metime I would be
happy to play for you if you like no no
you're going to ruin me you're going to
ruin my life please stop talking to
me book of I thought I said speculation
specialization grants two weapon set
passive skill
points uh okay I guess now she'll start
playing songs you receiv
[Music]
okay
mhm h
I don't know if I'll be forever having
this energy shield around
though you think I should scale into
[Music]
it I could just go up
yeah cuz I mean look what's ahead of
us I'll give something to strength
why not oh one
more yeah so here I should perhaps
decide do do I want to go left or up or
right I don't [\h__\h]
know oh there's minion damage stuff over
here and different stuff too and Tropic
Incarnation oh yeah yeah minions should
I go there
okay let's put this one into
intelligence
maybe
ah M mhm yeah why not never now then H
wait I'm
done oh I need this one
oopsie there we go a little bit too
early hold your
horses it is good to see see
you I've collected these oh I like this
one be
careful all right
uh want decks I already have it I
already got enough decks for those items
that I wanted to put on the Hat
uh
specifically good place to stop yeah I
think so too do I have to save the
game doesn't look like
it
cool cool cool cool cool cool cool as
abot likes to
say
oh all right
exit Path of
Exile sounds
good I guess I'll read super chats No
Maybe not maybe I
won't maybe I
won't ah quick
notice Advent calendar tonight will be I
think the first
Duo chat where are you
what
the what happened with
you what happened with
you oops I oops
what
keyboard there we
go yeah today will be a
Duo actually like I have a lot of the
Future Days already filled up but I
don't have the day tomorrow filled up I
I've been asking around like a lot of
girls are like oh I can only do like
later dates so I'm a little bit
struggling and scared I can't fill up
that one day wor Cas I guess I'll uh
jump in but ideally not CU I'd have too
many
appearances um we'll see but today will
be a
and then tomorrow stream
H I was thinking of doing the Koke I
don't really feel very prepared though
is my problem I don't know if I can
actually sing all these songs that I
want to sing I need some practice and I
feel like I don't have enough time to
practice especially if I'm going to like
stay up late
again um
but it's weekend and next weekend I
can't probably
so I'll
try like if I do it later in the day
like my usual streaming
time H then it would be fine then I'd
have enough time to practice but I
wanted to do it during like prime time
for
Asia for once very
rarely but maybe I'll just do it during
my normal
time and then rebroadcast it
during Asia friendly
time let me look at the
schedule just so that I have more time
to practice I guess so
[Music]
yeah that's what rebroadcasts are for
maybe I could even rebroadcast it like
next week when I'm not like supposed to
be streaming you know maybe maybe
manager
son can rebroadcast
it okay in that
[Music]
case pretty late would be good I suppose
maybe 10 p.m. W
time the set list won't be too huge so I
don't think it will be more than two
hours 10 or 10 or
p.m. what time so like around now but
like earlier a little
bit Yeah so it's like good for
na good for EU just Asia will have to
wait a bit
for the rebroadcast I originally really
wanted to do it prime time for them but
I need more practice if I want to do
that I think I need more practice time
before the
stream so I'll put up the proper stream
reservation and proper time tomorrow
when I wake up but it's going to be
roughly around that time I suppose
yeah
yeah P VOA is the best
Exile Exile
huh
well if we see it as path of Wawa is the
only path and the last path the first
the only and the last path that you'll
be taking I guess it is somewhat of a
Path of Exile
I choose exile over the Wawa path all
right
then
goodbye have a nice day oh
[Music]
smoothie did you hear
that and flop there she flops and
stretch
cute maybe she just came from the toilet
and from a nap
thanks for stream T you thank you too I
hope you
enjoyed the
stream
yeah I'm going to watch Breaking Bad
finally and eat
something I have a good time I like it I
mean it just feels weird because
I'm simultaneously playing Diablo
4 and it's just the same kind of game so
it's like I'm playing the same it's like
bad timing actually really bad
timing we're just yeah doesn't feel like
betrayal it just feels like rep
repetitive in terms of the content I
offer on my Channel right
now yeah yeah you should pick one to
focus on
H
well if I focus on Poe then I'll forget
even more about the story of Diablo if
we get back to
it uh but Poe is at least fresh and new
right
now yeah maybe for now I'll play Poe
I still like Diablo if Diablo 4 is one
or two streams from being finished yeah
like at least the before the
DLC oh hello she just jumped up I do
think that like even if I finish the
main story in the end the DLC thing
whether or not it will happen is kind of
questionable
now
um well maybe if it really is just one
or two more streams then not too bad to
have it going uh around the same time
right I'll just finish up Diablo and
Poe uh at the same
time it is what it is smoovie is
wandering around the table what are your
thoughts smoovie you're going to sit
down
you're such a baby such a
baby I wonder like Larissa has a cat now
right she must be like in her stream
constantly talking about her Kitty
now if I'm always talking about my cat
and she has a kitten like that's that's
something super special and it's very
fresh you must be constantly talking
about it
[Music]
did you hear about cie's cats
what what what happened
what why
what they chewed up all her it
it huh she had that issue since a long
time ago that they like cables oh but
they actually chewed through the whole
internet cable
like bro they got into the studio
overnight so she thinks it's it happened
over one
night oh [\h__\h] how much do they love
cables bro thank God mine don't give a
[\h__\h] at all about
cables oh my
God oh my God
need to find a way to prevent that I
mean it's hard like my cables are out
all out in the open
and I I wouldn't even know where to
start if I had to like protect the
cables somehow from my cats
but yeah if you have cats that love
cables then you got
to go the cables in hot no what the
[\h__\h] you'll kill the cats with that
but yeah you could like cover it with
like a panel for example like you know
like behind the PC and like down from
the monitor down on the ground you know
like under the table all those cables
like I feel like you could cover it with
one big
panel for
example
yeah or yeah like uh that requires a lot
of work no I literally mean just like
buy like a panel
from like I don't know some
shop just put it there not like mount it
to the
wall like so prople it just just put it
just block
it wrap it in double-sided tape ah it's
like a fly trap
then yeah she'll figure it
out I hope the cats are okay
crazy
cats okay
GNA uh be gone Nino thank you for
watching I had lots of fun I think we'll
continue playing
it uh both uh so yeah tomorrow is Sunday
so I'll try to also make a schedule for
the next week since you've been so good
without the schedule this week you guys
also don't forget there's the new
members wallpaper on the members
Community it's really beautiful you
didn't download it
yet
[Music]
M very Angelic magnificent
yeah if you want to hear my reaction for
breaking
bed the last the finale I'll see you on
Twitter goodbye guys and J we say see
you tomorrow for unarchived
K bye-bye
n
[Music]
down