K ho ho
[Applause]
ho hello everybody thank you for
Gathering today this is the press
conference of Taki K
Claus uh first and foremost you guys are
already going a little bit overboard
please stop the flashlights they are
reminding me of some sad days on the
North Pole uh takanashi Ki Claus and her
crew of very very talented individuals
uh very motivated as well are working on
the Advent calendar again it is
happening again F year with more support
from the management thank you to the
management side for um financially and
and or logistically helping out yes yes
no questions yet please thank you um
just like last year uh it will be under
the same domain and every day it will be
up updated at GMT UTC Z midnight
Midnight o00 0:00 whatever how you say
it I don't freaking know 25 days from
the 1st of December until the 25th of
SE sep I mean December December what
what is that what that is uncertain uh
and if it was then I would not tell you
cuz it has to be a surprise of course
yes the little Chum out in the very back
yeah what do you what do you have to
ask oh yes all all 20 whatever wait how
many are we 50 I don't yeah all whole
life English whole life English whole
whole life English members will be
included indeed yes he yes what is
that yes there will be um perhaps a
couple of
collaborative uh videos as well some
solo videos some unit videos yes what is
that
yeah and then of course we have our
wonderful wonderful P pong
P again on the team to help us with
really really cute adorable icons again
yes so please look forward to opening
the door each day and I wish you all a
merry merry merry uh holiday season
thank you so much for coming today this
is all the questions I will be taking
for today I think that is enough you all
understand what this is right yes okay
uh really really quickly in Japanese
though
uh
[Music]
thank you everybody I'm looking forward
to your support and your visitations
in
insanely never seen before numbers on
our website please be careful to crash
it though Do Not Crash it that is my job
I will crash it with my
sle all right then thank you everybody
and in German we say Al we ho ho ho
ho