dancing
out sorry so emotion
[Music]
feel it r
r
feel it R through me
[Music]
oh
honey night ising
[Music]
it R through me
intoxicating DJ keep
[Music]
playing emo
CR
baby me
[Music]
feel it rush through me
k h
k
[Music]
Yahoo I shouldn't be tired I slept like
enough but I've been up for a few hours
like since oh God it's already been 6
hours since I've been awake and I've
been like doing stuff because I've been
trying to get some stuff done and clean
my
apartment
um I don't live in an apartment
anymore clean my house uh because yeah I
came back from Italy
and U I'm going to uh Japan
[Music]
soon
uh yeah I've got some stuff do I have to
unpack I at least at least today I
finished
unpacking some stayed in the suitcase
anyway uh because I'll be taking them to
Japan
too
yeah I'm doing all my laundry so much
laundry I'm washing all the towels as
well uh for for the caretakers of the
Kos uh yeah I turned DVR off again
M yeah yeah
yeah and uh yeah lots muchos much's
laundry and some gardening ripping out
some
weeds is that the word I
forgot
um um BL blah
blue blah blah
blah trying to find things like plug
converters in my
chaos uh and then I had a call with
FedEx because I missed something and
they need they need my signature so they
can't deliver it while my friends are
here now I won't be there for a long
time so they they made a they said okay
we'll make an exception we'll keep your
package for over a [\h__\h] month I'm
like thank
you then also some email stuff with my
tax
lady I got a letter that confused me
about the the fendom that I told you
about
previously this confused me like okay
I'm still getting some things to my old
address apparently but I have the the
thing that brings them over to the new
address right uh I have that set for
like several
months and so because of that I think
some things arrive later than they
should so when I checked yeah they
they're getting forwarded yeah when I
checked my uh mailbox I can't think of
words when I checked my mailbox I saw
two letters from
the finance department so to say uh one
was like hey [\h__\h] pay us extra money
what was the word again Fen fend
English seizure yeah that's such a weird
word because it it has a completely
different meaning
too yeah we want to seize your money so
here's extra amount of money that we
want to seize
right I saw that letter now but I
already paid it right cuz my tax lady
told me already paid it but then the
second later letter was saying I feel
like it's saying that the previous
letter uh is is now invalid and our
request for the seized money uh has also
been made invalid due to you paying the
other money
on time but I didn't pay it on time did
I I mean on time when I thought it was
on time but in any case now it was
saying like cesure seizure cancelled
please ignore previous letters so I'm
like what do you mean does this mean
there's no further seizure or that also
the previous seizure is canceled so I I
I I sent an email to my tax lady asking
if I if I paid it for nothing or uh if
this just means no more further
seizure I'm not
sure I'm not sure it probably yeah it
probably just means don't worry about it
anymore but there was there it was kind
of shown
confusingly oh
well I'm going to get a seizure yeah if
I I see any more seizuring to be had I'm
going to have a
seizure So today we're going to do
something very very normal we're just
going to play which spring
R um but the thing is so I'm I need to
drink uh energy drinks
today because now it's 400 p.m. I've
been up since let's say 6
hours and
the the amam spelling be is at 2
[Music]
a.m.
so I will not have the
energy I just you know I just need like
two sippas and I'm good but I got an
interesting energy
drink that um
RBF has been
uh recommending to
me and now I'm kind of curious so I'm
going to try it let me show you do you
know the Austrian drink that I told you
about the one that goes I'm
D someone in the mountains goes like
that it's the it's the no not Red Bull
OA is Austrian herbal soft drink fuzz
fizzy fuzzy soft drink and it's pretty
good pretty good I I really like it but
I I want like if I'm sitting somewhere
in a restaurant and I can I'm like
ordering something to drink I will not
order or dla because there's other soft
drinks I like more but this is pretty
good you know now apparently they have
an energy drink now with natural
coffeine and my my RBF cells
uh this tastes like o dla we'll find out
we'll [\h__\h] around and find out this is
the
drink it's probably been around for a
while now I just haven't noticed it cuz
I don't look at the energy drink section
normally but you can tell it's like
obviously the O design made into an
energy drink with mate and guarana
so I want to find out
now I'll just take two zippies now and
then oh we'll find out no I'll drink
more later but just two sipp
now come on I don't want to
spill
okay
the oh it smells like o
Sia
oh
m
n the OA flavor is pretty weak and
there's probably the M I don't know what
that is
the uh in English
M
English what is this uh ah mate wait how
do you pronounce this in English mate
mate not friend no the the
thing uh but it seems to be a thing in
uh is a traditional South American
caffeine Rich infused herbal drink yeah
that's what's in there so you guys know
what that is
right I think that's giving it a a
little a little bit of a bitter weird
flavor but it's it's bearable you can
ignore it and if you think really
strongly about O dudla then this will
maybe just be o
dudla
yeah funny for German speakers the
little the
little uh sign in the middle it's funny
chunky
[Music]
wony okay well this will hopefully wake
me
up can't wake up Wake Me Up
[Music]
Inside okay chunky wony she's been very
clingy lying on my keyboard uh half half
of her body on on my keyboard the whole
day when I'm doing work on the
PC
yeah so yeah yesterday was kind of
shocking and
um no yesterday just didn't happen let's
just pretend yesterday didn't
happen and
today is everything's normal everything
is normal
today I'm just going to
play a nice little game as always jrpg
YooHoo for several
hours who's with
me hello
Chad I didn't get bonked no no no no
no no but I I
just I'm
shocked like
nothing was intentional like I didn't
expect it to be this spicy but like I
mean it's not like I have a choice when
I look like that when I'm hot I can't
help but be hot
and it's you
know it's it can't be helped like I
didn't do anything I was okay I was
twerking a bit for fun because I was
just having so much fun being stupid cuz
I mean I know I can't twerk although
there were some moments where for one or
two seconds it was indeed twerking it
was
twerking but um besides that I was just
messing around and I was just having fun
so can't blame me right I was just
having
[Music]
fun yesterday today's K is yesterday's
Kiana today's Kiana is today's K we are
different people at the moment uh why do
I stop moving so often stop stop stop
moving yeah I was having
fun and it certainly was
something it certainly was a whole
experience wasn't it why do I stop
moving again
I'm restarting the
app
okay are we chilling now oh
o w we're not doing so well in this app
today
[Music]
huh m
um
[Music]
wait I'm changing some settings right
now uh oh oh there we
go mhm
[Music]
ah s
s
okay okay if that uh is not working so
nicely today uh then I'm sorry I will
have to
undress uh but in
on the good
side you can experience this kada
again just trying
[Music]
to
um oh you can see these things when I
show them
I don't know if there's
any like way of opening that menu
without showing
it ah wait actually I had an update but
this is the not updated version I
think oh well
[Music]
insert
ha goodbye hats goodbye no
more no more I feel like don't look at
that wait just I'm goodbye goodbye let
me let me see I feel very very
stiff was that normal
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay but no
hands I don't want
[Music]
to I don't want to set up
the the things right now
[Music]
the okay now this is fine
I wonder there must be a way oh can I
put can I put a PNG on here in this
program let me see where's my where's my
hat here is my hat that's the second hat
let's see if this works how does this
work oh
oh so small hat how do I make it bigger
uh oh like this
slowly but
surely and then I need to bring it
middle click Target to always on how do
I put it behind my
Bonnie how do I put it
behind settings distance to
[Music]
Avatar what
doesn't
change ah it's
[Music]
probably no that doesn't
change
[Music]
huh don't understand this app so
much
wait change size middle Target to always
on top middle click
ah no idea okay maybe no maybe no
hat but uh we can do the cape for
example not the whole dress let's just
do the cape cape should be
easy bigger bigger bigger bigger bigger
bigger bigger bigger bigger biger biger
bigger
okay
yeah that's
[Music]
fine I need a witch hat you recommend a
tiny white one that's not a witch
hat that's not a witch
[Music]
hat
okay all right then we shall begin I had
the game open for a while now does it
show up
[Music]
surely it will show
up wait did I even set it right oh no I
didn't now it's there yay
okay uh let's
go and play the
[Music]
game it's been a while
what do you mean finally it's only been
26 minutes and six of those were loading
screen this is fine this is normal what
are we doing going going to the
snowfield go to snowfield entrance where
is
that and was I supposed to prepare
anything before I
go Maybe not maybe I'm fine snowfield
[Music]
where is where's the
snowfield nothing here looks
snowy ah
there what's the closest
here a yeah we're finding that one ice
witch
yeah ice witch
oh nice ah that was just a healing thing
do I go this
way let's go of let's go of pet Maybe
maybe in a moment what's can I see
the
oh lots of stuff you can backtrack
to well I'm not supposed to be here now
am I although where does this ride take
me again just to the Temple Place thingy
or what's this what's this one this one
is like come later again right oh wait
this is an enemy this is like in the
other like lava temple place or
so it's the source of the water that
flows for illusion Temple the water it
produces nourishes Temple's glad live
it's best to stay away from the
statue
oh oh water jet okay so they're telling
me to not mess with
it any secret items here
no oh
is the game still in Korean ah yeah the
voices may still be in
Korean should we change
it back
to
uh what
Japanese did this change is this how I
want
it I know
yeah it's been
weeks let's see where this takes me
maybe it will get me to the snow
fields doesn't look very snowy is there
more to this is there teleportation here
oh wait that's interesting at
least
Yay see I totally came for that because
I think when the story when the story
brought up here I think they kicked us
out and we couldn't uh explore this
place oh can we can we go down
there
no three or four weeks what yeah know I
know this is where I met my mom I know
that one I know
that now we're adult and we're still
using this like baby carriage to
Traverse for the
water I'm an adult now a grown ass adult
with a grown
ass uh where the [\h__\h] oh oh but the
there's arrows that show me to go to the
top
right maybe it's better to go via here
oh I can teleport so easily
oh wait I didn't I don't think I knew I
could do that Bea the map
hey
y hey what's
[Music]
up
oh he realized I'm older
now what do you mean what do you mean
how did you notice like I got older but
I'm obviously still looking the same I'm
even dressed in like very similar
clothes
I fought everyone in the game with ag
up yeah I think that's what I also
fought but the time didn't pass overall
just we regained our what was it like
our magic power regaining that made us
uh older or
so did you need something from me bro
can I do this
again ah no
okay yeah yeah not maybe not regained I
don't know but anyway that's how we grew
oh
hello this
person just from looking at her like
this looks like she could be from an
aelier
game by the way aelier Sophie is 50% off
on Steam right
now I saw it because I was like looking
through uh steam today a moment
ago who are
you oh she has a
dragon a tiny baby
dragon
[Music]
cute byebye
what we're not going to talk more than
that she's just like oh oh sorry okay
bye what what what that's weird why do
you place that NPC there when we're not
even going to
[Music]
talk it's freezing cold do we have a
winter call
no we have to
go it's called World building um excuse
me princess
chicken and there's something up ahead
let's investigate wow investigation
let's go
oh is that an
animal there's a person it looks like I
don't know an animal to me but it's hard
to see
[Music]
okay
oh is was that the name of the girl
so I'm guessing the spirit is not the
girl that we met before so the spirit is
someone we didn't meet before but
probably the one who froze this guy is
the girl we met
before just put some fire on it fire his
ass up come on
he's like let's turn back second time
already he says that and she's like I
don't give a [\h__\h] I'm a grown ass woman
now
[Music]
woo fire fire light the Ice
Cube another one another one stop stop
stop
Robin he has a
name
oh cute
might take a few more seppies than two
today of the energy
drink even he got some artwork so we
might see him more often than once
yeah I would assume that it's not as
strong as Red Bull but I don't know
where does it say how much is in there
there's a lot of yap yap yap in
there no
idea no time to nap well depends on how
long this is going to be I don't want to
cut it too early we'll
see if I get bored or so
but in theory yeah I would maybe I would
maybe have some time but I'm going to
try to stay awake
because I don't
know I even if I start sto like two
hours before so I'm still going to have
some things to do I'm I realized it's
already [\h__\h] Friday I have no time I
need to get [\h__\h]
done super chats yeah I'll be reading
some super chats for sure
what a realistic young
man I'm I want to make a
[Music]
joke uh he can't possibly be a deserter
game sound gone what
why I'm trying to make a joke right
now if he's in the snow field he can't
be a deserter okay I fixed
it it's generally kind of quiet I
[Music]
think he can't be a deserter cuz he's in
the snow right
now you know
[Music]
yeah it's too
loud well his voice is on the same level
his mine maybe it's
fine
chat is loud
okay lowering it a little
bit Luna that's her name did we know
that what could it be she
wait who did
I
[Music]
no oh
no she's got trust issues now
don't we all have trust issues like when
somebody says like oh I I have trust
issues I've been hurt too many times and
I can't trust people anymore like I feel
like everybody has that
so I
know we all should be generally wary of
people I guess not everybody but
yeah when somebody tells me that I just
want to say well same
[Music]
same but like not even
necessarily like you may assume that oh
trust issues because of love life or so
no like even just like normal [\h__\h] like
people always want
to abuse people's trust a sad sad sad
story
especially when you have valuable
information in your
head they're going to send mind flares
to suck it out of my brain if they could
if they could they
would not tax people
but I take people at face Valley but it
doesn't mean I trust them really
M yeah no no no I I have to be careful
because especially since I joined whole
live everybody wants to be my friend I
have to be careful
this is true it is truth it is
[Music]
truth okay yeah he's a chill dude okay
so I should wait for Luna she came to
the board plane looking for
strawberries speaking strawberries so my
strawberries I told you guys they didn't
have many fruit to be picked and it was
over pretty soon and then nothing seemed
to be growing anymore and my mom also
was like yeah it's over but I kept on
watering them anyway I mean of course I
don't think I should have stopped right
even if it's over but right now I'm
seeing a few more
growing like not like a million just a
few you know it's like a second growth
spurt wow and also while I was in Bella
Italia my mom was taking care of uh my
garden yeah and she picked a
cucumber cuz my mom gave me a cucumber
plant and then I planted it and it was
still pretty small back then but then it
absolutely took over everything cucumber
plants are crazy they go
everywhere and they they have these
little little
arms they have long long strings and
with those strings it's crazy like every
every day I look at the plant the
strings are somewhere else holding on to
something they want to like touch
something and then hold on to it and
then grow over there too you know it's
like trying to reach new places they
grab everything yeah it's so funny but
like it's actually when I ignored it for
a while I I realized yab how do I
untangle this now because it was
absolutely tangled up because of those
Vines the strings it was so tangled and
it wraps itself around something like
several
times it's
crazy that's why my cucumbers are
permanently grounded wait wait wait wait
do you mean like now you saying but is
it a joke or are you saying they're just
on the
ground both could be the
truth yeah yeah it's so funny and uh
apparently uh like I haven't been seeing
much grow there was just like one
cucumber growing out of it and my mom
picked it and it's in my fridge now it's
[\h__\h] huge it's not long it's like
maybe half of the length that a normal
cucumber in the supermarket would be or
or like 2third of it but it's like so
thick it's so thick you would think it's
maybe a zucchini but even thicker than a
zucchini it's it's giry it's super giry
it's there's so much cucumber there I
don't know I want to eat it before I go
but it's just so much [\h__\h] cucumber
how am how am I going to eat this whole
[\h__\h] cucumber before I go to Japan
it's so girf cumber is yeah what a
strange top
I'm I'm I'm just I'm just updating you
guys on my garden make a salad yeah I
want to make a salad but um I guess I'll
make it tonight uh cuz I made some tuna
noodles yesterday and I made so much
that I'm going to eat it yesterday today
and
tomorrow I'll just make a salad to go
with it should be
nice just eat this a snack with some
salt yeah I need to take a picture
before I cut it up it's such a fish fake
cucumber it's amazing but I'm just sad
there's nothing else growing there right
now maybe maybe I got to give it some
time maybe only one cucumber can grow at
a time there's still like these like
fuzzy little buds I guess a lot of them
on the
[Music]
Cucumber some fuzzy little buds I guess
that's where it grows out
of
yeah and then I've got some I've got
some other stuff growing to like
tomatoes uh but like not much there
either I need
more I need
more I'm planning when I'm back from
Japan
maybe I'm going to hire some
professional Garden people to help me
with like garden
design because I don't know it's a lot
of work um and I I feel like I want I
would appreciate some help with that and
then they can maybe plant some more
vegetables
too yeah not really Landscaping not like
not not too much crazy [\h__\h] I just want
them to place uh to plant some stuff and
uh but not too much and um I just want
them to fix some things that I already
[\h__\h] up in my garden cuz it's my first
time being a gardener and I already I
already messed up some
stuff
yeah I did not think that you could mess
up a garden so
quickly cuz like for example I would
have like a plant pot a big fat plant
pot and I thought wouldn't it be nice if
not everything was outside of the grass
what would wouldn't it be nice if you
had some things on the grass so I put
them on the grass and then I realized
after a while when I moved the pot the
the grass underneath was was completely
dead like it was muddy and disgusting
and then after a while even when I
removed it and it dried there's still no
grass growing
back and I did that several times
already I I I did not learn from my
mistake
immediately yeah yeah I'm sure it will
grow back it just takes a long time
right I just need to give it sometime
but I don't know
yeah now it was like suffocating from
the like water too cuz there were there
was a lot of rain and it was just
getting really
disgusting grass bald patches can be
regrown with
seeds yeah I'm probably going to do
something or have something be done
about it I we just do some nice things
I'm I'm thinking wouldn't it be nice
also to have like a little water
fountain for my cats like a tiny one cuz
I I have a water fountain indoors but
I'm thinking it would be nice to have
one uh Outdoors too my chat stopped
moving hello there we
are yeah a birp bath no it's a cat maybe
birds will come too but it's it's for
the
cats
yeah yeah and then decorate it nicely oh
I have some cat uh Na nap nip catnip
catnip catnip catnip catnip
catnip right I should re um replace it
re
um put it around the fountain that will
be put there
relocate around that thing and it will
look really nice I think replanted yeah
m
cuz they actually they have like some
small little flowers the catnip it has
like purplish small flowers and it looks
pretty nice and I think it would look
cute
anyway anyway
strawberries thanks for the tangent
game B be straight edge but her cats
aren't they're not like they forgot
about it like they used it once and then
they forgot about the existence I
haven't seen them rub against it
uh ever
again but I'm
sure should be somewhere here I'm sure
that they'll find it again especially if
it's close to a water fountain I hope
they will use it oh I need to cover it
like I need to give it like a little bit
of a coverage above so that the water in
the water fountain will not be
constantly hot from the Sun ooh we can
be creative with that we can be creative
cuz I don't think they will like it if
it's
hot it should be normal temperature at
least if we could have some kind of
cooling mechanism that would be even
better but maybe it would be cool enough
if it's just
uh like in the
shade oh you're a fake chunky boy aren't
you did I fight you
before Oh I haven't but you're probably
weak as
[Music]
[\h__\h] wait let's not waste my time let's
just
okay swing that one y
2 Hp you [\h__\h] kidding me my plan was
to get a uh another turn cuz when it
dies I get another turn and then I was
just going
to use the one that the the AOE that
hits four of
them mom mommy here this is what I was
trying to
do this
[Music]
two HP in a dream so what about you can
I talk to you
now still
no what about you guys did I fight you I
haven't oh oh I at least I was able to
fight them automatically okay cool
[Music]
MH have not fought
before isn't she supposed to be here is
the board
plane more than just this over here I
guess as well is she here no I was
already here ah oh okay I just had to
walk a few more
meters and then see I didn't go further
because I could see with my own eyes
that she's not
there she looks like
me I like how they look so like similar
and pretty and cute and adorable I love
them hello mhim Moshi
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
girl what
happened ah she sensed the
Warriors she was like I'm out of here
you deal with those [\h__\h] girl
alone okay I will only if you come back
afterwards
M we got
tools four four who all of
[Music]
them
POG real POG moment she I wonder if
physical is okay or decent enough maybe
a triple swing
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay Justice
jce it's Justice
eh never saw her she wasn't here what do
you mean it's just me all
along why are you hallucinating it was
always just
me what do you mean for justice guys
everybody always saying for justice why
for him why what's he's not that special
he's not that like important why is
everybody always saying for justice
these days I wouldn't do it for justice
I wouldn't do anything for
justice wo
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
what how can you not
W come
on
games a lot of games do this it's
obviously still her voice is the same
too color theme is the same bunny ears
are the
same pretty much the same overall
uh what the [\h__\h] is he charging is
charge rifle or what what
the uh
y um
okay should have charged less my man
would be R to see an out version well
but it seems like this world knows that
witches can change their forms and all
that like it's not such a weird thing
for a witch to be a few years older
suddenly I think
[Music]
SK
oh pberry in the water why
[Music]
oh actually now that we're back to
Japanese I don't think we heard her
Japanese adult voice before and I'm
actually liking it a lot more than her
uh child voice so this is a lot more
bearable
anyway yeah I think her the the child
voice I prefer the Korean one and for
the adult voice I don't care like both
are fine but uh this one's this one's
like
definitely more bearable mhm
I like it I like it
before she was
[Music]
like that's what she was
like not help you wa
no
no no
[Music]
H
noise that's kind of somehow that isn't
that kind of fourth wall breaking you
see a teleportation Altar and you assume
okay if there that's if that's there
that means there's something important
in this dungeon like very important yeah
very meta
what
what I did not even expect to see any
other witch
girl anymore now we suddenly see a new
cute bunny girl witch girl showing up
what the
[\h__\h]
what she is so cute what the [\h__\h] what
she's a
God wait is she wait wait wait wait wait
EV uh Every Witch is a God so now she
calls other witches just Gods by default
or
what right okay okay
okay she's so she's so cute I like her
hair oh my God and also she can golf she
can play golf with her witch stick the
bottom of it is basically golf stick and
if she takes out the the the big okay
it's a little bit too big but if she
takes out the ball in the middle of her
stick then she can play golf with that
it's a bit too big but still she's so
cute oh my
[Music]
God
C wait she's probably if we do fire
magic the other girl does um ice magic
maybe this one does water magic if they
differentiate that
cuz she looks
[Music]
blue hocky yeah yeah yeah yeah hockey
golf whatever same
thing this cave I entered to escape
Justice this no it's a bit strange I
found a teleportation alar and a child
DT I've never seen before as soon as I
entered let's explore the cave oh my
God
qule oh my God oh my God
this is crazy
guys oh what the
[\h__\h] do we know this
guy he looks uh very very well
armored who immediate
attack okay pberry hold your
horses is the other girl going to help
us oh oh maybe not maybe we're on our
own
ouch
9,000 over 9,000
what was this
again ah oh I have to activate
this
[Music]
ah okay
pets uh for
fre mow
[Music]
oh only a
thousand it's a pass of ability really
it looks like I have to activate it
though in order for it to ever take
effect
it's been a while but I'm not forgetting
that in between the battle I can ask my
little burp to help me
[Music]
out what should we
take maybe this one this is good 140 HP
I don't need that much that's okay and
then uh 200
MP I need that that's
perfect and then
we let's try with this one
okay about the
same it activates automatically ah okay
okay so I don't have to activate it it
looks like I would have to cuz it's in
the
menu like
that wait now we have we have
the we have
the crit uh which one of these doesn't
take up a turn again
this one right let's do the crit of the
[Music]
arrow did that crit I don't know no it
didn't because it doesn't take up a
turn uh we can do thises this what uh no
maybe
not we could do the magic storm
[Music]
try here we go
Kap oh wait that wasn't the ah that
wasn't the crit what what was the thing
on the very right side or maybe that's
just a sign for uh something has charged
in the special
skills Al so now is ooh I forgot okay
we'll just go with uh he's almost dead
anyway even even without a crit we could
be
fine y 3D model
yay you like this 3D WWA this is the
first time I've used it since I revealed
it immediate recovery in the
back not a stretch PE
now is when that girl comes out to save
me
right
right right
wait is this actually the girl she just
like shape shifted in a like buff
Warrior that'd be
fun be
funny cuz they're both like blueish but
nah
no no no way must be funny though
wow
huh kill him kill him
no nobody is being killed in this game
so probably you're
fine so you want to recruit him
it's for justice
[Music]
right I'm trying to make a joke you will
have the last word
before you will see the last of this
sword
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
not going to happen
jce maybe management played this
game and they were like just like him
Justice a good name we should name our
next Generation that
the blue one is advent suppose
so it
girl I want more
violence you got
another new
grill what and she's
hot as
[\h__\h] uh is this narissa wait this looks
like
narissa this is
narissa narena
Nena I do I still have my oh oh
[Music]
oh oh my God oh my
God oh my God this is like narissa from
another
timeline like she has the same color
famee like also with black and and and
white white blouse and stuff oh my God
this is narissa Alter
wow I want I want her to see this and
like it's it hits even stronger because
they're fighting Justice right
now and they're like the opposing
side it's Canon
I love her I love
[Music]
her I will join the death
squad I will join
Advent take out all the
cuties
OMG there she is the cute small one that
plays
hockey the death squad yeah it's a bad
PR name like that's intimidating and it
sounds
evil maybe they mean the death of of the
the evil but well that's not not good PR
[Laughter]
indeed yeah it should be more
like salvation Squad you know you're the
secret society who opposed the pope
right wow that is well drawn
fairin we risk our lives for a dream of
a better world I am Vin the leader of
Des I'm Pineberry and love pie and
strawberries that's so funny to me
H best of
fendo the enemy of my enemy is my best
of
fendo fore
[Music]
to so many cute
girls what can I
do those pants are so so
cool
halfway cut
halfway through cut flare pants out of
leather oh my
God
okay
[Music]
for
for oopsie I'm going to do automatic now
and eat some
Patos assed
amazing no I only seen
Nissa ow only
seen experimental nuke supposed to be
like a reference to Nuke I don't know
[Music]
strong forap
a good man a good
King now we just hear about the king
now for
[Music]
this is a Game of
Thrones we're slowly Gathering several
parties into an
army some crazy [\h__\h]
like instead of dragon
well okay the tut okay because of
the thank membership
welcome so we have to go get
her I don't give a [\h__\h] he can die and
rot in that cave
Forma but pie be is pretty Savage
generally
so maybe her wanting to go and see she
just wants to point and laugh at
him I could see that honestly she's
really Savage
pberry loves strawberry and pie but she
hates weakness so she hates
Justice it's that
simple cracking those
nuts with my bare
hands my bare fingers
one more just one
[Music]
more
M maybe one
more yeah
crashing them is cool and all but what
would be more hardcore is if I ate them
with the
shell oh my God new friends where did
the witch
go the sweat we shed today will be the
blood our enemies shed on the
battlefield wow that's a mantra I made
up to encourage the squad members very
violent but for some reason verin
doesn't seem to like
it he doesn't want to be as
violent is all of this their
headquarters
shees who the [\h__\h] are
[Music]
they oh another
executor have I fought this fought this
one before the outfit is familiar but
I've never seen her before she has
barely any magic Evo what a mistake is
she dying it would seem so unfortunately
that poor girl brainwashed and then sent
out to fight others without even knowing
why yeah cuz uh executors are witches
brainwash witches right was
that what that
was they didn't even put him in a cell
is this
more like condescending than being in a
Cell I don't know it's funny they can
just put him into the
cell oh yeah right she does have like
kind of a crush on
him and now he realizes it's
her right away it's not right away girl
it's been
ours
basically but okay girl cope cope
because you like
him no what the [\h__\h] it looks the
same so so yes
oh this is some gimron level torture
let's go let's go now now kill some of
his family right in front of him while
he's chained up do it do it bar I know
you want
to
oh just by somebody getting closer to
you you're like kill
me social social distance is very
important to this
guy
cabon what kind of cabon is
God what what is
this oh no she actually punched him she
actually punched him just
now but punching she's trying to like
make him be like get yourself together
right but if you want to do that don't
you just slap them but she just punches
him it's pretty brutal
girl you're just trusting what people
say the the rumors that they're
spreading you don't even know oh for
sure you're you're ba like basing
basing everything you're doing off of
one room or you heard
brainwash extreme
[Music]
fore fore
oh no oh no oh no oh
no you know what this
means Shion Senai is in
danger Shion Senpai is in danger keep
Justice away from Shion Senpai at any
cost
hot is she un undoing the thing
no what did she
do all right she shut him up
[Music]
okay she called me sire
is it
really maybe
she she's not even a grown ass woman yet
like I
am oh
you're good girl you're not that much
weaker than I am
[Music]
I wonder if she calls you UN in Korean
oh could be yeah that would be
[Music]
cute
for for
[Music]
cute oh we got raided
by oh now I see
it look at this cute girl
everybody look at all these cute girls
guys
hello we're having cute girl time right
[Music]
now I am a Senai of this cute girl can
you believe
it welcome
welcome yes I'm playing wit spring
[Music]
see you later right at the
spelling maybe you going to get some
sleep in between I'm going to stay away
go sleep louder sleepy time
[Music]
she's so cute oh my
God finally it's time to find Kaa I fin
finally found the death squad that Kana
was looking for and heard the news about
kana's father she was so happy to know
this y
yah was taed out
okay is this related to little wiin bet
no not at
all but it might be a better game
overall is there something there I feel
like I saw something
ah does that heal no it was the stats
upgrade okay so so
so wait where is Ka at Matt's house uh
the the hidden
house but wait where are we now
is this down here leads
to vilia
Road okay I think we just teleport to
Matt's house but I'm kind of curious
about this
connection is there something
[Music]
here
no okay yeah the trees they all have
that one hole there's must be a lot of
owls or wood Pickers I don't know true
they they all have that one exact one
yeah that's all it's all the same
tree it
is I didn't even notice that until now
you have a good
eye hey
yo ooh they're looking
[Music]
strong
10,000 giant Palace go him honestly I
could probably kill them but story-wise
I don't think I I'm supposed to do that
yet 10,000s we had stronger way stronger
enemies
before okay um Matt's
house which is
out where was
that ah there but I can't go there so
I'll go here
yeah I fought 40K enemies before Mama
Mia that's
crazy U there's no teleportation to
their house right so I got to walk I
think what's the how do I get
there I don't remember is it this way
no is it this
way I need to use a key which one ah
this one ah is that way I always have to
choose the
[Music]
key wait this is where I need to go
right ah there she is she's so cute look
at her
Ka
hello she doesn't remember me come on
we've talked several times you should
realize that I'm just an older version
of
myself okay for people who haven't
followed our playthrough uh in the last
time I played this game through gaining
more magic and becoming more powerful we
have grown up into an adult now people
are acting like I look completely
different I want to see Ka grown
up can we make her grow up
too yeah teenager not adult I
guess I
guess yeah I'm bigger than you you
little
[Music]
[\h__\h]
Bro all within the game it's all within
the game we hate the pulp in the
game and we want to kill the pulp in the
[Music]
game let's
go let's [\h__\h]
go wasn't there
tell
too of course an evil
one not
a it's something
religious Prett
Comm the Angel that's that's basically
the
[Music]
she s so
happy it's a pink [\h__\h] robot let's
go really bad at camouflaging this
one won't be able to hide that one in
the wood like they did in H
[Music]
O Let's with all my Game of Thrones
references can't help it I'm so
excited next
episode cotton candy it looks like it's
a Cotton Candy Factory
[Music]
itself C
what are you doing
here
finally he finally moved from that one
spot did you like a certain scene from
the last episode so I already talked
about this a little bit on I think
Tuesday but yeah uh people were kind of
like telling me without spoilering me
that I would like this
episode um and that alone even though
there was no other hint really
beforehand that alone made me speculate
in my head that you know that what
happened might happen I'm not going to
say what but what happened at the end of
that episode I thought that could
possibly happen just because people were
saying oh you going to like this episode
I'm
[Music]
like oh there was hints well I wouldn't
say hint like I think like they could
have uh easily gone through the season
and the whole story without having that
happen but it happening does make kind
of sense I
mean not because she seems to be
interested in that but just because they
definitely were really you know hitting
it off and getting closer and they were
vibing they were definitely vibing
yeah yeah and yeah I watched the uh
recap from uh Al shift the guy who makes
really indepth reviews of these uh
episodes and seasons and all that and so
it wasn't in the book at all
but
uh now there wasn't even a hint was
there there wasn't but that's okay
that's that's believable because overall
the book is is just a few a few rough
notes so the details aren't in
there chat you you're spoilering it
you're spoilering it yes
spoiler it wasn't scripted which is
something we like don't we we like
unscripted
things but then Al shift yeah I like the
way he breaks it down but Ali mentioned
you know the whole vibe alicent and
had when they were
younger saying that there was some kind
of vibe there I don't know about that I
don't really I don't think I felt that
but when he says it it makes
sense you know what I mean know you know
what he
[Music]
means H yeah no there was no Sexual
Energy was
[Music]
there was there I'd have to rewatch it
they did say that behind the
scene ah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah the actors mentioned that there was
not quite Sexual Energy but like some
kind of like spiciness there
maybe
mhm so they're the actors are coming up
with stuff
now a chemistry yeah a
[Music]
chemistry h
so yeah I I
I I don't know hot woman hot so I appr
prob but I don't know if it really fits
into the
story hot hot women
[Music]
hot you know I don't know but I I prob
but does it fit does it fit I don't know
we'll see we'll see how they how they're
going to
move along with that what movie is this
we're talking about House of the
Dragon Game of Thrones uh prequel
[Music]
show yeah hotwoman hot speaking of
hotwoman
hot
Italians M beautiful I saw so many hot
women in
[Laughter]
Italy uh but yeah that's uh unrelated
[Music]
what did you get
her for
[Music]
Golems bro we don't just like rent out
golems do we look like a [\h__\h] rent a
Golem place to you or
what
huh so what you have a battle upcoming
or what
[Music]
afterwards
game post game
content do you think
likes
visitations want to take her to one
[Music]
I don't think she had a chance to talk
about that yet possibly she likes on
[Music]
no
I I went I went to a few on now but I
still don't really like them that much I
prefer going to like a spa uh Resort
kind of place with pool and massage and
stuff rather than an on
[Music]
unless it's like a really private one
where just I will be but that's
[Music]
rare was it illegal to trade with
witches
[Music]
you just don't like other other people
saying a nak right boss
yes and I don't like seeing other people
naked
either like I just I just really
struggle with like where the [\h__\h] am I
supposed to look when there's so many
naked people around if it's only like
one or two then I can still avert my
gaze but in the few experiences the one
with narissa they it was so
crowded it was so crowded with naked
people I didn't know where to look and
also I I noticed they were looking at me
and I don't want that I don't like that
no
no please stop looking European card
revoked H just because you're European
doesn't mean you like to be naked but I
have um you know with s with saas saas I
have the same issue but I've been going
to SAS more in the past
years and kind of getting over it also
this past weekend um I was in a I was
staying for a few nights in a hotel room
with my best
friend
and I made her boyfriend uh uh stay with
someone else so that I could be with a
girl in a
room but they gladly separated from me
so um I stayed in the hotel room with
her the whole uh trip and
um and yeah we we just because the room
was small and I don't know we got we
changed cloes so many
times so we ended up being
like kind of you know you know bare
breast a a few times and I did not give
any [\h__\h] anymore but that's with her
okay I mean I wouldn't like I I still
like kind of covering them and like
turning away from her but at least I
wouldn't like go into a different room
all the time and then on the first day
when she Unleashed her boobies I
right in front of me and like still
talking to me I was like like looking
away while talking to her but on the
last day we made progress by by the time
of the last day when she did that I was
looking straight at
her while having a conversation when she
was be breasted so there was some
progress
made but that's my besty
so you know
that's my
besti you have strangers it's a
different
story what does this have to do with on
hello are you listening talking about
how I deal with naked people it has very
much
bre it has a lot to do with that
oh what about Hollow Man and no I'm
still very weird about that like the
other day I was in a
3D uh in in the 3D Studio and I was
supposed to change into the suit while
somebody else was changing out of it and
I was like nope nope nope nope nope nope
nope nope n you go first you go
first so yeah I I I waited until she was
done so that I could get started because
yeah I wasn't even wearing a bra so yeah
anyway
shaio I'll be the same good
yeah all the Ian girls were like that
right not all of them but a lot of the
Ian girls I think would definitely
prefer to change alone but if they were
put into a situation where they end up
being in the same room at the same time
changing then a lot of them would maybe
just be okay with it but they would
prefer to be alone I would say most of
them H but not everybody is as strict
about it as I
am yeah yeah not
nisso I think it's mostly a myth thing
to be so
shy yeah I do think I do think uh guda
and am would prefer to change
alone uh I don't know about Ena to be
honest if she cares that much
Callie also is uh not so yeah I mean she
goes to the onson so much she doesn't
care yeah and I think by now she's been
in changing rooms for 3D with other
Japanese members and so on so many
times more than
me so
yeah yeah yeah Kell's
fine Ena seems to keep private things
private
yeah same same same same
same myth grills are reserved mostly
yeah mostly that's true we're a very
introvert
[Music]
generation introvert or shy people don't
think or believe that I'm an introvert
too but I one thing you cannot deny is
I'm shy and
it's more shy about my body than I am
about human interactions because I'm I'm
good at human interactions but it
doesn't mean that I like to interact I'm
just really good at it because I know
how to cope and handle that
stuff but but I'm I need so much like
recharge after human interactions and
I'd rather stay at home for months at a
time without meeting anybody I'm fine
like there's so many people who need to
meet up with their friends at least once
per week or so but if if everything's
like just chilling then I will stay at
home with my cats for for months with no
problem I don't need to meet anybody I
just want to be with myself and my
cats so yeah I think
that's what defines an extrovert if you
crave interactions with people I do not
crave it at
all the opposite
I'm good at it
[Music]
though cat lady I am the crazy cat lady
yes
proudly Okay so we've been like intering
this guy several times but this red
beard guy is trying to
[Music]
smuggle r Jewel through trading with
witches I
[Music]
suppose ah now he has it and he wants to
give it to them
[Music]
she's she she's like oh too bad we can't
go anywhere right now I wonder who else
could go in my
place looks at pie
Berry
[Music]
M we have the red gem
text box was not finished as much as you
want was supposed
[Music]
to
oh what if I just take that and craft it
into something
[Music]
e
for Fore
speech fore
[Music]
for
for I want to go
[Music]
gambling what
you okay so
uh Mountain that sounds
snowy sounds like we're going back to
the
[Music]
snow okay okay but before we move on I
want to quickly I don't know I got
distracted and I I want to do this whole
time I'm going to
switch the uh into the
updated model that has
[Music]
eyebrows
okay should this should
yeah let's go
I've got eyebrows again you guys are
going to like
[Music]
these okay
where is some oh
okay
yay oh but I look down too much
[Music]
H
okay
ta
eyebrows secret controls
eyebrows Angry
Eyebrows pan
eyebrows shook it
[Music]
eyebrows
y frog ribbit he
yes smug oh smug is so
good very nice
okay let's
go let's go let's go let's go let's
go nice
yes
smug where were we and we're going to go
to Southeast laak Forest where the [\h__\h]
there's so many laak forests it's so
confusing uh can I teleport to where
where wherever we need to
[Music]
go Southeast but I can't okay I'm just
going to I'm just going to walk
all
[Music]
right
ah no not the
hats can you raise one eyebr can
I
no they're
connected
no maybe that's one more
thing yeah that's one more thing we
could fix adjust
[Music]
why did you
mention oh do we get money again oh my
God this is endless money hack over
here
crazy
[Music]
and oh the kids are here again
come on come on you
[Music]
know so cool I
mean would
say no no no no
[Music]
foree
for foreign
[Music]
oh
no
gorilla oh yeah looking to the side
weird I thing is fixed too
can you tell when I looked to the side
in the previous version it had this
white thing in my eye but now it's
gone
Yahoo yay yeah it it kept on bothering
me when I looked over so I needed to fix
it ooh the poison
berries so now we go northeast we can
walk there
too a nice little walk in the park
and some head shot in
between boom head
shot Get
Wrecked 360 no
scope is this northeast
yes Northeast Northeast big gorilla
there it
is but we we didn't fight us
[Music]
before do they mean as a as an adult
maybe cuz I'm pretty sure we fought this
guy before no
[Music]
holy
bunino are you
insane oh he literally just needs one
more Bonk
[Music]
okay we pulled out some hair too but the
isn't the grass basically his hair I
feel like it's the same
thing but she's already back to
[Music]
normal cute
this is this is the the grown-up cute
girl version of the small laala fell
people uh it's so cute I like it she
still has that leaf on the top of her
head like a leaf
Aug
fascinating M yeah it does give M
Vibes grown up potato
yeah eat some laala Fells with some
Hummers let's
go oh what did look so cute holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay wait to wear
this C the designers of this game are so
goat holy
[Music]
macaroni new outfit yeah but only within
the city where we need to
hide we are it we can even swim naked in
the Stream what what
what oh oh what are you implying we swam
naked together
already I don't remember
that
what we were just talking about stuff
like that yeah
[Music]
can I change
now
[Music]
fore
for I'm out
[Music]
you I like the hats she has
have my cat looking around for the
intrud that reminds me I watched the
video today I think on
Twitter I think it was on Twitter or
what may have been a YouTube short um
about a Brazilian prison using geese as
instead of hounds dogos to alert people
when somebody's trying to
escape because it makes so much sense
it's so smart they just honk at every
movement of people and you don't have to
train them or like take special care of
them uh as you need with the
doggos and they're they're even louder
and even more reliable when it comes to
that aggressive honking honk honk honk
honk yeah it's
[Music]
amazing those must be Canadian GE I
don't know they're in
Brazil go to Brazil
GE taking dog jobs I know I think it's
actually so
genius they're they're less work less
money cuz like training those dogs I'm
sure those dogs are more expensive
too how do they deal with annual
migration no idea I guess they imprison
the geese
well that's kind of funny though for
real cuz they're in a prison
already poor geese
man probably CLI their wings oh my God
that's
terrifying oh H informed Sarah that Anna
had passed away
[Music]
I forgot that she was
gone but that makes sense yeah I
remember the
[Music]
she kind of ruined that emotional moment
for me
rest in pie rest in [\h__\h]
pie imagine pberry watching Anna die
slowly both are sad really sad sad music
playing sad faces and then she's
like rest in
pie that little [\h__\h]
[Music]
and then you would hear
a I thought I was over it but my grief
for Anna is still deep in my heart rest
in pie I should visit her house for the
first time in a while and see if there's
any pie left
over this girl only things about pie
understandable I'm on point today right
I
[Music]
know cute oh my God this one's so
different from the other one I thought
they would make a really similar one but
this is so different from the other
disguise I like it it's cute nice cute
super cute holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] it's so
cute the ye the the the the the
really like low
saturated uh yellow with the pastel blue
is so pretty with the dark brown oh my
[Music]
God where are we going on this house
where was it again up down left
right not here it was
up don't mind me
guys probably this
[Music]
way cute aggression is
strong but who will I have pie with no
no no she's more like who will make pie
for me now what the [\h__\h] you can't just
die now you got a pie
now pie now Anna no Die Pie what the
[\h__\h] you turned the D the wrong way
around it's turn it around again if you
turn the D how many
degrees and it's going to be pie just
turn it around don't
die amazing
[Music]
amazing I'm on a roll baby and I cannot
find where we're supposed to go this way
maybe we can descend
here this is this place
yeah that's not where I want to
go oh but the the wait we can teleport
to
um here and then from there we can
teleport but they gave me the outfit for
a reason so that I can walk there again
and I'm not walking
there wait was is this the one no it was
desolate
Hill they have a grave there now
[\h__\h] oh
[Music]
spee fore
H yeah [\h__\h]
[Music]
you stupid
excuses
fore fore
fore
okay Dam
an
[Music]
it's like you only appreciate her when
too late when she's [\h__\h]
[Music]
dead should have had her back when she
was
[Music]
alive for
okay yeah I guess they tried but
still gentle pie maker sleeps here why
is it capitalized like this like
GPM
what what
P that's her real
name yeah why what why it's like a title
No write her actual freaking name
though that's so
weird at least write both the name and
the title
GPM goed pie
machine Express GPM
that's that's
weird seems almost like
a I don't know maybe reference or
something
pie
p oh
[Music]
don't be don't be like that
man what the [\h__\h] let's get out of here
it's too
sad where are we
going uh I know
what do you say like the the sky is
sweating or
so or there sweat from my eyes
[Music]
what is this not
voiced this that's this lot of text why
is not
[Music]
voice Steam your high elasticity spring
as much as you
can fighting the
traps oh right I wasn't supposed to go
to her I was supposed to tell ver about
her a
mistake
mistake what I need to open it to get
through back as
well death squad
[Music]
uh uh
uh
[Music]
uh uh the bors near the bors uh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
ah
ah ah found
it why don't they show the like a marker
that I have to go
there
brah come on please help me out here
give me a break
[Music]
this is
epic who look at her she's like doing a
little magic circle thingy over there
everybody's practicing getting ready
Co um I wouldn't call it that
what do you mean you never thought about
layering magic circles we did that for
our
[Music]
spells person isn't here I'm bored so
maybe I should look at Justice
instead trigger him a little bit
more with
[Music]
love wake up what if he's
dead everybody thought he was sleeping
but he was sleeping for so long and then
I realized H wait he's been sleeping for
like 48 hours should he be awake by now
well I think he's maybe dead oopsie
[Music]
that would be nice that'd be
fun oh welcome back what a good
timing
fore fore
fore
[Music]
foree
fore for
[Music]
you can do it little girl
oh yeah she keeps on escaping
me we met her a long time ago and today
again we only for short
moments everybody's yapping
about m
show me to
him a
key thanks for the Super
[Music]
Chat a pistach are so good
convenient spee
[Music]
and
then
okay I can do
[Music]
this I can find the
directions South and then
[Music]
West
okay let's get out of here
whoa she's got far in this short time
with drawing this stuff what are you
guys about to
[Music]
shoot looking nice
girl and she's doing all of that with
her bare hands how can she draw such
perfect
circles how's she do it
[Music]
H is this all I have to go uh South okay
well the they're showing me a marker
anyway let's get out of
[Music]
pet so then we're a little bit
faster are we going to the entrance that
we saw earlier
today with the big big enemy that we
were like oh I can fight this oh yeah
oh yeah it seems like
[Music]
it what the
[\h__\h] hums is this cutie now what the
[\h__\h] they're still bringing out
more oh my
God another
one but she is enemy look how bouncy she
is yes I am on a God I am God on a god
what do you want from
me you mean nice because you were just
looking for me
h h
[Music]
why evil why
evil oh she won't fight
[Music]
all right bring it
on easy look at
that
1,600 are you for real like you can't do
[\h__\h] how many are free
okay
wait can't just because of the the way
the spreads I can't get all of them
sadly
[Music]
warms beautiful pathetic
worms you want to give it a try let's
fight come on
girl I would be delighted no she's being
[Music]
what being treated
ni got
[Music]
on you guys think that's funny I must I
must save her
I must save
her I must add her to my collection of
cute
girls okay there's no other path around
it so it seems like we have to go here
now let's go I'm not healed however so
that's going to be fun
I think I can survive one
round oh this hits all of them let's
go
nice have
EG the giant Palace Golem that's all you
got
what did you you put all of your skill
into HP and defense what the
hell
patic
[Music]
though he's charging
okay the magic thingy charged I I do
think it's it means that one of these
things charged probably let's do the
arrow take up a
turn
and M
[Music]
stor and he's pretty much
dead a I didn't even get to my Critical
Hits beautiful more strong enemies
please
more ooh nice Bridge
wow definitely dangerous to stand
here or here or here or
here or there or there or there or there
or
there or or
there but besides that marvelous
Bridge would you like to disguise
yourself as a human and walk among the
Warriors No I want to just kill them can
I not is that not an
[Music]
option they don't give a
[\h__\h] wait what was
that are we going to stay here we can't
leave our post hm she was so cute oh my
god oh
oopsie I'm already disguised am I not no
oh I did change immediately
okay
oopsie are are they going to make
comments again
no can I not bring out my pets to ride
it out here I assume
yeah okay makes sense but this place is
[Music]
Big Su sorry please let me
through that
illustration I need to go here there's
too many cute
illustrations you guys didn't even see
the full cuteness of that Michelle
girl foree
imagine the rest of the
dialogue two large SES of magic are
colliding don't Magic in the direction
of my mom's Temple let's hurry
over P
panu run run run run run
run now we can
summon
[Music]
us let's
go
executed EX
oh was
he
oh thank you that's actually nice sounds
like a
plan but as long as you don't kill her
just set her free as in not
killing is she
dead she was such a pretty
[Music]
oh damn she's gone rest
in foree
[Music]
that was very
s what
the nice
fret uh you get two red beards lir i eh
to get I can't read to get to Redbeard's
Lair I have to go for vilia Village I
have the close from s so nobody should
notice me as long as I'm careful so
we're going back again okay but what's
over there what else is
there holy [\h__\h] this who makes a bridge
like that going up and down and up and
down that's only fun if you're like I
don't know on a scooter or skate
skateboard and you guys could very well
be on a skateboard if if you guys go to
omocat uh.com or
so and get yourself a nice little fancy
takanashi kiar skateboard and then you
also could
be happily sliding up and down uh a
bridge like that which is a very common
bridge that you can find
anywhere uh I'm trying to find the
picture that I saved from the skateboard
to add onto my plug there it
is wouldn't you love to go up and down
Hills like this it's so fun going up may
be a little bit exhausting but once you
go down with the wheels of my fire
skateboard you will forget all the
exhaustion and pain you had to go up
here and will'll only be feel feeling
the freedom and the
and refreshing wind and of going down
the hill enjoy and then maybe at the end
you can just do a flip try a flip become
Tony Hawk
[Music]
himself now available on omoc cat.com
takanashi Kiana skateboard and many
others
does it come with wheels I'm not sure
maybe not but I mean wheels are easy to
uh acquire at I don't know Home Depot or
so I don't [\h__\h]
know yeah you can be Tony Hawk literally
from chicken to
Hawk Tony chick Tony Phoenix
H wow wow wow wow wow wow wow random
plug I am a business lady after
all no wheels sow but yes it is very
versatile you can use your skateboard to
snowboard down this hill as well and you
could even go to some Dunes Dunes Dunes
Dunes dunes and go down the stand Hills
as well any kind of terrain any kind of
biom is suitable for the takanasi Kiana
waa
board go get it now oh this is this
place
oh
co remember
[Music]
guys
wow all connecting
[Music]
now oh it definitely works you can go
down to sandun yeah
yes you
can damn it I already changed
again all the biom is yeah you can even
use it as a
surfboard I
think all the
elements fire the elements
lava lava also
works I
think
oh
wow I
music guys he it or is it too quiet
we're so close to assassinating the pope
like it's he's right there but we're not
going to do it
[Music]
what did I say that was out of
context barely I'm being in the game
today I don't think so like last time
you guys were still saying I was so far
from the end
[Music]
oh
oh hey you hear the news you're talking
about how most of the Warriors sent to
lak Village have returned was there some
kind of demon or another evil witch why
else would the palace's Warriors go
somewhere so far who cares with the pop
protecting us who cares if what shows up
I'm just curious that's all in the early
days of the witch hunts they used to
burn witches in the Square almost every
day how fun but we haven't had such
treat such a treat in
I wonder is that how how they fought in
Medieval ages to I mean certainly they
were like somewhat happy to see a witch
burnt on the steak just because evil is
being
destroyed but would they see it as
something to look forward to and event
that you would call a treat I'm not sure
about
that you think it was
entertainment h
I wouldn't go that far certainly they
were not unhappy about it but
[Music]
entertainment well we will never
know public executions were sometimes I
mean yeah there's always people
Gathering and they're
like like you know wow wow wow making a
racus but it's not the same kind of
entertainment that's in like a theater
watching a nice play
I would
say not quite not the same
Vibe oh what do you have
oh
[Music]
my
wait I'm having a never right moment
right
now not never right you when my is
real is my real is my
real no okay because obsidian yeah cuz
I'm thinking like I heard it in Lord of
the Rings and now I hear it here again
does it mean it's
real okay no but why are you laughing if
it comes up twice and and and I had the
obsidian thing before it's not weird for
me to now be like eh
are we having another obsidian
moment okay so they took it from here
from lot of the
[Music]
Rings um ooh this is where I can spend
my money huh is it worth it I wonder can
I make better
[Music]
stuff wow high rank Warrior Shield
70,000 gold
[Music]
120,000 gold okay I can afford and this
is 40,000 so this is Step plus 70 this
is 60 magic resistance 12 uh 15 15 12
honestly this is way cheaper and it's
not that different I wouldn't say 3% is
that crazy of a
difference should we get the 40,000
gold
one I used the money to buy stat items
from
rph I think I bought a couple but I
didn't want to over
bu it does I think yeah cuz it's blue
that means it's
better wait let me check something
though no
[Music]
ah 15 magic resistance 10 physical
resistance
40 40
death this
means wouldn't it be red on the magic
resistance if it means um if the base is
zero and it it adds 15 on my current
armor but it adds 12 on this armor does
it mean 15 + 12 because it's blue you
know what I
mean cuz wouldn't it be red if it was
the base + 12 do you know what I
mean or or it's
penalty when it's red it's
penalty
really but then in any case it's not
that much better than what we have
this would be a bit more of a difference
I don't
know I have to think about
[Music]
it yeah they're not factoring in the
current gear I think just going by base
stats yeah I'm I'm fine I'll C C
something again when
I when I have stuff to
craft okay
potions
armor just normal everyday
stores what's this normal house
treasure 5,000 I like this bed it's cute
but I would put the head of it against
the wall it's
weird I'm I'm strong
enough
checkpoint what brings you here um well
um you entered without permission didn't
you eh that's okay my heart is always
wide open for
you ha how many times do I have to tell
you that's not how you do it allow me to
apologize for my for my initial
impression but your beauty has
penetrated even my
thake what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] isn't she like how old is she now
and also that's so
Random how about we talk more over some
tea why is everybody so in love with me
now this is not the first
one Mama
Mia I'm sure that will change when you
see the face beneath my haml prepare
yourself I said no thank you no I want
to see it
though Woman these days oh shut up you
oh sorry hey but take off your helmet I
want to
see I would like to see
that oh oh
oh hello hello
yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep
yep the Witch Hunter is declared
[Music]
over what the witch is almost captured
it's the perfect time to sign up you can
get a share without even having to
find I'm sure they know that there's at
least me still out there so I don't
think they would declare the
hunt over for real
maybe publicly they would do that to at
least make it seem like they're doing
well they don't want to lose face right
by constantly failing to get this one
child
witch where did she get those
clowns they just arrived from laak
Village they what I told the car driver
to let me know if any
stuff came in you mean the same car
driver who used to argue with the
Warriors every time he came by uh yeah
how' you know that idiot got thrown out
for arguing with the Warriors that's why
the news is so late so I was the only
idiot who had no
idea oh my God ew why am I wearing such
an old fashion item from one week
ago when there's already the newest
Gucci dress out there and you're wearing
it [\h__\h] I hate
[Music]
you ah this is the
one I found that key in the back
alley 10,000 gold or was it aund wait a
was that 100,000 just
I feel like it may have was it
10K oh
really okay that's still
good anything else no
[Music]
mind
cleanser I am a little thief doing some
fing you know what this reminds me of
this
place T of
arise the place where the dad got
[Music]
executed giving me similar
Vibes oh wow under the
bar see he still he sees me as a
kid so why are these Knights hitting on
me
bro wait where am I supposed to go
there's also something
[Music]
there all right attention everybody my
name is Robert at mid-rank Warrior I'm
your instructed today for what I would
like to begin you giving by giving
thanks for the peace to and prosperity
in of our village R God of creation
thank you for granting us divine power
and prosperity amen you've done all this
through your faithful servant Salvage
the last
proit wait is Salis like Jesus
what now that prayers have been
concluded today's subject is the
continental shield does anyone know what
a continental shield is H who doesn't
even sh even children know that the
entire front of wall of the Pop's Castle
is in the shape of a crucifix
Shield H I suppose I started off too
easy but do you know why the front of
Pop's Castle is shaped that
way uh to signify that is something
solid that will never fall because the
pop is strong d uh well actually uh the
true meaning of The Shield requires a
little deeper thinking that giant Shield
signifies not only the Pope's will to
protect everyone in this Village but
also his mission to protect the entire
continent and Beyond and
Beyond oh that's
right I like how the flag is not blowing
in the wind at all while the people on
the bottom are still
moving that's right the pope seeks to
protect us not just himself indeed which
is why even the dragons dare not leave
the sou in haunts to harass harass his
Village cuz they're currently busy being
casted and acting out House of the
Dragon actually the pope did not take up
a sword but chose a shield instead and
in his hand a staff to Bear the weight
of his mission let us give thanks for
his grace long long let above long let
above long live the kingdom of ailia
with prosperity of all for all long live
long the
king hey
man hey man that's not cool hey man
[Music]
and shall we walk over for
here the blue sky is the P's Grace and
the water drops comprising the clouds
are our people what what do you think
it's my entry photo's poetry contest oh
isn't it a little short I was aiming for
impact you know short and
sweet I think it's a little too
generic what's that supposed to mean
this listen up I'll [\h__\h] you up man with
my poetry
slam in the world of Darkness your magic
creates a spark Str SP a light at which
everyone
Marvels but I know your true self is not
in the candle flame but in the melting
Candlestick uh okay what do you think
what a lousy
metaphor hey you better watch your mouth
we'll see who's laughing when the result
comes
out they have a poetry slam
contest wow
not going to e drop uh at them cuz
they're probably just talking about nice
dresses
again don't
[Music]
care what's now what's
next how has it been only three hours it
feels like I've been playing for 5 hours
[Music]
TBH water water water let's
go you were just saying that really
water water water
or look over there so many
warriors high ranking with giant weapons
H they must be guarding this Garden
animal of the dur temple on this hill
anyway let's avoid a confrontation here
after all the Pop's Castle is just
around the corner from
here okay so we don't go there then they
do want me to go here
huh theck
came who is Among Us in the
let's
go where's a red beard
guy what if the red beard is just a
metaphor for something else and he
doesn't have a red beard at all that'd
be so
disappointing uh this one
wow
[Music]
cool what if he just shaved it oh this
is supposed to stop me
[Music]
okay he's got a
beard redhaired people be like
lives in the cave yeah he's been stuck
in here for a
while fin some good character design but
it's not bald
though that would be even better
right
[Music]
foree
spee
fore
[Music]
foree foree
what was the
heart I have a
heart no don't leave again
I got a screenshot by
[Music]
accident
for oh I got what you
[Music]
want
fore fore
[Music]
for real for
real
which executor pretty new executor hot K
if evil why H why
women
H why the [\h__\h] are they here yeah for me
did they sense me my existence here
don't kill hot woman
[Music]
no oh hit Me Harder
woman 20,000
okay nice nice
oh uh uh a good opponent for once
[Music]
let's do this at least we'll see her
face for a while cuz she got a lot of HP
or not really her face because she's
covered up but p h she's hot
like her why do we have to kill
[Music]
her this is the one that when they hit
me they get damaged back right was there
any downside to
[Music]
it the enemies
receive there's no downside to it
right just that it takes up a turn oh it
doesn't even it doesn't
let's
[Music]
go nice she's actually strong I'm I'm
delighted she's so dead inside the way
she
talks just can't use the arrow at the
same time as ah right right right right
right ah so if I use this now it will
deactivate it maybe but the magic storm
can I use the magic
storm
probably h of
[Music]
De strategic crit oh my shield is gone
this is perfect actually
this may be perfectly timed
because the crit always takes this
amount of time if you activate the
shield as soon as you
can then you will have your crit
ready for when the shield is gone and
then you can use the arrow wow
[Music]
genius okay and then we get another
attack wait that was a critical too on
its own
[Music]
she what it's just a normal sword I
would say and that's just the
handle it's just a sword what do you
mean double crit yay
don't really need healing right now but
I'm going to uh take it anyway for the
next fight cuz I always forget to heal
myself in between fights thanks for the
membership
[Music]
welcome okay that should
be with my pet attacking hopefully yes
[Music]
but no why w we kill her
no oh she ran
away maybe
feel no she's
strong a bunch more I can't handle that
no more cute girls
please
much my
heart no he wants to
trade the first steam engine created by
m
[Music]
cuz I'm making her nervous
right her heart goes doy doy when she
sees
me
[Music]
theice all right cuz he's like the
opposing Traer so he wants to be better
than him
okay I got the engine let's go but what
about the device don't you won't you
give it to me now and
oh oh can I buy
these this stuff looks like some kind of
like um Harry
Potter uh you know the Quidditch
thingy looks like they made a staff out
of that
thanks for the thanks for the r yeah
golden snitch not the
Broom the snitch obviously it doesn't
look like a broom
[Music]
guys giant dark magic stones are hard to
store it's a pretty tricky request even
for me so they want giant dark magic
stones
Oh you mean those weapons are pretty
Infamous they've been lost for quite
some time i' never have expected them to
be here the
weapons peaked with
Q you wow fancy writing for every
request you complete for me you can
choose one oh
H wait how many do I have do I need them
myself I think I used those for crafting
too
um I may not have one right oh wait is
it this yeah that's wasn't I keeping
them from
crafting but I would I guess I could
give him one if one
equals one weapon then that's okay if
the weapon is
good can I choose
though oh it seems like I can choose I'm
going to go for the stuff it's probably
best for me cuz I didn't stat stat much
into like
physical not sure what this one is looks
this looks like the Minecraft Enemy that
kept on popping up when when we were one
blocking the staff is filled with Fire
magic isn't that uh isn't that how do
you do this for a isn't that Relic love
staff where did humans find something
like
that the stuff on the left side is the
ingredients to craft it myself or what
huh
okay like a shortcut to
it no it's already the weapon I think
not for not a recipe right it's
obviously just already the
weapon what a scam if it's not I'm
pretty sure it is
yeah plus
108 our attack's going to hit even
stronger
and plus
12 wa let's
[Music]
go I have nothing here why is this
empty why was it
empty upgrade yeah yeah yeah I barely
get
home should I activate this
okay where next Matt's
house I know where to go I know where to
go the best allrounder staff can be
found now too is it not that
[Music]
huh Jack back next request it wouldn't
it be another dark stone I don't want to
give him one right now I'm quite happy
with
this
oopsie why you making me choose each
time just choose the one I have in my
inventory
[Music]
unnecessary oh wait I was confused just
now the staff on the girl on uh forgot
her name looked to me like brown hair
like little twin Tails or so and I
thought it was a new girl
[Music]
again I thought they were introducing
another
girl thank
[Music]
Goda
and
S C
[Music]
fore habit
[Applause]
[Music]
praise me
more let's go pink cute
[Music]
real
test
oh oh
oh so summoning it means it's going to
be in my like magic thingies
[Music]
yes or as a pet
I already feel at peace man I'm
surrounded by all these cute girls I
feel so peaceful
[Music]
she thought her dad was dead now she has
a letter of him in in her hands
[Music]
oh she's too good at hiding and
disguising
[Music]
herself daddy is proud of you
not as much as I
[Music]
did
for I'm so
popular yo look how my staff is glowing
it looks amazing
[Music]
no put down the L fell at
once the [\h__\h]
oh let's introduce ourselves shall
we let's let's go let's
go let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's [\h__\h] him
[Music]
up burn you bastards burn in hell and
never come back rest in pie [\h__\h]
[Music]
I mean I think I would be a little bit
ter terrified
if if I was one of these
kids and the witch that I like so much
just comes by and literally kills these
knights in front of my
eyes like even if she's helping me with
that as a kid if you see her killing
someone murdering someone I think that
should be a little bit intimidating and
scary yeah but surely they're just
unconscious
yeah let's say that is the
case now back to pretty
[Music]
lady pushed
they were
dead okay then first no with her oh
[Music]
okay nah I don't need to but she's
attacking from
behind with this formation I don't think
we had a formation like this before but
that means that my
skills the AOE ones will definitely not
hit her if I use them
on um the ones in front of me oh only
three wow
what a
deal oh they turn towards her
interesting okay
[Music]
um need some MP for
sure I
[Music]
use I don't know
I'll use this mind
cleanser that's 80%
[Music]
wow oh wait it does hit her like that
a could do that I
[Music]
could should
I
sure not much damage though because
they're strong
wow w w w w w w
[Music]
wow the mea oh my God yeah the name is
003 uh
y
y I can't heal with uh our Bird right
now I have to use my own heal
um this doesn't take up the turn right
so I can do this and then heal myself
[Music]
yeah a bit unfortunate I didn't think
she would hit me this
hard what the [\h__\h] you already powered
up when I was gone or what well we
didn't see each other for 5
minutes yeah bab we need to crush them
immediately oh counter attack let's
[Music]
go oh
I
choose maybe one of the weaker ones
first oh
AO ow ow ow ow ow ow ow yeah you're just
hitting yourself keep on hitting
yourself yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah this might still be the best
option right now until
[Applause]
they I forgot that thing does that what
exactly is that though it it it became a
helmet for
me midna
style does it protect me does it give me
defense but I already have the shield on
so I don't really know the difference
[Music]
now
okay crit time
[Music]
baby Ah that's new what the [\h__\h] is
firework
Festival oh does it come with my
staff multiple Firs at s let's go
this better be strong but wait does it
take up a turn then we got to do A's
Arrow
first that does take up a turn yeah if
it's like the magic CL mhm okay let's
go he several targets but I choose the
first one or what
[Music]
damage was a little
bit okay that thing is definitely
protecting
me I should check out what what that
does
again skill info Bell armor lightning
belless mantal its body and transforms
into armor for its Master while wearing
Bell armor a portion of damage is
absorbed restoring HP equal to the
damage absorb each turn
[Music]
oh nice okay cool cool cool how long is
it staying on me though I think the
maybe
the look at my mouse this thing is
probably the timer for it or or this one
no one of them whichever disappears soon
with it
together we'll see
M probably should
[Music]
heal eh maybe this
one oh my
well you're just continuing to protect
me okay
thanks yeah he's almost
[Music]
dead
mm for
[Music]
um how about we do a swing on this one
that might the double swing might get us
a kill on
him or it doesn't should have gone for
the
Triple y
it the helmet is so
[Music]
cool okay we should kill this one cuz
it's their turn next
I might not I'm not sure if I'll survive
oh but he's doing an AOE but you only
hit one and he misses okay okay okay ah
nice nice nice
nice this is actually
tough Lea
pudding
uh six turns after comb we rarely get
this one
this one takes up a turn I think which
is fine but we could use it next turn
for the
[Music]
crit yeah I think I'll do
that yeah finally challenging battle
[Music]
yeah she gets to attack twice after this
maybe I should put on my shield it's
kind of scary cuz she has something
special I think Brewing that red glow on
the bottom right is kind of scaring
[Music]
me okay let's see
oh yeah he still gets an attack
okay oh it's him oh okay no more
uh no more protection
from oh he's
back he's back and we get the crit but I
have no
mp uh wait did did did me taking an it
take up a turn I forgot I forgot how was
it so far cuz I think I need the MP um I
think it plays into the damage
here oh no no it's Max MP not like the
existing MP
right not not the one I have currently
just how much I could have it does take
okay I think I understand this as 562
MP not 6 MP
so we're probably
fine wow 6, free
H
wa
y okay the Bell armor is pretty good
right now she's actually strong I
actually need this that was a good
choice of
pet annoyingly
[Music]
and she's pretty much dead how about we
try with a triple swing to finish it I
hope I won't regret this but I have no
MP ah four
four and so many
[Music]
dreams
okay
[Music]
yay 6,000 over for 6,000 damage the
crit that's a good
one but you got to be deep in the battle
Six turn
[Music]
or would you think it's maybe the witch
even cuz a lot of witches
are evil here
too buta looks like could be
evil but she's the most like motivated
about cutting them and killing them
who could it be who could the mole be I
don't think it's the leader because that
makes no sense unless the plan is to
like and now I'm putting my tinf head on
unless the plan is to gather people to
gather an opposing team but that itself
is a trap obviously the opposing team if
you're for the pope you want them to die
so you you get them
together promising them that we'll kill
the pop and then in the end you'll just
bring them there into a trap you know
that could be a genius yeah big brain
play
but no I don't think it's like justice
that they wouldn't call it a molden just
an
accidental you know and he's been
sleeping
so Irene sounds a bit chaotic and
unhinged it could be both of the girls I
think it's definitely one of the girls
but who knows which one
she doesn't seem very
evil
but I don't
know maybe all the time when Dana is
like saying stuff like I want to kill
him I want to slice him up maybe she's
projecting her feelings that she has for
us towards them just to seem you know
like she's with
[Music]
us we find out
soon we find out soon yeah definitely
only just playing the
part uh wait where are we going first
Stein was where uh somewhere far over
[Music]
there there right
yeah person was ABS
point that could be a hint butt then no
way that would I just like tin foiled
out of my brain would be what he's
doing that's so big
brain
who but hey should we go back once and
train a little bit that witch really
made me feel a little bit insecure the
the the executor made me feel a little
bit exure
insecure about my
skills we should heal once and and
train I think we
want this
one
[Music]
and I might want that it's the most
balanced although some agility maybe are
we low on agility is this low is 88
low
uh maybe we should do some agility but
there's
no nothing for agility only this is plus
two this is plus
three then I'll add the running
one okay
[Music]
okay I was hoping for that that was
relatively easy square triangle
cirle wait should I have done stage two
I accidentally pressed
that ah would I get more if I did stage
two
no God damn
it
[\h__\h] well at least we didn't fail
it they should just go stage two
[Music]
automatically train will keep feeling it
feels pretty slowly this is our first
time training today and I've did a lot
of story and
fights okay maybe way more story than
fights there weren't actually that many
fights but still
plenty is there anything we can
anything useful we can
[Music]
craft new shoes agility
15% the current shoes we're wearing a
these agility 2% + 12 what does that
mean 2% plus 12 oh from 2% to
15 oh that's so worth it we're skipping
these ones let's do it look up look
looka like in
Italia
Italia let's get
them that's a big
Improvement nice and
then otherwise I can't make anything
else that's
fine can we improve any of our magic
[Music]
circles not with these materials what's
this stuff combat AIDS I don't ever use
maybe I should
[Music]
huh I can make like one of these or one
of these but I don't no not one of these
one of these I don't think there's any
point in making
[Music]
them oh I can actually make a lot
more yeah uh people have been saying I
should go back to Redbeard to see what
he wants
next so we can do that too I right I
need to upgrade my stuff oh uh what do
you want now I just realized didn't we
have our previous weapon fully nourished
and then we never upgraded it did we I
don't
know uh oh we can't upgrade this one
right now but we can nourish
it so what are we going to put in
[Music]
there a couple of
these couple of these
couple
[Music]
these couple
these I don't know what I'll be
[Music]
needing okay that would be Max let's go
performance boost 20%
Nice now all we need is a lava eye and a
lava Stein
core I think we can maybe make a core
but the
eye is there anywhere where we could get
one of
those already or is that later in the
game I wonder
[Music]
no we can actually not make one of those
stones either I
think you can get those now when you go
deeper in the lava
area I kind of want to go
then I kind of want to check it
out uh no I want to sleep how do you
sleep again here how to sleep
[Applause]
[Music]
bring me there's a lot of these thank
you time to skateboard over some lava
yeah yeah with style with K
ofp okay the lava
cave uh now I'm going to have troubles
finding it again left or right
[Music]
um
no left
side
really why do you guys remember
that all right if I go further through
here it will become
lava
somewhere uh left right yeah
mhm CU I
farmed someone has to
true true
true wait I still get drops from them
right fire stone okay
nice should Farm
them just for the jobs
ah it's fast as hell
anyway uh what we have to go through
here
again he has only 2,000 HP I should be
able to quick hunt him as well TB
[Music]
nice why do we have her out by default
again now she wasn't out in the previous
fights I think what the
hell I think your strength or magic has
to be over their
HP
yep or this door you just always have to
f it cuz it's a
door oh cuz it's in the
house okay okay
okay can I change that from
here maybe
not can I ride him no
nah we should have been riding like on
the top of him ah
oh I F these
too I think here I wasn't sure how to
proceed was I I didn't understand this
one switch lights oh I guess so
well let me try oh yeah that makes
sense that actually makes
sense okay
like
okay left right right left right left
right left oh right left
[Music]
okay wowy
he no why did I do that it makes
everybody stronger but it also opens
this door so worth it oh my God my HP
[\h__\h] hope there's a crystal here no wait
I'll find one slimy
[Music]
thingies no
Crystal okay I have to heal
myself fine
fine do it myself then
[Music]
fine okay let's start with the single
one lava it's just lava literally that's
it magma from the body of Lavin that
possesses a great amount of magic
5,400 shesh it's defense element is fire
too bad my magic is all
fire except for the
lightning oh
[Music]
Okay lava eye I think we need six of
them or just one was it six or
one seven oh dear we might not get all
of those unless there's more of these
mobs
[Music]
elsewhere ouch
oopsie lava Rises and Falls opening the
pathway
d
a didn't see
that CA
[Music]
hi oh my God
kill
him at
[Music]
once they still got so much what the
[\h__\h] these are actually
strong I think it's good that we're here
for a little break from the main story
so we can level a little bit and get
those
Ms please don't kill me please don't
kill
[Music]
me it's you
oh my God thank God they missed I mean I
don't think it would have killed me
but okay more lava
eyes it's the eye of the
lava it's the mats that I
want to upgrade my staff for more
[Music]
power I don't want to wait any longer
for them to spawn just give me enough to
use them
up eye of
La not lover
[Music]
lava I need these
sure okay let's ride
this WOW difficult riddle
uh let's go right first
cuz what how can you be faster than
that oh there's a treasure chest there
let's go my RPG instincts let me through
the right side let's go
[Music]
it's [\h__\h] bastard he's like why me why
me out of these four why did you choose
me tactical thinking my
[Music]
friend strategic thinking
didn't go in with full HP but I
mean that's way more damage than I
thought I would be
getting
bro do I need more
HP generally
[Music]
better armor I didn't put on the shoes
yet let me put them on after this fight
[Music]
oh wa
3,400 + 400
counter counter isn't always that strong
what's going
[Music]
on maybe they like physical damage maybe
I should attack more physically to those
enemies boost the power of Fire
[Music]
magic
um oh let's change this one we don't
need that anymore the dark magic one oh
I didn't have any shoes
on okay we got the the spiky
shoes that's a bit
better more
agility way more agility
[Music]
okay how do you make it I even stepped
off way earlier than I usually
did okay this one's
fine
okay okay what's behind here a boss deep
lava level ooh oh oh oh God I don't
think if the minions are already that
strong I don't think I'll be able to
kill this how much
unmeasurable extra large unmeasurable
we've never seen unmeasurable
before well definitely healing beforeand
I I do want to give it a try because
trying doesn't hurt in this
[Music]
game although a little bit of an armor
upgrade would be nice ni against this
one to be
[Music]
honest y
I forgot about this one
cute I should probably bring this one
into the
battle maybe even from the
beginning so that he will activate
earlier I was just looking for water
pets but I don't have one U but I do
have like lightning and stuff and wait
the turtle is water though no it's
nothing I have no water and this element
is explosive
it does say aquatic for the rable thing
I I'm I don't know if I should bring
this one in though uh I'll just bring in
a lightning one
probably once we're in there is there
anything else I can do yeah probably uh
we should use a an item for sure hey
what happened with my mp
should I save does it make sense to save
I'll just
save how to save again ah can I not save
in here but I think I don't have
to I doubt we can do it though I'm
[Music]
measurable oh yeah right I don't think I
tried feeding this one
before no wait Affinity best it's
already Max okay
strength for agility maybe more agility
to kill it
faster I mean both would result in it
hopefully
but okay let's see let's see if you guys
me measure like whatever how much damage
I do now and then see how much percent
uh that did on the HP bar we could
calculate how much HP he has in
total do it
guys yeah I love I love it when the
question when the bar says question mark
question mark question mark if this was
a tailes off game I would use the the
thing to find out how much he
has he has below
100K well
well maybe it's 9 N 9
99,999 if it was like 100 H 10,000
that's okay cuz we fought eh a 9k won
before and wasn't our maximum 40K
before so if it goes by how much higher
it is than my own then it must be over
50,000 or so because we saw the HP on
the 40,000 one
right so it would have to be over that
probably not just 10,000 minimum
probably 50,000 or 60 or
so wow wow wow wow wow
wow okay let's summon
[Music]
immediately base
attack okay base attack is the strongest
on this one and this
one I don't know about explosive
explosive versus fire but as long as
it's not
fire right or should
I this one's also cheaper in mp but oh I
don't
[Music]
know rain Canon double cannon that seems
more AOE
though maybe I'll go for a
Golem hit the lava jellies hard did
he I'm I'm so ner okay whatever it's
going to either be pleasantly fine or
I'll get [\h__\h] so whatever
um should I put up a
shield who's this again oh should I put
up this
one no it's it's passive anyway right
it's already active is it is that how it
works I don't
[Music]
know okay I'll put up a shield
once Ah that's not
bad damage I don't know
but we can already turn on AIM heart's
absolute
defense is my does is my shield still on
after one it doesn't is only one turn
yeah only one turn
[Music]
MP I think we can do
it think we could do it it's going to be
a little bit tough probably but we can
do it at some point he's probably going
to do like a really strong rough attack
and that's going to
be scary but besides that we already
have the arrow
or we wait until next turn for the crit
I think we'll
wait yeah we'll wait we'll
[Music]
wait that was also a critical so it was
smart of me to
wait we're getting we're getting
defended by our face armor let's go
with A's Arrow easy look how far below
he's already with his
HP see by
nice firework Festival I don't know this
wasn't as strong before I think and it's
AOE and it's
fire would it be stronger
[Music]
anyway then if I use
my no normal uh lightning
attack
2,600 but it doesn't say clearly how
much this is 100 plus 55% of magic I
don't know how much it
is he will take full
damage okay let's let's see how much it
does oh it's that was a crit in there oh
oh total
5,200 that's good how much did my
lightning attacks
to oh [\h__\h] that
hurt
roll
um thanks for the
pie is a heart's defense still on no
right I don't think so
maybe I should turn on the shield and
then we
continue okay 2,500 so half of that okay
okay okay okay no
problem don't use
shield no I think in this case it was
all right I know it uses up a lot of MP
but it could save my
ass yeah that was a double turn
so is my shield still on when I get a
double
turn no I don't think it was
off it was off
now oh that's why you said don't put it
on [\h__\h] okay oh
well
uh uh
uh trying to find the best item
50/50 water balloon frog
[Music]
mucus
perfect he's pretty much dead oh we have
the lightning oh we have the lightning
bolt I could wait one more turn but he's
already so low on HP that I think I
might do it
now oh oh 6,000 even without the crit
previously it was 6,400 with crit I
think wasn't it
oh
4,5
4,500 from the
pet comat exper 65 all set increased by
%. oh we're so much stronger now
suddenly training Effectiveness one 20%
Str Str crit 150 16% maximum pet summon
cost eight yes second equipment amount
four h Okay
Yahoo
yo
okay guys do not get intimidated by such
a thing as
unmeasurable just measure it just do it
just measure it
anyway put a [\h__\h] ruler right up
there can we go deeper we it seems like
we could
unlimited
power
[Music]
bro oh another strong fire Golem oh he's
got a sword stuck in his heart
no n do you need help oh are we not
going to fight
actually this thing has a lot of gravity
what do you mean with
that is is that
a a way of saying he's
big a nice way of saying it cu the
bigger you are the more gravity you
have
gravy he's
[Music]
dense a big
boy it's true
right saw my fredie he saw my fredie so
what is that why he stuck a sword in his
heart that's blast one of the three
great spirits of the continent of filia
doesn't seem like he wants to attack
me Spirits I thought it looked a bit
like a
BT but one is that sword on its chest
the cling T of BL chest per periodically
adits large Birch of magic power when
that happens blast can control itself
and comes above ground to go on a rapit
according to a legend that sword was
wielded by a hero who sto Blast from
going on a rampage perhaps the sword was
able to hold back the power of blast's
compact son but that sword's magic seems
similar to blasts maybe that sword
absorbed the compact Zone's magic seems
like
it so oh seems like we can find him
unmeasurable what do you think
would he be similar to the previous
enemy anybody who played this before can
tell me if it's cuz this one's extra
large he has
100K how much did the other one have can
we see it in like our
enemy guide
book
uh oh f
[Music]
50,000 no if this one has actually
100K if it's just the HP being stronger
uh being more then okay if he however
also doubled his other stats then I
don't think
so I don't think so but also we just
leveled up
[Music]
too this is boss for end game ST maybe
we'll come back if we feel the need need
to you
know hit something really hard and level
up again a little bit we we can keep him
for another time surely we're a little
bit too weak for him
[Music]
now I think it makes sense to come back
to
him okay did any of the enemies respawn
by now probably not
ow
whatever you w show me when it respawns
I thought you did normally ah there okay
it still takes a while but I got two
training sessions back
already ah ah
ah oh I can't you can't just run over
there uh endlessly you actually have
to like even if you still have enough
HP you have to try at
least oh my God okay I did
it what do you mean I can't I can't do
quick didn't I do a quicky on these
before I don't care I don't want to I I
don't
[Music]
want I did on these
no oh but they're hide they're they're
protecting an item oh I think it's just
a normal one
though oh the bull was here should we
fight the bull again
quickly do I need another Horn of
his six wait 6,000 is nothing at this
point oh my
[Music]
easy
I what a cute thing to
say the staff already also needed the
horn but I already got it yeah maybe
I'll need it for something else now
let's go to the Red Beard guy can I
teleport from
here
um look what that okay uh red beards
they're so close
together I think you can evoke his staff
oh do you think I have enough let's see
what he
wants a Lightning Dragon horn do I have
that I don't think I have
that you're giving me a request that
you're not even sure as possible to
complete the Lightning
Dragon all that matters is that the
client wants a Lightning Dragon home
I don't know if I have
that oh okay I don't have it because he
doesn't seem to
even let me check okay um let's go
home it's accessible but need to find
the Lightning
Dragon
H
[Music]
uh
wait
oh ah ah I needed one and I already had
one now I have two cool okay but I can
actually upgrade it we got enough eyes
we got
10 and the Lavin core I guess we got
from one of the bigger enemies
ooh oh oh meteorite
judgment is not there we go that's the
one summons and drops multiple small
meteoroids woo 150 8 12
times nice so we nourish it again but
this one this is like Max it can't be
evolved
anymore all right what oh what I have so
many of these let's throw
in oh oh wow oh that barely does
[Music]
anything I need more mats all kinds of
mats okay we don't need to get it all to
the maximum
anyway can I make something bigger out
of the five stones will that be be more
efficient I
[Music]
wonder I don't know this fine for now
yeah I'm already strong hi I'm Matt are
you
really Olympics opening ceremony is
going to
going on right now oh hey I thought it
already happened cuz yesterday I saw a
really epic video of the guy shooting a
fire arrow straight into the
bowl that was pretty
nice you lie on the internet what's
wrong with
you the Olympics going on right now yeah
oh by the way I was uh briefed on like
you know Olympic stuff streaming it
maybe even more complicated than the
waa so I don't
know I have to discuss with management
for each single competition if they let
me do it I don't
know I'll try
though even if I don't show it on the
[Music]
stream I'll see if if
if anything interesting is going on next
week I'll try
to do one next
week need to check the
[Music]
schedule this is like lightning stuff
isn't
[Music]
it this cir cir
where do you get that
from I want new
[Music]
armor Rich pudding juice if I drink this
will pudding become
rich or will I drink the money of
pudding each drop in there each drop
that I take
in makes pudding more
poor and drains his bank
[Laughter]
account amazing sounds good let's do
it ch ch chug chug
[Music]
me to Stu up back on
these uh I need more of these basic mats
huh I'll make one of
these okay
I need where do you get dried pie from
again I don't remember I'm out of
[Music]
them dried
pie what you got
[Music]
that and
those dwarf Golem grass ah from those
dwarf
[Music]
Golems beating up lowle soldiers oh
I think we still have plenty of healing
items so maybe I'm fine I could also
just buy healing items I
guess
um
okay so I think I just got a lot more
powerful in terms of
attack I wonder what I should
[Music]
train maybe always throw in one of these
because why not very
balanced maybe one of
these
[Music]
no oh it's this one okay this one stage
two this time stage two
ah okay it's only 5% that I lost last
time okay
okay
clse
okay count to
clockwise okay nice
one I always get this one I'm glad I get
it because I know how to do
it
yay so
cute
Kaboom
nice all right all right
all right why not sleep a little bit ah
[\h__\h] I forgot to run errands oh
man
I I will quickly go
outside once you're like off of the main
quest route you just can't
stop doing like all this kind of like
lowbob
[\h__\h] I can't stop myself huh give me the
grass
thanks so much ah
YouTube
hello
[Music]
hello are you
back are you back
[Music]
y you
good it was
[Music]
Regional why am I doing
this
okay we are so back let's go
me back but laggy okay by the way did
you guys see there was a a little
announcement I did retweet it of a
stream that is still very much in the
future um with me Callie and
Ena on the official H life Japan
Channel yeah the NOA one mhm so we'll be
in Japan for that
[Music]
yeah it's going to be basically an all
collab but I think it's going to be
mostly no I think it was going to be
English was it I forgot cuz I think I
asked are we doing this in English or
Japanese and I forgot the
[Music]
answer I would think English though but
noas English is not as good as it CH I
think
[Music]
but not too bad I think we'll see there
was an English announcement too but it's
on a Japanese channel for their program
so you
know what do they drop again
yep oh the
crystals all right
[Music]
what's over here I forgot oh more of
you
okay I'm just going to kill them and
then we'll go back to main story
[Music]
maybe damn damage is
[Applause]
[Music]
crazy here somewhere we never fought
did it say I never fought these
[Music]
before now we been here before I
remember flying
off I remember flying up
here yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we've
been here we've been
here what do the enemies here drop see I
can't [\h__\h] stop I can't stop
stupid
birds why do I they have 50 HP why do I
have to fight them
properly
[Music]
huh what do you
mean oh we should kill this
one beautiful white
wait there's some [\h__\h] Birds here too oh
they exploded all in one go ugly bird
meat wait what was the other drop
see you know Rhino okay
Rhino
y y did I fight this one I don't wait I
don't think I fought this one it's
another Golem isn't it
white giant or did I no I haven't I
haven't 14,000 ah what a joke let's do
it maybe he has uh that one match that I
thought looks like like you know
interesting
[Music]
no I didn't fight this one to try mind
controlling the looka too in that area
[Music]
looka Okay hercul Stone
UL Stone I didn't see that in any
crafting I think I must have missed it
[Music]
yeah that was very
easy a consumable permanent buff oh that
that
stone oh oh it
is but this one is too like can I just
use it now cuz I might not need the r
one anymore and they're really easy to
get anyway I
guess should I really use it I don't
know if I need it for crafting at
all I I'm so like
hesitant on using these
[Music]
but this one is for using right because
I it looks like something you craft just
for
that why do we have so
many maybe keep one if you're
unsure but in the end like we know where
it is now and it was an easy easy
kill
so
[Music]
yeah you would have held on to them
until end game until the very last day I
can't do this again I need to use my
items special
increas
no
okay cool cool co co cool
wait is that a chest I didn't open
before
no is it Dragon thing still here
no west of Illusion thing or is it
[Music]
here anything else I want to check out
I'm still here what's over there
[Music]
tiar oh did I go there before
over there to that
mob feel like I
[Music]
haven't
oh never fought before a little I I can
probably get this one yeah mind control
possible small and cute type of te wait
if I get this one maybe I'll be able to
talk to that lady with a dragon for some
reason because she sees I have one of
these dragons she like she's like oh my
God let me teach you about these dragons
or so I don't know maybe maybe maybe
maybe maybe if I talk to her with the
pet summoned maybe that could be that
would make
sense these summon pets yeah it's it's
actually so [\h__\h] weak uh I would
accidentally kill it
um this Miss uh but yeah placees place
in home this
[Music]
one how am
I going to do less than okay maybe
normal
swing okay
okay ooh Thunder
damage okay it's
weekend um
[Music]
I was so stump and then I had to look it
up and you just
really I'm such a
genius my tin foil hat is
amazing it's it's I don't need a tin
full you guys need to stop putting the
tin fo hat on on top of me because
everything I say makes sense and is
reasonable and comes
true oh that would be amazing let's go
to her
[Music]
um
where where where where where where here
is
here I
think gold foil
next do I get an upgrade to a gold foil
hat hey you're here again
[Music]
no yeah I think I know where to go she's
right there
okay I'm such a
[Music]
genius oh
oh
wow
wait same it's still same but she's
going to be like wait you have a
dragon right
[Music]
mine's bigger than
yours that's what he said to another
guy that's what a suspicious suspicious
person would
[Music]
say I like her
I human brain you don't see
that
byber
Savage is a rare one
[Music]
oh maybe okay I didn't try this yet do
did we get uh a heart with it
immediately cuz in case we don't what if
this would be amazing if I figure it out
if if I don't even I don't even know but
what if in order to get a full heart
with it the food that we have uh none of
it would work we don't have this item
but she would have the item that would
that we would need to feed it to get
full Affinity so we have to bring this
Dragon to her you know that could that
could be a thing but I don't even know
if we don't already have full Affinity
with
it but that would also be kind of Genius
that there's this one there one animal
there one pet that in order to get full
Affinity with it then you got to go to
this lady and she will give you the one
item her Quest is only for more pets oh
okay
but that would be that would be even
more
[Music]
amazing when is later
oh research payment
7,000 well we'll never know her name cuz
she never said it out loud in Japanese
cuz I skipped it Skipper
Skipper Skipper Skipper Jack the Ripper
skip skip
[Music]
ah wait what did it drop I wanted to see
what it drops I was like kind of
curious damn
it should we go back to main quest I'm
like kind of having fun running around
randomly
aimlessly aimlessly UNL un unlike aim
hard he aimed so
hard couldn't be me oh you guys Dro
something that I want right yep the the
uh pie oh yeah all
right about you
guys need to go to sleep good night
thanks for coming
[Music]
bye wasn't there Dragon close to the
island with the
ships I can't remember that one was that
a big one or a small
one oh we get to attack twice this
Dragon
th
force
[Music]
force that was not bad little Dragon
Chun that's cool his standard attack is
like AOE that I can choose targeted AOE
not AOE but like you
know
[Music]
wow oh he's strong actually
I mean if you add it up it's not that
much different from other pets attacks
actually but it's nice if you can attack
like several small
mobs and kind of clean them up so that's
useful
[Music]
always I don't want to use up all my mp
unless there's a a healing
stone close by
shock
fi
oh hi wait I got a sword from him steal
the Supreme War's weapon glor wait I
fought these before I'm just now getting
the
[Music]
item I don't think I got this
before strength 100% plus friend 80
magic traces Sword Play SK but this if I
wear this it replaces
my
yeah I don't think I want that cuz I'm
focusing on wearing staff cuz
staffs but good to have I guess it's a
rare drop huh maybe
yeah maybe it
is gold gold d
I like having this little dragonfly
around
me H insufficent okay I think we
teleport to where do we need to go death
squad but uh first home because we do
have training points
again m is surprising solid if you build
for it I suppose so but you know I feel
like it's just wrong we're we're playing
Rich Spring are we're playing a witch it
feels wrong to skill and fight with a
sword
even though it seems cool as well maybe
in the second
playr
oh how is that plugging for your for
Team Canada you're you're saying my
streams are better than the
Olympics thank you for the Super
[Music]
Chat yeah you think you feel the same
way same Gand used the sword well not
always
if I could use both like if she would
use if she would switch to the sword
whenever she attacks physically that
would make sense to
[Music]
me okay I think I'll
do we never train defense maybe I should
do it once
[Music]
this one push-ups did I do that before
yeah how the [\h__\h] do I do it oh
okay okay that's
manageable you just mashed a
button is it always X or it gets more
difficult I think the more you
go but
Ming okay
easy I I used gamer grip
[Music]
okay all right little
[Applause]
[Music]
sleep let's go back
to welcome back
[Music]
H one last check if I can't do any any
uh if I can't craft any armor any new
one where was it where was it where
[Music]
was there it
is nope I I need to make
these h
maybe next time I feel like upgrading my
power then we'll go by the help of the
chat we'll find those items surely
they're available
somewhere uh death squad
right and we'll find out who the
impostor
[Music]
is place your beds now wait let's do a
poll let's do a PO PLL I want to do a
poll
um who is the
impostor uh what was the name of the big
guy
[Music]
uh
uh ver okay what's the name the the
narissa is
Raina uh Arena what was it the the small
G
it's hi what do you mean shut
up you mean I go in there and then I go
out and and without me knowing I'm
reporting to
someone should should I know that would
I
know okay start pole it's not me
bro I would know if I was the one
place your beds
now D it D it D
it all very
even very even this now we never went
here should we check it out is there
some
items oh there's a chest
there I can go through I can SL up for
the cracks 1,400 let's go or 14,000
[Music]
14,000 anything else here cuz it's kind
of nicely
hidden everything
[Music]
okay I think that's
it with verin being
gone uh that kind of makes sense for it
to be
him
right but now Dana is not here seemingly
so that's also sus
[Music]
oo
for I think it's the witch
[Music]
wait is somebody completely different
unrelated to these people
who gave this to us again some Warrior
friend but
who there was a tracker on
[Music]
it but maybe she didn't want
to and we sus these nice people out
let's end the
so it was me well but not
really not in the sense that we F
Justice Escape admin's the one to
escape out of
prison oh how the turns
table he the Cannons
himself so really shouldn't have the
Cannons aimed into the right direction
right in front of the
Escape
for prisoners
to oh we're going somewhere where
there's dark
magic should I put on that accessory
again
[Music]
M I still have nothing here what what
goes
there who goes
there
uh which one was it this one
let's
go
Jus okay so we'll
[Music]
save should go alone this is a flag F Fu
he'll die in here won't
he no
nah what do you think
guys will he die would be
dramatic kind of
random
for 40
[Music]
Mons so
fast got my answer
25 is also a long time thank
you fight fight fight fight fight let's
use my newly upgraded staff and my
amazing new skills why is there no pet
out oh is the mask
on is it on I don't know is it
wait where did my Golem go oh over
there thank you
guys for being a member for so
long my chance ooh
[Music]
yo that looks cool
whoa
nice I like my pets my pets are amazing
[Music]
everywhere everyone's showing off how
green they are Green With
Envy that they can't be a phoenix like
me but just a mere
chicken no you guys are
beautiful as the chicken that you are oh
is that the one
[Music]
North okay
oh I wonder if we wouldn't have talked
to him if we could have even proceeded
here
[Music]
and we got four
no why does that one pop up later
funny okay okay okay we get it you guys
are green
we got
[Music]
it how did they
survive now they
[Music]
die my cute chicken too yeah you're a
hybrid though
[Music]
diso you are a
species oh he's here now ha
TNI that
mean
e East we
go for stopping bleeding uhhuh
how do I get down
here can you fly us
over it broke after he stepped on I
guess here we
go executor
is that a new design
or no that looks
new similar to the first one but looks
new
[Music]
cute oh was is she trying to
rebel I feel bad for these girlies
[Music]
is still fighting we need to save
her it's her her mind inside of her
brain she wants to get
[Music]
out who that's a sick weapon
wa I love that
Design Your
Design you going to attack me too or
favorite would that be mle oh favorite
test
subject
mle makes
sense but I would think that she would
have a little bit more like stand itish
design from the others but maybe not in
this form who
knows whoa
but that's yeah that's probably me
though the fact that she's rebelling and
and and
rampaging that makes
sense there we go flag flag flag flag
J where are
you
J I need to heal
[Music]
can we get all no
what the
hell stop hurting me you're so mean
everybody bullies
me I'm just I'm just looking for a
friend not really a friend but she has a
crush on him
[Music]
so won't you guys support a little
girl's Crush
or you going to crash it
eh you man got no heart you just
jealous you're just jealous
oh look who's there
ah he's talking from so far oh he jumped
down I haven't seen Lydia in a while
[Music]
true what if Justice got back through
this
[Music]
and doesn't seem closed when there's
light coming through
[Music]
it
Minecraft
[Music]
for is that
you
[Music]
for she doesn't seem wet
she just came here and rolled on the
floor and was
like and I gave her a belly rub and now
I got lots of hair on my
[Music]
hand but I rolled it
up and disposed of
it sweet
cat okay wait what I was kind of
listening but uh
H which way now this
way oh oh oh I would not want to walk
down
there that's scary
sker
sker oh I see Justice he's not wearing
all of his clothes
anymore what are you going to do in
front of that door huh how you going to
break that
one should I
heal there's been no healing
thingies wait I got another like rare
weapon
I was like hey this weapon changed its
looks but no it's it's a new weapon 90%
press
fre this one's stronger though oopsie
what did I just do oh
okay sword Max but this one has boosted
magic traces
[Music]
30% h
okay bring it on
[Music]
Justice a great or a gate
huh I talking to
himself like a protagonist but he
doesn't know no he's not the
protagonist he doesn't
realize it's me jce it's
me and you
know protagonist always win in the
end
oh nice texturing
so it's different just
similar uh 44,000 he nothing no match
for me although the last one we fought
that one was 50,000 it's not that
different but I think we're fine without
tools
probably probably
what do we have out
the oh nothing oh
nothing I don't understand why sometimes
you start the battles without a pet and
sometimes with a pet what what's I don't
understand
[Music]
explain armor armor
armor okay that looks good that looks
good already ah that looks good too uh
no a little damage and fire seems to be
pretty efficient but we'll use the
absolute then there should be no
problems at
all some cut scenes remove the pet
[Music]
oh that's weird that it doesn't come
back oh he's already already oh r a
cough
I must have really gotten a lot stronger
with those level up
things cuz I'm barely taking
damage I I I don't have a need to heal
myself oh counter want to do a counter
let's go y let's
go there we go a lot of stats and stuff
oh my God we're so much stronger it's
only 6K HP difference from this mob to
the other one
damn The Cauldron spinning making my
noodle arm stronger
damn yeah I upgraded so much so
quickly
nice wait is this a crit turn it's a
crit turn you're so dead my friend
you're so
dead we
[Music]
got
yay wow oh
it recharges right
away no my
crush he says it so
savagely it looks like justice is in his
limit will he die from this sacrifice
he's right
now what you going to do what are you
going to
do what are he
doing
bomb
punching punch
[Music]
spe spee
oh my
God he's just her little p
[Music]
ahut what are you going to do now swim
jump with me onto my turtle will you you
little
[\h__\h] looks like we're on Dragon
[Music]
Stone yeah get FR of the Dragon
he has the curse that Damon
has oh
no I felt that
[Music]
hi Barry time to show up now hi Mary you
would have caught up by now I'm pretty
sure you were right behind him you
opened the door for him you know where
he
went hi
Marry m
Mia she's a thirsty little girl
[Music]
fore foree
she's so cocky
[Music]
now she chose she's not going to let him
go this is a love story
[Music]
now hormones Must Be Wild
yeah makes
[Music]
sense the hormone boost must have
shocked
her immensely
[Music]
she's she's she's always abusing his
situation when he can't move when he's
in shackles or when he's like half
dead girl
[Music]
face
to you dude that the
executors seem totally [\h__\h] brain
dead like come on they don't seem like
they're rescued and saved from their
evilness and now happy and you know free
to do whatever and have their own will
they're obviously not doing
well but yeah think Justice B
[Music]
bin doesn't die he'll probably come back
as they just
hinted mated from the dark
[Music]
mag
fore
[Music]
foree are we the
bests
[Music]
for it liia not
liia for
[Music]
almost dropped my
controller shut up
you're annoying
me I hate
you no [\h__\h]
[Music]
idea haven't seen
her whole stream
[Music]
fore that's me
you get it
[Music]
now why what is this atmosphere
set up
[Music]
already oh he's back he's
fine
really
[Music]
for how can you do that
he died is
[Music]
this
special he got some stuff left for from
the sub from the
[Music]
testing why
did test the pope has been testing on
witches but he also tests the humans or
is it the same kind of test so to say
that what he offered to Justice for
example for power
enhancement it's kind of a different
test I guess
so so he was the first enhancement
test it got [\h__\h] up real
bad the
witch but that really shocked me just
now that scared me when he when his face
was shown I mean I I I sensed it
something was
[Music]
off we we still don't feel like maybe we
should set up or so no no okay it's not
awkward no no
[Music]
will die in the
proc won't
he wait
minute
minute that's his
dad obviously that's his death
dad is there anything that speaks
against it they both have blonde hair
they both have red
eyes and there's going to be a dramatic
uh end of the story where at the end of
the game when it all comes down he's
going to find out that he's his son but
then he dies in the process of helping
to kill the pope and that'll be the sad
end that he realized that it's his dad
right
before he dies I'm cooking once again
even though he's a zombie and he doesn't
seem to be able to die he will die in
that
moment shouldn't Justice have recognized
him I don't know how long has he not
seen him I don't
remember maybe he lost his memory I I'm
I'm not sure I don't remember what he
was yapping about I think he
knows but he doesn't want to admit it or
what I wonder but definitely that's how
that's he will die his dad will die then
and there and then it's going to be
like
Daddy Justice
will the dad the dad probably
[Music]
knows they both maybe know dad knows for
sure but he doesn't want to say it for
some reason maybe to keep him safe or
whatever I don't [\h__\h] know
okay yeah that makes a lot of sense
that's just typical RPG
[Music]
storyline nice
to okay I think we'll leave it at that
for today I think that's a good stopping
point for the
game um
I think we got really
far 5 and 1 half
hours we got pretty
[Music]
far now I really wonder if
maybe we could finish it in one more
stream or are we still too
far if I did a longer stream like 8
hours or so do you think I could finish
it anybody who played the game two more
75% two more streams okay I think I
should be able to play it in Japan on my
laptop should be should be
[Music]
fine I'm surprised how big this mobile
game is it's not a mobile game
anymore with me pressing leave to leave
the game that's not it it's
this even
more I was going to point out in the
beginning uh she's so blurry but on the
bottom right there's
Livia oh but now look now these two
girls are there too on top of the
[Music]
Golem nice but you know who's missing
Justice I guess cuz they're only putting
people here no that's not true they're
not only putting people here who are on
our side liia well an is gone oh that's
sad but yeah it's like
a Olivia
Olivia liia I guess is on our side she's
just like not
[Music]
officially but Justice is our crash when
is he going to show up well maybe at the
end he's going to be sitting next to
pyber up there holding
hands the roof is a witch head I yeah
cute there's flowers where Anna was
[Music]
oh that's
cute okay it's 9 halfast 900
p.m. amam spelling be is in 4 and a half
hours it seems like I could take a nap
doesn't it I mean I'm going to read some
super chats but four and a half
hours I could take a
nap do I want to take a
nap if I want to take a
nap I'd probably like if it's just 1
hour I'm going to die it would have to
be like 2
hours 1 hour nap when I wake up from
that I'm
like kill me I want to sleep more so
usually my naps are like
hours you took one just now good
morning I don't think I could take a
longer one because I read super chats
maybe for 30 minutes or an hour and
then I maybe I probably eat dinner
first yeah dinner question
mark and then I need time to fall asleep
oh also actually no I need to
be ready for the stream they wanted a
lot of time earlier to set
up so need to be there
earlier so maybe not too
[Music]
long getting some DMs
next time no no no no I'll read some at
least 30
[Music]
minutes should I stay here I like the
screen which spring wa
[Music]
where were
we for super shut up more than that I
can be more efficient than
that which bring
ma which spring wow that's so hard to
say which spring which spring which
spring uh K with guests and merch
okay my stomach is feeling a little bit
upset already from the energy drink I
drank I think half of it by
now I feel I feel the upsetti
spaghetti I can
[Music]
tell oh geki is opening her memberships
today
geky cute
grer gremlin
Grand it's a cute doodle from her
[Music]
cute
yipp I like
her rebroadcast not the rebroadcast
right or is it the re wait where is it
where's the Stream
[Music]
ah this one I found
it by the way I already got the member
uh the members wallpaper for next
month quite early this time and it looks
so
cute I already changed my my screen
my PC screen to
it can't wait to show you
guys
okay ooh wow a lot of colorful oh
because still kind of birthday is sure
well that's that was
the that was the Kad that's why there's
still so many colorful super chats
okay Mund D for two
pinkies happy fourth birthday wava you
are our dedicated passionate kind and
creative burp boss you inspire so many
of us and are array of sunshine to us
all this has really felt like the year
of the Wawa really my birthday wishes to
you are uh for you to continue grow and
be happy as well as a lot more cat
cuddles and yummy food you deserve all
the love people sent to you please
continue being an amazing o thank you so
much yes get cols more more more I feel
like I'm already getting enough but the
next 1 and a half months it's not quite
one and a half maybe one and almost half
is going to be a little bit rough I'm
going to miss my
kids but hopefully time will pass by
fast I I'll be I'll be
probably more busy than I
[Music]
expect today I looked for my schedule
and and uh checked where I could do my
dance lessons where it's
empty
um and yeah I mean I still have some
empty days but if I fill it up with
dance lessons and I'll be needing a lot
of them a lot of different chos
considering that yeah my schedule will
fill up
nicely borrow Callie's cats again I
might I might if it gets rough but it's
never it never feels honestly it doesn't
help like if I see other people's cats
I'm just like oh I wish I was with my
own cats right
[Music]
now doesn't really
help hope you will get time to relax too
I hope so
too that's why I was thinking I should
go to uh a spy with laa or
so I liked hey hanging out a little bit
with her last time before and after my
stream we hung out a little bit and I
think we got along really well we talked
a lot about uh Italy last time I think I
told
you cuz I told her about my plans to go
to Italy and she told me ah I've been
I've been to that place where you going
to a few
times we talked about this and that
yeah I feel like we have a connection so
I'm happy about
that maybe maybe males
[Music]
Canada
MDI but what about
Kik I don't know I have to Choose
Wisely it also depends on who has
time and you
[Music]
know taking
applications I watched you do this for
years now what take girls to the
moldes a new wife
H I'm always going to a different uh
Island
though don't know to which one I would
go this
time maybe I kind of want to go back to
the to a previous one but it's so
expensive that one last time when I
checked for last time how much they
charge on on the peak season it was a
lot a lot
more I have to think about it well maybe
maybe maybe you know I think I enjoy
one-onone cuz it's more chill but maybe
a triple would be nice too but the thing
is most rooms there are for like
couples so we'd either like we'd either
have to get a room where one person has
to sleep probably on like a lesser bed
like a couch or so and that's not
nice or a room that's too big where we
would probably have space for four
people minimum
we got to make it four then yeah we
could have two couples two
[Music]
rooms that' be fun
too I guess it could be fun I have four
wives no three when we're four in
[Music]
total I still have a lot of time to
think I still I'm not sure yet when I
would go
anyway but
usually January February shouldn't be
too busy I
think cuz it's after New Year's and
stuff well the B trips will happen for
sure for sure
it's difficult to plan with cie she has
like so many things planned ahead she's
so
busy it's a bit difficult with
[Music]
her Gaden to Austria yeah Gaden Gaden
Anda will be visiting me seemingly
within the year if things don't get too
crazy
that's crazy
though can't
[Music]
imagine let's
go be nuts
yeah I'm very open to go wherever they
want to go cuz I don't think we'll stay
only in Austria I think we would go to
other countries too and there's so many
good choices in
Europe I have
have some at least one country in my
mind that I think would be good
for
them [\h__\h] in
spook will you offer them M balls nah
no no if anything I would go eat Saka to
with them and other nice food not not
freaking mot
balls okay anyway thank you so much
Munda for the kiss I'd like to give mine
to all of the rest of kfp you hear that
[Music]
kfp come to
America you know there's one thing that
I found out about about America that I
find fascinating that I want to see one
day but it's also
like m what do you call that word I
think it ends with
opic opic uh dyst dystopian not opic
dystopian there's a very dystopian thing
or dystopic is that a word
too um that I discovered recently about
America and I I kind of want to see it
but at the same time I don't want to see
it because it seems
[Music]
insane
and I feel
like I don't know it's hard to explain
when you want to see something but you
also don't want to see it you want to
know what it is I think it's only in
like the middle of
America bies
[Music]
[Laughter]
bies Buck
is yeah look it up if you don't know
what it is it's spelled b u c e e
s the [\h__\h] gas
stations it's dystopian
[Music]
the [\h__\h] gas stations are
insane how did you know about this place
I only found out about it recently
because I was binge watching Jet leg the
game on YouTube and um they were doing
like uh racing through America from the
northmost part to the sou most part and
they and also in a different episode a
different season too I think uh I saw
bies and I was like what the [\h__\h] this
is impressive and amazing and also
disturbing very disturbing it doesn't
seem like you need that many gas
stations is it ever filled up that
much that it would be full I doubt
it it's very off footing when going in
I'm the inside is amazing too right but
I also think just the gas stations are
already insane they are full on holiday
weekends really you have no idea they
can be
really it's [\h__\h]
insane it's insane so I want somebody
maybe C to take me on a road trip and
then drive me to a
bies and then after that we can go to a
waffle
house but it's like only on in like the
middle part of America right it's not on
the coast Co coish countries right I
think from what I understand
only like in the middle of [\h__\h]
nowhere on the countryside of the middle
middle like Texas
yeah it seems like it's in the middle of
nowhere from what I've
seen yeah yeah it's like a giant company
in gas station yeah yeah yeah I saw I
saw they got some cool stuff there not
going to lie
[Music]
gas
station you should go you should also go
to Costco I've been to Costco in
Japan but that's the only place where I
ever been to one I wouldn't mind going
to one again it's been a long time and
uh I didn't quite
grasp the reality of it back
then I want to go uh in America to
Costco but do wait do you need
membership yeah right you need a
membership in American Costco too right
it's not just
Japan Costco cookies but it makes no
sense really for me to go shopping in a
Costco when I don't live in the area CU
everything's like
bulk I should just go and then look
through and then the only thing I'm
gonna buy is apparently there's hot dogs
okay then that's the only thing I'm
gonna buy like the food cord
stuff there's a crost in France
oh probably not the same go with
giggy all
right does giggy have a driver's license
I mean she drives taxis but does she
have a driver's
license okay she drive me to a
[Music]
bies I mean that would probably be
really far
but well just generally can she drive
into a Costco G do you have a driver's
license or are you just posing as a taxi
[Music]
driver I I think she said she doesn't I
I think I remember her saying that in
her
stream I think you
don't time to get one gigy get one for
your stai drive me
[Music]
around I think she said that in her
stream was that CeCe I feel like they
both don't have one
gigy doesn't seem like a person to have
a license think it's only has a license
really I feel like herb has a license
like she seems like someone who would
have a license and
laa La does but she says she shouldn't
what do you mean
shouldn't
[Music]
H gy has one
really gy drives really
[Music]
doesn't like
driving I wonder if she ever drove in
Japan
before not confident in her skills okay
I mean that's really rare somebody is
saying somebody who has a license not
confident in driving that's really
concerning like even shitty drivers
don't seem to be concerned about their
skills s really concerning
[Music]
oopsie see I've barely read super chats
cuz i' I'm having fun talking to you
guys let me let me
continue h for7 py
an Soul thank you for
the
sh wow no text at
all thank you so much for your support M
mwah mwah mwah
Mah you're you're like one of those
people who never write in the normal
chat I don't know if you're here right
now or if you're more of a VA Watcher
but thank you so much for your support
very very nice of you very kind I
appreciate it thank you for your
generosity
[Music]
got turned down for L engineering
position because he said he has a
license but he's not confident in
driving do engineers Lan need a
license like would that be the breaking
point the [\h__\h]
[Music]
where are you I hear you oh you're there
under the table suddenly smoothie under
the t under the table cat under the
table why going to get you out of there
come here come here don't don't lur
around in the shadows under the
table show yourself
[Music]
oh I got her probably now she's
wet I assume she
is I'm not going to touch her I'm not
going to touch her purposefully on the
butt you you're fluffy oh you she's wet
on her chin
[Music]
did you do some sippy
sippy Mrs sippy sippy
Mississippi hydrating so that later you
can surprise me with a wet butt M I see
how it is I
[Music]
see okay I have absorbed some more cat
hair this is good I see every
opportunity of touching my cats as an
opportunity to um get rid of some of
their hairs for
[Music]
them
G reply to
[Music]
me she does have a
license let's go drive me to Costco
sometime please thanks
[Music]
let's
go hope she doesn't drive like she does
in her
streams really [\h__\h] stressed
[Music]
out Crazy Taxi
g py
d d K thanks for the pinky happy
birthday waa thanks for the past year
together with kfp and all those memories
you made with us please know that kfp
always has your back okay get some
chicken mustache if life ever gets rough
here's a pink coupon for one thank
you yeah I'm definitely going to get
another one in
Japan I still have this weird pain deep
on my left
shoulder uh on like not on the shoulder
but lower behind the shoulder blade it's
weird it doesn't go away hurts like a
bastard like a son of a
[\h__\h] shoulder blade you not say
shoulder
blade you do
[Music]
right
ah been lifting
no I've been boxing but it was already
paint painful before that don't know
what I did think I just slept
weird
[Music]
probably what did the doctor say about
the last time last time E I mean this is
new this is something else this is
[Music]
separate oh yeah I've heard about
massages from the ID
girl those notes froma I'll take them as
a reference
yeah thank you Dominique thank
you I'll I'll make use of the
coupon SP wonderful thanks for the pinky
wa birthday okay you know you make me
believe phoenixes are a type of angel
with your angelic voice and your
angel-like personality and cuteness I
just love your voice and singing so much
when I hear you I'm happy thank you
that's nice if me singing makes you
happy then you have an easy shortcut to
happiness just got to open my Spotify
it's as easy as
[Music]
that she meowing at the
door I'm not letting you out girl you're
crazy she
crazy yeah so in order to stay happy Dr
Wawa tells you to continue listening to
W
music a guarantee to happiness
simple ton dang Jacob 47 dang for the
red super chat happy birthday to the
cutest orange Idol Phoenix oi there ever
was it's been a great year so far and I
know the rest of the year will be just
as fun I got tickets to both days for
breaking Dimensions at w
tour can't wait to see everything you
have in store wa oh my
God damn you're
winning you're
winning have fun
[Music]
on
luck
yeah damn share your luck of some of the
Unlucky Ones Will
you but no it seems like most of you
guys who who wanted got what they
wanted I'm not jealous at all e did you
try and fail
[Music]
I hope
not
well except
me next
time really the good thing is about
being kfp is like even if you missed out
on like breaking Dimensions you have
several chances to you know see me at
the world tour even if only two of them
are in America still like in theory you
have several chances this through this
uh World Tour which is way more than you
would get with other oshis
maybe you'll go to Atlanta for me let's
go thank you looking forward to seeing
you there oh my God chunky wony no
smoothie what' you do a you jumped up
didn't you I just heard
[Music]
something yeah I know the CU was
insane absolutely
[Music]
insane that reminds me of something let
me do this really
[Music]
quickly okay I need to I need
to say something really
quickly what was it
[Music]
what was
my oh no I don't remember I don't
remember what
my thing
was never
[Music]
mind or
no I think we're good I don't
remember okay thank you
Jacob thank you sh see you at all of
those concerts let's
[Music]
go coton things the red CH happy
birthday
Tel thank you so much happy birthday to
me
indeed it's already been like over 2
[Music]
weeks next birthday so far so far
but you can still get my birthday
merchandise if you want to it's
currently on
sale thank you na for the
support Studio of the
[Music]
pinky stre
and course is
[Music]
[\h__\h] description box is missing a link
yeah cuz I copied the settings from the
previous witch spring
stream it's okay it's okay it's okay
we'll be fine we'll survive I think
people who are in this stream are pretty
hardcore anyway the ones who want merch
probably have merch uh ordered already
[Music]
right thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you Manuel
Schneider I than Lulu than you for the
pinky happy birthday thank you so much
Lulu
[Music]
flaming pants than infinite hech thanks
for the pinky happy birthday wow I'm
wishing you a happy birthday indeed it
was a happy burpday a burp was happy on
that day many burps were
happy the happiest birthday ever thank
you so
much razor x d Dixon Le D FIP D crow in
the Box D jelly red d
Jack Redwing thanks for the pinky Ki
happy birthday my favorite streamer my
one and only Kam
oi I hope we could celebrate your
birthday many more years on also
coincidentally the previous year while a
birthday pack just recently
[Music]
arrived oh you know who else
arrives hey
last year's birthday did you order me a
geek check or
what probably cuz it's a Hungarian Super
Chat oh my
God oh my
God one year well at least they timed it
to another
birthday they were like oh we're late
already but six seven months might as
well wait another couple of months to be
timed with the birthday the next
birthday might as well move it a little
bit more to
later I hope that doesn't happen again I
hope this one comes earlier Jack I'm
sorry about that man it
sucks at least I didn't get
lost knocking on wood and on Heaven's
Door
[Music]
for the pinky happy birthday dear wa you
are such an amazing and talented Idol
and person the amount of happiness and
joy you bring to me and thousands of
jimins are incredible I always feel so
proud and cool when I tell people that
wa is my Kam
really thank you a I'm glad you feel
like
that man you the B
thank you so much I appreciate it I'm
glad when you guys can feel
confident about
wa I'll try to make you guys more
proud with the concerts and all
that thank you Ryan C dunu 7771 D Garden
Park
[Music]
not
P I think thanks for the pink Super Chat
happy birthday wa today is your day I'm
so happy with that
sing W waah
[Music]
I appreciate it thank you Korean Super
Chat from Australia wow wow no no wonder
you have a a a rat in your profile
picture is this Bay in
Disguise
n superan blue D JT mations
D Kim
[Music]
I think yeah thank you for your red
Super
Chat Phoenix birthday is first birthday
or last
rebirthday oh Phenix birthday is
basically just for the sake of having a
[Music]
birthday it's just it doesn't it's not a
real
birthday we just celebrate so that we
have something to celebrate ah which is
nice thank
[Music]
youal SciFi freak scii freaki
freak k
s mama
typh thanks for the red super chat my
tal my queen my oi over 4 years I think
I've said how much I admire and love you
more time than I can count and it is
still true after 4 years and it will be
true for many years more to come I will
cheer you for as long as I can because
you've earned
it wow thank you so much
W that sounds promising it's a promise
it's a
promise yakusoku thank you so much for
staying with me for so long much
longer our future together is
wonderful
[Music]
promising but I'm from myth yeah
weird I your friend for the pinky and
cheering emojis yeah thank you for
cheering for
me CH D starting to feel sick
man
oh too much I didn't even drink the full
bottle feel sick
[Music]
I don't want to end it Midway
through but there's still a lot there's
still a lot
yeah I'm starting to feel sick from the
energy drink what the [\h__\h] how much was
in there but it's like natural Cofe does
it have
[Music]
talvine no I don't see
any don't think it says
[Music]
any hi
smoothie crashing already did you eat I
didn't eat uh dinner yet because I mean
it was lunch I just had lunch like
something like lunch before the
stream cuz I had big ass tomatoes in the
fridge and mozzarella that my mom mom I
think left so I had mozzarella and
tomatoes with balsamico vinegar
and
uh those
leaves is that an empty stomach I ate
pistaches
[Music]
too I love this game I had so much fun
today with it
man I had so much fun with it today
today was so chill I feel like the first
3 hours went by really slowly but then
after that everything was going like
smoothly and chill and like you
know yeah let's play more soon while I'm
in
Japan really cozy and good progress and
fun the story was uh kind of like
grasping me today
interesting story progress lots of new
characters that we met a lot of new
characters today it was
fun makes the drink more effective
really if you drink it with
food uh well I had the
pistachios I can't have a full meal on
stream I'm not
way hey chuny W both cats are in the
room y they want me to end the
stream hi
[Music]
baby who was your favorite new girl
chunky wonky don't jump up
here not doing my stream okay you cute
you me and favorite new girl the the the
new
witch Irene or whatever her name was her
name is hard to remember
[Music]
Ira yeah my stomach is upset
now I need to eat something going to eat
something and then maybe I'll lay down a
little bit I still got
[Music]
time should
I junky wonky pushing down the F with
your
leg so cute
oh she's rubbing her face against the
iPhone oh now she's oh she turned around
to get belly rubs oh y she's
purring belly R belly R
belly ah she cannot ever get enough
belly rubs man this girl is
[Music]
crazy y
you need to show that you are the myth
speaker of I'll do so badly
probably what kind of words will they
come let's can I is there like
online online spelling be is there any
webs okay
they they would say a word out loud and
I would try to spell it
right how do I start
this what how do I start
this how does this work
what what this is not what I think it
[Music]
is what is this
yeah yeah they want us to
suffer they're going to make us
suffer okay here
um how
about give me
a stationary word
[Music]
pen clipboard clipboard
we going to type it in somewhere pencil
case wait it Tapped Out the [\h__\h] tap
tape oh come on it's really laggy
calculator
calculator easy is it going to be Speedy
like you got to be Speedy too what did
you say brush I I don't I don't know
what he said didn't hear [\h__\h]
you these are baby words
yeah can can they a paintbrush can they
not give me like more difficult ones
[Music]
immediately I cuz I pressed
hard doctor
[Music]
ridiculous
hairdresser remember Road's is what
[Music]
scientist
ah dishwasher so
[Music]
laggy Lumberjack Lumberjack while we
getting more difficult now dancer dancer
[Music]
Artist
Baker B
[Music]
Baker politician
politician Okay window cleaner
wow reporter reporter this is jobs
now car salesman car
salesman teacher
[Music]
teacher nurse I want to get to the
difficult
ones
Carpenter good that they don't ask the
meaning of it mailman
mailman policeman
policeman this
aign contest as
[Music]
well waiter
waiter
firefighter firefighter
uh Musician
musician I'm spelling them farmer
Farmer but I guess receptionist saying
it out loud maybe is more difficult than
typing
it it might yeah that is that the catch
driver cuz now I'm just typing it
cashier
cashier electrician
[Music]
mechanic okay wait let's let's not
computer
technician okay let's just do technician
t e c h n i c i a
[Music]
n but now I'm not typing it so will I
fail this in the in the oh
God better type it out pilot p i l o
t doctor d o c t o r hairdresser h a i r
d r e s s e
r scientist s did we already had those
did you reset me s c i e n t i s
t dishwasher d i s h uh w a s h e
[Music]
r Lumberjack l u m b e r j a c
k
wow dancer d a n c e
r artist a r t i s u r a r i s b a k e r
it's too easy
chall p o l i t i c i a n I almost said
s because C seems like an El but that's
not what I meant my brain was thinking
of c w i n d o w c l e a n e
r can I just say V instead of w cuz in
German it's V and it's so much shorter
than
[Music]
W okay I'm going to stop there this
boring
boring don't rush I don't know maybe
they're going to count the time
[Music]
too
okay my stomach and my cats need my in
attention so I shall now
[Music]
perish see you uh in a few hours 3 and a
half
hours on is it on am's Channel or GAA
Channel I think I'm it is
[Music]
it I'm
it am be is she going to show up as a
Bee be I should show up as
frogy froggy came to see
Ami but I think it will be only
[Music]
pngs I'm
you know how I'm going to spell every
word all please spell
polition Please spell
detective Please
spell uh love
interest Please spell cutie
patoti Please
[Music]
spell oh that would be funny if that
came up s t a r d e n b u r d e n h a r
d e
n b a r
t it's not even a real
word they should give us German words to
spell extra round for me and uh
CCE okay let me go thanks for watching
today see you uh tomorrow for EDF and in
a few hours at Amy Channel
[Music]
Andy by bye EGF
EGF EGF EGF
[Music]