[Music]
so
hello hello
you stopped moving for me
oh now you move again
welcome to the collaboration i am
training
amelia today as a kfp employee
yay oh i'm excited to be an intern
and do work that connection has been
lost you know what i think we can
do it without being in each other's room
okay uh because people are gonna
probably have two windows open anyway
okay i don't know this has been
happening since uh two days i don't know
why but we'll figure it out
we don't need it we don't need it we are
connected by our hearts right
yes our souls ame
is helping me today
to do something important
uh i have been building
a house with some chickens and um
i've uh they have um procreated so much
that it's uh been giving me a hard time
to collect all the eggs
so i hired uh watson
industries is that how you say it
industries or yeah
industries what's an industries
to work for me also she's my i hired her
once i opened up membership i hired her
anyway against her will
so she has no choice she will help me
build an automatic egg collection
cart underground system and you're good
with rails anyway right
huh rails are your thing right oh yeah
yeah
yeah yeah we specialize in rails here at
watson industries
and inside industries i thought it was
industries
i mean you know it's potato potato
tomato tomato
industries is that british aren't you
british
amelia yeah mike
are you in the server yet i'm trying to
connect uh
yeah i'm i'm here i'm just gathering
materials okay
uh uh nice viewers have sent me
uh references on how to do it
so we will try to copy that there was a
i've often sent
some various uh
ways to do it but um
one person sent me a chicken friendly
way to do it
and of course i wanted to be chicken
friendly
yes i've copied the blueprints uh they
did not copyright their intellectual
property
so it's up for grabs and it's mine now i
own it
eh you own it now damn
okay i'm in the game like crying
virtually i didn't show i didn't show
that
i just spawned in my room but i didn't
show my stream yet what happened in my
house
do you want to come over ame uh
okay i'm just making sticks really quick
hold on
okay sticks i have a lot of sticks
though oh
many sticks okay i see i see you in your
house like
like through the walls i see you
it's creepy i can see you too
okay okay hold on i'm just building up
the last few things that we need to take
like 30 seconds
okay no problem no problem i'm waiting
kind of a bad view here i need to re
re-uh position my window so i can see
you better
uh okay
wha what are you scared of ame nothing
i mean you placed your house there uh
after mine was already placed so
it was almost like you were asking for
me to stalk you
yeah that's true
but man you got the best spot for your
house i don't know i should have thought
of that
it's beautiful thank you beautiful
all right and oh i see
and zoom i have a zoom button
no ctrl is not working as a gym someone
is telling me
wrong information in the chat
why would you guys lie to her don't lie
to me
z for j you're gonna be but i'm
fantastic oh my god does that mean
did you amen did you also install
optifine
oh yeah yeah yeah try pressing uh
c c see the button c
wow holy
i don't think that i don't think it has
to do with optifine
and they told me uh since since i
installed optifine it will work
and zoom ah she comes here she comes
i haven't played my house a little bit
welcome welcome welcome
i come in so um
everyone please look at this room and
read the sign
the one and only papa
and we have today added hookah papa to
our server
uh i made a room for him wow he changed
it already damn why
did he make it so fancy he's only been
on the stereo for two hours
he has a black bed and i wrote this sign
here hook
up a bit yes doll it
he has a puffer fish why does he have a
puffer fish oh and he's been collecting
some materials for me
like uh orange and red wool so that we
can build a
restaurant isn't that cool like he's
another one of my slaves now
yeah i'm playing i'm paid employee papa
lives with me papa has his own room very
fancy
and i have a chicken in my house now and
i have many chickens over there i have
too many chickens amen
too many we might have to call the
population a little bit
it's too many lord save me
collect the eggs collectively
you let them out oh wow that's okay
i have too many thank you some of them
can escape
okay i'll try to
[Music]
go back in go back in it's ah
okay things can't escape it's okay this
is just inevitable
[Laughter]
hello i kill you though i will kill you
i'll kill you i'll kill you with
ah
sorry what what is it called a
winner winner chicken dinner yeah
yeah why why does that phrase exist
also oh my god i i started this i did
this today in my in my
minecraft stream but holy my papa
um
my papa uh
yeah i don't know what he did here yeah
bye
and he made uh orange orange sheep
papa this is not huma how would you how
do you say humanic
human this is not humane this is a very
um
disturbing wow this hurts my heart
but wow this he did all of this in like
two hours
where did he get all the all those sheep
from
they don't maybe they multiplied yeah
but not so fast
but that's um
um i don't know what to say when i look
at this
i think some some renovation has to be
made yes amen
can i hire you for that
that wasn't in the contract
no no no i'll do it myself but i mean we
could kill some of that now now i need
the wool i need the wool i need it
anyway so basically this
chicken house uh either remove it
or we lift it right
right yeah so the blueprints that i saw
require uh
like a block down here yeah so the
the rail would be this height
where this block is here but because
your floor is
essentially this block you either have
to raise it on the inside by one block
so we can dig this out and then put it
back
because we need to get in there to be
able to put the rails on this level
so that uh it can collect the eggs at
the right height
uh i am confused
i am confused uh what is the better
option mrs amelia watson
um let me let me let me assess the
situation here
they have escaped now they will die
well i think what we could do here is
we'll kill like half of them
okay well i have enough eggs that's okay
why why would you kill half of them what
is that necessary for okay okay okay so
we'll we'll recording them off we'll
split it in half with a fence and then
we'll kill one half
why so that we can fill that half with
dirt
and then bring the other chickens from
the other side onto the raised dirt
and then we can fill it fill the other
half with dirt so that
we fill the whole thing but in in steps
uh chat would you say that that makes
sense what you guys get it right
it's i feel like i have to make a
diagram
can't you just dig down low
huh can you no no apparently no
can we not know i mean
yeah that's very noisy here very noisy
we need soundproof walls on it
yeah we can do that but then we'd have
to mine the ground under the chickens
that's fine yeah
okay so we'll go down we'll go down
three yep
maybe i need maybe we should bring a
shovel yeah
i need a shovel too okay wow finally the
chicken noises are
over my my way would have worked
too oh i believe you look at this chest
i mean look at this big chest
look what i got today in the actually in
the
watson shaft in the watson shaft oh
good choice do i have a shovel
i don't even have a shovel let's make a
shovel
oh god i have so many eggs iron i could
make some
okay maybe we should sleep okay
okay counter plus one
so adorable oh my god
i will never forget the first time i
heard amelia hick
that was beautiful yeah what is that
what is that yeah
pretty sure that was your reaction was
it was it how do you remember wow you
you're not only smart you also have a
huge memory card
i just remember really weird things
okay i'll make you a shovel too thank
you then i'll
make a uh egg chest
i have too many eggs
all right so if we dig down three
wait three yeah yeah and then we
hmm wait a second
hold on my brain is processing
yes yeah yeah yeah okay i see i get it
okay i trust you
i'm i'm i'm not really planning on using
much of my brain today anyway
because i have uh watson industries with
me so
yeah yeah this is this is my job
but i was honestly i i uh today when i
streamed minecraft
it was the first time for me to see
our server since the last collab that we
did
the five member collab i haven't played
minecraft since then i was shocked
at how how much you have done for our
server mrs watson
it was very impressive so much it has
been there has been a lot done
yes thank you wait do you have any
pickaxes
yes but in my chest be right back
i really i really like those those
stairs
and uh when i complimented your stairs
i said uh um something about the shitty
stairs that we had before
and that moment ina was watching and i
didn't know she was watching
she was like i made those shitty stairs
sorry ina they had to be uh upgraded
now but they were good they were good
while they lost they served it's perfect
uh
indeed indeed indeed
do you how many do you need pickaxes uh
just one i think
okay
i learned how to throw items there you
go wow thank you
wow i've learned so much
okay so yes now
what we're gonna do you can you see how
i put two blocks here
so this first block is originally the
floor already for your
chickens and when we're done we're gonna
dig out this so that they drop onto this
level
we're to dig out this one i mean so they
drop onto the bottom level you know what
i mean
sure sure i totally understand
this is a two by two space and this is
the
level that our rails will be on okay can
i dig on the on the road next to you
yeah but probably i don't know how long
let's see let me
how long this goes this makes sense
right guys
does it does it
should make sense it will work for sure
yes chad says yes it makes sense nice
as expected from what's in
industries with her stolen blueprints
the sound of the sheep and the chickens
it's really nice music to my ears
sorry that was not me
emma can you make can you make chicken
noises
please everyone clip it thank you
blessed blessed black
let me see how far we have to go on this
side
[Music]
you know uh it'll be kind of bad
when you have the sound of the chickens
and the sound of the sheep and then the
sound of the uh
the cart going constantly well i mean
whenever i will go there to collect my
eggs i will put on
uh you know those headphones that that
uh
that oh yeah your ear muffs
your mufflers no your mufflers i mean
like more
the sturdy ones when you when you do it
go like
yeah yeah you like fly a plane or
do uh i know what you're talking about
yeah noise canceling uh
badass headphones yeah yeah
all right so i have a task for you yes
do you have any iron
yes okay we're gonna need
a minecart and a hopper okay
i'll start putting the tracks down and
yeah
uh uh uh how do i make a hopper
i don't know i don't have a recipe for
it yet
are you sure
okay let's see i have lots of iron
beautiful i need a another chest
[Music]
ami you're so quiet what happened uh i'm
just putting the rails down
okay i'm focusing on her work yes
actually i don't think this should take
too long i think i'm almost done
wait take your time mommy
this is this is the only thing we're
doing today
actually but i don't want to think it
hurts my heart but i
do want to eventually have an automatic
grilling thingy
ah but it just hurts me to even think
about it like that that's just
my chickens my baby but in the end what
else am i gonna do with those chickens
right just
multiply them until there's like
trillions and billions
what am i doing yeah just the way of
life
wait wait uh i need a mine card with
hopper right
um yes yes yes okay so i make a hopper
and then i make a minecart
and then i make a minecart with hopper
yes yeah yeah yeah well you can just
make the minecart yeah and then you put
the hopper in the thing
oh wait not or i don't know actually
no yeah that uh that was yeah i'm mine
uh
a minecart with a hopper i have it i
have it i got it
and we need another test probably uh
yeah
yeah yeah unless you already have a
chest for eggs we can just repurpose
that
no i got it i got it
mrs watson i have been useful for once
perfect er you're you're
usually useful usually
wow it looks exactly like in the picture
yeah you're making the redstone blocks
well i found it in the nether somebody
left it in a chest so it's mine now
it's fine i can make more if they want
it back damn i have a lot of redstone
too though
yeah that's fine this is good i have
enough it's already
i did i asked in my in my last stream i
asked
how much time do they think we will need
and some said five minutes another set
one hour and some said five hours
so i'm like really confused as to how
long this actually takes but maybe it
just doesn't work the first time you try
it yeah yeah maybe yeah
why is this so easy we can almost
testing so uh i actually
miscalculated the roof so i think the
roof we're gonna have to fill this
you know like where our headspace is
we'll fill it with dirt yeah
and then we'll we'll drop the chickens
the two dirt blocks
so that they fall where our head is okay
i get it i get it
exactly okay at the same time you
started talking i saw a comment in the
chat saying the exact same thing
okay nice think they agree with you
mrs watson
all right i think this looks so
professional
i think uh this should be good enough
i'll put another one here
uh you can put it anywhere i think maybe
i might need more
i might need more rails oh more
i need more more uh gold rails i mean
for like
to keep it going constantly because i
don't have gold you need a gold to make
those
yeah yeah all right put a card on it and
we'll see oh there it goes sorry
i'll push it once it goes it should oh
my god more one more time
oh i think i need some more
stream over goodbye thank you thank you
for your services
it's good it already works what the hell
yeah all right now i just fill in the
wall thank you thank you
i'm impressed all right let's let's pick
up this cart if you could
uh uh how oh i stopped it just hit it
yeah
you might i mean yep
uh do you have any dirt because i don't
think i have enough uh
probably somewhere yeah i'll pick it up
yeah i'm all out and then uh what we can
do
is uh um i guess we can build it
i guess it can be right here we can
build like a little
a little place to collect your stuff
because we'll well the chest will have
to go somewhere
hmm oh wait why did i put one single
rail did i take a rail from somewhere
ah you probably picked it up while i was
doing stuff how can i how can i give you
the whole
64 package uh go into your inventory and
then pick it up with the mouse and drop
it
right why did i forget that i am stupid
thank you do we need torches in here
maybe to brighten it up while we're
working
ah oh hold on hold on i have
i have an idea there we go does that
work for you i'm holding a torch in my
hand and it broke it brightens up
everything because of the uh
no but it's okay i don't see the light
but
as long as you see the light and don't
hurt yourself while you're
practicing your practices
damn she's skilled
damn she know what she doing
i think all right we're gonna have to
send the uh my
okay so put the minecart with the hopper
and uh send it on its way and then we'll
we'll follow the rest
wait why is it separated how do i put it
back together chad how do i put it back
together i think if
if you put the minecart on uh the non
actually you can put it on the red part
and then uh just put the hopper inside
of it oh my god
oops i have to craft it again i have to
like put it together
[Music]
goddammit like if you pick it up once
it's uh
just dissolved i didn't know i didn't
know
okay this
and this makes this okay
i'm coming back
okay and i'm back so just put it down
like this should it should i start uh
should i push it
what yeah yeah push it and then when
it's on its way okay
is it going yep will it just really go
endlessly what if we log out what if
does it still collect when we're all
logged out
i wonder it should i think
so then uh the chest we would put like
here
and then uh we could shorten this to
make it like
two steps instead of three
here and then now just uh
yeah that works but okay not gonna work
not gonna work well yeah cause we have
to
we have to finish taking out the rest of
the uh floor in the chicken house
oh so that's a good test apparently
i'll make one more okay yeah yeah but
wait are you guys thinking like
are we gonna i want to be there when
when we um
oh wait okay okay should i i can
um oh did you forget to put the hopper
in the thing oh
no no no it's in there
what's in there it's in there you guys
open your eyes guys
should i bring some seeds so that we can
distract the chicken
ah that might yeah that might be helpful
so i can dig
uh what did i come here for uh for a
chest okay
bird brain forgetting what i came to do
in two seconds
upper direction chest under rails oh
chest has to be under the rail okay we
can do that
okay like under under or just like
if we dig if we dig
like there it should be okay if we put
it here
chest oh the chest has to be under the
rail with another hopper
oh okay i'll make another problem
no under under oh okay one more happen
one more
okay happy happy
happy happy ah on my chest so many
chests
one more
okay i got it i got it i got it
but if i do a double chest don't i need
two hoppers
uh i don't know i don't know how it
works
no okay apparently no
i got i got one test and a happy
hey hold on i gotta move this block
really quick
ah one hopper shift click to chest okay
this game is like so smart you can do so
many things
yeah i'm fascinated there's a lot you
can do i wonder if they
ah wait what do you guys say underneath
you mean like what do you i don't know i
don't understand
hey i thought that this can like exist
without a block
no no i don't think so
sad hey but i feel like i saw that
before
weird ah oh wait what if
put rail on top of hopper okay oh okay
okay okay
all right wait but
uh first chest
go away and then
hopper shift click
down one more level underneath
uh just
one more level down
chest under the hop ah you mean like oh
you mean like here the chest
oh oh where did the chest go did you
pick up the chest
oh yeah i have it sorry i but we're
gonna make two
move
yeah you can take just take out the
other rail too
all right for now i'll uh do this
okay do you wanna yeah
put that chest down there
oh no i'm just putting this there we go
oh god the chicken noises make them stop
you can turn it down yeah but
it feels like i'm muting my family i
don't want to do that
you can't open the chest if there's a
block over it what really
hmm
i keep on hearing the plan
but doesn't that the chest have to have
to be placed first
oh yeah you have you have one chest
you want to put that next to it and then
shift click yeah
people lie to me ah okay shift right
good
wow but this is supposed to go
this is supposed to go
the rail yeah can it not go on top
next to it uh but apparently
we don't need another hopper apparently
it just has
to have one healthy
i don't know i mean don't you have the
chest
i give it to you yeah no i don't have it
yeah i give it to you
no i don't have it is it somewhere here
i
i dropped it and and uh i saw you pick
it up well unintentionally pick it up
oh weird weird i'll make one more
off the block slab okay i'll go make a
slab really quick
in the my chest if my chest is in the
chest
what what
is the chest in the chest
no chess is not on the chest ah you mean
in my other chest
let's see i placed it
what do you mean in the car what yeah
but i need i made two
chests guys i um
side chest side
side side side chest okay
yes and this will be placed here
but don't we need a block
damn i got it i got it but they said it
will not open
oh it does open egg party
cat party egg party let me get my dirt
ready
yep okay but
how about do you have a shovel for me
and what happened to your shovel yeah i
don't have you
yeah get
now we can fill this back up oh
why do things keep on disappearing
ah the chest might be in the mine cart
nah
no wait
okay now the chickens we lower them by
uh two blocks
okay uh ooh spada no spider
no no no no no
no no i guess that's the bad thing about
having uh automatic doors on the outside
yeah but usually they don't we haven't
seen many
issues before so uh
wow there's a huge egg party going on
wait how do we
how do we do this um so
we want to lead them away from at least
one block and then i can start from
there
okay no problem one second i'll get in
there and uh
actually i can just do it like this
they're just falling in
all right i have to see it
oh my god this is okay you know what
i'll just put them all in this
little i also fell
okay they're all going on anything we'll
dig around them after they get in there
okay oh my gosh
oh my god it looks very fluffy in there
like you could fall in there it would be
really
really comfortable bed
do you think maybe if you pull out seeds
oh okay this is
nice okay no they just keep jumping in
the hole
is that not what you wanted
where did you go um
i killed one sorry no it's a cut
i have enough i have enough some
sacrifices have to be made
well they keep getting in my way i'm
sorry
they i did not uh raise them properly
i've been too busy you know there's too
many chickens i cannot raise them all at
once
i don't know where the father went they
have no father amen
please understand education is a bit uh
poor on the server
help me i'm suffocated by my own
children
help me
[Laughter]
are you saying are you saying i look so
much like them that you can't see me
when i'm in between them
you're so
nothing is more efficient than the
watson way
all right we're almost done actually
nice
and as i expected i just
have the chicken stare at me while
watson is working
all right it should be done after this
walk
yeah get out
all right now just stairs
we could put like actual stairs here no
oh uh no problems this might this might
need to be modified a bit
ocean because i was still carrying the
seats
don't look at me go away my children be
free
be free in this one room in this one
tiny room
ah there's already five eggs in here oh
there's also a chest in the chest
that's where the chest went yeah
it wasn't there when i looked before
interesting
oh my god eggs it's working
yay we did it oh
the first automatic
first automatic system in the server
oh my god and that was so fast we only
had
it only took us like uh 30 minutes
yeah that was really fast but
okay and when it's full then it's just
it just doesn't
uh fill it up anymore but the card
probably keeps on driving i guess
but i want to see what happens if we
both log out then this is really
still collect uh it should
since the server is running on its own
so yeah everything should still
do its thing um
can i hire you again soon
i mean what are we supposed to do for
the rest of the stream now huh i don't
want to do that 40 minutes that's a good
question um is there anything you would
like to do that i can help you with
uh remember i was telling you i want to
build like a xp farm
oh yeah uh i do want to build something
like that but
i'm not sure like uh pekura did
she did um pyramid
ah yeah
yeah yeah yeah like it's all dark in
there yeah and then
i'm pretty sure the way it works is
there's like different water sources
probably like in each corner of the
pyramid that pushes them down into the
one
hole where they fall down but the thing
i couldn't figure out is a
how the door opens because they press a
button and then the door opens up top
but i was playing around with the
redstone
and it doesn't it doesn't travel
vertically it only travels on the floor
i wasn't sure how he made it so
you know what i'm saying i i
i have watched the compliance complete
stream that piccolo did but
i can yeah yeah
probably a redstone torch tower as they
say red red
redstone torch towers ah
you understand that wow someone
understands it
i get it yeah okay wanna get started
with that
well then i have to i have to think
about how we're gonna make this or where
we're gonna make it
okay let me think about it a bit
cause i kind of i guess the pyramid the
upside down pyramid is like the most
i mean it doesn't have to be yeah i
guess it makes sense for it to be an
upside down pyramid
how would we even start that i feel like
actually um
i will make some sacrifices
right now
[Applause]
i just killed like 5 million birds
oh my god this feels so
wrong it hurts my heart
i'm so sorry
how could you know your own children
but i have so many eggs i i need to make
more space for the newborn babies
oh my god i can't stop i'm gonna stop
mean
i can't stop myself from killing my
peers
i'm getting foxy yeah that's true
that's this is an exp farm so
oh my god
yeah but okay i have to stop myself this
is too much for my heart for my soul
i feel like i've killed my family
i can't get back up
well you guys have chosen death
okay be free go
he decided to go back in
i was trying to free him oh god
let's take some eggs i will i will
create some new life right away this is
not a sad moment this is a happy moment
some lives have to go to make space for
more
but why because it's just i don't have
so much space and i need food
no i'm gonna
have an egg party you wanna watch how
they hatch
okay sure okay one second
egg bazooka
[Laughter]
and another generation has been born
wait so what was the point of that uh
well we
kill them to get meat but the the the
chickens keep on recreating new eggs so
we have endless meat
i see i see i see ice and also we get
feathers for
arrows and we kill them smart huh
i just honestly i just wanted cute uh
chickens so that's all i wanted
oh my god yeah the cape you have is
pretty cool where'd you get that
the what the cape oh
uh wait turn around amen
you don't have one apparently i got it
through
uh ah my shader for i think my shader
not of the fun
like when you install the shader that i
have you get my cape
apparently ah i didn't get a cape hmm
hey but are you using silver
yeah oh don't know eh other people say
it's optifine cave why don't you have
the optifine captain
i don't know yeah interesting
well all right so sleep i think i've
made my choice i thought about it a
little bit
okay
sometimes your pyramid that she made
it's really high up in the sky but i
don't think we need to do that
okay there is there would there be a
reason for being so
high up maybe just chat to you because
it looks cool
do you see a reason
is there a reason yes there is a reason
there it is uh the fall damage
okay but we don't have to make it so
high up
um do you not have enough blocks
oh i should have enough blocks yeah i
have i have a ton of cobblestone
me too i also have a lot of blocks like
we still need more
i don't think we need to make like um
i'm just trying to think of the layout
for it i don't want to copy her exactly
like i'd rather come up with it myself
you guys like
why do i have so many eggs to help
because of me
when you work with kiara once you go
back home
you cannot get rid of the eggs for the
next seven days
is this is this my my payment yes eggs
i hope you're satisfied thank you very
much for your services
i guess it's worth the thing
you can have your own chicken in your
house now
oh yeah i can make more chickens yeah
why would you if you if you have a
chicken farm already in your
neighborhood
yeah i could just take eggs from you and
you would you would never notice yeah
i have so many too many too many eggs
kill like half your chickens and then
you would never notice
they can only be killed by my own hands
i'm their man okay
i'm their family okay i mean i did kill
a few willows uh
you know it was an accident though
okay so i think i've decided the
location
possibly for our xp farm unless it'll
look too ugly here i don't know we can
build something on top of it
did you did you when you killed those
chickens did you make a grave for them
at least
ah i mean i used my shovel and i dug a
lot so their body might have gotten
buried at some point
okay good enough thank you
you want to say some words to remember
them by
yes i don't know which one of you
it was but i hope you had a good life
uh with your friends with your family
with your companions
but in chicken heaven at least you will
not be made into a phoenix burger so
it might have been a better life we have
amelia
um only to thank her she she has
given you another chance in some way
please see it positively
yeah the phoenix you'll be reborn
through your eggs
yeah what the phoenix will be reborn
like a phoenix they will be reborn
through their eggs
like a phoenix yeah pretty much
rest in peace my dear chickens
beautiful i would like to change the the
outside uh design of my
of my chicken house someday though it
must look bad i actually want to build a
huge chicken on top of it
oh my god like uh some pieces
yeah big duck yeah oh
cute all right so i've decided
yes we will try to build
decided to hit okay
uh we'll try to build it uh we're saying
we have to build it in the ocean so
we'll we'll take good as old atlantis
spot because she's not gonna build it
there
oh really where we'll put it why did you
yeah her mind
because she wants to build it in a coral
reef biome and i tried looking for one
but i couldn't find any and
i'm pretty sure there's one like really
really really really far
then what what did we uh dig
for
[Laughter]
okay let's leave that question
unanswered
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's okay it was fun and we have found
uh well we can do something else with
that spot probably
it will it will be yeah we're well worth
something else
also there was a village there so that's
that
there was oh yeah yeah yeah there's a
yeah we could we could put all our
automatic farms
there maybe actually maybe they would be
better off closer
yeah it should be closer but for the xp
farm i think it's fine for it to be
pretty far away yeah yeah because we
don't need it every time just when you
want to like enchant something yeah hmm
sounds good to me uh yeah get your
levels back for whatever you need it for
dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun
dun
wow i feel like such a farmer when i
play this game
is this my real purpose to be a farmer
farming stimulation satisfying indeed
indeed
wait sorry i'm almost uh back with you
it just feels um a bit wrong if i leave
my
my field without planted seeds
it feels wrong thank you time where are
you anyway
i'm in my house just gathering resources
for the next project
okay
um
amelia not only detective
but also architect is there anything she
cannot do
i doubt it
everyone hire amelia watson
my schedule is uh booked currently but
you can go through
uh my assistant who is your assistant
your dog tina oh you know
have you heard the tragic that has come
upon ina
what happened while i was streaming i
was like oh let's check out how
uh inna's house is looking and i went
over there
and pretty much
uh 90 of the cows were gone
you know how she had like millions of
cows there
yeah and they were all gone and you know
didn't know i thought that she just like
he ate most
but it's very repopulated was this
papa was this my papa again
it's really repopulated now how did this
happen um oh and sheep's
went since when it cooked
why is there sheeps now
i think she was uh i think she might
have been playing a little bit earlier
got the night oh it was not
my papa anyway she we were like okay why
did this happen did someone eat all the
all the uh all the cows because it was
really like
only like four cows or so in the in the
in beside
in inside the fences so
inna logged in and she checked it out
and she realized that she left like a
glass block
somewhere here and that's how they got
over the fence
and she was like i have only myself to
blame is what she said
was very sad very sad but she
repopulated that so quickly
damn yeah good job you ready yes
i'm ready okay now you're my intern
okay oh i need a bucket
okay i i have a bucket if you want it
but i don't have it in my hands right
now
okay you get your bucket i'll get my
bucket i think we'll need okay
like a few boogies actually i got that
bucket from inna
so i'm sure she doesn't mind she will
never get it back i'm sorry you know
where is it where's my bucket oh this is
a very big project it's okay if we don't
finish it
[Music]
oh yeah i'll i'll stay with you for one
more hour because after that i have to
do super jets
okay that's fine i need more
i need more um i need more coal
damn am i running out of coal do i have
more coal
honey you can use your bucket to get
lava
you can use the lava for your furnace
what how does that work
uh you just fill your bucket with lava
and then you put in the furnace and you
take your bucket out
and how long does that work i don't know
actually i think somebody said it's like
15 more than coal
15 times more
[Music]
amazing the knowledge that that is
inside you does it not
like is it not heavy to have so much
knowledge
amelia well chat chat they like forced
the knowledge on me
wow wow
well
um sorry i've been uh trying to
organize all the stuff
just put it all in there more eggs more
feathers
if you see a bucket just take it
okay did you find it i see a bucket oh
it's in my bucket
oh oh i see a bucket is it the milk
bucket that milk
where did my pocket i'll just make a new
one otherwise
there should be a bucket there should be
there has to be a bucket okay
i have the pocket i have the bucket i
got the bucket is there anything
anything else i need
[Music]
all right we should sleep now though
okay let's sleep together
on the other side of the room you gotta
check out what i wrote on the other side
of this
size i did that after my stream
calliope for whenever she comes back
she has a a bed next to a chicken which
might resemble
me but at least like like she doesn't
want to sleep right next to me
but she'll sleep next to this chicken
which will hopefully remind her of me
yeah like subconsciously exactly she'll
wake up and she'll be like wow i miss
kiara yeah
i feel like that that will work
definitely it's good that you have a bed
for her because uh she always picks up
her bed after she sets the respawn point
ah that's a weird habit
yeah and she doesn't even does she still
not have a house
uh that hole over there you see that
hole
oh that's uh that's cali's house
kelly's house she just she decided to
leave my comfy cozy house
for this
oh she has a bed wow
she also dug into my tunnel over here
but it's fine
should i pick up some water here uh
yeah if you want yeah well we have to
take well yeah that's fine
i don't know no actually because we need
the source i gotta take it from the
source
from the source
i got it all right
we're going to take the minecart all the
way
next mission experience point
farming tower right
well i don't think we'll finish it today
but we might get pretty far
okay i have a good idea of how to do it
i trust you i trust you ami i respect
you
i have so much reason to take this car
okay
um how far do we go
all the way oh okay i'm going down
x x atlantis spot
hmm okay yeah we'll have to change the
signs since it's not gonna be atlantis
anymore
i'm zooming in on you ame oh
it feels much slower when i'm zooming ah
makes me dizzy
oh cinematic oh my god
into this floor
[Music]
we could shoot amen we should make a
movie in minecraft
or we should make like a sitcom episode
and put in like
laughter laughter noises afterwards
yeah okay i like it if you write it i'll
help shoot it okay i'll write it
it will be okay but we also need uh inna
to co-write it for some bad puns
that's a genius idea sit down with
uh all the halloween members uh
featuring minecraft and stupid jokes for
inna
i think some people have already
animated some stuff uh some minecraft
stuff about us yeah that looks so good
i retweeted uh one of them i think
looked so
like damn like how did i do that
yeah but if we make it ourselves we can
add like dialogue and stuff
yeah and we can voice it ourselves we'll
have cali do the uh soundtrack
okay i don't think we need to put so
much effort into that
yeah yeah you're right low quality we
don't have much of a budget
uh detective watson
yeah that's true well then again well
yeah i mean
maybe there will be some people who want
to
uh how do you say
free work in uh invest invest in time
sitcom yeah
damn it's it's a long long shaft huh
a long mineshaft oh we're we're almost
there this is the last part actually
okay
yeah when we make a right that's like
yep this last part
okay i remember i remember this draft
yeah that one's pretty big i wanna dig
more there's a bed here
oh two beds oh yeah
minecart emergency bed made it wow
hooray
that's very uh motivational i like all
the signs that you
all put in here thank you
very inspiring i didn't have to ask one
thing
there's free chat yeah this is for
uh treasure hunting this is our dock oh
i wanna go sometime soon
yeah we should we should all do treasure
hunting if we we end up doing collabs
again soon
or the weekend everybody collab it's so
pretty or we could just go just us oh
you wanna go there
what okay so we're we're just uh i'm
just uh
i think we'll make it like in the middle
of this thing and i just need to ask
chat
uh what do you guys say fall damage from
the
zombies uh how many blocks of fall
damage is the
ideal amount for the last hit because uh
the idea is if you're making it high up
you're doing it because you have
more vertical space so that they drop
and somebody says
20 22 23 okay we'll do
we'll do we'll do 23 blocks okay
i'm gonna start building a bridge here
okay
you you you boat around uh you know do
whatever and then
i'll let you know i will need you soon
okay okay okay i'm boating around
yeah the water looks so nice with the
shaders
yeah it does unfortunately though with
the shaders it makes it harder to
um makes it harder to find
treasure uh treasure because the boats
you can usually see them loading in but
with
the shaders because it's so shiny you
can't really see under the water
for long distances yeah
i see enderman looking at me from very
far away
handle man you want to fight huh i see
you're just lonely
you want to come home with me i don't
have any seats with or wheat with me god
damn it
and the man are you okay
i'm not looking at you he looks cute
meh meh
sorry killed you
yeah i'm just uh i'm almost almost done
i'm just going to redo
everything that i did why why why
it's not uh it's not even
okay oh my god there's so many and
there's an enderman party
or is that oh only one that just go it
moves really fast
oh i'm at cuda's old house
ah did she move her house too
uh i think so she mostly has been like
at her underwater cave um by us
i think she might have some stuff in
there still but like junk pretty much
oh how sad like an emergency
bunker it's like um like uh
how do you say like ruins uh
of of like an historic historic building
that was pretty funny we spent all that
time
yeah oh my god there's so many sheeps
i'm gonna bring them well you know is
the
tunnel idea was it was my idea um
but uh yeah it didn't work out
emma do you like ice skating
i've never been ice skating before what
yeah i mean one day if we meet in the
same country probably japan
then we will go ice skating hopefully
it's fun it's easy and it's fun i mean
in the beginning if you fall down a lot
but we should go together yeah but i
don't know how to
i don't i'm not um
it's really easy you learn it quickly
but don't you know how to ride a bike uh
you don't know how to ride a bike okay
so
i am actually also not good with riding
a bike
uh i'm really bad at it like really
but but ice skating is different
do you know how to roller skate
no i can't ride a scooter a camera at a
skateboard i don't know how to
rollerblade
i can't ride a bike wow driving a car
what i know how to drive you know how to
drive well
i don't have my license huh
interesting how did you learn to drive
[Music]
okay it's okay i'm really ice skating is
not that hard
once you figure it out i will teach you
i will hold your hand and i will
i will teach you it's really fun uh
yeah okay and one day
you should come to to my my
my my home my
my other home which i will name
where many phoenix's live and every
every winter
there's like a really really crazy uh uh
ice skating ring there yep
it's really nice i can see the the moon
through the water
wow you can come back if you want to
sleep really quick and then
and then i'm going to start i'm going to
start building up now people are saying
hand-holding is loot
what is luna mountain holding it's a
little lead
no no no it's not
nothing lured about that i see a
sparkling from the distance
me yep your enchant oh no that's a is
that
okay no that's you that's you right or a
zombie no
but it is you it's me
wow am i wearing something purple oh
yeah yeah
uh so all i did while you were gone is
make this bridge
okay beautiful it's a bridge to the moon
yeah oh that's so
so melancholic
okay come on oh yeah i came to sleep i
forgot do you have a bed do you have two
beds ah they're inside
smart you guys are so smart how do you
think of these things
well good and i would treasure hunting
we would come back here and put our
stuff back
but then we didn't want we didn't want
our uh
no no wait
it's the card uh driving away from you
wait i could catch up okay i got it
um yeah okay sleep
good night good night
good morning emma i like how we wake up
morning look at each other in the eyes
okay oh wait i'll take some of that
all right uh we're gonna build some
stairs
going up i don't know how high up
we should go actually we don't have to
do that
we don't have to do that okay do you
have
do you have cobblestone yes okay
we're going to build you can have the
other block and i'll have this block and
we're going to build up
we're going to go i should have brought
more but
you have 64. okay yeah that's fine we're
gonna go 20 up okay
okay oh look at that okay how many was
that
you count uh yep oh one
two three four five
[Music]
no you guys this is just to go up and
then we're gonna build further up after
we build our platform
how much are we going up this is good
okay this is right now we're gonna start
we're gonna start building our little
platform
okay uh we might replace i might replace
this with glass but for now we'll do
with cobblestone good that it's safe
here to fall down because i'm not sure
if i
uh understood how this works now
well uh after we build this then we're
gonna use our water buckets to make like
a little water elevator
so we can go up and down
[Music]
how big should the platform be very big
right
ah it doesn't have to be that big it was
huge
uh with piccola's stream
well this this is just like the the base
area and then
this will be like where you hit the
monsters and then
further up is where we'll we'll put the
uh
the pyramid oh should i not make it this
long
no that's good that's fine all right
i'll i'll just match what you're doing
okay oh i know how it works now i can go
until the edge i didn't know
you could just save yourself a lot of
pain no but i did i did press
shift back then i don't know what
happened maybe because you only pressed
it and like you thought it was toggle
but you have to hold it
i'm not sure what i did no ah goodbye
oh um here i'll build the i'll put the
water elevator thank you
let's see well it had to happen
you travel up there you dropped
something
okay you dropped some stones
ah with oh with space
[Music]
nice feet hatama would love your feet
[Laughter]
i'm sure she would
i think i think this is good how long we
made it
i can't move you cannot move
i
i ran out of stones no can it be out of
wood
and dirt no no no
you take this oh
it has to be well i'm going to replace
it anyway so it really doesn't matter
you're going to replace it
yeah because i'm gonna i'm gonna i think
well becca is made out of glass and i
think it looks pretty cool but it
doesn't
it doesn't have to be glass it's not the
best from here
bye-bye bye-bye it's taking a swim it's
really hot here
so a lot of hard work
sweating yes
i need a counter uh of how how often i
fall down from here
you shouldn't fall down now okay so now
from here
we're gonna build up and pretty much do
the same thing
okay all right i'll do it from
the middle i guess how many should do
from the edge how many should i count
uh this one is okay we're gonna do 23 on
this
23. okay einstein
from six seven ah nineteen
f twenty
[Music]
i forgot how many did you say 23 i think
i did 23. i did 28.
okay okay that makes sense yeah i keep
while i'm counting i keep on forgetting
how much i can
how much i needed to count yeah you're
getting too into it
okay from here we're gonna do the same
thing and build around it
okay uh i don't know i guess we'll
but if i fall down you decide how big
you let me decide okay
yeah don't oops don't fall
don't fall chiara don't fall don't fall
don't fall piano don't fall don't fall
maybe there's a way to turn it on toggle
instead of shift
or uh now it works i just
cannot lift my pinky don't lift your
pinky kiara
or what but how do i stop how do i stop
wait
[Laughter]
how do i get make them
are you going to make another elevator
wait i have the water oh yeah
oh yeah you have the water oh my god how
do we do it
you have to build back up actually
wherever you build back up from do it
from like one of the corners that we can
sort of match it
okay try to match it
okay good idea
okay i reached it i need to count in
german otherwise i can't count well
hello i'm back so uh
you want to match it then i made it way
too long over here
yep let's see if you can fix it without
falling
you have the bucket right so we'll we'll
put the we'll put the bucket uh
on this corner over here you see where
it ends it's very slim put the water
there
okay you put the water right there do
you think i can do that
just put the water am i not gonna push
you down when i come over there now
oh i think are you gonna give it to me
uh yes oh please just take it
uh um but what if the water bucket falls
down
i don't think it will okay
i don't think i can push you off
okay we'll put the water here right now
it dragged me down okay wait
wait where is my okay here okay i feel
like all the stones will fall oh wait
wait i haven't been thinking oh wait how
do i
oh also ame reminder to eat because i
always forget
reminder for what to eat because i
always forget oh
okay oh wait i'm eating raw raw potatoes
goddammit i thought
oh i only have rock i thought those were
done potatoes goddammit
well i'll stay alive
didn't you just like harvest those
what ah
i can't do it on it
what
[Music]
hard i don't know i i tried to like do
it in a way that i can also collect them
oh it's okay i'm gonna have to
go i have a lot
amelia i have an important information
for you don't
press w when you go up oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah
you just gotta let it go let it go
let it go okay i don't think we're
allowed to sing that
yeah just three words in the random
melody
let's see if that holds up in court
don't worry uh amelia you're not only a
detective and an architect you're also
my lawyer
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay let's
after this we can go
go sleep okay
[Music]
oh pretty sunset right that's what i
love about this
shader and amelia
she looks so beautiful in the sunset ah
your hair reminds me of a sunset
actually like the colors
oh thank you that's the orange the blue
amelia's just gonna stand there not
gonna do any more things don't stop
there
oh no no the golden hour is over i'm it
it's over
oh it's nice i'm working
we're almost done trying to do a short
photo shooting here
maybe song what no
oh my god i always thought i have half a
heart left
half half of a heart
[Laughter]
i'm here to fall i'm just here to fall
this is my reason my purpose my destiny
is to fall
that's what you get for slacking off
don't worry i almost got it we're almost
you can go back go back to the button
i can be useful sometimes
see i closed almost the hole
okay
okay now let's go back down and try not
to die okay
well i only have a half a heart left but
yeah
do you have some do you have some cooked
food or something
wow thanks edible i can give you raw
potatoes for that
uh that's all right okay thank you
though thank you joe
uh if you want to you can cook some here
in the furnace oh
nice good to know i don't think there's
anything to burn unless you have
we can put some of this i have charcoal
i have charcoal
oh okay does that do the trick yeah yeah
okay good night ame good night
we got to forget that i was not very
helpful just wake up with a fresh mind
i was totally happy yeah yeah it's a new
day new day
new day and a new hick
a good day starts with a good hick
good morning sunshine
wow this is this looks pretty cool so
far i think yeah
beautiful following piccolo's footsteps
[Music]
you having issues no no no no that's
fine
i got it
i'm having issues i'm gonna take down
this extra pillar that you made here
water looks so nice
huh oh why am i why am i dying again
i'm coming i'm coming my chat is
counting down as a
as me falling down that i didn't i
didn't really fall down that was not
falling down
no are you even up here no
i took the following accounts yeah it
shouldn't count oh
should not count
[Laughter]
but you fell out of the waterfall yes
and i took fall damage from that
is that isn't that unbelievable that's
not fair
uh when you get up there you can i'm
trying to give you stuff to do
um
we're gonna be building a upside down
pyramid
so i don't know exactly how to start it
so if you can think of a way to start it
you can do it i think i think right you
have the brain power
yes totally yeah i believe in you side
down pyramid okay
but like on top uh from like the
from like um how do i explain my thought
uh the base here is that the smallest
point of the
tip of the pyramid or do i build a tiny
tip
on on top of that uh
platform yeah i'll be right there okay
all done i'm almost i'm almost there
i think you you have the right idea i
think you guys already i just have to
see what
what you're talking about
just like see your explanation clearly
there's nothing to see though it's just
imagination
yeah yeah yeah you can like do a little
guide
okay i'm coming up
you know that deutsche technology is the
best
technology uh
okay i'm here okay question was
it so if we're building an upside down
pyramid
um does is it like the tiny
tip the one block tip of the pyramid
is it supposed to be in the middle i'm
thinking or is this huge platform
the smallest uh tip smallest
uh whatever whatever
let's see what's okay so
there this is this is the tip of the
pyramid you see this
[Laughter]
okay so we'll build
this is the perimeter of the tip and
then we build like staircases
up you understand like uh we should be
able to walk up each corner
from the inside oh from the inside you
want to build it
then yeah like uh
oh that makes sense we shouldn't be able
to do it like that
i think it is i think that's
but aren't we building
unnecessary blocks outside like like
like this one because we have to place
something
underneath every time to build the next
step
[Music]
we can well that's why we have this
platform here so that we can uh
yeah yeah you got the right idea i think
this is yeah okay
yeah but the highest yes
we got a problem okay so maybe go on the
other corner and then
this doesn't matter oh i see i see i see
hmm yeah
there you go
right
now we did this oh
okay okay okay okay okay i got you
watson
i think i think we got it okay okay okay
let's see
it doesn't have to be it doesn't have to
be exactly like this like now we can go
out
by two oh wait uh i think i finally
understand how i can do the thing
okay we'll go we'll go out by two this
time okay
and just to give it more um i want to
say girth but i don't think that's the
right
term with with
well with english words i will have to
trust you there
watson yep my british dictionary
watson oh wait i'm doing it why
why am i doing it differently didn't you
say that
because you didn't go you didn't go out
on the on this side you put it on top of
the one that's already existing you got
to put it
ah okay okay you just misunderstood when
i said
yeah yeah that's fine that's right okay
okay
i don't have many blocks left still
don't have many blocks i haven't i have
more hair
oh thank you oh come
if you need me to run to get more blocks
let me know
okay oh you have more no at home yeah 10
10 million as i say this is the
the fruits of our labor from the uh
tunnel digging
yeah like that's where that's where all
of our resources came from
pretty much for building i mean aside
from wood
lots of stone lots and lots of stone
and then you just extend yours by one
extent
okay on the same level you say
yeah okay oops okay
just so that uh it starts widening out
you know okay
are we doing that's right i wonder
this is well you know there's no real
right way to do it
i think for this part as long as as long
as we make it wait they wanna they're
trying to tell us something
should we send super chat to let them
know let them know what
two two two x two tip
they need a two x two hole ah oh
two by two hole up uh-huh
so
[Music]
yeah what is a two by two hole
this is the free by freehold
is it free by freehold okay
it should be fine i think it also works
yeah
okay okay
good i shall continue my
my building am i going up again
um yeah yeah yeah you don't happen to
have a water bucket do you
oh nope i do not
okay just jump down freely like a bird
yeah so you guys for the exit hole it
has to be
it has to be wide it can't be like just
one
for the hole where the the monsters fall
out
okay it has to be white okay okay okay i
got it okay we'll dig that we'll do that
at the end
so we don't fall what are we building we
are building
a tower of death every enemy that will
spawn on top
will fall down a tiny hole a really long
hole
and they will die yep and no we we get
the last hidden and then we get the exit
oh yeah right because you can activate
it with a button and then they all fall
down
and then you're gonna spin with the exp
you can do enchanting right
coolio i never enchanted something
before but
sounds cool should i widen it again my
row or
keep on going up uh i think widening it
by two
maybe maybe this time okay where you are
go oh i have no my stones left
should i go home once and pick some
stones up
oh if you don't mind i have i have some
but i get i don't think it's enough to
finish
husky i also bring some food
okay enjoy your trip thank you
probably take me like uh 20 minutes and
then i'll end the stream
okay just kidding that's fine we can do
a bit of i can do a bit of overtime you
have
helped me so quickly today
i don't know if we'll be able to finish
or test it because i gotta wait for
stuff to spawn so
finishing is probably not possible but
that's all right
i am pretty far working progress
you're so fast everything i i do with
you it just goes so fast just because i
jump efficient
almost time travel almost as fast as
your mom goes when
i i don't know
not going to finish that
i'm not good with mom jokes okay
oh my mom is watching all my streams by
the way mom i just said that because ame
does all the mom jokes it's because she
always does it
mom i i don't do mom jokes you know mom
that i don't do it
she really watches all my streams
i think i've heard her say a few mom
jokes before so i wouldn't really trust
her word here that's not true
i've said maybe one mom joke but only to
copy you
i'll never say mommy's story my mom
jokes if anything
probably just stories about my mom that
weren't even jokes but they're so funny
but they're not jokes
uh uh well i guess you're in the tunnel
so you can't sleep
when you get back you let me know yes
i'll instantly sleep
[Music]
amelia would you like to say something
to my mom
she also um watched like all the other
girls so she also checked out you
what do i remember what she said about
you
checked me out huh i just told her that
you're
you're very smart and uh
very sweet and very helpful
ah thank you
well if i say something to your mom um
oh you did a good job kiara's really
nice
uh if if i were kara's mom i would be
proud
that's so cute
well mama is very proud
ah told me she's very proud i'm very
happy
that's really nice what about um would
you like to mention any any anything
about
ground pounds um
no no not today
not not your mom that's only for chad's
mom
okay okay chad's mom okay okay
who is who is chad chad's chat
just kidding i understood and i was just
trying ah
not funny there you got me
poor chad poor chad man
always getting bullied but chad really
just doesn't learn
the lesson they keep trying to teach
amelia watson but there's nothing to
teach emilia watson
she already knows yeah she's also a time
traveler so everything you're
telling her now she already learned in
the future
or in the past or whatever
there's nothing yeah you can teach
amelia watson
and i shall sleep now sleep
ah okay hold on i gotta go back
there's there's nothing to teach amelia
watson except the height she should be
building at
interesting i got the right height
no should be right now i guessed it
myself
by reading chat and and inferring what
the correct number was based on how many
people were spamming it
why 128 for best spawn rate
okay what 128
box wide everyone's uh why
why the height why 128
apparently apparently
what did i come for oh for stones
stones stones stones stones
128 tall
oh why why because it's the best spawn
rate
they say oh why
why did did you say why again
[Laughter]
uh because that that's how the game was
programmed
what what happened
nothing you guys it works there's a
creeper that spawned on top of my
platform and almost killed me hooray
well it seems like it works yeah
yeah it's fine even if it's not that
efficient it'll probably be better than
nothing
i agree it should be fine
but the the the pyramid can still like
grow bigger no
oh did you finish it uh
what did you finish i didn't oh no no no
no they're just saying because the
creeper spawn so successful
oh no uh yeah with with the
pyramid we can still go up a little bit
and there will still be more levels i
don't think it'll be
i don't know if we'll reach 120 i don't
know what we're at we'll see
i'll be able to check once i get back up
there because okay pyramid
levels are still going up so we might
reach 128 at some point
okay they're saying to put torches
before we are
like actually using it so so we're not
getting
uh yeah interrupted
by creepers yeah trying to destroy we
work
yeah yeah stupid creepers
today when i was streaming i was leaving
the watson
shaft with diamonds in my inventory and
i was about to also end the stream
so i'm right at the door of the watson
shaft and i'm like
answering a question from the chat and
in that moment when i open the door from
the watson shaft
a creeper blows up behind me and kills
me while i'm having diamonds in my hands
it's uh yeah a lot of the mines
i had to name them like f this mine
because
that uh happens a lot
oops i went off i don't know why i did
that
yes er anyway uh
because that happened one uh one glass
panel got destroyed in that window but i
replaced it with a stone because i had
no glass
ah that's okay i can fix it at some
point
um if you will ever notice
i'll find it usually though i guess
something like that happens and if you
have dirt
uh i usually fill it with dirt because i
i'll definitely notice if it's dirt
like when i go back through it's like oh
yeah
hey wait was it really called watson
shaft
um was it really called what's in shaft
yeah that's the name of the manual okay
because everyone is laughing about the
name in my chat
i don't understand why why is it so
funny
what's so funny about what's in chat
there she goes laughing you guys say i'm
the loot one
well i didn't name it after
yes i have arrived
and with many stones and many potatoes
oh wait i also got potatoes down here
[Music]
you're here already yep never mind
what do you need watson uh
now i'm just gonna ask for pickaxe
i only have my own damage
yeah check the y level
[Music]
we're at 112 that's not bad but it'll
it'll be a bit of work to go all the way
up but we don't have to finish so we'll
just go for
as long as you said like uh uh we don't
have to go over
anything yeah maybe like 20 more minutes
yeah that's fine okay see how high we
can get
i am here hello hello
let's see i have i have lots of stones
so let me know if you need stones
okay i think i'm good for a while i
had a i had a decent amount left
wait oh i'm making too wide oh okay
oopsie
oops whatever i'll build on top
oops that's good
don't like uh
like a little area here it's like a
small lake it could be really nice to
build something there
i don't know what though you want to
build something in the pyramid
no no no there's like a little lake oh
you look behind you
see over there oh
oh yeah that's a really pretty area
maybe i like a like a holiday home
vacation a vacation house we could build
there
like a hot dog's hotel
nice watson
hotel made by watson industries
maybe not maybe not a hotel maybe i'll
build a
banana boat banana butt
yeah that'd be cool okay
what what exactly is the banana boat is
it a boat in the shape of a banana
uh yeah we can make it that what is it
actually
i think i think it's a type of boat oh
yeah let's make a yellow boat in the
shape of a banana
a giant banana in the water
sounds good i know
a bunch of yellow stuff i know what a
banana wait do i know what a banana ham
is what is a banana hot milk what is
that and what am i saying oh god
[Laughter]
where is he listen what did i just say
[Music]
what did i say no no no no no no
no no i can never get rid of the bottom
left thingy oh god
can i like can i undo what oh god what
did i say oh god
is it like a type of underwear
uh well you could say that because of
the shape yeah okay
this is embarrassing um
no you didn't know it's okay
i forgot but you know what what a
hammock is where you can like sleep in
like between two trees i thought it was
maybe like something like that
i understand once i said it i was like
wait
this is what i get for that i fell down
i'll add it to the counter
made me too nervous
um no there's a lot of words like that
that have a you know double meaning oh
it's normal oh yep okay
ah creeper i am
come closer it fell down nice oh no it's
back
don't don't don't explode don't
just just don't explode is there is
there something there
yep two creepers but i have escaped
safely on our platform and on the on the
on the lower
one uh-huh on the first one wait how do
i get
to you oh it's already it's already
effective
yeah on the lower level even how did i
get to you
did the water like uh stop oh wait no
no there should be water in the back and
in the middle
okay i'll just have to dig through it
and replace it again
okay is this tree really big or is that
just a regular tree
there's like a big tree but i guess it's
just regular it looks big
i want to see the big train it's not i
mean it's not that big but it looks
it looks pretty big from here that tree
you see it
right here in the middle of this horse
field oh it does look big yeah indeed
yeah but i can't tell because the trees
over there look
i guess they do look smaller oh they
said it's big they said it's a big tree
wow
um how do you say
[Music]
english
nice nice shotgun what's happening in
yeah observation not exactly but nice
observation
ah thank you the sun is going down
oh nice
talking about the job as a detective
in the among us stream
you were just too good of a killer
aren't you thinking about maybe like
changing your your career maybe you
could become a reaper
kelly assassin oh yeah
oh damn assassins are like really hot
that's why i like cali so much you know
oh
yeah yeah yeah badass if we go sleep
uh yep uh jump down
okay okay i'll use my last two blocks
okay when we come back it's gonna be
dangerous because we didn't put any
torches down so oh yeah that's
that's woof oh someone sent a super chat
to tell us something about our thingy
wait i shall read it in the second
i wish i could have uh done the imposter
uh thingy one time
but oopsie yeah i'm doing uh a mangas
stream with the viewers tomorrow i think
oh yeah hopefully i can beat them
but i wonder how it is to like play it
with the viewers like if
i watched it when when polka uh played
it with her viewers
and they um they let her win
and like really didn't play it like like
norm
like normal people would yeah yeah
no i don't know i want to play it
normally
otherwise it's not fun but i think tell
your employees that they'll get fired if
they don't
abide by the rules yeah i think we can
communicate and
and yep tell them how to do it don't you
also want to maybe try that like playing
among us with your viewers could be real
lots of fun
why so many creepers why why why
okay um you know oh we can go right in
the back to go away wait are they gonna
blow up if i go past them in the
waterfall
um good question i think it's fine
i think the back waterfall oh sh goes
all the way up
okay interesting um
platform okay yeah looking for okay
nothing that we cannot fix okay okay how
did you get in here
well i went for the middle waterfall
uh-oh
okay let's continue building until the
night
okay whatever that's good yeah what do
we have
let's see our why oh we only went up by
two bucks yeah
it's a long long process whoopsie maybe
we can go up
uh on this one we'll go up by two
instead of out by two
yes i i i i brave i feel i agree with
you
uh-huh uh-huh where'd you go i turned
around and you were
there and there i'm there i'm there
don't you see me you need some glasses
watson
you need glasses if you don't see me
maybe i'm just going too fast
oh yeah yeah i think my game is bogutiya
sometimes the
enemies show up is invisible so maybe
maybe you're also invisible on my screen
yeah does that ever happen to you
because i haven't seen me a lot
no never happened to me
it happens to me like almost every time
i play monsters will be invisible
yeah yeah well that's weird
it's spooky i think my game is haunted
okay where did i stop here
don't fall down kiara it's not that hard
just we're building up on the first on
the first row
and then we'll go out on the first row
yes oh okay sorry
i don't place this in your box no
problem
i have enough now but it'll just not
look pretty from the outside are you
okay with that
what's in uh i'll fix it okay
we're building uh original design
um inspired by uh
senpai yes
and what now i think
uh let's build up one more
and then build out
[Music]
and then uh it'll probably be nighttime
but yeah by the time we're done with
that
okay actually
oh yeah yeah someone is trying to tell
me something oh yeah
uh about the mob farm it's better to put
the farm
120 blocks higher than ground not at
y28 it's because maps despawn instantly
when they're at
120 120 plus blocks away okay so it's
not 128 but 120.
okay we're pretty close okay i think i
think
uh as long as the top
the top top level is at 120
it should it should be okay because it's
still it's still accessible by the mobs
all right now we go out
okie dokie wow people are like finally
finally i love it when we can make them
crazy like this
finally she read it hallelujah party
party
well we had the right idea i think
didn't we we were pretty close
wait now they're like no kiara no wait
what did well
what now what now they didn't understand
that we did not understand apparently
the base wants to be at 120. does it
really i mean does it really have to be
so
strict on the numbers because we were on
the lower platform and they were already
how many monsters were there there were
like seven monsters already on the lower
platform which wasn't even at 120. so
you guys
you know there may be a specific way of
doing it but i don't think that's
it has to be you know it's not like the
law it's not like it's
not gonna work at all
it's not that strict 128 is sufficient
okay well i will follow
what watson
oh wait i only gave you one here i have
one block
each
thank you you're welcome now you only
gave me one block
no it's down there down here ah
thank you i can give you more oh it's
okay i think this is good
okay
almost fell down almost fell down
wait wait wait wait they're saying 120
above the ground well it's too late
too late i'm sure it'll work
yeah it will work
we're widening it again right
yeah yeah yeah okay
it should be two ideas okay
god this is difficult
it doesn't work but not be as efficient
well too bad
i mean it feels like i'm falling down in
a second
oh no i'm fine i'm fine okay up again
right
yeah up again okay
[Music]
i'm out of box oh that was fast
yeah you thank you
[Music]
uh i guess i'm not really a kfp
intern at this moment it's more like
reverse roles now
yeah well you have already done your job
oh did you fall
yeah got distracted
is this but this is your first
accidental fall right
yeah yeah good job you have you have
uh you have some good balance
we need one of those signs that they
have like at a factories or like
construction sites
it's been zero days since the last
oops it's never been more than zero days
yeah that's true well i'm speed right
now
i'm speed i'm down
[Laughter]
i just see
too good too good
it's been in zero days oh yeah we have
to put it in minutes
oh spider-man oh creeper
okay well everything's good down here
everything's cool
no mobs
wow this looks so impressive from inside
yeah it's like a coliseum
[Music]
spike no
[Laughter]
i got a good number of ten times falling
down that's a good number i rounded it
up so just that it would look like a
nicer number
that's why i just fell down just wanted
to finish that
i'll leave some stones here so that
they can be used thank you
mice is not closing is there a lag
oh yeah there we go wow
wow let me take a screenshot let's see
how do i undo them like that okay
let me take a screenshot for next
thumbnail
beautiful
better angle
run run run run
[Music]
thank you for the congratulations on 10
falls i know impressive but right the
light is horrible now
i cannot work like this my work is a
photographer
i cannot do it like this hold on
okay i'm coming back okay
where are you um down there down down
down down
okay hello hello
i put the stones in inside this
box
continue building well amelia
watson it was a pleasure to work with
you today
um we are making some nice progress on
my side and on your side
yeah we did a lot today yeah it's not
that i only
used you you and uh
uh yep used to your
your body for working and
yep i also helped you so
everything's cool
should we take this back and we can do
our exit as we're going
oh yeah this is the next time you start
you're already
at home back to farm you can take that
one
okay what about you what about you oh i
have a mine cart here
okay let's go
and now the ending credits yes
roll the credits roll them my friends
roll them
oh there my my child is trying to be
funny by um
you know how the number 10 uh
it's uh written as t-e-n you know right
ah yeah yeah yeah and tencho is
one of my nicknames so they're writing
the number ten and then two
hahaha funny funny funny
fluffer clever very clever
because i fell down ten times yeah
potential
it has a different meaning respect me
i'm your i'm your boss
i'll fire you if you keep on joking
about that
i like it i think it'd make a good
hashtag too oh yeah
don't don't give them too many ideas
don't give don't make them feel like
they're funny or something or smart
they'll think they can work at a better
place with a better salary if you if you
motivate them like that
all right should we say goodbye yeah
yeah
okay i'll continue my stream with some
super chat readings though
so yes i'm not saying yeah
beef hats are really nice to listen to
oh thank you
i do sometimes uh usually i try to get
through it
pretty fast yeah there's a lot to get
for you
yeah um yeah thank you guys for watching
we made a lot of progress today
hopefully it wasn't too frustrating for
you to watch and if it was frustrating
uh i hope you could bottle it up and
deal with it in a
healthy way
uh yeah so thank you for watching and
kara will still be streaming after this
i will not because i'm gonna do super
chat reading sometime tomorrow because i
got a lot to catch up on
yeah you go watch kiara stream as soon
as we get to the end here i'm in are you
going
to sleep that is the real question am i
oh
oh yes uh yeah i'm going to go to sleep
for now i probably won't sleep that long
since i slept for a little bit earlier
ah while i was sleeping i i had a dream
i had a dream that kiara moved the
stream to like two or three hours later
and then but it was like a weird dream
it's like i heard her voice she was like
talking to me saying um i moved the
stream two hours
later and i was like what and then i
woke up and then i checked i checked my
my phone and i got a message from her
and she was like
i'm gonna move the we could move the
stream two hours later
it's really weird like my my brain yeah
it's up on
on the message you can uh
you can see the future like for real
you're a time traveler
yeah you saw what i was writing to you
on discord
you saw it in your dream and heard it in
your dream
yeah but actually i maybe you just had
my stream open because i also said it
out loud
no no i didn't i didn't have youtube
inside mysterious mysterious in another
case that must be solved sometime soon
yes yes
your voice echoed through time
well then amelia if you wanna uh want me
to help you out sometime soon with the
tower again you can call me anytime and
thank you thank you otherwise uh if you
don't want me to help you with that next
week
otherwise i must challenge you for a
chess rematch next week
either this or that good choices
okay i'll think about it i'll ask
what they want to do all right
bye bye bye
thank you thank you good luck on your
super chat thank you
bye bye thank you for your help what's
in the industries
i'll say i'll send you the bill or the
other one you sent me the bill
and i will not pay i'll just take your
eggs and we'll call it even
okay bye
i should take my eggs she's going to
steal my eggs
we on our side will read super chat
[Music]
hello
one vote for chess please okie dokie you
shall get it
thank you my super dads well well
well
let me see we stopped we stopped where
did we stop and
we stopped at um
[Music]
uh i think we didn't read the among us
right by the way baby i should move
oh now let me one second i need to move
here i'll show yourself
ah ahmed was like so helpful like
i didn't really have to use my brain at
all for that
for that uh egg thing actually that was
that was what i was hoping for
that i wouldn't need to have to use my
brain and that's what i got
amazing
should be back and my back and my back
happens sometimes don't worry about it
just out for
two seconds don't worry my brain broke
no i did not why would my brain ever
break
i didn't even use it today
[Music]
starting from the hollow among
us stream
everyone are you ready for the
dunkishans thank you
no jumping mastaka
just vibing
[Music]
i think they're having a conversation
with the super chats here again
the gamer free eleven thank you and they
love sixty seven pancashin vault nexus
packaging v gamer free eleven thank you
soon
they're talking about raviolis and pizza
bagels what the hell
are you expecting me to read these they
probably write these
thinking i will read them
yes we can simp if we want to leave all
women behind
act like we come from out of this world
leave the real one far behind what
wait is that supposed to be some song
and you change some lyrics
wait i think that seems familiar yes we
can simple if we want to leave all the
women behind act like we come from out
of this world leave the real one far
behind
safe to dance what
i don't know that
but i feel like i there's some kind of
melody inside my brain
that tries to come out maybe i heard it
before
safety dance safety dance i probably
heard it before
guys sing the melody for me try to sing
it so loud that i can hear it because i
can't remember
there's this ah
it just doesn't come out
[Music]
something like that
no okay well but i guess not
double orientation deal of 67 glory of
combat thanks
oh i didn't pay the concert ticket fee
from the kia nina collab
thank you my friend told me to send this
oh thank you
looking for the top thank you first time
watching among us all
there will be much more i think aaron's
pee duncashin
hello thanks for coming
i don't know if i'll have much uh funny
stories to offer but i'll help put in
some
story time in between maybe
tanaka patrick payment for a large
jaguar burger set with extra seiso sauce
before
the stream thanks for wangyang for
taking the order everyone have an
enjoyable stream
and that was never sas so weird before
the
before the among us stream we all
practice together
all together and uh the first the first
uh meeting for no reason for the first
game for the first meeting they they
kicked me out
they all voted me out i was like okay
that's funny
you're welcome to do that again
when when the real thing starts but they
didn't do it it would have been funny
[Music]
they actually just tried to vote
somewhat seriously when the real stream
started
i was never suspected never even though
even when i was running
around all alone i was like oh
they're gonna
suspect me even though i'm not the one
i'm not the imposter
but they might suspect me because they
didn't see me
but they weren't that smart i guess
oh yeah they needed to keep me in the
group and keep me alive
otherwise they wouldn't have had
translations there was one time though
i generally muted myself when i was dead
because you had to mute yourself
but one time they they were they really
seemed like they needed help so i
unmuted myself
even though i was dead just to translate
for them did you notice that
did you notice i came back from the dead
to translate okay
[Music]
best translator ever thank you don't
phoenixes get unlimited
revives anyway yeah
yes somewhat unlimited
to a certain extent i guess
what is thanks and i'm confused oh danke
shown is thank you in german
rico duncan crackpot crack
crack butt soft bee
soft bee crack butt thank you
[Music]
ah here's the people trying to figure
out why my microphone was only on one
ear
it was just streamlabs it was nothing
complicated but i couldn't
i couldn't change it during the stream
because i would have had to restart
streamlabs
you know yeah
azure blade bankashan jk monkey
[Music]
oh by the way guys my clouds uh lifter
arrived
today but i'm not using it yet because i
need uh another cable that i have
uh at home
how long did it take you to learn your
non-native language well english i
learned in school over
many years but japanese i taught myself
in like one
one year i was flown down for one year
not even lying i was actually i was
fluent after half a year but
you guys won't believe me so i'm just
gonna say one year but actually only
took me half a year i have
proof but yeah
[Music]
it's actually just half a year yeah
let's just say one year because people
don't believe me
yeah of course i can read japanese of
course i can
smart bird question mark question my
question why are you so confused and
surprised about that
[Music]
you used to say others have skills but
you can only speak japanese i'm also a
translator
hope you know being a communication
bridge like you is impressive oh thank
you
and being on topic right now top light
[Music]
burps can mimic well
that's why i i can speak so many
languages
nah i did not learn japanese to watch
anime better just
that was not the reason
here's my pay for today thank you
japanese i taught myself
i did not attend classes i did not even
use books
yes ashika umi uma sam
thank you multicultural
i was too lazy to use books i'm i'm
really lazy like one thing i will admit
i'm
extremely lazy so i did buy books but i
never even
used
thank you thank you
oh thank you thank you thank you i'll
try to reach you super chat
soon general pickle
oh here we go okay among us super chats
are done
we are now at the super chats from today
[Music]
um
it's just the easiest way to learn a
language is just for communication so
you don't and i mean you need you need
passion and motivation
and interest in that language i had all
of that
so it was really easy but when i tried
to learn a different language where i
wasn't really motivated about it
it didn't really work well i didn't
really
have the motivation to like get it into
my brain like for example when i tried
learning italian
the vocabulary just i just didn't go
into my brain but when i learned
japanese i read one word and it never
left my brain because i was actually
interested in it i mean not saying i
actually
i was kind of interested in italian but
i just didn't have the same
passion and motivation about it i guess
which one was right which one was left
how do i say top right in italian
destress right test okay what's top
what's tub
hey there's some people who speak
italian in the chat one
top pasta
yes that must be how you say it
wonderful i am alto alexa
no no no no no no
every word in italian is pronounced
pasta
lasagna
oh man i want to eat like real red
lasagna again i ordered lasagna
from ubereat eats a few days ago
but i'm in in japan so the lasagna was
very
underwhelming
[Music]
have you ever had a dream that you um
you had your
you you could you do you once you why
does that seem familiar
it goes on but i will not read the whole
thing me gamer stop
joking around with me you're just
playing with me stop playing with me
vgamer
stop playing with your boss
why do i know why do i know that it's a
meme
general pickle jackets monkey dancer
you have anything to say to defend
yourself
keep on playing with me stop it at once
[Music]
not here he ran away he was too scared
he he sends this super chat thinking
he's funny
but then he's not here to face the
consequences
be gamer tell him tell v-gamer he's
fired
oh there he is
[Laughter]
oh there he is you are rehired because
you sent the super chat
thank you for for paying your boss
rinse the pot thank you dude bro guy man
thank you
fox thank you thank you general pickle
i'm pretty sure we all enjoy seeing the
progress on the whole ion server so you
don't have to worry about overplaying it
oh okay thank you minigamer for eleven
thank you
oh eggs don't do damage at all yeah i
think i've i've noticed that by now
thank you and so bee danke shin johnny
mckee danke shin
texas dies dan kashin by another player
dan kashan
obi-wan kenobi i love watching your
streams and i always try to catch them
when they're alive no matter if they're
late or really early for my
efforts may receive a headphone no but
thank you
dusty kfp and pineapple
uh
need to close it those fences completely
sheep can jump out from the dirt blouse
i think i think it's fine now
thank you pen more than ting and linda
and go back home in the phoenix plane
ah dying oh yeah that's the phoenix way
the only right way to go home is to kill
yourself
and then spawn back at home if you're
lost
if you lost that is the best way always
revive
mine red ribbon studios
vampires
sorry i don't have much to donate no
problem thank you for working hard for
us viewers your upbeat attitude is an
inspiration to me thank you for all you
do thank you
for watching tell by albino rhino
dankeshen or albino reno
wild nexus duncan in all seriousness
among us collab would not have been
possible or as
successful and fun without you it really
shows how much of a linchpin what
you are for hola ian and how important
you are keep on shining
thank you i love you thank you
so sweet check it out
lord
[Music]
m
you spread a lot of positivity so
naturally you get it returned definitely
a bright sun on the world thank you so
much and thank you for the red super
chat
mwah
your kindness and friendliness
friendliness brightens my day every day
i have been depressed lately but
watching your streams helps me cheer up
and reminds me of the good in the world
oh
danger i'm happy to hear that
i hope you feel hugged
sarah loves paola and thank you you're
an amazing translator don't be sad about
it it's
truly an amazing skill i wish i could do
be proud but the thing is okay
i'm not a i'm not a professional
translator okay
professional translators would do such a
better job but i'm glad i could help so
but don't please don't misunderstand
it's not like i learned
being a translator i'm just i'm just
trying
to to do live translation as
at the best as best as i can
but yeah i'm not that professional
buy another player dan kashim what a
simp thank you ninja star
i think more than even translating you
make a fantastic host
ah thank you i enjoy being a host i
enjoyed it
be it as a translator or otherwise your
energy really brings everyone up
thank you i i actually i enjoy being
the host because i i like to like um
have things go the way that i plan them
to grow
i really enjoyed uh hosting the holo yen
collab on my channel that one time
really enjoyed it because like i thought
i thought about what to do
and how long each each thing will take
and uh yeah i thought about all the
questions
um you know the answer
so yeah i like i like doing that kind of
stuff
[Music]
thank you for joining the membership
thank you
thank you guys
lucious cypher thank you sapphire kitten
i was discharged from the hospital today
oh i'm glad you got discharged
i watched your live video during my
recovery in the hospital
oh thank you these videos are very
interesting and give me a lot of
motivation please accept my blessing oh
i'm just happy you're healthy again
hopefully
congratulations on getting out of the
hospital
please stay healthy and safe
thank you sapphire kitten listen here
attention you gotta grab the rabbit by
the ears
you're gonna strike while the carrot is
hot basically good luck with pecora
we all know but i just imagined me
grabbing piccola by her ears
ah is any artist here right now can you
please draw me grabbing pakora by her
ears
recently there has not been much fan art
but here's
a request from my side please draw me
when i uh with me like
picking up pikura by grabbing her ears
pants
[Music]
500 subs just now oh yeah wasn't she at
499 or something before we started to
stream wow
she's not watching i guess but
congratulations wait let's write to her
[Music]
et
i was gonna write that first
you only no know it because
you're listening to my street
stream damn it
kung congratulations
[Music]
500 that's half a million half a million
sounds much more impressive than 500k
somehow
[Music]
500 500 500. wow so that's
that's kelly gurda and ame who are
already over 500.
oh wow
wow wow wow
damn
kelly sent us a photo of her new setup
holy
looks so her new setup looks so good
[Music]
you know
because i saw i visited her home before
and i saw her old setup
she lives in like a tiny ass apartment
um had like a table on the floor which i
mean that that's not
a type of like a like a low table
uh i don't think it's uh it's pretty
normal in japan to have like a low table
and sit on the floor
pretty pretty normal
uh but she had no space because of that
i think she told it in her stream many
times that she has no
no space and that she sits on the floor
and
i saw it i saw it she really had a bit
of space problems but now it looks like
really good
nice
floor gang oh i'm also on the floor
right now though
i'm also sitting on the floor with a
tiny the
a tiny setup but that's just because
it's uh
time limited setup
tomorrow i finally i finally be uh
streaming from my house again
yep a temporary yeah that's what i
wanted to say temporary floor gang
what's up although i i do enjoy like
sitting on the floor and streaming on
the floor and actually
i've been doing this for three weeks now
and i've been i've been enjoying it
more than i thought i would i would i
would like to stay on the floor
can i stay on the floor no probably not
one second i'll make myself bigger
there's many ways to sit when you sit on
the floor you don't always have to sit
on your legs or in
your knees now let's drink some water
damn it looks so cool
[Music]
that looks so cool
damn
yeah jealous keanu sounds
can i schedule where the week isn't even
over
you already want a schedule for me huh
give me some time my friend give me some
time
anyway anyway let's continue
[Music]
my throat is hurting again my throat
hurts again so quick
ah cough
[Music]
does the bird do any sports the bird
does
um mental sport
the birds um
yes bird bird does sports every day
yes yes yeah
yeah yeah of course of course of course
of course i do
i mean look at my shoes
have you seen my shoes
those are the shoes of someone who goes
jogging
every day don't you think
[Music]
what are those
damn legs oh thank you 10 out of 10 legs
nice legs
legs damn kiana nice legs
that that that meat oh
oh conoponito
[Music]
um stopped moving so this is a bit
awkward
having no reaction to this is a bit
chad come back to me
chad are you okay oh there it is
hello chat stop moving again
chad is not doing so well today
chat
hello maybe
maybe my legs made the jack too
too excited so it broke the chat
ah there we go oh it's moving again
ah it's moving it's moving
that's moving i think it's back everyone
say hello
say hello so i can see how how
how much the delay is hello
oh there we go okay that was fast okay
we back we're back
moto takes time hold on
okay okay but i didn't see your reaction
to my legs
can we uh reenact it
look i have no stickers wow look at
those sexy legs
but my chat broke again mata chatukawa
wait did my legs break the chat
ashi
[Music]
oh it's back it's back i think it's back
oh it's back chat goes
okay i missed it again i missed your
reactions again
i'll show you again look maybe it works
this time
wow look at those legs oh wait it broke
again
yeah i'm not even kidding it broke again
eh what's wrong with the chat
now it's working again okay
no wait it's not it's ah there he goes
huh whoops sorry
i got to close there
okay i will never i will never know your
reaction to my legs
well my dear chad keep on spamming the
duncations i'll be uh reading the super
chat
it keeps on like breaking every once in
a while
where was i
and now my child is acting normal again
now you act normal
hey what the hell that's so weird it's
really reacting to my legs
interesting out loud thank you
y'all go interview when let's do it
sometime thank you for the red super
chat
[Music]
sounds like you put a lot of thought
into how to make use of your skills yes
and frankly it sounds absolutely amazing
tension involved to top right thank you
thank you soon hey l'oreal
kids thank you laura look at thank you
jimmy
i'm so excited for this interview
project i always shed tears of joy
you're very excited who your ambition is
so inspiring looking forward to that
yaga interview oh yeah oh
that will be legendary but it has to be
the last bus
last bus thai yoga thank you
for your time
[Music]
i think i answered this stream as
a question in the stream
i think
um
but anyway japanese was not my first
language my third language was japanese
looking for the top tank
[Music]
where i'm from the united states there
are german speakers but the german they
speak is
different than the european german they
call it pennsylvania
i want to learn it is it a joke
is that a joke is that like uh
making fun of a certain english accent
or something
oh here comes the red super chat writing
something
it's true
what did i say to make this happen i
didn't even i you're doing this on your
own
i didn't even make it happen this time
hey did i say anything to start this
again
i didn't say anything
slap them
well we'll see and
i'm still then reach them they just
wanted to have
oh oh they do want it to happen
huh are you guys hoping for a slap
or a kiss
[Music]
but you guys are so sweet
for doing that like on your own you
don't even have a reason
thank you for your support you're trying
to be funny but thank you for your
support
actually i really appreciate it maybe
idiot
he
i didn't even do anything this time
i didn't even complain and you started
on your
own
okay then what okay then what what
i understand what are you answering to
i cannot have a conversation like this
bottom left you changed your name i see
your icon
aren't you aren't you um uh looking for
the
top you changed your name didn't you
or am i wrong now but i see your your
icon you're
you're looking for the top no
you think i couldn't i couldn't notice
huh
oh yeah he did
i don't understand what you mean with
bottom left anyway
well i just want the wing oh
hmm
do you like how my whole body moves when
i wink
do you like it
uh
i'm winking i'm just blinking i'm just
[Laughter]
blinking
i can't help it i can't help it but keep
on moving
okay
[Music]
every time i try to do something fan
service for you guys
my chat stops moving is this
is this the punishment that i get
for trying to
i don't know uh go home stopped again
my chat stopped again
today my chat is acting up so weird now
it's moving again
it's moving again lootness is breaking
the chat oh damn
kiara is just too sexy
kiala is just too sexy and chad is too
thirsty yes indeed
why am i oh is it because my mom is
watching
mama i'm sorry
i just uh like myself a little bit too
much
i just uh i'm sorry mama
she even watches my my my super chat
ratings
mama don't watch my super chat readings
they're a waste of time anyway
i mean for you you're a busy mama
phoenix
don't watch my super chat
please give me give me a little bit
of space where i can act sexy
my mama is probably when i show my ties
she's probably
reporting my stream to youtube see
it will happen yep yep my chat stopped
moving
oh there he goes there it goes there it
goes
mama will probably call me after the
stream and be like kiara
kiana what are you doing
your face is up here remember kiara okay
okay i know i know i know i know i know
okay
and now i have reached a point where i
have to reload osi 75 right here let's
remember that
button
[Music]
where was i
oh god the sneeze chats i'm not gonna
raise the sneeze jets
i hope you understand that my friends
kusami knows
where did i stop scrolling scrolling
scrolling
ah there i am
[Music]
i'm super excited for your new interview
segment this is going to be an amazing
step forward for all the whole life and
you are
the one who started it yay the one who
is going to start it
if no one steals my idea before me but i
have stated it in my stream
so if anyone does it before me you all
know
i had the idea before but who would do
it who would do this besides me
it can only be me
what if what if
why f did my stream die
why are you effing
why guys stop acting if you don't mean
this
it's confusing because that can actually
happen
uh for the sneeze chats
make me think my stream is dead new rule
only write f in the chat if my stream is
uh disconnected only
then you are allowed to write f if i die
in a game or something write rip
okay got it employees
follow the rules follow the rules
it's actually confusing
f no not f super jack
no no
huh
no
where was i comfortable
thank
thank you for the great streams thank
you for the red super chat thank you for
again
thank you again for bringing the jp and
ian grip together i'm so glad you're in
hollow life to bring that experience to
everyone
holoyan wouldn't be the same without
everyone that's in now that is true
thank you very much for your sweet words
even my papa sent a super chat
uh about the about the sneeze
about the fake sneeze even
skip skip skip skip skip
skip skip skip oh skipping skipping
skipping
oh and there come the super chats where
i told everyone to stop
sending sneeze super chats and they keep
on sending super chats
just to annoy me sorry
[Music]
papa
where do i start again yeah here
here's fake money for your fake sneezes
i need to go to sleep but your money is
real
[Music]
it was a fake yawn i'm sorry i apologize
deeply
i do not and i'm not sorry sorry not
sorry
[Music]
uh
your name is your name change your name
back
but this one is actually shorter
so hmm but uh
change it back
looking for the top ah lftt stands for
looking for the top ah
i thought you kind of like miss wrote
left
oh now i get it
change it back
replicated yeah i came up with that
right oh god it was me
but i didn't i didn't come up with the
bottom one
i only said lftt
wait when i say lft
it sounds like i love titty
[Music]
well he'll probably never change it back
again
he'll probably never change it back
[Laughter]
albedo i get you i got you
okay focus focus guys focus
patrick chen duncan replicated potato
sanctuary gamer for 11
jk
my
wanted to donate this earlier but didn't
have the chance congratulations on being
a translator
congratulations
it feels weird being congratulated for
that for being
a translator it's like
and all the japan collabs as well don't
know how else to say we're really proud
of you you're a huge contribution to
halloween viva la cara thank you
but i'm i don't know it's weird uh
i i'm
i'm not a translator but uh
but yeah i guess i did translating
yeah it sounds as if i'm getting
congratulated on a new job
but that's not my job i'm an idol
thank you thank you for your support
thank you i am doing a lot of things
yes yes yes yeah i'm not
what are you surprised about
i'm an idol part-time yeah i do every
job
part-time
either
even even me being being tenzho also
vital
have you ever heard of a boss of a of a
huge worldwide
uh fast food franchise
who's only doing it as a as a part-time
yeah that's me
part-time ceo
[Music]
idiot
you so much
[Music]
oh counting my falls
please tell amelia to stop ground
pounding our moms
she has chronic back issues that she's
still recovering
oh i'm sorry that i'm laughing but
ah i'll tell her
by the way i still i still don't really
understand what ground pounding even
means in my mind i
imagine like a wrestler like jumping
uh from from the edge of a resting ring
onto your mom that's how i imagine it is
that how it is
that's about right okay
[Music]
let's leave it at that okay okay
it's a mario reference all right
oh oh because she was playing that mario
game
what was it odyssey
was it odyssey or galaxy i keep on
mixing those up
i'm 64. and why did i not get that joke
i also played 64. huh
it's odyssey maybe one day i shall play
odyssey to
understand this joke
asian dankeshin axis one two four seven
thank you
that's finka thank you so that's the one
i already read
in the stream thank you thank you
shannon
uh do you love 67 live is amazing
that finger dancer
[Music]
stop teaching me stop teaching me
don't teach me these things when when
then i you complain about me being to
loot okay i don't understand
what does that even mean
and my mom yesterday i was on on the
phone with her for one hour okay i
wanted to take a nap that's what i
tweeted about wanted to take a nap and
in that moment she calls me and
and she was like getting really excited
she was so cute she was so excited about
telling me that how which stream she
watched and
and she enjoys them so much and she told
she tells me
oh kiara your child is so nice everyone
in the chat is so nice i was so
surprised they only write nice things
no bad things don't
disappoint my mom you can disappoint me
but don't disappoint my mom
she's probably watching right now i
can't tell her to skip it when she's
watching
probably watching
be on your best behavior guys it's
this is like me introducing you to my
mom
sanji shong dang kashin by another
player dan kashan salman samaritan
kashin
they love 67 snapple facts thank you
nils muffin thank you
pickle dance
[Music]
is
sorry i'm just talking about this
question in japanese asked me
about fan letters and presents and at
the moment
you can send fan letters to the address
of whole life
in in japan presents are usually only
accepted
uh when it's birthday time but
at the time at the time where it's my
birthday i will not be in japan
but i think i cannot confirm this but
it's probably just gonna be like
because for for the other girls they're
also not in japan right mostly so
probably everything will be sent to
japan and then they will send it to each
girl's respective address i guess but
that
that will be figured out whenever that
birthday time comes
but for now for my case
for my case and just um fan letters
can be probably accepted anytime
until i leave japan and after that we'll
figure out something new
um
foreign
[Music]
oh
foreign
currently we are accepting uh
fan letters and message cards or boys
but
for real presents like anything that is
bigger than a letter
they will be open right before birthdays
so yeah and the address is usually the
one in
japan see the
en whole life website for details
for
manager in the chat
manager in the chat yo welcome
just want you to know that you've become
my inspiration to continue my nihongo
language self-study maybe not only me
but
other kfp crew as well love you thank
you thank you
that's nice to hear mr mark gaming thank
you
vegan my friend dan kashin can i send
chess lessons via mail
i don't need chess lessons
i don't need such a thing
hunter rose thank you meru sudankashin
bikini inu
dr oopsie mission is broken what
how can it break how can it break
who broke it who of you was it yukihana
dan kashan yukasan
[Music]
you're a big sweetheart and very
talented phoenix kiara thank you for
everything you always make me smell
every day
thank you too you make me smile too
[Music]
thank you
i rather see your pretty face than your
ties anyways i'm sure you'll reach 400k
as soon as possible due to your strong
fan base
keep on going and never give up give up
i'm amazed with your
big brute skills thank you
thank you everyone please keep on
sharing
my tweets on twitter and keep on telling
people about my streams and sharing them
and uh commenting and voting uh give it
give them a thumbs up so they
go through the algorithm you know and
turn on the notification bell
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding off 67 oh
yummy
you listening hello hello
a slap for you did you hear that was
that too quiet
did you hear that
you're welcome i love refrigerators
ah do you love 67
ah it hurts
you're welcome do us zero
again challenging me again
double slap
uh i love refrigerators
you thought you would get a slab but you
got the keys
foreign
i read it as bottom left goddammit i'm
just too used to it and it looks like
the word it looks like it lftt
and capslock looks like left
anyway thank you for the red super chat
slap chew slap keys alias
sake donkey saucy
this is just sending mixed messages
sorry sorry masen
alvido thank you speed and shiny love 67
[Music]
thank you
and here we go probably last refreshing
we're almost at the end my friends
almost there
me
[Music]
didn't mean to make you cry if chad's
not back in five minutes carry on
carry on because super chat doesn't
really matter what
what song is that
[Music]
didn't mean to make you cry if chad's
not back in five
minutes carry on oh wait carry on
carry on because if a chat
doesn't really matter something like
that
i figured it out by myself
no no no i don't get copyright striked
just by that
[Music]
if anyone wants to uh say something say
it now or
say it never i'll give you i'll give you
uh 10 seconds 10 thanks for joining the
membership
10 9 ah
[Music]
something no no wait
i didn't mean that
i didn't mean that to you
i'm drawing that request oh thank you
i'm looking forward to that
nice okay
and refresh for the last time
everything that comes now will be no
more
red konato kurosu
masento okay
where did i stop here
you heart i'm not reading you guys
heart on the blade thank you 18
just got home from a bad day at work and
you are here to brighten my daytime so
yeah
but oh aren't you late
love to hear you doing anything same
amazing ever thinking of singing my bb
handle no never
but thank you and good job at work today
another orange for the old friends oh
it's uh oh renzo
oh ren's collab it was just that good
thank you
[Music]
i listened back on the two after i came
home
and i was just still i was enjoying it
because
i never had such a good audio in my
karaoke streams before
even with my new microphone even with my
new expensive microphone because it's
just um
the delay that messes it up and and kind
of like
um the music overpowering the
microphone but i bought a cloud lifter
to make it even better and maybe
tomorrow we can try it out if i have the
right cable at home
we will see
it's almost a four hour stream again how
much how long was my
stream before that
how long was the stream before that
you broke super spin um excuse me i
would like to
uh i would like to defend myself
that bin was like not even a real bin
okay it was just like two um like
thin uh plastic uh
thingies and then like
you just clip you should it's not
it's not even a drill trash bin three
hours three and a half hours was the
stream before oh interesting
i don't know how to explain it it wasn't
even a real
ah
it's a it was a trash bin that you could
break easily
it's not made for sitting on it okay
no i did not
people think i'm fat
it was not it was not the kind of trash
can you guys are thinking of
it didn't even have like walls
it's like like a trash can without walls
it's just like
no i don't know how to explain it
time for the ring for the adventure to
prove what's wrong hey
[Music]
a wire bath is i don't know then it's
like um
a two um bull bull how do you say
in in english sticks
like two plastic um poles
thin two plastic two thin plastic poles
holding it up and then there's like a
uh like a frame in the top in the frame
and the bottom
out of plastic and then you just yeah
you just uh
put in the the plastic bag
you you clip it at the top but there's
like no walls okay it's not stable
it's not made for sitting on it
do you understand i wish i was a trash
bin
shut up
i think you understand yeah that is not
a bin
i think we need a deck
[Music]
she stole something important it's our
heart
something
[Music]
last one joey draws dancing
okay that was the real one oh
okay how many hours did i stream today
seven hours maybe
i think it's seven hours
seven hours i think
[Music]
thank you everyone for watching today so
tomorrow
um there will be new internet set up at
my new house
which is super old and has ghosts in it
and it's scary i don't even want to live
there right now
oh yeah i decided to play a horror game
on halloween i'm not looking forward to
it
but with that house it will be even
spookier
yeah halloween
night
so anyway tomorrow the internet will be
set up and i will try my best to stream
after that if it will work
it has to work i'm gonna kill someone if
it doesn't work
i'm gonna kill some chickens in
minecraft if it doesn't work
i'm gonna go insane and kill every
single chicken in
yeah minecraft my chat uh broke for a
second
spare ascii spare us
but it has to work and uh i will
i didn't make the schedule yet i'll make
it tomorrow i guess
but the plan for tomorrow is among us
at astane
internet um
tomorrow at seven o'clock
japanese seven o'clock in the evening
japanese standard time
among us for maybe one and a half hour
with you guys with you
among us
that's what i'm playing planning at
least
now let's just hope it goes well
u.s services are being hacked what
what what in what way in what way
we played on n a server the other day
it's not pretty what do you mean
i have been spammed oh
yeah well i'll use the asia server i
guess because i'm
in asia
[Music]
um
see you tomorrow 7 p.m probably probably
probably
i'll probably not
[Music]
i really i will reserve the stream but
caution i might move it a little bit
depending on how the situation with my
internet is okay
but i will make the reservation so
everyone can check
when it's happening thank you for
watching today it was a long day thank
you for everyone who stayed with me and
hung out with me and had fun with me
thank you for all the support
through the uh super chats and thank you
for always watching my streams
i love you all meenada
now what should i eat let's eat some
soup
[Music]
bye
i will eat you
[Music]
ah
yum
[Music]
oh
what did you say
albino you're fired
excited
how dare you insult your bus
mother