[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
can't get anything
yeah
sorry for the wait
oh
[Music]
kick it again
the gun is back yeah the gun is
perfect for this
I would say although
and I think I need to make some fixes my
arms are too far apart
but besides that it's perfect I love
this gun
a beautiful gardener
feeling okay yeah okay yeah she's
feeling a bit hot
I pour me some water
I already watched the new rings of Power
episode when I woke up
it's Friday everybody earrings of power
time yeah yeah yeah I think it was fun
this episode
um
apparently next episode is the last one
oh no
oh
next episode
but I think houses of dragon will still
continue for a couple more episodes no
I would hope so let me out of the
[\h__\h] window why I'm pressing Windows
button let me out okay
task manager
thank you task manager
oh sure oh
there we go
come on
and move this here
task manager coming in to save me when I
need him but we're gonna make this full
full-size window again right
how do we do that again
there you go and then chat you go
you go you go you go here
I I become a bit smaller
make me small small
how does this look and then I think I
gotta be like
uh last time last time we put myself
here now put my gun
I'm gonna be here
I'll I'll be like here yeah it's [\h__\h]
Trevor
ah why is he here in the title screen
no one wants to see that get out of here
final ride better for mapping yeah but
my gun
oh my God
oh we'll see how it goes
I don't think we'll have much more of
this game unfortunately where we were
speeding through it
um
next stream might be the last one who
knows
but yeah uh let's let's enjoy
um today a little bit earlier than usual
a little bit earlier than usual are you
all awake what time is it everybody huh
oh yeah once that's done we can try
online once we're done with the story
hmm
but yeah apparently I really have to get
the uh PlayStation version or so because
you know hackers apparently hacking into
the gate
10 40
perfect
perfect 6 43 a.m Not So Perfect
[Laughter]
9 42 am
decent
[Laughter]
3 40. perfect same time zone
yes it was a Stein skate reference of
course my whole existence is a Steins
Gate reference look at me
I am hookah Papa's child
so okay good morning most of you but I'm
surprised you guys are here
I I scheduled this one a bit earlier for
the sea peepsie
Automotive
starting a bit early
so let's go
let's play GTA
yay oh yeah
travel hand in my ass crack ew
ing
he's like half
half unconscious
and the one thing he says is I got sand
in my ass like what the [\h__\h]
are you
a terrible flyer or what what's good to
say is this helicopter drunk
or is that me
from the previous string oh now they're
just going straight up
I think that one's drunk well I'm drunk
maybe my vision is drunk speedball
votes
oh what
hello he's on the line too hey Trev all
right I need your whole crew over at
Cape catfish we're moving on the
chemical weapons plant no no no no no I
just gave something chemical weapons I
need to deal with some stuff get back to
Los Santos just just uh give me a week
we got the equipment with your Polito
money
the gangbanger is already on the way the
window's open my friend and you are
jumping out of it what's going on
going anywhere bud
I don't remember well what did we do the
boat thing last time with Trevor I
thought we did it with Michael or
Franklin anyway let me bring these balls
to where they belong
[Music]
whoa why did that happen
oh [\h__\h]
I didn't touch anything
okay and into the water
actually never mind they don't belong
here at all guys
um don't don't dirty the ocean wouldn't
this be floating at the top there you go
I thought so
well I wonder how far we can bring this
thing
wow such a
um and Beach ambitionist goal I can't
[\h__\h] swim straight Trevor you [\h__\h]
drunken bastard
let's bring this to the other side of
the world come on come on
switch to Franklin oh I will gladly
switch to Franklin
um
why are we I
we are ending it's here last time this
is weird
anyway the balls are being taken care of
uh evil evil balls
always be careful of the balls guys
oh and we gave uh drunken Trevor a nice
shower
maybe that helps him
wake the [\h__\h] up
this place is nice there's more balls
table balls but these will be hard to
bring over there
what about the evil board
don't worry guys I was not genuinely
scared
that was just me acting I know it was so
realistic but it was just reacting
bamboozled
no that actually really does it you
would now if you knew a thing or two
about me because that was delayed did
you not notice my
was a little bit delayed and not very
genuine
oh
[Laughter]
Trevor what am I even doing I'm just
like chilling right now oh can I go in
here
hello
I hear Michael I feel like I hear
Michael
I heard someone's Voice who was that
sounded like Michael
it's not the only thing delayed today
what are you talking about the Stream
I guess I'll just stream I already
delayed it so I don't think you can call
it a delay
some a plans delay oh is that Trevor's
car
oh yeah I found it by accident
that's a nice car is it a muscle car no
for real though I know I know what
muscle cars are now let me take a look
this is not necessarily a muscle car but
it's kind of a mix of a muscle car and a
Cabrio Maybe
it is oh my God oh my God that's a car
but the muscle cars really have these
these tops normally because that looks
like one of those tops actually no never
mind
no it's not
that's not one of those removable tops I
don't see the the
things
where it would go back
it's a must
ARD for the lucky guess
you know I've many people many people
have sent me
uh guides on how to differentiate
certain types of cars not all the info
has stayed in my brain but I've
certainly remembered that a muscle car
comes with a big front
where all the power engine is right
because all muscle cars are about is
about power power power power so they
make the front longer and put more stuff
inside right
foreign
[Music]
now I'm gonna see how that feels to
drive let me in
how does it feel to drive a muscle car
get on the other side yeah
looks freaking nice oh yeah wait uh how
do you change [\h__\h] music in there we
go I didn't put in any new music I'm
sorry
[Music]
oh
yeah that's nice
nice
it makes boom boom are we faster than
that sports car oh why is he picking a
fight with the bike
okay that was not my fault
you guys uh
can you guys bounce for me that was not
my fault
battles
okay now let's chill a little bit here I
want to know what we're supposed to do
uh healthy Healthcare argue
now
somebody said switch to Franklin right
um
[Music]
let's do that
oh
what's Franklin up to
ages Steve
[Music]
I want to make clear that's actually a
pre-recorded podcast
this stream is not pre-recorded though
believe me believe it I can prove it
people in the chat are saying go to the
B go to the B go to the B okay
my favorite character
and he's not bad stream do you indeed
it's almost at one million I don't know
how far we're off like maybe two
thousand three thousand or so ah this be
what's the big stopping every
since before [\h__\h] let's go you didn't
say that that was me banana
llama chat does not pre-recorded no no
one's pre-recorded
baby
where the [\h__\h] is this where am I
this is not Los Santos oh
wait where the [\h__\h] the Beagle
what did I just say
just say it's wrapped it return land
huh
disrupted
it's bug
I rammed the cup wait what the problem
what was the problem of ramming a car
none there
was so sensitive
we barrier come back okay
you can't be so sensitive in a game like
this
okay the B is back
was that was that car so important oh
hello hello who it is it's Amanda Amanda
de Santa
we met at my house oh yeah oh [\h__\h] where
you at look I know that you and my
husband and Trevor Phillips are I don't
know what the [\h__\h] you're up to but I
can make a pretty good why there's some
weird things going on is he okay I don't
think okay is the right word well he's
alive you should call him he appreciate
that now I don't want to speak to him I
just wanted to know he wasn't dead
somewhere thanks hmm
don't tell him I called oh I should wear
it oh
just be honest
and call him I'm telling him
oh wow
okay B
I don't know why I'm marking it it's
right there
no Ramen cars now
it's nice and all an anime and movies
and whatever but in reality I think it
would be hard to have a relationship or
especially a marriage
well and it's important you're honest to
one another right
to this person
hey what's up and what's up Michael
oh hey man
I'm doing
how you doing
I'm gonna have you heard from your
family
yeah sure
no that's a lie I haven't heard a
[\h__\h] thing
I just literally heard from there we
could tell him
we're all Gower anyway what's going on
ladies oh Trevor hello Trevor
what kept you business Michael business
all right I'm the CEO of a big
international corporation it's very time
consuming nothing of course you'd
understand
look at you
being from being not worthy of my
presence
if you want something done go to the
busy man
this Rich [\h__\h] is useless
could y'all knock that [\h__\h] off oh look
boys your boys it's the feds huh
how if I be where's the other three
[\h__\h] guys so stupid this is a six-man
job no you didn't Dave did no Dave
didn't you said you'd do it that is a
freaking lie I do not get things wrong
all right and we're out of here let's go
you three can do it alone
[\h__\h] you you do your own dirty it's okay
we have plug armor I think we'll be fine
scum like you and you're doing a great
job sir you want this job great job
conspiring with others something like
that come on
come on mister
let's go let's go save America who the
[\h__\h] are we saving it from this time
this is the real deal my sources are
convinced there's a plot in
international Affairs you know the
agency they're using this facility to
make a serious nerve toxin yeah
which they plan and they're mind-blowing
Insanity to let a major terrorist
release on a metropolitan area so they
can continue to get funding nothing
increases funding for fighting terrorism
more than successful acts of terrorism
that's all right so let me get you
straight then no no no no no no no there
is no getting it straight that's the
point now we're doing this YouTube I
mean it makes sense but Michael
who was
flippers
can we do some flooding let's go
oh
inside of you and neoprene is something
nice
get in you're driving Anita wait go down
I can I can put things behind my model
now can someone make me a scuba diving
tank
I guess it won't really matter after
this episode oh well listen to me Steve
no Wise Cracks got it no [\h__\h] cliches
where are we going for the freedom of
the people today Don't lecture me on
patriotism you've been living outside
the system too long social
responsibilities a joke to you so maybe
I redeem myself get killed in the
process that old [\h__\h] no one is
dying on my watch not even the burnout
bank robber with temper issues and
nothing to live for a hero's death is
too good for you you'll die in the igna
mini you deserve oh thank God
very safe through these selfless acts of
charity
foreign
[Music]
is it really this bouncy with a boat
like this on the ocean
I mean I've experienced it with like the
speedboat thing before we can get in
through the discharge tunnel I guess I
guess it really do be bouncy huh
oh
Into the Water Press app to dive into
the sea all right oh
and fish
Michael's a fish
oh God hi I thought you were what am I
dropping there
I thought you were a shark
should I do this with controller here
I'm switching to controller let's see
how it is how do I swim
oh that's how I fight what am I doing
uh-huh
is it X
X to paddle with my legs okay
no sharks here hopefully
x x x x x x x x
on my next vacation I swear I'm gonna go
diving
I I mean my next vacation in a place
where it's possible
I will go diving no matter the cost
okay using the action I wonder if you
can go diving in Bali
uh hold our teeth start to cut into
him that gas will last forever
oh wait uh we're cutting on the green
spots
am I doing this right now
sure you can
you can in Valley really isn't I wonder
it's probably cheap right I would I
would somehow assume that in Bali you
could go diving relatively cheaply no
facts for me from the instruction manual
once it drive it's good okay
full of windbreakers oh and maybe some
nipple clamps
okay I don't have I was I was thinking
it would open up but now as long as it's
red it's fine okay okay
wow that this feels like
so Mission Impossible
by the way maybe should we guys watch
Bond movies because I think in my whole
life I've never seen a Bond movie before
are they good are they worth it
[Music]
would you guys recommend them more to me
than Marvel movies
they are they are
I mean I can become the Bond girl
someday
sexy blunt girl
one's so much better than Marva
oh
well the first one is really old isn't
it when did the first Bond movie come
out
foreign
how
water in the fire
1963 too oh holy [\h__\h] that's so old that
should do it
why
what happened it's on fire why
[Laughter]
find the access point
uh okay okay
by the way these people that are with me
that's not Franklin Trevor right they
went somewhere else these are the the
FIB guy and the other guy right that's
the Intel is good we're 100 yards out
uh
[Music]
you feel that water's getting warmer ew
you wet your pants Davey this is a
cooling tunnel of course it's getting
warmer know when urinated
that ain't true
wait who said that last sentence the
voices sound so similar to me
because you haven't said it peed into
the water in the events
what's Michael oh God disgusting
that's what all the bubbles are
dumb nobody did this it's funny
my God why are you so disgusting I
thought it was Trapper's job to be
disgusting no I don't believe it he
didn't do it
or maybe he did but if you're in a
wetsuit and and you pee in the wetsuit
does that even like I can't how do I go
back
wait
what would happen if you pee yourself in
the wetsuit because the material look
feels or it looks like it would be
pretty good in holding it back and not
letting the the liquid actually outside
yeah doesn't it like kind of stay nearly
there
thing is that Michael's current state
that's an air pocket take it up to the
surface where the [\h__\h] are you guys
I don't see you
huh
did they go up
you said take it to the surface right
it's so hard to go up
there's a ladder there becomes a wetsuit
and the truest of senses
there's a ladder oh I see
oh so shiny oh shiny Michael but
how are you huh we ready um only happens
in dry stuff what's the plan hey hey
relocate the toxin
we got great lead the way
oh God
we shooting
are we shooting them or no
I have a zapper
oh that's so nice of us to not kill them
whoa
have you guys ever been Zapped before
how does it feel
what exactly does a neural attack
probably another one right
never it hurts yeah card
how do I collect the swipe cut
how can I do it
there it is I thought it was on him
round to the right come on we're fine
when collab of cool it's so interesting
to me how um Indonesian viewers
they ask me so often when I'm collabing
with code they literally come into my
chat only to ask that question it's so
sweet you guys want to see it so badly
huh
wait should I have not done that
oh it looks like it's fun yeah
it's okay it's okay it's just kind of
funny and cute to me
I guess it's a good sign
what are we doing
take cover from the security guards to
cover I'm like covering or let him go
okay where are you
at once
the island only looks like I got this
one though but just in case you know
just in case
honestly
I wanna I I if I could I would collab
with every whole life member every week
are we going I'm trying
the toxin what it's not that easy you
know can we go through
is this possible to go for it along
got this
oh we're gonna do
what you gonna do
oh there's company oh
my friends are so useless
and perfect got the nerve toxin oh
wow
[Music]
does it kill people who doesn't just
like I don't know make them sleep for a
while
refrigeration unit warning yeah
are we done with like
um doing it the friendly way
on [\h__\h] he was a real gun uh wait I
forgot how to switch guns there we go
okay
um what are we going for
um
pistol honestly would be fine I don't
have a pistol
okay
[Music]
in his in his between legs in his third
leg
okay it's been a while let me give me a
second
wait there's more coming
um
you're talking to every Chihuahua right
now you realize that don't you
don't you wish your girlfriend was hats
like me don't you wish your girlfriend
was a freak like me don't you
first thing that's tomorrow
good tomorrow guys wow yes tomorrow
what is going on WOW
[Music]
no screams on you
is he dead
let the monkeys breathe and then we
should be singing who let the monkeys
out
wait why can't we let them out so sad
subjects come with us
we can make a zoo
three
oh
uh-huh see this is how rust should have
been yesterday
I forgot how to take cover guys how that
was so what's so right
was it cute oh it's cute
uh-huh
okay oh one of us is already there over
there whoa
okay I'm here I'm here I'm here oh I got
a medkit nice you guys not need one
let's get out of here
container container
container
is it safe to go oh
wait security here very weak
lips in my pocket there you go a pocket
lips
get this thing ready to move
it is ready get over here man oh okay
Switching to controller
because around the end there was a scene
uh uh where
um
oh yeah yeah during was like yelling
with his father right
they were both yelling at each other and
I honestly felt like
even the dialogue feels like it would
have been fine if you would have just
um talk normally with each other
what's up
hey
what do you mean Light It Up
I don't know how to fly this thing
how do I get back
[Music]
where exactly do you want me out here oh
this is so difficult
moves like this
[Music]
agency response team's already in the
building it's never too late is that
scripted let's go it's too risky fancy
though that Bird Goes Down
[Music]
can walk over them
dedication
[\h__\h] you I should attain you I just took
a phone from my country
okay okay uh
let's go I don't know how to fly whoa
whoa whoa uh wait how do I how do I get
higher
I think I'm failing this
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I'm tired
[Music]
nerve engine was damaged oh that's too
bad oh no
no
it's right
how to fly okay okay
I got it I got it
it's like like with the helicopter right
okay
[Music]
with a 12-inch aluminum flashlight
we're the ones hoping we'll outrun the
agency response team I think Franklin's
the one taking the easy way guys got to
speed up in an aircraft Hangar look
let's just get to the airport so we can
finish this [\h__\h] all right
I'm on my way can I trust you to dispose
of the chopper I got more important
things to worry about mess around
like things that actually mean something
not made up more with made up enemies
matters of the heart oh we're here
probably not
ah
I'm gonna try my best here
land the crate on the trailer why does
it always have to be so be so excited
[Music]
Rome wasn't [\h__\h] built in a [\h__\h]
day okay
Batman
[Laughter]
wait there's a detached button okay
I had it I almost had it
[Laughter]
Atlanta copter okay
what what I'm landing it
nice
so
hey Frank
it's cracking man chemical weapon in
there right if it even is a chemical
weapon hell it could be shaving cream
for all I know by the way next time
you're getting wet um
my best for you I always try yeah well
maybe this time maybe this time Steve
will succumb to the strains of enhanced
interrogation techniques
they're probably decorating him right
now hey yo he got something damn
TV just try and keep your heads down
yeah
yes
what's up man my days in the wilderness
are over
Lester he settled up with that crazy
Mexican [\h__\h] gave him the
artifact
now as long as Trevor handles the wife
we're good but what about him man and
[\h__\h] him he likes the desert besides we
do one big score we're all gonna have to
go our own separate ways anyway oh man
no I can't wait to get back to that
movie studio yeah not live your mid-life
crisis
holler at you later then all right
I'll tell you what you could take this
desert and stick it my life may be a
World of Pain I'm here on out it's going
to be cool comfortable air conditioned
pain
take it easy
Michael Michael Michael Michael
poor poor Michael oh no we're switching
back to Trevor okay but okay I'm
interested in this one but we both know
I made a vow to my husband
we can move to a country where you can
make more than one vowel
you have a great
thing wait I want to listen to the
dialogue properly
and inside you but you are a beautiful
man beautiful
so happy
you have a beautiful way with words
I am subscribe
I am going home
I know are you good Trevor
I know what
what
yeah he's really unstable but I've never
I've never
that must be fake right
oh sorry what the [\h__\h] never seen him
like that before
oh yeah he's is he still drunk maybe
because what the [\h__\h] is the matter with
him
oh he wanted a girlfriend
[Music]
well I mean Trevor not saying you can do
better than this actually I don't think
you genuinely can
now how it is in America sometimes in
certain places
Kyle just walks over I guess you know
that could maybe even happen in Austria
we have a lot of cows
maybe that happens on the countryside
here too
no other senpai
have an idea
just walk over the streetlight dad
carelessly when there's a car literally
coming right at you
oh
you know what what I'll be eating
and I'm back in Japan
[\h__\h] you
the real deal the good stuff
um just with a Sprinkle of salt made by
a Teppanyaki chef oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah baby stay
Trevor
you better change
the other ear of course all the drama
wow that's such a desire delay Michael
we're friends now good friends
such good friends that we will make a
great effort to avoid one another
[\h__\h] perfect
I think Michael for the Statue it is
exquisite
I will
ah what on Earth is happening
when did they bond so much
what happened behind the scenes huh
Monkey Business that's a black eyed
Peace album
hmm
the best one if I may say honestly
really the best one oh yeah let's
destroy these fences oh yes yes oh yeah
oh yes
ah I'm stuck
oh that feels so good
why why why
oh nice
okay uh now
uh we even go to like
um tea
or we switch to another character I
don't know
okay
hi
let's go towards the team t for Trevor
Trevor goes to meet Trevor
oh Trevor CEST
um
Trevor loves himself
too much I'm not surprised
is this a muscle car no that's not a
muscle car let me tell you what's a
muscle car that's not a muscle car
that's not a muscle car that's not oh no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
if I see one I'll tell you cause I'm now
a professional car reader yeah yeah
that's a sports car or something like
that or is it no
[Laughter]
I've become too knowledgeable I've got
to
[Music]
the muscle car
muscle car expert yeah yeah call me call
me if you need to
compare some cars and find out which one
is the muscle car
I'll be there and help you out
don't be so bad so bad
why are you gonna be such a Karen what's
the male equivalent of a Karen
somebody who's so sorry
[Music]
oh man
do people actually say that though I've
never heard that being used like that
before muscle car no
um
foreign
never heard that me never
hmm
oh
don't worry I got it
I mean I forgot how to wait uh uh is it
okay for the shooting
what a gentleman and for once do you
want to be his girlfriend down because
like he really needs one
and hey
please please
be my friend oh please I can make you
happy I've made I've made another lady
happy until recently she was very happy
trust me bro
I would have kept her if I could
says Trevor
but sometimes if you love something you
have to let it go instead of muscle card
I think that was a muscle car maybe
could have been could have possibly been
a muscle car
this is not GTA far away what happens in
GTA 4 oh muscle car was that a muscle
car
stream stuttering is it no
that's not
I know I'm not as sure as I thought I
was
fine for me okay wonderful
[Music]
man that was a long ride
but I am here
you need to go back to your driving
school oh he's dead um I guess then you
can't too bad
how unfortunate why are there so many
cars in the way yo that's a
that's an that's a ball it has a big
friend is it a muscle
because it looks like the mix of a
muscle car and the and the sports car
what is this
it looks nice
no it's not okay well I guess big front
doesn't always apply
it's a Viper I miss you already
hello
Travis back what airport are you doing
here it's a funny way to greet your
cousin because I hate my G damn cousin
Trevor I thought we was family but
please just go and ruin somebody please
no one my sweet hey by any chance you
can catch crabs at that conference
ah
this is pretty cool regular little [\h__\h]
faster guy come in I'd like you to leave
right what's happening you guys are so
anxious
going on right yeah with every executive
and director of communications from here
to Bangalore taking it left right and
Center in the name of
training right I mean now that's what
Floyd told me yesterday
my penis without glasses she looks so
different oh look this is all I've got
all right I had a tough upbringing my
daddy was not nice to me
okay
why can't we all just be together oh you
can have Mondays through Thursdays you
can have the weekends all right I know
that's not normal but in this crazy
crazy world it was normal so good okay
Trevor's not insane anymore boys
will you marry me
oh
too like oh my God
what's love yes
there
you made me swear you're a crap Floyd
crap
you're not a man at all Bob's right
about you oh who's Bob I want both of
you to go now you you and your weird
friend whoa hey
my name is Trevor sweetheart this is so
complicated
I don't give a [\h__\h]
me not the gun no people aren't
[Music]
sir
what would I be censoring
hey there Wade
get your meat Deborah interesting lady
I should probably go say hi I wouldn't
why not
let's go get in the car all right let's
go have the time of our lives
have to say something
was it censored I guess it was censored
this is like a censored version of the
game
Golden Strip Club
to the strip club
wait can I go back inside
no oh my God did I kill both of them
oh my God that's a yum
that's a yup if I've ever seen one he's
absolutely insane he needs to go into a
clinic for insane people
Asylum
holy [\h__\h]
I could run in again
[Music]
you Carling this guy
huh
how can you
how how can you how can you vouch for
him huh
oh my God I know she seems kind of time
because she can have fun no I don't
think she can wait just forget Floyd's
gonna meet us there boys trip exactly oh
Trevor I hope you got all over yourself
you're all red you got you got scared
yeah
strawberry cereal because travel likes
that so much you sure have but
it go take that Cara have you tried face
[\h__\h] all right just
no licking okay remember really sure
last year
and you stopped in Sandy Shores to get
lit and you met a dealer and he looked
after you when your friends had
abandoned you that was weird
Target The Last Comic song is with you
driving out to a quarry and then they
just disappeared right I mean they were
gone some friends right and now cousin
Deborah don't want you around I mean
there's a pattern here the Congo did get
messy the pattern is you can't rely on
anyone anyone except me
uh I Rely and trust everyone except you
uh
um
well I mean I'm glad we didn't have to
look at it you're too closely what do
you think
that's at least something I don't think
I would have
would have slept uh comfortably tonight
if I would have seen all that in detail
I don't like him he's a real homebody
um yeah do I have to bring out the
froggy Wawa or maybe something else it's
gonna be some exposed boobies
don't we wanna see that well I will I
will see it if you want to see it in
detail you may have to play the game
yourself
anyway here's a
there's a he's just cute lava
it has been quite a bit bigger than that
maybe that's good
it's so cute
oh no oh I'm gonna it's gonna it's gonna
it's gonna wait what's the word
glom glomp you you lost that apartment
interestingly you and me we got a new
home
where
how soon
[Music]
I had a Mustang playing first class up
in the sky all the champagne living my
life
on a glamorous oh the classic last thing
and the glamorous the Glamorous
glamorous yet glamorous
say oh God I love I love that song so
much I sang It In karaoke before no need
for sensor really right here Mustang
[Music]
so this whole life summer came back
whole life summer looked about as much
uh skin exposure as this no not close
enough
YouTube YouTube I want you to give this
boy this is this this is it hold up
Summer oh
a bullying like that after I'm unnerfed
can I get one like that one of those
please Jen ma this this is the amount of
booty that I need
through there and take two doors to the
right it was quite a Kardashian book
say glamorous on the Glamorous glamorous
all the glamorous
honestly
that was nothing
huh
my switching
no no
oh Michael home hey Lester hey uh Trevor
just called about the um the big one the
the ud you know anything yeah I told him
we could hit it you down of course I'm
down look I'll get my research together
and meet you at Trevor's he's taking
over the Vanilla Unicorn gentlemen's
club all right message Franklin
swim swim
past what did I do I didn't do [\h__\h]
was it going for a daily swim but all
right on my past it okay we are gonna go
press it to yoga oh would that help me
with something
all right everybody
it's relaxing time
and take a deep breath
feel
the positive vibes
what's this mean again
feel the positive vibes
flooding into your body
into your soul
oh you [\h__\h] up Michael you're such a
loser such an amateur
I wasn't sure what to do
breathe in
Ayah oh yeah breathe out
Raven
Brave out beautiful that's just how I
like it and one more time
breathe in
and then let out all the negativity out
yes
now this one is a bit more difficult I
want you to make sure
that your mind and body
is as one
become as one
connect everything
so that everything is well unbalanced
according to keikaku
all right we're not done yet
now this one
I call the
Flying Phoenix move
yes yes yes
this one will teach you how to reach
a greater
dimension of yourself
oh do you feel it yet
no of course not it takes a little bit
more effort than that
it's difficult
it's very difficult but
I believe you have to believe believe
feel it feel it
yeah that's it that's it that's good
that's good stuff
yeah yeah
now
do you feel how the wings are growing
yes yes you're a bird
you're bad sorry sorry I got excited yo
you are a bird
you are a phoenix
[Music]
namaste
ribbon
don't let KFC take over you
you are your own chicken wing you are
your own chicken nugget
no one can tell you
in which box you belong to or if they
want you with six pieces or nine pieces
or eleven to twelve who whatever no no
no no
you are not part of their system
no
you are
you are kfp
Phoenix of the people
Phoenix
yes
oh beautiful beautiful how long are we
possibly doing this is there an end to
this or is this uh endless
[Music]
let's go let's go of your worries
let go of the salt
accept the Ping
accept the all the hacking and rigging
as being used against you
um
flawless
yes I knew you could do it
I knew you could do it
oh so you see that plane that will be
you one day
flying in the sky
and no one can stop you
oh wait what did I get for Dad what did
I get for doing that ah no stamina is
from running just now no
100 out of 100 stamina
I wish I had that in real life oh man
huh
it's pretty hard Steeler
it's like the nice what
[\h__\h] but you're only weird
my daughter is writing to me she's not
completely ignoring me yet
I'm so happy I'm happy
huh if my car is still good question oh
yeah I put a nice car in here let's see
if it's there when it's not there is it
oh
it's there anyone come back oh
[Music]
[Applause]
well if I drive with this now and I let
it
um I let it go somewhere because I have
to go somewhere will it spawn back in my
garage
it won't come back it will disappear
really all right then
I won't use it now
I'll use the other car
yeah that one is just to flex the fact
that I have it is enough for me
all right
or treats
[Music]
this is when the song becomes super
relevant again
foreign
[Music]
I don't remember the lyrics at all
now
it's so short
full version Oh man
full version
[Music]
ah
mess Behavior
what
mama
sorry
and Miss Smith is this whoa does it have
a meaning
what does it mean where am I supposed to
go
on it the team was over there but okay
maybe I have to enter through
a different way
can I go through here
oh really I can't wait go in go in go on
hello
Vanilla Unicorn oh
I asked for your number but they took my
phone I think I'm right here you want a
special dance
for you I can get a special dance
we'll have to check it out at least once
I think I'll have to censor it though
ah it's a private dance after all I
can't share it with all of you guys no
no
[Music]
way a bit bigger maybe yeah I'm kind of
scared though because she said let's
want me to get naked for you is she
actually gonna get naked
like actual nakedness
okay
maybe is this safe enough maybe
okay okay that should work
okay
oh she said oh yeah well she's naked she
is immediately naked
where's the build up girl
oh bye
touch and flirt with a dancer to
increase her light meter
[Music]
no when they show which Mouse button it
feels like it's the other one
[\h__\h] I canceled it ah
oh that's too bad
I was feeling really anxious about this
going badly so
maybe it's better this way
but she got
some easy bucks because she didn't have
to deal with my stupid flirtiness
wait why am I even in here I thought the
team was leading me here
you got it now
oh yeah
[Music]
I knew that was a familiar voice here
I know it
I was like I know this voice
oh
it's the dressing room
oh wow you don't mind me going around
here do you
I think
I'm confused when which back room I'm in
the back rooms
I don't even see the tea anymore oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
I can't even run in here that sucks
is it canceled
on it
is actually gone the t's gone
hmm
the dance canceled it it's no way yeah
what if I leave once a little bit and
then come back
what the other dudes here
let me move away a little bit
of problems for the security firm
she's back okay
[Music]
are you guys feeling hot
oh
yeah oh oh why does more damage than I
expected oopsy jewels
okay back rooms back rooms ah from here
it didn't look like I could enter it
wait no I actually really can't enter it
oh it's not where I went out of though
enter from the front but then go all the
way to the back but like from the front
sit only
okay okay but I know where to go now and
I know no no
Francis no spicy dances okay okay I
need
a little bit you know
you look like you want a private dance
vmca come and get me
wait that's the wrong
wrong wrong wrong wrong
I don't know the song though
it sounds like something I would know
[Music]
I like it
um
is it maybe originally made for GTA do
they do that
but there you are before you ask the
fridge is broken that's all right I've
had enough of your hospitality already I
have changed even I know this song What
yeah I'm done with that crazy [\h__\h] all
right I want to square things away with
Merryweather agency ain't coming back
after us and then do one last big score
and then you get you back with your
family me I'm just gonna live here I'm
gonna run this this good business
showing people a good time yeah I think
this is the right job for you Trevor and
then you know yeah I'm happy happy
so how'd you come by this place anyway
about it for ages
so you must know Leon the old manager
Leon I didn't no yeah whatever man
what's going on here what's going on is
the big one
a long long time ago in a far away place
there were three guys
Michael Trevor yeah
plans there sometimes as well maybe
there are other guys though too so uh
anyway let's be talking about a long
time ago
pretty much lived a low-life kind of
existence but always dreaming of one
thing and one thing only
big one
the big one
the big one the union depository around
200 million in gold bricks all taken
from kindly Uncle Sam who will spend the
rest of our lives being hunted by
government officials if we live through
the attempt
our Masterpiece your average so
Gentlemen let's do our civic duty and
get out there and find some gainful
employment this way
go we're going for the big one what
is that Leon is that the Leon
Mamma Mia
hi thank you for repairing my car oh
wait that's not it wait Did they clone
my car
it's my old one the broken one
uh-huh hey we are taking the temperature
yeah you know getting a feel for it
security exit routes General Vine all
right okay
driving to the bank I'm basically here I
hear some music we don't want that but
I'm already getting out of the car so
it's okay
I'm here I've arrived games
[Music]
where's the yellow spot I don't see the
yellow spots
oh wait there it is it's really hard to
see
although my screen is a bit brighter
than it should be probably really
of course clap clap what are you talking
about Frank
let me stop the whole traffic man it's a
standard bank it's getting on the ground
it's hard ain't that what a Metals kept
right now we gotta stop outside the
Arcadia Center down on Alta Street we
can get a view of the back from there
sculpt out the back entrance okay
hey man you might not notice it but I
picked up a few things rolling with you
I mean there's times I think I gotta be
the senior partner oh wait I'm wrong
here from the way you and Trevor oh
sorry there's history there yeah it
still ain't fully been explained to me
though no well remind me to go over with
you again sometime but not now
okay girl I'm not coming for you chillax
yeah I guess I could have driven down
the stairs but I don't know how that
would have went so I'm going this way
this is fine
normal day in Los Santos
Los Santos
why why are you on the way
okay okay okay
see okay and this time I saw that I saw
the yellow spot oh dog right again man
it was a timer yeah a [\h__\h] Eerie
ain't it man you think they put more
than one [\h__\h] on our national
[\h__\h] Reserve true maybe we really are
broke
hahaha
travel time
I wanted to be quiet okay
I'm sorry we are going to the Airfield
job before something help you with I
ain't even talked to Mike about it yet
but he's gonna
afford he's
he's what is it ain't it obvious
Trevor's always the flyer isn't he just
went 13 30.
we need to be in Murrieta Heights
uh-huh uh-huh why do you talk to Michael
about it oh fine [\h__\h] I was gonna pay
you man
you're a hard guy to motivate
it was a pilot in the past
wait that was his actual job
ex-pilot in the Army oh I'm talking
about the schedule last
interesting and yet when I fly as him
it really looks like
a puppy that just woke up after a long
sleep
Mike's observation
Hancock wasn't bad
that was smooth my Landings are [\h__\h]
though
oh oh oh that's a prison
the prison
waiting on a signal from the ud won't go
out on any other call and it's never
been hit man those guys must get bored
to work for the government is not
workers love more than to accept tax
dollars oh yeah that's spying on
innocent people getting paid
nothing and spying on innocent people I
paid my taxes by the way
just letting him know as an update
oh God
for you yeah yeah is it good for me
more of that give up give up
just smarter than that now
perfect
[Laughter]
wouldn't that be like pee or tea
why would BF out of all buttons hmm
oh God why why can't I fly straight
please
can we get much closer
ah
Circle it's telling me Xbox functions
with their drawers down but I guess that
won't work here
for finance okay okay
browse for them
ah the same Principle as a men's room
yeah
I guess
uh-huh what am I what are we doing I'm
not doing anything right now it's all
automatic what do you want me to do
am I supposed to
do something
oh
fly fly towards them okay now I'm doing
something what about hair for the job
where under one of the bridge just it's
on
route there's a number of get outs and
we'd be conversations
we could recover the cars with the right
equipment we'd haul them up
some sound from being picked up from my
microphone
[Music]
who's that my cats Maybe
thank you
ah we try we try come in Michael we have
a baby
we're mapping the route and finding an
ambush Point stay with them
I'm I'm so close I'm like scared to Bunk
against something if I oh my God I'm so
aggressive
[Music]
drawers down but I guess that won't work
here no it uh won't we're looking for
somewhere with cover for us and okay
browse for them
ah the same
wait oh he's like ah
it's it's in the game it's him bunking
on the table or so sheesh
it sounds like it's happening in in my
room that I'm in right now
acoustically it's like so it feels so
close to me
got me twice YouTube
one second I didn't turn on
hybrid chat
okay
when in doubt use hyper chat
off the road into the river we could
recover the cars what was that
he just down there in the channel flags
all over the place
bye
what was done my cat's on it's not in
the room
I'm thinking
a close proximity to you for its dead
periods of time what the [\h__\h] is
happening it sounds like really loud
cats
what's going on
it's so scary
where do I check
what's what was that what was all that
it
huh
it stopped when I paused
Electric
[Music]
I don't know
no smell but let me look around hmm it
wasn't maybe it was
actually
what's happening
it's my my room seemed fine
check my electric out how what would
they look fine
I don't know what I'm supposed to look
at or find
let's stop
it it's in the game huh
[Music]
he's in the game it's in the game the
moment I tap back in it starts again
press F to fixations
it's an audio bug audio glitch in his
camera
a bug
[\h__\h] jump scare worrying bug this is
the most realistic bug that I've ever
heard had before
okay
okay get used to it we'll have to get
through it
mm-hmm
oil
hahaha
oh oh that's what happens when you fly
it too close don't fly Too Close guys
okay
interesting there they are back out in
the open and
a quick turnaround it stopped in there
it's done
man that was so scary oh my helicopter
it looks like we're gonna need some
ideas to get in the building this way
I'm assuming that's doable last why are
we so far away
we're done okay
we're done
I'm gonna crash no no I'm good 30
tell that to the trash do they have to
be so exact wow so strict
onion
onions did you
get garlic that was growing an onion and
why in my kitchen it was not an onion it
just looked like it it was of course
another garlic inside of garlic
chill
[Music]
I couldn't control myself
let's go
if I remember
Excavating
challenge
Roger that looking for a big [\h__\h]
just for the construction entrance
distraction
what there's construction on that
building
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
okay flying a helicopter instead is
really difficult oh my God why is it so
fast
how do I make it less fast
also this this looks like Construction
how about this oh yeah yeah yeah
this construction is this the wrong
construction site
when the Browns will start
need to show me where oh wow
I don't even know where
no whaling is anymore I'm I'm lost
after slow down
it would work like that
let's see maybe up here
if I remember the construction is
happening on the north side of the was
gonna head that way
that way ah well finally they're showing
me a dots on the map okay let's go let's
go let's go
[Music]
Trevor really needs to stop drinking oh
God that's that's me from another state
file oh hello travel number two
oh God oh God oh God oh God
I can't control myself
ah okay here we go here we go here we go
oh that's a phoenix that's a phoenix
burp statue holy [\h__\h] it's beautiful
okay it's not quite a phoenix
oh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh oh
um
are we going up or down huh
oh hover near the construction yeah
proper above it while I take a look
ah here okay okay
I am completely still it feels like
forever
no handsome supporting structures for
the walls
I see everything perfect
go to the Airfield okay
foreign
the camera mode saved me
of 200 million dollar question if the
armored cars are a viable option we'll
bring out the gold in them huh we'll
have to fire a shot if everything goes
to plan when does everything go to plan
if it's ever going so far our missions
have always been according to keikaku
oh we can modify this topper to carry
the weight but we need another one to
match easy enough to get if we use it
for the job would you consider taking
your name off the side you think I'm
taking down the Union in anything
a chopper with my name on it well then
you don't know me bro [\h__\h] idiot can
you say that maybe that's what we should
ride on the side of the chopper that's
still your name isn't it
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
all right all right all right around
hey yo
swap to Michael oh
gladly
get me out of this [\h__\h] Chopper
please
back in the city
oh
take Franklin to his house all righty
Franklin Franklin is not allowed anymore
today to play with his friends no he has
to go home and do his homework yeah
pretty good we got Lester plan good
point go get us options there's you a
guy I know I can depend on
and then there's Trevor ah yeah yeah
Trevor get it done hey Willie I hope so
man I hope he holds it together hey you
ain't done too good of a job at that
yourself you feel me yeah well pissed
off Hillbillies bikers came out of
nowhere some Chinese gangsters in a
private Army okay so there's that yeah
but you just pissed off the FIB and the
IAA and your family man you know what I
met Amanda and I know who scares me the
most point taken so you gonna tell me
about this Brad dude and the deal with
the FIB what happened in North anken
back in the day anyway this ain't the
time man we're about to go in together
on the biggest job ever being poor there
ain't never gonna be a better time to
fill me in on this [\h__\h] it's complicated
all right get on my ax trip
[\h__\h] man you sound Shady dawg real [\h__\h]
we'll talk all right
just later
oh why can't we all get along
[Music]
we were living in such a sick house now
I knew but Michael
I think Michael's his first time here
but oh he's not even bring him in for a
cup of coffee what the [\h__\h]
surveying the score all right okay
Mission passed next
go next go next question mark
what the [\h__\h] is that skull
for uh Trevor I think
[\h__\h] I've never seen that before
[\h__\h]
D where is it what is it
what
are you saying that
is it even blue you mean okay but then I
have to go there with Franklin because
it's green
okay right because Sabrina's Franklin
yeah
I don't want to live in a place like
this it could even be 50 smaller maybe
even 70 smaller in this damn house I
would still be happy please please let
me live in a place like this
oh that would be so sick okay where is
the except here
what Richard's Majestic is still
outstanding he would be going security
what JB 700
so uh you want to get a drink or
something
yeah okay first needs to hang out right
you want to get us a card what
it's good that we left him right there
huh
what activities it's good hanging out
with you man all right well I hope so
yeah me too let's go no I haven't hung
out socially with anyone too much
recently not too much family no it's not
a main quest but okay all in my head
wait okay activities activities
um what what should we do go get a drink
drinks are close
and the movies are close too
hi
bowling oh is that bowling
I don't see bowling
we'll be watching do we actually see the
movie too
it's like an original I don't know I
guess I mean
I guess I mean growing older sucks well
I guess it beats the alternative yeah
ain't that growing younger
alternative oh dying I guess
Chase things get em hate them chase them
get them hate them so you got everything
and you're unhappy I don't get it well
I guess you gotta have something to
complain about otherwise life would be
boring man this is
you really do need help not as much as
Trevor needs help
anyway okay we're we're hanging out now
got a little bit of a
date going on you know we need some some
father-son interactions because [\h__\h]
Michael's real son we're taking Franklin
drinks a lot of drinks no I came here
for the movie but
is the movie okay too for you guys
oh here it is here it is
that what we're watching [\h__\h] in the
trunk
I married my dad
let's do it all again sequel too okay
okay Michael you coming on my way to
this prop 208 rally wait what what's up
these people are they cosplayers
how do I get into the
into the window maybe maybe maybe here
excuse me
now showing what what what what couple
level press e to watch the movie entry
costs 20 per person okay we're going
together right
whoa
no
[Music]
no no
just escape to Tab out the same button
to cancel the interaction
again we have enough money
I wanted to tap out to try to make it
louder oh [\h__\h] hell
oh
okay I hope one of those was the right
thing to me make louder
yeah we should do this again
ah maybe I can at least watch it alone
to see
what
I'm supposed to go to places and now I
don't have the car another bike
hello
what about here
please let me watch the movie again
no it's closed oh
unbelievable
I [\h__\h] up
yeah
[Music]
I was just trying to fix the audio man
what's the question mark here
it's so close by so I want to check it
out
um car
hey looking forward to seeing you on set
buddy is that a muscle car
[Music]
oh no
beautiful oh you know what that might
not is it oh is it it's beautiful
it's gorgeous
it is someone said it is
driving in style baby
it's a classic what one okay what's
going on here
why was I blew it I don't know audition
I should have worn the enema dress why
do you even go there a stalker
[\h__\h]
anyway I know you're coming here to suck
[\h__\h] so it's all right what the [\h__\h] you
talking about oh hey look I saw a
quarterback blues man and you know some
of those older records of years even
they sound a little bit closeted I'm
just you think I'm someone else don't
jump black man walking in Vine would you
think he clay PG sellout you [\h__\h] ass
punk [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] man oh hey I'm
sorry dude I didn't didn't have my
contacts me I love black people yeah you
know like uh I've Got a Friend yeah yeah
gangster rap yo sup man who gives a [\h__\h]
if he's gay or not man the man is not
married it's his business leave
[\h__\h] Alone look I'm just saying
that that it's it's the hypocrisy that I
can't stand you know I mean of
celebrities I mean PG right oh he says
he's a killer and a murderer and all
that great stuff and then when he loves
his mother and likes show tunes I mean
really what kind of message is that send
in our kids you know what I'm saying
but why do you care man no sense because
they all think they're Gods right well
[\h__\h] them [\h__\h] them [\h__\h] them [\h__\h] them
[\h__\h] magic no no they're no better
than no better than me [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
my God it's Miranda Miranda I love you
Miranda come on come on [\h__\h] Miranda
[\h__\h] Cowan
eat me out your [\h__\h] man no no no no we
can make vocal bucks here man we get one
picture of her of her hairy legs or her
aging muffin we are in the money man in
the money bro come on well now you're
best friends with him what's up with
that what's wrong with me
let's go you'll drive I'll get the shot
we're actually doing this okay come on
come on all right I mean I have time for
a side mission let's go get us right up
alongside that limo
I think this is shots of her hairy legs
[Music]
I can't shoot [\h__\h] from here
here here
I ruin your life I'll make my day
come on come on Mark fostenberg's wife's
life
We Done Yet no she still looks too good
I wonder
that's where the big zeros are uh you
want her to look miserable okay wow wow
wow
so proud of you oh let's go again we
need the money shot
okay let's try it from the left side
maybe Ryan said was her chocolate oh
Beverly this one's mine
[\h__\h] he's getting the money shots
[Music]
so Beverly can knock him up okay okay
okay okay
stay on that we're ignoring the car now
oh come on
oh yeah I downloaded your pictures first
[\h__\h] Road Madison now grow up and get
up
well what are we doing I mean I already
kind of rammed them what do we want
we done
okay okay buddy let's get out of here
I'm already late for another Stakeout
[Music]
that sounds like Beyonce
what's up Beyonce's song there's a small
person can I play Redemption Courtyard
in morning there and you can keep the
bike because I look after my people I
need the bike but I know when a ride is
coincidentally
dog all right homie it's been an
education it was Kelly Rowland keep on
making the world a better place you hear
me at the public it's not a good defense
deserve answers
not if the question is how low is
Miranda Collins muff hanging off she
getting banged up by the second round we
need to know everything from crow's feet
to camel toes hey hey
come by The Manor next week we'll
continue the song no don't tell me oh
I'm waiting for you homie
I don't think we'll ever see your face
again
yeah
okay
I say I think I understand now
what he can be a director
anyway we are going to the
do you know I think
that was a really random
mission
sorry about that I just kind of felt
like doing whatever is closest to me
but you know maybe it's realistic in a
city like this I'm sure there's a lot of
paparazzi's whoa
I've never seen paparazzi's before
though in real life like not in not in
Austria not in any other country either
where are they hiding out where are
those rats hiding oh I see I see you
yellow Dot
I was paid to be a fake Paparazzi before
what
what to show hey Molly
is like really famous go over the wall
and find the car on the lot and then
what only the principal actors and stunt
people are authorized to go near it so
you could get in wardrobe and play the
part or try something else all right
when you're out of there and clear of
Studio security call me
okay
all right
find the actor oh I see him on the map
already
this fruit salad has pineapple in it I
don't know how many times I have to tell
you I'm allergic do you understand do
you understand oh no pineapple is great
I'm so sorry for you
you can knock out the actor to get his
clothes okay
you know how many fights hey hey
hey hey hey you think just take that
okay and you both yeah
nice I think he's
he's done we should have just fed him
some pineapples or pizza yes yes on the
pizza
Pizza on the pineapple oh what no why
slick
so much for stuff no no this stuff
just be aggressive
you have to force it sometimes you need
to get on set huh excuse me are you
talking to me [\h__\h] rude where the
hell is Brandon Jesus are you gonna find
him someone's gonna find him I mean okay
she likes everybody in the hero of the
day or of the evening is here movie star
I am here what is the point of building
all these sets we gotta put Brandon's
head on the guy's body shut up will ya
please get him a mask for makeup or
something
what what what's going on why let me
redo it then what but I don't understand
I don't understand
what did I do wrong okay I'm in the car
oh
okay I didn't attack the director no
it wasn't the way I was trying to talk
to him
where the hell is Brandon I understand
now someone's gotta find him
I thought I had final approval on all
stun performers
I don't know who this guy is
something where I'm not supposed to
bring in
um damage to the garage oh my God it's
definitely already damaged oh
hello
got the wheel I need to get the [\h__\h] out
of here
[Music]
that lady will never use her legs again
because of you
let go of the [\h__\h] wheel
s
no
I'm not cool
I mean chill out I'm just interested in
the week
this buddy says right
in the whip I could buy this car with
what I make in the morning I think you
underestimate the value
[Music]
I always estimating your own tap
[Applause]
yeah [\h__\h]
but I got other priorities
someone kill this demon
oh
that's exactly what we need if you have
the car bring it to Hayes Auto in South
LS Mr Weston is marathon training but he
can reconfigure his route
no drum that's cool the studio was
enough of a money sink without the costs
that that drama can bring what kind of
shape is the car in we plan on refitting
the guns to take live ammunition do the
traffic spikes and ejectors
both of those is going to need replacing
all right good one more thing Mr
Weston's security detail are concerned
about a suspicious figure near the
garage let us know if you see something
uh-huh
okay okay yeah no um car is looking
great if you um look at it with one eye
closed which is
perfectly fine everybody to understand
these days
can I just get in the middle of a fire
shooting
we did I did
wow
um muscle car of course not but it looks
nice too what is this car this is not a
muscle car and I wonder what it is
[Music]
whoa wow close one
yeah but those kind of actions make the
world feel really alive huh like random
random stuff happening in the world
where which I can even interact with
like you know that that time when the
guy was stealing the ladies purse for
example
it's pretty cool that you can
like immediately spontaneously interact
with it and then
yeah you see the result
very alive
your car is that [\h__\h] so hot
I know thank you but it's not my car I
have to give it away again again I have
car separation anxiety
it's really common these days
a lot of people have it
Michael has a two
it was hard to live with it you know you
think you get to know someone a car
you think that
you're just you just belong together and
this is the one and then and then comes
the big bamboozle
and you have to separate someone takes
your car away
uh don't go where is the spot in here
oh there we go
hey sorry
I should know about this it's okay you
have to understand insurance companies
hate these kinds of Clans you don't like
cats with the Inside Edge shorten them
either so how'd it go smooth enough you
know movie people you know what the
irony is I'm a major shareholder in that
same studio so we just did is
practically legal
look at this [\h__\h] you're doing
it Big Mike
Lamar what the [\h__\h] are you doing here
Trevor it's [\h__\h] up when you got to
get your GPS location on your homeboys
through a [\h__\h] speed freak true
that Devin Weston Master of the two-hour
female orgasm what it is Holmes Lamar
Davies he was just leaving hey not on my
account you're looking for gainful
employment homie hell yeah I'm always
trying to get some [\h__\h] paper
just the type of guy I like to work with
predictable hey we could bring your boy
hair in on the last part of the ship oh
yeah [\h__\h] that's exactly what you could
do that's exactly right here exactly if
you want him in then you get him to
boost the rest of the [\h__\h] you got give
me my money and I can go with my
[\h__\h] life oh no my sense
intention here slick
he's the spirit but you're the brains am
I wrong I can see it look I need you on
point when we move this stuff out of
town yeah whatever man call me when it's
done and after this make sure we got our
[\h__\h] check all right Ciao Baby
it is what it is yeah it's so funny it's
such a weirdo it's all these characters
they're such characters I I don't trust
me huh I don't get down like that oh
yeah let me tell you how the world Works
Slim
playing Counter well look at me looking
really [\h__\h] hot nice
yeah looking good in that suits with a
white top beautiful
all right we are going next to the L
ucha
okay
we just need a car hey girl oh nice spot
oh
how are you good morning how are you oh
Beverly's talking to me I signed you up
to a wildlife photography competition
no thank you
on your car
[\h__\h] I'm not taking that shitty ass car
oh he's he's standing still again
perfect time
okay
bestie I'm sorry but I have places to be
at places to go to please understand
to take a taxi you should know by now I
like to take things into my own hands
okay
I like to decide where I'm going and how
I'm going there and how long it takes me
to get there yeah and I like to enjoy
this beautiful scenery and if I wasn't
if I was taking taxis all the time then
I wouldn't have a [\h__\h] rocked Mario
Kart last night wouldn't I
huh
yeah
it's like so good Mario Kart last night
you guys were astonished by my greatness
yeah
hey I was really decent at it okay
that was a side mission
oh what how do I know that anyway
should I ah wait
wait what's what's that what's that blue
dot here
is that Michael
let's let's go to Michael then
um
and Michael can go to Michael
uh to m
I feel horrible
after the date with Franklin's why did
you not like the movie
he's he's looking so casual today my
cold
all right it was all my cup
my bestie oh
we are indeed very close
ah we're going to our house
I wonder what's going on there
can I tell you guys a little bit I still
have a tensions I wanted to tell you
guys but just don't catch a [\h__\h]
break in this game it seems
can I tell you
yeah okay okay so remember uh last
Sunday I was
um but it's so close I can barely talk
last Sunday I was at the on the Comic
Con right and I told you guys that I
first met up with uh my my childhood
friend I told you that right childhood
like oh you can't even call a child but
it's more like Teenage Hood
um
yeah yeah I told you that and then and
then I got the autograph and all that I
told you that in cartoons
tangent best tangent
and then after that
I met up
at my home
with her again like I went home a bit
early to clean up my apartment because
spontaneously we decided to have
um my my old high school friend sleep
over at my place because she kind of
needed a place to sleep otherwise she
would have gone
uh back to her parents place I suppose
in a different city so
yeah I was like okay okay okay you know
what I actually really want her to sleep
over because she has never seen my cats
before
and I I really wanted to show her my
cats and I wanted to show her my
apartment and all that you know see how
how I'm doing talk a little bit have a
cozy time because at the convention she
was spending time with another friend
mostly and I was like that's fine you
know I can have her for myself and at my
home so yeah so I went back home a bit
early and and cleaned up my apartment as
well
possible
um
and then at some point she arrived
sold and I showed her everything and she
is a cat whisperer she got along with
smoothie and chonkers so easily and so
fast
it was so sweet yeah she was fascinated
by my kitty cats
actually
the thing is that she I've been like
following her journey with her own cat
like she lives in Japan normally you
know
and she got herself a kitty cat a while
ago like oh two three years ago maybe I
don't know
and I didn't meet her cat but I'm I met
her in Japan at the time and and she was
like talking about it how
um I think it was like a a kitten from a
shelter or cat a cat from a shelter I
don't think it was a kitten in the
beginning but she had big problems with
that cat because it was
it seemed like a pretty traumatized cat
from the get-go
um it it like would hide from her all
day
um would not not want to interact or
what was really scared and spooky easy
to be spooked not spooky not spooky cat
no no easy to be spooked you know one of
one of those cats who need a lot of time
to get over whatever issues they have
and I've been like following their
journey and she it took her like I think
over a year until
her cat was like okay with being you
know
um
spending time together relatively close
to one another and now they're best
things but it took her so long but I
respected like when I saw the progress
in the beginning I I thought oh my God
this cat maybe never never is going to
be normal with humans but
um
and with the effort it seems
um so then I was really happy to show
her my cats because you know we both
love cats a lot and I I I
remember when I was younger and I would
go to her place after school or so
and she had a couple cats too and they
were really really sweet and really cozy
and cuddly yeah yeah but she's been
living in Japan for a long time
um yeah and got herself on her own cat
but then you know this was the first
time in a long time then she went
um back to Austria and to you know have
a vacation and all that so anyway she
slept over at my place but first before
that
um um she likes Game of Thrones and all
that too so I got
um I got her to catch up on the reason
the house of the Dragon episodes because
she was still missing two or so so
um while uh she was watching those
episodes in my bedroom I'm on my TV I
was getting the guest room ready with
the bed and all that and I got her and
me some pizza I served her the pizza on
on my bed I was like stay calm feel and
see the pizza together
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and then we
watched the newest episode
uh together the next morning
yeah
that was um there was there was one one
a little bit awkward
um scene but besides that was thankfully
not as bad as other episodes
in terms of awkwardness yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah but
talked about myself and we caught up and
all that
now
the reason why I wanted to talk about it
is because I wanted to flex a little bit
about my friend
oh let me Flex okay it's not a flex
about myself I wanted to flex her thing
she gave me permission okay so the thing
is we both went to art school you know
and now she finished it unlike me
and now she's still doing
um like you know
stuff related to art and I'm like so
proud and fascinated and inspired by how
far she has gotten
because
you know that new Street Fighter 6 game
she has been drawing uh backgrounds for
it
holy [\h__\h] macaroni right
holy [\h__\h] macaroni yeah like several
of the backgrounds are from her lots of
the background elements but you know
there's there's like so many people
working on that so
um it's hard to say which one she showed
me
um like from the street fighter 6
trailer she was like oh this one's from
me and this one's from me and I'm like
hey what girl
girl what holy [\h__\h] looks I'm so proud
of her that's crazy yeah she's been
doing stuff like that for a while now
years yeah yeah yeah it's so cool
and then
um I asked her if she would like want to
draw something for me
because yeah she said she's she said she
could she would like to do me
a favor and like do something for me
yeah
so um I I you know gave her some ideas
of what I could possibly need at the
moment in terms of backgrounds
yeah and she was like oh yeah I'm
totally interested I wanna
yeah let me try let me try
yeah so uh in the future we'll have a
background drawn
school friend isn't that salted
yeah and yeah even though it's not I
don't think it's usually like my type of
game
um but I'm thinking of trying out Street
Fighter 6 just because you know my my
old high school friend is involved in it
yeah I saw what the [\h__\h] why is it
what's with the controls
I thought um Zeta was playing it a
little bit so it seems like we have
permissions
um
yeah
[Music]
foreign
why is the music so weird
in here
anyway that was a tangent I really
wanted to tell you guys oh that was beta
access Oh I thought it was already out
or so because I saw her playing it
what [\h__\h] what do you want I'm your
friend I don't want anything man come on
your company's good enough people always
want something from one another yeah
thanks I really appreciate that so
family ain't back yet huh
nope ah she's a goddamn fool man
despite all the chaos of these last few
weeks
big star admission figured it out every
Mission you're like oh this Mission
sounds ridiculous mom actually it does
not sound ridiculous you know because
you
you're a killer do you mean that you
know literally man of action
you do not sit on couches you take
scores you're back man we are back all
right all we gotta go do is bust out
Brad and then we're Golden man Franklin
he makes us Multicultural is that what
we're doing things it's cyber we're like
modern America we just get ourselves a
gay friend bam no it's not it
I got money it just makes you miserable
I want to make movies great great
it's like there's little Lego toys
I want to play Lego we're gonna do this
last big job and then we're gonna
dissolve the partnership
this is not a game to me all right this
is a [\h__\h] way of life
no one gives a [\h__\h] about me
I do
okay
[\h__\h] you do you
do you give a [\h__\h] about him I saw your
grave I mourned you and then it turns
out that everything I [\h__\h] thought
about you was wrong everything you're
not dead and you're not a man what the
[\h__\h] are you I'm your [\h__\h] nightmare
enough with your goddamn threats
are these boys 12 or something
[Music]
a man
let me just ask you something all right
something I've been I've been thinking
up in North Yankton
exactly who was buried in your place oh
[\h__\h] maybe no one
or
I never gave it any thought a spicy doll
you know what I'm thinking I had no clue
you treacherous piece of [\h__\h]
you're [\h__\h] dead you're [\h__\h] dead
oh
Trevor hey T
oh wait we know already
we know that's my car I have another car
is it time to use it
come on
I need patience for these doors
all right
[\h__\h] you hey come on where you going
smooth [\h__\h] you you don't need to go all
the way to North Yankton to find out
what I can tell you over a couple beers
back in my house come on we'll order
pizza [\h__\h] yeah
this is insanity oh no no it's clear and
reason thought finally stop your car
come on come back we'll talk oh I'm not
gonna listen to another one of your lies
hey I'll lay it all out for you
everything just stop the car turn around
I'm going up there to see it for myself
you'll be disappointed oh I'll be
something it'll be an anti-climax the
Braves just a bag of sand something like
that mirrors
guys how do you do it man the game is up
I'm trying to save you a trip you've
done me enough favors buddy all right
save your [\h__\h] breath Trevor come on
[\h__\h] you Michael
soon enough I will
well what what
oh
okay
big turning point maybe in the game
special agent Norton [\h__\h] interesting
[Music]
I think
think they talk I don't know how he used
his head but does he know does he know
it all hey he's on his way up to
ludendorf to confirm his suspicions [\h__\h]
then what then who [\h__\h] knows what I
don't know I'm gonna go see if I can
reason with him but I come but I I I I
yeah don't worry about it it's between
me and him besides if it goes wrong up
there I'm sure you ain't far down his
list that's good to know
all right okay wow wow wow
interesting
interesting we're gonna have some drama
llama
some drama happening between the boys
anyway
when was I
um
I think I want to talk a bit more about
my friend
she was here
we watched half of the Dragon she liked
my cat she was
they were you know smoothie was cuddling
up to her instead of me at some point
when we were watching TV
I was jealous
um
jealous
yeah I was I was like it's moving at yo
but but honestly happy to see they got
along so well
took pictures of my
kitty cats
because she loves them so much who
couldn't who could not love my cats
everybody who sees my cats falls in love
with them
but
it loved me the most no matter what
happens
at night time they always
join me in my bed not not the guest
room's bed
no no no no no
always my bed
post up
that's um
that looks exactly like
what's that again
UPS yeah thank you thank you looking at
it I completely forgot what it looks
like
UPS uh upper
uh
yo look at me in my fancy car
it's just like in the movies
what are we here why are we at the
airport are we gonna uh go on an
airplane
I'm almost there
save the car that's good if I want
another one of those I know where they
are they're they respawn at the movie
theater
and we'll movie movie set
go to the second level terminal entrance
on La fate
seems so
I mean maybe not 100 necessary but why
else would they let me park the car
there
um
one high all right
it's been a while since we've been here
up up we go do a lot a lot more oh
wow
no I don't mean waiting table
s
are dead
oh
bye bye pretty car
so sad see this is why I have car
separation anxiety ah this is
[Music]
Amanda
we're going to move to Los Santos oh
it's my memories I made a deal
slate
totally wiped clean
trust me darling look at me Amanda
it was the only thing I could do either
everyone dies or one guy gets out I'm
that guy
status his name is Dave Norton nice guy
realist he gets the glory I get out
it's not even a decision Amanda I don't
have a choice
do you want to die here where it's
always snowing
where do you want to go and live where
it's always sunny all right at one final
months no I like snow
Always Sunny is boring too always
snowing may be boring too
should go to a more balanced Place
honestly
it's so deepful out of town you don't
need to know trust me nothing is gonna
go wrong
nothing yeah I hear you
I did the deal Amanda this is so
dramatic
Maybe
we get out the atmosphere be happy be
normal
it ain't supposed to go down like this
I wasn't supposed to be like this oh no
ludendorf again very German battling
why so German why is everything so
German in the skin GTA creators really
like Germany it's over
just this one job and everything is done
everything is done
can't take this seriously oh it felt
pretty serious to me go to your grip
okay okay okay okay
what
hey yo what the [\h__\h] why can I not
hello let me go okay I can't
somehow I cannot
I'm rich side am I supposed to go in
here
German Theft Auto ah oh here is good
perhaps
oh spoopy hell don't like graveyards
don't like graveyards
your time
is that why you flew out here huh tell
me I'm wasting my time
yeah that's what you look like
the guy who doesn't give a [\h__\h] that's
ridiculous how long are you gonna keep
lying for Mikey huh when's it gonna stop
oh this is so creepy the whole Act of
comes out in the Life digging up a great
rest Trevor
there's nothing there
this is it
Moment of Truth Moment of Truth
oh [\h__\h] this
oh
does that happen no
Brad
the one who's supposed to be in
we know what we got to do to survive
this thing it didn't work out the way it
was supposed to oh how was that huh can
we get a ride in the cannon me in the
ground or or both of us in the coffin
Brad got shot you saw it can we get a
flashlight
I got shot I did that's that's it
I think the only thing that didn't go as
planned was me showing up on your
doorstep 10 years later Mike yeah I
mourned you and I missed you but I got a
[\h__\h] family Trevor
we were all gonna die he did die you
reptilian [\h__\h]
I didn't want to come to this yes you
did you just don't have the [\h__\h]
balls to do it but I do I got more to
lose than you never a true a word has
been spoken brother to be true no pull
the [\h__\h] trigger
he only got the guts
take the [\h__\h] shot
who is that oh [\h__\h] yeah
Joe Phillips Mr Charles has requested a
word hey ho ho I'm not the guy you're
looking for hey
get the boyfriend boyfriend
[\h__\h]
what's going on what's going on what the
I'm sorry who are you guys
who are your friends t
well they're shooting me so I'll shoot
back
full GTA GTA or anything really logic
[Music]
and another van okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my God what is going on
on where's my
Adele where the
where the should I just get the car
nice
oh wait go [\h__\h] yourself
[Music]
what
should I just run run car
my car okay I'll kill cookie
okay
[Music]
oh
hmm
okay maybe we need to fight some of
these people oh
so who are your pals Trevor
whoa
oh [\h__\h] oh this is pretty pretty tough
man okay okay
bottom
are you calling back up who are your
friends t
ish
oh I only have to do so right now there
we go
I'm scared
what the [\h__\h]
um
foreign
how many are they gonna spawn endlessly
I hope not hey can we do this where the
weather's better
pretty decent
one one more get down get out oh [\h__\h] up
you confused pieces of [\h__\h]
[Music]
in the way
[Applause]
making good use of my my favorite new
gun rifle everything sniper everything
so more
you're a mom
ENT
[Music]
you're way off [\h__\h] can you [\h__\h]
hide you idiot
okay okay uh one for you one for you
one for you
are you dead yet
because of the snow it's kind of hard to
see my
my cross thingy my cross hair is that
what you call it
everything looks like it
okay we can go we can go we can go hey
guys
Overkill wait isn't that what's in my
title
I feel that's what I
wrote in my title to this side go [\h__\h]
yourself
oh it is well there you go I was hoping
for the title to come true last time was
very much Overkill a lot of the times
Phillips went that away
I don't see it it's hard to see it
you're out of your element
[Music]
come so far
shouldn't there be
you're making a mistake
foreign
there's like one day I don't see him
where is it
[Music]
wait for him to come out maybe
is he gonna come out
yay
one left one left
hey can we do this where the weather's
better reloading in the voice first
possible time there we go there we go
where are they coming from next oh
crane oh oh
mower Vans of course
no no no where's my oh you forgot to
check the train schedule yeah uh which
way do we go though
you got nowhere to go boyfriend uh all
right all right
get out the [\h__\h] clock
we killed so many people for nothing we
got caught travel why
come on let's be Bros bros for Life
Brian prose before hoes oh oh controller
oh
oh man
what is Trevor planning to do next
oh hello Mother Phillips Industries Mr
Phillips this is Wei Chang you know my
eldest son Tau yeah the X nut backed out
of a contract we agreed on how is he
still learning the ropes thank you my
friends miss you in North Yankton I was
hoping we could talk
was that your people ah of course sorry
I had to cut out your operation caused
this problem for me
I want to expand into Blaine County but
your business and your temperament
prevent me from making inroads oh wow
too bad I don't know what you can do
about that I've already done this [\h__\h]
we have your lover whoa whoa whoa
my lover my Cody Center
you live in your trailer together
you
know how much will you give up oh [\h__\h]
for his safety
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry what was how
do you grapple he played this thing
again the buttons
I'm sorry wait what
let me let me retry
ah L1 R1 thank you thank you that was it
ah
okay
a
I hated this is cool
Trevor Phillips Industries Mr Phillips
what happened so much this is great
achievement
oh yeah massive e head backyard we
agreed on how is he still learning the
ropes thank you
we've been watching you Phillips your
operations cause it's problems
sometimes
oh viable what the [\h__\h] is wrong
Phillips from the trailer my lover if
only horses
you live with him with your maid he's in
a custody now give yourself up and he
will live oh air turbulence
man that's a that's a tough break look
you guys deserve each other hold on to
that fat Trader can we fly highlights
the higher applies the more safe
I hope I hope we don't get in trouble
with the military
okay
foreign
eagle
meet me at my crib me and Frank going
roll on that last car for the rich dude
you win
Trevor's a little bit busy right now
please understand
and dialogue was different
um
oops
but wait
can I still
oh
this area is fun okay I'm about to land
and how how to land
can I just can I just I I stop stop okay
uh we're gonna try again everybody
[Music]
oh
holy [\h__\h] okay okay
we are so [\h__\h] close
yeah wasn't there a bug for that
I'm on the controller now though
hell free really don't really who can I
trust in the chat
triangle okay oh God oh God oh God oh
okay okay
oh
[Music]
my God
I can believe you guys
but you know triangle sounds unfamiliar
triangle
and finally I don't know what triangle
no
oh no no one's the actual button for
landing gear huh
I I remember from like previously
uh I realized okay okay triangle is the
F on the controller but I forgot that
one two Phillips Industries
oh yeah
how is he still learning the ropes thank
you
what the [\h__\h] is that we have your lover
Phillips from the trailer my lover yes
my Cody Center you live with him with
your maid he's in a custody now give
yourself up and he will live
okay all right ahead of course man
that's a that's a tough break good look
you guys deserve each other hold on to
that fat traitor and feel free to
torture him to your heart's content
you'll save me the trouble
was that different too than the previous
one
plastic
okay this time you're not lying to me
thank you thank you
okay
I got Bamboozled big time once again
why doesn't always have to be like this
okay and slowing down I can by just not
pressing R2 huh
let's try that too I think yeah yeah we
are we are there
your landing gear slowing down
okay oh oh
could it be any smoother than this I
don't think so yeah
yes
[Music]
I was rewarded for that beautiful
Landing
[Music]
oh I got a cheap one for that okay
what now
oh parachutes are now finally
automatically equipped
about [\h__\h] time
taxi back to the hangar which witch
hanger
where do we want to go next there's so
many question marks are we going to the
why why what is that one anyway
I really wonder let me see is there is
that written on here
uh Rampage Rampage
or I don't really understand
um
I like that one I had before oh I did
that before
well where should we go to the to this
one
see I'm so far okay I might actually use
a taxi how do you use a taxi
how how does it work I never did it
before
okay can I get out of this thing oh
hello
huh who is this it's me I shouldn't have
called
Mrs madrazo hey are you behaving Trevor
no not at all
Patricia
I really miss you a time together
it's very important
I have to go
should we go see her
can we
my beloved
okay
um but no we're gonna go taxi taxi
Mr taxi taxi taxi and drinks Matrix
Matrix means in contacts
[Music]
ah here cab service styling
I need a cab for Toronto I'm sending one
out right now I'm glad to hear it wait
what
oh you meant something about parking my
my my my plane properly anyway it seems
fine also where's the taxi gonna arrive
at hello
now just wait go to the road oh hello
hello
oh
um
oh wait first of all turn that down
thank you where can you take me
um uh uh the thing that I marked in the
map please choose destination little
soul all right let's hit the Rope
wait what
what
a hug
I don't know how what
oh wait how do I know which one here you
go no no
no no Rampage ah wait no no no no
[Music]
no no
Mrs madrazo driver oh I miss you all you
boys I miss you too I can't speak for
the other boys You're such good friends
uh it's a bit more complicated than that
actually Michael and I you know not
speak old friendships cannot be replaced
hey how are you is Martin looking after
you dude wait it's raining outside let
me have this conversation in here oh no
um
oh I think I get it now
huh
oh my God the weather is terrible oh
yeah
this one this one right
okay
You're Gonna Go
why is it a controller thingies still I
don't know what B is
I've been making
I'm gonna make him go
so what what
Circle your thing man I've been driving
this cab for okay seven years
you can choose a destination and then
you teleport there and that's why you
guys keep on telling me to take a taxi
in the end if I'm just looking at him
oh I can skip it for extra money
um why does it cost extra money what the
[\h__\h]
all right brother here we are
a hundred
that's pretty expensive wow
[Laughter]
so where exactly am I am at the wait I'm
not even at the right spot
what
oh
see this is why I don't use taxes
laughs
[Applause]
[Music]
again
what the actual [\h__\h]
oh
yeah
[Music]
gorillas
ah they got some good music in here I'm
oh oh there's so much Korean this is I
guess this was called little soul
Young
[Music]
I think my sister really likes gorillas
my mom probably too
who does not like gorillas right
everybody loves gorillas
and save the guy nah
nah I don't wanna
uh
boom boom [\h__\h] you taxis I am boycotting
taxes forever
that's why no one uses you guys anymore
and everybody uses Uber and other [\h__\h]
like that yeah you can't even get me to
the right place man
ah pathetic Mark Davis what's up I'm
part of the team that's what's up team I
don't do teams uh Devin Weston's car
still in team the one Frank's running oh
oh yeah that one hey look I boosted the
ride I'm about to meet your boy Franklin
and I need your ass to pick up the
Packer meet us outside the garage and we
taking these [\h__\h] up to falito
Bay all right buddy fine that's a long
trip
um
are we switching
we don't be switching
who are we right now no Franklin okay
where am I going am I following the blue
line
well yeah
fine little fam
blah blah blah bloom
I can't wait until karaoke tomorrow wait
why why am I
sometimes the controls
are [\h__\h] me up
I don't know how why
maybe it's me
no I'm right now I'm using the keyboard
again I only use the controller when I'm
supposed to fly somewhere
and I think I I may have used it for
diving
oh yeah
where is
where is the golden spot here
the G-Spot
oh golden car
beautiful
oh actually not golden I guess it's
yellow
wait wait
wait I mean I gotta get in your car okay
I'll gladly get into the car
[Music]
Monroe
there was no golden spot the Boost homie
just a golden car any problems you know
me huh yeah I do know you fool so what
you think smoothly
[Music]
that amateur [\h__\h] behind me I'm a
professional now like
so tell me what happened I saw the ride
I took the ride no drama no secure no
one said who the [\h__\h] is this gangly
[\h__\h] doing in my car nothing
that's worrying man what you [\h__\h] with
this ride for sorry sorry
you know I can't hold back it's just too
much fun
I keep on getting pop-ups
from Steam favorite gangbang
hello am I supposed to put that up there
all right all right around here Dad
there's the golden spot
remember his pose spot Ty post Trevor
oh my God why is it so difficult
like yesterday or so
she only plays for an hour what happened
Sonora freeway
I wonder if she's gonna play more or if
it was a one-time only thing
[Music]
rumor and hearsay we've got a long way
to go I'd get comfortable
in this thing the black one in the in
the front [\h__\h] is your operation slick
[\h__\h] if you are all right driving I'm
gonna catch up on some sleep go for it
you can make another clip now my
daughter like mothers sleep yeah I'll be
asleep when your ass stop talking [\h__\h]
some boss
like mother like daughters reception
you can make it worthlessly how many
more times this is gonna happen days
everything that's funny because like the
boy Frank didn't mention [\h__\h] about that
and as a matter of fact I don't even
know the dude but considering the mutual
acquaintances
nobody I used the term retirement
euphemistically it's hard to see
anything with those things it eats dudes
and [\h__\h] dudes you talk fruit it's
unconfirmed well so confirmed the fact
that you talk stupid or the fact that
you do some messed up [\h__\h] or where the
other dudes at like maybe he's dead the
last one oh [\h__\h] man [\h__\h] do Frank know
about this I don't know if Franklin
knows but let's just let him sleep he's
sleeping yeah
it wasn't a good guy he made out man
dude was a killer a thief a liar and
irritable as [\h__\h] yeah a liar above all
else oh fire I hope you sound like some
[\h__\h] he ain't called like uh he lied to
me I am some [\h__\h] he didn't call for 10
years [\h__\h] man he [\h__\h] you the [\h__\h]
his heart is broken
man the first time's always special I
hope he was gentle with you enough
about me
I was I was a little overwhelmed by the
place
but that ain't who I am for the most
part but the Michael [\h__\h] you
Redemption Arc the Michael [\h__\h] me and
the Michael [\h__\h] brat and the Michael
ran off with the FIB Brad who who the
[\h__\h] is Brad Brad is our boy back from
the day and Michael killed him Michael
got him killed he died when Michael
faked his death isn't this where the
boat
um
was in the ground and Michael was in
hiding and now Michael's dead and it's
all okay Michael's current condition is
unconfirmed I said that but if he was
dead you'd be cool because of this Brad
dude who died whenever
yes man I thought you and Michael were
tight so did I okay that'd make a lot of
[\h__\h] sense
it seems like
like the trying to make me life Trevor
hey I couldn't say I mean not really a
Rosa Road it ain't got abandonment
issues
making do I don't need to make do I need
to make snaps on these rods sure yeah
the time will come that's what happens
before we get paid is what Franklin's
asleep it's just me and you what what
you trying to say you want me to jack
you off or something Jesus no God no of
course not
unless man use a sick hello
friendship friendship yes right whatever
man can you make my truckers or symbols
oh my mentions like Cowboys gangsters I
don't know how many mentions I'm scared
to look at them truckers are about the
unsexiest myth I ever heard apart from
hobo uh maybe tied with hobo freedom
loners in the night you know what
truckers do cut up women and get other
dudes to Jack them off come to think
about it aside from not looking Freight
around the country you got about all the
necessary prerequisites for a fine
career in Hollis was that no shame in
that I don't know you get paid or enjoy
human contact money's [\h__\h] so is
friendship all right all right all right
I see you still touching
yeah we're going a long long long long
way over there oh dude getting paid to
sleep don't even worry but how many
times have we mentioning that's Franklin
is like in charge on this one we got it
he's a kind of figurehead
a puppet if you like with Devin Weston's
hand up his ass
right up to the elbow yeah
it's repulsive well once he's paid it's
not really about me being popular
recently
I read them all can't save him five
minutes later I got five more mentions
there's so much going on now that's
something I want to see so uh
tell me man
Michael introduced us never catch me I
didn't exactly travel in similar circles
ah I mean the creeper Michael yeah I
don't know yeah sorry I don't want to
reminisce
the wounds ain't healed he's such a
delicate that no [\h__\h]
you got in there screw you yeah that's
good let it out homie don't let it out
then
he's probably playing me from the start
right yeah probably how you doing where
when all right all right the [\h__\h] I was
running this small air freight outfit in
North Yankton tiny operation there's one
Beagle I could borrow when I needed it
we were kids kids were playing so this
guy I know says there's this other guy
needs some hot cargo moved across the
border oh [\h__\h] what's happening wake up
you nosy [\h__\h] what time was on
the Rock what you gonna do oh fearless
leader
I'll handle this if you keep driving
to get rid of them
we're on board hey don't forget the
headset homie
truck standing for Franklin oh my God
okay what are you doing they must have
waited till we was out of town it seems
so
okay okay
stay steady what are you doing oh my God
oh my God
it's really hard to drive while having
that
camera on but I think so far we're doing
a good job oh God okay never mind never
mind
oh
oh sheesh I'm sorry Franklin I didn't
want to do that to you you good okay
he's good he's good
[Applause]
[Music]
I am Sam
my yeah small
real smoothies
[Music]
how are we gonna do that
oh oh oh oh
uh what's up y'all ass [\h__\h]
defend the truck from the cup okay
we're ready
thank you
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh my I have guns oh yeah right oh whoa
let me catch up let me catch up let me
catch up
[Music]
homie
good job I'm only the passenger
[Music]
a good aim even though I'm not aiming at
all
[Music]
I died or did I no oh
we were abandoned I mean Trevor and
Lamar are abandoned one
what what I mean what am I doing
oh I didn't read that
man you brought the cops right to us dog
okay
okay okay
spikes are so useful
oh come on
we have a license for that car
s
some more spikes summer Sparks here and
there a few here a couple there
[Music]
one million do you hit 1 million
Millions riveting point of time
whoa Mr Clinton
we're coming up to Goa is all over
because they slowed us down son that's
not surprising the insurance companies
have been pressurizing them to find you
since the studio breakage
man you could have told us don't get
emotional we're waiting at procopio
truck stop be here soon
the lawyer checks up at the procopio
truck stop
oh ah Kylie Roland oh a lot I remember
just now I like one specific song of
Kelly Rowland but I don't remember which
one
[Music]
yeah
we may have needed two tries but that's
only because I didn't realize I had the
spikes chicken
[Music]
definitely KFC
much better than roadkill yeah
okay everybody
I can still drop spikes funny yeah
should I drop them in front of that
truck so it moves
[Music]
of our economy
foreign
guys yesterday
felt
felt so properly German even though I'm
Austrian
it had by swished for lunch
with some good sweet mustard
and uh
-huh I think my slush is a quite common
thing to eat at Oktoberfest
yeah
Bavarian look you're saying bavarians
in Germany is very much you're taking
care of head back to town
meet with Molly okay
nobody's made it what about the blue dot
here
I think I'm gonna make some more after
the Stream
some more advice wished
it's like
um it's a sausage a pretty white sausage
that you have to um put peel off the
skin yeah we're Devin it
I'm spoiling it before eating it I don't
know why you have to do it I don't know
why you have to peel off I wanted to
look that up on Google like for other
sausages you don't do that but for this
one you do it you peel off the skin and
then you eat it with a sweet mustard
what's the problem with that skin
specifically
that's too much work it's not that
difficult it gets off pretty easily
hmm
because it's tough It's a figure yeah it
feels it definitely feels like a thicker
skin yeah
um yeah you'll peel it off but I
switched it's supposed to be peeled off
hmm you guys if you ever visit Germany
or Austria so
my God girl this is triggering
welcome back to the Stream
uh no but if you ever ever come to
Germany or Austria and you get to eat a
vice versa make sure to peel it off
although maybe I don't know if you get
it served as like a restaurant or so
maybe it already comes peeled off I'm
not sure is not perhaps the best idea
for you two to be seen together for a
while where's the money
brilliant investors the world has ever
known he's
obviously I did have it in Germany
look let me be the first to tell you he
ain't gonna fall in love with your ass
now where the [\h__\h] is my money
the best thing that could have happened
to you in the situation
he is going to hold your mind invest it
in his Alpha fund and make the funds
available to you at a time as the
transfer will not induce any undo thank
you thank you which is a polite way of
saying I'm getting robbed are you
[\h__\h] kidding me that is a
short-sighted and frankly immature way
of seeing things Mr Clinton
let's go
and pop [\h__\h] maturity is not
really my [\h__\h] thing
oh man
Franklin been scammed he's too nice for
this world you know
too nice that's why I like him oh my
goodness
let's go soda
does that give us any effect status
effects please
no no that was all right that was all
right
you liked it
Franklin what's happening Lester hey
look you seen Michael man the contact he
set me up with is holding out on the
payment dawg
hi I'm gonna see his phone is offline
his credit cards aren't active well this
is aberrant Behavior the last usage is
for a flight to North Yankton there was
a signal from a cell back in Los Santos
but now nothing damn is he in a city dog
[\h__\h] he could be in trouble huh I don't
know but it's worth speaking to Trevor
most likely he was with him in the
midwest I'll get him to come see you
[\h__\h] all right homie look sending to my
aunt's crib all right
auntie
yay it's been a while
oh wait uh well what's that market I
have on the map we're not when there are
we oh God we're so far we should take a
taxi huh
this is where I need to go right
this this is my my auntie's home
I'll try calling a taxi again okay
and okay I know how to do this
contacts
called texting
it's a bit annoying I wish they made fun
family
right now it would be nice if I could
choose a spot on the mat click it and
say
make taxi send me here
and then
I can you know immediately skip it
that would be really really I can
what
oh
way point and then enter
huh
uh the tax needs to be here
well then that's not exactly how I
wanted it to be
I mean I want to go onto the map click
one point and say bring me there baby
where's my taxi what the [\h__\h]
hello
did I cancel it by accident or so
why is it taking so long
[Music]
Mr taxi taxi taxi commoners measures
no hey can I get a cab sorry all the
drivers are busy right now please call
back later ah does that mean that I
already have one on the way
taking a sweet time though
it means I can't that's trouble
hey yo what the actual [\h__\h]
try to blimp what's a blimp
what's up
Zeppelin
I can do that oh that's crazy
trivia
oh I find the deer that pissed on me I'm
gonna eat it's warm liver is that are
those the cloves of uh what's your name
Miranda
oh
looking cute
[Music]
song
not quite your size but uh
yeah looking fabulous why the [\h__\h] am I
up here it's like uh yesterday in rest
with the horse
yeah what on Earth
what the [\h__\h]
it's the hiking trail
he's grieving
what I mean
let's go back
deal of his [\h__\h] now
you're the prettiest princess he is so
pretty
so taxi I'll try calling once again
oh maybe the blend but no let me see
first if they send me one or if they
still say they're busy
I need a cab as soon as possible stay
where you are I gotta drive it right
around the corner okay there you go now
I'm staying where I am I'm staying I'm
not moving
I thank you for the one million also
read five million today oh hello eh you
expect me
to walk over there
maybe it's gonna turn
over there
what what the [\h__\h] is that taxi doing
I still see it
is it gonna do a turn
I don't see it anymore
oh oh
nah
I I
will stay with my original stance
say [\h__\h] taxes atomic blimp Services how
can I help you today do you got any
blimps available right now well of
course sir I'll get one sent out to the
nearest available drop-off Point
thank you for your business call us
anytime
nearest drop off where would that be
blimp.com how fast
isn't Gonna Come
I don't know what so he's gonna blimp
Bieber yeah
on the map
oh
wait what I feel like I saw it on the
mini map yeah I see it huh
I don't see it on a big map
it does not you can't I saw [\h__\h] with
me you say I'll take the blood but it's
not even gonna come to me
I have to go all the way into the city
that's but that's literally where I want
to go out
okay okay see
was wasn't there a car right here
[Music]
okay please stop the car
hold it back that's fine too you know
what I'll take the bike thank you
this all sucks
Gotta Go My Own Way
never trust chat
I mean
get out of here
well I help you oh dear what the [\h__\h]
let me save your life really quick
how are we doing this on it
not sure how to help you
how
oh wait oh shoot oh
you've seen that okay here take it easy
I got it
I saw the Bulldogs
I saw it sometimes it's difficult you
know
it's got to be a hospital near here
somewhere no no hospitals can you take
me to Sandy Shores I got people there
who can help me out
um
you don't have an insurance do you look
thanks for this another 20 seconds out
of had the cops all over me that only
the car where you fit into don't worry
about it okay oh my God oh my God
dead body
you want my help you're gonna have to do
better than that okay
yellow one now don't wanna know
trust me I do I've seen enough Jobs go
wrong I want to be clear what I'm
getting into
so you're in the game
yeah
but it was a thing cops are waiting for
us supposed to be an easy job go risk
20K each uh she's one of us and not a
very good one hey I gotta do three
roadblocks we had half a San Andreas law
enforcement on our ass we'd have been
home free if that son of a [\h__\h] hadn't
pulled the blade on me at 100 miles per
hour like her voice after trust me I put
you down the voice sounds good chance
sounds like you need to find a better
crew
considering I got two in custody and the
other one dead on the side of Sonora
freeway I need any crew period why you
know someone we are the crew
names no addresses I left all the money
way too hot to wash I'll get myself
patched up Lilo in the safe house for a
day or two then see what I can put
together man that's a lot of blood I can
get her as a driver
oh yeah I thought so since she talks
about you know doing this kind of stuff
herself
it was like she would be available
later for us
not that we really specifically need any
more people but okay
maybe she's a good driver
oh lucky yeah I met her I'm gonna get
you there as fast as I can
we're literally basically there
what's your name girl what was your name
tell me you're kind of cute I want to
know
will protect you
okay okay made it in time yay this is it
listen I ain't sure what you're into but
you need a driver anytime you let me
know
we got her as an option
yay taliana Martinez okay and now we
follow the purple
purple road because we gotta get back
into the city we
fantastic here nah
OH police is busy
what you doing
we're so fine
airport
uh I don't know where's the airport
um
where the [\h__\h] are we oh yeah
toy but whatever let me let me look do I
have a tangent let me check my tangent
list
I'm trying to look at my tangent
and nothing good
nothing really good
[Music]
I have some really random like
thoughts in there but they're so small
okay okay you want to hear some really
random thoughts that I remember
when I was younger
yeah like small really small small
Chihuahua
you know I like I like the being some
some forearms like of a of a music band
that I was following and other forums I
don't know a rope role play when I say
role play I don't mean anything weird
okay I mean like you know role playing
some kind of vampire school or something
like that
vampire school students or or like a elf
Warrior whatever [\h__\h] like that really
cringe but um
but anyway in some of these forums
they were like what was really popular
was at some point
with these these hundred questions about
me everybody would post their answers
to those hundred questions feeling like
super super good about themselves
thinking they're more interesting than
others and oh yeah totally people want
to read all these 100 answers about
myself did you guys ever fill out
something like that
it's not a personality test or anything
like that it's just ton of questions
what's your favorite this and that one
no
I I filled out those questioners several
times back then I think
everybody did it hahaha
it's kind of
weird but maybe you know if I would fill
it out now I would actually have a lot
of people interested in the actual
answers yeah back then I don't think
anyone can give a [\h__\h]
but now you guys would like the answers
wouldn't chat
I think didn't the first generation
um
do we like a stream before I think that
before their concert you know the first
gen concert I think they did something
where they
um you know they filled out like 100
questions and then went over it forever
remember right right right
I don't know what kind of questions they
were but it was probably similar like
kind of casual
all-around questions
I remember them doing something like
that oh there's another thing there but
I don't care
oh
Maybe
I can do something like that for you
guys one day answer your 100 questions
but that's basically just like a
marshmallow
basically we could just do a marshmallow
Ed
shut the [\h__\h] up
thank you
all the way here before me I mean I
wasted some time with taxis but still
what's up homie what's up
[\h__\h] idiot is that how you act I
wanna when a friend makes a mistake yeah
no really oh no oh so what it's just me
getting hurt I think it's a dress huh
gonna put you in the [\h__\h] ground you
laugh at me again what I'm gonna calm
down are we done with that kind of [\h__\h]
a lot of [\h__\h] in my life but you you
want to become Michael do you Trevor you
think you're so much better than him
[\h__\h]
look how about this man
calm down chill it was funny
I made a mistake
unfortunately man you fail
it was fun all right I apologize
I accept
your apology
okay
all right so
let's hug it out
oh my God
right yes
I swear
he's out of control
[\h__\h] I had a difficult
childhood and you're having a difficult
adulthood
as far as I can tell
I love you right but I would have
I would have [\h__\h] look man Lester
said you had some information for us
about Michael Michael [\h__\h] Michael I
hope he's dead man I know y'all too man
come on man you too happy before what
the [\h__\h] happened in North Yankton
somebody pinched him man who
friend Ron met these Chinese [\h__\h]
they're from yangshan and China
we had some problems
they mistakenly thought Michael was a
human being and kidnapped them and now
it looks like they holding him somewhere
in the city yes
come on interesting go [\h__\h] yourself you
want that piece of [\h__\h] that's your
[\h__\h] business all right he's dead to
me all right
I see him he's gonna be dead to everyone
else as well he still mean something to
you pushing your luck pal
don't you still love him
what was that what was that uh nothing
[Music]
baby
what anger issues
maximum angry shoes hey it's me what did
Trevor say me and Michael's being healed
by a Chinese crew because of Trevor the
irony isn't lost I'm sending you an app
for your phone but Michael cell just
came back online this will track its
signal it'll work better the closer you
get be careful sure uh-huh trackify hey
can we help uh
what I told you he ate my Jeweler don't
try to persuade me you're not lovers
he's laughing at you you [\h__\h] idiot
you're making a mistake oh it costs a
lot of money to track you down
every favor I put in the Midwest and
then you'll kill several good men good
day huh
already
I guess we can't do anything right now
find this location it is time
launch trunk from the bottom right of
the phone up menu
where is it
I don't know
turn that [\h__\h] up
here
okay
bag of these kind of things okay I'm a
boomer
wait how does this work it gets stronger
The Closer I Get I get that oh am I
further away now
at least okay see now I'm like if I go
straight I would reach it right
now let's go this way
[Music]
I'm just following it okay okay
um
[\h__\h]
I'm gonna do it a second time
okay okay
going this way nice Bridge
beautiful bridge this way maybe balance
it out of it I know it's very much uh
wrong side but let's go
I was gonna say let's go left but
there's something in the way
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm I'm fixing it I'm
fine
Michael Michael Michael
[Music]
I can't have you suffer like that
when you suffer I suffer
save my microphone
oh really
lucky in here
what do you mean in the here no way
how are you getting like this like these
perhaps
am I
am I am I right here
oh I think I'm like pretty much there
what what do you want from me
I passed it was there like a DOT
oh oh it's like
let's look here
maybe maybe I can enter from here the
ladder the ladder is mighty suspicious
huh
or maybe not you guys say you wanna say
um
yes good idea okay
no yes
whatever we'll figure it out
now I'm going further away from it oh
but I hear him
I hear a living room
oh
hey you
what you want me you're in the wrong
place are you holding my friend a kiss
as well
[Music]
wait happened
wait wait one second I don't know how to
get out my weapon anymore
uh I forgot I forgot I'm like really
stupid sorry there you go why didn't
work before
should I have not been caught Maybe
[Music]
would have been a better idea
thank you
okay okay yeah I'm using PC to shoot
okay looking looking clean
rescue my girl
I would love nothing more than that
Michael Michael Michael Michael
you in here man
my uh health is a little bit dangerous
already a house
oh [\h__\h] oh yeah okay
oh there's a there's a healing pack here
okay okay we're full health now
in case we figured out I ain't paying no
risk
shut up
[Music]
yeah we'll match up
oh
yeah got his shoulder but we're just
gonna get back up there we go there we
go
mommy what is that what is that is that
can't face frying oil
you guys ready to jump in here huh a
cozy bath I prepared it for you
wait this is a slaughterhouse indeed
isn't it before
what is it for
oh oh it's cows are sick
time to release this dude
I gonna get missed
[Music]
all right
ah [\h__\h]
oh we're standing somewhere else here
okay let's be more careful I I have a
better idea of everything now
shut up
yo
woman
all right baby
I died once but don't worry this one is
the the right
hey Michael
he's not answering what does it mean
Michael you idiot man
Michael answer me I go
[\h__\h] hey what it got you man
where you at bro
huh who's that him all right no way
huh Michael dog where you at
Trevor don't give a [\h__\h] about this
mother okay I don't really need the
medkit right now I'm full health so
whatever
you got the wrong guy here
holy [\h__\h]
I didn't realize that that happened the
last time too
oh good shot wow that was a random shot
honestly
[Music]
dude
okay okay going much better than some
mhm
how's it going in there huh
they're ready to be sold in a Happy Meal
sick
by the way my mom has been watching my
GTA streams really likes stuff
this is the perfect game for me and I'm
doing so well
foreign
so funny
she likes the the pew pew games
[Music]
well that was mean that was a really
mean shot he died
I was going so loud
[Music]
which character which character my mommy
likes oh I'm not sure
honestly
she might even like Trevor
[Music]
hello I know there's still somewhere
someone there
well oh I thought someone was behind the
car never mind
oh
where's that person
okay
you got it all white dude that don't
belong to you
hey Michael
remember Rayland is doing it
automatically you know
is it r
hahaha
oh
but it does it automatically too right
time to release this dude where you at
bro
I think we're good okay I'm gonna take
it even though I don't know
Trevor don't give a [\h__\h] about this
[\h__\h]
in case you ain't pick it up I ain't
paying no risk
oh
kill it
more more miles come at me bro oh yeah
I shot his knee and he still died from
that I didn't know you had your heart in
your knees
she alive
does that tickle does that tickle your
feet please huh
[\h__\h]
okay okay
you
better take cover it's coming
why can't they take so many shots and me
on the other hand man
[Music]
foreign
experiences with grenades you know
it sounds like fun but
I'm scared
I always [\h__\h] up this far you know
sick
she ain't gonna get missed okay okay The
Dangerous Ones are gone I think two
seconds
what two seconds
[Music]
[Applause]
good step good step I think this area is
clear
yeah it's safe it's safe
feel disgusting
well oh there he is there is you want me
to waste your boyfriend what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] this guy
oh man I was
like
a really bad spot I was like [\h__\h]
oh I need a weapon Frank uh here uh e
there you go
take the Pistons
[\h__\h]
[Music]
what else am I gonna do
what does he be like super dizzy at this
point like how long has he been hanging
on there look at the corridor then we'll
get out of here
wasn't all the all the blood in his head
be rushing to him and like he must be
like unconscious by now what are we
doing
could I help you no can I do I move on
I think I'm moving on
what's your mate oh my God is this
hollow meat
[Music]
someone there
hold on me that Anya was talking about
map pack oh I want to take it
foreign
hard to take cover
everything's just meat
okay I think I can go
oh oh oh no
you got him got him
was not a headshot I'm sorry
about [\h__\h] time
let's go
yes
I'm coming maybe a different weapon will
be better
I've got no problem with uh
with a pistol although there's only 19
out of 11. hmm
19 11 out of 19 or so I don't know come
on Mike hi
to see happinessian beautiful sorry boys
this is my ride
you should be pissed with you
[\h__\h] get him now how many times there we
go
okay I am I'm switching no oopsie
switching
Philly
[Music]
ah this is a bad deal here
yeah yeah
let's go Michael
don't fall into the
into the thingy what do you even call
that
oh no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
what was he trying to do is that his
meat Shield That's it man let's go
okay
smite
a grinder ah come on
it's okay keep going I just want to get
home
bye bye
Franklin rescued his adopted new dad
turn around
wait why does it turn
s
oh oh nice we crashed them we got them
to crash
because of my sick moves
oh I have a oh oh nice one that makes a
lot of sense
how the [\h__\h] did I make that time
[Music]
[\h__\h] idiot
ammo
you see what we did to your boys in the
slaughterhouse no car aim no no Mike
lame
[Music]
I'm wrong
uh whatever we're staying on this road
what do you want oh because okay the
thriving hmm
maybe I would do a better job at
shooting
but isn't it just about
getting to the yellow Point anyway
how you like me with a gun in my hand
since it's like God oh God
oh the [\h__\h] sake
oh I can only be in Franklin right now
okay
foreign
[Music]
how do you even know I got snatched
we're up there and Trevor freaks the uh
sorry about that
was too fast they couldn't handle it
sure you don't want to come in
we depressed enough already all right
well listen listen look man before I
mean you have a sick house too what the
[\h__\h] happened Even sickered in our house
like crazy tried to kill me I got jumped
by the Chinese man before all that I'm
talking about the feds trapped this guy
Brad man I know you don't know anything
about bread
all right get the bullet hole in his
head I made a judgment call
I don't know if it's the right one I did
what I thought I had to do
I had a young family Franklin
threw a crazy [\h__\h] without a
gunshot right on the floor
a future for me for my family I took it
you took it man you burned every
[\h__\h] you've ever known it was
that or die
look I know it sounds cold I don't
expect you to understand it not yet but
you will
when you've got ties of your own
one day someone jumped in the pool legs
they just give
just can't run anymore
um
all right man look you watch your back
all right
when Trevor finds out you're still alive
I don't know what the [\h__\h] he gonna do
don't worry about Trevor he's not gonna
get near me
hey
you watch your back you hear me dog it
ain't me he coming forward
we straight it's you dog it's you
oh man
now everybody wants to
[\h__\h] with Marco
poor Michael
[Music]
he's got nothing left
you know nothing's going right oh man
oh man Michael
oh with everything just
[\h__\h] sucks nothing goes well fresh
meat haha ironic so funny
Michael had a tough yeah that was a good
Mission though yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
wash the blood off your face who got
sick stinky
so stinky
it will be like that sometimes right
oh man
no no that's not what I wanted
sorry
[Music]
um
cannot look outside
there we go that's what I wanted
um
one more how about the s
ick one more and then I think I'll
going super chats it's already been four
hours
no car
ah no car no what the [\h__\h] told him to
go meet at the Garment Factory get over
there as soon as you can and I'm going
to
audit
I'm going to s
I don't know oh yeah super chats are off
but I think I have super chats from
previous streams to read
so I'll be I'll stop please stop thank
you I'll be reading Jones
come on bro
oh is he gonna report me
is he gonna report me he better not
okay I have to turn around oh shh
yeah yeah but then I'm hoping to not go
on for too long because I wanna
um cook something
yeah I was lazy last night and ate
lasagna frozen lasagna but tonight I
have to cook
yeah the other day
you know with the with the garlic onion
the pasta that I made was so yummy it
was really pretty simple I think I'll be
repeating that a couple times
um really easy
but uh today I think I'm
um I'm not sure what I'm making today I
have two more recipes
I forgot what one of them was
[Music]
wow what a car
and these rich people
got some sick cars yo oh I see I see I
see
some fat
Jazz look delicious it was simple but it
was I think almost the yummiest thing
I've had from hellofresh even though it
was so simple
Johnny man you're a couple real fat
asses put a beat down on an old man
nothing what where are you going nothing
more
happy to do than that eliminate Rock
eliminate
it's an aggressive way of saying it oh
the music right now is not even the
radio it's just
funky music
no dmca this time wonderful
eliminate
see I saved that biker
from a really Grim destiny
what
excuse me sorry I have to look at that
ain't got no time
I got no time
can I shoot
tried to play nice
is this what they mean with eliminating
[Applause]
I should have whacked you when I had the
chance
I told you to stay away
am I getting some stats for that
um no
I'm only a paraplegic but you can't feel
anything ah yeah you're throwing me
softballs The Rum Runner but speaking of
accidents
add one oh if only we'd met 20 years ago
Michael maybe I wouldn't be in this mess
yeah you and me both brother look it's a
pain I know but could you come by the
studio now I guess someone would like to
show you so close by
oh yeah yeah of course I'll be right
over
[Music]
all right people no no no it's fine it's
fine so far I've had no issues with
Melinda GTA boss I think
they're not monetized all good
oh you guys know that song I don't know
that song
I feel like normally I know a lot of the
mainstream songs oh what the [\h__\h]
not today I guess all the music is super
DMV really
it's my favorite car still here honestly
this Sunday changed kind of like what
they have here it was different before
but it's not the car I arrived with
originally
that one's still there but I don't care
about that one
[\h__\h] what if like smoking lettuce
damn it tried it
coming
thank you thank you ah maybe Return of
the mission is done business after all
oh my friend you're a Sentimental Thug
with zero artistic training and nothing
interesting to say I would say you're
overqualified anyway shut up and take a
look at yes I like being an anime model
very much thank you oh
every morning I wake up like this and
I'm like [\h__\h] I'm beautiful
actually done something yeah a movie
welcome to show business oh how [\h__\h] is
this movie let's see I want to see
show it to us all right Michael come on
let me show you some rushes I think
you've done it
move it hey baby
yeah
I think sorry this is really important
everybody
no matter how old you are this shows you
at least you can still make your dreams
come true wow Michael so inspiring isn't
he
take Michael as the perfect example all
right
get him more maybe you'll have to Rob
some banks but no he didn't have to Rob
any banks for this to happen
right
oh that was easy that was so Speedy I
thought this would be a longer thing
oh
all right unless we can squeeze in one
one more thing maybe maybe maybe maybe
the L
going for the L
a little small one no this is just a
small one small small
you
all right all right last mission for
today kill cycle
you got lucky buddy
muscle car in the back so the muscle car
the front is Big the back is small
nothing nothing that's a muscle car yeah
and it's wide right that was another
feature the front is really wide too
yeah
this one muscle car no this one not
right
back is longer
[Music]
you wow I'm smart I can Flex my
knowledge now
[Laughter]
so guys yeah last time I was looking for
them so long
muscle car that's another muscle car
trained eye
[Music]
[Applause]
now we gotta find a bucket while bucket
are you hinting on
[\h__\h] is the matter of you
are you hinting at my my affair with a
bucket
it's a muscle stream
I can take my car back and pull whoa I
mean I don't care what What car what car
I don't care about
what you mean you mean the the white one
the fancy one
ah
it's fun
it's fun I'm okay
it's not like I cry every night thinking
about that car
no no
I can also buy cars who the [\h__\h] buys
cars in GTA
if you can steal every [\h__\h] car that
you want huh I mean okay unless you
really want for some reason a really
specific one
don't understand but okay you do you if
you want to buy a car I guess whatever
run run run run
all right what are we doing here
do you I know I know do you yeah what do
you what did I say something do you
what's going on just just enjoying a
little labor dispute
dude we're about to do something really
really bad so I need to present myself
as a proper textile magnet so oh so you
stop making anything
nothing looks more suspicious in America
than someone who's actually prepared to
make something
what about you uh
pocket Trevor so true that's the
problems
Brad
whatever I know I know I picked one
million things
especially now that he knows thank God
you guys are here you alone Davey
where's your boyfriend Steve he's on his
way up yeah they're up here
the shit's about to hit the fan our
entire lives together has been nothing
but a series of fans and shits sort this
problem out for me and I will get Mr
Leisure wear off your back and if we
don't then I will go to jail and you
will get shot ah [\h__\h] you Dave I've
heard it all before not like this you
haven't has he briefed you oh well yes
he has he told us that if we do what you
say then together we can take down the
big bad wolf that is government
corruption yeah and if you don't
we're all gonna fry because the agency
is on to us I've even got some fools in
our own Bureau that are questioning my
methods the guy
a liar
um fits very well with Microsoft
according to Travis opinion and I need
you guys to find out what they know all
right so what well Lester here to hack
into the system wipe it all clean oh no
no that will not work the only way to
access it is through your buildings [\h__\h]
me
Michael think of guns very big favor
if you do this I will make sure that all
your files
promise you hey
that's the last thing we do and we're
done period
worse I'm a man of my word Dave let's go
you're really gonna be done
finger got dangerous molester let's go
good luck gentlemen
XXX
parking garage entrance
okay
um
I I said before you got any idea how
we'll do this maybe at one million
um uh dance dance version but I don't
think I can do it because the footage is
a bit
difficult to use for a full dance
version but I think the choreographer
Kiana is gonna upload a full dance
version so at least there you can see
the full dance if you wanna I mean it's
not me but yeah at least for people who
wanted it as a reference hmm
uh you'll eventually see me you know
performing it
at some point somewhere and then you can
take that as a full dance version
yeah I'm gonna scope it out again
start by finding a way into the building
no no no we're waiting for someone to
come out of it a janitor all right and
then How's that gonna get us in if I
ever get the chance to record my own
version at some point and have it fully
fully uh when usable for uh a full dance
version then I'll do it okay but for now
please uh you know watch watch my
choreographer and says the janitors
they asked for a day off so we find one
of these guys we turn him and that's our
end okay you're a particular guy I'm in
the temp company's database right now I
found a guy about to clock off thank you
for your understanding let me see sorry
Harvey Molina license plate eight three
qsl722 and we'll follow him see what we
think sounds was good
maybe I can upload
I don't know a dance version of Sparks
instead of so because I think I think we
have a
good good data of that one we need to be
facing the parking garage
or maybe next time I I'm in Japan you
know when if they have space for me in
the studio what what's the parking car
are in there but the spot is here what
do you want from me
I was saying if I go to Japan turn
around and face the garage entrance okay
okay hi okay wait wait I get it now
then maybe I can record something next
time
some small dance video
[\h__\h] hell
may not be able to do a full stream in
3D but maybe they can let me record a
small dance you should be coming out
here soon
ah
Channel
[Music]
oh is that here we go
another guy oh so what do you think
about this whole messed up situation I
think they'll either kill you after this
is done or keep you doing these stupid
jobs until they don't have to kill you
because someone else has done it for him
yeah that sounds about right
foreign
something's coming
I see it I said that's not it come on
what do we do now what can we do we do
the job and maybe you can delete the
files when you're inside doing whatever
else you're doing that might be a way
out yeah yeah the way out is exactly
what I need already played it was really
good
uh but yeah yeah yeah I hope I can do
another freedom
that's the opposite of a muscle car
isn't it no because it's hard to get
motivated on a job without Financial
incentive you can't put a price on
freedom well that spur won't be there
for the crew I'm gonna ask Mr Haynes for
a budget maybe the leftover cash from
the Polito score and we need something
yeah see what you can do
oh yeah yeah Callie killed me in that
one
[Applause]
remember it's been such a long time
that's the one oh
okay let's go stay behind him but don't
let him see you how
[Music]
so what's gonna happen when this guy
gets wherever he's going he's gonna get
his severance package huh I can't tell
if that's some creepy euphemism or a
plain statement of facts it's whatever
you want it to be okay
creative freedom
okay no not so close okay okay
you mind put away the smartphone or pad
or whatever the hell that is for a
minute no surfing while I'm trying to
tail this guy it's work related yeah
well I'd prefer all hands on deck right
now if it's okay with you god you're
worse than my son I'm gonna break into
the fib's West Coast headquarters you're
gonna need more than a janitor's license
plate number and let me work on some
angles while you uh keep this car behind
that one in between these white lines
that's it I mean other than a few
missing expletives in terms of racial
abuse that was my son in spades
oh too close too close for comfort
what was that saying oh yeah somebody
were you know you missed the co-op games
you've got the budget
if only there were more good co-op games
like that I feel like we played through
all the good ones
need more need more of those split
screen what do we do when it gets home
we need cooperation and maybe his
overall okay I'm an ID and if we don't
cooperate you know what it's like to
clean up [\h__\h] for Steve Haynes he'll
cooperate
is that so
a teaser for a new one when could that
possibly
come out
five years one year
he's pulling up park down the block
down the block okay all right
point
[Music]
can I get out
go in and have a word okay Harvey Molina
um I'm busy the only one she needs
something
Resident Evil
I don't know I've never played anything
before 9 series and it was kind of
spooky and scary
um
[Music]
so
they walk in with him is it okay to say
hi now or
oh follow him into well I can close the
door
knock knock
easy you need to lock your doors best
interested when you live in a city like
this with money and all you got to do is
take a little vacation someone's crying
good job man take any break I can get it
yeah hey you want the beer I'll just
take the overalls oh and your ID it's in
there oh and Harvey
I probably don't need to say this
but you don't play ball I'll be forced
to do something I really don't want to
do enjoy your beer
that was easy really friendly what the
[\h__\h]
okay
well we're gonna have more of an
argument
guess not
it's another
typical normal day
janitor just wants to be a jazzer oh
yeah
taking his own business
the factory
ah
that was easy yes you were right Steve
Haynes is a shitty boss hey I called
Frank while you were in there he's
coming to meet us yeah frankly who we
need him for grunt work information
gathering what information the plans to
the office there aren't any digital
copies or if there are I'm not clever
enough to find them the architect is LS
based so I thought Frank could tell him
take a hard copy sounds complicated you
sure you need these plans yeah I do if
I'm gonna find a way to bypass a couple
of hundred million dollars worth of
government security millions they blew
that much government contracts license
to steal wow we are in the wrong
business wait no we've just taken the
wrong contracts
are we done talking good perfect timing
ah he's already here
okay
this is a different Frank
is it actually not Franklin
I'm confused
someone here
hi it's my Franklin of God what's the
problem dog Steve no Trevor's that's my
favorite it's always Steve hey that is
not strictly true let's see the Steve
Haynes
his family it's always one of them yeah
that's true it is always one of them
well battle [\h__\h] with a horrible family
even worse the big one I told you
Franklin I ain't a good role model here
whatever dawg it's either this or Dylan
dime bags the bullets come cracking at
your ass either way
we need to find out something about this
FIB building weakness or a way in next
time I meet a morally destitute totally
delusional highly corrupt government
agent I hope he's a nice one man I'm not
going in that [\h__\h] by myself no
no no nobody is going in we need to do
some Recon we need a little more
information she I need the architectural
plans
anyway so I'm going to need paper copies
the architect's name is Chip Peterson
this was his first big commission and
the office is down in Backlot City all
right
all right dog I got you yeah
try not to hurt you cute butt good good
good
looks like
although Mario from the movie has even
less but to be honest
cleaning out the beer Room Mission pass
all right we'll get deeper into that
heist mission next time
and we're gonna end it here I'm gonna
read some super chattels from previous
streams
very clear
and I'll be back in
two seconds I'm so hungry though I don't
think I can take it very long the Super
Chat rating oh I hope I don't have too
much
really [\h__\h] hungry
I could I could quickly make myself a
snack though AKA
um
a crap with Nutella and strawberries
which I can make in
I can make and eat within six minutes I
think
I could do that
then I wouldn't have to suffer so much
I've been speeding those crabs recently
because the crabs are already finished
should I do it what about us I don't
have so many for all of you
Nutella called Zone
you mean like a sweet Pizza
I had something like that before yeah do
it okay then we're going to the Super
Chat intermission I'll try to be back as
soon as possible maybe I'll even bring
my crap here okay
I'll see you guys in a little bit please
be patient and wait thank you for
watching today
finishing GTA next week
um and yeah tomorrow unarchived English
maybe maybe also Korean uh
so please be there or be square okay
[Music]
still alive
break I will never again
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
show me
foreign
[Music]
still alive
foreign
[Music]
yeah
yeah oh yeah louder
[Music]
I had a little
um
a little
how to
say
um
a little moment with chonkers behind the
scenes oh
I did something
that I apologized to her for and she was
it was so sweet because she was like
it's okay it's okay I feel like she was
literally with her meows and her pools
and her and and her um rubbing herself
on against my leg she was like saying
it's okay like I really think
I really think she was saying it's okay
yeah yeah let's just say I stepped on
her tail anyway I did not eat my crap
because I had to say sorry to drunkers
let me let me say goodbye it's
um with strawberries and Nutella um
oh yeah baby
um
[Music]
accidents happen but she loves me okay
she loves me a little bit too much my my
sweet baby
my sweet cherry pie
I love her
oh
how's the gun taste
yummy this is my favorite breakfast
um
is that double
[Music]
um
okay I'm so sorry
I love you I love you you know that
right you know that
[Music]
he's such a baby she's such a baby
um now recently I found
um
pre-made uh pancakes
at the supermarket
um which was like an eye opener for me I
realized oh my God I don't have to I
don't have to make my own pancakes in
the morning which if I if it wasn't such
a [\h__\h] annoying thing to do then I
would do it every morning
[Laughter]
um so I tried out those pre-made
pancakes and they're pretty good when I
say pancakes I mean like you know it's
like a crap but it's a thicker
thicker than a normal French crab that's
our Palace
no it's not frozen it's not a mix it's
like uh you have to keep it in your
fridge it doesn't hold for too long
but it's a package of pre-made pancakes
and they're actually pretty decent so
um
[Music]
mm-hmm
um
yeah well I know how to make pancakes
I know how to make crepes but if I have
the choice
in the morning
to take 20 minutes to make my own
or just take these ones now honestly now
I chose these ones
what what
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
I think
I think she's kindly requesting some
belly wraps
okay last bite
oh
[Music]
mm-hmm
yeah cooking in the morning too much
effort
oh okay that helped me so much I'll
listen to me
pancakes
[Laughter]
okay let me bring the plate back to the
kitchen and try to catch chunkers again
she wants my attention and she deserves
it okay
she deserves it let's go chunky monkeys
[Music]
oh oh my God I'm sorry I'm sorry
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
no
but
um
well in an attempt to catch chunkers who
was speeding at me
charging at me
um
smoothie was charging at me too
and then smoothie got a little bit
bonked by the wall but
yeah she's okay
[Music]
you smell a little bit funny chunky
wonky
yeah but it's okay you smell fine it's
okay I don't mean that in a bad way
why are they so cute right as I
questioned that every day I I wonder
oh sure okay
enough cuddles
for now
have they been using ah I
I didn't know I couldn't I couldn't use
it yet because I
um I don't know I was like hold on
waiting for something
waiting for the right moment when I have
a moment to properly observe them
while they are
trying it out but I feel like even if I
put it up they're not gonna use it
immediately right but they're gonna like
sniff sniff sniff
procrastinating no it will definitely
get used maybe maybe you know what
tomorrow I think tomorrow I have some
time
uh well I'm like mostly done with like
hello talk I I did everything a bit
earlier than usual this time
[Music]
um
yeah so not so much to do in terms of
hollow talk
um
oh by the way please don't please don't
like expect that everything is gonna be
like super new and wow different though
the general format is staying the same
so what's new is the studio
a complete overhaul but it still has the
same atmosphere kind of
and what else is new
some some other thing is new but besides
that is
pretty much the same so yeah chill chill
baby take a seat and
oh she wants to be close to me she's
chilling in the room where I am in even
though I'm streaming and talking
yeah yeah yeah the facelift I guess yeah
yeah no please don't the thing is like
first
you guys know first the the break wasn't
really intentional I just had some
troubles getting uh the guests in
and then it took me so much time that
eventually I
I don't know I was like okay now it's
been such a long time that if I come
back I should come back with something
nice
yeah I got busy too yeah I got sick I
got busy I was traveling all that
so then then finally the studio was more
or less done and I was still having
troubles finding someone so still more
delays
now I finally have I am a senpai
who was not the one who fought uh she
was already on the whole talk it wasn't
there
um but yeah
I'm glad I'm glad I'm really happy I'm a
senpai accepted and just needed some
schedule
adjustments but we're doing it this
Sunday
finally finally
and then
yeah I'm gonna try a few more times to
get the coming girls in the right order
but if it's too much of a pain in the
butt then I'm just gonna move on which
is unfortunate but I I I can't you know
the whole talk will go on breaks
indefinitely if if I have so many
problems
getting the right people
[Music]
um
yeah did great job yeah I caught myself
a Pokemon called well Joel
oh
[Music]
unfortunately she won't be using the
stage
um you know for performance
but I want to show it up anyway because
the stage of course also
got a
and renovation
everything everything got renovated and
I want to show you guys
I don't know I'm excited to show you but
maybe maybe I can keep the stage for the
next guest if the next guest uses the
stage and then we still have something
fresh
steam client update what the [\h__\h]
well you're lucky I'm not
I'm not uh
playing anymore anyway close that [\h__\h]
go away go away go away
will be great to have her for the whole
talk return show yeah
and um whole talk anniversary is in
November I think right
I actually have
some special things planned for the
anniversary
really special so
um I can't wait
next month yeah uh I'm not sure what
date it was I wasn't it like at the end
of November
on November 20th okay okay yeah that's
kind of late November
um
yeah
indeed
it's really really special
so
look forward to it
we'll be here before we know it yeah
honestly time passes so fast the weeks
are it's crazy
it's crazy I wish I could make it go
slower
hear that
she's so Selena she says your baby I'm
gonna give her so many cuddles after the
stream oh my God I have so many mentions
oh now I know why
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
[Music]
I got you I got you she was about to run
away again but I got you oh you you
oh
my cutie patooty
why do we have to start reading super
chats you guys know what's the oldest
one
I just saw jenma was dming me
about that popping sound that we were
hearing sounds electrical check your PC
chord see if there's a burning smell
she was worried about it
oh but really it was just an audio
glitch apparently in the game that was
so weird
and then it got more and more and more
I'm really worried me
that was that was really weird right
thank God it was
nothing
nothing weird actually in real life
um
did you guys tell me
well do you guys know where I need to
read ah I think I have I do have Super
Shots from rust right that I private
that so they're not on the whole elizer
I assume so I'm gonna check that in
YouTube Studio
finale okay I'll go okay
cartoon
oh
hmm
[Music]
oh okay sorry okay yeah
you know what
uh holy myth original song also reached
1 million yeah kind of on the same day
more or less
oh nice nice so that one was speeding
he's the [\h__\h] speeding ticket
damn
so many milestones
happy okay let me go
and get the cartoon Super chats
no
cartoon
[Music]
I think
hmm
I don't know I'm still unsure
sure about rest
if I wanted
back
or not I don't know
archive for real time and URL and put
the Streamline
oh Marty there
oh so that works for all on archived
streams
[Music]
yeah
um I don't know man
unlisted
um
[Music]
the thing is analyzed rust is like if I
don't
bring it back and it just kind of has no
ending you know what I mean
no ending it's such an open ending for
everyone who watches who gets into
kiwawa later on and watches the VOD
later on and go through the rest spots
the last spot that they will have seen
is the one where they see the tower in
in hopes of
seeing me use the tower at one point but
not that I really made use of it in the
last episode much but you know it just
doesn't really have quite the ending
[Music]
I'll think about it a bit more
I don't know
I feel I feel kind of
self-conscious about
um
yeah getting emotional meow
[Music]
um
and you know I I know that
when we public people or me specifically
show emotions
too many emotions or any any kind of sad
emotions
publicly then it gives people a reason
to [\h__\h] on you which is so weird and it
shouldn't be like that but
people basically will [\h__\h] on you for
being sad
[Music]
like that's a bad thing
yeah
that's how it is
so that's why
it's really hard really hard when you
try to hold it back but then oh oh we
just can't
hmm
so as if as if we weren't human yeah I
mean I'm a phoenix Bunny and we're we're
something like humans so I I can't
expect us to be
perfectly happy all the time can you
what
that's that's just something in the back
of my mind that kind of
um always
it's like always a voice
telling me
always need to be happy publicly
you know you know
it's always there
anyway
died your boo so let's read some super
chattels
wanna get the thumbnail
hmm
I got an interesting VM right now
[Music]
I don't know
that's so Random
anyway I'll answer that later
how was GTA today
how was it guys I think I did a good job
everything went smoothly mostly
chunkers I'm not talking about this
movie don't be jealous I just said it
went smoothly should I say it went
chonkers
sorry
don't be jealous it's moving I wasn't
talking about her
talking to me
she's so cute oh sh cute this is cute
isn't she oh I did a thing with the
thumbnails
[Laughter]
man
I was making the thumbnail for the first
one and I was like come on you know what
this will probably be two parts so
actually perfect time to use
uh this new fan art
since there's two versions
[Music]
yeah I can be your angler or your devil
okay
you got something to say to my chickens
yeah I got some good to you fan art so
many people tried throwing me in black
chihuahua and white chihuahua
looking really stylish
[Music]
when's the poll oh you remember that
I wanted to make a Polly yeah yeah
maybe now
[Laughter]
I can make the fall now
community
[Music]
I've never done a
one of these before
should I should I use the ah should I
use some
kiwamo fan night
oh should I use the cool Ari one from
the cartoon thumbnail
should I use a different one I got
different ones too
I'm gonna use the cool everyone they're
really spicy
of course I'm gonna credit
so
here this one
it's it's a fair game because they're
the same pose basically
so it's really just a club so that their
friend
do you like
um
black or white or
no this Wawa
and
go
[\h__\h] I forgot the credit
[Applause]
cancel cancel abort mission
could have could have just ended I
wonder if I could have just added it
yeah and then did you see it did you
guys get a notification
all right bye
one
think
it is a YouTube account [\h__\h] let me just
go
link to Twitter
yay
okay very important I'm doing a
University study here okay I'm doing a
paper on it
do you swalla
oh please swallow
okay
on community post
okay it's up now have fun
I wonder I wonder which one which one do
I like more generally I feel like I like
the the white one more but that's
probably just because it worked
um just so well with the backgrounds and
the all the the light effects and all
that
I think both look really cool
in this case I have to say
oh black chihuahua is winning right now
what the [\h__\h]
I vote on my own Pole
okay you wanna vote which one do you
like more huh
he's just rolling around on the ground
being like
[Music]
where is it it's in the community thingy
on YouTube
update
oh black Chihuahuas winning
Orange it's not a choice right now
[Music]
no you want it that's why you're rolling
around on the ground but the moment I
try to get closer to her she rents and
then I go back and she comes back and
then I go her to her and she runs away
and I go back and she comes back you
know it's always like that
telling you to let you see easily the
full images oh
oh yes generally not really made for
that looking at pictures on YouTube
um
she wants she wants to run and she wants
belly rubs both
black chihuahua had the best scenes of
the music I I think it's still the
opposite
but I mean they're both great
so can't really fight about that anyway
let me start reading some super chats
Cruz dancing
[Music]
thanks for the pinky first time charm no
work sadly but fourth time will
that mean I promise him ah no way I
don't know what it means I promise I
will immediately buy the gummy chicken
and book hotel as soon as available
why I want to finally thank you in
person and get a specially signed card
also you pioneered something that many
other holos will use
I'm not gonna be a document ah it's
about meaning green ah yeah I can tell
you at this point no no no no no no
don't call me
so no need to plan for it
I don't know why you're
why you're talking about it as if it's a
certain thing
NOCO me 2023
um
I told you guys so many times don't
don't you know just assume it and then
buy it I try to Hint it at you guys
without being too obvious
you just don't listen
[Music]
I mean some of you guys seem to want to
go to docomo anyway because it was fun
and I agree I mean yeah
it's a good spot to meet up with with
um friends yeah I do agree time to bring
you to other Yukon yeah it would be nice
but you know I I I'm not sure what a
good equivalent is
in Europe
um
yeah oh well how
important for the rest of the chat
meaning
[Music]
foreign
actually during the meet and greet they
were also
some moments where Chargers was going
crazy and meowing so much
that the meet and greet people could
hear it very clearly what
[Music]
yeah yeah I know she she's like being
really weird right now
ah
foreign
no we cannot
I was joking like you're having a meet
and greet with chunkers now yay oh hi
chunky
[Music]
looking straight at me with her big
round eyes
[Music]
on me like that
before this channel
[Music]
okay maybe she's actually still angry at
me
many of her meows are not even audible
to you guys she has a lot of smaller
meows too
yeah big puppy eyes but it's cat eyes
I have not paid my cuddled up fully I've
I agree I understand
hmm
baby bubble bubble
you fluffy little baby
should I catch you again
do you want to be caught
let me try don't run don't run
don't run
oh
yeah
okay
I got the kid again hello
hello jonkers is with me
you failed once again at escaping me
you need to get better
but I know you're doing it on purpose
[Music]
where were we tickets
again thank you oh
called out by employee number for
watching Bay streams I would like to
explain some time ago I mentioned that
I'm a big
whole Aussie fan does I do watch
hatchimals and bass streams however if
there happen to be stream schedule Clash
I would always prior to husky Wawa
I have decided to leave my employee
number entitled in my name to show that
you're my only Aussie even when I
comment in in Super Chat in other
streams they know that I only belong to
you
oh
wait is this about me seeing you in
someone else's stream
foreign
[Music]
are you here now
oh someone oh
someone else was like
ah now I remember
okay yeah that did happen someone was
like ratting you out hmm
[Music]
someone snitchy snitch chicken
well yeah I know
is she chicken
one more bubble machine
you want to go again okay bye bye
bye bye bye chunky monkey bye
I let her go
[Music]
Mata
foreign
exactly
she's on my beans thank you for the
recipe is one of the people who is lucky
enough to meet you and said oh oh yeah
right and I remember because I remember
I was like is there anything you know
any name that I know you buy like what's
your what's your YouTube name or
whatever
you said cheese on my beans and I was
like hmm
that is a funny name I want to express a
great what a great experience it was
even though I was incredibly nervous you
did a great job at making me feel at
ease you're very charismatic and easy to
talk to yeah thank you now doing a good
job a lot of a lot of the participants
were a little bit nervous or did not
prepare anything to talk about so I
asked my usual questions
yeah
yeah yeah because it's always really
interesting for me too
to find out like where you guys found me
and when you guys found me it was your
favorite streams of me and so on
it's really nice to like actually hear
it
directly straight from you guys
[Music]
one I remember one meet and greet was
like
not one person but two people someone
had their cousin
I think their cousin in the same room
and I I saw them both on the camera some
of them had their cameras on some not
some apparently thought they were on but
they had it off and then later on
regretted it
but anyway it was like two people I'm
like who the [\h__\h] is there
take it yeah it's my cousin I'm like
okay I guess
do they also watch your whole life and
they were like yeah
so I was like well you you're really
lucky you're really freaking lucky to
get a chance here and I will forgive you
yeah and then they only listened they
didn't really like say anything
um
two for one special
um should have brought the whole family
I guess
that would be so embarrassing for me to
for me though if you have your whole
family there listening to the meet and
greet huh hazukashi
[Music]
how long would it be in grades oh
five to seven minutes I think
um
oh yeah so Olivia's beats
what's dressed up as me and in the
beginning of the meet and Grant was
asking me and I was saying I am number
one
I'm a gosling but didn't have their the
the camera on at the moment so I was
like no what the [\h__\h] no what do you
mean no no [\h__\h] way shut up
and then
once once beats realized he didn't have
the camera on
turn it on and then I see kiwawa and I'm
like okay now that makes sense now you
can't even say your number one on the
Gosling because you're dressed up as me
yeah bamboozled
huh
anyway there were a lot of interesting
meet and greets and uh yeah people from
people from Europe people from America
people from Korea people from Japan yeah
from all over a lot of them I've never
heard of before but a couple of them a
couple of them only just a couple of
them I knew from Super chattels and so
on so that was nice too
yeah some UK people
with really nice
accents meow
really Pleasant to listen to
um
[Music]
and thank you cheese on my beans
thank you soon and yeah hope you enjoyed
the meet and green thank you so much
passion fruits
for the pinky I can't believe I'm
finally fried it always felt like
something very far away hmm and Out Of
Reach but it's finally been a year and
I'm a bucket now I know how you feel
yeah it did feel so
so far away it's been a great year and
I'm looking forward to many years of
membership until final batch one day
yeah hopefully
talk with people wholesome if you only
put your kind of way I'm too lazy no
anyway yeah right now the final badge
may seem very far for all of us but
hopefully we'll reach it
foreign
so you gotta stay until then and then
you can proudly wear it and say I was
here
since quite the beginning almost the
beginning
or the very beginning
Resurrection thank you logical paradox
oh 25 months
yeah I can imagine them adding five here
six to your badges at that point
I can totally see that happening
and I know
I've known this but I missed so much I
always miss you kiwawa
you missed so much
you missed me so much right because you
never miss anything you're always there
you think you forgot an important word
there you missed me so much yeah
understandable
my mommy here I'm always around
[Music]
oh I got you I got you
got you you got your water drops on your
Channel
hydrate are you a bit stinky were you
also on the toilet
wait you are stinky okay go away chunky
wonky
toys
stinky
stinkers
and maybe it might not be strongest but
just the smell coming from the toilet
I'm not sure I'm sorry
she's turning her back on me
oh I'm sorry
no she doesn't look at me anymore
oh
okay she's she's fine she's she laid
down towards me
a robot yeah yeah okay give me some time
maybe I can try it out tomorrow
Lucas and thank you oh happy belated
birthday oh
the older I get it's easier for me to
celebrate it with my family oh really
why
Sky Dancers
thank you for the red super chat hey
tencho it's my birthday and also two
years since I got introduced to whole
life just wanted to say thank you for
the years of entertainment and I look
forward to supporting my OC
let's go Lena thank you so much for
being here for such a long time
yeah always together
thank you so much for being here and
supporting me and not giving up on me
thank you soon be kissed to you
yeah yeah
yeah
thank you
a red Super Chat thank you
attention
okay
my nose itchy again always itchy it's
it's knees and see I have an itchy nose
foreign
from six hours ago
I have covered here I'm gonna watch this
later why do people love kiwawa why why
why people love Chihuahua
important question
yeah I think I've seen a video from this
person about me before I
why Kiana is a master Communicator from
one year ago
I think I remember that one
what why
why people love Kiwa people love kiwawa
why
love kiwama why
[Music]
so
so philosophical
okay I yeah
wow
I'm gonna check if that works with the
cat passing through
so sorry guys
getting your attention when he's asking
for my attention so specifically
ah here rust
so I take the URL and I change archive
too
archive two what was it real time
and then I put in the
end here
after the HMG underscore
probably oh do I have to make it
unlisted for that or
see maybe this works
well that does not work
let me try
like this oh that doesn't work is it
weird for it wait what was it real time
or real time
ah I found a way I have to get rid of
the HMG
okay
um
uh here we go
rice
[Music]
well indeed wow yeah I know
oh yeah I know I know I know I know
let's read these
she's so needy she's under the table hi
baby
[Music]
okay I got her again
what are you doing bubble bubble okay
for the rest of the chat this is for
being based this is because you're cute
thank you
[Music]
thank you so much you're pretty based
too you know that
you are
it ain't no secret
based on what yeah what evidence on what
evidence am I based on what what was but
based on what evidence am I based on
no no I don't know what you're talking
about yeah yeah yeah yeah
thank you for the pinky today is my
birthday I'm happy you changed your
stream time now I can watch on my
birthday yeah but I'm sorry it ended up
being a private stream and not really a
happy stream even I mean I guess I guess
you know it was okay it was like
nothing special though I'm sorry pong if
you don't mind can you say you little
[\h__\h] in ASMR style it's my birthday so
uh can I ask like this anyways have fun
today let's go shoot Show Who's The Boss
okay I will do this for you
listen listen
you can get it with cat purse perhaps
yeah
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
Punk
your [\h__\h]
[Music]
you got a little extra there I don't got
a little extra
oh
I was holding her up she didn't like it
she doesn't like to be held up like that
so she's complaining
oh
cows
yeah and some purse as well there's pong
here
and there you are you're here I hope you
like cats I hope you're not allergic
um
happy belated birthday congratulations
[Music]
chunk is doing my handsome are fun to
know that what's on purpose I held her
up on purpose
can't wait for my birthday oh I don't
know if chunkers will be in the Moon
I like cats when I'm allergic to them
that's like the saddest thing that can
possibly happen to any human being on
this world
hmm
I'm allergic to cats it doesn't stop me
though
good attitude good attitude like if I
was allergic I would take medicine if I
have to in order to touch katos
foreign
I would do anything
[Music]
I can't smoothly do that do what
hmm
the camera
thank you for the pink super chat comes
on Me Down
foreign
thank you
such a charmer
thank you soon thank you for the sweet
words
oh
sweet
rice over Italian Kitchen oh wait oh
this oh there's really not many Super
Tires we're gonna be done in an instant
rise of reduction eight thank you for
the pinky It's Time to Say Goodbye to
Russ but we'll always remember that time
you were almost late to your idol
meeting uh I mean the time when picker
and that's a kid
built a tower for you have fun today
in that case it was really an idol
meeting because I was just late to my
collaboration with some more other idols
[Music]
hope you can see some action from the
tower I really did not see any action I
killed one NPC
tried to shoot one one whole life member
that's about it
but it had potential to be more than
that it was pretty cool and it made for
um you know some interactions
even showed it several times on her
stream so
not that I built anything but
it was it was very ambitious however I
will not be joining rust in the next
season I already noticed that like
this season all the EM members pretty
much disappeared no one really cared to
stream anymore
so well if they're not playing then
there's really not much reason for me to
play
anymore either
well
yeah a lot of Japanese members also kind
of dipped out so
I think I think
I think we're done with this
I try to be part of it and we got a few
interactions and that's fine but I feel
like generally this kind of these kind
of games where
you
um you can collab but it's not
necessarily going to be a collab you
know what I mean like Minecraft and rust
and so on
uh are not not the best kind of game for
me I mean Minecraft I can still enjoy
because there's so many other things
that I I like to do there
um
but yeah
if I want to collab with someone I will
have to continue to organize collabs I
mean it was it wasn't only it was also
like you know time zones as well and the
times when I did log in I don't know you
know things happened
it's fine it's fine it's all good
I'll just I prefer planned collabs
anyway
prefer them anyway because then I know
this person is here for me I am here for
them
I know what we're gonna do I know you
know this is better for my
Mental Health
way better
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
structure yeah the structure feels good
to have
hmm
ah so it's a relief
foreign
[Music]
the same way
so I can say it was the last rest and
it's literally the same word
[Music]
comedian nah
nah
Teresa mastonia
my beloved Stone
how funny
I I if I don't bring this bot back then
I'll at least reuse the fan art for a
different thumbnail because I think
I think the artist was happy about it
and I retweeted it but then
I felt kind of bad for not using it
um
where was I
ah
wait no
Aya video freak 0618 thank you and thank
you and happy belated birthday yeah
yeah I hope you had a lovely birthday
um scratch cat Meowth donation and hello
chunky monkey hi what is
this what is it
um
I know I know I know I know I know I
know I know I know I know Mommy is gonna
end the stream soon okay
[Laughter]
wow start now
leave stop sniffs now
isn't it so cute though
it's the cutest
the cute fluffy baby demanding you to
love her
pure happiness
couldn't ask for anything else
Patsy Danke Schoen
Jammer out for the real real stream
right right now I'm wearing
um alpaca pajama
uh bottoms
with an old uh oh from 2011.
uh a t-shirt merchandise from special
life Yokohama Blitz
uh Betty's Cobble t-shirt I don't think
I was actually at the concert I think I
just got it from another fan back then
who shared some merchandise with me I
think
a blitz concert from Betty's Coble no no
no I think I would remember that because
Yokohama Blitz was quite the the special
venue
yeah but they had like special
merchandise t-shirts for every [\h__\h]
occasion
so I use them as pajamas
the dress of course
no I don't think the training logic
concerts was really a a thing that would
happen often it was more like you know I
came in as a foreigner
um with barely anything because in
overseas you weren't able to buy the
merchandise so I got some merchandise
donations basically out of pity mail
[Music]
hi hi I got her again you got too close
to close chunky monkey
[Music]
free stuff yes free stuff good
it's not very good
where is your raccoon oh who knows
I haven't seen the raccoon in a while
Maybe
and I need Papa go Papa
oh she's purring so loud
holy [\h__\h] oh yeah you need to hear this
uh ah microphone come on
let's see let me turn that up oh my
God
[Music]
hmm
why are you enjoying this the chin
scratches
my rifle is purring
Papa
no
[Music]
see how she's always enjoying this when
I cuddle her
always purrs no matter what I do
but she complains when when I try to
hold her or so but she will still purr
she's like half enjoying it and half
complaining
baby
all right but you like in reality
whoa what would you like it oh
um
[Music]
you need to try a little bit harder than
that
okay
but why do you keep on coming back if
you don't want to be with me
oh she's looking the other way now
oh she's so soft
okay oh bye bye
oh so many counties
asking the real questions yeah I'm
confronting her she doesn't like
confrontation that's why she left
oh
are you hearing this double I'm asking
again I think we would have told me by
now right if this was double
I think you would have told me
okay good
my dad
yes
for the pink Super Chat it comes with a
Korean message
it says
you're calling me
illusion
to audacity ah
what it said
manager you were doing the broadcast
early so I ran after work why LS are you
angry that I started the stream early so
you had to stress after work to come
back home faster is that what you're
saying well you shouldn't have any other
job to begin with besides working at kfp
I'm not a me problem
nah but thank you I was I was hoping
that you know when I streamed earlier it
would be better for him for my sea fans
you complaining to me
it's okay it's okay it's joke thank you
for watching I'm sorry the stream didn't
go so well
um
loves to live in danger
I should go to work oh it's okay
we're almost done
um
thank you
I hear myself so clearly right now
because I changed some
I think the the
volume of the microphone
put that down please no
tell me to put that down one more time
and
I will put you down huh
oh no
okay I think I have super chats from
Mario Kart left
cool I know thank you for the pink Super
Chat I love you kiwava
oh
thank you so much
you've got so much love in you so much
we need another Outlet Maybe
maybe get a get a dog go and take logo
on walk
Dogo will be very happy
give Dogo love love
I'm saying I'm even though I love cats
I'm recommending a doggle because
I feel like there they would be more
appreciative of all the love that you
have to give
cats are more like yeah well whatever
not necessarily though no hate on cats
see chunkers this movie they appreciate
my love
what did I miss not much I don't know
when you
when you left but you know you're just
reading super shadows and GTA was fun
what do you guys think can I finish next
week
I think at the beginning of today's
stream someone said I have 22 missions
left
I think maybe I did about half of those
today
felt like I did quite a lot
did only eight
huh well I did like some other unrelated
stuff
in between I guess
[Music]
it's not much though that's well I mean
13 14.
whatever missions left that's like
barely anything
well maybe we can have I know I said
frog week next week but I think I'll
just have broccoli closer to Halloween
um
until next week we have snack box and
probably GTA twice
and then
besides that
I think there was nothing else rolling
Frankie Ada yeah
um it will be a couple days
couple days of froggy Wawa
I'm just a bit sad because it seems like
I can't use
froggy Wawa outside of like VR streams
um
well but at least I have the the Frog
onesie remember
with the nice cleavage
it's not technical reasons
management reasons yeah
yeah the one for me the next up that one
looks really nice too yeah
I'm vaguely recall
that's why I've been asking for VR games
uh where you can like see in the froggy
Wawa you know
friends Netflix review and frog week
sounds fitting oh oh I did not realize
that
no it's not about licensing no
no it's just you know
well
things
inside VR is okay
but
maybe I can find the work around
ha ha ha
purple Coronet don't know anything about
it hello chunky monkey
what's furball coroner
whoa interesting Alexander
what
considering it though
small doggle
hmm
foreign
let me look that up
sounds interesting
furball
[Music]
let me look at that a little bit is that
the left thing
cute
it's cute
the angry face is cute
oh Chunky Monkey Jumped up here hello
did you hear the blue when you jumped up
here
oh yeah
hmm
[Music]
oh
you want to stay here oh you already
want to go
you want to go behind the monitor okay
just don't unplug it
oh oh oh squeezing through the gap of
the monsters good job chunky monkey
I got so many hairs on my face
oh my God
there's so many so much cat hair
become as junkers
no
thank you for a bulk you up
that's not so unlikely anymore
but I spent with some nice purring
wasn't it
such a baby
language
I just got back from a small surgery
probably gonna miss the night's stream
to rest more so I hope you'll have lots
of fun with kfp I also being extra based
as usual I know we can always count on
you when things happen good luck with
racing thank you oh I wanna I wonder are
you okay now
I never had any kind of surgery in my
whole life I think
if that day ever comes I'll be so scared
so I'm proud of you for going through
with it I hope it went well and I hope
that now you have no more problems hmm
thank you blue for being here get well
soon mwah
Chen
you're not even a tiny one no no
no no no no no
foreign
thank you for the pinky I'm sorry boss I
really want to play with you but I don't
want to switch so please eat me being
eaten by you would be an honor now is a
good time too since then two months I
won't be a bucket of fried chicken
anymore
nah that would be such a waste because
you'll never reach your your final form
then
no no I'll eat some other chickens
yeah
some some non-member chickens
here I am but you have to stay alive
or become alive again yeah yeah
that's better I think you'll be more
useful to me that way
hello thank you
thank you our help a cute winter in here
two cats turned me into a frog recently
and I don't know how to change back do
you know how to break the curse do you
you forgot to write it in caps lock
and without the y o
that was a missed chance missed
opportunity
I wanted to be a chicken again so I can
be rewarding so many Phoenix in the
future love you kiwawa nothing I think
for now you'll stay Moon frog because
maybe until after Halloween isn't this a
nice costume
um frog frog frog frog although your
profile picture is still doggle
so Moondog will need to change to Moon
froggle okay
yay and frog yes you frog now you just
need to try to practice the sounds yeah
and listen to M frog from takanasikiwawa
and then you're good to go
you can make some frog friends and then
you turn into doggo and then you you eat
them
genius idea no have some free food some
very very fancy food sophisticated frog
legs
first you get close to them make them
think that you're their friend
and then you change back into doggo
bamboozle and then much much much
yeah yeah I'm no genius
wow thank you Moon frog
pets
to protect I I heard a chance to be
eaten by Chihuahua
I'm for a while but I also want to play
with your tight shoes or maybe eaten
more well what did you choose any and
papa did you play with me or not
what's Papa no I also can't eat you no I
don't feel like it nah nah I'm having
something else tonight
I refuse no thank you
you will stay here
for a while longer
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
in the game
thank you for the recipe can I pay you
100 bucks to not play with you
all right I'll take that that's a good
offer
yeah
acceptable
I wanted every single one of you to play
with me yesterday but you obviously
didn't manage to do so
but in this case yeah that's convincing
oh oh do I hear me out from behind the
monitor what's your problem there Mrs
Mrs chunky wonky you're not comfy enough
here are you looking very comfy there
I don't even see her but I I reached my
my arm under the Monitor and give her a
squid scratch
foreign
ERS Malcolm's actor had brain issues and
he's forgotten also the serious attacks
actor actually got together with him
often all through help remember oh also
an alternative a tournament ending to
Breaking Bad has Hal wake up next to the
mom with Breaking Bad being a dream oh I
couldn't talk it's reaching under the
monitor for the the papers the remaining
papers the wrapping papers of the
Cough Cough Drops cough cough throat
candies
she wants to play with it ah it's like
only her paws coming through
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no you want these hmm no no you
can't handle this is
your frog now oh no because of super
chat right now I can't see
Super Chat uh hyper chat because I got
the
pictures turned off
anyway
uh does he not remember
oh
oh even after being
like does she keep on forgetting or did
he just forget like once and then
like is it is it like
he just needs to be reminded and then he
stays in his memory or would he keep on
forgetting it
said that he was that was a myth he did
have brain issues but it's not related
he was just too young and there were too
many episodes okay that makes a lot of
sense too
ah okay okay okay
how did that come up in the first place
and that that
statement
um
it was a lot of episodes and honestly
like I don't remember
much or anything of what I was doing
when I was like 10 11 or so I don't
remember anything
so yeah
but still having brain issues like that
that is true
apparently so that's really unfortunate
but I've heard of that before yeah oh
wanna hold hands no
outside never once breaking bad but you
guys made me kind of like Curious I was
going for the kfp hashtag on Twitter and
someone was talking about breaking bad
oh no someone was saying that there's a
sequel to Malcolm in the Middle and I'm
like yeah what
so I typed the Malcolm in the Middle
Sequel and what I get was a video that
was a mashup
of Breaking Bad and Malcolm in the
Middle or so it was really funny so I
understand now it's just because I'm
breaking bad those it's the same actor
right okay yeah yeah
it was pretty funny
it was so dramatic it was like using
Breaking Bad music and phrases on top of
Malcolm in the Middle footage
and it worked surprisingly well with one
another
yeah
it is a real alternative ending
nah [\h__\h]
now fish officially right
funnel's favorite show
he's a great actor um
of course not officially right
what is wrong with the microphone
is it because I changed some stuff does
it sound weird
I feel like it sounds very clear
press f for the fruit quilt
sounds fun right
okay
ah Nick sdb dankerson
Kentucky
thank you for the pinky hey wow you
should use the froggiana model for the
first question
it will be very appropriate
hmm
maybe I will but I don't think it will
be part of the Frog week because I want
to do the snack box stream as soon as
possible
yeah yeah yeah
yeah you dork dorky dork
Jim Tracy Duncan kitchen
Ellie glazed Dragon uh
you made me laugh at that moment so I
couldn't speed up anymore and forgot how
to actually gas gas
I don't remember one moment anymore
sorry
that was a fundraise you're the best
happy I could join and still have some
time before you eat me
yeah isn't it nicer this way
I'm glad you were able to join hope you
had fun
I know it's really difficult to enter
the lobby so I'm really lucky that you
made it then hopefully everybody can
play with kiwaba at some point
oh yeah oh you remind me yeah maybe I
should I want to ride to Bells
hey
snack boxes on the way now by the way
should arrive
um
in the next
five days probably
if you want
I I can be there when you open it
on stream
if you do it stream
uh
and then I want to say oh
you should by the way prepare some
sparkling water
for it
need some sparkling water for you know
what I'm doing syrup that I got her
don't tell her she doesn't know what it
is she just needs to prepare some some
sparkling water
[Music]
and yeah the drink
meow chonkers left to chat by the way
bye bye chunky monkey
yeah yeah yeah yeah I hope the syrup
arrives safely I put it in like a like a
um like a wrapping
a fluffy wrapping so
hopefully it stays safe
uh Randy RJ Duncan Hildegard Duncan all
right Ellen I already read your super
chat during the stream so I'm not gonna
read it again but thank you thank you
um
thank Lord weed smash Danke Schoen
Martin eight thank you for the pinky you
playing on the desert track during the
collab a while back
hmm you mean the one where I was saying
this is not a new one I know this one by
the way speaking of Queen and Grace it
would be cool if there was uh something
for anime New York
but how do you keep winding up with no
breaks during them
hope you're feeling better ah yeah I
mean the the previous ones at
conventions
there was no exact like like time
schedule for those
um they were just waiting outside
waiting for their turn so you know I I
can take a break if I say please stop
but sometimes they would sense the peeps
in so fast
like okay next okay next okay next and
I'm like okay I guess next okay
gotta keep on going so that I get done
and finish it I also have by the way no
idea when anime in New York even is but
it's not really not really in my
my hands to the side of which
conventions we are appearing at or which
conventions we're doing meet and greets
um
Mario Kart thumbnail oh
oops thank you for telling me [\h__\h]
late on that oopsy doodles
this is a good thumbnail
s
Marie sorry about watches for what
looking for their mansion I have been
reading super chats from Mario Kart for
a while
yeah
not scary no no
no no no
and I I was feeling better thanks to
Mario Kart yeah it was fun fun fun fun
fun fun
I enjoyed it had a good time even though
I was screaming I still enjoyed it very
much
hey Google
[Music]
ah
foreign
[Music]
movie I don't think that's ever
happening if anything they're probably
doing like I don't know Ocarina of Time
or something or Majora's Mask
I don't know
one of those probably
[Music]
foreign
wow that was that was really horrible
wow
staring at me okay I'm done I'm done I'm
done I'm done junky monkey I'm done I'm
done I'm done baby
oh maybe she's hungry yeah I'll have to
check
I will go check
I will also cook something for myself
now
so thank you guys for watching today
[Music]
I will be rebroadcasting the karaoke of
course at some point for a better time
for sea viewers so don't worry about it
if you can't catch it but I would be
happy to have you there so I'll see you
there schnitzel
that doesn't sound like me that's in at
all
okay okay okay okay
I'm coming and is Germany
and otherwise chokers will eat me up
bye-bye
[Music]
oh my God
meow okay okay I'm coming
[Music]
foreign