[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
oh
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
because it's also up in the thumbnail
and I didn't wanna you know
um
bait you guys with promises that I won't
keep
because I'm already not wearing the same
outfit but that's because in the game
there is a chihuahua
in my dress but I can't fight in that
dress so I'm I'm wearing my wearing my
sneakers that way I'm more flexible
but with my dress so to look like uh in
the game
but with my leg up cause I am ready to
kick it kick
some
well Idols I guess
[Music]
oh I have two outfits for oh really
tutorial where is the tutorial do I get
into the tutorial for proof play or for
training
[Music]
training okay okay yeah yeah we'll take
it slow because this is kind of my first
ah
game like this to stream at least
I think maybe in the past in an arcade I
played a fighting game before when I was
a child
but besides that
yeah I played a little bit of virtual
fighter when I played Yakuza because it
was a mini game yeah
and I felt like sometimes Yakuza gave me
fighting game Vibes even when it was
turn based and then when it was in turn
based two I don't know and smashed too I
guess eh
[Music]
uh
try to keep lowering the announcer
volume to below 30 to see what happens
what does it tell me to not lower it
anymore or what
I wasn't that bad was I
um let's say till now
oops was I too loud I wasn't that loud
was I oh was I too loud oops was I too
loud I wasn't that loud the iris
um
[Music]
did she record this for the game
because the the quieter I make it the
more it sounds the the phrase sounds
like uh specifically for this
Iris
[Music]
then players who leave the announcer
alone what
what that price was funny but you guys
are saying it's not Iris
[Music]
okay what okay those phrases are really
specific she's saying she's the
announcer that's dance testing one two
three
that's so cute that they did that
one two three testing testing one two
three this is the announcer volume
sliding so it's just someone from the
team how do I sound loud and clear are
you sure think testing one two three I
mean okay the more you I think about it
not being Iris the more I can hear it
not being Iris this is
announced slider how do I sound loud and
clear mic check mic check one two three
this is the announcer volume slide but
even I feel even the pronunciation
sounds like Iris the this this
[Music]
why are there like some people really
certain it's all this sounds nothing
like Ollie this is the announcer volume
sliding
not only
you guys are crazy
[Music]
oh did only do something else though how
do I sound loud and clear interesting
it was still quiet I could barely hear
it but what happened did I do it on the
Friday
has she not accepted
no
no I can literally not hear it
what does she say someone needs to like
really boost it up how do I sound it's
okay you can be like testing test 100
that's fine that's fine
okay
okay well anyway so this just released
it's a new alternative music yeah
whatever
um
uh a new fan game man we have so many
games in the whole life now
damn
um this one's looking really good
quality and fun
Mouse on screen IL what the
and it's a fighting game this time we
haven't had one of those I think
yeah and and I saw one of the devs or
artists
like on screen it's a KFC so hello
at least one kfb I'm happy to have some
kfp representatives in there
all right I I might really not be good
at this but at least I got my controller
to work so that's something
um let's let's hope I can oh okay I
think the font
and color choice of this the green stuff
is not so good
it's hard to read it's a bit hard to
read eh practice against researchers go
for lessons learn how to play the game
view the moves in the building okay we
gotta do the tutorial
oh one by one okay basic movement
probably just yeah
yeah oh you can do it with the d-pad too
main focus you can jump straight up for
the backwards jump arcs can be all the
slightly up wait sorry what's jumping uh
just up okay
Crouch is down good I'm playing corner
double tap or Dash what
I did
what
double tap
what what
some
it doesn't work I apparently it did but
it doesn't really work
eh really fast I can't do faster than
this
what it can be pad easier yeah
yeah I think so
no I need to do it again I need to break
this again
maybe I'll play with a d-pad
look
look she goes down when she back
what back back dashes is so cute
light attacks are the quickest but have
low range uh land and light attack on
Iron Man and when I prefer like just
like in terms of the grip I prefer to
have the
the
my thumb on on the on the
thingy
I hate words
um you know what I mean it's it's it
seems more natural but then I really
can't do the dash on the stick the
stick anyway line attack l
hello
what's l
oh
[Music]
what's owl
X X but X is u b
I'm using a PlayStation controller
this
maybe maybe they mean Square yeah I mean
Square okay Square isn't a basic attack
me and attacks are generally
far-reaching but the range is vary by
character hit item of a medium attack
uh
uh is this okay okay uh triangle is a
medium attack heavy attack I'm guessing
is a circle
oh Santa opponent longer a crouching
character has a new set of attacks that
are distinct from their standing attacks
hit I am over crouching lights
crouching light all right oh I'm sorry I
am missing point the crashing heavy
attack will always launch your opponent
oh it can be followed up by jumping oh
why it's I'm over crouching heavy why
would I jump after that
why
why is it telling me that wait did I
what
with what oh why is it not even am I not
doing the heavy one
this was the heavy one
uh move to start air attacks M while in
the air characters have a new set of
attacks this thing for understanding of
them I don't need him
okay we did that
[Music]
all right a normal attacks from please
oh it's like a color variation it turns
this into okay you look cool hold back
and block I didn't block it what how did
I block it
what it happened
[Music]
how did I do it
backwards
what
is
[Music]
think that I have to block while walking
I don't get it
but
I really don't understand I need to go
back in time
walking back is vlogging okay but what
if I don't want to walk back what if I
just want to stay here and block
do am I always walking back
Crouch what Crouch
what
was Crouch Vlog is crouching itself a
block
is this a block
we still look
together
Crouch and hold back
she doesn't do anything
no I told you I never played really
maybe when I was like five or so
I want to re-round it because you guys
are not helpful you guys are just I feel
like you're just guys just screaming at
me with words that I don't understand
can I restart this
foreign
backwards okay
[Music]
okay it was really just walking
backwards and then low guard
just crouching
Fire Guard is the same as
that's basically the same as the other
one though the only reason I couldn't
walk back is because I was cornered what
I don't get it we're just we'll just be
very aggressive so we don't have to
block
h
M
what's I'm not why is why does my steam
when I play games and I have the
controller and it acknowledges it as a
PlayStation controller why does it still
never show the actual
Circle and triangle the actual control
so this is at the same time
she sneezes that's disgusting of course
advice is that like something she does
Steve straight into people's faces
why is that weather for moves
I guess sweep uh sweep attack can knock
the opponent down and must be blocked
crouching
most tags will not hit a character in
knockdown
I don't understand anything
age what was h
uh I guess it was Circle
uh What uh get hit
[Music]
use Quick was quick to recover faster it
gets hit wait wait wait wait
wait I've hit the whole background
just that we're okay
I don't know
knock down attack completed okay
just just jumping away after being hit I
suppose
uh all Pros are unblockable
whatever Ariel opponents cannot be
frowned you can also break a throw by
pressing grab at the exact moment you're
being thrown
crab or L plus m
what's what's the grab button then
L1
or L1 doesn't work
R1
let's go oh what
that was easy
[Music]
iron one
it's been a while pressing the special
button with different directions will
perform different special moves
uh s
what could s be
[Music]
oh it was X
uh those different directions okay whoa
chain saw
retro even more retro could on it you'll
be
noise
down okay through small small
chippy retro coordinate air specials
wait I have to do it Elizabeth from
further behind okay
did I not
[Music]
I did
yeah you'll be chainsaw
I don't want to hurt solution boy motion
inputs there are also special moves
linked to specific motion inputs
performing a quarter Circle forward or a
quarter Circle back motion and then
pressing a button will perform a special
any button
[Music]
oh guys Super Chat
oh
what's that not in I'm trying to do it
was
triangles uh M right
[Music]
it's not working you're hitting the
right button right yeah I think so too I
hit it too early wait
oh wait
[Music]
is ready to burst
oh she's ready to burst
oh
yeah
what
I can't do it
it's Kaylee shoot yeah it is
d-pad how you do the the sweeping motion
with a d-pad
oh what was that
[Music]
is this it apparently not
that's just a normal one
right side move
slide your phone
[Music]
I'm sliding it
the house is not it
roll your thumb
I want to get over her please thank you
[Music]
apparently I didn't I'm probably never
gonna do that again because
mostly it puts to down down l
uh double tapping down plus an attack
button will perform a special move while
usually defensive the effect of this
move varies from character to character
perform a ddl okay down down down down
what I think I did it
that one was easier wait that's not it
ah wait that was a heavy one
[Music]
there we go it looks the same
oh it looks the same to me though that's
weird but what I'm saying by looking
good performing a motion input along
with the heavy button oh no the result
in a star special move
oh God there's so many things to learn
these also significantly more powerful
but consume one bar of the star meter oh
please
heavy weight heavy right heavy
man
that looked really good but apparently
that's not it
I think I'm fine I'm just that
oh
man eventually I'll probably just be
button and mashing and just hoping for
things to work out
sorry about that fight even though you
helped me with my computer when I was in
Japan now I'm hurting you like this
I do respect you as a senpai though
really I do
[Music]
I'm pressing the right button right it's
supposed to be a circle
what do you mean opposite
same
yeah yeah I'm mirroring it but even when
I don't it's the same wherever I do it
no
not really it's just sometimes happens
to be
the same I guess it doesn't
feel the same way through the controller
as it does to me yeah but it doesn't
work anyway
I can't even do it in any direction
I found a controller would help
you need a hand cam
we want to come over here put on Senpai
hmm
please no okay all right
wow
I did something there
I got a super chat for it
what was that what did I just do
almost
um no I didn't I swim doing to the left
maybe I started too much on the right
side
wow
number I want a chainsaw
[Music]
yeah this is a great start to the Stream
just can't do I guess I'm not made
for it
I'm pressing too fast
too fast later right it doesn't work
either
[Music]
then I just jump when I wait longer then
I just jump
oh I sneezed should I do it from further
behind
me no no I did the other one again
wait was it didn't you wait no chainsaw
chainsaw right
that's just jumping and that is done
using a PS4 controller yeah
I think
we're so PS razor controller
I will pay your hospital bills
afterwards Autumn senpai
[Music]
I'm kidding
I don't get it
read the Super Chat which one
that wasn't super chat I don't know
which one you mean
um
what was that
[Music]
well
I did it but
it's just luck at that point
now we have the same with the other
butt
wait what book was that
was that
was not the same as the other one which
we're just trying to get but I was
pressing X
isn't there supposed to be something
else I didn't press Circle
this is so weird see I pressed X again
different version of the same move
so what am I looking for now
[Music]
what do you mean
I am compliant okay I am going from down
to upright
it just I don't know what it's doing if
it's doing something else then it's not
my fault
foreign
[Music]
on the icon it goes it doesn't just go
sideways it goes up
[Music]
oh
cool
this supercharmina slowly films over
time before motion inputs to fill the
meter faster
what okay what's the super cat meter the
one above the star meter
I don't even want to do the tutorial
anymore if I'm not
[Music]
wow
if you're time to block just as you are
hit by an attack you will perform an
instant block which increases the Super
Chat meter and pushes you back less far
okay
so timing
idle skill I have skills are unique
special moves that fill a soup chat
meter faster their effect varies between
characters
[Music]
okay
s s was the X right
I didn't I didn't hit her but I did it
right
Super Chat cancel a bar of Super Chat
meter can be spent on subject cancels
after hitting the opponent a special
move can be canceled into a different
Special by spending one bar of the Super
Truck what what what what what
after hitting the opponent especially
move can be canceled
what
[Music]
do I stay on the left
yeah okay I don't let go
uh
[Laughter]
gaining super Jazz you can store up to
two or three bars of Super Chat perform
motion inputs and idle skills to stack
up a bar of super chats
what
[Music]
um
okay I guess I did it
[Music]
play it start calling players mustulate
both a playable character and the collab
character collab characters
is it assist can be called in for two
bars of the star meter to perform a star
calling
whatever you say
I surely understand
isn't this just an emotion input
[Music]
do I need to hit her for somebody said I
should go back
she's hella naked senpai
damn okay
hit it without even looking haha
clap wait there's a collab button like
the grab button
[Music]
hey what what
even happened what
can I do that when I have like both of
those golden bars at like Max
or is that different is that the purse
there's a there's a burst as well
your very soon is gained by taking
damage when the burst meter is full you
can perform a burst to escape for your
opinion wait which one is the best I see
a burst up ah the circle on the top
form a burst first what verse L2
whoa
so what what is it
doesn't make me stronger
or do I get like when I'm right in front
of an enemy do I boost blast them away
knocks it back
Escape oh okay okay
basic combo cancels canceling attack
allows another move to start before the
previous one finishes this is essential
for combos any normal can be canceled
into another stronger normal upon
hitting on the phone
yeah okay thank you at least that was
easy
uh canceling into the same button after
hitting an opponent moves can also be
canceled into different moves of the
same strength level
why why why do why would I do that
anyway
I don't understand fighting games
what's the same button though
what I'm going down
okay
fast well
after hitting an opponent any normal
attack can be canceled into any special
move
heavy and as
[Music]
yeah
okay yeah that's fine
I get that wait was that
uh
until where did we do it could we do all
of it now
we did special move we did this we did
we did this we did this
I don't think we did bro and knock down
on Tech did we do that
the finished oh okay
[Music]
I'm still used to uh
switch controls
okay
just play without thinking
I guess let's try it wasn't arcade I had
also a god Club of fights wow
we'll start with uh AI first I guess
I got and yeah let's go with very very
very easy I think that's best for now
we got
a couple characters to choose from or
someone that you can unlock apparently
in the future interesting
I
wanna go with actually I do want to go
of course but I still Hong Kong oh yeah
that looks like
[Music]
wait who's that supposed to be
blonde
okay
yeah okay okay and I want to see the
others
uh
pink
green eyes
oh
let's see
that's that actually does kind of like
look like this is because Lisa has
you know that pink Parker
yeah yeah
that's my locked who will that be oh but
that's a nice solution like the
different colors
turning into the different members that
they maybe can't all separately make
it's supposed to be ASAP
yeah okay
[Music]
uh besties and it does look like
European that works so well
cute
[Music]
great is that
where
gray with black and red
it's just Dark Souls oh
and some locked ones
wait so
is the colors make me think a little bit
really really
okay Supergirl with long hair and uh
kind of like Japanese outfit very cute
yeah I was making Matsu or some water
but
probably because of the color is super
awesome
[Music]
um
wait
also for cookie
oh
that wait wait uh
love love love love no reference
I like this one though I like the colors
no then she will have dark hair
because they always change the hair
color to the person they're trying to
resemble
[Music]
that looks good
I could totally imagine this being her
design from the get-go
from if she was like this at debut
I would be not even wear like a Snow
Lion I like that
meow it looks good
the orange looks good
too wow
I love them all oh they look all so good
these I feel like these are the best she
does her whole generation
nice
oh
[Music]
wait wait
oh
I didn't expect
okay makes sense
[Music]
[Applause]
no way what
that looks good I like that color
combination
yes
and then oh here we go here we have
Matzi Senpai and I saw this one on
Twitter that looks really pretty the
Luna nanora version looks so good
pink and girly no no
and oh
and we already have elsewhere
oh wait did we have anything else no
okay an answer is a sample
[Music]
pink
because of the clothes
oh wait pink hair
ah I don't see her sister oh
exactly like Thomas and Fire
that works so well
oh that that's really good
that's really good
I think the original works so well is
because of the hairstyle also being kind
of like to listen buns you know twin
tail the curly twin tail
huh
wait I am
I know that why it doesn't look like
mermaid
[Music]
is it supposed to be
supposed to be cute
oh cute
or Anya no I think movie
[Music]
but now you make me doubt myself
hmm
oh wow okay all right there's actually
ratings oh beginner big very beginner
oh very advanced
not so Advanced but you know you know
pretty advanced
very beginner Iron Man
also very big okay okay well in that
case
I'm gonna go for Amazon but in
um
I know this one looks cute oh
[Music]
wow
oh wait the star call in is called
Sparks and the off collab is
and there's amitu
[Music]
question mark coming soon boy
he would I want to see them in full body
okay okay well I mean first of all we of
course have to go for quinoa we're
fighting against cornea okay
I know I can choose hmm yeah let's do uh
[Music]
in English form or I can choose that too
can I go random
I am this is random
[Music]
because
oh
hey this is like Ian references
huh wait what's this
midnight Rose
main stage all right hey I don't know
let's go Japan
[Music]
foreign
okay let's let's get blasted no no there
is difficulty selection I selected it
before already
say hi to the viewers
100 Irish you can't tell me
[Music]
okay
before killing opponent okay
yes smash buttons
[Music]
going to their ground pound with me
yeah
do we get like a second round stream
offline
we cannot kill her too fast
[Music]
come on
L1
[Music]
for me is she doing anything
what was she doing
see you next time what did you do
there's this feeling is she my shield oh
victory
hook chat what
I wish I was going to fight with me too
my dog plays games yeah that's probably
true too
[Music]
can you please say hi Honey hi honey
once you sample here
lies lies
this is a fake chat I think this is a
fake chat guys
yo but this is cool it's like a YouTube
screen this video recommendations down
there
cool
that's so cool
okay let's try
[Music]
um
the other very easy one is
[Music]
and then
uh you'll be
I don't know like if I put an easy AI on
an advanced character they're still
gonna be not so rough with me right
hopefully
what was that left
hmm
you can have Miko senpa I guess I don't
know
they won't move him okay okay
and instead let's look at this one
oh okay I didn't feel like I chose maybe
I chose by accident
[Music]
I I made subconsciously I made MI cometo
what the
I was gonna say the animation of Us
coming in is uh
like in the concert
[Music]
is that from uh not not rust what was
that other game
but the animations are so funny let's go
again the attack ideas too
[Music]
wait can I use my special
that is so funny
[Music]
I'm uploading that yeah
wow so many I'm so honored thank you for
coming to the stream button matching is
the way yeah
the learning the control is very
frustrating but this is more fun just
mashing the buttons is more fun
again
Ah that's what they call the the studio
the game Studio
behind it the one that they just created
it for this game or if they did
something else too
let's do another one
I mean realistically speaking she could
also be in the room chat
[Music]
let's do random
in
in Cosplay 2 whatever that will be we
won't know until after
okay and I want Mighty simple
I'm here random too
and one in random what do we get it's
gotcha
it's gotcha now
random stage sure
oh I'm full okay versus solar Senpai
everybody Sapphire is our collab
[Music]
is supposedly relatively easy to control
I love that look on her that color
variation oh and she's
as uh
don't run away why
why would you let yourself be cornered
by me
what was that
yeah
[Music]
somehow this AI is not as smart as the
one we were just fighting yes
[Music]
that was called
[Laughter]
better stay away something with those
musical notes it's dangerous
is she gone no she's still there ah
there we go
[Music]
the mighty safer comes in to sing a
little bit
Lost Empire singing
oh
I can bring her in too oh she's at the
hug let's go oh she holds her
up how is she still alive
she has a comeback guys
yeah almost she almost killed me
[Music]
oh
yes she keeps on blocking damn
[Music]
nice
that looks so cool when she does that
she's not using the opportunity either
though
can I throw something to have any
throwing
yeah that one
okay that's too easy to dodge
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
nice
I see Cali is a hologram debut
down there I think that was your
hologram debut
how can you see where you're lagging the
way what do you mean I can see perfectly
fine
what you should be asking is how I'm
playing with my hands up and my leg up
[Music]
who should we play I'll just leave it up
to chance again
cosplay free with random and random and
um free and random
yeah my left foot then yeah it must be
foreign
we have to bring her in
was it L1
but at the golden bar has to be full or
what say hi why is it the Super Chat
[Music]
and she is
how do you keep on letting yourself get
hit by those
apparently they're gonna change the
voice lines because she was not
satisfied
good job
I like them though
let me make that go away
[Music]
oh she's horny who wants a horny hug but
no I won't let you how do I call him oh
they're already this oh this is the
updated version
really
[Music]
L one didn't work so did I not have it
ready even though it's like golden yes
I want to call her yes
[Music]
but I downloaded or installed the
foreign
what's this
she's still talking
[Music]
how long does it work
s
[Music]
we need more meter barn on full hey
wait let me wait
uh
now there you go What's it gonna do
[Music]
she just screamed like a gremlin
and then there's the beard
[Music]
the one thing she doesn't Dodge is just
slowly incoming bomb but she brings
still modern Senpai to give me a last
hug
sweet
wait a second I need to check something
oh
I wrote uh
yesterday that I'm planning on playing
this game today and if anyone is online
they're welcome to play against me uh
guess who said they're ready to play
with me whenever I'm ready
hey there's me that was me really I'm in
the Holocaust yeah killed a Cali yeah
but I'm scared because Cali I saw a
tweet of her saying she's practicing
okay this be easy on me
all right all right all right
I'll have her for a few matches if she
wants
she already had like a stream on this
game uh collab with vatam isn't by Ryan
so she knows a thing or two I think and
I think she played fighting games before
she's more familiar with it than me I
think please be gentle yeah
okay let's do random again I'm in voice
chat until Cali or appears
[Music]
oh yeah Guilty Gear For example yeah
we're football again with Mikko versus
Coco and amen already
be gentle
she spent all day playing it oh my God
is this something you can unlock like
the more you play the more you can you
know like and hold a cure
like invest some points
[Music]
can you not
and there's a story mode
[Music]
what the monkey makes out the thing you
put in that
okay
[Music]
it was so close though
she's strong
[Music]
this time I kind of dodged it I think
oh
my God
the way but I absolutely blasted her in
this run live stream let's go
finally you challenged though
well
done
[Music]
got me again
no
[Music]
call me again thanks for watching oh
that is the win for the robots
humans and chickens and phoenixes are
useless oh did I just press rematch
that's okay all right
yeah
let's get down to business yeah no I
can't let it stand like that
[Music]
you know I have a handicap okay this
movie when I was playing with her
he scratched me real bad okay on my on
my on my thumb so on my right thumb my
right bump is really slow now with the
input okay
I was bleeding
[Music]
yes
my special
oh
what spray match rematch
what's up
I mean she is a big a big woman
tallest woman of her time
like a stone Mario attack you know when
like he becomes a stone Wait no that's
Kirby that's what I'm thinking is that
like a Kirby attack when she turns into
the friends
[Music]
I'll never win
I'll never win against Google Sapphire
[Applause]
[Music]
thanks for watching wow
I have to
have to give up
no no I can't give up but I mean maybe
with not cool or not not for bookie
Senpai let's get this stream okay I'll
try one more time
it's so disrespectful
[Music]
oh yeah
come on come on
mashing keep on mashing keep on mashing
[Music]
taunting me she was talking to me
gotta win one more time
oh I got the first taste
oh
[Music]
I feel like if they make me a character
a proper character in the game
they should just put me in the same you
know make me a skin of Coco Senpai
because I have fire as an element just
like her I got orange hair I got purple
eyes just like her
but wouldn't that be
to make
see you next stream
I know I'm an assistant but but but
yeah I also got I mean at least
I'm not as tall as uh Coco Senpai but I
got the the bot and I mean I should have
the butt
and the boobies you know yeah so so body
wise so so
pretty good match I would say
speaking of matches we need a different
match because
that was obliterating me and
even though I love uh won and the last
time when you could do something about
this
[Music]
let me just write one more thing to
Kelly
oh sure
okay it wasn't your problem since when
so let me restart this
why
why Frozen July
[Music]
oh
it's not only my face wait it's loading
there we go
[Music]
oh sure okay
now I fixed it
for sure
I didn't realize sleep paralyzed I got
cramped yeah
oh I've seen that Vlog plenty of times
we just like to not show it on stream
when possible and now I'm Coco standby
versus
[Music]
oh that's an interesting matchup
oh
and we're on the stage let's get down to
business wait her hair is that on
purpose her hair is there earlier
oh there you go I did the move but you
got this
oh those hairs
I'm a bad girl if anything
but okay if you say so yes
[Music]
wait how did I do that oh come on
nice Dodge
[Music]
is extremely strong
because now that I'm using her
[Music]
it's an easy time against accusations
I love how she can get wings
dragon wings
[Music]
[Applause]
how did I do that how the did I do
that
she's blocking for me
hopefully oh and stuff some fire
for watching lucky inputs
[Music]
button match ultimate
was a good match I would say
oh
I'm a muted
you be you be alone now
every man we don't need a rematch of
that that was too overpowered
[Music]
star oh wait was the story mode where is
this so called story mode
this is
[Music]
okay
we can do that
additional mechanics
use the decaying UB
what
accessories are passive items oh God
uh in Virtual front or which power up
your character each has a unique effect
hit the upon repealing your accessory
has a chance to inflict okay
[Music]
anything
does it have to be that you'll be
yeah
anything okay use the burgerfox item l
ol
doesn't tell me what item is
R2
then
[Music]
did that heal me
uh freestyles at a time it can be
consumed by pressing its corresponding
input you have the Yuki yoduki which
phrases you upon oh
ah okay
with h h
well do I have to be close to her to use
that though
[Music]
does it always hit consume audio onigiri
okay
um
consuming them all will prevent you from
using them unless they're refilled
[Music]
no no
rip
okay so just extra items all right
and back
[Music]
can we start now
choose
um I don't know
don't really it doesn't really matter
what's up boy
oh
[Music]
I missed I don't know what she does
still but
thank goodness you're here it's
pandemonium right now wait what's
pandemonium a computer virus is running
wild in the virtual world is corrupting
massive amounts of data and has even
kidnapped Yago
it's been spreading like wildfire things
will turn out really badly at this rate
that's why you come in with your help we
can save everyone and hopefully get rid
of the source of this mess so buckle up
once you're ready we'll boot you in and
get down to business
assembled some gear for you to take on
your journey please grab one before
heading out
[Music]
white armor
glove ah and it was Auto combos
imagine the same attack button will
execute powerful sequences
if you don't want a boost
and greatly increases opponent's
strength but nah okay I'll take this
okay
glad to see that you're ready to go our
recent reports show that anomaly is
using that animal is using malicious
clones of the girls to do its bidding be
prepared to fight
we'll be helping out as much as we can
from the sidelines
I begin the upload process now good luck
out there
[Music]
what is this
route so that can take
yeah
mine's extra girl oh man the remix
makes it even even more chill and sad
uh opponent
[Music]
fight against a simple opponent okay
snack settings
[Music]
well like if someone's an aura that
deals damage to enemies when close by
yeah
do I have to do something order
oh consumed automatically well that's
nice too for someone like me
[Music]
oh wait is this the first time we're in
this stage it's really new to me where I
was just too focused on the characters
in the front
[Music]
it's all right
victory victory that was easy ah you get
the curse you get is Pecos 46 Pecos it
sounds like it could be a currency and a
small hill
or do I have to choose that
oh I have to choose a thing oh okay I'll
take the currency
[Music]
next
oh she already has 400 more HP damn
[Music]
it
it looks like it could also be cool and
uh
prisoner clothes oh I should focus man
[Music]
it's not you is
that why are you going hard on me whoa
oh I use that by accident oh wow
why not why not
I was in the background where victory
Victory careful
you mean the chicken
what is this your attacks of a random
chance to inflict Decay yeah or provides
free super chats at the start of every
fight
I'll take the garlic thing
now we can oh we're going to a level
where there's like a a mermaid bag
why spooky oh is it a shop oh it's like
it's like slated Spire that these roots
what you can buy items
circus instrument box automatically
generates explosive music note
projectiles
water made on helmet
the quizzes incoming damage per flat
amount
spanner speeds up passive supercheck
collection oh
how much money do I have oh not so much
Passive A Generous money as time passes
during fights uh suicide train increases
grounded Mobility
and the glasses
provides the effect of free random items
oh but that's really expensive damn I'll
go for
I don't know
a hat
[Music]
this one or this one there's two there's
a real hat I guess
[Music]
oh
are you guys posting the loading emote
because of moonmail because YouTube is
actually loading that's so confusing
don't
[Music]
know me man women might be used to that
kind of joke but I'm not you guys made
me think that YouTube Broke My Stream
you make me concerned you're doing me a
concern
I'll take the Super Chat I don't care
get some more money buy more items was
that a good idea a good good deal I'm
not quite sure that sounds like
something she would say
because I am also not sure
what is this
there's so many things up here I want to
check that out
we can rest
[Music]
cute
okay refill snacks we can do a combo
deal for six pack of three stars health
and refill snacks oh
I don't know I'm not doing that bad
um
my snacks so it only fills up the tea
right
[Music]
okay
supporting
good luck out there thank you
does she know she's in a game like that
someone has to let or no
okay we're fighting Aki Senpai but she's
already at 1500 HP damn
your meter consuming moves do four times
the damage
oh
okay okay
let's get down to business
[Music]
she might kill me but that's okay
I like the logos that they made for the
game too all the character logos under
the HP bar
thank you
if they were mine
okay wasn't so bad it wasn't so hard
[Music]
oh I can take onion with me I take Yum
Yum Yum Yum more healing items what is
this movie time
well Devil's prank TOA walks up to you
carrying a bag of money you've never
seen before this is really exciting
inspired to be now because it also has
like these little
[Music]
um
thingies of options that could help you
or not help you
lying on the floor close by and is
wondering if it's yours well I don't
know the outcome
it's it's not mine I am an honest person
she appreciates my honesty
and still gives me the money
how devilish
see I knew it was the right choice and
we're gonna meet Wayne again
wait a minute heal me again please
[Music]
I miss you
let's go fishing someday no thank you
Wayne I'm not a fishing type of person
The Witch of nuts
this is you in the dead of the night she
asks you what's your favorite nut is
my favorite but they probably didn't put
it in because it doesn't have nuts in it
it's almonds
[Music]
oh maybe the chestnuts comes with a
chest of treasure but I'll go live I'll
even wait Chestnut
isn't that like something you Rose I
mean you can roast all of them but like
isn't that like soft inside
I'm not sure if I ever had a chestnut
before
I'm gonna go for walnuts I think
is it this should I answer seriously
[Music]
the cashews are not good too though
I don't know
good choice before casting spell on you
you suddenly feel straight here you will
now take less damage nice oh
really it's a roguelike game wow that's
so cool
[Music]
um I'll go
I'll go here so that that could go down
because I'm curious what that cocktail
border is
you look strong Wanna Make a Deal
[Music]
but it has a few weird side effects I'm
looking for someone to test it out for
me in a fight
[Music]
so I want to give it a try if you make
it out alive I'll be happy to open my
little shop to you
sure why not I guess
except take a random error item for the
next fight revive and receive a reward
upon when well I must win
[Music]
is this papaya
um
[Music]
I like this remix they should sense this
remix to Ahmed I feel like she would use
it
[Music]
did they remix any of my music somewhere
I want the OG of the remix
chess was nuts funny
[Music]
I could listen to this forever
hinotori I didn't hear it long enough or
like at all
let's go I know you had an interview
[Music]
being knocked down damages you more but
briefly
invincibility companion pigeon to a
phantom Thief
okay okay
let's go
[Music]
oh
cuckoo's Empire with really low HP why
enemy holds a random selection of items
uh why is she so weak now
is that random too huh I thought they
were continuously getting stronger but
it's nice
but I can't let my guard down because
when I was playing against her she was
always ready
never mind
[Music]
three
oh is that from ital increases maximum
HP onion
provides a free meter at the start of
everything
[Music]
I'll take the onion
oh this is so cool
hurry up get in the van I've got the
goods
scent I fought for a second it was a kfb
reference but it's a crony reference
isn't it
while active regret regenerates Health
but inverts control Dr oopsie massively
increases your attack power but deals 10
000 damage to yourself upon wearing off
ten thousand
unused refills all use so you want to
like kill the enemy before it wears off
right it just refills all your snacks
but decreases your maximum health
talk with a pancake
you saw that
decreases the maximum time for every
fight but provides an attack boost for
each fight based on how quickly you
completed the last interesting
charges meter automatically but removes
a bar of meter
but yeah
[Music]
no I don't want any of these
not giving her any money
sorry Emma not buying anything
feels like a scam
to be honest but I mean I'm not
surprised that your shop was trying to
scam me
why does this bar is a Cali no ah I
don't know
[Music]
oh what they put a face okay
it's not immediated effect but arrives
you if you die during a fight cool
[Music]
well active opponent attacks May
randomly whiff with what do you mean
with
what does that mean
is that an animal sound
what it says there do you know damage
for Houston
never heard that before
and the freezing one refills all your
health snacks to maximum uses
[Music]
complete invisibility
on on use the opponent's next frigates
will deal never damaged nor had stun
I don't know I take the bucket because
it's my bucket cute
if y'all please
no no no no no no no no no no no more no
more I'm saving my money
bye bye
moving on to where are we oh another
movie thingy
ASMR you're having upon a videotape it's
labeled relaxing ASMR do you want to
listen give it a go chance to gain or
lose health
[Music]
I would probably lose health because
ASMR for me
do we actually get to listen to it
though
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
we haven't fought in a while it feels
like
enemy copies all of your accessories and
snacks damn okay
wait that means she copies also the
buckets
which means she can revive
[Music]
yes
that is not good
right but okay well I guess I'll be
using up my bucket soon as well then
maybe what can I do it
[Applause]
all right
[Music]
my thumb
I forgot how to use the items
I want to use the onigiri
I forgot how it was I know the M button
but that is what
did she survive already okay okay okay
okay I didn't get it
that's right
it's basically made use of almond
broccoli
yeah
Victory there we saw our reduction on ah
yummy there's a fox Burger
oh it's not food
[Music]
no I want to keep my actual food I think
I need healing Elena please help me
I need healing thank you I love you
Bueno soya sleep does she really say
that
next is fighting time
solo Senpai fight with low grab low
gravity uh do we like fly more in the
sky
[Music]
she flew up hi there okay this is almost
like a Mario Kart tournament
[Music]
and not Mario Kart uh
Super Mario maker
[Music]
please
oh is that yes
[Music]
didn't we say it's like evil
definitely not poison on use does
something probably something good
are you sure
no I don't trust them that has probably
like random effect
or is that a new skin that I unlocked yo
[Music]
um
uh-oh why is it that's the first time I
have a red battle is that a very
difficult one
no well not flinch after that doesn't
even sound that difficult
okay
overall it's an elite really
what happens if I die I mean I still
have a bucket but what if I die for real
for real oh
oh oh she's strong
much stronger oh yeah
I don't know how to win this no no
please be nice
[Music]
okay
victory
thingy y'all
actually that was a really good choice
to bring AMA with me that saved my blood
because when I activate her correctly I
can get so many hits in
I'm a class I was so close
I figured out how to use almond purple
okay what should I use
um
[Music]
it's getting rough with uh
with HP I guess
okay we're almost at the bottom fight
with one more winner
[Music]
um imagine to refill because I'm almost
full HP
or combo deal
oh yeah because there's no more shop
wait did I just lose HP
[Music]
wasn't I at like 900
I thought it was a it's a visual okay
uh hopefully really just Visual and it
won't reflect like this in the battle
[Music]
oh
we don't think it's been what just
happened oh there's no actual boss you
just move on to the next stage ah
[Music]
go I'll go here
oh the 900 was it I am true because
I was really low HP when the fight ended
the truth
[Music]
is fine too
that's some cool items
yay
and what should we get I'm stacking
Christmas tree in the room increases
grounded Mobility
[Music]
onions
the ray of death
[Music]
you proceed toward a lined curtain with
four people behind it they're all
claiming to be modding which one could
have been
number one I'm the real who show Marine
[Music]
I know you'll choose me I'll trust you
Ahoy I'm the actual one you love Santa
don't you it's me I feel like I might
before
[Music]
and the Clipper was still
oh what
yeah I I have to go with my guts now
[Music]
three two they all give you something oh
okay
you guessed wrong yes I'm fine she lends
you some fresh bandages there's a
consolation prize
help you die I needed that anyway
you don't get fully healed after coming
to a new stage home
okay with Marine
oh Kelly replied again she's gonna wait
until I'm done with the virtual
furniture that sounds good
how long does it take though
how many stages are there
[Music]
oh my God
oh
three chapters
[Music]
[Applause]
did I do that yeah okay
Victory Hallelujah
[Music]
uh I will go for the heel let's go
we're getting back up there
slowly but surely
[Music]
another challenge for you what do you
say
sure I assure you yes take around here
yeah what
yes I knew you'd accept good luck out
there
oh wait I didn't oh I accidentally
pressed the button on the back of the
controller makes it go away what did I
get
what was that
sorry for a Split Second
hopefully something helpful
wait why am I losing his feet
why am I dying
taking my XP gradually
excuse me what's the actual
okay
[Music]
holy victory
what the was all of that that felt
very chaotic and I almost died
ooh
that was close I thought I was gonna die
but once I understood how serious the
situation was
with the help of Amir once again we
clutched it now we're doing your next
attack is powered up
wow automatically generates explosive
music note protectors oh cool
now get over here and buy me stuff buy
my stuff oh
that's almost the same thing
temporary provides invincibility but
decreases defense won't active
I gotta say oh man
[Music]
oh my HP though
um
[Music]
not so impressed um
um
these are all cursed
I might know
you better keep crying about this I'm
watching you punk
I like how it seems on purpose that her
items are kind of questionable
I want healing
well hey there's a fight thing
no wait no there isn't there's a movie
Next
oh
Uber sheep has released a limited time
offer to deliver us fast food to the
virtual world for free
and what about kfp
rivaled a new rival has appeared guys
order something from the menu
uh kind of common snack and random soft
drink snack
[Music]
should I do
foreign
ER yeah we'll bring him down no more Fox
Burger only Phoenix Burger
we can also sell Fox Burgers though
possibly
you can you know like eat up Fox Burger
the company and include their menu and
hours and then everybody's happy
can also have rarely uh purely good
items oh okay I gotta keep an eye open
them
I'll take a snack
small sheep on the mobile the rise of
your meal looks tasty I got a box Burger
[Music]
I could refill the onigiri Dome
but it's just a small amount all right
I'll get rid of the onikiwi
to be very low though yeah I wish I can
I can can I drink the tea like right now
probably not right
I still have my bucket though
can I manual
[Music]
well all of them were on manual holy
okay
now it should be fine let's get this
stream started yummy
[Music]
drink the tea drink it drink the tea
why won't you drink the tea
Chicago
[Music]
okay I used the burger at the KFC bucket
I was so
too
not having to do that oh well suck
yummy well active significantly it
decreases enemy damage noise
wait
I can keep the bucket though
significantly
get rid of the burger
foreign
[Music]
was that unrefillable okay next item I
get I replace
[Music]
oh your friends are holding a tournament
for a popular card racing game oh I
wonder which one it is it's time to
gamble who are you putting your money on
foreign
[Music]
okay
fight in an environment where time has
been sped up
so we have less time to fight or
that was fun
all the attacks are freaking fast
yeah that makes bug smashing even more
intense
what the is going on
okay
what was that special
that looks incredible wow
that was incredible Audrey
okay
provides money for every Super Chat
cancer performed in a fight oh I don't
do that performance object cancel
Netflix randomly default from the enemy
um
[Music]
I I don't do I have a super chat cancel
I'm not even anymore what that even is
it's canceling some action but
better not do it probably huh yeah okay
you find yourself in front of a shrine
at the front is a prominently displayed
button with a sign and track instructing
you to press a fortune
I'll do it you pulled it too that's a
neutral result nothing happens you
decide to continue away okay okay at
least something nothing bad happened
is it is it a reference to the Ian
Shrine that I built with mume or is it
just any Shrine because we did have you
know those numbers it sounds like our
Shrine but I didn't want to assume
it kind of sounded like mice right now
[Music]
yeah I just didn't get my super bad luck
thank God
fight against the stronger
and smart uh yeah that will go badly to
you can do it no
no I can't
go
[Music]
wait wait
up
[Applause]
[Music]
energy oh but I got some stuff unlocked
at least I mean inside the spiral I also
didn't win my first run
and not my second one either
I hate to be like that sometimes that's
okay win five fights to unlock on use
your next attack does triple damage
an avocado
oh wait what is this
interface it kind of confuses me
win a fight I've used what are the names
of these items though
complete a virtual Frontier run you
unlock the collection you can access it
from the virtual Frontier manual
seems like someone's waiting for me
look at that
is it a character
collections
where are collections
where would collections be
[Music]
inside virtual Frontier
that's what she voiced for the game
Ollie how did that happen
oh the background cute Holo police
[Music]
welcome to the collection
uh-huh
the items you've picked up so far in
your adventures together more the
collection of old girl even bigger
gosh I wonder how much out there is to
find
as much as you're running I'll be here
whenever you meet me cute he got the
side job look at items
for moral support either way take your
time thank you ollie what do you got
yeah what is this collection
or did I just unlock this is that what
they mean the collection with Ollie that
is what I unlocked
what's e
which is the keyboardy
ah and these are all the items that I've
had before I wish it could have stayed
longer but okay
sorry Ollie see you around yeah say
another time
okay now
um
Callie I don't know if you're watching
but I'm done with the thing
I'm I'm ready
can we
I'm ready
come and destroy me
the real boss boss battle
yeah cause they don't have boss battles
at the end of each map so at which stage
so this is my my boss battle will be
with Cali she'll teach me how to do the
online thing here there's a a function
for it there
okay wait
just waiting for her to see my message
how does the online thing work if I
press it doesn't ah I can create
join and search
like when I create one do you
immediately see
[Music]
I did
I'll post the link there or down the
code you won't know what it is
but I don't know how fast Kelly will see
the message she was just like typing
something a couple minutes ago
oh
EU to Japan online maybe a bit laggy
yeah with games like this that are on
Steam but they're like an indie game
do they have to have their own server or
is there like a steam server that they
can use
does this Idol Showdown have to use
their own server how does it work
ah yeah right now she's not in Japan
yeah
peer-to-peer see I don't understand
really what that means
I will be hosting
[Music]
huh
is that good is is that usually
decent
my computer talks to careless computer
I wonder if they'll have like a a good
connection
a good
you know what I mean
I ship them
ship our computers
peer-to-peer tete computers
computer friends oh sweet
[Music]
oh while we wait oh wait she saw it now
she answered no
[Music]
I don't know well she joined voice chat
too
oh
Kawaii pimori is it you I think oh wait
I think they don't hear you one second
hello
[Music]
wait wait they don't hear you what oh
it's okay now they hear you hello hello
hi guys I just woke up hello you just
woke up that's good and you have a
handicap because I'm really bad at the
game
no what do you mean you're so fast
you're so fast yeah I don't know what
you I don't know what you mean by that
because you got pretty far through the
virtual Frontiers so yeah but just for
button mashing
yeah the tutorial and really confused me
oh
so many inputs just didn't work the way
I was you know trying to do them yeah
you still you still might beat me
um I've been having a hard time I think
I'm overthinking the game really but
yeah that's okay well you'll try
experience right the with like fighting
games experience is an interesting word
experience is an interesting choice the
word there I play them a lot but I'm
just I'm notoriously not very good at
them I just really like them a lot
because of the characters so I'll still
give it a try though wait wait chill
chill four more and I'm looking for a
picture of you I think I have one
somewhere yeah
who's your main so far I kind of changed
mine
in the middle of the night
my main the whole time now I was playing
botan Senpai and just smashing buttons
yeah but I think it was going decently
I think the best button mashing
character is probably
ayame or Elaine yeah she's a really
beginner friendly character like nice
close range
um it has like a bunch of really quick
attacks like she focuses a lot on speed
um so that's she's the reason I switched
from say to botan oh
yeah you should give her a shot I think
if you like the button mesh because she
gives me the hardest time out of
everyone I'm still trying to learn her
weaknesses
[Music]
but you've been practicing you're really
motivated I mean I I guess I only just
now got to the point where I can beat
the AI on medium before that I was
having a really hard time yeah
wow wait is it because I think I'm on
very easy and then it's a very easy easy
medium
um yeah very easy easy medium and then
it goes up from there oh yeah very easy
was too easy easy was also kind of easy
but medium was kind of kicking my ass
last uh last night
interesting yes so trust me it's very
fair okay okay
apparently the connection isn't so good
it says I see well we are very far away
from each other well is it 28 Ms ping is
that bad uh it's not the best but I mean
I collabed with what's a man we had a
fun time so I think it'll be all right
yeah and I'm not in Japan so let's get
ready do I have to get ready yeah you
have to get ready it's like choose your
character and your collab okay I guess
I'll go with Iron Man
oh yeah it does kind of sound like her
huh totally yeah definitely I had to be
told several times it's not her oh sorry
guys you don't hear the game audio no
one second level I switched something
around oh
should be okay if I do whoa this
now it's much louder I like how you
raised your little leggy here
yes it's uh oh I want to lower the Audio
I can't is it too loud for you guys
can't do it now
I could do it if I go out of the screen
completely probably is it okay okay it's
pretty loud for me but oh I will
be okay
yeah I'll turn up Kelly maybe one second
oh yeah I think it would be super cool
to to be an announcer for this game but
I I don't know if we can right which
kind of sucks because I'm like oh man I
wish that like I could like like help
and contribute but you know sometimes
maybe it's it's best to just but only
contributed uh she voiced her own like
collection thingy right oh really we're
allowed to do that dang I think she must
have done it before the game even
released maybe she heard about it being
uh the game being made and then asked if
she can contribute and then it just so
happened and then Senpai said hey I
wanna you wanna make my own voices for
the game and then they switched them out
already
oh my God I did notice that there was
something different yeah so I think
generally like for example if you say
one day when Cali will be a character in
the game uh let me voice it myself and
not just use Clips they'll they'll
totally do it oh cool awesome
lines
sort of simple yeah awesome then I'm
gonna do it yeah
did Mom I have a shop or something like
that I think so yeah so you also do a
little voice I think you already have an
assist in the game yeah uh I didn't
really uh it was it all happened so fast
I didn't really know like what was I was
I saying anything at all
I don't think you were but I bet I bet
that they could give you some some voice
lines ah Steph and chat hello Devin chat
hello develop first of the game I was
like you know we're here very openly
talking about being open to contributing
to something like this like also other
games and like uh for example that that
Hollow myth anime I was always thinking
like we would all be open to voice this
but the fans that create this kind of
stuff I guess they they just they don't
even know how to reach out probably I
wonder if they don't think it's oh it's
like a loud yeah probably that too
company both of the those reasons I
think um I mean if no money is being
made it should be fine yeah yeah we'd
love to do it I'm sure so ah depths if
you plan on implementing uh Cali or
kiwawa anytime soon or in the next year
or so so feel free to reach out we're
friendly yeah yeah we are pretty
friendly yeah
shall we fight ready to throw down yeah
I'm ready to go I'm ready to
embarrass myself let's go you want to
embarrass yourself I might oh I might
light you all can be nice to me please
oh yeah hey that's my main combo
we're on the stage
oh it's a Freddy live concert
oh
wind sound isn't really working oh you
have to learn the character first Kiara
oh my God
character but you gotta kind of learn
this because you immediately recognize
that I haven't learned it
sorry yeah
I mean I am going easy
to learn the character while you're
absolutely obliterating me it's only
because I'm just now realizing it I'm
sorry I'm sorry you should go train with
the character Oh I thought you were
roasting me you fought ah you men would
like feel free to use me as a punching
bag okay yeah
yeah here look let's start off on a
different foot okay try some attacks
okay okay
uh so I know this is light what what
does it do it's just a nice punch with
the handle of my Katana or so we're
using a controller yes okay good
um I recommend so a lot so all of these
buttons If you just push them once have
like a different attack there's like you
know different there's a light one a
medium one and a heavy one you kind of
want to mix them up yeah so like I've
been trying to do that yeah kind of try
and like do a mix-up um which will kind
of keep me from moving especially with
ayame if you if you get like a really
good mix-up and she has a she has a good
amount of range I think and I think she
also has a cool sword attack where like
it has so much range she has it go from
like the bottom of the screen I could do
like an arc is this oh yeah that one
that one yeah that's a really powerful
one
yeah okay you know the one thing that I
had issues with uh no matter how much I
tried was the what do they call them the
motion thingy where it goes in a circle
yeah like the the quarter Circle half
circle yeah I never got it it was always
just a coincidence after five minutes of
trying
ah yeah that that stuff is yeah it's
kind of difficult to figure out in the
beginning
um I feel like I just do it with random
buttons and see what comes out sometimes
I've learned like a lot of the moves but
sometimes I'm just like what if I do
this especially with a character I don't
know so you'll be surprised what comes
out if you do like a hat oh the timer
yes suspending all right um yeah you'll
be surprised what comes out sometimes if
you try um like different 40 circles you
shot me in the head girl I did I did
sorry about that
at least you let me have some hits in
the beginning yeah are you are you
trying right now I don't think you're
trying but I want you to look I
recommended the character to you so one
more question though
um L1 activates the the bar uh for like
for example my Kiwa support right but uh
only when the Super Chat bar is full
yeah yes but then what about the other
bar that says Max right now for me the
golden one
uh let's see there's like different ones
right
I'm pretty sure so they're like two
different levels of collab I believe for
example with Marian she has one where
she jumps out and grabs you and then she
has an even stronger one where her ship
comes out and shoots you oh that one I
believe I mean I believe it's that you
need to do a quarter circle plus heavier
special for that so you can't just press
a button cool yeah it's actually heavy
yeah that will never happen or special
or special either one of those buttons
works but yeah you have to do it I mean
they're not that if you have a
controller it's it's really not hard it
is
again I just gotta practice it
I want like the big kiwama move
here okay let's try all right I want to
see a big Chihuahua mold all right take
the joystick yeah and just just keep
just keep doing it just keep trying to
do a quarter Circle and then heavy don't
don't press heavy too
oh congratulations you won
no way rematch rematch rematch okay okay
rematch rematch that'll be pretty cool
you need to get the bar full again
though if you want to try yeah I'll try
that again
the golden one fills up with hits and
the other one with uh time right or
right yeah yeah
um yeah you need to use your special to
gather super chats I believe I think
there are other little ways of
collecting super chats but there are too
many for me to attention to
wait if I have one
uh one of those half golden bars full
can I already use it because it says one
now I think it's just telling you what
your progress is I don't think you can
use it I think it needs to be yellow
okay at least from my from what I
remember experiencing but
down forward as with the d-pad and have
you tried using the d-pad for the corner
thingies
uh the D you mean the analog stick uh oh
you oh oh I know what you're talking
about okay yeah yeah
um no I have not because apparently you
can use that one too but okay I mean to
me those are just kind of like buttons
again okay so like it doesn't quite
mimic like this I don't think they can
mimic the circular motion of like the
joystick as well yeah I think it's a
little harder they're saying it's easier
though they're all saying really let me
try
um Slide the pump over the deepest but
it hurts wait it hurts my thumb wait
d-pad they mean the the four different
um Arrow thingies right yeah I think
that that's what they mean
Direction pad yeah that's what it should
be from where do I even start though on
the right one and then go to the left
one
sorry no problem
I know are we
yeah
we're still learning
excited down and then bottom to what
deep
uh start with down and then so where to
write depends on the direction you're
facing I believe okay sure if it's a
back quarter Circle then if you're
facing in my direction you'll go from
bottom to left
um
they're trying to some of them were like
trying to teach me with the Emojis uh
arrows but it makes no sense to me
because there's a diagonal one and I
don't have a diagonal one on my d-pad so
I don't know what you're trying to tell
me yeah there is no depth you kind of
have to do both at the same time I think
um
okay I got it ready let's try Okay
that wasn't it
you keep trying
oh but you don't have the meter full
actually you don't have the meter for it
hang on I need to win this one
so we get another round
oh you did manage to use yourself oh
that's pretty that's the under one
that's the simple one that I can
activate with L one yeah well two is
enough
okay now we have more time for you to
get your your meter up okay okay no they
say it's enough though
oh it's I thought you had to be at Max
okay
I trust them more than myself I don't
use the collabs very much do I have to
hit to do that though no I'm freeze no
um it depends on the it depends on the
assist I believe okay so for example
with muddings I don't really need to hit
she'll just come out swingings but I
don't know about for you no okay then
let's stop hurting Callie
um
[Music]
wait squat I don't get it
I really can't do it
why not just try the analog stick
pretend it's like a joystick at like an
arcade yeah I've been trying with that
one to going back on the floor
oh what was that that wasn't it huh it
looked a little bit fancier
I'm not sure if that was just your
special or not down to left then special
the special is the bottom button ah oh
[Music]
um
back
uh
I wish I was there with you so I could I
could show you physically I should put
on a hand cam
oh
that was That was supposed
okay I think you're I think you're kind
of getting the button mashing part
you're figuring it out
[Applause]
there you go
okay oh man well regardless of the
um
the figuring out how to do the special
move how about we have a regular battle
now that it seems you've kind of gotten
anything okay okay
Kelly's gonna kill me I'm not I'm not
come on you don't need to be so afraid
yeah but Mash oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
yeah
[Music]
this makes you pretty cool to me no
because like you know not good I might
uh be better than you in Minecraft but
in this game you're currently better
than me
I mean thanks the way that the way that
it's described is against people I can't
really play against people that are good
at fighting games but against casuals I
have a little more a little more winning
ability just a little bit oh
it was dead soon because I know how to
block Etc
basic stuff
I'm just trolling on you with this
little diagonal right here that one is
fun too
on fire
[Laughter]
because I can block
congratulations
and I don't wanna what do you mean you
don't wanna you need to yeah
no it's not
I'll try a different one too
I think yes uh well I'm still going to
use both of them but you can use whoever
you feel most comfortable with thus far
it could be boats on too there are such
things as mirror matches
ah no no no no no no no
I'll try it
I felt like I had kind of fun of Coco
Senpai even though she's also difficult
a little bit more difficult she's
intermediate
hold on a second I just realized
something I just realized
freaking
sorry my speakers okay no problem
I did decent with Corazon you think so
really
all right I'm ready to go whenever
you're ready
[Music]
um
it goes off ense can kill your opponents
defense makes it so you don't get
murdered by hitting people hitting
buttons
oh well
I'll learn this is my first time playing
a fighting game ever since I was like
five years old or so obviously there's a
big learning curve yeah I mean
it's not uncommon it'll be fun do we
know virtual uh what was a virtual
fighter
I've heard of that before yeah so I only
played that a little bit while I was
playing Yakuza because it was
um a mini game in Yakuza yeah and they
said I wasn't bad at it but I wouldn't
really count it because it was really
just a short mini game
yeah
that's kind of cool Oh you mean like an
arcade game within the game yeah exactly
I see I love that skill I love that I
mean it's a good one
it feels really difficult to dodge too
yeah because it's a grab yeah
well wait how how much how long I got
you
meme
you gotta get better at the dodging
you can't toss Minecraft her grab is so
good
oh I did
sometimes I forget which one I am
oh what the
uh my bum my
[Music]
well then you should be fine in fact you
can play games for longer now over here
thanks movie that makes no sense to me
if it's numb you should know this you're
a long time gamer Harry don't you miss
your kitto yes I'm dying I feel pain
every single day and I cry every night
all right
yeah when are you going back if you can
stay soon okay in a couple weeks
just need a little more time oh a couple
weeks damn so long yeah that's a bit of
a bit of a while like summer
all right
girl
girl move
both sounds really I believe in the boat
downstairs
you are really strong right now
I don't think they need to be nerfed
that's not a request for nerves please
please don't make them weaker
I really believe those guys are like the
ones to beat right now
you got it blocked
you just gotta hold up
I have to take a step back and that
sucks really do try putting the cursor
or the another cursor sorry um the
analog sticking like the bottom right
corner yeah
yeah
you mean when I'm on the right side
right yeah yeah exactly so like as
though you're like leaning back pretend
you're like leaning back the opposite
direction going back is it not
I mean not quite here let me show you
don't hurt me okay don't hurt me let me
show you all right so here's just a
typical Crouch right you just go down
and see look I'm I'm holding back and
Crouch but I'm not necessarily moving
backward
so this would be like a low block yeah
okay so if you tried to hit me come over
and try to hit me
oh and you drive me
okay
and what if I just go down it doesn't
work
ah
yeah but it's explaining it better to me
than the game however the weakness of
this block
wow I'm glad I feel confident in just
this moment uh the weakness of this
block so let me hit you with a regular
attack but this is the weakness
you can attack from above from the sky
yes right that wasn't a very good aerial
attack that I tried to demonstrate right
now
okay you can fight me for real
sure okay
foreign
that's all that it is
I mean it's cool you made it through the
virtual Frontier though but I actually
leave that up to your impeccable RPG
skills yeah it reminded me of slate
Aspire like it had the same system going
on with like shops in between and little
um surprise I don't know what they're
called little little thingies nice burst
yeah oh did I activate the first or did
you
no you did you when you did that that
red explosion that kind of it said
Invincible on it when you fill your
burst meter you can use that to get out
of any sticky situation I learned that
but I already forgot how to activate it
so that was just an accident
I mean I don't know maybe I just got it
from Guilty Gear whenever I burst I just
press all the buttons at once is it kind
of the same as one of them
do all the fighting games have similar
controls okay
um I would say they're it kind of
depends I mean I think a lot of them
follow a similar model of like slash
heavy heavy well maybe not heavy slash
that kind of seems guilty gear-ish
I don't know I don't know what I'm
talking about
yeah they're only in the beginning
and then you'll be fine you'll probably
beat me once you learn how to block
it'll be easy
yes pretty good do you love the memes
ah you love the meme so much y'all that
grab is the only thing I can do to get
you to stop doing things well Coco is a
Grappler so it makes sense that she has
like the strongest
so like I just did a burst there
you're scream
yeah
just chilling just chilling just hanging
out yeah
chilling the chilling stream
yeah just a chill stream
ing
[Music]
of course yeah it's because I remember
them that I want to play with you
do you want to do use a different
character yes yeah
you know I'll use a different character
too okay I'll use cornet let me use
somebody I don't know how to play as
really well
um
I'll play I'll try actually Sora
who is this again guys
the skin who is that again
I think so oh okay yeah color wise it
makes sense
because of the Japanese looking clothes
oh that's true but I think it might be
the hairstyle
um
all right
did you see the Taurus Empire on suicide
Senpai that looks really like to watch
Empire
oh wait hold on a sec I want to see hang
on
that looks like really really good go on
Thursday Senpai yeah yeah that that
really blew my mind and I was like
which support should I use I really
don't know most of them
I'll I'll use music I will see how that
one goes
that has a Moonlight costume super good
yeah
yeah it's brown nice
animals
I don't know the controls for these but
I'm just gonna try and figure it out
while I while I play again let's go
say now we're on a decent plate Level
Playing Field hey
you'll still win
maybe not you'd be surprised I don't
know character well I've been using
Boton this whole time and characters
have very different play Styles so if I
try to play it Sora like both on it
might not go so well
by simply pressing the same buttons I do
is both on
or not have the same
wait how did I you'll be you'll be again
Russian for this attack
pressure oh what's that soda
I actually did the first on purpose I'm
so proud and everyone
too yeah although you are killing me
[Music]
I don't know
pretty good it was so close
let's go
Callie are you letting me win no no
I'm not doing anything like that
why would I do that why would I
embarrass myself on your scream in front
of all these people all right you're
here to impress everyone right and teach
me how to play the game oh now you're
actually winning I
on your own oh yeah I did okay one more
let's go
nice bone camera
oh that's pretty cute
[Music]
Lifesaver why does soda says I have a
lightsaber did I miss something
this is the Lord It's the Lord
trust the Lord don't question it don't
question me I think it's a good light
ah okay yeah that makes sense
wasted my burst
okay well I'm happy I want one
did win a match yeah
yay yay let's try it again but the more
time we spend on these characters the
more you get to know Surah Senpai while
I'm not really learning anything I don't
think that's true I think that there are
a lot of things you pick up just by
playing the character yeah a little bit
I learned how to do the burst
oh my God that's pretty and the burst
can save you in a lot of awful
situations so if someone's putting a lot
of pressure on you and you need to get
away first if you have the first
should be fine
yeah
sort of sent by just straight up doesn't
have an attack
I'll just try and do some some Gatling
combos
what does mio said by jewels
I'm actually not sure so
maybe damage different effects
[Music]
thank you
I'm pretty sure I wonder if there is
somebody in in live who is like a
seasoned fighting game player oh I feel
like a corn on the sample might actually
have experience
but I'm not I fit chat knows oh maybe
cool
I don't know you know Street Fighter
yeah of course there's this new Street
Fighter game coming out right the Sixers
so actually
um
when I was in high school I had this
best friend who was also a weak just
like me
she eventually moved to Japan she's been
living there for years now and working
as an illustrator really successfully
and she did a lot of Street Fighter six
uh illustrations like backgrounds and
all that
oh yeah that's pretty cool yeah
flexing with my friend so I actually
want to play it just to see what she
Drew okay my friend did that oh
be like hey my friend did yeah exactly
exactly and now I thought you were gonna
say your friend also did that no no no
no
no no no no no
I have no fighting game creating friends
maybe you do who knows
without knowing you never know because I
was also surprised when she told me
yeah a long time ago I like um
I actually did like a support
um on like different avenues like
patreons and stuff like that oh I'm like
illustrators of like um what I say more
Indie fighting games I guess like I
don't want to say 2D I don't think they
were 2D necessarily like animators that
did like 2D projects for some like
independent fighting games that actually
did pretty well I won't say the names of
them for keeping said people's privacy
some of those guys still follow me
[Music]
while you were talking yeah
the way to win you got to get them
talking
so by Cream to me and Pio Pio Tetris
remember when we just said you were part
of it right that collab back in the day
yeah people didn't believe I'd played
the game before I was like are you guys
new
okay
who made this yeah again there may there
may have been some new folks that do not
remember that so it was spotted even I
think it was a sponsored stream
okay see you're getting a lot better at
the character hell yeah
you're actually really
um making my experience much better like
like my enjoyment
I'm glad to hear that otherwise I was
just like what the am I doing yeah
yeah well it can be kind of difficult
trying to figure it out without like a
friend there with you
it sounds like you found your main qo
ing the tutorial they were making me use
Kona but even if the tutorial wasn't
having me do that I would have still
wanted to use Kona Because You Loved
Conan and she seems fun to use
yeah
you're welcome thank you for giving me a
win
no no like I said I didn't give that to
you I just really suck at Sora I don't
understand how to play her yeah yeah
well time to train the Surah Senpai next
Cali yeah yeah I guess now I'm happy
with both on both on meta devs please
don't change anything please don't
change Bhutan in any way aside from the
the voice oh they already did it seems
the voice yeah yeah very nice also I
want to switch characters I'm not going
to play both of them but I wanted to
maybe choose a different one really
quick I think it would probably be good
to at least have like another main that
you could always oh yes yeah
for a bit it was so sad but then I
actually got into online matches with
this say and playing against other
people and I was like ah this isn't
gonna work oh why are you playing with
randos
yeah oh not on stream or anything just
for fun oh yeah I guess we that that
could be also a stream idea though just
playing your hands try to get into the
lobby play against your idol yeah some
of the others uh have also been doing
that as well I believe I know that they
in Iris I believe were doing matches
against uh well they're against fans I
guess so you know they do the they give
the code but then yeah people are really
fast I actually I didn't say anything
but for iris's stream I was trying so
hard to just get in to her Lobby
no no I don't I don't want to do that
there
but that's kind of don't want to be a
nuisance it seems like Super Smash
Brothers but without the leg
yeah exactly because it wasn't lagging
that's definitely a good thing
I don't know I think the aristocrats are
having fun with Iris I didn't want to
barge in I thought it would be cool
though if I just popped in though it'd
be like Dad hello is that really Cali
yeah apparently it's really difficult oh
man so many people playing this right
now I'm really happy for the deaf so you
know such a popular big success now you
know it's free it's free
yeah free game why all these fan games
they publish them for free pretty much
all of them like Holo cure too but they
put years of work in it and like so much
effort into it and they don't ask for
any money man they just love whole life
yeah but it makes me feel bad because
for this one what they spent like two
years or more on it
it makes me feel bad like damn and so
many people are playing it I feel like
at least like a cash shop for cute new
outfits or so
is acceptable like take our money
I think the way that you can also think
about it because I don't want you to
feel too too bad about it I feel like
the thing is I think this is kind of a
reward for them right getting to see the
people they dedicated the game to play
and react to it yeah and I just realized
they're not allowed to charge money
anyway
they literally can't which is the only
reason I say that otherwise I'd be like
yes charge money because it's impossible
I think you know the best way to repay
is to just enjoy to the fullest and I'm
definitely gonna stream this game
several more times and um I actually you
I know you saw the the message that I'm
I'm planning a little something already
just say it if you're going to say it
like that just say it already Kelly okay
geez I would like to run a tournament
for this this game I've already kind of
put in like the permissions request for
permissions for um we're gonna do a live
tournament uh yeah yeah I saw it and I'm
like hmm I was I saw the message before
I started playing this game for the
first time today and I'm I was like yeah
yeah it sounds fun I'll I'll probably
participate and now that I played it I'm
really bad at it I'm like hmm well let's
hope that the others aren't so good at
it either
I think a lot of people are starting on
like um a similar skill level which is
good but I did I do want to give
everybody like a decent amount of time
to practice so probably won't like do
anything for real until like late June
maybe I think is the earliest that I
would do something like that so people
have time to practice practice learn how
to block learn how to block yeah oh no
the best
what do you say the best defense is a
strong offense all right you kill him
quick enough yeah but that's not how
this works
if you don't learn how to block right
you mean I can never defeat Bhutan or
no Oh you mean the real question is the
tournament yeah
yeah because she has some some skill
apparently chat was saying Luna has some
skill well I don't expect to win against
all those with experience but yeah well
you might surprise yourself I mean for
example who was it was it Iris that like
didn't know anything about Mario maker
and then actually got pretty good her
team yeah
her team absolutely kicked out yeah
that's great so you never know oh you
can learn to get super good are you
planning to have Japanese members
participate in the tournament or yeah
yeah I was thinking uh enjp ID
well if that's a live tournament if
there's a lot of
um uh participants then you could do it
like the Mario Kart Club where you have
like like two different categories after
the first initial rounds where then you
have a taco cup for the bad ones to to
win something too yeah that would be
cool yeah but I would appreciate that
a Redemption bracket for the losers to
also have a chance to be a winner yeah
yeah do you also want to participate
though right you don't want to just host
it of course I would like to but I'll
probably be kind of busy but we'll see
maybe get some some assets commissioned
for it and stuff like that I love doing
things like that yeah well I'll I'll
I'll try even though I'm not good I'll
try to be there
yeah of course I mean only if you if you
want to if it if it's just a fun thing
you know at the end of the day what do
we get you know the glory I guess no
glory for me
it's okay
you might surprise yourself well cool
now I was doing pretty good no no no you
didn't have a
category where you know you choose what
you want to choose and then also
category with random you just random
a random match I like that well I'll do
some brainstorming with the with the
company and see what we can come up with
you could also do a mirror match
mirror matches yeah this could be fun
we'll find a way to mix it up to make it
interesting so alrighty I think it's a
good note for me to end it on Albertson
super chat but thank you can we you're
welcome that was fun yeah thanks for
inviting me thank you have a nice day
thanks a lot I'm writing songs all day
and then I'm playing with slime so I
don't know if you actually you don't
like ASMR
yeah but like slime is so pretty and fun
to play with like I've been really into
it before I go to sleep these days all
crunchy with like the hands and anyway
I'm gonna go now have fun with Dad I'll
do my best bye bye see you later
kfp bye
yay I gotta win I can't believe it
I have to turn on the light in my room
I was like I was like once I was like
really focusing on the button
buttons not doing not doing it blindly
and when Cali was using a character that
she didn't know well then
you're fat what's that
I popped off this corner yeah
but I have to say the the Coco Senpai
grab is like overpowered damn
that was the only thing that I could
ever get Cali with when she was playing
as botan the only thing
the only chance the only way in
oh
I think the devs should at least have a
coffee open or a patron or whatever
just saying
take our money
oh grabs are unblockable like literally
this but not every character has a grab
do they
I haven't noticed one on everybody the
deaf super chatted me oh oh I don't know
if I can get to it uh within this stream
because I still have a little bit of a
backlog which one is it
is it this one that guy Nicholas
no that's not it is it
you can cancel you you have to avoid
crabs if a cat that has one eh I'll have
at least one fro that's not a grab is it
it was a pinky
ooh wait wait I can find it
I found it
wait you're the one you're the one the
art can do you call the artist deaths
too but you're the one who is kfp and
you're the one who drew the the art uh
was it this one this one for example is
up there right now because there's so
many different Arts
High attention artist and UI logo design
oh I really like the UI and the logos
the only thing that I didn't like about
the interface was you know those green
and yellow fonts
the the smaller ones I've been watching
your sensor e and debut so I was very
happy when we made your inclusion for
the game hope you enjoyed Kitty key oh
what do you like why are you influencing
because not everybody is in there were
you like influencing like hey hey hey we
need a Chihuahua assist at least come on
please
yes then thank you
thank you sir
[Music]
I'm glad that there was one kfp among
the devs
maybe someday but I just wonder like if
it took them two years to make this
it'll take a long time to get everyone a
playable character right
[Laughter]
[Music]
maybe need more help maybe the team
needs volunteers
if the credits show the devs or she is
oh interesting all right
why do I do it
let me see okay
top credited Project Director project
funder recruiter
guns
oh
what's the scroll
like that
but I don't recognize all of the washing
marks like this old pekkooshi
what's the flower again
um
nobody
[Applause]
and there's a mini game in the credit oh
[Music]
this is a mini game for me
guessing which ones are which
is
[Music]
wow
what the how can you be nobody
watching the book the book
[Music]
a book who's about books
our best but that's what I don't know I
don't remember those I only remember
remember girls Mark that was I think
hatama then
the song is so cute
and I still don't know
[Music]
the paper that's Rico that's Miko and
Iris and Zeta
it's set up
the scroll Santa okay oh what are all
these names
[Music]
thank you
someone passed
what
rest in peace what
uh what
[Music]
others sad
is it good is it the looping
present
okay
what
what what
that's uh that made me sad
oh
what they worked on it for most of the
time because you said 2023
wow
my condolences
last week they added it though okay
um we're gonna read super chatos uh the
gaming part is done for now
let's go to my office
I turned the button off don't worry guys
what am I doing down here
oh no don't look at my buttons the other
buttons
Rachel
and I put my leg down now I'm kind of
exhausted all that leg Action Man
oh sure
there's still other buttons yeah you can
see right you didn't see all my buttons
Don't Look at My Buttons and don't match
them either
you can't match those buttons you
literally can't
oh
potential jump scare what do you mean
I didn't jump I didn't scare you did I
oh
okay now looks good now we need bgm how
about
how about this one
another oldie
you wanna cut in half no no no no no no
no no you don't know what's below the
table
okay I'm glad there's at least one kfp
there man nice to see thank you Nicole
and thanks for watching since the
beginning I'll I'll read the super chats
now though not from this stream but from
where we left off
are you sure
I'm still up yeah why not why not
um
well I'm sorry I couldn't show you like
professional uh play uh Style
uh but
I hope it was fun nonetheless for me it
was fun especially playing with Cali
so if she does a tournament for real if
there's enough time
I'll try oh didn't see that I'll try to
train a little bit at least like one or
two characters and focus on those
um
yeah because it looks like fun
and if I'm lucky I get matched up with
someone who's just as bad as me and then
as long as I make it for one round one
round that would be nice I don't expect
to win but one round
you might have done well on that
um who said furlough did you watch
one to the Mario stream
did you
are you sure I would have done well
yes you did yeah yeah you you watch a
lot of my streams so I'm confused
you have lots of room to grow that is so
nice of you to say
I mean
I mean I saw like Ina playing uh like
her first stream from her training Arc
and she was pretty bad yeah uh I don't
know how she did in the end did she
improve
because maybe if she can improve them
then maybe I could have improved too who
knows
she did she got bird you mean her group
got bird
and she was carried or do you mean she
on her own got burned
team got burned saying her team got
burned so it wasn't she teamed with some
really good ones like bang was really
good that's all I mean
you are saying he's saying so proudly
she got five
[Laughter]
yeah it was good and when I saw Bales
playing she was good even though she was
new oh
I'm not throwing it I'm just being real
like from what I saw uh from Ina
it was oh yeah about as good as me when
playing Mario
oh
yeah
the lag of course everyone over
that was affected by it some groups
weren't so much affected
but yeah
she spies about the snitch
wow
they're nice I mean come on even if you
snitch eat a nose right
you don't know she's not as good as like
what who's the best anyway who who was
like really the the bestest
is just someone who was absolutely
killing it
Anna oh but yeah she didn't really get
to play much did she I saw she had
struggles
no internet uh
that's so unfortunate
really
wow
yeah
how
I saw one friend with like Marine sale
by being really fast too
my new sample was doing really well
Yoshi
I didn't stay until the end I didn't
know wow
impressive
fun is correct
he's just playing the hardest laughs
possible oh yeah I saw a little bit of
that that's like yeah
it's like uh
like polar ice bath
training
you just train yourself with really
extreme challenges
even if you fail at those it will make
you better in the end at the easy things
I guess
yeah yeah impossible levels
[Music]
it seems like it helped
okay guys what's up chats are you
reading did I write passport 22 I think
I did so is it the Hotline Miami next
I think it might be
I'm not that far away
okay okay
oh thumbnails
it's Sunday guys it's the end of the
week have you realized
damn
I was like
rushing and grinding for the week that's
what it felt like to me like every day
there was the week started was like less
not so many streams but I still felt
there was so much going on the whole
week
for me
I'm glad the week is over I'll take it
more easy next week
and tomorrow I gotta record because I
didn't get to record today
ah ah another another
Diablo open better
another one huh
I don't know if I want to participate in
the next better because you know I
already did play it in the previous
battle
no need to play it again I'm already
gonna be busy with other games
stress test right
um and then there's a tell Cali to check
it out
well that's a good idea let me tell her
um
can we can we can we can we
carry if you're interested
weekend
is it on the weekends on the weekend
Diablo 5 has another open beta
we have
perms I put light on another awesome
better
time
and it was really really good
four
just if you've got time and interest to
play it I'm recommending it
because in the future I also wanna play
with pony
and we can do a squat
she's already interested
she's like oh
same weekend as Eurovision oh don't
worry I don't think Kelly will be
watching Eurovision
oh
[Music]
the release when is the relation like
July
June 6th
oh wait that's not that's one month to
go
wow
oh well
yeah I don't think she may be not have
uh will have time for this weekend but
at least she's aware
ah they want the
can I say the S words
say say
s-a-t-a-n can I say that
they want that number
Santa yes Santa Claus number
I can't I want to be careful you know
because there's isn't there like you
know some some satanistic
Cults or whatever I mean
they surely also Santa Claus quotes
right
you think they want me to I mean I mean
you know it's like you know even if they
don't they might hear about me
mentioning it and then they're gonna
Target me just like the Illuminati
and then I will suddenly disappear oh
God oh God I'm scared I'm I'm I'm I'm
I'm scaring myself
um
mm-hmm
all right let's read super chatos from
Hotline Miami that was so much fun I
want to play it again next week
let's see if I can schedule it
is
Hotline Miami
what did I say
what did I say Fuji television that was
a scary dream who said that who
remembers that who brings that up
and cell
uh
-huh
oh I also noticed while I was fighting
with Kelly I did notice the the kfb in
the background
noise
watching the archive but that was fun
you're pretty good ah you mean Hotline
Miami
oh I had to get good though
I had to get into it it was very new for
me but it was fun
yeah big plus but very much screamo I'm
practicing my screamo voice
no I'm not upset I mean they only have
like what how many characters that you
can play
one two three four five six seven eight
eight or sell and then a couple skins
for each
oh no
you can't they would have done everybody
they would have apparently probably
needed even more time with another year
or so so it's okay
um
no problemo
if they did everyone but me then I would
be sad
yeah yeah this just looked pretty like
chihuahua in this outfit
look very pretty in the pixel art
yeah we have so many characters now with
characters we have so many people now
in whole life too that
it is
challenging too it is it's it's not nice
to ask you know the man put us all in
but
surely they want to at some point
I was teased
oh I wonder how difficult you'll be to
play
mmm
maybe I'll make her my main one she
gets released
oh she's already in the files oh you
guys are looking through the files
that's illegal
wait the directional inputs
you're saying that and you're making me
think of arrows and her laugh
her inputs are just her laughing every
time you press something on the d-pads
you should laugh
ah
you know
like in the clips they always put arrows
for her laughs I love that
write it down write it down
yeah I love that
look that's exactly that what they do
I'm so funny
okay let me get started on the
superchargers okay
Jacob 47 thanks for the pinky can't
imagine telling 2020 me Kiana would be
playing Hotline Miami one day looking
forward to the Stream
thank you well actually well actually I
agree with that statement but you know
this fan art that I use
is from 2020 I think
yeah I dug it out somebody saw me back
then and thought Oh would be funny to do
a fan art
of Hotline Miami kiwawa
and I don't think I understood nah I
mean 100 I did not understand the ref
reference back then
yeah yeah I wonder I wonder I was
checking the person's uh Twitter account
I was like stalking after I put up the
font nail I was checking back to see if
they reacted to me digging it up but I
don't think they reacted I checked a
couple times
I'm not sure
I feel like they maybe didn't
Stock Show yeah I was wondering I
thought oh I actually made them very
happy if they see it
a death Crow tree tweeted of Hotline
Miami
what do you mean
this stream
no they seem to act check again
why did they react for now
well let me track that no no no
the artist follows you yo
why what did you do
and where is my where is a tweet
call
there it is
called more skulls called no there's
nothing
no they they tweeted since but or like
retweeted stuff since
when they you know often fan artists
when I use their art for thumbnail they
often um uh they like retweeted
uh but no nothing
not even a like so they probably didn't
see it even though I tagged them
they probably don't even know they also
follow me but
I didn't like the tweets so they
probably don't know
I was hoping they'll be like damn that's
such an old fan art how did you remember
find it
I mean I don't care that much I feel
like they would
yes I looked at the likes I looked at
the replies I see nothing it's not like
I care I I don't I don't care
that chicken is doing it voluntarily of
course what do you how do you even
assume that there would be the chicken
would be earning money
of course it's just voluntarily
my chickens don't ask for money from me
why would they
ridiculous
I don't hire chickens
that want money from me
all right back to Super Chat where was I
here ah yeah Jacob
you're welcome
you and everyone else I know you were
very surprised
and yeah I think like the visuals
normally wouldn't really appeal to me
but you guys at some point recently for
some reason were like pushing it onto me
and I think because it was also on sale
like somebody mentioned oh it's on sale
and then more people said Miami
and then I was like hmm yeah okay
I guess
I needed short games and I saw botan
playing it one looked okay
hmm
yeah
you guys kept on saying you love the
hola Miami
don't don't you think don't you assume
that this is gonna work every time now
no no no no no no
you can't make me play any game like
this
it really doesn't work
this was an exception
of
mind manipulation
that worked
it doesn't always like no no no no no no
no no
no but Xenoblade is the game that I'm
actually interested in
but I think as a streaming game
it would be even worse than uh or or on
par
with a certain other long game we
recently finished
um it's it's very long from my knowledge
and yeah
it's much shorter than fine Bloom really
well still
I've heard people say it's not a good
streaming game and I mean a lot of the
games I play just by being
jrpgs and that being an unpopular
category to stream and watch
um a lot of it is already unpopular
I'm just trying to not make it
much worse
um
I would love to like you know
I I
envy Subaru Senpai a little bit because
the water said bye plays like
you know the RPGs just like me like
tails off
Symphonia and it goes really well same
for pecula you know
um
I think jpgs work better for Japanese
audience in general
like they're more
more open and accepting and supportive
of that
it's just you know they come from Japan
and
they know these games and probably also
a lot of the audience played these games
already so they don't mind watching the
story and all that unfold again
they don't get spoilered and just
generally there's like more of an
interest for it more of a market
I think
so yeah
it's a bit unfortunate because I really
think these games that I do play I think
they deserve more love and more
attention
I think they should be on par in terms
of like viewer numbers
as other popular games that is my my
personal opinion
I don't see why they're wait I don't see
a good reason why
it shouldn't be like that
so good
more interesting than a stupid shooting
pew pew game
no
yeah beautiful visuals Beautiful Stories
beautiful characters
this is more interesting to watch I
don't get it
um and yeah tears of the kingdom is
gonna be interesting because I think you
know in the western audience it's way
more
um
welcome
than other
J yes I'm gonna say jrpgs that I've
played
um but it's still gonna be a long series
and people don't want to get spoilered
or they're playing themselves they don't
have time to watch and play for ETC so I
feel like it's my it's also not do so
well
um but oh well
oh well
it's okay
I wondered I wonder I wonder
we'll see how it goes but
um
I think maybe
one of the first
one of the first few episodes like one
two
will do well and then
soon after a lot of people accept my
regulars will be like all right I'm I'm
done I have commitment issues I can't
watch more than two episodes of a long
Series yeah
yeah yeah yeah
I don't play along oh yeah well good
luck I hope you're fast
but it's okay I'll be slow
that's how it is with most streaming
like long streaming series
it just falls off after a while but I
don't want to end the playthrough just
because it falls off you know I feel
like that's
outwardly
I'll finish it
even if I lost 50 percent of the
viewership
don't care that's no
um
not choosing these games because of the
numbers obviously otherwise I wouldn't
play them
[Music]
um
elderly I didn't uh stop playing because
of viewership I stopped because I felt
like it was really frustrating for me
gameplay wise
um
reply to Kelly
don't blame you there hmm
[Music]
more dedicated ones
yeah
I guess so yeah
Western RPGs like what
why not why not you guys like in the end
you can be like try this try this try
this and that and I've tried other games
like besides jrpgs but what I'm trying
to say is I will continue playing a
variety of games such as of course still
jrpgs no matter if they have views
because I love them and I will not
completely replace them with other games
just because they do better so it
doesn't matter
yeah I don't mind like looking into
Skyrim or Oblivion or whatever
and eventually and until now I've also
played I think Western RPGs probably as
well
or just Western games in general
that's that's not the
the conversation we're having here I
think
I'm just standing my ground and
protecting the jrpg honor
checking the honor I want to have more
appreciation
for
chair peaches
um
yeah if I give up on those games
completely
I don't think I'll be enjoying my
my job as much anymore
a lot of games will just be me playing
them because I got nothing else to play
and
you know they won't be my first choices
and yeah they might still be fun
because games like Hotline Miami okay
for example wasn't my first choice was
was fun
but then I need like longer series
to Carry Me Through The Years because I
can play one shot games all the time
and if we're talking along a series
that that kind of needs to be something
I enjoy
because if it's more than free streams
or so
and it's a game that I I don't really
like passionately enjoy
and it's gonna be rough to get through
it
the GTA was a lot of fun something like
GTA is fine you know
yeah yeah
but I'm not gonna basically what I'm
saying is I'm not gonna force myself to
play
uh games that are popular I'm gonna
bring in the numbers just because I've
said this many times just because
they're bringing numbers I'm not gonna
do that
you guys know that
and if you expect anything else
I don't know why you expect anything
else
if it's just like short One-Shot games
you know I'll consider certain ones
but especially as a series
that's difficult if it's not something
I'm really interested in
no
I'm so hungry I'm gonna eat some of you
now
Red Dead Redemption
that one's fine
that's fine
I mean you guys are yummy
Babel
I requested favor a long time ago I
think never heard back
I think I requested all of them
who's the publisher
another attack
yeah because I played Fable one I guess
when I was a child
it's kind of traumatic though it wasn't
like isn't that the game where like in
the beginning probably that was probably
the beginning everything's like burning
was that fable
right now
what was that about why was everything
burning I don't even remember
I just remember things are burning it
was kind of traumatic
yeah the village
that's right in the beginning right
yeah yeah yeah
that's the problem of the original
publisher just disappears
then it's really difficult to get perms
um
ah you guys know you guys played the
game huh
abandonware is a problem yeah
it's nice when you guys know what I'm
talking about
um
if it's the game that I think you mean
I have a physical copy of that for like
five years or so now
that's pretty but that's also not very
long is it
yeah it's pretty short
this short came green Style with my old
laptop fable
came pre-installed did you buy the
laptop second hand
what
I don't think
Microsoft sells laptops as a set with
fable
pre-install
is it yeah I love black and white
I love that I feel like I also asked for
black and white too but I think black
and white is also abandoned where
thank you that's what I'm saying thanks
for the member message
so much abandon where I'm so sad I'm so
sad
I was worried that I couldn't play a
Sims one for that reason
because it's hard to get I mean Sims one
isn't quite abandon aware but it's kind
of you can't even buy it in the EA shop
all right
how's that going
um
I uh I I figured things out more or less
it's playable now
uh and I checked with genma
if I can
she said yeah
and
it's just one thing now
Colin Stearns me
yeah so I'm just still not sure fine
shoot stream it
uh there's like a
a graphic glitch
glitch when zooming out
um
[Music]
and normally I wouldn't even zoom out
that much anyway but when you switch
Maps
when you move for the neighborhood it uh
defaults back to the most
um zoomed out option
and then you will see the glitch
and I don't know if that's a problem
[Music]
well
ah
the s sims I played that one you mean
the one what's it called
no I know which one you mean I play that
one it was very different from normal DS
games
Magic the Gathering developmentally Ah
that's interesting but I also haven't
heard back from my magic the Gathering
request
um
was it herbs there were two or three
even
there were a bunch of DS Sims games
different ones
yeah the aliens one I I played the
aliens one
yeah yeah yeah there's like some aliens
or so and you have to collect those
those
uh those sticks and throw them in a
generator or something like that
you're cleaning the floor with a
mop or so I don't know
oops was my favorite back in the day I
don't even remember if I played herbs
but I definitely watched a playproof
at some point
it's funny
well this there's this one game
one of the games that is on my most want
to playlist
but I can't because it's abandoned wear
is the movies
ever since
long time ago
that was I I think I asked about it but
you know with abandoned where it's
difficult It's Tricky no one replies
but it's so fun yeah that was so good
you can make movies
I told you before all those lion
head games man lioness
why why did you disappear you made good
games
what's the problem with lionhead games
lionhead Studios
all the games are legendary oh they were
bought
eh
then what happened why why don't if they
buy a company why don't they adopt the
babies
eh
the
did they just ditch the babies and throw
them in the trash what the hell
the Forgotten babies
um they didn't sell enough
I feel like if such a game was released
now in like the quality of games that is
possible now like adjusted I think it
would do really well
would it I don't know now there's like a
million times more games than there used
to be
but I feel like well
I would play it
[Music]
as my fable was released on Xbox and PC
but after trying to push connect too
much Min making why I had to make games
for that they closed
oh
so um
you want to see me playing racing game
go with me to the arcade
or watch my Mario Kart streams
or watch me play Euro Truck Simulator
one day that's a racing game right
Mario Kart doesn't count
you're so biased
oh well let me continue reading I
haven't read in a million years take it
monkey next year like it literally read
two super chats in like an hour
the gamer great dangers
and Jeff star thanks the two pink stick
wait free pink stickers what's going on
laugh
you're a big fan of Hotline Miami or
what
thank you so much you know what you get
a kiss for that because that's free
pinkies
man of little words but big ass stickers
thank you so much
I don't know why you never want to talk
to me
thank you for the support
black virgin Nike student black Richard
Duncan sure and black virgin donkey
shirt
for the pinky lucky wah wah
I can read your Korean name now too
wow
thank you for the pink super jacket
soon
death
ah I I have super hot somewhere in the
back of my mind for the future
thanks for recommending already who's
aware of it I'm planning on Sunday
trying it maybe
um
super hot
maybe even in VR although it looks
stressful
and the game Recreation ghost is a
coffee addicting thank you glad you're
enjoying the streams
endless
thanks for the red super chat from New
Zealand fancy Hotline Miami was a lot of
fun to watch glad I could watch it live
thanks for streaming ah because that
stream was kind of early in the day for
me wasn't it so must have been easier
for you to catch
you're welcome thank you for coming I'm
glad you enjoyed it it was a lot of fun
yeah
many many screams
and I know you guys enjoy
you are screaming like a monkey or like
a headless chicken
welcome to the member
and zebra
yeah what do you mean bro are you from
Australia
can a headless chicken scream
well internally yeah
it surely is screaming internally
thank you
mm-hmm
but you're basically Frozen sisters
stretch
yummy
what
sizing
yeah
that's a weird question
yeah I think austrians are very aware of
the size of other countries
that we are very small exactly because
we are small
I feel like maybe bigger countries are
often not so aware
sorry I got a bit frustrated during the
tutorial it wasn't on only the game's
fault it was also the chat making me
feel like flashbacks to
some other time where it was really
frustrating
yeah but then once I started button
mashing
smashing it was really fun
um I don't know Cali
you drove the entire length of Austria
to drive to the east coast Meetup
yeah Austria are very small
yeah I think we know like mostly like I
can like
roughly
imagine or guess
at least like visualize the size of
other countries I can't like tell you
how many people live in all countries
but
I mean I've seen the world map often
enough
y'all I feel like Austria probably fits
into Germany
for
at least four times if not five or six
if you cut it and then you know squeeze
it in everywhere like Tetris
Germany is pretty big
now Italy is big but it has a weird ass
shape
um Austria would probably fit
twice for three times maybe twice only
actually for
tomorrow it doesn't feel so big
weird shape it's really long but
boot shape
um
twice mentioned can I talk is there
twice fans here I need to I was gonna
tweet it yesterday but the more I
thought about it the more I thought the
most people who see this tweet will not
be able to relate
we have to talk
since I've been watching Charmed so much
I noticed something
and
I feel like probably most people will
not relate or understand
maybe only the two or three twice fans
but even those will probably not
understand what I'm talking about you
must also watch Charmed to understand
twice as Momo
with
dark straight hair
visualizer like recently she has dark
straight hair right first set me free
looks even though she's Asian
very similar to me
as
charms Pro
please
I feel like photos
there's not if you Google prove Charmed
then the pictures that come up are not
so good
you need to like look at like
screenshots from the actual show I would
say
they look so
ah
really
give me a sec boss okay okay okay okay
yeah and you can look up the actress too
I guess but the look that she hasn't
Charmed I feel like you know you see it
you
see you're Googling Google faster
thank you I mean not the old
Shannon Doherty because with all the
plastic surgery it should looks very
different but you know that's why I'm
saying charms doing her Charmed times
mm-hmm
just a place to see G Hill more really
I was thinking Momo
and I saw it especially in that like the
moment I noticed is when I re-watched
her uh I don't know what the guy was
called but she did that Rover uh YouTube
short right or Tick Tock probably too
bad what the why are you telling me
that me now make me jealous
um
but yeah in that Rover video I was
watching it again I was like wait a
second she looks like prune
especially in that video
we find a good side by side you should
tweet it that's what I was looking for
yesterday like pictures that really
prove my point but I couldn't really
find good ones
um that's why I was asking you to sing
twice really the high cheekbones you
maybe and I feel like I feel like the
eyes are also similar in the smile
and especially with the dark hair you
know
um
yeah so when I realized that yesterday I
was like I gotta tweet this
I need to have people agree to me but I
couldn't find a good picture so I gave
up
because it came to me through like
moving videos
the pictures were like not so convincing
feels like a stretch you're a stretch
I'm gonna put you on the stretch torture
thingy little chicken
I'm gonna show you what to stretch
gonna stretch your body your wings
until they rip and then I'm gonna Grill
them
just kidding just kidding I love you
I would never hurt you
please don't be scared of me don't be
scared of me
[Music]
I just want too much like medieval shows
in my lifetime
bring it
I watched so many medieval shows and
they like to
um you know stretch people
no
I mean they also did it in handmaid's
tale which isn't even medieval but yeah
I saw I saw like they they do the same
thing in the concerts right I saw some
clips already
of all the performances
like Mina did a Ari song I think
um
are you referencing to Elizabeth I only
know that chick from FGL
man you guys are like
so distracting me
they like the stretch me
[Music]
my my my words these days are very
problematic I've noticed
that clip of me talking about
um my
uh incident with the police
I said something
that everybody pointed out
I didn't I I didn't do anything illegal
that they would know of
was a big quote
and then yesterday
apparently my reaction to incest was so
calm
that was all my guess also
questionable
but no no it's um you know it's just me
being uh not English speaker
you know that that's what makes these
things
so oopsily
[Laughter]
can't talk
yeah Game of Thrones
[Music]
um
Sally
it was the influence of Game of Thrones
but
[Music]
um
I feel like you know when I was like
unraveling it in my brain I was
unraveling it step by step
It Came to Me Slowly
but I would then like boom in your face
so it wasn't so
like wow
it didn't
it was a Slow Burn
it wasn't so shocked and also it's just
a game you know it can't shock me that
much when it's just a game when if we're
talking reality that's a different story
then I would be like what the but
it's just a game
can't take it so serious
even though I was pretty immersed in the
game
you
money yeah this is a game and that was
just a game
can't complain I'm doing the same oh
it's a Game of Thrones also
I feel like everybody was like
and like yeah you but Game of Thrones
it's Game of Thrones and in the end the
Game of Thrones is like it's playing in
its own world so if they wanted to they
didn't even have to make it a weird
thing they could be like hey it's normal
here this is what we do in the Game of
Thrones world
um okay they made it indeed something
weird
at least
at least if you're not a part of the
targaryens
even though I found it so interesting
that
you know with Game of Thrones you get
this image that for the targaryens
incestors okay but then when you watch
House of the Dragon
you see that even within the targaryens
and all those little dragon people
like splits
the opinion is like split and they do it
but
it's not like everybody supports it
and they deny it
yeah
yeah damn what was her name
always always Prego Lady damn
damn
that very very
um
it's been already a while since I
watched the show but
I don't think I like her yeah I like the
the the the normal girl that married
that was her friend and married to the
king I liked her
much more
I forgot her name though the brown hair
chick
was was that they were there no no you
you're saying when there is yeah the
pregnant lady
feels like she was always pregnant
yeah
I like Allison way more like her morals
just
spoke to me way more
team Allison yay
yeah
House Green yay green green you forgot
the last episode I maybe did but support
songs oh yeah okay okay okay okay okay
okay
um
yeah I don't know you guys are so
distracting to me
[Music]
after it's writing me stop talking to me
don't
fault
don't don't
why don't we even
I don't even why did we even get to this
point
it's your fault no it's your fault
no you
mom
well
uh what it wasn't Allison's fault was
that I don't remember anymore
still like her anyway
um
no I'm reading them
just it's distracting when the chat is
moving
all right where where was I Brandon
Duncan unless you get a kiss though mwah
a black person
misses
Sean our Facebook pinky yo Tanto in case
you didn't know Star Wars day was
yesterday a franchise I know you just
love yeah
so I want to lend you in on a secret if
you want to know why Han Solo is really
popular then check out his epic dance
skills in Star Wars connect
what
is that on YouTube Han Solo
the words connect
I have desktop audio muted
uh there is one with 7.8 million views
at it
[Laughter]
this is probably it
though let me check
[Music]
and and
I forgot what was the other dude's name
oh
yeah yeah
let's go let's go
no it sounds so long that's the way his
attitude right away pisses me
off
that's it in the sky
oh
what what they they did it change the
lyrics or did they make the song for
them
he's Han Solo
Dance games the moves are so repetitive
so easy
do people actually play this and then
use the moves like in an actual like
dancing environment like the Disco or so
oh that's a good move oh oh the slide
move is pretty good
um
Carbonite is gone
I'm so happy it's over now the pain is
gone
I'm a shade to cover up my eyes I'm
jumping in my ride I'm heading out
tonight I'm so low I'm Han Solo I'm Han
Solo I'm Han Solo solo picking up my
blaster put it on my side I'm jumping in
my Falcon Wookie at my side I'm solo I'm
on solo I'm Han Solo I'm Han Solo solo
Oh fire fire
hey does this have an original
[Music]
oh
R2D2 let's go
let's go so good
do they have this one I want to sing it
oh it's Lando time
um
the alliance feels so good oh feeling
misunderstood back in the game who knew
I wouldn't oh so flat time I spread my
wings loving myself makes me wanna sing
oh oh yeah it's like High School Musical
told me to get my act together now I got
my act together yeah now I made it
through the weather better days are
gonna be better
happy the Carbonite is gone
I'm moving on I'm so happy that it's
over now the pain is gone I'm putting on
my shades to cover up my eyes I'm
jumping in my ride I'm heading out
tonight I'm so low I'm Lando I'm Lando
I'm Lando Landa feeling like a star you
can't stop my shine I'm loving clouds
eating my head's in the sky I'm so low
I'm
no
um Lando I'm Lando Lando
fun I just learned this song
instantaneously
I'm Han Solo I'm so low I'm Han Solo
solo
fun
I don't know why it's a meme I'm taking
it seriously
now I have to watch the first movie
original song is writing solo by Jason
Derulo the voice sounded very familiar
if that's the case and it's probably on
kind of fun with the original lyrics
then remind me please to sing it next
time I do a karaoke
so good
I'm Han Solo I'm so low so low
I'm so low so no so no they sang it did
you sing the OG or the Star Wars version
and did she even know about the Star
Wars version
it isn't kind of fun let's go
perfect
Han Solo pretty stream of Han Solo
connect
I'll see what I can do
Bae knows nothing about Star Wars well
just like me for real for real I mean I
know a little bit more than she does I
guess now
oh because they just sing it because she
knows the OG huh
it's like one of it's like when I sang
uh
just because I love the song the OG
never heard about the meme stuff
surrounding it and then you guys let me
know about it and I was like
yeah American boy oh I love that song so
much
oh with my jam back in the day
on a trip I'd like to go somewhere
back mid to New York I like Francesco
Bay I really want to
you'll be my American boy American Boy
I didn't no no I was just reading a
comment
I didn't say I wanted to watch the first
movie no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no such
such lies
you'll be you my American Boy Hey guys
we'll be my American guys
is what colony would sing it like
is we finished
no I'm still reading super yeah I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm reading some
um
so thank you Sean R this was just a
reply to a it was literally
with Shawna because he thought taught me
about the video
just an extension of a reply to Shawna
just making my my chickens happy trying
to you know give them
a good long reply make their Super Chat
worthwhile
yeah
it's true it's true
that's why I have 10 out of 10 on Yelp
you know
best Super Chat ratings they say
best super jet ratings in whole life
English they say
I mean for real are there any better
ones
people say Super Chat ratings is a fun
part and give me
I'm a professional Super Chat right
there yeah
yeah yeah
what what I missed yours
what did I
eh what do you mean
I missed yours
because I probably didn't read it right
in that stream did I
um
Lucas I'm glad you think so
I'm somewhat of a Super Chat reader
myself
oh
didn't read them at all yet well then
I'll get to it oh actually I forgot
about that
guys didn't tell me to read them
yeah
when I will not leave all of those on
red no no no no
don't worry
um
thank you
oh wow okay okay we'll have fun
tonight
oh yeah I won't if I don't feel like
finishing it I won't uh but I feel like
you know it's a Zelda game
is beautiful
if I don't have too many struggles with
um
you know the crafting and the fighting
and all that
if it goes well then I'll finish it
I'm currently really Unsure how that
will go
so much
next is this one because I will finally
finished
next up 12 minutes shake up thank you
soon I'll be your friends with a pinky
oh
you believe in me should be simple
enough are you sure
and what I just think might be annoying
you know like mid fights switching
weapons because one broke or you know
you have to they're really strong you
have to make a bomb and this is
that's just annoying I just want to have
one weapon and then
keep it the whole time
I don't wanna especially when you have a
game like breath of the wild where
there's so many items and even more now
I saw that you can um sort them at least
but still you have to go through so many
right like go through them to find what
you want and that takes up time and then
while you're doing that you're like
you're like you stop the game right so
then you go back into the fight and I
have from experience
uh whenever I like pause a game to go
into an inventory for example of tales
of a rise too at least hands of rice is
really easy so no problem but when I go
into the inventory to like find the
healing item and activate that and then
go back into the fight if it's a
difficult fight I'm like
okay now I have to get it back into it
uh and I just stopped it I feel like
that kind of throws you off
some people defended their ability
mechanic for some reason I love the
weapon durability personally yeah I mean
it's fine but I don't like that you have
to continuously like go through yeah
yeah I will definitely hoard good
weapons
and be like scared to use them
but yeah
I think also the system on its own is
good
it's breaking but a lot of things just
break too fast don't you think and then
yeah going through all of that
man
and just seems I don't know I don't know
I never played it myself I only watched
people play it so I don't know how it
will feel to me in action
but I would imagine it to be a bit
annoying
[Music]
yeah I will have to just use everything
I have because I understand the game is
just pushing you to use everything you
have
even if it's a really seemingly good
weapon just use it Until It Breaks find
a new one don't hesitate to use the
things you have
um
the game is not for toddlers
you're exaggerating
that easy
but if there's a difficulty setting
I might go for easy
time
I'm scared at least if you can still
change it afterwards and I'll ease
myself into it with easy
there is none oh
okay
[Music]
it's making me nervous
it's an easier route oh well do let me
know more about that when we get into it
Evie you're thinking for the pinky cat I
love you
and
I think I know what you're doing there
and I had tons of fun watching the VOD
of your Hotline Miami stream yesterday
I think I recognize this pattern
s once again hope you have fun with 12
minutes today I I feel like
[Music]
like a thing
a little bit because I feel like
previously you maybe you wrote a Super
Chat like this where then
the German part was
um I don't know made me feel
um
I don't know it's kind of you know you
know
and now you're doing it again but this
time you're being super nice
in the German part
ah yeah too cute
yeah and then you were like in German
you were like but something like yeah
but you're stupid I really like you and
your experience but but in German you're
stupid something like that
I could have your classes or so
in the school
did you not have physics classes or so
yeah roasting me and now you're making
up for it I see what you're doing
you're not talking now but I see what
you're doing
ah
you're blaming the system the school
system but I have to say
our school system isn't even that bad
I just I I just think you know the cope
it might be copium but
not every child can excel in every
subject
and yes
I really wasn't good in physics and
chemistry
basically for me I was the worst at math
then chemistry then physics
uh yeah those were like my top three
worst subjects
I believe that too thank you I mean I
think it's true you know there were kids
who were good at math and those subjects
and then they could they didn't do so
well in English and you know creative
subjects and all that and I was I was
not good at you know
it makes sense when you hear my top
three of subjects and bad ads
you can sense a pattern I think
because I was like
the pro
and English like linguistic and and
creative subjects
um
those were easy easy easy
oh I I wasn't like super good at history
but I really enjoyed it and and I was
like mid I think
history stuff
I think
a lot of depends on the teacher yeah one
problem I had with math was that three
years in a row but even I guess
if you count
Junior High and High School
probably like five to six years in a row
I continuously
had a diff or even
yeah yeah six years in a row
I had a different map teacher each year
for reasons of switching schools many
times
and yeah so each teacher had a different
way of teaching
um no it's not normal normally we
usually have like the same teacher
if you stay in the same school and like
in the same class because you don't
repeat a year normally you have the same
teacher here
that's normal in us oh but not here and
I would have personally I really
appreciated keeping the same teacher
it was challenging for me to have a
different teacher and then get used to
that the way they teach it they were all
kind of different difficult and weird
they all had like weird quirks
and also like
when the year starts and you have this
different teacher a lot of time they
didn't
pick up where the others left
um that was also confusing
Math teachers are just weird
they're now I wouldn't say they're weird
uh but they're they're yeah the strict I
always had strict Math teachers
is it I don't want to say they're all
strict but for me
all my math teachers were the strict
teachers
and all my like German and English
teachers were sweet teachers
really sweet
it's just the Math teachers for me they
were all strict and it makes kind of
sense to me it fits math to be strict
that just makes sense it's just
it's a match made in heaven
yeah
different person are you
you like your Math teachers
well I I liked them as a person somewhat
too
when I felt so
useless and bad and wow my self-value as
a child was
as a student absolutely destroyed
because I failed
so much and I feel like that contributed
to me continuously failing even more
because once I had that in my mind that
I'm bad at math
I think that was like blocking me
from getting better mentally
um
and the the fear
especially when you're under the
pressure of like yo I have to pass this
otherwise I have to repeat the year
that's the worst pressure
wall
man I'm so glad I'm not in school
anymore
I was miserable as a student my
self-worf was negative
oh
terrible
I was crying so much
more not a test pack
and I saw the result
and the other students were like mostly
fine and I'm like in the corner
I'm like hell
again
I'm crying alone in the corner
no
I'm just I never want to go back to that
I never wanna go back
it was so bad I'm out of that nightmare
thank God it is really a lot of pressure
man so much pressure
ah
and now that I said it for like for the
first time I really like
said it out loud and realize that I
really do think
it's not just my IQ
it's really like the mental pressure
that school gives you
that made it even more impossible for me
to improve in math
so stressful man
had this blockage in my hand you know
if there's anyone here still in school
and struggling
then I feel for you
but it will be over
school is very limited amount of your
lifetime thank God
and good luck man try your best
and even if you don't succeed
don't worry
they will make something out of your
life nonetheless
it's not
the end of the world as they may make
you think that you know everything
counts on your grades no no no no no no
no
even if you drop out of high school
everything can still be turned around
easy
grades are not everything how do you
pronounce sales
yeah and on that wholesome note let me
finally continue reading so much
Tiana's forgotten curl thank you oh
oh
finally back from the store sorry
to move for this tutorial now
said this on the
on the Twitter reply but the reason I
ended up never bringing up uhu during
the myth Breakers finale is because I
found at every Point like several times
I was like hmm should I bring up should
I bring up uhu after like an hour in or
so
until that point I was like if I bring
up uhu now who will probably get like
really hurt for example that in in the
school you know it was kind of iffy
uh after we opened that
um that door with the explosion I
thought if I send uhufuru who's probably
gonna get lost they're always gonna get
hurt by this like toxic whatever
Etc yeah I felt like better not to bring
uhu up now and save uhu for later and
then later I was like
um
if I bring up uhu now then I I wonder if
maybe there will be an argument with it
you didn't bring up uhu for two hours
stayed in the school outside
because I didn't you know mention who at
all so yeah and then it just got more
and more dangerous so I just felt like I
I I'll just not mention at all
boohoo is waiting in the car and
listening to music the AC is on and is
listening to its favorite song on the
radio yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
the dog meme
cute
yeah who had a PTSD about school didn't
want to go to school
[Laughter]
ah man
usually assumed and they're always with
you
I wasn't sure at that point if I should
do it because like I don't know
I felt like
you know
like I'm if I mention it after like two
hours when we're stuck in this like
weird after world
claiming I smuggled with me for all of
this who had no scratch
it would be weird
yeah
no no no no in my head Canon uhu was
with me the whole time and still is with
me there on the Mountain at the end
but we were fine without I ended up
doing so much damage on the bus you
damage dealer takanashi kiwawa AKA
tiara
um saving the day may have gotten rid of
one of one of those legs but still
saving the day
just doing what's necessary
yo I did the most damage y'all
Wild
Eno is like always talking
and was
trying things but most of the time
failing
and her attempts
oh man
yeah yeah and Ina was also failing a lot
unfortunately because it was really
difficult
meanwhile I'm just like dotting the
damage getting me down chipping chipping
it away
with the I wasn't sure you know if it
was even possible to do
um damage to the boss without hurting
watoto
so I just went for it
I bought well he's coming closer to us
I better do some damage now
I can't wait because I don't know
no no I would not ask Kelly because I
should not know if that's even possible
I couldn't have known
no no Tiara kiss for what at all well
who knows what happened behind the
scenes you know
a whistle
well so I don't remember whistle but can
you blame me
after all this time in between all the
episodes
I don't remember a whistle
um
yeah I don't I don't remember whistle
anyway anyway
what's I am thank you for the pinky uh
thank you for maybe my cave name better
and shorter oh yeah you changed it I
chose kfp
S and P by the way I forgot to deliver
the message from Mommy last time Mama
Said twice about her wanting to do a
tutorial the usual room with me she was
very interested in there I didn't see
kfp
oh really she wants to see the usual
room well
she should watch the usual room video
maybe it will change her mind and if not
then at least she would have seen it
through that
yeah seems like something she would uh
be interested in like operating as well
and
giving some input in how to improve it
probably yeah
my little torture trip and
uh location chamber uh thank you what
same for
delivering the message
okay
correction yes
you know it's hard to um put it in words
because it's just so many things at once
you know
um
I talked to my cats in Japanese and
young really
you're saying
[Music]
you sing that to them see what happens
it was like a
like a disco remix of that that I really
liked back in the day
[Music]
there we oh yeah
no new macros and years
this is so long since Delta
maybe an airline having like a problem
with
coming up with something that will Top
Delta Delta was so good it was so
successful
um
they made like so many concerts too with
Delta with the voice actresses
six years ago
well I mean there's no way that my
course just ends like that that says you
know
showy
I don't know working on something
really bye Kerry they're so good they
are so good I love them so much
like music wise Delta is definitely my
favorite
story wise
still gotta give it to
the
um
okay my mind is black but the langari
one
but music I just can't help it Delta is
so good did you win boss I've won once
against Cali once but besides that she
obliterated me oh yeah Frontier
my brother had great music too
of course of course
they did definitely
but wow carry
to listen to them in car rides too
oh
so good
yum yum yum yum
yes I gotta watch more macro series then
oh I'm motivated someone to watch more
macarons
sorry I'm like so
easy to distract today
thanks for the pinky awesome playful
thank you very much glad you enjoyed I
will play uh not more because now we're
talking about 12 months I thought we're
still talking about uh hold on Miami but
yeah if I finish that in one stream
gladly thank you for watching hope you
enjoyed it
foreign
fortunately Kato didn't want to be held
for the entire stream or my arm would
have fallen off uh so it wasn't really
fatal
wait I didn't say that because I was
wearing the F unfortunately and the
cuttle at the same time your cat is
surely not fatokato I'm sorry I didn't I
didn't want to say that that was an
accident but surely cattle didn't want
to be
actually Kato didn't want to be or would
one want to be held by you eternally
which I'm really very jealous about
20 pounds how much is that in kilogram
that sounds like a lot
if you had the arm strength for it
it would surely love to be held for
about 10 kilogram that is a lot yeah
okay
is
uh definitely
applying to that
like chonkers for example is really
feels really heavy to me but the
doctor's saying
tronkers is normal weight
so no problem I guess but I really feel
when I touch chunky monkey belly I feel
you know like a a vampire in German I
feel a vampire hanging down
like a stomach
[Music]
um
like a hanging part yeah
a little
I mean yes
that's the prime Oriental pouch but
smoothie doesn't have it
movies like
like if she did like a belly sucking
surgery
I was kind of Henry has it
primordial pouch is that not just an ex
and and a cope
uh liposuction yeah yeah
that's okay I love uh chunky wonky and
touching the belly makes me very happy
but she's definitely healthy weight so
I'm glad about that
anyway thank you spanking him you made
me tangent about my cats that is always
a good thing
thank you
[Music]
what
now
TV table train tickets
Richard D thank you thank you soon thank
you thank you oh three times even
uh
I'm the first person on YouTube you ever
subscribed to wow
that is quite something even outside of
YouTubers I am the first
damn
supper is ready I don't know that song
what
um
thank you I hope you stay subscribed
forever
[Music]
yay thank you for the support yeah I
left a good impression I guess
I can't just from two 2011.
you didn't subscribe to anyone
for over 10 years
oh
I'm just that good huh
I mean I think there are a lot of people
who just rely on the recommendations and
keep on coming back to like certain
YouTube channels
um like for example I keep on watching
videos from
like several True Crime channels but I
don't subscribe to them
whenever they put out a new video
YouTube shows me those right away like
on the same day anyway
yeah I just don't want to subscribe to
too many channels I guess so I think a
lot of people just rely on that most of
the time
um
especially if
like if a channel only uh puts out
content once in like a month or so like
really few or if they put out a video
every day like me I guess then I
don't want to subscribe
because it's either not worth it
subscribing or it's just too much of a
Spam to subscribe to them but you guys
can subscribed to me and I'm spamming
your inboxes inboxes inboxes and I'm
grateful that you guys are doing that
thank you for letting me spam your inbox
alongside probably other YouTubers as
well
um
I couldn't do that
I mean I am Subs to Pomo for example but
well
can't have too many
I don't even know memberships existed
until whole life oh
yeah because that's why I also something
you really only notice when you watch
live streams on YouTube
if you just watch normal videos and
you probably don't really hear of it
you're mad enough to follow you on
Twitter as well that is yeah also quite
something
kwj nankishun Ben Madeleine Duncan thank
you
I can thank you for two pinkies I caught
up on super I had scheduled some chicken
sandwiches for delivery during my
layover and it never came I only had 20
minutes so I made sure to schedule it
before I got there even tipped them oh
man yes we eat on the bus only one
Center has a room microwave usually we
we are in the middle of nowhere so cold
food is usually the choice or anything
good for on the go
well you know what I find fascinating in
Japan
like in Japan there's so much more
cold
but really yummy lunch options like a
lot of cold bentos that you can just
really enjoy
as they are cold without warming them up
like in Austria well you got like
sandwiches
but we don't really have this whole
Bento culture
so not warming up your food in Japan
really doesn't seem like an issue but
yeah in other countries probably
more
you know you probably mostly can rely on
salads and
sandwiches then
um
yeah but then I wonder if you have time
to like meal prep your own Bento
get yourself a Bento Box
and meal prep Bento Japanese style I
feel like that would bring you a lot of
happiness because you have really yummy
food without warming it up it's really
good I mean I say that and I probably
wouldn't have like the motivation to do
it but people who have the the
determination to do meal prep
I'm so jelly
because they do great things for their
tummies
you're one of the winners if you do that
like even or
like for example all the shinkans and
bentos not all of them some of them even
are self-warming but most of the
shinkans and bentos you're supposed to
eat them cold
they don't even they don't microwave
them
and I ate uh that
don't Bento
normally I wouldn't eat that cold but it
was totally acceptable cold hmm
even that what I really like is I don't
know what it is about Japanese eggs
I think I think they put in like some
soy sauce and some meeting
I really need to try that
because
I think I might ditch my pancakes
once I figure out how to do Japanese
Dashi
dashimaki tamago
um
is I think like a little bit different
is like an under category of tomato
Maybe
is made with the Dashi and that's what
makes it really juicy and kind of sweet
and I love that so much every time when
I'm in a convenience store or a
supermarket in Japan I look for the
dashimaki tamako
oh God I really need to try making it
I could eat that like endlessly for
dinner for lunch for breakfast Ever
every time
hmm
pancake cream will bring you back before
you know it yeah it's okay
it's okay some variety right sometimes
sometimes
although the pancakes would be nice
that would be nice
but those two moms in Japan
I think what I mostly ate for breakfast
was bread
and
yeah like kamago stuff egg stuff
sandwiches
because I didn't really have access to
like Crepes and pancakes right away in
the morning they do have some like
pancakes in the convenience stores you
know like packaged ones with some Jam or
so in between but those those aren't
quite what I'm looking for
iPhone
[Music]
foreign
to learn how to make tashimak tamago you
know I buy myself one of those
uh
rectangle
a square
shaped
frying pans
go to an Asian supermarket they should
have meeting
I think
rectangle okay
you need a rectangle frying pan
we'll learn how to do it
not even if it turns out a little bit
messy as long as you got the taste down
who cares
I don't
it's just for me to enjoy
oh Korean meeting and stuff as well it's
all the same
I'm gonna learn it
okay okay guys stop anyway I can thank
you um
pinky you might not have been in the
tournament but I think a Mario Maker
stream would be pretty fun one day as a
field stream if you ever need one really
looking forward to that next week yeah
yeah
[Music]
have that on my radar too
yeah I don't mind that
I mean I need to be reminded about
certain possibilities for fellow games
every once in a while
so that they're back on my radar
I I was thinking so too I mean I was
probably more open for that before my
last
2D Mario stream
I must say that
kind of um soured
everything
and uh delayed my plans to play any
Mario games again in the future greatly
it's just left a very
sour or bitter aftertaste in my mouth
Mario
yeah I'm so tired now
what will I eat tonight
um
anyway
what's up you like uh today I see you in
all those super chats and I see you in
the chat the normal chat
feel like you were gone for a while
though
have you
have you like
realized that you love me after all and
came back to me
you have come to your senses
right see I know that's when my chickens
are gone and when they come back
my cute accent what accent
what accent
feral wilderness
well but I'm glad you're back thank you
yeah I know
I mean
more often I notice when someone's back
that's like really easy for me to notice
um
I'm like oh wait
you
haven't been around for a long time
you're scared to take a vacation you
must ask me
or tell me that you're leaving but the
thing is like vacation okay we you mean
you just you know you're gonna be busy
for a week or so okay no problem
I mean oh sure as long as you come back
or some people they just they leave and
they don't know if they'll come back and
often they don't come back at all that's
sad
that's sad
well you don't want people to tell you
they're leaving it's uh difficult but um
if you're if you're telling me that
you're just gone for a week then sure no
problem you're not making me sad because
I know you're coming back
if you're never coming back then
honestly
makes me sad to see that
because it makes me feel like I failed
as a Entertainer a content creator
streamer because I couldn't keep you
on my ship
you lost interest
and you're leaving
makes me question my abilities
and I mean there's no and I know people
get uh sick of things that's why I keep
on saying it I know you guys will get
sick of me eventually
but just don't wrap it in my face
because that just
it's totally normal but having it rubbed
in my face just
you know makes me lose confidence
going oh I guess something else is more
interesting now I couldn't be I couldn't
keep up being interested
yeah
yeah yeah
but I know it's only normal because I it
always also happens to me
there's channels that I don't pay
attention to anymore that I've been
subscribed to before
yeah yeah it's totally normal
but yeah so
if you leave
and you tell me in the Super Chat you're
not coming back
yeah that's unnecessary
okay it's okay
I mean it's also sad when I eventually
at some point remember right this person
haven't seen that person in a long time
in my chat
I wonder what happened
I wonder
I wonder if they lost interest or so
but
I guess it's a bit better than
people saying it so directly like hey
I'm out
I'm gonna do all the things I'm gonna
watch all the YouTubers now sorry I lost
interest in you
as much as I don't like
someone leaving without saying anything
in this case I guess I also don't like
people leaving with saying something
it's a con conundrum is it
was difficult just stay the solution is
to just stay
you're in depth with me
oh
that's good
yeah solution is never leave
good
really happy you guys are here
really appreciate you guys and I know I
know it's inevitable at some point you
lose interest in me I know I know and
it's it's okay but
um I'm I'm always trying really hard so
maybe if if the time comes where you
lose interest and you like move on to do
other things
but you stay subscribed just because
you're too lazy to unsubscribe and I'm
just one of those dead you know
things in your subscription box
um maybe every once in a while still
check back if there's a thumbnail that
or title where you see it's it's
important maybe like a a birthday stream
or an anniversary stream or a New Year's
stream or so maybe check back in because
usually there's a lot of effort put into
those and who knows maybe it will spark
the fire again
you know could be
just just give it give me a chance again
okay
let's not Paris social what you mean
Never Gonna Give You Up
I'm just saying if you if you happen to
lose interest and eventually you know
what I'm
just like a zombie in your subscription
box
just give me give me a chance once
once in a while let's see maybe if it
changed okay
if it didn't then that's okay
hmm
[Music]
I'm just saying I'm putting a lot of
work into my work
and and even if you're like maybe sick
of it at some point there's always a
chance you you could find interest in it
again
hmm
you're parasocial
no no you
[Music]
anyway
if I'm in the hospital barely conscious
I'm still asking the nurses to put Wawa
on
you the real one
no you
I'm gonna go now
but you know what I thought was funny
yesterday
quick tangent before I go
I was looking for
um like recent
I don't do this often uh at all but I
was just like uh I don't know what I was
even looking for but I was looking
through recent Kiana Clips I was just
wondering what people clip of me these
days
so I typed in
uh takanasikiana on YouTube and sorted
by newest
and one of the things I found
was that's how I got reminded of it and
tweeted about it one of the things I
found was like World of Warships content
and
I I'm like not mad at all I just found
it was really funny
um reading some comments
from especially German people
who have no idea what YouTubers are and
thought it was really cringe
cringe you know but but you don't
understand you don't get it it's you
know it's this whole thing and then the
thing that hurt me because I can't
explain it is
um like some people cringed about me
saying and in German we say alvinas in
but but you understand it's my
catchphrase
I've oh
there's a reason why I'm saying it
and uh
I I just know that there's like or I
found out or realized through these
comments that there's a lot of like
normal
normalized to they don't consume anime
or YouTubers and stuff kind of people
who play the game
and when they listen to those whole life
voices not only my own
we had some
yeah Korean like they were cringing
those kind of reactions and I thought it
was really funny
to see how
normal wink people react to that kind of
stuff
and then this one guy who's like uh
showing it off was however
happy even though he thought you know
squeaky
kind of weird but I thought it was funny
all right we're cool at least that
um
there was a German announcing voice now
yeah
you said that oh yeah last time it was
only Japanese I didn't understand
and this dude I guess he plays a lot of
World of Warcraft in one of the forces
in German uh it's quite I don't know
popular I guess also in German speaking
countries
um
yeah yeah so didn't understand anything
from the Japanese announcers
or or Muna for example
but said it was nice to finally
understand something it's cool to have
like German representation normally
they're always like other languages
you couldn't really tell that you didn't
know a lot of the words well the thing
is they also didn't give us much context
I mean some of the words I asked like
what does this even mean so I understand
how I should be saying this but there
were so many and even after they like
roughly explained some words it was
still
yeah well without playing the games like
I don't know what I'm talking about I
don't know when how this will be really
used
so it was a bit difficult and
yeah
but they were listening
um
people from the game they were listening
while I was recording so I was like
asking you know if you want me to say
this in a different way like if it makes
no sense the way I say it please tell me
so there was like live feedback
so if it really doesn't fit then that's
not even my fault they were directing it
um
there was live feedback and
and they were really nice it was already
a long time ago but they were really
nice with oh directing it and they're
really chill
when I said I have no idea what I'm
doing they were really chill about it
um
yeah no it was fun
it's nice to I I think at first I was
like kind of
not so happy about doing it in German
back then when I first recorded it
because I I don't feel so
I don't feel so
comfortable with it but now in hindsight
I'm okay with it
because we all got some good feedback
for it being in German
and
it's something different
and since the others are doing it in
their own languages too
it's nice to represent
German I guess but still like I feel I
feel like there's like some
um
weird
I don't know it's hard to say what I
want to say
um
like one person like one Randall I saw
was criticizing like uh oh German dubs
suck uh why do they even dub it they
should just keep the OG and it's funny
because there is no OG this is not a
German dub it's just me I'm not like an
anime being dubbed over
people just really don't understand
yeah it's not like the OG was better
because I am the OG this is what you get
oh I'm not a dumb but okay like I guess
you know you see an anime character you
don't know whole life you don't know V2
is I guess you would assume it's like a
it comes from an anime
today I randomly like
I I rarely check these kind of
notifications uh sometimes on my phone I
see like a YouTube comment notification
of a new comment
I rarely like look at those
because they're they're really random
um but this one was left on on a really
old video from last year where I was
teaching Iris German
and this person came from World of
Warships has no idea what YouTubers are
but just wanted to leave feedback on my
voice acting for World of Warships and
didn't know where to do it so they went
on onto that VOD for some reason maybe
it came up when they typed in takanashi
Kiana German
because otherwise I don't know why you
would get there
and and then left the whole comment
about how they thought I think they said
they were like oh it's so impressive
um thank you for learning German like
you did such a good job you sound so
native like you must be like absolutely
incredibly intelligent to be able to
learn German so well and so fast
the whole comment was about that
praising me for doing such a good job
and I'm like
what how can you I don't I never what am
I not being clear about don't I sound
native because they were praising me
about sounding native but that's because
I am native what I'm I was so confused
I couldn't hold back I ended up replying
to him to that comment and needed to
explain it like dude I'm Austrian German
is I'm so good at German because German
is my first language
oh yeah and then he also said
um like your German is super cool you're
super good oh but but but the and in
German we say happy design was cringe
that's basically what they said and I I
wanted to defend myself
like I understand from an outside point
of view okay okay okay okay okay yeah
there might be some you know references
to my streams that you guys you know
Outsiders don't understand so it's
cringe but into my ending grading and I
basically do that to implement some
German in my streams that are always
English
but that's why we say it in German we
say everything
[Laughter]
yeah and the thing is the World of
Warships people they also wanted us to
I mean they wrote you know the script
and all that but they also wanted us to
include things that are kind of like
personal like like have to do with us
like references
not just like random all the time
yeah you saw my reply now
so yeah that's it's just you can't help
it it will end up having lots of
references that
people who never heard of YouTubers in
whole life will not understand
and it seems like in hindsight it's
confusing the World of Warships
Community very much like what is this
so I suppose
the whole life collaboration is really
mostly for whole life fans
to enjoy to download the games of the
game not so much for
existing World of Warships players
like the feedback was okay this is fun
this is cute but uh
squeaky and too much to listen to all
the time
change but yeah
but I like the real feedback you know
it's interesting to say to see what uh
Outsiders think about it
because often I don't see that kind of
feedback at all because we're so niche
such a niche that normally people you
know okay a lot of people fell into the
rabbit hole from outside and then they
stayed but then
we're still we're still this Niche that
a lot of people just don't get in touch
with
so I rarely hear that kind of feedback
from people
um
you want you made everyone on the play
If Only to bask in their confusion
maybe the people who found you from the
collab fund you're Australian
but why would they why would they know
they just they I think the confusion is
because the name was takanasikiara
from Whole Life English
so what you would assume is that I'm
either English speaking
mainly like natively or I'm Japanese
because I got takanashi in my name
so no matter how good my Germans they
would assume
oh she can't be German or Austrian for
that matter yeah it is confusing
the name isn't German at all and I'm
From Hell live English
so yeah
it is confusing it is misleading
um
yeah yeah
I mean I saw some uh good feedback too
from Outsiders and that actually
surprised me
yeah
somewhere like you know oh who is this I
want to get this voice back too where
can I get it who's this
nah
that was surprising to me
oh
yeah come on over World of Warships
Community jump into the rabbit hole and
get stuck
I think he thought Iris was you you
would have won learning German yay I
don't know but like
he was definitely confused
it was definitely confused yeah
but he was very nice though like even
though you know the end in German we say
seemed to be cringe for a lot of people
um they were pretty nice about it
they were
um like some of them were like what what
the is this manga
this manga crap
um I love it when when people just
default to what is this Sailor Moon
manga crab you know
they don't know they don't understand at
all
Raiders oh hello oh I was about to end I
was going on my last tangent
hmm I am not a manga and I am not an
anime
but sometimes I also default to
explaining myself to strangers like like
the um
American Immigration for example
in like yeah I I I I or I mean it was
actually his first
assumption right so are you like like a
like an anime
when I said oh I'm a voice actor so you
mean like anime you like anime anime
yes I guess
uh
that was a funny story
I am an anime I I'm a magical girl
really really are far you think so
I don't think I really met someone who
like is like so strictly against it so
ignorant about it
um
especially these days
maybe it's just it's just the people I
surround myself
well for the people I get to know
are usually pretty open-minded
oh
well
don't feel
bad or or anything like that when you
see stuff like that
they're enjoying whatever they enjoy and
we enjoy the media that we enjoy
which their own doesn't mean that
something is right or wrong
something is better or worse
um
in the end I'm also just a streamer no
so the membership pool
it's not about Star Wars no what
just talking about the interesting
feedback from like Outsiders I guess
yeah
but in the end yeah that kind of made me
a bit happy that I did it in German
because I saw a lot of feedback that was
like oh this is I don't know who this is
and so on but it's cool that it's in
German for once
on that note in case you didn't see it
on Twitter
uh and didn't like for some reason uh
you know hear about it but there's a AME
and kiwawa boys
uh on World of Warships now that you can
get and from what I hear it's not very
expensive I think you can get an in-game
currency I think
the football game was already before
wasn't she
furuki and Malin were like from before I
guess you can still get them
oh five bucks oh yeah okay that's cheap
you get a lot of voice lines hmm
if you're interested in the game feel
free to download the game and then get
the kiwawa voice
in German
it starts off with a loud key
it's a good deal
I think so too yeah enjoy
I know there wasn't like much promotion
about this uh
so I felt kind of bad and like promoted
it yesterday on Twitter
um
so
um please
if you're interested
give them a download
much
so now I'll go
and in German we say as cringe as it may
be I'll
visit
yay
bye bye guys don't call me cream
trying to implement my my Austrian Roots
man
tomorrow my day off I'll put up a
schedule tomorrow
bye bye
bye bye see you later alligator
thanks for the membership
[Music]
when was movie come let's wait
foreign
[Music]
off and she'll probably come immediately