[Music]
oh my gosh
we're good shall we start out with the
introduction and audio test everyone say
the name one by one then we test each
other's audio in each of the streams
yes sounds like a good idea okay i am
am i loud am i quiet what do you think
guys on the other streams
next up or i think they're cool it's
fine to me next up who wants to go next
uh hello testing test test
[Applause]
[Music]
again fasting hello one two three hello
all good okay
next up howdy i'll check
once oh wow that was loud for me
hello let me turn that down goodness
gracious me i did not realize
excuse me hi my name is uh clappy maury
first apprentice grim reaper you guys
know the deal hey
what's good please die that's all
i don't want to die a second time today
okay well you've already filled your
quota then so never mind thank you
wow you're good all right
[Music]
girl
we're gonna beat up the big old lizard
that lives underneath the
somewhere i don't know yeah
yeah that's what we're doing next
nice i'm very loud in my own ears though
ugh
guru is muted of course gurus
is that not just the way i'm going to
throw
my mouse
oh no not the mouse why did my settings
hello all right obs decided to set all
my audio settings to default for some
reason
i mean i didn't start her stream yet oh
yeah
oh yeah don't worry you guys keep going
i'm just setting up the
discord things though
almond will be live in a moment yeah
live in a moment please wait look at the
moon
ah the moon's pretty today yesterday
the server is coming together so nicely
it's so
pretty we're gonna go to the game now i
think so too
um well i think uh we should all
bring uh the stuff that we need and the
chest or two chests so that we can put
it all down safely
uh in the in the uh stronghold
instead of taking it so we we have a lot
of armor like in
in case we lose it uh we want some of
them some of that
in the in the yeah over there also
i don't know if you girls planned on
doing the
bad strategy but in any case everyone
should bring at least one
bad boy just to sleep there and have a
safe point there uh-huh
so bring your beds okay
you want me to make a chest uh yeah just
bring one chest i guess for you safe
to keep your your belongings safe once
we get there
okay let me make an 18. never mind i
just remembered
right yeah just wood and whoa whatever
give me more i can make
more
we're not going to memories someone's
tree down not this time
this time no no other people's trees
will be chopped yeah what else are you
no no no i didn't i have ender
i didn't tell them to sleep in the end
i'm telling them to bring
a bed to sleep and in before going into
the portal
so that we if we die we don't go all the
way back to
our uh it's the ultimate payback
i got the map in the end i got a tip
that we should bring bottles to like
capture the ender breath or something
yeah capture the stinky dragon breath
okay
yeah you can just bring some glass and
you can just make a whole bunch of
bottles ah
oh gloss in the forest it's really dark
i didn't make a bun okay not like that
i forgot where i put my glass like i
forget where i put everything
oh this is a very beautiful area it
might be something yeah
i don't know if i have the
the hands free to be capturing breath
never mind
i mean one yeah you can be hitting the
track and
not and how do you oh my god capture the
breath
i think you just put you just use the
glass where it's like doing the breath
attack
oh okay yeah
i'm saving the wood hey where's the
diamond armor
let me tell you all right so if you go
uh if you're on the way to my house
uh yes on the way to my house you will
see two chests
i am standing there as well the left
chest has armor everyone may take
uh two sets i guess
for themselves okay i don't have many i
didn't get many weapons but um
do we need to bring food or this
shouldn't be like a
we should bring i mean a little bit yeah
yeah
people too oh yeah and um
after you guys are done prepping come to
my come to my house i can give you guys
some
uh slow falling potions so you don't die
okay
oh yeah i need i need some shoes
two golden apples from the chest where
the armor is in as well everyone gets
two golden apples
and i will tell you how to use them
[Music]
and cut the apples
i didn't know you can have an ender
chest before going to kill the enemies
[Music]
i think yeah okay and then a golden
apple stack right yeah with two two
golden apples yep yep
what is super thanks okay
it's fine and i'm just uh i'm just going
on a little journey
excess access work uh if you
like the sword is better if you do like
quick uh hits but the axe
does more damage if you do like shorter
slower hits i guess does that make sense
basically yeah
it's like it's like a heavy
target yeah yeah yeah florida's aov
attack
the sword is quick damage light damage
are all my junk in these chests
okay and then okay yeah
you guys got the food
got cookies cookies come on cookie
water book bucket and i wonder if we
want to bring like something like
scaffolding
you guys definitely want some um water
i'll bring sand all right forget this
guys i gotta look at the um
[Music]
maybe not send what is it the
coordinates the coordinates
nothing you buy pops up right no no no
always your graphics card i'm just
kidding
was it f3 i've played this game in so
long
yes
[Music]
went to go get some wood so i could make
a chest but everything around our areas
is owned so i had to kind of go
outside the area the trees are not old
i'll give you a tre
a tree i live your chest if you want yes
can't touch anything anymore okay
what is this what is the x y area
i can't i i don't know where i am what
is the x y
don't don't hide phantom is it
70 what is it
[Music]
can someone tell me where they are
did someone please tell me could someone
please tell me where they are
oh where are we please give me the
coordinates
please of where we are you mean where
does where ours
uh 326. okay
why 79 although y doesn't really matter
and
set minus 481. wait i can know
400 gotcha okay
i didn't hit any of those oh hello cat
hello cats yeah there are a few cats so
they were attacking us
oh really
yeah that's how i got a lot of the
membranes for the potions
so by the way i brought i'm bringing
sand in case we want to
go up to the towers with sand instead of
shooting them
and and i'm bringing dirt because we
probably have to build like a bridge
from our
portal to uh the actual main island
and what did i say the coordinates wrong
and that is x and z is minus wait sorry
it was not 400 it was
wait what is that no no minus 480
470 something like that
how did i get this far away i was just
trying to retrace your steps and i was
like
where where did you go i mean i was
walking in the darkness
sorry for yet another delay you guys i
had to contribute
being useless at least once so let's see
the adventures
basically like getting ready for the
family trip you know
yeah everyone everyone gets ready for
the lost what
[Music]
chad are you trolling you i am correct
you guys are incorrect
idiots i'll decide
it's covered up but
except yeah thank you ina thank you enot
look at the the one below there you see
it more clearly
ouch this is
turning out to be a bad morning this is
a bad morning baby i'm already enjoying
this
where was cali or where is cali i don't
know
we all don't know where she is oh wait i
thought the last time you played you
were like uh
doing the ferris sale or no oh i know i
i was um a couple minutes ago uh i went
to go make a chest
um so i went into the darkness and i
went looking for wood
and i made sure to go far away just to
make sure to go real far away
a flare if you look inside the sky do
you see
some of our monuments or like the do you
see anything like that subscribe
nothing i'm thinking about just dying
guys like at this point i'm thinking
about that
i think the problem is that we're giving
her our
base coordinate when she's all the way
in phoenix town
ish
i left from the base town guys okay okay
okay
did you go through amme's house i'm up
i'm up like
ah where the i fell
uh oh uh i i just want to die guys i i
honestly i just want to die like reset
callie gotta find the third darkness
oh god what is this sheep
where you are stay where you are kelly
where are you
tell me your coordinates okay 299.
what 299 299 219
77 which doesn't matter and then
this is the one that's effing me up that
i can't see
negative six hundred ninety two oh it's
just reels it down
oh not really right oh i think i
i kind of know where you are maybe i
don't know which drink
i'm on my way
[Music]
actually i don't know where you guys are
if you're already going then i'll stay
yeah i'm i'm more young you're better
with coordinates
can you write sorry
yeah one sec hang on oh sorry
okay let's see are you on snow or grass
right now
i'm on grass uh-huh
glass wasp
she couldn't have gotten far yeah
exactly there's only one
only one place you can go where there's
trees
[Music]
dressing on this way
is somebody bringing a leash so she
doesn't get lost again
please
one of those like those baby ones that
strap around your chest
oh i haven't there's three of them yeah
people like to walk their children
yeah one person with three children and
they're like all over the place
mommy tried to put me on one of those oh
what color
it was like green tartan
print plaid okay what are the
coordinates cali
uh 305 for x and negative six
nine two for z five
negative what
[Applause]
i'm thinking like cali yeah something
wow where did you go five negative six
nine two i just walked into the darkness
really
just tried to go somewhere away from the
camp turned around and couldn't find the
camp anymore
i'm gonna get up on a pillar
okay that checks out
uh you you got lost really quickly that
might be a record
that really probably was a world record
it's definitely a world record yeah he's
on a different server
honestly i would not be surprised would
not be surprised if i was
[Music]
okay getting closer
smell cali and it's negative six nine
two by the way i'm on a tall pillar
i see it i see um yara
and uh
giant stairway yeah there is a giant
stairway right above me too
you should just follow that yeah i guess
i should
okay please just let me see signs of
civilization
follow the moss-covered rocks i came all
the way here for this freaking wood i
will sit here and i will hit it with my
hand
until i get it even though my axe has
now just broken
i will hit it with my hand because i got
lost for this wood
determination hey who was that are you
guys all ready to go by the way remember
this
yeah please literally holy
[Music]
pretty much do i need
who needs insights anymore when you can
get glowing ink sex
why don't you even use ink sacks for
they seem useless and ugly
pink it's a stress ball
moistening
oh i thought i hit it i guess i guess
you're back
in base cali
okay good i have a bucket do you need a
bucket
sorry i have a lot of buckets oh i also
have
drinks for everyone thank you god please
randy
at taco bell you guys think we can play
some of those
those minecraft minigames have you seen
like the minecraft
mini game servers oh yeah yeah i'm
i'm a lost child
where did i get this from there's yeah
all right tally in here
okay uh welcome to
come right why atlantis you're selling
the chest i can give you one
oh it's okay i have one i made one it's
okay i went out of my way to make one
don't worry okay everyone
come over here to my my lab
yes open up the right chest and take
some
slow falling potions okay
you'll need it you got it this time i
got it now
thanks for the clap clap clap chat i
appreciate that
always been a rough morning
slow falling potions i think you can
take uh
five one two one three four how many can
we take
i'm sorry ina uh four or five i forget
oh i already have a full inventory
yeah i mean i'll take the leftovers
myself so don't worry yeah
but i can't seem okay oh you can't yeah
can i have buckets
open up uh there's seven in this chest
over here and there's like four
on the outside one i got something yeah
so feel free to take okay thank you for
all the preparation you guys did
this is really helpful you guys are
amazing sasuka
wow yeah do you have any extra ender
pearls on you
me i have one yeah if you guys have any
extras could you
not have somebody i'll bring some blaze
rose just in case you know our eye
breaks before we find
okay i have like
a couple legs i have three
uh as for diamond armor is that in front
of kiara's place yes come to my house
yes okay there is did everyone else
already take their sets of armor
you should like take probably two but
well what if we die and burn and then
they all burn but if we die then we'll
just spawn back at spawn and then we can
try to meet back up in the yeah
wait i forgot ah wait yeah did you take
the under just where the chest i didn't
take the end of my chest
i took and the pearls holy my sauce ah
kelly
wait wait go back up okay you see me
[Music]
yes i see you i'm here
this is your house oh it's my new house
yeah just just have me fun
left chest please take
two two full sets of armor
okay would
one you shall wear right now i guess
like 50 something would okay and the
other other one in case you die and lose
okay and then on the right side
[Music]
okay how do you say shield in japanese
what the hell happened here
please take one of the diamond axes
all right one of the bubbles one of them
uh maybe the the second the first row
second
one are you okay i'll see
i guess you can also take the iron sword
that someone put in there
wait that's not you iron sword okay
and then one of the uh take yeah take
one stack of arrows okay one stack of
arrows golden
no the normal ones the golden ones are
not probably not really useful
surprisingly did you take an axe as well
the diamond the diamond one um
axing all the questions yeah can i ask
so now you might actually take one more
one more
bowl because you might lose one oh okay
if it's all right okay which one should
i take any of them
uh it doesn't matter oh as long as it
shows our tooth and strong
all right
[Music]
all right okay and one stack of arrows
okay
yeah um i am also bringing
some snowballs but i don't have many uh
ina didn't you also get snowballs are
you bringing them too
oh yeah i was gonna make this snowman oh
because that's
gonna shield guys i was gonna use the
snowballs
to shoot the towers uh like there's
towers then you should gotta shoot the
top and the snowballs are really good
for that i think
oh okay okay i wanna build a snowman
[Music]
right
sorry one more thing two golden apples
from the chest
yes ma'am i'll go ahead and do that
nice crossbow
[Music]
is
my
[Music]
is somebody more responsible want to
hold the scaffolding because i do not
trust myself
i certainly don't trust myself
[Music]
i lost the new trust
believe in you that believes in me
should i have a pickaxe you guys
[Music]
i don't think tally's using optifine so
i don't know i am
me too you are okay it must be optifine
then because yeah this is
enough i should bring some shovels and
stuff too i forgot
it's free and i dig chad
ouch i'm so glowy
okay now can i give you
um the free and the pearls that i have
oh yes because you have a stack anyway i
guess i'm gonna make sure
if i don't lose
come give me your brains where are you
where are the
wrong kind of membranes but membrane
that's like when when the membrane wall
of a cyst
have you ever seen cyst removals you
have to remove the membrane wall
otherwise the cyst will grow back oh
shots shots absolutely yeah beautiful
shots i always put in the corner i can't
see anything
all right so are are you ready
can we see i guess yeah we can start the
car
yes everyone got their snacks we got
food snacks
good all right let's see let's start
with this
yelling oh there's another one
are we sleeping
yeah i guess so let's go sleep too
there's another bed over here i think
i'll have to go into something
oh well please stop that please stop
the phantoms are so noisy
[Music]
all right good morning everyone
it's time kelly in front of your house
there's a dummy i will destroy it
okay
there's a lot of enemies out here oh my
oh my god
why are they after me are you okay oh
yes yes i will just run
so much oh
wait wait wait there callie
okay i'm not moving where's scally
okay you can come out now try to destroy
them right you can come out no
there's no more no more explosion
waiting for you
okay that was horrifying uh inaudible
can you take the ender pearls out of the
chest i have a full inventory
ah okay not this chest inside my helmet
is
thank you you're gonna see that ender
pearl tosser
am i the here please choose free in the
picture
that's what they're called right oh
thank you yes hey better swing
yeah let's just keep our eyes on this
all right
all right guys i have to i have to grab
a chip i'm sorry my stomach hurts so bad
one chip one chicken just enough to not
hurt my
yes i have a sausage that's supposed to
be spicy but ever since i ate those
spicy noodles nothing has ever been in
spicy
oh thank you for this assassin
okay
[Music]
if you need to make more bets then i
have one two three four five six seven
eight beds
oh maybe nine i don't know i thought you
can do it
many two but yeah
normally two depends thank god oh the
pain is going away
everyone okay everyone has checklist
everyone has
armor yes everyone has weapons
yeah everyone has arrows and
everyone has slow falling potions yeah
everyone has two golden apples yeah
everyone has a food some kind of food
yes i have some leftover in case
everyone has
one chest at least
i mean we probably have enough space in
the other shoes yeah and everyone has
maybe one
or more but more than one water buckets
they could be
i mean i don't know if you if you were
if all of us are that skilled i'm
probably not skilled enough but i
brought
a couple of water buckets and because if
you fall down
then you can do a swoosh and then you
laugh i have a boat
i guess now and i have some building
material i don't think we all need
a little building material because yeah
just one of us has to come out
some kind of bridge part of it so okay i
thought it's gonna push each other off
okay then i'll
put some water buckets back or do i i'll
just bring him along whatever okay let's
go
where are we going
i just gotta toss this right and i'll go
towards it yes
yes keep your eyes on it though because
i think you can collect it again oh yeah
how do i toss it no idea right clock oh
where did it go
i have no idea what happened whoa i
think it was that way right
yeah did he go behind us we lasted what
it didn't even like usually it travels
and then it thinks
that pinged right away are we like
what and i think it went up
i mean just just wait here let me see if
it's just did you throw up or at the
ground
it kind of threw like horizontally
yeah okay uh
he said chad says it went the opposite
way maybe opposite way
oh there's no way we can how time to go
yeah i don't know
everyone's gonna try to look funny
[Music]
because i will get lost marco
polo come on oh can you make one of
those
was that not supposed to uh you need
blaze rounds and endothelials
has all that stuff yeah surprised
well uh
[Music]
i don't think we'll find it
does it do these spawns
in like five minutes probably all right
a radius like if we know a block radius
then we can do like a you know a
circular sweep
yeah i think there is sweets goes but
all right let's go the other way we will
calculate from where
through it and then we can set up maybe
okay throw another one it didn't go that
far because it pained really quickly
[Music]
cool that's 10 to 15 blocks okay so
let's go back to the original one and
then
search 10 to 15 blocks away from the
corner that you know through it that is
so close
yeah that is pretty close
i'm sure we're just missing it it could
have broken apparently
ah yeah that's true they break sometimes
right away okay
i said i probably this is probably
broken
okay i'm gonna group up and throw
another one everyone feeling like
where are you like wait wait wait wait
wait why are you we can see which way
i'm coming back to uh keira's roof
[Music]
i lost it disappeared
i was in third person so i was looking
at i didn't see anything
yeah it actually literally just doesn't
work are we all using
shaders yeah because it went down
but i i checked in okay if you don't i
mean the kiara's house
is not i wonder if it is a shader's
thing look down
i didn't know i turned off shaders
are we right above it no way
there's no way there's no way and we
then we would have probably like
dug into it with amelia's
underground subway the cave turns way
further that way
like to the left but maybe we should dig
straight down from where you're throwing
it
[Applause]
you're forbidden to use it from now on
what sweats
and i mean we didn't try dig down but
somebody said not a good idea it's not a
good idea
i don't before we waste all the pearls
though there's no way that it's here
[Music]
oh
like near the ocean oh okay
like the flowers we'll go back to the
cabinet yeah like like behind my house
ish
ah yeah like where could uh guna was
gonna make atlantis but
we went to the second floor don't worry
guys i definitely know where my cabin is
it's just not optimal
okay don't let your dreams be me you'll
finish the cabinet memes
and memes boys and girls so we already
wasted two of those
end up
so as long as there's pearls that's all
we need
flat enough i think
it would know better
no no no oh well you have to do it to
him because no no
surrounded by water
[Music]
over there we can do that that looks
flat
okay i hate that boat
and you know what i'm getting okay and
you want a ride
i would like a ride actually i have a
boat with you
i'm on your side i'll ride with you
you're out
tandem with me cali
nice cool girl's new house flat
have you seen your cape pretty cool it's
so dark all right i have a good time
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
i'm not there yet oh my god wait wait
wait wait
knees okay uh who thought this is
good one person look towards inna's
shrine
i guess one person looked towards them
i'm gonna look towards another village
what
[Music]
should we sleep i'll have my third
person
i have beds if we need to sleep really
well i can sleep
everyone should have first yes yeah
let's sleep first before
well down the beds lumber party ladies
[Music]
all all right okay oh maybe if we go
maybe enough you go really high up like
on a on some blocks like this oh okay
okay uh what's the easy block okay dirt
would you like a dirty bottom not
is this good i think that's good all
right i'm gonna throw it towards
towards the tory gate okay everyone
ready watching
three two one
[Music]
don't we have to keep throwing it that
way until it goes down
yeah yeah yeah yeah get it down okay
oh there it goes oh it's working
is it there no i got one more
should we go again uh let's do it from
the toy gate
yeah good idea you want to throw that
one
oh you do it you know this is fine what
if i mess it up
okay oh
oh wow really far
oh god well maybe the last two houses
just broke
that would be pretty unlucky do we have
to i mean
we still have like three spare ones what
should we do here like should we make a
bridge or should we just go
in that direction and then do it again i
feel like the bridge is just gonna be
wasting blocks possibly we have other
boats because if we have the other
other boats we could just go in this
direction a little bit i gotta go again
i'm going until we reach let's go this
way until we reach land
yeah who has boat i got a boat who needs
a boat
i don't have a boat boat thank you gura
yes for the ride well we need one more
let me check in this chest oh yeah there
should be one more
that we rode on the way
[Music]
oh
oh okay okay keep going
yeah i think we can go a bit further
before we frame this one
because yeah we're wasting them do you
still have enough you think
yeah 12 girls 12 plus three pearls and
five blazers and that makes like
a couple of okay it should be fine let's
go until we get to
land and then uh we can do it again
we have like a perimeter to check this
feels so cool you guys
i feel like it could be
i'd be unlucky though i was walking on
water damn
what a pro gamer i'm in
pro gamer
let's go dolphin yeah
i'm the photographer
we're taking pictures of us
beautiful on the way to the ender dragon
yeah right now beat up the underdress
i'm gonna look up epic minecraft music
all right copyright rta let's go
i don't know there's a minecraft
playlist that i'll put on like a 10 hour
playlist while i play
when everyone gets here we'll see
hold on
i'm gonna play all the nether tracks oh
yeah a good idea
[Music]
oh hello sorry
can i play that too
nether mind yeah look up the nether
tracks because if you look at magic
mic epic minecraft
trash no that that'll give you remixes
from from other music producers
okay so look up yeah use the nether ones
minecraft soundtrack all another tracks
2020.
500 sounds trustworthy
everyone here yes no um
[Music]
let's keep going for like a couple
minutes
yeah how many blocks maybe like 500
vlogs is there like only one
or is there like oh we're back at water
maybe we should go to where those
[Music]
until the tree trees go onto the tree
wait i lost you girls me and kelly are
too far away from you girls i'm not the
only one yay
i'm not the only one that's lost anymore
oh
i am so close i see some names i found
found you
cal you're following yeah yeah go to the
top of the hill and you hello
i see them i don't know
uh about that
wait i have someone's bed
[Music]
all right let's go drive drive drift
is there only one or is there multiple
welcome to the mountaintop i'm gonna
is there multiple yeah that's the one
it's the one god had to get out of the
there we go
yeah yeah there's tons okay okay so i
guess it's just the one we're closest to
uh-huh okay cool
[Music]
we should have roller blades that'd be
sick
and go faster maybe i should've oh
there's
i saw like a like a that is really
close relatively close i guess
what's what's close wait for everybody
can you go a little further uh sure
okay just a little bit
maybe like on top of the yeah
yeah oh yeah i was thinking that to you
we're in unexplored territory
exclusions
fill in the map we would have needed a
really big map so if he went real far
yes
[Music]
naturally possible pumpkins all right
guys
wait on which i saw some on my little
head but that's
what i heard you are oh okay
okay oh there you go okay thank you
[Music]
to look for a portal right yes yes
yeah we gotta triangulate or whatever
and then we break minecraft's number one
rule
don't dig down
from here i love digging down
i will stay behind i don't want to lose
all the stuff
i did not make a shovel where are
you hey i have a shovel
i have diamond shells i'm gonna throw it
i have a shovel i have a shovel
nevermind
whatever
[Music]
over time no it's not on the ground yeah
yeah i don't see it
oh it's real dark sleep over time
[Music]
there's a bed over there thank you okay
i heard it break really it is on the
tree but i thought it still hit the
ground
what's on the tree i mean
we can check hold up oh i have your
bedding oh it's right there i see it
ah there it is so thank you so much for
hearing it break
oh my goodness
oh that's bad i think that was your
heart breaking
we're going to get it right girl
okay
[Music]
okay hi kfp worker
we do it like at the edge of this cliff
here yeah
[Music]
watermelons
oh oh oh oh oh okay somewhere here no i
don't care
hold on someone's down here someone
stand here
oh okay and stay stay put sit
i can stay
i'm really good at standing still and
not doing anything
the one thing i'm great at at this game
oh i think you're on to it yeah
someone someone stands like somewhere
here okay me me me
out then i am
yeah can i move i already moved
hold on yeah let's stick where where am
is
okay okay here how far down is it yeah
i don't know it's pretty far down i
think we're digging
until we see it yes well i'm sounding
all right ladies
i can help oh no she's digging straight
down
[Music]
she'll be fine i'll dig somewhere around
here
you'll know that because the stones will
change it'll look like brick stones
i should probably stay with someone i
don't have a
picture where are you and me i opened up
a cave here there's a cave down here
we'll build some stairs we can mosey our
way dance oh yeah good idea
should have brought torches i can drop
water over here and then you guys i have
torches
i dropped water uh if you guys
oh there's a creeper here you go you
know you have an arrow in your head
thank you there you go
don't worry about it welcome wait no
space not right
here like uh oh but i guess it'll go
through the wall huh
i have i have no space in my inventory
oh if there's a cave though then there's
another
good chance it's okay they'll they'll
find it
okay i'm gonna stay with you uh i have
no clue okay
nice shirts oh they're down there dude
i'm gonna
start digging down again just to see i
didn't bring it home
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh
wait wait for us
[Music]
oh
can you open the door for me yeah me
[Music]
yeah there we go
okay nothing here nothing it's a maze
oh wow so it's like that huh so exciting
this is so cool there's like stairs
is that possible i think so oh my god oh
my god oh my god there's a lot of people
here
i i don't have any more uh torches i
have problems
don't look at him don't look at him
there's a library oh
[Music]
as well i know there's like cheeky uh uh
uh
joke walls you could buy this is anybody
doing watson uh throwing away blocks
that was scary this library is so cool
yeah i probably shouldn't try and hit
this spiderwebs
we can take them yeah hit the spiderwebs
with a sword they go down really fast
oh cool thanks oh i think i found it
nice there's a ladder i don't want to
get rid of the spawner though
oh yeah there was actually a spanner
that was really spawner
yeah i'm gonna borrow a torch
here i can give you some i didn't look
at you i don't
look at you i did not look at you i just
saw us
yeah that enderman is really scary uh
oh you did find it the other way that
was fast
want me to go get the one i have i have
one more no i have exactly 15.
oh dear gosh oh my god okay okay
everyone every one
kelly follow good fine dino wait 12
minutes oh never mind
i get it i go get it
this oh yeah good idea
okay got it i got the screenshot that's
great let me make sure i'm absolutely
prepared
chest should we get on the chest guys
just in case yeah
oh my god what the is wrong with
you
what do we know what the hell stop it
there's a thing you gotta kill it they
come out of the
the walls and stuff what are we starting
in the chest
uh your importance like your second set
of armor
and uh yeah super fish maybe some arrows
stop it a lot of buckets hey
some some of the potions we don't
that was not me i did not do that oh my
goodness
okay i did not do that get rid of them
uh yeah this is
this is what the hell the bed is about
to burn
does there have to be another underneath
the portal
if there's no lap on the portal will we
break it for some reason or can we
get rid of this number oh can we break
the splatter
yeah we're like lava required can i pour
water in the lava
yes okay we don't we don't need the lava
all right
[Music]
i don't know they don't look all how
about the uh the potions you guys
the slow falling yeah maybe bring in one
one only for now i think oh maybe two
here because it's pretty dark yeah
we've got 11 and one leave it to me
leave it to me
[Music]
okay i'm gonna start putting the eyes in
all right here what's up
i'm i'm putting two books into the chest
but those are those dudes are
mine okay
okay yeah forgot about that
take pickaxe oh yeah i will
bring it that's right okay
everyone ready
can we take a group picture can everyone
get on the stairs and uh
i want to take a picture
[Music]
okay i got it thank you me too yay
damn it maybe under chest here
different people use the under chest
does that mean
they have their own storage i opened
yours earlier and i didn't see anything
in it oh that means you guys can use it
too
to store your stuff in oh wow we should
have done that i wish i know i hope she
didn't
oh well
okay well i'll put
it looks like
well okay are you ready are you okay are
we going yes
no okay let's take a plunge
be
maybe not all at once because we don't
know how big the
platform is when we land and we might
push each other off
where we stand want to go first i'm
nervous okay
watson all right how is it is it very
narrow
like i can't see wait wait wait
i have a torch it's a small platform um
you guys can okay do we have building
okay
yeah everyone ready yeah should i be
holding something
specific you guys are holding blocks you
have to
build but yeah yeah to build yeah i'll
help
uh okay do we use the you know do you
think we should use the
falling potion right away i think when
we when we go in we can
use it when we start fighting okay also
uh kelly
don't there's a lot of enderman's down
there like a ton
um oh when you go up to the dragon
try to look down because there's really
an army of and the dragons don't look at
them they will
kill you once you look at one of them
okay can i make one
how do i don't want to do a staring
contest no no we can't
do it can you anger them or water and
get in it oh yeah they can't
they don't like what they can't swim but
kelly remember we're not fighting the
ender
men because that's the fight we cannot
win we try to fight the in the dragon
i don't have any more okay and we can
look at that one right
i have to make them yeah we can look at
the dragon safe okay
okay okay all right i'm waiting
i'm ready now
it broke oh i don't know
is this working yeah i'm so scared i'm
inside you kiara do you feel me
do you see me
dude purple i'm inside someone's hand
they're
i think we should probably make a bridge
over to the bigger platform before
that was too much the portal is too
powerful
what is this place this is cool
i think i don't know who wants to
felt wrong i want to build a bridge
we're going to connect over here
yeah i don't know we're building
materials oh here's
another 52 dirt i also have a lot
[Music]
okay wait which one should i build
because there's one close to our left or
should we just build upwards because we
could build stairs here
i got one i think we should go to the
main main uh platform over there where
the dragon is
yeah okay i am
just let almond do her her thing okay
don't go push her what the hell is this
you won't get anything back
is that normal does the sky look like
noise
to you as well guys yeah it looks itchy
it doesn't look like that in uh
in without the airflow oh my god
[Music]
yeah okay okay
you question do you know when you're
going to the nether and the thing that
goes
can you and you can like hit him hit the
fireballs back
can you do that with the ender dragon i
don't think this is what is the smoke
can i walk into it
no that's this fire in the ground that's
the end of dragon slap oh okay
is it gonna have to wait then we
couldn't build it
[Music]
oh wow i'm in bad shape right now okay
this is bad
it's bad i need to build fast
yeah how do we make the fire stop
oh
[Music]
please collect my items please oh
does it break walls also
i don't know we always missed the dragon
with that purple stuff it doesn't break
walls
all right we'll have to build walls
there get your stinky breath out of here
you big
scaly thing there by chance you guys
your stuff is all still here you just
gotta get here
okay i'm coming no actually maybe not
for cali
[Music]
yeah fire's done you can come in okay
that's fine i'm not gonna start over the
game
i want my things all right i got a bunch
of stuff oh god the diamond armor is
already so low we really should have
brought all of it yeah
what does that mean hello mr dwayne
whoa thank you wait what's in this what
is that i cleaned him up i
what is that oh huh
oh it's a enderman
it my game doesn't work anymore without
shaders
you need to choose build stairs you
really want me to step out there check
i chose 1.171.1 the
most recent release without the shadow
well this isn't great guys oh
sure my bow and arrows are gone
maybe i leave my stuff here for you yeah
i am using dots
wait can you guys serpentine
thank you watson you don't have to all
right
you sure there's there's more out
outside oh okay
do you go outside catch the fire
wait somewhere i'll
like uh manually maybe
i'll put your eyes in the sky what's
home
watch out behind you with fire fire fire
are you are you guys already fighting
the dragon oh no he's not yeah
he's coming back oh no
i mean the others can't see it i mean
this one's already angry so anyone have
a pickaxe so i can
you can't you can't use uh arrows or
arrangements for endermen yeah
home tony i may have a picnic may i ask
cool
ladies and gentlemen oh my god yeah that
works too
exactly what kelly died so whoever
picked up callie's stuff might have my
stuff
[Music]
i don't have pictures i don't know who
else kelly got all my stuff
okay should i turn off shaders did you
guys turn them off or did it mess up at
all
okay do you have to like reload the game
if you turn them off
i'm worried about my stuff yes oh my god
uh oh that's bad
can you i'm coming
thank you thank you because here is a
bit safer to give me my stuff
thank you i built tunnel stairs
okay that's better one side of armor and
like some dirt blocks some arrows
um i only have i only have one set
but you're wearing one set yours and you
have one yes extra right no
i'm i'm only wearing the one that i have
hey where are you
this is your this is definitely yours
yeah we have your axe
here you go oh you you fell down
everything that you have is myself
that's okay i just need some weapons
okay here do you have my dirt blocks do
you have an everest yeah
no dirt yeah okay wait can somebody kill
me so i can go back no no no no
you can't okay you know what let's you
keep from the other
wait i don't want all your stuff though
no it's fine it's fine there's more
stuff
uh here she asked me to
can you bring me one uh yeah we need one
full set of armor because we're sharing
right now okay
yeah there's two full sets here so i
don't have one either
oh do you have a oh damn it the
the golden apples oh uh yeah i have two
here
a dutch chip i just need one one
kelly do you currently have two options
yeah one potion two
no i don't have any it's fine okay it's
cool i'll just try not to die
oh do you guys have bows how many bows
yeah yeah please
one bowl please one bowl
a few more arrows that's scary
okay
[Music]
um go get it you guys are amazing we're
going to light your cheesy dreams wait i
have to let me want to please
the homie house see though because i
don't want to do that
i got a bonus i think i can make some
but they won't be enchanted
yeah and i'll be right back uh just
putting some building blocks just in
case
yeah how do we leave do we just leave
the game yeah
all right can i leave these things here
and then come back you guys
yeah would you be able to hold my things
real quick yeah my
my thanksgs oh yeah i guess technically
oh wow that's loud all right i'm going
to go
play some sudoku be right back okay and
good luck oh my glass bottles
oh i'm holding a shield god i'm such an
idiot
all right well i got regular bows wait
kelly
[Music]
three armor tops here three pants okay
we need one
one full one full set all right what i
missed yeah one full set for cali
and a top and a headphones don't make
anything else for me please just keep it
you guys
survived i prepared two seconds for
everyone there should be a
one more set for you and one more set
for me it is missing
but no i have everything sorry i have it
in right now
i was gonna go back with it hold on i'm
gonna be right back
yeah baby we have a because we can store
everything i mean i guess maybe we can't
store something
yeah can i shoot this thing or is it
gonna come after us
depends on what the thing is
shoes and pants okay
thank you mint ice cream anyone
destroy the crystals all right chet
they're at the top of the tower right
the crystals i've only ever watched
speed running of this so i won't i i
barely know what happens plus i always
bead runners always have like the uh the
like the program
outlines turned on and stuff sure oh hi
i mean we just gotta get good and shoot
it
i gotta get into this ice cream first of
all the crystals are the things making
the beans they feel it yeah
yeah okay i can't get into my ice cream
sandwich oops nice nice weather here
today on what you think
how's the weather up there you know no
it's a little bit
clutter with the chance of dragging
fireballs
what material is this is it like sponge
is
[Applause]
this glass bottle to capture something
yeah i don't don't worry about it
yeah and phase two of energy and it'll
come down and do like
that okay is it okay to eat the apple
now probably yeah right
yeah yeah wait wait where's callie
because callie said she uh
she'll be right back
it says the server is outdated yeah
that's because you turned out the
shaders uh
um i had the same thing just now you
have to
uh you gotta read download no no no no
use
use the option that says optifine the
normal one that you used up until now
then once the screen is open
uh you click into options and turn it
off manually
um before logging into the minecraft
server
um you know where you can choose the
minecraft service before you click that
you go on options and then turn off
uh at graphics settings you go to uh
shaders and then turn off the shader
manually
okay dragon is threatening
thank you
[Music]
no please don't give me anything please
don't no no no no i'm
[Music]
don't touch it i'm not touching it
all right she's back in the yukata for
revenge
we need him dragon's breath
oh no i
like this music
[Music]
oh that was sensory overload captain
hold on i need a what's what this is
nice pink pink
step
pink skelly okay
video settings and then
let's see shaders graphic settings
yes cheaters graphics dmca
sorry keep keep focusing on the game i
need food i need food i need food
is pig step part of the game or is this
a remix hello do you have
food please that sounds i don't know
like copyrighted
copyrighted
there's anyone literally from the game
oh we'll take a risk i'm standing right
next to you
anyone who has food
[Music]
yeah i got it thank you all right we're
good
[Music]
okay
trying to destroy the towers
we have to destroy them can i even shoot
that farm
oh i got my destroyed one i destroyed
one
it takes only one hit what the hell one
hits
as always right into the bullet oh yeah
did someone look at me
don't attack me guys don't attack me oh
my god
in a bullet bull's eye not bull's-eye
bullets eye i don't know
boom boom okay let's go
that is the second time first try
okay i got a problem i got one you get
enderman
on it a bit higher water use water
usually
oh my god
hold on where are you guys oh yeah we
gotta do the towels first
okay what all right
powers first oh okay
what
[Music]
it's only those with the cages right
tell us what all the cages we can do who
wants to watch me die
come on do it again
can you can you not drag oh no
drink the potion how do you drink a
potion
you used to like food yeah i destroyed
the third one
how many more do we have i can't
how do i destroy that one ah you're
going up that way
okay oh wait there's one here how do you
blow these beds up
maybe one more know why is that one so
low
i'm back it's yeah okay got one
okay i don't have an axe
oh this looks much better i can actually
see okay
oh you go right click right here
okay i have no more arrows
unfortunately thanks chet oh so far i
appreciate you guys
i'm good it's it's gonna be okay i'll
definitely building well it's
i'll climb i'll find you guys don't
worry wait i have no building
um i can does anyone have arrows
i have some uh i have infinity so i can
spare
14 for you i think oh right i'll
see you guys okay i think it's free or
something
i'm in front of you or behind you in
front of me
sorry i'm sorry i'm in front of inna i
see you guys
thank you gotta get the one inside thank
you
yep got it i have a picnic
[Music]
the under man use the water
oh i want it
i always just use a potato oh yeah
oh oh no yeah someone angry
crystals they seem pretty angry
okay wait are all the cages
destroyed or not i think so buddy
well we'll see i guess i'm missing all
my stuff
okay oh yes regenerates
it doesn't seem to be taking any energy
from any of the tallies anymore although
but is that one not two or three does
this mean it's still
shooting
oh nice i hit i hit him yay
[Music]
i can't see
thank you kfb
i think i was hitting for a little bit
but
you're not flying here maybe it actually
isn't good all right
i'm still gonna win enderman get lost
yeah bye nerd
where's my stuff where's my stuff
where's my stuff
where did i land oh that's not about
water oh i think
what did you see myself it's raining
oh yeah
taking back some of my water did he
regenerate or not
nope i don't know red
all right
until oh wait there's water did somebody
hit the bed
i was working perched on that would be
too easy
all right
stay in the water see the water stay in
the water okay okay yeah that's right
that's right
we can do it
yeah sorry i would have grabbed one
like i need to blow this lizard up with
this bed that's my life journey please
are you gonna attack me oh yes sarah i
prefer to die
i guess i think i prefer to die at this
point
you can get a sword
hey did he take my stuff no way he did
oh
[Music]
have the wind bro anymore i don't care
about the water admitting yeah i'll get
there like that did cara have a sword
i'll borrow it i'll get there
oh oh no don't don't don't
don't hey
[Music]
i am
it's fine oh at least he's not there
i threw i threw my things out there if
someone wants to take him
i know i had a sword or something like
that i hear
[Music]
did you pick up my stuff when you said
you're taking my sword
nope was that a yes or no
no no no under man
it's a creeper okay just kidding time to
go back to you oh
and my stuff near the edge no
[Music]
do i have a time is this here arrows and
pickaxe
you guys follow me
[Music]
the water kills me whoa that is a
powerful portal
okay is there a way we can put out this
fire
they didn't like no i don't think we
just have thought yet that you know
where kiara died
i i think i think the bottom oh okay the
sword it just use the bottle
blocked away i got a bottle i'll feel it
where's the fire in my head
i found what did you find my stuff okay
and all right
i am useful again okay let's go uh
as long as i have oh shoot i should be
fine
my things my helmet and my chest plate i
wonder if my bow is here
are we still doing the best strategy are
we trying i have yet to get it to work
okay it might be a pipe dream
shoot shoot that down
yeah i get them that's an experience
just i've only got a shovel but
goddammit i can try i miss you all my
show is dead
all right all right
[Music]
all right we got the bed in position
who's doing the bed get him down
yeah get him oh my god
[Music]
i'm definitely not helping but it's well
it's nice to feel like
[Music]
oh she went through the portal already
oh
we have to go yeah okay okay
pc go by minecraft it's the end of
minecraft it's over
no more is it over
let's go
yes take care it has reached a higher
level now
kiara halloween oh this is like meta
gao ghoul it can mean they're talking to
us
whoa that doesn't matter
we are part of the game wow
i like this player it played well it did
not give up
it is reading our thoughts as though we
they wear words on the screen
who wants to read next what about the
egg what egg i think we're at different
points
daddy left something important imagine
many things
when it is deep in the dream of a game
that's confusing
we go back maybe
i don't know can we re-enter the portal
oh yes you can
because like in that underworld
there are treasures and galleys so
from now on we can
explore that i'm gonna find the rails
for the ender
but yeah my my mission is to get an
elytra as soon as possible because of an
elytra you can fly
uh yeah as long as you have fireworks
cali you might want to get that yes
eventually but they're
yeah let's go
yeah it took us so long but we finally
did it
you guys did so much amazing prep work
in the beginning but
[Laughter]
it's so great oh when is a win
a win is a freaking win i'm just
privileged to have been able
to come along to watch the journey that
uh
that you guys prepared so hard for i
hope that my few arrows could be as well
yes of course our power together as five
is stronger than anything stronger than
that stupid in the dragon
yeah yeah flush him down the toilet
he's going restless so glad we did it
together
and yet they play the game nice guys
zero dance club hello can anybody else
say the same
that is pretty dope i will say yeah that
is kind of awesome
girl oh yeah pretty good with the bed
that was like something out of like a
crazy action movie
that was unbelievable speedrunners do
the bad girl do the bed
i think i got a lot of uh tower shots a
lot of towers
shot actually first try shots were quite
quite a lot of them i would definitely
give piara the sharpshooter award
but that was really only luck same with
them
with the um festival the summer festival
that was also only those games
skip credit oh how do i skip them can i
scroll up i want to get a screenshot of
gal guru player of games that's going to
be my gamer title now
i'm changing my manager jason i'm
changing my twitter bio
do i want to skip them
can i just go jump real quick back
inside i just wanna um
nightmare
would be a lot of fun to uh explore oh
the endermen are still here oh there's
your mind
they live here oh this is their home huh
yes
cool oh i see the i see the portal thing
wait once you go where does it spawn us
back
how do you go out oh there's the egg and
the stronghold you get spawned back
there's the portal thing a woman inhaled
on me
what inhaled the meat a woman gathered
the atoms and she inhaled
the player in her body we got bored
what are you reading
i think everybody else skipped it now
yeah i'm listening to that you're
missing the good stuff here
where are the treasures made from milk
and love
the player is made from nothing but milk
cali what do we do the end is basically
like
insanely endlessly huge so when you ask
for the treasure
sometimes there's a ton of treasure
spread over
millions and millions of miles oh wow
so you might not find it right away but
you gotta travel from like islands
there's like
all kinds of like islands separated you
gotta build like bridges and
to get to another island um
yes but what does it do
i can let it land on a torch you can
respawn the dragon with the egg
oh just leave it for now i guess okay
the dragonite yeah i won't touch it it
won't go anywhere
become daenerys
should i i don't know do i want to go
there
how do i get out sometimes
we're being spoken to and code you guys
zeros and ones
it's the mark of a true gamer wow
the universe said they love you by the
way oh
that's nice to know oh that was very
kind also the universe is inside you
oh that's true it makes me feel violent
no i'm not skipping the credits i gotta
know more universe says you're not alone
it's not a scuffed stairwell egg
there's the egg there
and then you never said and my mommy
said that you are the knight and my
mommy said
the darkness you fight is within you and
my mommy said the light you seek is
within you
am i
wow did this take us less than two hours
you guys yeah
wow in the universe i thought it would
take us three it's only
because you are like 20 minutes or
something
it's only gonna take longer to uh find
the place
only almost two am here i thought it
would be much later
uh-huh yeah oh wow don't hurt me
minecraft you're gonna die
before you die jump into the water or
jump into the portal
oh you know there would have been a
better choice here oh that's okay i can
go
let's go back in that moment i don't
know okay let's take another picture
outside yeah outside you guys are still
in there yeah outside
we'll make our way back anybody have a
pickaxe you
are i have pickaxe where are you uh
i'll come in okay they in or out
because i think they live outside okay
everyone
uh just uh read the title if you want to
use it that's important
okay oh stream heart challenge
that's right that's
[Music]
what are you doing
mr president
[Music]
oh nice i'm going to take some books
dude because i lost so many items what
the hell
did you guys see this dress up here
there's books in it there's not much oh
oh
well now what
um
went i i might have been the uh first
one to open the chest and i might have
been the one who took something out of
the chest oh
what was in the chest um yeah two
two books that were in enchanted nothing
super special i think
oh yeah well i'm level 68 68 wow
wow it almost gets a nice how nice
nine
i was over 30 earlier hey how do we get
an elytra
can we get that now what i don't know
you have to look for treasures
in the in the world yeah oh
one do up you guys
there are enough for japan members to
keep on getting new ones
even though they lose them all the time
how many are there there is no limit
it will take a while infinite might take
a while to explore because you have to
find the place
where you have it and then you gotta
like clear out
stuff gotta kill stuff
oh we wanted to take a picture
yeah should we not take that like in the
end
that would wouldn't that be cool again
in the end and then we'll just take a
picture and quickly go outside again
sure how do you want to do that wait
where is it where is it
is it where is it that goes back
[Music]
all right okay i'm going in did we get
the egg
i think you have to leave it there
leave it down until we know how to take
it safely
let's get to the egg and take a picture
in front of it
yeah let's do it you will give me one of
my
um self-touch pickaxe so
one percent i have cut in corners
oh yeah that's
uh someone looked at them
uh
because i thought something dropped uh
why don't we take the picture
in front of you though under under man
this thing one
[Music]
if i switch views will it make me look
at them
um not necessarily
touch go get it this is like opera
nice and easy you guys you can't mine it
don't touch it don't touch it don't
touch it
touch the long ones then break the block
under it with a torch
now the block under it that has somebody
says you need a piston
yeah just don't touch it right now yeah
later let's just just ignore the link we
can take a picture with the egg
picture yeah yeah yeah the egg is part
of the journey
you blow myself up okay do we want to
get
close like maybe in front here
oh we could build like our own pillars
right behind the egg and look really
cool you stand on
a pillar do you have that yeah some
building material
then i fell in the portal
i have thumbs up oh i'll take him kelly
here you go are you sure oh
it might have oh no i got it okay um
then
okay just one touch it won't work will
it oh don't touch it
there's a little touch oh no so
victory now yeah where are you
wow they're real quick they like to move
with the blocks mm-hmm
oh yeah they're real mad yeah
i'll sit here for a million years until
i get this i'll just stand over it i'll
just run
i'm in i'm a homie
[Music]
oh they're angry this is going to be
tough yeah
[Music]
uh where is
it i'll be back okay okay
i'll be back thumbs up
this place is a lot less scary without
the uh dragon
search how to get the yeah without the
dragon
so without the shaders but yeah it was
not the dragon as well
yeah the sky is prettier without the
shaders but it's not yet it's much
easier to see without it
yeah pitch black but i mean yeah it
wasn't much better when it was nice
you can get his head they don't share
the program
you can mount it to the wall
use any tool or even your bare hands hit
the ender dragon egg until it breaks oh
yeah remember
remember mikko senpai and suicide senpai
uh wearing those
ender dragon heads in the some of the
hills
creepy all right this is good
okay should we turn uh i guess
for every picture we can look into a
different direction
okay i think this angle works for me
okay
oh yeah this one works for me too
[Music]
i'll just look where you stand i guess
that makes that works
oh am i looking in the right side amen
yeah yeah yeah okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
anyone else who wants a picture um
i'm let's see uh yeah sure i'll look
over to you then i should be looking in
the right direction
all right everyone look up this way
ready
i got it i got it i got it okay i got it
all right i'm jumping in the portal all
right let's go
all right here we go
does anyone want to like go back home or
like
is everyone ending now or because i feel
like i will get
lost yeah i want to go charge your
hunting later
okay oh yeah you know what else are we
not doing the angle how do we do that
we'll look at it later okay yeah
uh no i won
can i have one i will i won i'm i'm
playing
minecraft later today guys so i'll just
uh
log out here i guess okay i'll probably
need more stuff
just don't take all the treasures
there's infinite treasures
oh cool okay well yay i don't know about
you guys ladies
but i'll be leaving yep me too
thanks so much everyone for the fun time
so proud we didn't
get it yeah
it was quite an experience yeah thank
you for everything you guys
prepare yes thank you it would not have
been easy mode without all of your
preparations no problems
is always cooperating whenever you
needed help
thanks for the fun time
[Music]
thanks guys bye catch you later
wait
hi i just want to say oh properly
i'll say it to you do you guys say
properly goodbye
that was oh my god let's have a tiny
chat maybe 10 minutes
let me fix the chat thank you guys for
the support
i hope you also enjoyed the the collab i
did with ina
there was a little warm up but it
stressed me out a little bit
um yeah oh yeah i don't know if you
if you if you guys are not on twitter
you might have missed it but uh
the summer conventions were announced
that's that's why i was
telling you guys that um this summer
will be
very very busy and exciting
because uh um all of halloween
will be in i think there's five
different conventions
and uh i'm going to three of them
uh and it's like for every convention
there's like other members uh
coupling up um the first one
will be one week after dokomi um
uh now for this these conventions
different to dokomi
uh we're not going in person but those
are real conventions that are actually
happening
happening in reality not in like online
only
in n a n a area i think there is like
one or two in canada
and then like i don't really know much
about like american
cities and stuff but uh
there is a one i think in calgary i
don't know where that is
or orlando uh
some places free in the u.s too in
canada
uh i'm going to
which one do i have it like
somewhere written down wait a second
wait a second let me
one second i'll find the information a
list list there there's a list somewhere
let's scroll scroll scroll
from scroll scroll
oh there we go okay i have it so i will
be
um
12 august to 15 august but i think
not all the days just i think just one
day
with amelia i will be at
mega con orlando
uh in orange county convention center
now i will not be there in person
but we will be there exclusively me and
ame for
exclusive content there so if you are
able to go to mega
orlando you will see me and ahmed if
you're
able to go to are these dates correct
they should be correct
uh they're on 10th september to 12
september
right before our one year anniversary
kelly me and ame will be at calgary expo
in stampede
stampede stampede park in canada
um but we'll we'll obviously not be
there on our
anniversary day um i think i don't know
if they are already put up the exact
days
yeah um but we will be there uh
and then another one where i will be at
is in the fan expo boston
on the 3rd september to the 5th
september with
ame and ena oh
i just realized there is no convention
that i am at with guru
by the way this was just um kind of like
like for example amma is going to all of
them that's just because she
she's like up for it but we were like
it was it was our choice to choose to
which ones were going or not
um but i was like i don't want to go to
i would i don't want to be at all of
them because it will fill up my schedule
too much and
um it will be stressful so i just choose
shows free free conventions
um kind of randomly because i don't
really
have any connection with any of these
places
so it was just basically randomly chosen
um yes i don't i don't even have
many viewers in canada i think uh
so but still i'm going to one of the the
ones in canada
but i hope that some of you uh from
canada
and also some of you from america are
able to come to
one of those conventions and are uh able
to see oh they're so canadian
thank you i think like for example
doesn't cali have like uh
like quite the following in canada for
some reason i just remember her having
these
these battles between uh canadian and
american viewers so i always have this
image that
she has a ton of canadian viewers
um i mean of course there's there are
there are some
i'm not saying i don't have any canadian
fans at all i'm not saying that
i'm just not sure if it's that many but
thank you
thank you guys so this summer will be uh
here and there a lot
some some conventions sprinkles here and
there
um dokomi however is the first one
coming up very soon and
at what date was it again
august the 7th in germany
so don't worry guys i know there's some
of you crying because
they're not in n.a uh don't worry i mean
i'm going to
to germany uh in person actually
um in august so who knows maybe
maybe if um
if events want us they will bring us
anywhere s-e-a
europe wherever but i want to tell you
something
the only reason why dokomi or
they could call me first of all was
possible was because
uh some of my viewers uh
wrote to what you know back then when i
was like right to the convention some of
my viewers wrote to doc on me
and told them yo we want takanasi kiara
as our guest
and it worked out and they invited me so
you guys who are currently a little bit
depressed or espresso
because they're like i'm not in any will
come to see me
well do it like my german fans uh
write to whatever big convention you
have in your country
and tell them i want this person or a
whole life english
as a guest if it's a tiny convention
they might not be able to
you know fund it or whatever um but if
it's like a big convention dokomi for
example is the biggest
anime convention in germany um
so yeah but uh just yeah right
they you have to let them know some
conventions aren't
you they're they're a bit late uh and
i know some organizers who are who don't
even really know like what youtubers
are yet they're a bit behind in on the
time
so you got to let them know that you're
interested in having youtubers as
um guests and then you can make it
possible you have to let them know
though and also you have to let them
know quite in advance because they
plan like um let's say half a year
half a year in advance so for the summer
conventions it's already too late but
you can already
let them know for winter conventions or
for next year spring conventions or
whatever okay
so yeah i think totally possible as well
for sea conventions or wherever i mean
we might not be there
we're not might not necessarily be flown
over
to uh whichever city but
i also wouldn't rule it out completely
once everything comes down
again hopefully next year then traveling
might be
a thing too and then we can do meet and
greets like i'm doing a document
oh by the way the meet and greet some
people were confused how that works
uh at dokomi in germany i'm doing a meet
and greet where i will be in a room
uh in a on a screen i will be in a
different room
in a virtual room but i will be
somewhere
somewhere in the city and uh
so you you will be able to enter a room
at the convention
that has a screen and a microphone and a
webcam probably
and uh i will be able to communicate
with you through that for like a few
minutes one-on-one
one-on-one i i got that idea
um from um japanese members
not the usual you will be going into the
usual room i believe i will be talking
to you from my office
um but yeah the japanese members have
done that a few times already
uh they've done events like that in in
japan in tokyo
and so on so i was like oh if i'm
able to go to this convention in person
i kind of want to try this meet and
greet thing
um you can still sign up for the meet
and greet thing but only if you have
tickets for saturday
that's a bit um unfortunate because the
tickets for saturday are already sold
out so only people who already have it
are able to sign up for that i'm sorry
about that
really sorry really sorry i wish i wish
there were still tickets for you to get
i know that was a bit disappointing um
but i would still be excited to
meet whoever is signing up for the meet
and greet
but yeah so what i'm trying to say with
that is
if you are unhappy with the fact that
we're going to n a conventions because
you are not in n
a well then go get your
uh email open it up write to whichever
convention
is closest to you tell them you want
youtubers as you guys tell them who
specifically and then yeah
conventions usually invite people who
they think um will bring in people
who they think are popular or yeah
currently
hyped up or whatever so
you you cannot just expect to have your
closest convention inviting them just
out of nowhere without
you even letting them know that you want
them there get what i'm trying to say
that's how dog of me happened yeah
so uh that's what i wanted to say what
else what else
um yeah tomorrow tomorrow minecraft
stream
uh i put it on the schedule that i
uploaded on the youtube uh
community not the one on twitter the
twitter one is
uh a bit inaccurate right what was wrong
with that one oh yeah because the
the play the tales of our eyes play
is not public that is private but
yeah i am going to go treasure hunting
but i think i'll have to go
back home home
to our base once to get stuff in order
to get treasure hunting i'm not sure
um but yeah that is the plan for two
days
for me it's already 2 a.m today's
minecraft stream for you guys it's
tomorrow maybe or
today i don't know um
yeah i'll probably need supplies right
uh
i'll find out what i need honestly i'm
not informed about treasure hunting in
the end
uh so i'll and for myself well you guys
can inform me
but yeah that stream i will schedule it
once i am awake again
create a new home near the stronghold i
guess so but like i don't really know
what i need
um yeah um
our goal will be to find
elite trust and maybe the first one who
knows
just go north eh is it always enough
super long ice bridge i don't know if
you want to bring my eyes to never as it
seems kind of kind of slippery
eh i need eh
i need endo pearls i don't need ender
pearls do i
it do i need ender pearls in order to
get
electrons what
you need like 10 stacks of what yeah
i do
oh wait what i can get and the pearls
where
in phoenix
[Music]
ah because they can teleport me to the
islands ah
yeah i've seen that ah can i not just
build bridges
[Music]
but i guess i'll end up pearls
i've seen them being used like that
before
i don't need ender eyes right i don't
need the ones that that inna was
shooting around
because don't those don't teleport yeah
i need the
normal and the pearls right
they're useful but not necessary okay
okay okay so i just need
end up pearls and what did you guys say
what was the other thing i said i needed
[Music]
sorry i'm really having trouble
breathing today
in the chest eh how do i but i can
already make it in the chest right why
do i need it
why do i need that because uh because
i'll be traveling so far and the under
chest works like
wait what does it how does it work like
again i don't even know
i shield the bone and then the chest
safe keeping okay i guess so okay
[Music]
maybe i can borrow you know signatures
in their chest and the chest
ah i save the elite render
mm-hmm
oh man i am i'm surprised how
how quickly we lost
so much in the beginning
i thought you know i thought you know
there will be some leftover
armor there will be some left over um
weapons
i was so wrong what the man
but okay thank god in the end it was it
was guilty enough it was barely enough
um yeah we did it anyway
thank god i can't believe i got like
three first try shots for the towers
holy holy
what the hell was that what was wrong
with
me what was right with me oh my god i
didn't i
i was just randomly aiming
i didn't i wasn't even trying i felt
like
it's not gonna that's gonna miss anyway
whatever
and i was the same when i was at the
summer festival
yeah i was able to shoot those that i
couldn't see but the ones that i was
able to see i wasn't sure how to hit
those
what is going on
channeling my inner tiara right tiana
confirm
close your eyes next time but if you
close your eyes
hidden fps player oh no no
no no no chiara you carried
[Laughter]
not alone not alone not not my effort
alone but
i'm i'm happy i was able to uh do some
damage and do some stuff
yes yes
uh sorry was there anything else i
wanted to talk about
uh oh yeah super chats tomorrow uh after
minecraft stream
i guess uh let me take a look at my
schedule
[Music]
how long will do you think the minecraft
treasure hunting stream will be a long
one
two hours three hours five hours how
long does that take
but we we need endless pearls and
yeah a bit oh
that that won't be long huh orangey
depends
could be lucky two to three four plus
because i don't really
sorry i don't really have time to
prepare beforehand because i'm playing
tails over rise beforehand
so i'm just i just boosted
i i don't really i don't really have
time to
prepare for the stream you know because
i have to play
exclusively um a tales of varieties
a test plane
[Laughter]
i'm sorry
yeah uh
oh my god i'm i'm stressed out
uh yeah all right
all right all right all right okay all
right i'm good
okay so i'll see you uh
at the minecraft stream
all turkey i have flashbacks
time to go pet the cats yes
my fluffy babies let the chat stop for a
moment
all right stress down hi
[Music]
oh well i'm trying to i'm trying to
think thank you guys thank you for the
support
um i i will i think i will go
i think don't forget oh wait does i'm
still have my pickaxe oh
oh all right into the
i mean whenever you're done with my
pick pickaxe
just put it either
in our hometown in my
chest or at the ender portal
wherever is convenient for you
okay stream high challenger is she still
streaming are the others still streaming
i mean kelly quit i know that
oh wait no okay are they still streaming
[Music]
i thought ahmed was like for real gonna
build the tunnel right now
[Laughter]
kind of seemed like it she was like
already preparing
um i mean
what's an industry is working fast wait
if she's already done then
didn't she already put the pickaxe back
she has mario oh yeah that's right she
wanted to play mario today cause she
didn't play it
unless today yeah yeah yeah yeah did she
put it somewhere in the end of the
stream did you guys see this did anyone
watch the point of view of ahmed
did she put it anywhere
what did she just ended without putting
it anywhere
i'm still digging still digging
digging forever all right if she already
logged on and it's not playing anymore
then i'll attack her
okay
okay she's using it okay okay well until
the next minecraft stream
she'll probably put it somewhere um
all right then yeah yeah
we'll have more time to talk tomorrow uh
when i'm
playing minecraft alone i'll see you
guys there
and please
have a nice evening everyone
[Music]
uh what do you mean callie is not
i'll i'll message her i'll message her
[Music]
meow
okay yes i missed it
i don't want to add something
[Music]
i know i could just leave but my brain
is too empty to leave right now
[Music]
okay okay i'm done no no thoughts have
had empty
uh yeah
[Music]
good
hello
[Music]
streams box
so
[Music]