​​​ ​Hey, guys!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kanata-senpai!​ ​​
​​ ​Since when can you speak English?!​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​Today I am the 10-second drill sergeant!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Understood.​ ​​
​​​ ​Scary!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll do my best.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​What's going on?​ ​​
​​​ ​You all sound so out of it!​ ​​
​​​ ​What the heck is that face you're making?!​ ​​
​​​ ​People can do anything​ ​​
​​ ​if they've got 10 seconds, which means...​ ​​
​​​ ​Get ready 'cuz I'm gonna drill​ ​​
​​ ​that idea into your lousy heads!​ ​​
​​​ ​Right now I'm gonna have​ ​​
​​ ​you guys introduce yourselves.​ ​​
​​​ ​Within 10 seconds, naturally. So here we go.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, sir!​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll start with that​ ​​
​​ ​little chicken over there! Go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who?​ ​​
​​​ ​Who's a chicken?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, oh, oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kikkeriki!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm hololive EN's top idol,​ ​​
​​​ ​boss of the major fast food chain KFP,​ ​​
​​​ ​and I can do it all, so leave it to me,​ ​​
​​​ ​Takanashi Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey now, hey now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​That wasn't totally awful​ ​​
​​ ​for someone going first.​ ​​
​​​ ​Though you did go a tiny bit over time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Next up, the octopus girl!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ready, go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Uhh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello! Nice to meet you.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Ninomae Ina'nis​ ​​
​​ ​from hololive EN Myth.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm happy to be here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Talk about mood whiplash!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow, that ten seconds felt like it was thirty!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, that's fine.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Last up, let's hear from​ ​​
​​ ​that diva in the middle.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ready, go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh?​ ​​
​​​ ​HiRyS! It's IRyS.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm IRyS, the VSinger from hololive EN.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you for invitingmetotheshow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​You even left a second to spare.​ ​​
​​​ ​Good, good!​ ​​
​​​ ​I am top class, after all...​ ​​
​​​ ​(Top class ego)​ ​​
​​​ ​10-Second Pressure Survival​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's the training program for today!​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll be tackling various challenges​ ​​
​​​ ​within a 10-second time limit!​ ​​
​​​ ​Q. What is this?​ ​​
​​​ ​An apple!​ ​​
​​​ ​A chicken...?​ ​​
​​​ ​but if you fail even one,​ ​​
​​ ​this video will end instantly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Instant End​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, no!​ ​​
​​​ ​We wanna make this a long one!​ ​​
​​​ ​It could end immediately​ ​​
​​ ​after the first challenge.​ ​​
​​​ ​That'd be an absolute disaster.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll put you through that hell if I have to!​ ​​
​​​ ​Even though you're an angel?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, enough with the wit!​ ​​
​​​ ​Enough with the wit, okay?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Choose your first challenge​ ​​
​​ ​from one of these categories!​ ​​
​​​ ​Shiritori​ ​​
​​​ ​One-off Gag​ ​​
​​​ ​What's This?​ ​​
​​​ ​Calculation​ ​​
​​​ ​Kanji​ ​​
​​​ ​Quiz​ ​​
​​​ ​What should we pick?​ ​​
​​​ ​What would you like?​ ​​
​​​ ​What to do?​ ​​
​​​ ​How about we do shiritori​ ​​
​​ ​as a warm-up of sorts?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sounds good.​ ​​
​​​ ​Warming up!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​We can just wing it.​ ​​
​​​ ​So that's why the bird picked it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, so you're going with shiritori.​ ​​
​​​ ​You just need to come up with​ ​​
​​ ​one word each within 10 seconds.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Turn Order​ ​​
​​​ ​Ina'nis​ ​​
​​​ ​IRyS​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll start with the "ri" from shiritori!​ ​​
​​​ ​Starting with Ina'nis-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ri... ri... ri...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ri—​ ​​
​​​ ​Ringo (apple)!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, good!​ ​​
​​​ ​Go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Go...​ ​​
​​​ ​Um...​ ​​
​​​ ​Go... go...​ ​​
​​​ ​Go?​ ​​
​​​ ​Gorilla!​ ​​
​​​ ​Where'd that come from?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gorilla?!​ ​​
​​​ ​*Amane Kanata is referred to as a "gorilla"​ ​​
​​ ​for having a grip strength exceeding 50 kg.​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys are too slow!​ ​​
​​​ ​I was trying to think of something else!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gorilla?!​ ​​
​​​ ​She allowed them another chance​ ​​
​​ ​for kindly trying to avoid saying "gorilla."​ ​​
​​​ ​Gorilla is a no-no.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, second attempt.​ ​​
​​​ ​From the "ri" in shiritori! Start!​ ​​
​​​ ​The "ri" from ringo (apple).​ ​​
​​​ ​Ri...?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ringo (apple)!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gochisou (feast)!​ ​​
​​​ ​Usagi (rabbit)!​ ​​
​​​ ​Challenge cleared!​ ​​
​​​ ​Great success! Well done! Congrats!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank goodness!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good!​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll just forget about​ ​​
​​ ​that first one and move on.​ ​​
​​​ ​On to the next challenge!​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you wanna do?​ ​​
​​​ ​Shiritori​ ​​
​​​ ​One-off Gag​ ​​
​​​ ​What's This?​ ​​
​​​ ​Calculation​ ​​
​​​ ​Kanji​ ​​
​​​ ​Quiz​ ​​
​​​ ​Because I can do any of them!​ ​​
​​​ ​Any of them?​ ​​
​​​ ​That includes the one-off gag?​ ​​
​​​ ​I can do any of them!​ ​​
​​​ ​Shall we do the one-off gag then?​ ​​
​​​ ​Are we gonna do that one?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hold on a sec!​ ​​
​​​ ​That might end the video,​ ​​
​​ ​so let's try something else instead.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hang on to those.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm, the quiz, then?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sounds good to me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay! Okay! Quiz!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm going to ask you a question.​ ​​
​​​ ​The answer will be​ ​​
​​ ​an English word with three letters.​ ​​
​​​ ​For example, if the answer is "sky,"​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara will write "S,"​ ​​
​​​ ​Ina'nis will write "K,"​ ​​
​​​ ​and IRyS will write "Y."​ ​​
​​​ ​The three of you will​ ​​
​​ ​spell out the answer together.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ya got it?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Got it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Turn Order​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​Ina'nis​ ​​
​​​ ​IRyS​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, here's the question!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ba-dum!​ ​​
​​​ ​Shirakami Fubuki's ears​ ​​
​​ ​are the ears of which animal?​ ​​
​​​ ​I know, I know!​ ​​
​​​ ​Start the countdown!​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys know, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​You know this one, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course!​ ​​
​​​ ​The ears of one of​ ​​
​​ ​your most senior colleagues!​ ​​
​​​ ​Easy! Easy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Easy!​ ​​
​​​ ​We finished so quickly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Time's up!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now let's take a look at your answer.​ ​​
​​​ ​Open them all up!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​Challenge cleared!​ ​​
​​​ ​I was like, "What's gonna happen​ ​​
​​ ​if that's not the answer!"​ ​​
​​​ ​Great work!​ ​​
​​​ ​The connection between you three​ ​​
​​ ​was clearly demonstrated here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Perfect answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mhm!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Our connection​ ​​
​​ ​and the respect for our senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Time for the next challenge!​ ​​
​​​ ​How about "What's This?"​ ​​
​​​ ​Shiritori​ ​​
​​​ ​One-off Gag​ ​​
​​​ ​What's This?​ ​​
​​​ ​Calculation​ ​​
​​​ ​Kanji​ ​​
​​​ ​Quiz​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm down for that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, then we'll go with "What's This?"​ ​​
​​​ ​If you can each name the thing​ ​​
​​ ​shown to you within 10 seconds,​ ​​
​​​ ​Bamboo shoot!​ ​​
​​​ ​Onion!​ ​​
​​​ ​Carrot!​ ​​
​​​ ​then you will clear this challenge.​ ​​
​​​ ​Challenge cleared!​ ​​
​​​ ​The pictures will all be​ ​​
​​ ​things you see often,​ ​​
​​​ ​so clearing this should be a piece of cake.​ ​​
​​​ ​Turn Order​ ​​
​​​ ​IRyS​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​Ina'nis​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, let's start!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ready, begin!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hamburger!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ramen!​ ​​
​​​ ​Koala!​ ​​
​​​ ​Challenge cleared!​ ​​
​​​ ​Excellent!​ ​​
​​​ ​Great!​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys are fast!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was too easy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Give us something more challenging!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I would be fine with that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is that how it is?​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, then. I'll give you​ ​​
​​ ​a harder one next time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's move right along​ ​​
​​ ​to the next challenge!​ ​​
​​​ ​Shiritori​ ​​
​​​ ​One-off Gag​ ​​
​​​ ​What's This?​ ​​
​​​ ​Calculation​ ​​
​​​ ​Kanji​ ​​
​​​ ​Quiz​ ​​
​​​ ​Which do you want?​ ​​
​​​ ​Should we try calculation?​ ​​
​​​ ​Calculation?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are we gonna be okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​Calculation it is!​ ​​
​​​ ​Calculation...​ ​​
​​​ ​Turn Order​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​IRyS​ ​​
​​​ ​Ina'nis​ ​​
​​​ ​It's time to start!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ready, begin!​ ​​
​​​ ​Keep trying...​ ​​
​​​ ​Um?​ ​​
​​​ ​Time's up!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's the end!​ ​​
​​​ ​You failed!​ ​​
​​​ ​That means we're saying goodbye!​ ​​
​​​ ​Stay tuned for their one-off gags!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's over?​ ​​
​​​ ​We're done?​ ​​
​​​ ​And I wanted to hear your one-off gags, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​10-Second Pressure Survival​ ​​
​​​ ​I heard that you'd prepared​ ​​
​​ ​a lot of stuff for your one-off gags.​ ​​
​​​ ​We did, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​You did!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well...​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh, yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Y-Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​One-off gag - Ninomae Ina'nis​ ​​
​​​ ​Ring ring... ring ring...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ring ring...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey...​ ​​
​​​ ​She promised she would pick up!​ ​​
​​ ​What a phony!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I'd better take​ ​​
​​ ​these bad puns and pun-t them.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep.​ ​​
​​​ ​You tried, Inya.​ ​​
​​​ ​Those were actually kinda amazing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe we should have had you do those.​ ​​
​​​ ​IRyS-chan, wanna give it a go?​ ​​
​​​ ​One-off gag - IRyS​ ​​
​​​ ​Why was six afraid of seven?​ ​​
​​​ ​Because seven eight nine!​ ​​
​​​ ​B-​ ​​
​​​ ​Or so you'd think!​ ​​
​​​ ​But numbers can't feel​ ​​
​​ ​any emotion at all, can they?!​ ​​
​​​ ​The energy in that...​ ​​
​​​ ​Seven eight nine!​ ​​
​​​ ​The vibes are getting weird in here.​ ​​
​​​ ​One-off gag - Takanashi Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm going to do some animal impressions.​ ​​
​​​ ​Please try and guess what they are.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't like where this is going!​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel this one's also gonna hurt.​ ​​
​​​ ​Fine, fine, go.​ ​​
​​​ ​I've got three.​ ​​
​​​ ​Start!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​It sounds like you're drowning.​ ​​
​​​ ​That was a frog! Next!​ ​​
​​​ ​A crow?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a crow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Last one!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, a crow!​ ​​
​​​ ​A chicken!​ ​​
​​​ ​Chicken!​ ​​
​​​ ​No!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a phoenix!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara gone crazy, huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh...​ ​​
​​​ ​The punchline was​ ​​
​​ ​"It's not a chicken but a phoenix."​ ​​
​​​ ​She even thought of a punchline for it.​ ​​
​​​ ​With a toast to your courage,​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​we'll say goodbye.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cheers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Goodbye!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please subscribe to hololive & our talents' channels!​ ​​
​​​ ​Also, check out​ ​​
​​ ​the previous episodes of 10-Second Pressure!​ ​​