[Music]
so
i'm so big
i'm too big
oh sure
hello
welcome
everybody to a super chat reading stream
nothing special just super chat super
chat super chat super chat
super chat as far as you can see
um
hello how are you doing today
uh
currently lacking energy a little bit
but we'll see
if it comes back to me
yeah thank you for asking how are you
guys
how
is you
um
[Music]
yesterday was so much fun thank you
that's very sweet
he's tired same low energy
i'm fantastic wow
did you eat yet yeah
i've had um breakfast and lunch some
kind of lunch
slacking on the job
you're at job you're slacking with this
job at your other job
that's perfectly fine
a hot dog yummy
game announcements do have me hyped
aha
yeah i didn't watch the
state of play
yesterday but
i only know that you know some yakuza
games were announced is there anything
else interesting
[Music]
tekken oh i saw that but that's not
really interesting for me is it
another horizon trailer that showed more
stuff oh
that's it
they had
nothing else yeah i guess i can say i
won too much of nintendo direct so
it would be
it would be a very luxurious complaint
of me to complain about the state of
play
[Music]
most important things were all shown in
the nintendo direct
er
i mean
yeah when i was like a child i think i
played some tekken on like a
some
in a game center in italy or so i don't
know but it's not really my type of game
i mean i know it it's familiar to me but
yeah
more interested in yakuza
but
i'm surprised they announced games until
2024 what
what
that's
wow
quite the
open planning
oh
um
thank you
it's not unusual that developers do that
well it's dangerous to do that so
ahead of time like two years ahead of
time because
then
[Music]
you know things might happen and you
you might not be able to finish in time
but i mean maybe they were confident
enough
they dropped both judgment games on
stream today
aha
what does that mean
i know the judgment games but what does
that mean they dropped them on steam
did they just release in english or what
oh uh-huh
just released on pc uh-huh
i was it was ps4 only aha okay oh
that's good
i'm
[Music]
come on give me something
uh let me open my audio stock folder
honestly i wouldn't mind listening to
just the old kiwawa music for a while
but
uh
[Music]
what are we to listen to
sorry brain slow
oh audio stuck
hmm
i wanna go on audio stock
get something new
i wanna i want something that's like
animal crossing but for real like the
last one i found was too short
uh
atsu
in in japanese
atsumori
[Music]
money money
ah wait
this one i've got it
oh wait
ah
[Music]
true i had this one but nah
that's not 100 like
what about this one
[Music]
oh that's a yes
i like it
[Music]
yeah accordion or something like that
what the [\h__\h] is your problem with it
sounding french huh
it's a beautiful country
have some respect
i'll be using it
whether you like it or not
no there's no such thing like that
albedo shut up
baby you live in [\h__\h] medieval times
okay
more sherry indeed bugget
this is supposed to
be animal crossing music okay
so that's more you play business
[Music]
out of tune you sound a little out of
tune
[Music]
i have people friend friend french
people curse so much well maybe
maybe i am french
that's why i curse so much
that's why people say excuse my french
right
[Music]
people do do say that when they
um
curse right
right
that was what they say right excuse my
french
[Music]
that's funny actually
oh i had an interesting thought or maybe
not so interesting but
guys
did the people in the middle age
call the age that they were in also the
middle age
or was that something people in the
later age
decided that that was the middle age
[Laughter]
of course it's shut up
no one called it one of them okay but i
want to know who decided
you guys suck
you know you know you guys
remember when
you were in school back in the day
and
you uh raised your hand
and you say to the teacher i have a
stupid question that the teacher says
there are no stupid questions
see that's
so
kind
that
that world made you think
there are no stupid questions but you
guys make me feel like there are stupid
questions so you guys suck
i should have never asked
i'll only ask google from now on
that's what you get
[Music]
okay guys
enough of that yes kiana state is
bullied exactly
being bullied here
let's read super chats
i had a meeting with my tax person today
uh
i saw some numbers
good meeting well i mean a meeting with
a tax person where you see numbers is
never a good meeting it's just a
depressing meeting
but um
[Music]
it's really nice that she's not
stressing me the [\h__\h] out
um i'm like is this really okay we
haven't done anything yet and she's like
yeah yeah
but now i'm finally
making my payment
um
in october
it's fine apparently
[Laughter]
the
deadline or not even strict deadline
apparently this is october
yeah
but i'm saying this because
i'm saying i'm grateful for her not
stressing me out because um
i
i had a like this is my tax person okay
but i looked for another um
person to work for me
uh
such as a
financial advisor because i just felt
like i don't know what the [\h__\h] i'm
doing you know
um and i thought it might help because
some people told me
it would help you know
and i looked for one only a while ago
like in in early summer or late spring i
don't even remember when that was but
i i went to an appointment with one
and
wow that lady she talked and talked
so much and
she was nice though we had a good
conversation i guess but
it was kind of mentally exhausting
because she was
way more talkative than i was
and such a positive and happy
attitude
that i could not keep up with
she should be a beacher
honestly
yeah
crazy whoa i was like oh so mentally
drained after one hour
of talking with her
um even on the phone still the same
but then yeah um she was like
i will let you know if i think i want to
work with you it's like i was
auditioning
i don't think this is so normal
that
you're kind of like auditioning for them
i feel like
yeah that's like an exception
and then a while later like uh
like two weeks later so
yeah she would call me and be like i
want to work with you how about you
and i'm like
yeah yeah let's go i'm so excited woohoo
trying to keep up with her you know
um and then we set like another meeting
uh
very far in the in the future
and then
something's happened
uh it's not like i was given like a
deadline or anything but suddenly
suddenly
she was like
i want this and this and this
within tomorrow
and i'm like
ugh
like some documents and then
and then
um
i was i was planning on doing it yeah
tomorrow i was like tomorrow
i was planning on doing it
um like it was until a certain time of
tomorrow
yeah and and then
uh unfortunately i already had some
important stuff to do on that day
and i did not even get home
until
like around that time when the deadline
was
so i was not able to keep the deadline
and she did however say that if i don't
keep the deadline she's going to
um she's not interested anymore in
working with me then
because um you know
um
yeah you know me
me receiving that spot uh
it was quite serious and she doesn't
just give it to anyone and uh yeah
and oh god she
and she's she she can't have it you know
like this this is not not acceptable and
i mean i mean i mean if i had the
deadline earlier
it was it was like more than like
uh like a later deadline and she wants
something until then suddenly for a
certain reason she wanted it now
um
i was trying but i couldn't and then i
was like
well
you know what i think
think i'm probably both probably better
off without each other
cause
i'm obviously
not good enough for her and me i don't
have the energy for her so
whatever i guess so then um
after that happened i got an email
saying
well since you weren't able to provide
what i needed i am not interested in
working with you anymore
goodbye yeah
so before we even got to properly
start working with one another
we have now broken up
and i was
honestly at first i tried but then i was
telling myself
this is not worth the stress i think
um
and not worth
no
the energy i would spend on this
[Music]
i don't think i care
about this
ending
[Music]
so
whatever i'll find someone else if i
really feel like getting someone else
um
yeah it was hot no i mean i think once
you get the ball rolling it was like one
meeting per year
and it wouldn't really be high
maintenance but
still that was
no
i didn't feel like it
that's weird
but
it's okay
like she was really nice and she was
i'm sure she's great at her job
but we don't suit each other
that's for sure
and you have to chase that you chase
after her with more money
[Music]
if your job you should still 100 find an
actual professional to handle this stuff
[Music]
callie the thing about cali
well that's i don't think that's exactly
the same situation
i don't think i'm in the same situation
as dad
but anyway
that's too
too serious talk whatever who's canada
talking about financial advisor breakup
ah
yes it's
fun yeah whatever
whatever
now
oh one good thing guys though what i was
told by my tax person
i was
like considering i
went to for example
the maldives
basically for content creation and
literally created content every day
even enough content to stream about it
afterwards i was like can i write this
off and and she was like
you know what actually yes
if you really made
content
every day then it's not even like one of
those business trips where half of it is
laser and half of it is business no you
say you make literary content ever and
honestly that's that's true and that's
what i keep on telling you guys right
that i
make these trips partially
because i need more things to talk about
and it's my my um pleasure to
make some content out of these trips
because i find it really fun to share
them with you
yeah
yes
yes uh the correct choreography i don't
know because i didn't make content every
day
but i could maybe write off part of it
part of the trip
[Music]
yeah i'm a travel blog no honestly
though that's kind of what i am in that
situation
and it's literally i'm i was literally
that was that was my
like
work content at that time
yeah
is true
it's not this is not even stretching it
this is not even trying to work around
it this is
you know my tax person is really
not one of those people to stretch
things to try to even stretch things
my tax person is being really real with
me and not
um
very
yeah
stretchy
[Music]
so anyway i was happy to hear that
though at least
[Music]
one more question i have guys before we
get to super chat starting you know this
is just warm up you know
um
stretchy sketchy no i didn't mean
stretchy but we could also say sketchy i
guess
so
how come
state of play
happened so shortly
and was announced so shortly after a
nintendo direct is it like a thing that
these game companies do that
once they they have something ready and
they literally wait
for the other one
to
you know announce there so that they
have like you know
the upper hand in trending topics or
something
or do they tell each other beforehand
[Music]
that hey i'm doing this you wanna also
do something on that day so we can keep
the hype going because i don't that
doesn't
[Music]
oh yeah or do they do it in time for
tokyo game show
[Music]
oh
i see that is actually
awkward but yeah
yeah
okay so that's just lining up with an
event okay i was wondering like
how how come they do it on the same day
basically that's kind of weird
[Music]
they don't appear at the event so they
do their own thing
[Music]
that to be true
yeah that was a state of play was it
midnight my time
i was awake but i didn't really
i didn't really feel like in the past
last time i watched the state of play
it didn't really have any games that
interested me and i i feel like
generally style wise
nintendo in general
i was very lucky this time but in
general they always have
um
games that are more my taste
than
playstation
you know
not as much as this time but
still enough to keep
me interested
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's more of my
style
so i didn't really care about watching
this time
chihuahua direct yeah
a long day for game journalists oh yeah
i'm still so excited about all the
announcements from the wawa direct
it's just so exciting
nintendo
and i just can't hide it oh my god
[Music]
you i brushed my teeth right before the
stream
and now my orange just tastes disgusting
well i rather review for tales of
symphonia
uh not a review but i want to play it
yeah
it's it's quite old but
i
love tails off and that is the game that
like
got me in like started with everything
that gave me
that opened a new world it gave me a key
to a new world and yeah also
normally i don't like to replay games
but it's been such a long time so yeah i
understand it will then be a good start
for
um
playing the sequel however
that's in what february um
and in in december no november we have
pokemon right
so until pokemon after pokemon were fine
for a while we'll have more than enough
to play
in terms of ongoing series
but until pokemon
oh
i don't know if i want to start some
series
because if yes then what um a zelda game
as much as i would like to do like you
know square enix stuff or so
or catherine
i can't yet so
[Music]
um
ori
ori too
i have a feeling that it will be very
very
exhausting though
maybe i want something more chill but um
[Music]
worry
or we won't even be that long anyway or
we
or reach
or two game
length
12 to 14 hours
on normal
difficulty well
that would probably be
[Applause]
[Music]
four streams
three to four streams for me if it goes
well
i guess that's like two weeks
two two or three weeks
could probably take longer though
yeah i want i want something with story
two
it's been six months since the last one
no wait no
tunic was one of them
once again
i argument
that just because
everyone is speaking a [\h__\h] foreign
language in tunic doesn't mean it didn't
have a story
it had very much a story it had a very
good story
i argue
shut up
okay i yield yeah you better
story heavy well it was on a [\h__\h]
diet
[Music]
but still had a story it was a story
driven game yeah
[Music]
just because it doesn't serve it to you
on a silver platter
and you have to go digging for it it
doesn't mean there's a story it doesn't
even have to be spoken as i said there
was a story there it was you have to
translate that afterwards there's plenty
of story but even if you wouldn't have
done that the game the visuals what
you're being shown
is story it's story doesn't always have
to be
talked or written
it can be shown
like a [\h__\h] picture book like when
you were a child
yes
yes yes yes
so
wise
yada is so wise i could be gandalf
[Music]
i could be ganda
such a wise phoenix
ah gandalf
randolph best boy
[Music]
so i stopped at like 77.
here we go
skye duncan for the pinky
[Music]
one of the twelve
skye
where's the rest
[Music]
sky
how much time did it take you to write
these skye i don't
i don't see the next one anywhere close
by
[Music]
skye
oh one per hour ah
okay
wow so you were planning on being there
for all of the hours
respect
one to twelve where's the rest of them
literally
beforehand congratulate on your two-year
anniversary always love how your
thoughtful energetic and sincere kiara
psycho psycho 12 hours enduring stream
let's go thank you skye
this is gonna be 12 pinkies
thank you so much
for the sweet support i'm looking
forward to reading all your messages
[Music]
happy second anniversary to our great
stencil so hype for this 12 hours fire
hangout let's go via viva
thank you
i hope you enjoyed the 12 hours thank
you for committing to it
glad you were part of it
thank you so much
thank you
thank you soon
[Music]
js i think that's 11.
oh no wait maybe it's not maybe it's
d-l-l-j-s
thank you
uh jackie lowe
pudding channel
dominique
felix zao oh
my god thank you
for
the five red super chats oh my god
thank you all
happy anniversary dance oh thank you
felix
i'm glad you're still here
thank you for supporting chihuahua for
such a long time now
big chat alert yeah we won't we won't
chad police is gonna catch ya
big chad
thank you so much that's way too much
way too much
hold your
hold your horses
hold your wallets thank you so much
wow
wow wow wow wow how can i thank you
enough
[Music]
a big kiss and another one
five kisses
thank you for for your support and your
generosity
[Music]
stark
happy second kiwa verse to me thank you
two years of chihuahua
yeah okay thank you for being part of it
and taking care of the fries branch
didn't know we have a
fries branch
like a branch that's only about fries
but
fries
are such an important feature
of fast food i love fries
could eat fries for days
yeah yeah
i'll keep on
[Music]
and having you in charge so please keep
on taking care of them thanks for the
support ethel thanks for the rest of the
chat and the pinky
f oh
that's way too
[Music]
much what the [\h__\h]
thank you so much
wait wait
why why why so mochi
happy second anniversary kiara thanks
for being so amazing for yet another
year
there have been so many fun times this
year with some of my favorites being the
mythco app holotoni collab
oh
you mean the one with all five
and you're for the birthday stream
thanks for always putting a smile on my
face and thanks for being such a
hard-working and awesome phoenix here's
to the third year being just as great if
not better
i hope it will be better
i hope
i hope things um
go
upwards for me and for you guys and for
her life
yeah
but it will need your continuous support
for it to be possible
hmm
getting better as a streamer
i've definitely proven my gaming skills
i think
thank you apple appreciate it so much
[Music]
nice to have you around always
for
sure
i have yeah
i'm a gamer yeah
no
jeff star
thank you
happy 2nd anniversary of japan opening
up travel slowly i hope your next
anniversary and birthday will be 3d
concert well
japan opening up travel slowly has been
something that we've been saying since
like a year
they've been teasing us
on and off with news like that
um
but i
i do think that finally we can
actually take it
somewhat seriously
i mean we do have indonesia gen 1 in
japan right now
i don't know the details of how they did
it but they did it
and um it should be possible for us too
[Music]
so
i would very much hope
that the next anniversary and birthday
will be in 3d i mean we already did this
year's birthday in freddy
[Music]
but it was
obviously you know
very
stressful last minute and yeah
had some problems here and there so next
year we will make it better
and i will
do hopefully more pretty content more
and more
[Music]
thank you jeff star
i'll do my best i'll work hard
thank you for supporting me
thanks for the pinky
large hand tossed buffalo chicken
[Music]
what
at
18.99 sixteen piece promising bread
vines
what is this super chat
for like 4.99 dollars what what do you
say super chat jared
are you here
what are you trying to tell me are you
giving me an order
you're giving me an order go to the
counter
this is the back office
i'm supposed to order here
kfb has grown so big that i don't
personally take orders anymore
go to the counter please
[Music]
good try though good try sounds good i
like your order you've been waiting for
a while huh you go better order it
properly now
before you start from
what
start from starvation
die from starvation
[Music]
but it still tastes disgusting
um
[Music]
thank you i love you too
appreciate it thank you so much
[Music]
thanks for keeping your shorts too
thank you sundance from the bottom of my
heart
congratulations on your two-year
anniversary kiara thank you for being
the most amazing boss the chicken could
ask for i know we teased you a lot but
it comes from a place of love
really
does it really i i'm running out of this
is my last froze kathy no i need to buy
more
oh no
teasing you know as a girl as a small
girl when when like your parents or
your teachers or whoever the adults
would tell you that boys
who tease you they do it because they
like you
it always pissed me off don't do that
you guys you boys are so stupid
don't do that i don't like it it doesn't
[\h__\h] work on girls it doesn't work
just be nice
just be nice for god's sake
i didn't like hearing that either
[Music]
that requires being honest it's not even
true it is true
okay maybe not all the time but it
definitely applies a lot of time and
even if you're not teasing because you
like that person then how about you
don't tease her
at all anyway
no bullying
stupid children
children
are so mean
children are so mean
i like bullying what the [\h__\h]
no
hope you're joking
hope you just mean you like bullying me
apologize exactly
[Music]
it's gonna be so awful yeah
like when i remember how the kids in my
school treated the teachers
especially like certain teachers who
were like
kind of
wide
man i was so sad because like you know
most of them were really nice teachers
and even the teacher that i found was
like
too strict and
my least favorite teacher i still
wouldn't bully them
[Music]
they don't have enough empathy yet yeah
yeah
you don't understand what you're doing
unless you get bullied too
but if you don't make that experience of
being bullied you don't understand what
you're doing to that person
[Music]
unfortunately i mean yeah that's just
the small peanut brain of a child who
cannot comprehend that people have
feelings they probably think that
everyone around them are npcs
oh
oh man i definitely cry more in my first
year of teaching than the previous did
they tease did they bully you
i thought your students liked you
i feel like you have a
better chance with kids if you are like
a young teacher
that has
you know
a cool
look
maybe even some sleek fashion style so
it will make the kids think that you are
cool
maybe
[Music]
anyway what was i i am
thank you for thinking and then code
also thank you for another pink super
chat kamsa nida
happy second anniversary
oh something with kiwanwa
[Music]
thank you for supporting me logical
paradox thank you
we're already at 257 in that list
it doesn't mean i read 257 but
that's like
[Music]
maybe 20 or so i don't know but i feel
like at the end there were
a lot more reds and pinks
than like oops in the middle
so i have to read a lot of messages
there
it's okay though it's okay this will
take a while and that's fine that's
normal
[Music]
oh i wish i
i have flaming pants thank you
oh you got a new profile picture
thank you for the pinky
um attention on two years you'll be
hootiful verb you i must reassure you
that even if you and i are not perfectly
compatible like we are with aki
i'll always love you the most i could
never leave you it was just a yoke
aha
if you were really afraid of me
leaving you wouldn't have you would have
attempted to throw me into the user room
like you tried to when mummy joined
yeah
good times these two years have been
full of them from that first kiki to
your blessed giggles to your random
jump-scare streams you've blessed mine
and so many other lives you have made
these days brighter and happier made so
many smiles even when life's life turn
turns
is this is this is this also a pun
for the worst and it's too much to
swallow
swallow that's a bird right
[Music]
but the turns i don't know
that one i don't get
so happy when i get a joke
i'm so happy
thank you for everything and again happy
second the key well we're sorry now
let's vote you on into uh you're free
yay trevor did
thank you so much for your love and
support
and yeah yeah well you know mummy is um
she's an owl after all an owl girl so
i i sensed danger when she came
to her life
that i would lose you to her
i think i think that's um understandable
but you're very loyal i'm very
supportive thank you so much for
everything
even came all the way to jokomi
i was very special
thank you so much for everything
[Music]
thank you you sure that danger wasn't
just mummy herself well yeah yeah yeah
that might be true as well
phoenix is a territorial
territorial about you guys yeah
good morning from europe morning
i'm in europe you can't fool me
it's
6 p.m dude
not even i call that morning
[Music]
did you just wake up what the [\h__\h]
were you up watching the state of play
all night but even i was i was probably
up very long too
actually though i
i wanted to get up late but you know
normally i i definitely always wake up
when i set an alarm but this time
it was weird i
i didn't even hear my alarm or i just
turned it off
half asleep but i feel like
i would remember that
but i was gonna wake up at eight a.m
for a meeting
but don't worry it was voluntary um
attendance
but i voluntarily wanted to attend but
then i slept through it
god damn it
and then you know at some point i was
like half asleep
but i was
like
waking up because i had this feeling
that
it can't be
before 8 00 am yet
still because i
i
you know my inner clock is telling me
it must be way past 8am and i should
wake up
now look at the clock and it's already
10.
i have a good inner
inside clock though
for noticing stuff like that
but it was already too late
i
i kind of was glad though
because apparently
nothing much
happened in the meeting and
yeah
it was probably not really i mean it was
nothing i would have
i would have said at the meeting anyway
i just wanted to listen okay something
important gets said but i don't think
anything important was discussed it's
all good all good
all good
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah very tired jewel
i had however had a different meeting
later on so i stayed awake
the tax tax person meeting
do you have enough sleep
yeah i think so i mean i'm like slightly
tired but
i'm fine
thank you for asking
[Music]
we have i think more meetings now
than we used to you know they added some
kind of voluntary
regular meeting thing
just to check up
if everything's fine
well for me for me things are fine
[Music]
ah meet and greets
i gave them like some dates but
[Music]
let me
let me ask
[Music]
um
uh
[Music]
okay
i just told them to
choose a date and let you guys know then
so that you guys can um
faster
put it in your calendar
hmm hi keyboard yeah that was not the
dana keyboard too
oh bring it back don't worry i'll bring
it back anyway thank you so much
travertine thank you
for all the love
so talk still sunday no i haven't
received like an answer from the guest
yet and um
also the studio is still not finished
so i moved it to next week for now next
week sunday
i need to get over this um
[Music]
this way this starting this come back
yeah yeah at least it won't overlap with
like the the debuts and 3d debuts for
the
showcases
because that's also happening three days
in a row friday saturday sunday
wasn't this sunny oh yeah i mean yeah
sunday yeah sunday do you
[Music]
at least we got the german devil done
finally
[Music]
for the pinky
four days off due to thanksgiving oh
yeah right but i went to work for kfb
today is a day to stream from 7 p.m to 7
00 am i'm ready for a long night and i'm
willing to watch and stay stay
thank you
ah perfect timing for you guys
i'm glad that it fell into that time
frame when you guys have some days off
wonderful
thank you for staying up i wonder if you
successfully stayed up until the end
thank you so much for
being there and supporting me thank you
kristaps donkey
bread
[Music]
just in case security kiss
thank you
for the rest of the chat
i want a security kiss
[Music]
finally played holocure tonight i chose
you as my first character and managed to
clear stage one without specials on my
first try
without specials you mean without a
special attack
[Music]
are you giving yourself like special
handicaps special
[Music]
things of making it more difficult
interesting
what a gamer thanks for the good luck
and for an amazing two years kiara thank
you
[Music]
yeah
also feel free to use
my special it looks cool it looks sick
but yeah apparently i'm really really
buffed now so i should really try it out
[Music]
oh
you have to buy it from the shop wait
was that
did i have to do that too i don't
remember that even
i don't remember i needed to unlock it
[Music]
revive but do i already have to be dead
in order to use the special then or does
it like give me like
kind of like a
zelda fairy where
it just activates when i actually do die
and it stacks or
[Music]
activates when hp hits zero
a 15 second buff
yeah
so i have to like kind of
um
use it when i think i'm about to die
i see
so i guess now i can look into the
future too
thank you mr bandit
thank you so much for being there for
two years
[Music]
wd thank you for the red super chat come
san nida
congratulations congratulations
it's my first time super chat since we
met on meet and greet ah
i was in pain every day but for me
meeting tanja was lucky so i wanted to
say thank you
but after that day whenever i hear
tantra's voice my heart beats so much
i think
you caught something
let me tell you
it's
chihuahua fever ah
you have to keep our fever
i can tell you how to heal it
you have to stream fever night
[Laughter]
stream favorite night
yeah
and then you give up a fever will go
away
and it will just become kiwaba love
forever forever
with chickenpox
no no
wow it's not chicken pox that would be
terrible that would be so terrible
[Music]
best remedy ever yum
um
[Music]
i'm already at the kiwawa love stage i
know you are
sound medical advice
well
i have a doctor's degree
have you had the chickenpox before i
think so
i remember having something like that as
a child it was probably
it was probably that
i think so
i remember me and my brother having
these dots all over our bodies
when we were small children
mommy kept on putting that cream
on every
every spot
and he was like don't scratch don't
scratch
stop scratching
but i don't i don't remember it being
too bad actually
but maybe it's just too long ago
other memories of my childhood were more
suffering and torturing than that
[Music]
anyway thank you so much
i hope you get better soon
thank you so much
[Music]
s
yeah forefest was announced i never
talked about it
since they literally just announced to
date and really nothing more about it
but
very exciting
yeah
hopefully
kiwa will get some time to shine
this time as well
[Music]
an idol outfit oh
no hold on
interesting
[Music]
hmm
no no i don't know anything i'm just
like
wondering if that could be possible i
don't know i really don't know i really
don't know
i really don't know
[Music]
but it would be nice that's what i'm
saying you know was it like that with
like fifth gen
like before
or or six no what
fifth fourth fourth or fifth gen they
performed once without
and then the year after they came back
with actual idol outfits or so i don't
know was that what happened
[Music]
yeah yeah right
so we also performed once without an
idol outfit it would be nice that in the
following year we would be able to um
perform with an idol outfit
yeah for yeah yeah they didn't have it
for a second fest um
[Music]
wants to do one super chat for every
minute of the stream you're [\h__\h]
kidding me no way how long are you gonna
how are you how long are you gonna take
um keep that up huh
you really going to do this
[Music]
lasted one homeman
zero commitment
ridiculous
every another call thank you for the
rent of attack key well i can't believe
it's been two years now i really
appreciate that the effort you put into
everything you do i will always support
you thank you very much
yeah i do put a lot of effort into what
i do thank you for acknowledging it
and hopefully you will continue to enjoy
my content for a long long long long
time yeah
it's nice having you around so please
stay and support kiwawa
crispy duncan
[Music]
did i give every another call for kiss
short time memory what the hell
thank you envy
[Music]
what what the [\h__\h] didn't you already
send so many in pre-chat
holy [\h__\h] tai chi
tai chi
[Music]
but this time it says happy anniversary
thank you
tiny are you okay i hope you still have
i don't know some money to buy yourself
some food
don't have to eat beans from the
from the can canned beans
every day now
or toast bread only with nothing on top
of it
oh my god oh youtube having some issues
right now not everyone apparently
susan
i dare you
yeah show susan the knife and um
surely
surely she will understand
[Music]
anyway thank you so much starches way
too much you're crazy
holy macaroni
[Music]
29 thank you for the pinky happy second
anniversary quinoa thank you for always
being able to put a smile on my face no
matter what kind of day i'm having
you're the best oshie ever viva la
gallina
galena what's kalina
so you're welcome you also put a smile
on my face by being here in my streams
thank you
female chicken
it could have been so wholesome i said
on twitter it's gonna be wholesome why
are you gonna do this
why are you gonna do this to me
of course it was something like that
bamboozle
[Music]
my disappointment is unmeasurable
use your room
three weeks
no more galena
no
optimus prime thank you for pinky now
don't disappoint me you're gonna
you know the right words to say right
optimus happy second anniversary kiana
wow time really does fly like a phoenix
right oh there you go
he knows what i am it were wonderful to
hear so far with you and all of kfp you
provided wonderful entertainment for me
since your debuts
love to you and all of you viva la quiet
do not give this man an award because
this should be normal behavior
this should not be rewarded because this
should be normal this should be the norm
thank you so much
[Music]
fine with me
thank you so much
thank you and i'm so proud of you for
being an example employee
thank you soon
[Music]
happy two years i'm so glad you're here
i was very sick for a couple months this
summer yeah
so long and you were one of the few
things that helped me through it
mentally here's many more years
oh man that sucks
a whole summer wasted huh
[Music]
i hope
i hope that the coming months will be
very very eventful and happy
and positive for you
please stay healthy
and take care of yourself okay
and i'm always here for you when you
need me
dan kishon for your support
night walker danke sun dead head donkey
shum
thank you for the red super chat
happy second keyboard
[Music]
thank you for being here cotton you've
also been around for such a long time
[Music]
thank you for making memories together
with me
[Music]
one hour passed down cushion sky
walking you in maniacs duncan
[Music]
pinkies
and when i saw your debut i subscribed
because i thought your mom was cute oh
you made me laugh and you seemed like a
good person proud to say that two years
later
you now have many cute models you still
regularly make me laugh and i think all
you chickens will agree with agreeing
you've more than shown you're a good
caring and genuine person plus you've
demonstrated a litany of other great
talents such as your dancing singing and
art abilities
oh
not only are we proud to support such a
top tier entertainer but also such a top
tier person happy second anniversary
kiwawa i'll happily still follow your
amazing holo journey over the coming
years i'm sure with plenty more
of my usual silly sappy messages keep
being your amazing boss
feelings impressed i will give a froggy
future project teasing european in
control chimpanzee adopting cat loving
lesbian
expressing horse bathing
[Music]
then finding self
but
thank you
that's a lot of titles
thank you always
they always have such sweet words to say
thank you for caring so much about
kiwawa
i appreciate you being here
you know i'm glad you're not tired of me
but you seem the type of person who
won't get tired of me for a long time
i feel like i can
rely on your loyalty thank you so much
visible thank you soon
[Music]
how do i read this
foreign okay
i think that's that's how i'm supposed
to read it thank you thank you
jim tracy thank you soon for the rest of
the chat congratulations on your second
anniversary kiana it's crazy to think
it's been two whole years since smith
debuted that time flies when you're
having fun i just want to say thank you
for all the fun and fun fun memories
can't wait to see what your freeholds
love your attention
yeah i can't wait to see heber
at the moment it's still
very unclear
but i hope it will be many fun things
many good things
that we can share with one another
let's hope for the best okay and work
hard towards it
please continue supporting me jim tracy
thank you love you too
[Music]
already tired maybe i should do
like i i've read the super chat's worth
of
one and a half hours of that 12 hour
marathon now
maybe if i do
one hour of super chat rating per day i
should be done
in like
10 days
sometimes i could do more than an hour
it could be a good plan but i
i want to read a bit more
i want to read a bit more even though
i'm already so tired
[Music]
also my throat
man
yeah no i i don't think i want to keep
them off for so long
did you watch house of the dragon
already yeah i did
um
i'm glad that that was not the episode
that i watched with my mom
i'm glad that the one we watched
together was uh
um
a more um
uh
family friendly one
[Music]
and i hope
i hope that that won't be like a regular
thing
because
yeah
i don't i didn't i don't know
didn't enjoy it much but i hope that's
just something they had to
get over with and then continue on with
some actual story please
it was the whole situation was pretty
long yeah
oh
yeah
i mean
if it was just
the damon and renera thing
you know
in their own room or whatever
i wouldn't have
felt so uncomfortable but um
yeah
i was uh too much too much
it was shinta something natural
i would hope that
what they did is not
natural
[Music]
they do too much for shock factor i
really think so
yeah i agree
i know you probably mean something else
but
[Music]
wow
that's true for targaryens not quite
though because like even the father was
like
really shocked it doesn't seem to be
even though it's something that happens
in the targaryens and
that people also know
that they do like look kind of like a
prejudice
it doesn't seem to be too exact except
the ball in within the family even
well duh he's her father
but if it was that normal i feel like he
would have already
[Music]
made that
i don't know whatever yeah
yeah
because of not being married
i guess so
because it was damon yeah
yeah
maybe he would have been more accepting
of it if it was a different targaryen
well it um definitely
opened
quite a conflict
messed with him politically
it was weird like
just
weird
[Music]
i mean it's not reality so i don't
really care it's a fantasy world i don't
care about you know the thing itself but
the way it was
um
put
into scene
i don't like that
anyway
how was i
jim tracy made me
[Music]
thank you for the words of a chat
congratulations on your second
anniversary kiana it's crazy to think
it's been two whole years since my debut
that time flies when you're having fun i
just want to say thank you for all the
fun and fun wait i already write that
one
never mind thank you
thank you
[Music]
that's the vault then thank you for
pinky congrats on your second
anniversary quinoa
i wasn't expecting to fall into this
rabbit hole two years ago but here i am
and it's all thanks to you your kind
heart made cave be the great community
it is it's been amazing two years and
here's many more thank you there's a
vault
i'm happy you fell into the rabbit hole
i'm happy all of you fell into the
rabbit hole
it's something so fresh
something so fun
and you all are part of it
yeah great community indeed
thank you so much desvault
glad to have you
jumped in like a cannibal
so ready
yeah thank you desolate
tk thank you bishop
[Music]
oh
already the third sky's a pajama this is
uh
almost the beginning of the
one two
of the second hour one
but you sent one at the beginning and
then one after one hours and now
one after two hours so it's the third
one thank you
thank you
thank you for the rest of the chant
[Music]
i always wonder about your profile
picture duck attack who is that
looks like um
some
old actor or singer who is that actually
someone famous probably
someone who i should know oh it's han
solo ah he did look a little bit
familiar but i every time i see the
picture it's really really tiny you know
why do you have han solo as your profile
picture
why
star wars right
hello no game today yeah i have to get
like past some super chats
[Music]
he's a cool guy he's literally oh my god
you want you all love him so much huh
ah
star wars so popular
he's so cool you guys are saying that
because you want to be like han solo
right
you look up to him huh
since you were a little child you were
like ah he's so cool and then you grow
up and now you still think he's so cool
cute
good
i imagine all these little baby chickens
looking at star wars and be like oh
that's so cool i want to be like him one
day
but all you became was a chicken
a little bit disappointing
[Laughter]
oh man
me bug with idols
but i became an idol
[Music]
anyway
han solo is fictional don't worry about
it guys you could have never became
become
han solo don't worry
it's impossible
so don't feel bad about not becoming him
han solo
yep
it's not helping
10 year batch han solo
no han solo if anything han solo i can
give you that
oh i i already hear
dakuman's starting to draw a chicken
in the attire of han solo right now
and we'll call it han solo
is that one
here
i hear i hear the pen on the tablet
[Music]
i don't see dakuma but word will gets to
out
word will get out and reach takuma
surely
in class uh-huh
are you saying class is more important
than me
well yeah i guess it is
[Music]
guys
speaking of class
my book club consists of including me
six people now
six people
let's
choose
[Music]
i'm not gonna say who because who knows
maybe um even though they were
interested and they won't make it until
like a certain deadline and then they'll
dip out after all but i'm surprised i
got
so many
interested people into books
we don't we didn't choose a book yet but
i i wrote to them let's choose a book
preferably one that is pretty well known
so that the chances of the viewers
already
um
knowing it or higher
i'm not sure if i can i can get them to
read lord of the rings because that's a
huge commitment
um
that's a huge commitment
and
i think lord of the rings
according to my mom is a bit difficult
to read
or like maybe no that was game of
thrones maybe
she did say that um
wheel of time was an easy read
oh it is difficult to read that's what i
thought yeah maybe the hobbit
i was thinking so too hobbits could be
nice but
i don't know
[Music]
um
huh
[Music]
okay
uh no not no mangas just actual books
although maybe i'll uh maybe maybe
maybe i'll just
um
listen to an audiobook of whatever we
choose
i mean it's still the same content right
yeah where's the [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
keeper don't make me say like that
that's so weird tick tick tick tick tick
tick tick tick tick tick tick tick tick
tick click decollete
i don't like saying folk
that's cheating that's not cheating
i think i'll be able to pay a better
attention that way
[Music]
i see so some some
some
[Music]
discussions some discussions um with the
move girls
[Music]
kiana audible sponsor oh yes please oh
this stream was sponsored by
okay i won't say it i won't say it i
feel like it's illegal for me to say it
was sponsored by something when it
wasn't sponsored
shadow raid legends just kidding
um where was i
oh yeah i was gonna read a text of a
chat but you got me it's a tangent
because of han solo
[Music]
happy anniversary kiara thanks for all
the inspiring stories games and other
content i can't be the only one who
feels the utmost gratitude to our
wonderful phoenix goddess i hope you can
hear more tangents and stories for as
long as you want to share them
thank you very much um i'm glad you like
all my stories and tangents
unfortunately i don't have as many
anymore as i had in the first year
um but
now that i know i can write off my
trips
as business expenses
well then
i'm gonna continue taking more of these
trips for more tensions
hell yeah
i'm gonna travel i'm gonna be a v
traveler
perfect
v traveler
virtual traveler
no i travel in reality but i report in
the virtuality
[Music]
okay let's change music
i'm sick of it even though it's good
[Music]
i love that but that won't loop properly
it's cute
[Music]
hey
that gives me ghibli vibes [\h__\h] no i
want to watch a sibling movie
[Music]
haven't seen one in such a long time
nice but it's piano only i don't know
hmm
there's barely any anything tacked with
atsumori
[Music]
how about that oh that's more
a little bit more
[Music]
oh
what's this
that's so chill ah
[Music]
that's so relaxing
oh you guys already heard it wow that
was fast what
did she tweet it out
[Music]
oh yeah kelly tweeted it
oh
[Music]
oh interesting
uh i was delayed
[Music]
yeah unfortunately um i saw it coming
though
yeah
[Music]
soon hopefully don't know don't know a
new date yet but soon i hope
[Music]
yeah do you still happening yeah
yo this is so chill
i'm downloading this one
[Music]
i love that bgm
beautiful
super relaxing
chill
time that's what i call it
it doesn't even do it justice
nice it's a bit sad sounding no it's not
sad
it's like positive
soothing um
you're kind of like
i don't know i
i feel like this sounds like um
it could be a background music of some
anime scene
or like a actually no even rpg or
hmm
or like a it's like a evening music from
a town from a village
evening
music london ranch
something like that
at night
that's the rat vibe um
you got it you caught it exactly the way
it is
that
turn it up dj turn it up
[Music]
nice
oh this is so nice
[Music]
oh
happy anniversary tantrum thank you
it's not only my anniversary is our
anniversary so thank you for celebrating
together with me
jeremy clarkson thank you
[Music]
thank you that was a short peep
longer beep
thai fan thank you
is it a rainbow it's like a
you're missing the blue i think but
that's that's somewhat of a rainbow
thank you
it's so hard to believe it's been two
years since your first debut if you had
told me that an amazing entertainer on
the internet would have such a positive
impact on my life i would have never
believed it the trip you've taken all of
us on is just indescribable personally
you have motivated me to try so much
you have made me want to travel more try
new foods and music and be part of an
amazing community perfect wonderful
as stressful as my life can be you've
helped me smile for so much and keep
pushing to do better it's not just a
smile still seeing how hard you work and
watching you overcome all the obstacles
inspires us too you push us to be better
even if you're just trying to make us
forget our struggles for a few hours a
day thank you for the two years and
thank you in advance for however many
more you are able to give us
this fits so well with the video
you've lifted so many of us up with your
beautiful love and an open heart we
truly love and admire you
you're a truly beautiful and
irreplaceable person thank you for
making me smile and i couldn't be
happier to support you for years to come
viva
thank you
it's wonderful to have you be part of
kfb thank you soon
i'm glad that you're trying new things
too
you definitely should you should make
the most
of your life i know everyday job life
can be very stressful
but don't don't let that like suck you
into this hole of
nothingness
yeah
i'm like currently very focused on this
and not giving myself much time to
really
enjoy
real life and do stuff but
i'm accepting it because i know
i can do plenty of that later if i do my
best now
[Music]
but that's because i'm i'm doing a job
that's you know you know it is what it
is so
i think it's fine but you should you
should do your best to like go out and
enjoy life
while of course also always watching
kiwawa
[Music]
thank you so much for your sweet words
and for your sweet support
hi team
thank you for the red super chat tashi
[Laughter]
oh my god
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
you're spoiling me too much stop it
what job do you do please introduce yeah
tell me
maybe tai chi is a v2 player
maybe tai chi isn't hold alive
that's why they can send so many red
super chats
maybe tai chi is a famous vegetable
maybe he's yago
[Laughter]
tai chi is definitely an oil baron yeah
tai chi
[Music]
well
thank you very lucky thank you for
sharing your luckiness with me thank you
[Music]
um
oh wait
i thought i had to translate that never
mind it actually translates to sakurai
suzuka
sorry
[Music]
sticker
thank you thank you thank you
very much for celebrating together
thank you
7g
skydiving brand
where has the time gone it feels like
only yesterday we were celebrating your
one year anniversary but here we are in
two years i'm glad i've gotten to meet
so many caffeine last year and hope to
meet more and maybe even go to four fest
hopefully
yeah
all right four fest all live
[Music]
whole live super expo 2023 home life 4
fest is in march
march 18th
that is six months in advance you guys
have
in theory enough time
to plan for it but there is
still
still this barrier that you currently
don't know if you'll be able to visit at
that time because of border
restrictions so that's um
yeah it got announced like on the
um five-year anniversary stream
that it's being held on the 18th and
19th
march 2023
again two days oh yeah also ticket
lottery that's true
that might be a bit difficult to enter
as a foreigner i'm actually not sure how
it works
yeah that's that's a pain in the ass
[Music]
yeah probably safer to
stream it again but if you want to try
good luck
i hope it goes well
i hope i can be
in japan at the time as well
would be nice to be there
when it happens
[Music]
whoever wants to participate i wish you
the best of luck
i've
gotten tickets for like lottery concerts
and stuff as well before
but i may
not have gotten it for the lottery
[Music]
um
it's improving
i i think there's a slight chance you
guys could try to go because the
situation is improving actually
for once it looks like you know
it could get better but march
we have it's half a year half a year
with the current
um
development
i think there's a chance but if you want
to risk it or not that's your decision
[Music]
shame about the song being late yeah
unfortunate i hope it gets um released
soon
but kelly assured me that you know
it won't be like
on the day i released
she's being
considerate so um it won't be like
within the 24 hours before or after i
hope
[Music]
[\h__\h] cube yeah no cubes
no cubes here
there was a little lag yeah i felt that
too actually my
my pc stopped for um two seconds
i'm not questioning it because i close
my eyes in front of problems
[Music]
yeah yeah
nice
[Music]
do
sorry i'm amazing suggestions for books
oh i spoiled it i'm just gonna be part
of it
of course i'm just gonna be part of it
it's like whenever i'm in
no that's not quite true but whenever i
suggest like i want to do this just who
wants to participate i'm not i'm not
always
i'm always
like
ready to
be part of something i want to do she's
always there
[Music]
oh
oh she's making books book suggestions
[Music]
not for
amelia watson
[Music]
she says she she's
[\h__\h] english she shows you
she suggests that
a book that has something to do with um
timelines and she said but timeless
stuff can be a headache and i said not
for amelia watson
she sells seashells by the seashore she
sells seashells by the seashores she
sells seashells but she almost had it
[Music]
oh
she sells seashells by the seashore she
sells seashells by the t-shirt she sells
seashells by the seashore wow
let's go
[Music]
three times and i said it fast i didn't
even read it i just
called it from memory
wow
[Music]
nailed it
she sells seashells by the seashore she
sells seashells by the seashore she
sells seashells by the seashore yes he
says [\h__\h]
[Music]
she sells seashells by the seashore
i can imagine
with this bgm in the background
a little girl selling seashells in the
evening by the seashore and collecting
them alone
and
i can imagine oh it's so cute
wow imagination
incredible
chihuahua's selling seashells by the
seashore
small kiwawa
okay continuing
[Music]
i think it was pyro homolog with the
four fest that got me to tangent again
thanks for the tangent
jackson has been thank you for the rest
of the chat happy two years we're sorry
i never thought it but i'd be so
happy to be fried and put in the bucket
but after all this time with my horsey
bird how could i not be big love from a
very happy duncan thank you
you have
accepted and adapted
the kfp culture
i'm so proud of you you are one of us
jackson
thank you for supporting me and letting
me be your aussie
yay much love to you thank you so much
one of us one of us one of us
[Music]
anthony well thank you for watching
happy to your anniversary quinoa you're
an amazing lovable hilarious and
talented phoenix thank you for making
life vibrant for us jenkins oh
no i think you guys as an entity do so
much more for me
and i do for you guys but thank you
i'm glad really that i can have a
positive impact and
play a positive role in your life
but remember i'm just a streamer okay
i'm just a content creator
i don't want to be the only happiness in
your life you guys should
you know
i mean i'm happy about it and i'm
honored but
i want you guys to like i don't know get
married have kids and stuff like that
you know
have a fulfilled life
um
just i'm just saying this in general now
but
yeah i want you guys to to have your
dreams come true have a dream job have a
beautiful house or whatever
if you don't like kids then you should
get like pets
cute cats like mine
yeah
or doggos
i don't know just
i want you guys to just find your kind
of happiness whatever it is you know
maybe you don't even know yet what your
kind of happiness is
so many of you guys are like nah i don't
want i don't need it you guys haven't
done that something about your own
life's happiness
[Music]
it doesn't have to be exactly the way i
described it
hmm
[Music]
but i want you guys to have the
the tools
to find happiness
as i hope to have them
myself one day
[Music]
i already have a hammer
i have a hammer too it's such a cute
baby hammer
did i i think i showed it before but
every time
every time someone my mom or reaper so
they come here and they're like i need a
hammer and i'm like yep there you go and
they're like oh it's the kiwa baby
hammer
but my mom my mom really likes that
hammer even though it's like a joke
hammer almost
it's my hammer
cute hammer
mini bunk
it works though
i've um bonked many nails into walls by
now with that baby hammer
[Music]
the hammer is a good metaphor for my
relationships
[Music]
i don't know if that's good or bad
anyway thank you anthony
much love to you too
please continue
being yourself and supporting kiwawa
thank you soon
[Music]
i don't want to know how much time you
spent in the stream on me
tai chi what the [\h__\h]
tai chi is the definition
or the reason why the word what the [\h__\h]
was invented
the phrase
like someone once in like like 5 000
years ago
received a red super chat from tai chi
and that person was like
what the [\h__\h]
and that's how that phrase was coined
[Laughter]
a history lesson for you guys thank you
thai team
[Music]
my god mr big thank you and rogan
striker thank you soon brandon thank you
and junkie chuck thanks for the rest of
chad hold
what am i holding for
ah it's because i changed the game here
[Music]
thank you thank you i'm already so far
i'm like uh
wait what oh ah that's actually no
that's when i restarted my pc
i think um
restart
thank you for holding the light junky
chunk
strong
so strong legs and arms so strong stroke
[Music]
successfully held the line
thankfully uh safely connected back to
the stream
[Music]
and downstairs thanks for the pinky
roses are red violets are blue this
super chat is not for you
happy anniversary to janma too
right
all right
[Music]
genma
happy
manager versus
manager
first serene
not quite the date
the right date but oh well
actually yeah when did
oh [\h__\h]
wrong one chat
[Music]
when was the date she started managing
me because it wasn't from the beginning
[Music]
it was a chat where genma is in but not
the right chance
oh well
it wasn't the beginning i don't wonder
when's the date hmm
must check the archives of
our logs
when
when the official date is
i left it up
[Music]
after it was yeah it was definitely
after i stayed
over hmm
like i mean
well maybe it happened while i was
staying over but
once i started start staying over i was
not managed by her yet
she's typing
[Music]
ah
no
denman says happy talent bursary because
i said happy
happy managerial we're making up words
here
so glad to have seen you for two good
years
love forever
[Music]
i still have that
laugh forever
did i ever upload that on the discord i
don't think so
love
writers don't laugh forever
oh oh genma has it
love forever thinking
i don't have it
jenna sometimes has like really cool
emotes
from
like
you know
whole life-related stuff that i don't
have
so jealous
give me
give me all of them
anyway continuing
[Music]
and of course she definitely has discord
nitro
i'm sure she got it
[Music]
[Laughter]
who knows um
thank you telstra
and strawberry
[Music]
e-n-e-m-i-e thank you
anthony because i think last time i read
that name everybody was like yeah bye
skye
thank you schneider
for the pinkie
alex
[Music]
does next enough yet hopefully
not a
[Music]
so yes what you watched a different
[\h__\h] v2 by yesterday
excuse me
[Music]
uh
only only my graphics card but i don't
even i don't know [\h__\h] about those kind
of things like i don't know what's
compatible
and
you know
because apparently there's some things
that no no they're not compatible right
[Music]
now just i'll just ask rbf or so
i know a lot of our pieces wish i could
help now it's fine it's fine it's fine
it's fun it's fine that's your boo
look you think of modernity who's in the
knee yeah she's there
so is this
[Music]
i need a certain motherboard types yeah
anyway this pc talk bores the [\h__\h] out
of me
anyway i have a good service and that's
it just normally sit here that's what
statistics happen after scissors episode
[Music]
it's extremely hard to believe it's been
two years already thank you for
everything thank you happy anniversary
thank you it really is
it's hard to believe
but it's really such a weird feeling
i've said this many times in some ways
it feels like i've been doing this
forever and in some ways i've been doing
this it feels like i've been doing this
only for like
a short time
it's weird but
it's because i'm it's just the daily
grinds that goes on and on and on and on
and on
thank you alita for being part of it
yeah please continue supporting ki rava
otherwise you will have to go into the
usual room yeah
i won't let you go
not gonna let you go
[Music]
how do i read this i don't think i read
this in japanese
i've been a sound viewer for at least
like years now oh but you're still
enjoying thank you so much
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
intro oh i did ask ame if she wants to
make a new one and she said yeah like
overhaul the old one even though it's so
classic it's actually
a tough decision i'm not sure because i
think
normally talk shows they go with the
same set and the same logo and the same
opening for years and years and years
to keep that familiar vibe
and with the new
hotel studio we're not doing something
so super super super super super
different that it will look absolutely
unfamiliar
um
but you know just freshened up um but i
don't know about the
about the opening what do you guys think
i should do
should it be like changed
or just just a subtle change i don't
know
what we definitely have to change is the
landing go because i would land in a new
studio
[Music]
maybe change just that
just the landing
that would make sense
[Music]
hmm needs more explosions
a german train
wow
[Music]
nah
german trains are always late [\h__\h] that
i would always be late to holotalk if i
did that
[Music]
um
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
you know there was a while where the
baby didn't show up after
some point and i was i was sad but it
came back to us and it's still around
ah
it doesn't grow up though huh i wonder
maybe maybe like one year later what if
it changes its name to like instead of
baby um it would be like toddler
and then in the fourth year it could be
like child
just to have some
character development going on
[Music]
like preschooler
it can't really age anymore it doesn't
in its name it doesn't say anymore that
it's a ghost or that it died or so it
kind of reset its stance and it's just
called the baby that's being eaten
[Music]
something happened
so it implies that it's currently still
alive but it's in the process of being
eaten
[Music]
yeah
a baby bubble
or maybe
if the bubble bubble hurts
what i'm talking about you're welcome to
um turn into a toddler at some point
i wouldn't mind the
character development
thank you for your support for so long
um
it's nice to have like familiar names
popping up
always
yeah merry pippins
[Music]
i'm like
i'm more than halfway through i think
we're not quite i'm like
not not more than halfway i'm like about
halfway through
approximately
[Music]
jd says
happy second year anniversary hot wings
ggs
thanks for the continued fun streams
real talk and
cattle intermissions
i don't do them so often anymore though
for a while they interrupted me
more than usual but they stopped again
they had a face
but they're more chill again
yeah yeah
they're used to it i think the time when
they
interrupted me more
maybe
maybe it was after some kind of vacation
or so
where they missed me
[Music]
baby one baby two
yeah baby one baby two
oh
baby one baby two
my babies
stay real my oshie really glad i decided
to watch your streams after seeing a
clip of you in polka
oh that was what got you into me
here's some more years to come thank you
was it from that failed minecraft
collaboration
was it from that
[Music]
i wonder
that's a long time ago yeah
that was
that was um
that was so
stressful i was so stressful man
you guys liked that one but for me it
was such a stressful experience
because like
i was still relatively new and i got so
much
[\h__\h] and criticism all the time that i
was so scared of [\h__\h] up again and i
kept on [\h__\h] up at that time like so
many like technical problems and
it was so stressful for me the the
pressure like i wanted things to go well
but they mostly went badly
and i was just so scared of the backlash
and [\h__\h]
and i wanted the first collaboration
with someone
to obviously go well to leave a good
impression
with them as well
with the collab partner
yeah
oh well i'm sure she didn't put
as much thought into it as i did like in
terms of
being so worried about things going
wrong
but at the time i
i was yeah
wrecking my brain over these kind of
things
[Music]
oh thank you though gd that
you came to kfp
and joined us
in our adventures
yeah thanks mate
i love you
under that tv
thank you for the pinky and i'm not
thinking no thank you sorry
but thank you
thank you soon
[Music]
on your two year anniversary dental even
after all the time your content feels
fresh and fun you never cease to
entertain and i love to watch your
streams
i could not dream of a better oshi love
you and thank you for the time so far
thank
you love you too
yeah
thank you you need to chad you're so
sweet
always so nice
thank you for being around sticking
around
and always wanting my streams always
being here thank you means a lot to me
[Music]
now we're at the six hour mark yeah we
are
damn
i didn't think i would get so far in
such a short amount of time and i've
been tangenting too
damn
my god
halfway through
oh
we're halfway through
oh yeah super
[Music]
my throat feels better though than at
the beginning of the stream so
i can go a little bit longer we can go
for
a bit longer but the thing is just that
you know eventually it just it's the
same message
again and again and i don't want them to
feel
so repetitive so
we're not gonna go endlessly
[Music]
i spent 1.5 hours looking at the kfe
minecraft world i spent 1.5 hours
looking at the minecraft world last year
so long really it didn't feel that long
oh
that was last year
[Music]
i mean there was a lot to see there
okay okay okay
thank you for the pinky
arigato
[Music]
congrats on your second anniversary
chiara
cheers to two years of unforgettable
memories and great accomplishments
beer icon oh
kanpai
i'm excited to see what the future holds
for you in year 3 and beyond
lucky wow
wow this is a six hour mark how are you
holding up
oh you mean the the super chat reading
kibaba
oh kind of tired
kind of tired what decides that oh
pretty good thank you
thank you
for asking you're so considerate did you
play cookie your moo kookyumi
did you play that game before
or are you a natural
and reading the air
super chat to future quinoa
[Music]
i just want to take a nap
those streams were some of my favorites
[Music]
what sorry what did we talk about oh
cookie yummy
sorry short time memory
oh my god
[Music]
of train
no i missed the pot of train
[Music]
i didn't i didn't get into the train on
time
[Music]
yeah
oh
that's where the joke came from huh
from cookie omu
yummy
yummy not cookie yum
[Music]
sorry just turning into a cat for a
moment
[Music]
crispy cat thank you for the pinky
happy second
anniversary i wish you all the best in
the future i hope to see you
until
the third 400th
500th anniversary
dear god do you want to kill me crispy
cat
500 years of streaming
you're trying to torture me or something
like that i mean however you don't
necessarily have to be
there for an anniversary people
celebrate people's anniversaries even
like like for example idol groups
anniversaries even after they're done
with their activities so i guess okay
okay okay
you might not see me at my 500th
anniversary
but it can still be celebrated please
tell your
children and your grandchildren and tell
them to tell their grandchildren to
celebrate my anniversary
in 500 years thank you
thank you
[Music]
it's not pointless no
no it's to honor my memory
[Music]
ah family tradition wonderful
create a shrine make sure to pray to it
yeah yeah create like some kind of stone
statue
and then 500 years later people will
look at it like they look at you know
other statues then now we have no idea
what they're really
um
what the what the history behind it is
yeah
i'm tracking you guys into having kids
[Music]
well you have to tell someone about me
someone to carry on the memory come on
come on
please uh
don't want to be forgotten
but as long as the internet lives
as long as youtube lives
chihuahua lives
i wonder 500 years later youtube will
still exist probably not
probably
maybe humans not not even gonna exist in
500 years
[Music]
perhaps humans won't even exist anymore
yeah
let's not think about that
that's very dark
[Music]
tonight
that's an ideal world yeah
only cats will survive stray has proven
it straight is from the future it's
proving us
what's gonna happen in the future
blazin tidus or titus duncan
welcome to halfway point future kiana
another one
just want to say happy second
anniversary thank you for being my oc
you're such a kind and fun phoenix and
excited for what you have in the future
thank you
thank you moon dog
how is it on the moon
is it ready yet for us humans to go over
to the moon huh
can we can i pack my my my stuff already
[Music]
now we just talked about not being
able to live until 500 years later but
maybe we're on the moon
maybe this will solve our problem
[Music]
or are there currently only dogs they're
getting there okay good good good i'm
i'm counting on you moon dog
i'm counting on you
can you build me a home
with a pool
please thank you
[Music]
at least
i know you're safe on the moon
that's good be careful please
don't eat the moonstone okay
don't eat it
i wonder if you eat the ground on the
moon does it make you sick
[Music]
what's the ground on the moon made out
of
[Music]
what's the ground
on the moon made out of
lunar soil is composed of various types
of particles including rock fragments
mono-mineralic fragments and various
kinds of glasses including
agglutinate particles volcanic and
impacts for rules
can you eat lunar soil
did anybody anybody ever ask this
question before
oh my god someone asked
oh is luna soil toxic a study has
recently shown that human neuron and
lung cells exposed to simulated lunar
dust experience dna damage and cell
death even in very small quantities this
isn't totally unexpected earth dust can
have similar effects
toxic or not volcanic ash has been known
to cause bronchitis and emphysema when
inhaled
there you go my question wasn't so far
off because i said you shouldn't eat
them the moon ground and yeah
i was right
[Music]
and someone asked on quora
can you eat the moon
[Music]
oh my god
someone answered no the moon is over 73
trillion
metric tons of rock it is too much and
not eatable on top of it
edible eatable
they're all eatable
eatable because they're from austria
apparently
uh
[Music]
it's edible
what an answer it's too big you can't
eat it all well
time to prove this person wrong
let's eat the moon
what
someone selling nasa
moon dust that got eaten by cockroaches
talk about fine dining this just might
be the most expensive meal in history
too bad humans didn't get to eat it
we're talking about moondust retreat
from the guts of bugs that scientists
fed
lunar soil collected by the apollo 11
astronauts brought back in 1969 among
other critters cockroaches ate and
digested small amounts of the soil so
scientists could study its effects and
the remains of the insects last meal are
now up for auction are you [\h__\h]
kidding me
along with some of the bugs bodies and
other
memorabilia from the study
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
oh my god
[Music]
what auction estimates that its roach
lot will go for four hundred thousand
a hefty price considering some of the
dust was spilled and gathered back up
what
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
what did i how now now let's go back to
super chats
this is cursed
this is just facebo face palm material
this is how we create alien cockroaches
maybe that was the plan maybe that was
the reason they tried it
[Music]
oh man
dog
again thank you oh maybe that's a
continuation it's been a roller coaster
of a year full of exciting moments kfb
is super proud of all that you have
accomplished here and you've inspired so
many of us thank you so sweet
yeah we accomplished some things but
there's still things that we have to
tackle oh it's a rainbow
you got interrupted one last thing in
this rainbow kiara is amazing thank you
for the rainbow
you're amazing too
thank you
[Music]
thank you so much
i hope you will stay
a chicken
for a long time it's your destiny you
have to fulfill your destiny you know
don't leave me hanging
please
uh our firm thanks for the pinky happy
second anniversary boss it's been a
wonderful experience seeing you succeed
i don't know where i would be if it
weren't for you and myth y'all keep me
sane on the long weekend shifts like now
much love to you here's to another year
oh i wonder what you work
i won't know when you work but i'm glad
that you can enjoy some myth content
while on the job
we are gladly your entertainment
material
thank you so much for supporting
[Music]
much love back to you and hopefully the
coming year
we will have a lot of fun together
[Music]
thank you
happy two year anniversary boss i've
enjoyed being here for the streams i
joined kfb because you've handled some
heavy super chat with a lot of care ah
that one that one
i give my friend credit for introducing
me to a whole to whole life via pick on
the clips nice good job
good job the best kind of clips out
there are piccolo clips
[Music]
thank you for becoming part of this
community i'm glad you found
pekora and then me
[Music]
that also is a destiny it's a miracle
so so artist
thank you
my heart
thanks you dearly
[Music]
true yeah yeah yeah
big ups to cow carrot for the great
clubs here
right so free danke soon
space wonderful kitchen
endless thank you for the red super chat
happy anniversary kiana thanks for the
varied and frequent content looking
forward to continue to tune in to your
streams in the year ahead thank you
it's my job
it's my job and i enjoy it
thank you for letting me make all this
kind of content
thank you
[Music]
a kiss for you perhaps you fancy a kiss
from kiwawa
there you go
we're now at the six and a half hours
mark of the 12 hours
i could go longer but it feels like it's
starting to be
[Music]
you know
repetitive
sorry
maybe we stopped
you know we read a good portion
we got pretty far thanks to that it
won't haunt us forever
now
let me look at my schedule tomorrow what
are we going to do tomorrow
[Music]
actually i wanted to stream longer today
but you know super chat reading
[Music]
nah i wanted to feel special when i read
these messages so i don't want to go on
for too long
[Music]
what do we do tomorrow
um you tell us
[Music]
i'm scared of playing holocaust because
what if it lacks again so much
i'll have to test it out in my free time
and see if the problem fixed itself
[Music]
yeah well i'll test off streaming
the iron beats nah not this week now
are there new jrpgs to start
[Music]
at the moment still not really but
yeah maybe
you know since this week i have no
schedule i don't want to start anything
like super
surprisingly big
maybe for next week
i'll start something i'll i'll put it in
my schedule here
maybe
maybe but
ah tomorrow let me look at my steam
everest i don't know
i think i'll play rest on the weekend or
so
um
how about
i can
i can offer also uninstall this game i
have like no space on my pc i don't know
what takes up so much [\h__\h] space
i recently
bought
12 minutes
[Music]
i never played that when that was like
super popular
[Music]
and
it's a good first experience
yeah i like i from what i've seen so far
it looked really like
riveting
um
[Music]
i find it interesting
it's a fast no no no no no
i've seen people play it for hours
it's unique yeah that's why
why
why i got it for like a
[Music]
game someday to play some day when i
don't know what else to play
[Music]
a lot of repetition well yeah that's
that's the thing you have to keep on
repeating and
like solve
the problem
in 12 minutes
yeah
solve the puzzle
ah
so either that or i'm gonna
dig a bit in my
in my games list
[Music]
i'm gonna dig i'm gonna go digging
it would frustrate frustrate me you
think so
really
[Music]
that's why i made no schedule for this
week because i'm so brain empty about
games this week
i was so focused on the anniversaries
the collab and the song anniversary and
do you and all that that i didn't really
like my brain is like what what what
[Music]
yeah i'm gonna play again soon
i'll check what other people have been
playing
on
their channels recently
there's been a lot of splatoon but i'm
not really
interested in starting splatoon right
now
[Music]
i'll take a look i'll look around a
little bit
[Music]
no i don't i don't feel sims right now
my other book club members say they're
down for anything that's nice i might i
i i suggested wheel of time
maybe we'll get the real time i'm so
selfish with this that i'm pushing wheel
of time now just because the
[Music]
i recently watched the show
and my mom told me it's an easy read
[Music]
14 books
oh
oh that's too long
maybe the hobbit how about this frame
books or is it just free movies how many
books is solvent
[Music]
hobbit book
isn't it just one book
it's just one
right
how how small when you guys say small
[Music]
how small is small
300 pages
that sounds very
little
one tiny book stretched into three
movies that's actually insane when you
think about how other books that are
like free books are
like like squeezed into one movie often
[Music]
how long does it take to read 300 pages
i'm not i don't i can't imagine
[Music]
it's for kids
two days
interesting
[Music]
oh i mean of course you could read it in
one day if you wanted to
the hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy
[Music]
i wonder if all the other girls read
their books in english
if i should read it in english too and
or in
german because i think i would have an
easier time reading it in german in
theory
uh
i mean i understand english but
especially when it comes to like fantasy
books
i feel like my brain will be
having an easier time comprehending it
in german
i like watching tv shows and movies in
the original language english mostly
but
i think because i like the original um
voice acting and all that it's not voice
acting just acting
for original voices
but for reading
maybe german
[Music]
oh well anyway sorry at the moment my
mind is like i can't
i can't make up my mind about anything
it should be way easier in german
old-timey english yeah there's also a
thing old-timey english
confusing
[Music]
yeah we'll continue discussing which
book to read and
i will continue thinking about what game
to play tomorrow
[Music]
i'll see you guys tomorrow do you have
unpacking
um i don't think i ever bought unpacking
but i want something more interesting
than that i think
nothing against that game it looks
really chill
actually
i have
um grand theft auto purchased
[Music]
maybe i'll play
maybe i'll play dad
and that will be our game until um
until
pokemon
grand theft auto 5
now that's an idea
i want to drive a kind go vroom vroom
vroom
okay i think i have um motivation for
that one just need to check if i can
spontaneously play it i think
i think that one should be fine
grand
hmm
[Music]
doesn't exist
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'll find it
ding
[Music]
no
i will not play your truck or a racing
game if i want to drive something no gta
is a racing game
it's a driving simulator
yeah
with some story i guess
when i was younger i would like hop into
like my brother's
grand theft auto
game and just drive around a little bit
and i thought the only content in this
game was driving and shooting people
stealing cars
running array
like i did not understand that there was
actually like some kind of a story there
there's a story right
[Music]
it's not half bad okay there you go
there you go
that's a good story
i'm sorry has a story has a story
wonderful okay we'll play that tomorrow
tomorrow
gta5
unless i need to like ask in advance but
otherwise this will be it
okay
okay i'll go now
thank you for
um
keeping me company while reading super
chats
[Music]
didn't i just say i'm not going to start
any big new game
in this week and there we go now i'm
doing gta 5 oh well
wait
gta 5
game
length
50 hours just for the main storyline
whoa that's pretty long
[Music]
50 hours
wait another one says 31 and a half
hours if you focus on main objective
which one is correct this one says 50
just for the main storyline but extras
take 130 hours but the other one says 30
to 35 hours
[Music]
always play as big as you want to make
it
okay
3240 okay but i think that's a good
filler until pokemon
[Music]
not really the usual kind of game i
would go for but
i will
take a look at it and we'll see if i
like it if i don't like it you know i
won't force myself to play it but i have
a feeling it could be fun it could be
fun
okay
oh am i
haven't gotten very far but i still have
fun
oh
yeah well you know i'm the game finisher
the other girl girls never finish games
roasted
[Music]
although i'm impressed that ami is still
playing elven ring
she's still playing alvin ring and she's
like on her way to finish it right
[Music]
roasted and served
yeah she really liked it like beyond um
beyond just getting
some moist
um
i forgot the word
[Music]
moss yeah
[Laughter]
i heard someone yesterday copied my
phrases and just kicked the key and
alvita's in we have to cancel her
cancel that [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] that's my phrases
unbelievable
[Music]
don't even don't even think about it
chickens naughty naughty chickens
naughty naughty
okay bye-bye
[Music]
don't betray me
why
love quinoa
[Music]
i guess
of course
[Music]
ah
roughly
um i'm thinking of starting at like 6
p.m
or 5 p.m yeah
[Music]
you