[Music]
oh
spe
[Music]
oh
hello hello
not sure what's going
on
yippe oh no what's worse is that the
resolution is not correct that's the
most horrifying part okay now it's
good at least no game name sounds
mayhaps not sure if that's a blessing in
disguise or
not you can kind of hear the game
audio kind of who are you people
huh hello can you say that again hello
oh where am I where where are we oh
hello stay away you guys can talk yeah
I'm kind of scared what's happening oh
my God my
hands what happened to my hands they're
so
blocky where's
Waldo why is it why is it so
pixel I don't know why my body looks
like this it's so Square it's so Square
what happened
oh my
god wow everyone's so Square every looks
like squares oh my God what happened I
think I hit my head what happened who
are all of you I think Kiara I think
that's your name I think you should be
unmuted maybe I think you should open
your
mouth I think you are unmuted maybe you
should unmute Maybe crazy you look
famar hello are you guys from another
world
maybe see the lights I wonder you can
people here did you see the
lights hey hey hey you know
me wow what's going on why are you in
the corner feel no pain I feel no I feel
no nothing in my Bon I'm
loud they're loud voices did you see
give me a second
why what
happened
server server close what what does that
mean server is
close I don't understand what that means
what does this mean that I got
isaky wait what what does isite mean
wait I'm going to the black screen again
oh
no
hello hello hello
lights oh my God we back oh it's so R
we're back oh you can open your mouth
now wow Aon I was trying
to I I have this feeling that you might
want to massage me so I was turning
around and like you look yeah of course
yeah I don't know why but I have the
sudden urge to massage you you're so
good at that oh thank you about you you
look cute thank you I'm a
rat wow what what are
you it is really loud here that's soing
you will have to figure out the C thing
later as gods are telling
me it's just so much talking yeah that's
why we were like
mut I I guess I guess
so hey you know something kind of czy
hello here how are you
you guys know that oh you're muted on
purpose see their names I see I
see people have been telling me about
you
are how do you know asking me if I
remember you how do you know it's Mor
K me will it make the people watching
you feel bad if I say that I do not no
because I also don't remember you oh
okay God Square I I guess it's probably
no
problem
hello what is your name I like you
because your voice isan G too loud
really I feel like that's not really
what it you can stay in the corner and
that's not really what I'm thinking
right now what are you
thinking fair I don't know I thought
maybe your name was G like a g
yes Jonathan with
aath be surprised
isane people Jonathan really yes yes
Jonathan I thought it was more like I
don't know like g g
g like
itan G is my
initials G oh like a Triple
G yes Jonathan G oh I see that's a cool
name thank you
Jonathan name my my name is
uh uh I don't know actually I
think what is my name can you give me a
name your
name let me let me let me really get a
look at
you what do I look like me oh this is
also a very
nice right who
I think your name is what is your
favorite color do you remember that I
think it's I think it's I think it's
blue
name is
the S the what the a the Azure Maiden
The Azure Maiden that's so long oh then
it can be
[Music]
okay my name is Tam what's my last name
I think it's
like am
Gander Tam Gander yeah I think so yes I
have feeling that I think your name is
Tam Gander thank you
Johan that really settles
in thank you I I thank you too for this
this most auspicious meeting oh what
ceremonious day
yesah
huzzah
thank Gander I know there are so many
voices in my head it's getting mixed up
Tam
Gander now take a
gander What's a sneak
key what is a sneak key sneak sneak
sneak Who I Am the world I live
in and more than
anything the people I hold most dear I
don't hold anyone dear I don't
know face with Oblivion I feel
empty
relieved perhaps
distraught I do not
know so much I don't know so much I
don't know oh why are their voices I do
not and yet and yet that bright light
bright CLS to me bright light there's a
lot of lights oh the bright is light
white I must I must go yeah don't fall
there's oh don't
fall can you fall through
actually I hope not oh this looks
dangerous I can't do this this place
must be
like it's
shiny happens if we fall oh thank you
than go to the
light is this the light is this it shiny
are we going to shoot up do we shoot up
like
Las no
bad very powerful with this say they
have him
pretty take me take me
aliens is this is this feels to be wait
what is an
alien so many voices do we can we go we
go I like this should we go towards the
light what am I that looks like an egg
this
is that looks like at that that looks
like a soul gem a broken what is a soul
gem is this a hole but what came first I
think I watched it from an anime but
what is an
anime oh I can walk through it oh
nice
are oh
okay we're dead sick
oh it's the Le bestle cast oh that's
cute you there what are you doing here
you have the look of Outsiders about
you wait could it
be quick send word to his
majesty the heroes have arrived at the
sanctuary
right
away am I the chosen one my king you are
so cute can I call you cute is that
legal welcome Heroes this is the kingdom
of liestal and I am its
king the guards who brought you here
have informed me that you remember not
but your own names yes Cam
Gander hm a side effect of travel
between worlds no
doubt this must all come as a surprise
to you but hearken well to I who
summoned you
here you see an unpresented Calamity now
threatens our
world it has swn the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our
homes this blighted land now gives rise
to creatures of Shadow known as stains
this Kingdom of liestal and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us
leeston but should the Calamity be left
unchecked this only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire
world oh you just got off your throne
like
that faced with this Prospect I scoured
the ancient texts for ways to combat the
Calamity and therein I found one
the ritual of hero
summoning you who hail from another
world oh it's isekai that's just like my
web Tunes except I don't know what a
webtune is have been summoned here to
become the what to become the saviors of
liestal I just nodded only you have the
power to save our
world and so I ask will you make marry
me
what your
majesty what is it a great host of
Stains have broken through our defensive
line
no we're rushing to mounted defense but
the situation is dire Your Majesty we
must get you somewhere
safe
No but he was just proposing to me who
are these strangers
what say you Heroes will you accept this
Destiny no but there is no option there
is a great power within you will you use
it to save us to save this world
I kind of don't want to what's in it for
me
I oh my God there's
food oh my my
goodness Ru
Ru
orange
Celesta there it is you look
like you look like
that that cookie dough guy I feel the
king might have been
mistaken king the king is
the he think that I but is a do
boy this cute look at it ear flaps it's
adorable look at that can I hit you no I
can't I'm so sorry I'm so sorry no I'm
so sorry I didn't mean
to I'm so sorry I just I just wanted to
know you
what is this sassy little
[Music]
child I want to punch it apparently
that's a very
odd oh what is
this hello what are
you is that the only thing you can
say hi okay she might be broken this one
a little just a tiny bit little broken
this one over here what kind of accent
is that kind
ma'am we don't remember we don't
remember we don't we don't remember why
are you laughing kind
man this situation is so funny to me I'm
no hero oh it's a coping mechanism I see
you what this what
exactly
you I do cuz I'm in the same
situation I am no hero why is everyone
holding a sword a great
mistake the King was going to propose to
me he said will you and then we got cut
off I think we were in the same spot but
I
could for the throat I did not realize
I'm in the face of royalty your highness
yes honestly your your highness could
you maybe go back to the king and get
him to change his M because the bab is I
am not I just want to find a cabin in
the woods live a quiet life for the rest
of my days I know I understand my my
little peasant
however my little peasant but I I was
going to be crowned as Queen
but like I said I was rudely interrupted
by one of their servants but I promise
you after we save the
world I will make you have a good long
retirement
life oh you hardest you most
generous no need to thank me we got go
sa I regret that you must face such
danger so soon after you danger no
maest explain to you our
[Music]
King why is this this using so many
difficult words I don't understand these
words I we come from a land of simple
words too late to save this world
this is our duty to defend our King it's
your duty not my duty this is not my in
my hand bra
herow I not this is horrible how can
this
happen people scar me enemies
[Applause]
that's
crazy maybe we have to kill
the you can die is
dying what does D
mean yay okay we're doing
great many hits from so many of us oh
wow it's so
strong you
believe in the by
eating we heal for whatever
reason what an interesting mechanic this
is good job good job teamwork let's
goal there's no
way oh no everyone's dying this is just
like my eai web Tunes this is crazy but
I'm not dead yet because maybe I'm
chosen
maybe that's crazy oh it's peaceful all
of a sudden nice one thank you get
him I'm that is a very cute looking
dog
oh
Revelation re revelation
Revelation
re
Revelation re
Revelation mayhaps it needs more
energy
Revelation revelation
re
Revelation re
reation hold
on
[Laughter]
Revelation
okay oh okay
oh server has closed oh that's
weird I guess I wasn't Shing it um too
well
okay okay that's okay that is a
okay the quest has not failed I don't
even know what the quest is to begin
with so
don't don't never
worry never
mind what is that interesting
[Music]
screen it seems
like this world is a bit unstable at the
moment
so I guess we're going to be stuck in
the void
together who who's Kyla and why is it
her
birthday that's
crazy oh my
God what what to do in this amazing
world I'm amazing and scary and
terrifying having Flash backs having
voices in my head wait
hello what are you guys called my name
is Tam
Gander what's your
name hi I'm T we're married I I'm pretty
sure we're not married I I don't
remember what I am but I'm pretty sure
that I
have
remained very devoted
to I don't know this one person in my
mind she was very
beautiful but maybe maybe it's all
wrong oh
God
but but maybe it's just all a burning
memory now where have I heard that
before must have been a popular quote
back then we loved each other every day
that's
crazy no but I was meant for greater
things I was meant to be the
queen the queen of
lesto did you see I I think we're
sharing a vision together but I saw if
you saw what I saw the King was going to
propose to
me but but I guess it didn't happen due
to some rude interruptions but you know
what if I achieve something great like
saving the world with my
fellow my my fellow peers then I will be
able to
be loved by the entire Kingdom of Le
bestto and that's why the kingdom has
given me this great
challenge I'm laughing because this is
my coping
mechanism what what are your names I
don't think I've gotten your names do
you
guys what are you guys called
called
cro tamies
cronies
tamies
whoa you know that reminds
me there was this place called wait what
was it called I don't
remember but I think they
had these things called
Timbits and I don't know what they are
they're just popping up in my head but
it's just it was really
good and I think oh I'm getting a
headache but I think I had a cinnamon
bun today and uh what else a
blueberry custard Danish cuz what what
it was it was a cheat what is a cheat
day
what that's
crazy what is what's
happening
this it's a date cheat no
wonder
okay oh
great oh joyous day
how this
is I'm in the void this is very
nostalgic to to the days to the days of
when I was
born
born as a concept what a
concept I
thought I was human I must be human I'm
human I'm still
what kind of I don't
know I
don't I don't
think wait I'm a human I've always been
a
human this this can't
be do I
bleed I think I bleed I haven't tested
it out ever since I've been dropped here
but
I I don't
know I think I can hear my heartbeat
wait I don't think that's normal am I
dying if I can hear my
heartbeat I'm good thank you for
checking in um cronies I
guess I I don't really know I guess I
call all you guys
cronies my name is
Tam Tam
Gander tamies I thought you guys were
cronies that that sounds really similar
to my name though if you guys want to be
called
tamies I I kind of don't like that it
overlaps with my
name
really what what's it what's an
Oshi you would OSI Tammy what my name's
not Tammy it's
Tam what it's a food you oi Tam so that
means you're going to
turn me into food what's going on oh
wait I think I think I can oh the light
the the light I think I can enter once
again
mayhaps what what is a
Mojang
farewells oh wait I've been in this
place before this is so deja vu oh my
God we're back guys did you know we we
failed to save the world once that was
that was the that was the world oh my
God wait is this a Time
Li oh my God this just like my web
Tune Time look reincarnation oh yourness
maybe we could you could go back and his
hardness will finish the proposal and
you can get me out of here is very
correct if this is a Time Loop then we
can go back to where the king is and I
I'll call it off save the world and
youness you can't call off your your
your marriage no no no I'm not going to
call off my marriage we're going to call
off this journey and you're going to go
to your retirement and I
will hail you with a kingdom and you may
I will entit I will give you the title
of
Dutchess oh your highness I must most
hly refuse that sounds like way too much
pressure and responsibility oh
fine mayhaps I can give you the land of
the north why do you laugh do you laugh
my I find it absolutely adorable that
you win the Kake you similar vo
capillary like may have
by your side until this L finishes your
highness no need my
fellow uh what do I call you
fine is fine your highness your name is
peasant Bay peasant V Bay there is a v
in there peasant V Bay
youus wait your name is the p i mean
tile is the
B it's the Bae oh bae you are so my bae
they've taken a weapon yourness oh oh my
goodness stay calm everyone stay calm
everything is under
control everything is my food my food I
really needed bread I wanted bread
the all
powerful what are you yapping
about they won't let us out of these
walls man maybe you belong in these
white
walls oh no it's happening
again oh Echoes of Forgotten
memories de sha
Vu I can't be in the loop anymore this
is my second time who Who I Am the world
I live
in and more than
anything the people I hold most
dear faced with Oblivion I feel
empty
relieved who is
nanam Nana Nana mum she keeps entering
and leaving my
head perhaps
distraught I do not
know so much I don't know and
yet the voices should pop up any minute
now that bright light it calls to me
oh oh my goodness I just skin walked in
someone hello reion hello hello reion
hello oh you stink oh my goodness I'm so
sorry excuse me what did you say to me
oh no I'm so sorry no no sorry sorry so
sorry what's your name what did you say
repeat I no no no no I I was just like I
was just zoning out for a second I'm so
sorry I'm just panicking makes me want
to go what was your name what was your
name
sorry I am why do I been here before
gwange name is yeah that's a pretty bad
name just kidding kidding I'm kidding
nice to meet you go that was very weird
nice to meet you nice friend what is
your name I'm
M but my memor is a bit
fuzzy oh say fuzzy above your head
perhaps how can you read that perhaps
I thought I was the only
one I too can read that's crazy it says
it says dumb ass above your head whoa
excuse me what does it say above my head
it
says you
are Dumber times
two that's a lot of words I know more
than you could ever
learn you'll have to teach teach me if
we're stuck in this cursed land for much
longer I know but I think we may have to
go towards the light
first which one there seems to be many
the the light over there with five
pillars of light in the
middle I see your sense of direction is
I know I am meant to be Queen your
travels yes I am meant to be Queen in
this
Kingdom wow I know
oh this time I'm going to change change
my
fate you there what are you doing here
you have the look of Outsiders about
you wait could it
be quick send word to his majesty okay
I'm going to change my fate now the
heroes have arrived at the
sanctuary right
away my
king my
love I am back here I am its
king yes yes my name Tam Tam
Gander side effect of travel between
worlds yes yes
you see an unpresented Calamity now
threaten yes it has swn the Earth with
corrupt yes I know but most
importantly you have to
say something in which
case I
do oh yes this is
right the ritual of hero
summoning also known as marriage
you have your way with
words yes only you have the power to
save our world yes together we can save
our future and so I ask I do I
do hey get out of the way we are having
a
moment hello I said I do where is my
wedding ring I want like a three karat
ring like three karat diamond ring
hello okay a three karat is like too
little how about like five maybe like
eight I know like you know this I don't
know there there was this lady with a
big butt maybe her name started with
like Kardash or something like had like
a six karat maybe we can top that and
have an8 karat oh come on me oh hello
didn't we have this before sounds
familiar yeah do you want a
massage yeah I can you massage please
please yeah outside of the castle Yeah
yeah I don't know how she knew that I
needed that endless
loop to do it right this time thanks
that that's sword that's a nice
technique you got there yeah thank you I
thought maybe some equipment would help
her oh Special M looking for Heroes okay
okay all right thank
you eventually
I I don't I I don't peasant the bay I do
not wish to talk about it I would love a
massage oh I
see I well you see I did my best he was
going to give me a a nine karat ring
nine karat diamond ring I I know
unbelievable but but Fate has pulled us
apart I knew
he he was he was being so romantic and
said only you can save our world
together and I was saying I
do and veritus veritus is a villain vus
is very is so that I will put my life on
the line to protect you from enemies
your highness oh oh thank you peasant
the B call right now Captain can't hear
you you they should be they should be
here any moment if me mem say serve me
correctly yes we've been here before I'm
sure what is
this my I think I to protect the my own
Fair maen how have you faced through
that you mean I am
the you are one you have F I am R May
you're
Ru right
you are rubius it seems you have eaten a
fair
Maiden they're tricking those two
newbies oh no the voice the dialog is
you
imile
power has his majesty no doubt explain
to you our kingdom faces an unprecented
unprecedented
crisis the Calamity befs the land
leaving it B of life and infested with
wers known as
stains you mother not even the mighty
liestal Castle can be said to be safe
anymore the color red where's the pink
one
grandmother mayhaps it is too late to
save this world from destruction
nevertheless it is our duty to defend a
king and our countrymen to the very and
bu of Heroes From Another World let us
go forth with Valor and fight together
glorious I know how they move you must
prot the queen
oh the what a what a what an
amazing
[Music]
Queen charge my
peasants I feel bad calling people
peasants I am too humble for this
[Music]
maybe I've memorized one of your attack
so hit him from the back make sure you
after all really I don't think I I sure
hope
that down you go do it I sure hope my
chance works this time they're only
going to get in our
way hey hey no attacking that's not cool
my new friends oh boy oh my goodness I
don't want to die he's very your
motivation can't hurt the big thing we
have to
I cannot die yet ones
too go out be careful I'll protect
you no no no you
don't yeah I can see why you might feel
bad
you are we
win we are
winning or maybe we're losing but at
least we look cool doing hello what are
you guys doing why are you guys
we are having a battle we are back up in
case you fail so we can be like the
second we like the The Raid group on the
B excuse me it sounds like you're
procrastinating I'm not a procrastinator
I've never done that in my life I can
people are dying on the
battlefield well maybe they should get
good three people have died while we've
been Dilly dallying I don't think that's
true that sounds like a skill issue how
is that our problem you heathens
oh here we go again oh my god oh
okay
Revelation yes the stain host has been
routed you vious despicable you fought
bravely kind Heroes I pray you are not
injured that Mighty armored one must be
their leader the stained King
fascinating Most
Fascinating well I see why they call you
arrows we'd be in a right pickle without
your help you have a weird accent about
you we sustain shut shut it shut your
mouth fitus we sustain gain minimal
damage thanks to your Valor our kingdom
is in your debt thank
you I must hasten to inform His Majesty
of our Victory will you accompany me oh
okay never mind maybe mayhaps you would
redeem yourself there it
is my king where did you go my king I
heard the news though we called upon you
suddenly you Rose to the occasion you
have my deepest gratit that's great but
do you not wish to face me are you shy
what interests me most however is the
strange power you manifested during the
battle with which you were able to
defeat the
stains that power May well be the key to
saving our world from
Annihilation my king no need to be shy
we are to be wed according to the heroes
the power came to them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke the word
revelation this was the good ending but
once they used it to Route the stained
host it seems that the power vanished
Without a
Trace well that's bloody brilliant is it
so what are we supposed to do the next
time the stain
attack
revelation we must uncover the secrets
of this phenomenon if we are to Prevail
against a Calamity many questions remain
but one thing is certain the kingdom of
leest still stands today thanks to
you here here so Heroes I ask of you
once more will you lend us your strength
to save Le bestl from
ruin marvelous on behalf of all leeston
I thank
you we are blessed to have your Aid kind
Heroes allow me to introduce the four
Great guilds which are responsible for
for ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity The Haven for the Curious
where knowledge and creativity are
valued above all the Scarlet
wand the home for Glory Seekers with
ambition and vision where closest allies
become fiercest Rivals the Amber
coin the sanctum of healing where the
spirit of empathy and devotion thrives
the seruan
cup the Beacon of the oh they're all
invisible they are all shy the beacon of
the righteous and loyal where great
threats are faced with even greater
courage the Jade
sword one of these guilds will become
your home during your time
here Beyond this door lies a room of
Truth therein the will of the ancestor
shall decide your guild fear not
introspection is a vital step on the
road to Enlightenment excelsia as I
always say ever
higher time to roll that I say being
seeing some of you down lot down at the
Amber corn
Guild let us save this world
together the room of Truth awaits go
forth with
Valor I am crawling that door is so
shiny
step on the platform and receive the
will of the ancestor yes I
will midst the endless flow of time seek
the power that Amber
grants I'm a seruan
cup I
what is
this am I wearing
it am I wearing
it armed with an unwavering will seek to
defend the soul of
Jade Celeste celest
oh
Tam oh
Jonathan what e summoning egg what what
are all these things radio Wast spin
what what is what is your name there's a
map there's a
map I'm looking waist bin I have a cool
cloak
magical map let me just put on my cloak
what happens if I Ste summoning it
is so fast wow oh my
God where's my horse okay that's so cool
what horses so
quick Ki be you
oh Jonathan do I have my Cape Jonathan J
you're here Jonathan G can you see my
for short uh I think there's a something
a little
the different about your K really oh yes
your oh oh my
goodness what is are you moner who what
do you mean my God you're going ah I
cannot beare look at you what you're an
impos evil you're evil black cape where
is that where did you get that from the
the
void what I'm one of you you're you're
one of wait so are we all s and was it
we are all ceran we're all
ceran the k Master Okay Master K the
master I am on my
horse an is busting upon you hero
welcome to the kill h of the Cilan
Club I didn't read the first
part where's the quest board even so
soon after your summoning speaks volumes
about your selflessness oh oh as a
member of this Guild you'll be joining
the effort to cleanse this land of
stains and bring Salvation to the
world but one must walk before one can
run first you should learn about the
town we strive to protect as well as how
to accept and perform quests quests
Quest within this town there is a
location known as the quest board o
where is it where is the quest there you
will find a quest master who will impart
his knowledge upon you you may also use
this time to familiarize yourself with
the
town oh it's a quest all right
matter okay okay where'd she
go
she she is really fast yeah well we just
keep going this way okay I believe
yeah and where are we we go this
way and then we go that way yeah yeah
this way there we go yes the quest board
Quest board Quest
board everyone you too thank you thank
you his name is he must be one of the
heroes then the guill master told me to
expect you I thank you for risking your
lives to protect our fign kingdom uh
guildmates how do I get off my horse uh
shift sneak sneak sneak sneak sneak
understand your main duty is r g the
stains but I hope you'll take the time
to help some citizens in
need he must be tired of my battle by
now so how about we get it started with
the quest right away I see it looks like
perfect job fre well best of luck oh you
go
now complete what are the options what
what are the side
class okay we can I can read these right
materials needed at the Smithy I'm The
Apprentice at the Smithy and my master
says we're running low on raw materials
if you can help us gather some please
stop by the Smith can we only take that
Quest it looks like only I think so
everything's the
same okay Quest
accepted I will get on my horse too okay
accepted accepted okay the
Smithy uh Smithy where is the smiy where
is Where Art Thou the Smithy there is a
map so we can maybe look around and
uh
[Music]
ohc I see it where is
it
smoy Smithy R is this a Smithy Nom yes
yeah oh it's smiy Smith
materials
needed what do you need what you
need oh great you saw my quest I posted
well to start with could you bring over
10 Oak locks there are a bunch of trees
not far outside the town you can
chop
okay this person over
here all The Apprentice oh okay collect
10 coins completion 100 coins we can buy
food with
that why am I in a I guess we can get
out of the town what's the name of your
horse of your
Steed
Gigi oh mine is ninoa oh waa these are
very complicated names yeah what's
what's the name of your horse
C I think it's
a a COI wait are you are you guys in the
same party together not yet should we
join a party shall we party up I I how
do I leave my party shall we
party in a party I up by a random party
I don't know how I did it you're just in
a party yeah without
us
huh I got kidnapped oh well by who by
I'm green someone named I'm green GRE
I'm green I'm purple I'm green stole you
yeah she stole me I'm in her party for
some reason oh that's
strange kind of
scary I'm trying I'm I'm calling upon
the scriptures to see how to leave a
party yes I I do not know how to leave
this I've been
kidnapped okay well
well let's let's see maybe did you get
that party invite oh I did uh I did not
oh hold on how do I
accept let me let me look at the
scriptures the scriptures the scriptures
on how to free ourselves from someone's
party yeah
aha the voices in my head are very
helpful I have to find the person who
invited me but I don't know who invited
[Laughter]
me oh there's I'm
green so she wasn't just made up I see
she's probably very far away cuz we
don't see her
return Our member to
us oh maybe the magic to can help try
your magic tone Oh magic toone there was
something really sparkly over there for
a second did you guys see
that where in front of the quest board
ooh the magical to wait it a member of a
party but I'm I'm in a party huh what
what I did not mean to trade you oh I
failed to invite
you maybe
mayhaps oh might I think that if you go
to page four of the magical toome you
may be able to
leave that's magical to I I think I
pressed that magical to and it says that
I am not a member of a party but on the
my screen it says I have a part of a
party party so perhaps you might need to
uh unconscious yourself AKA oh yeah
perhaps close your eyes will come back
close my eyes and um go to sleep and
[Music]
then I will give you some privacy I will
look away from you okay
away did she leave this world where did
she go she left this world wa oh she
just came back welcome back oh she just
rageed quit welcome
back are you still in a party oh I'm I'm
good now I have escaped the gr of the
random people yes what an wait why does
they fail to invite player H we
good
what what why why can I can someone else
try to invite her to our party I think
only party leaders can so strange that
is difficult is still in a party how
about we remake the party how do we
remake a party uh click on your magic to
the magical to
yeah I've disbanded my party I will
invite you no fail to invite
oh
oh it's okay I
will I will
be the lone the Lone Wolf I I guess it
is my destiny to work
alone I suppose
free free m
who is
eating it's
Gigi
you I was hungry in
Minecraft what is Minecraft I mean I
mean you mean an enigmatic
recollection what istic
recollection I don't remember living
back to the quest board oh yes yes I
don't think
we are
we mayhaps instead of typing accept you
click on
accept is my humble
opinion red moment thank you
[Music]
yeah yay we're in the party now okay
everyone let's go get wood and beat the
other teams we have to be we're speed
running quick go your horse
go yay
this way exit uh the exit yes it is is
this the exit yes
yeah we are okay let's go all right get
the get the no that's not part of our
Quest that's not part of our quest part
of a future what she has a point but
we're getting the logs before anyone
else can let's go that's right
logs empathetic
healers oh wait is that a
stain there's a
stain we can't have a stain that'll
leave a stain in our
[Laughter]
Legacy St
guys guys we can get coins from
defeating stains
oh there's a
rabbit and a
stain what are these whoa away from her
oh thank
you seems you're okay okay that's I can
use it okay oh my God they're spawning
outside the walls at an alarm r
away wow we're so fast when we do it
together yeah yeah we completed the
objective did you complete your
objective ow I don't think so
okay oh I got eight coins from killing
that will it will it St when you
complete the objetive
you okay I guess I just got to keep
going you can also check your inventory
just to double check pock your pockets
your your napsack your bag the bag on
your hip
mayhaps this is they're sleeping kill
them while
cute these are kind of cute I want one
as a pet cool
down can we use our skill that is called
Revelation well not really it's not
called Revelation but you may use
Revelation okay Revel
I want to see re
reation
reation okay I need
one oh that was very cool thank you 20
coins yeah let me
Revelations it's on I am tired now yeah
I'm I am tired yeah I have a cool
down yes I have a
refractory some magical Tre I really
want a nap now back to
the
trees wow the spawn rate on this is
insane crazy yeah crazy stain slime ball
can be thr why would it spawn on top of
me did everyone finish their objective
yes yes then should we go back okay Hast
you cannot let them catch up I think
they already caught up no way
okay we go to The
Apprentice yes which is right
here right
here whoa what does that do oopsies you
cannot use the great you brought the
locks thank you so much see my master
over there if you bring the raw
materials to him he can make all sorts
of tools and items for you buy
okay people scare me wooden
pickaxe
okay I do not have the required
materials we need Oak plank from up
yonder hasth Fallen to their death hath
Fallen oh planks and
sticks want two Scarlet wand
member I would like a pickax failed to
purchase we are missing four five how do
I make a plane oak logs that's very easy
my friends oh I
think
got
information
exactly it is just that easy my
friends o of tools
easy interesting I have an
axe I think we need great now you did it
from now on when you find new materials
stop by here and talk to my master the
more different materials you find the
more things he'll be able to make say
what we need collect 10
cobblestones all
right onward oh my is
to
onwards I got this thank
you we will be so fast the
cobblestones and some ore
mayhaps might this be coal is this is it
what is what's happening I think this is
I don't know I think oh this is
bedrock this how do you know I I don't
know it just popped up into my head 10
you know so much more than you let on I
don't know oh you're being attacked I'll
protect you behind you oh no oh my God
are you sure you protected
me I jumped over it it was merely a
miscalculation oh thank you oh you saved
me there we go thank
you I collected 10 cobblestones have you
collected 10 cobblestones
not quite yet I I I have now collected
10 cobblestones yes we are making so
much
progress or have they been left behind
mayhaps I can give them a call let me
ring them
up a party
call hello I am in a party call it is
only us only only two of us is it is
only two of us what is the point of
calling if nobody else is picking up the
call oh no we are in danger I I'll
protect
you thank you I very much appr hello
thank you for picking up you where are
you guys where did you guys
go I'm just doing the quests I see I see
you finished are you I'm at the quest
Master now yeah oh okay we will return
to you post taste okay post taste W with
with haste with the utmost haste I way
10 cobblestones and speak to the
blacksmith P okay I must go my people
need
me oh farewell oh I want to I think we
can leave the radio now oh yes now that
we are together we hang up the phone
call yes goodbye my fellow party members
good day sir material we need material
wait do we need to bring the materials
okay what did they just say again
Apprentice we talked to The Apprentice
you brought the Cobblestone if you talk
to my master now you should be able to
make you stone tools okay uh thank you
for responding toest I posted with me
okay I don't know I didn't even know how
you called me what am I supposed to make
again I I I guess you let me know all
right are you ready to cut
down need you hang up what do I want
just double
check what do I want do I need 10 oak
logs maybe and we need we need 10 oak
oak logs yeah okay I mean that seems
like I'm going to get I'm a stone
sword
[Music]
she's want to make a party together
where did my teammates go you're right
invited you how
do AC the party though
G the party
okay go
where Where Art
Thou Hello whoa cool swords
[Music]
is this the
Smithy
yeah I am in barely I see awfully Big G
for tiny people oh teammate joyous day
oh teammate let us make haste to the
quest
board farewell maidens where do you
where do you wait farewell maidens oh
yes yes would you like to
um interested in construction go
and you'll find empty where you Heroes
that sounds good stop by and have a good
talk yes towards The City Gate there
will be an orb that will lead you
outwards oh my goodness that's a lot do
we have to go to the smiy first or can
we just go out yes you must speak to the
SMY to obtain you can do whichever can
we just accept all the quest said this
way is out you can we the wood and then
the Smithy can we can we can we just
accept all of them at once I am
accepting I'm gonna go get some wood do
you want to come with or do you want to
go to the maybe I should just accept
everything I'm accepting everything I'm
not
reading it's okay we can read it
later it is a future Us's
problem in the end we're helping those
in need yes as as is the rule of the
Cerulean um Team exactly
and and
devotion a deliver a wood
shovel okay that's easy Quest Mask Stone
Pickaxe hello
hello iron axe I don't think so oh I can
hear you I can I can hear you yeah even
if you're in a call we can still hear
because we have ears and you are next to
us all right are we ready to complete
more quests yes I would love to complete
more I just finished the the
cobblestones one I'm not sure what to do
we can we finish to the crafting a stone
pickaxe and a wooden
shovel oh I need to collect a
cobblestone I have not done that yet yes
yes yes oh spend where where would one
go said Stone you must walls got the got
the wood go a little further and there
should be a mound of stone oh let us
make haste to the joyous outside
world of Le
bestl wait ladies
okay here we are back again I don't know
how back outside the kingdom walls
pickaxes swinging side to side side side
side to side to side this makes me feel
a little sick watching this happen I
don't know I
just I feel some sort of attachment to
these to these solid like beings I feel
sick that you're kind of destroying them
appar L when you hit them Tam says they
become
Bedrock yes they do I don't want to I
don't want to hurt them though it feels
like against my nature to hurt them I
think you should hurt them they are
adorable and I think they deserve
death this one is like a cute
bunny this one has horns and it kind of
hurt okay I think we had to slay about
10 of them why are there so many
attacking specifically
me oh Fair Maiden do not worry I got
you please I'm just trying to get some
wood I got
you
maybe
owie these things are strong man oh yep
they are a bit strong mayhaps my humble
opinion Fe summoning egg mayhaps who oh
we should probably run I think they're
after us I may have brought a joyous
crew
oh my my
friends quick let
us oh I
heard ring ring ring yes this is Tam
Gander we are thinking
that we should stay on the phone call
just in case we leave each
other's hearing range yes I believe that
is a splendid idea yesk you Splendid
Splendid
Splendid joyous day oh amazing wonderful
feelings make planks tra all right I
made okay we need plank I have
planks I thought I was I was trying to
skip the process I understand I'm sorry
maybe I should ride my horse so I don't
get hungry see I got this um perhaps my
my
group it
must against The Rock it does oh you
must do it yourself I must do it myself
and then what do what do we have to do
now
[Music]
okay I am done we completed we are going
to I see it well I am going to complete
a
quest put the perfect job for you best
luck off you go okay I think we also
need to collect Cobblestone
now oh God damn it there are more
quests we have so many quests to
do these quests
so that's why
we you can repeat the quest you can
repeat the quest it's a repeat Quest
they so
needy wow talk to the
shopkeeper I'm not I'm not done you're
not done stay
HS to go we're going to go get
cobblestone what happened did you have
potato salad I maybe they have some
bread I have to speak to the child in
the gardens child in the garden child in
the Gard I so sorry my the bartend
friends what's going on do you need
assistance no I killed them all okay
what oh
no it must have been very hard my
friends where did all of you go
I'm trying to find a child okay I will
meet with you cuz I do not know where
the child
is oh I see you my fellow Maiden that's
a p hello pubs usually have food did you
speak to the child in the gardens
already mayhaps where is the child in
the
gardens I no not I was hoping you would
know where the child in the garden's
rest the child in the garden the child
in the
garden the child in the Gard the garden
child where are you oh I see it the
child in the
garden oh what it's a few many Ys away
Ys away I I have
a let us make haste I am making haste to
the child in the gardens huz child in
the gardens the gardens
my horse cannot jump can it it can't
jump never mind my horse can
n yes there is a leeston child right
here I have found the Lees child child
let us speak with
you everyone's doing what they can just
like
you the child does absolutely
nothing we are spreading joy and
heroism to this town this was pointless
in never yes yes oh we are inspiring him
you too can be a hero when you grow up
if you just look to the sky and Shout
Revelation and then you will die an epic
death because you are too small and py
no no our devotion the Cerulean leaders
would like us to spread empathy all
right empathy yes you may grow up to
become a shopkeeper one day or a quest
master or a hero or a great
NPC what is an
NPC what's an NPC yeah what's an NPC I
do not know it just popped into my
head a lot of things seem to pop in your
head wonder what calamity tastes like
it's like tip of my tongue
I wonder if it tastes like cookies I
have a few tip of her tongue
cookies cookies something about cookies
the tip of her tongue ah okay tip of her
tongue the tip of your tongue tastes
like
cookies this the only thing you can buy
the potions potions they're very
helpful
so I have 693 coins what do I do
we must purchase things I forgot what
the quest told me to do we have to speak
to pit Dorman who the heck dor pit
Dorman why do I have so much food now
who gave me
this
bread sorry I just get so hungry oh
where you can build Beyond The Garden
you can build freely I just realized why
is my horse in an
egg why not horse has come from eggs did
you not know oh I did not know in this I
found Mason they come from eggs well you
seem to know very well about this realm
you are very well acquainted how do you
know are you does
thou where the shopkeepers
are across the way from the Smithy the
Smithy thank you my trusty companion I
appreciate no problem why do we all talk
like this I have no idea like
what like what wow it is just how we
speak we can build our own and BR dear
friends Guild House let us build our own
Guild House yes oh how joyous day let us
make stay let us make our humble abode
yes our humble abode we have our little
plot on the uh near the
wall let us Build Together Miss time
lady yes
Rock I stop I I have seemed to have lost
my way shop is this way oh thank
you yes no
problem oh I I very much appreciate you
guidance thank you
anytime
rock thank you
block oh nice nice potions 100 coins
what a ripoff I ain't buying anything
place a
Coliseum oh I like the way it
thinks I think that's a bad not leaving
until you sh your pickaxe young
lady all right we're ready let's go get
cobblestone accept our call for
shop sneak sneak
sneak sneak why are you sneaking so much
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm just sneaking
sneaking remind me of s I don't know I
think I'm starting to remember a certain
song about sneaking like a sneaky
Ney a sneak how do you all know that
song have you grown up in the same area
I do not know these memories they a me
trying to Guild Halls they a you ah it
must have been a song you all grew up
with a nursery rhyme mayhaps oh now I
can talk to
the
mayhaps mayhaps I was taught as a
child excuse me excuse me uh you you you
seem to have a blue aura around you oh
yes yes our our other our I'm I am on
the way I found her I found I am on the
way teammates team to the not let be
taken from us hers try I know how to get
out of
here they're trying to take I am on the
way
what I am I am making
haste I am getting very don't know where
away from her she's
ours where is this occurring our team
where is this
occurring quick come with me quick join
our team I don't even know where this is
occurring you
win no you are
ours where is this occurring my
friends God damn I am so lost you are
part of our
Guild you would leave us what the heck
God walking away lost her
they're I'm taking her she's our know
you have two halves one dark and and a
lighter
one listen to
the oh my gosh she's suddenly hitting me
she's suddenly hitting me can't even hit
you even if I want I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm sorry no no I'm sorry I even
this is really
violent hey Revelation
Revelation
to
reation Revelation
Revelation oh god what have you done
oh nice
fist every has cool
moves they look like from a retro game
Revelations
re
Retro Retro Game yeah yes I know not of
what you speak hello who are you you
beautiful beautiful violin lady oh at
least you know I am to be the next Queen
of the kingdom of
lesto what I did not know of your
intention that's how you say it this is
not an intention this is meant to be
your destiny it was meant to be it was
meant to be are you are you related to
them no The King and I we have loost
eyes blood blood related are you blood
related to that tiny King what no we
have locked eyes and we knew that we
were destined for each other you married
the king that are you under cover with
the King it's complicated she married
the king he was to oos to
me well you don't have you didn't have
to
accept I wanted to to inherit the
power all right all right this is the
future queen of Li best yes
yes glad you know fellow
peasants
peasants my my I'm sorry for speaking to
you with such we will not protect you if
you don't respect
no no that's why you're in a different
Guild oh you need the you need the
support of all the
G was I mean whoever you are stay
away Queen she's to be our Queen where
is she it's the will of the
king where is she looking where are you
going off to yes I have no idea return I
have no idea cute brown owl what is what
is your name I my name is Iris and I'm
I'm curently yeah nice to meet you what
is your name my name is Jonathan G
spelled with a G Jonathan
G okay okay I'll call you okay GG for
short Jonathan J G oh Jonathan with a
G bread now yes he's Jonathan I I'll
call you Jonathan Jonathan oh oh okay
yes I would like that so okay um Queen
Jonathan um who are you hello I have a
name not
Queen you like I would like to be
addressed
as
for sounds very cute and then who is
this rock that was trying to kidnap me
I'm toer Ki beu has to be after you
subed the quest W your name
is I don't know why that sounds familiar
but slightly different from what I
remember different I don't know I don't
know I've always been beu yeah why am I
being surrounded by so many people we
are one of us we one of us you are part
of the ceran cup but yes but I but I
joined another team no no you did not
join another team you are one of us you
you always been one of us we are desting
for each other really what what makes us
what what what what why why am I one of
you guys because you have empathy you
have I feel your devotion it's kind of
being
s empy she's she's one of ours you guys
don't I don't know especially you you
don't seem like you would have empathy
excuse
me I am made of empathy you are I am I
am liquid empathy yes I've seen it in
her eyes in Tam's eyes the way she spoke
to that child she is full of
I see yes I I would have with my current
uh my current team members well you
return to us it
is Jonah Watson she wants to kill the
king J Watson
Watson oh it's oh no she thought she
thought Revelation was Revolution and
she was
planning the king
I mean I can understand that that
misunderstanding but wait what era is
this set in you I have no idea what era
what what is even an era I have no idea
you're
right hey she wants to kill the king
Jonathan would never kill the king
Jonathan
is the wait which Jonathan are we
talking about here
Watson excuse
me stay away from my guild member excuse
me hello that is my guild member you
don't talk to Jonathan with a G like
that excuse me excuse me excuse me
excuse me excuse you don't talk to my
guild member like that yeah your guild
member is talking to my gu member F
excuse me she just having a friendly
exchange saying
myed you holding a sword
never and we are loyal we are loyal
we're
empathetic you la empathy your father's
a hamster and your mother smells of
elderberries excuse me I bite my thumb
andv I've never known my mother are
disturbing the I'm so sorry don't listen
to whatever they had to say why is it
I'm
crazy hey hey oh don't cry don't cry you
want to kill the king it's okay it's
okay which which which Guild is that
which Guild is
that interested let's find out let's
let's find
out they're
listening smash you what Guild are you
we'll meet up where do you I can't talk
about this right now why don't you
guess I don't know you evil give Amber
no scar you are correct Amber you are
correct from Amber disgusting money
hungry IM I am from that
place disgusting yes we don't interact
we don't interact with those from now
on do not ever interact with am don't
talk to us don't talk to us I will be do
not shush me there
talk you I can't hear
you excuse me the air is very loud today
what are you guys from what are you guys
from we are from ceran
Cup oh okay thanks now I can report you
guys report
you who I'm going to report you guys hey
hey hey hey hey that's not a good idea
hey hey hey hey hey that's not a he has
absolutely
hello absolutely that's not even that's
not even the right place where are you
running where are you headed to she's
going to report us where is she
reporting us to I have no idea it's a
thing I think the quest
Master honestly you just got to tell the
truth we are value honesty in this group
well do you think sure can't do
this what the heck just happened oh
that's pretty we totally could do that
what else they do I can totally see that
happening in Naruto what what else
narut what is Naruto
Nar it sounds like what I don't know
what it sounds
like to your head this is my reation my
reation no no never I would never know
been so good she's that one movie do you
know that one movie where they sing
Jonathan hey Jonathan yes I thought you
were about to say do you know John Cena
I'm sorry I'm who's John Cena can you
see him is he around here I can't see
him I can't what is who is Jonathan joh
Jonathan Jonathan is to kill jingle
whenever you hear that name Jonathan
Jonathan is this an
inside it is it is Jonathan with the G
you know right why do I know that how do
I know we have to get your
de
it's we we have
sworn vengance no it's no it's on the
ambercoin ambercoin is evil if you kill
him he'll be gone but you
h i I put my my name on the line us am
mcoin have nothing to do with Amber you
are on the Amber are you of Amber are
you he's of Amber
you what's there been a
misunderstanding what are you talking
about I'm in your team I'm in your party
no you are team freaking liar you're our
team no you
shut huh huh I mean you you shut your
humble
mouth what did you say to me I did not
say anything El are I thought you
supposed to be a part of the empathy
team
you do not defect yeah I I don't even
they they they're the ones who reached
out of helping her well you're supposed
to refuse it man you're in Cilan Cup oh
well I mean I didn't know you guys were
in Cilan well now you know so come
back Jo our party we should we should we
should remove our I said join our party
should I join our party please our do
you have empathy or not if you have
empathy join if you don't have empathy
you are you are a traitor before they
ask any more questions that I don't a
tra does anyone not want does
anyone
part caring nobody wants you except us
SC nobody oh nobody wants you except us
the ceran cup so wow wow we are so
compassionate we are compassionate we
are taking you an outcast under your
magical tomb you see this the magical
book open your magical book and locate
page four locate page four your magical
yes and dissolve your
party wait click to disband click to
kick click to leave click to leave try
to leave yeah should I maybe say
something before I leave no just leave
no no no just just leave them I mean
yeah they did just with us they ditched
you they they did they they did they
ditch me did they really ditch me yeah
they ditched you you only have us now
it's not a misunderstanding yeah you
were just a decoy uhhuh okay you were
meant to be with us you are one of ours
let me let me just say let me just say
in chat I was ditched so I will leave we
accept you for who you are traitor or
not you can make a new Legacy with us we
we we have been tied by the strings of f
I'm sorry I will
switch yes
yes is this really the right
answer this is the right answer nobody
loves you except us
okay very toxic this feels very toxic we
are we are full of empathy we are we are
the empathy group we are the group that
is full of empathy why I'm trying to I'm
trying to leave wait wait wait okay okay
I can't open the book all of a sudden
wait wait that's recycling bin okay on
page four of your magical tomb do you
really want to leave your party yes yes
yes yes yes yes oh I guess the sword
doesn't have I have I have I have aone
no I have left now now we will now join
our team us join our party you are one
of
us oh okay okay you guys are actually
full of empathy right
we
arean take our love okay
love
yes radio feeling the love and now open
your magic radio yes your magic radio
magic radio magic magic radio what do I
do with the magic radio and join our
call us ring ring our radio call on our
is a party call yes it's a group it's a
group chat there go
y yay
[Music]
you one of
us everything done let's
go be the calm
one calm we are calm we are we are calm
we are very calm we Cal yes we're so
kind we know love we know peace we know
peace and love does our ancestors
actually know us I don't think they know
us yes maybe they were like us and they
wrote history oh God that's horrible to
think about by the way what is your
quest sorry my beautiful te yes my
beautiful teammates uh uh how do I check
what side quest I'm on oh you on your
magic book one more time and you you
flip to page two
oh check your oh okay okay yes it says I
do not have any active side quest what
well
you to the board okay okay the
board the quest board okay okay are you
guys are you guys you know fully
already much your
words guys just ahead of me we are three
quests ahead if I were to
guess I see
mayhaps is my humble opinion I I came I
came a little bit you know a little bit
after you guys probably because I'm just
that important you know uh-huh you are
we are just so full of empathy we
understand we know why the board not
the okay okay oh there's so many quests
accept all of
them all of them because we are helpful
every Quest I think there's only one
yeah I think there is only one
okay there is only one it looks like a
lot okay and then I go you want the fast
pass through some of the quest oh
there's a fast pass is this is this gizy
what is gizy land I have no idea what
I'm the special oh the enoa special
please give it to me me me at the Smithy
where's the
Smithy the Smithy the Smithy is this way
yes I would like a horse where do I
where do you get a where do I get your
egg you crack your egg oh my God horses
are are born from
eggs they are yes
oh well that's Neo knowledge is it over
here yes how do I get off of it oh there
we go do I just abandon the horse or
just go you shift the button yes you
sneak sneak yeah
gotcha oh
sorry okay
hello hello fast pass fast here is your
you are drenched you are soaked I am
drenched yes I just saw you in the water
wait I can't I can't give items I was
really high you have to tr no are you
you have to trade you get cold okay no
I'm way too hot it's pretty nice here
you cannot you cannot fast pass the
actions on her own you're drowning
oh oh no I'm not drowning I
just I I can't
I I am a m Jester thank
you I am a silly little
clown materal needed at
the drowning
right what's going on you're drowning
you are you are dying what the hell's
going
on someone toring I are you guys
torturing somebody no no we are having a
nice
bath I did not man this is such a
peaceful team I'm so glad hands under
the water though empathy you
no me down
must I couldn't get I couldn't Amber
team must have done it ambercoin used
their telepathy on
you is is the ambercoin our like our our
main enemy yes they
arey mhm are oh they are yes greedy
they're the ones that we should go out
to kill kind of enemies yes yeah in the
name of empathy we must kill them yes in
exactly in the name of peace I don't
think that's violence to show how
empathy Works yes I see I didn't know
empathy was so violent but it makesense
one of them plans to kill the king so
sometimes violence is the only answer to
to have empathy show have to restore
balance restore balance I'm starting to
understand a lot of things thank you
this is what empathy means empathy is to
kill empathy is to kill the bad in this
world empathy means to kill
unfortunately my my loyal companions I
have a a pool somewhere from the unknown
and I must wa are you being summoned by
the forces beyond your knowledge the the
the darkness is and I must can drown of
course um but I believe in you guys you
guys will you come back to us I I will
back come back I will I will come back
to you and come back to this world as
soon as possible please don't forget
about me okay don't forget I I do not
wish forgotten we will miss you we will
never forget you pleas never forget you
in your wi
words beu and I will return to you my
companions we will wait you return we
won't forget we won't forget you
forget I will I will see you again I
will see you again goodbye goodbye
farewell
fwell uh uh uh
uh she is gone
the she has
disappeared the greatly forces have
claimed the all oh no but she'll be will
that happen to all of us eventually
eventually all of us will die will why
do you have to be so dark like that
because empathy is sometimes dark I see
when there is light there is Darkness M
wise words Queen wise words wise this
Slay Slay the queen no no no no no like
slay like Slay Slay
Slay i i the Queen is slaying I will try
I I will try I will
try good good
good now can someone tell me where the
leeston child is once
again he was in the garden after you've
spoken to him oneon-one uh yeah about
the
owl oh Ena how do I open this box that
you traded me with like items oh I see
right click after you have it in your
hand what is right clicking oh okay
right click placing on the ground oh
yeah place it on the ground with your
right hand yes with your right with your
right maybe try
interacting okay I got it I got it on
the ground thank you thank
you man my thirat is dead I don't even
know why it's
dead because you were transfer that cost
it ah that makes so much
sense what what wait wait side quest
side quest sure where is the Jade sword
Guild Master does anyone mayhaps
know if you um find something
green green to attempt the arena
you will find
them inside the
arena I'm not sure but do you know the
pit
Dorman
huh need to talk the D you saw the quest
I posted with the pit
Dorman is he a Dorman or is he a Pitman
he's what a Pitman
M no idea oh there we go you mean like a
Pikmin what's a Pikman I have no idea
just came into my something something
something I remember it's like hey D I
am to be here oh my goodness remembering
the the art of I think I was a master
here I'm remembering something about
Pikmin and the only thing I can remember
is that you throw you throw them at
people but the art of Dand tell me where
your leader
is is there any other Quest I can just
found one of
is am coin members thank you jna Watson
even though you wish to kill the king
excuse me do you know what where are you
guys I am faced with an Amber coin
member and I think you need to kill the
king you need assistance I'm an Amber
coin member yes I feel threatened save
him where where are you guys I am
afraid where is everyone be right back
every I need oh oh oh there you are let
me
follow
hello where where are we going I have no
idea I thought you knew the way I don't
know the way why would you think I would
know the way I'm a baby Baboo hey let's
go tease the Amber coin hey
ambercoin lost you're right
amberin disgusting
Amber hey hey why why hey why are you
doing that hey don't to be so negative
about
that what we say you know I'm just I'm
just so negative about myself and the
ambercoin I
justed wish I wasn't part of Amber
they're poo poo stinky wait what's wrong
do you want to talk about it wrong yeah
yeah yeah we can we can we can we are
full of empathy we will totally listen
to what's wrong yeah do you want to join
us do you want join you yeah we're full
of EMP I must go speak to the
children the children children I want
start speak to the children in the
gardens they have children do you know
where they are yeah take us to the
children they're at the gardens this is
this
way do you know do you know how to find
your way of course I do I of the Amber
coin I am Amber coins are all about
money they're not a boat yes I love
money you got some money I can't get
enough of the gold I love it so much
leeston child does not have any
money oh this is not the garden well as
I am part of
ambercoin give them my
money what the heck is this place anyway
is this your CH is this your
child where is that is Henry what
Henry what kind of name is Henry
Henry ah pitch doorman oh Pitch Dorman
oh I needed to find this oh pit Dorman
thank you you are you you've met pit
Dorman I'm so happy for
you oh this is Amber
coin
GH h a
bookie do you think they like books make
a bet not okay now you got it there now
to the gardens
do you want me to help
you speak to the Jade sword Guild
Master Jade sword Guild Master oh that's
what do Jade sword this a passenger a
messenger whatever
abuki
abuki pit
dor where the heck is the Guild
Master hello
wait why did I get disconnected from the
group call conversation oh welcome back
thank you why did I get
disconnected cuz cuz G had to go talk to
someone I had to speak to
someone yes one
onone to spread some empathy she seemed
to have fallen on hard times and it was
a private call oh I see yeah ah P who
are we talking about
hello oh where's pad Dorman hello am by
the door cuz he's a hello hi who who are
you talking about the one that required
empathy oh um I I spoke to Jonna Watson
a little bit and I saw her side of
things she seems like a pretty good
person a good fellow she you defected
you've defected
she misguided she just she told me that
she plan on that wi that she told me she
told me I heard her side of
story plan on killing the King she
promised she promised she promised she
wouldn't kill the king it was only had
to do with her backstory her childhood
for
history what what happened during her
time
stains killed her Village and they
stains killed her Village The Village
was sent yes the
entire the wandering Village was
sentient and the stains killed her
Village and all the villagers and uh
they left a note and it was a note from
the king so she thought the king had
done it the entire time and she it was
cleared up with the meeting with the
king I see see mhm she had a
one-onone yes we all had one-on ones
remember when you met eyes with him and
he proposed oh yes right okay now I
remember yes he had proposed to our
Queen our highness in here yes yes I
remember a clear as day it's almost like
it happened like an hour
ago he proposed to you an hour ago it's
almost as if I can recall you know like
I can recall so well that it's almost as
if he proposed to me an hour ago uh of
course our our Majesty our highness yes
our lady in waiting
yes I'm glad you are aware I am aware I
am fully aware well worry not Jonna
Watson does not plan on killing your
husband not my husband yet your husband
to be yes
your be
hello where is the Calamity the St it
has
Bor where did Iris
go I have no idea lost the
call lament what has befallen the lands
of King
Revelation claming on the
stains possible Le being shaken toly
find mysterious ancient ruin we're not
really shaken to find ourselves in
another world come to think of
it pray you will Aid us in our fight oh
L them your Aid go forth with Val for
you to regain your the pl speak to Hess
of the Jade
sword is this a call for adventure
mayhaps why are we speaking to
disgusting Jade sword when we should be
talking with her seruan
who is Valor and why do we have to go
with him
exactly W the
Coliseum you're in
another why does she keep leaving us
again she keeps leaving us no she she's
in the party she still not in the
call if you see on the right our party
still in it
okay you trolled
us refer refer to page four once again
yes wait where did she
go it seems the
party is a little
bugged should we just remake the party
cuz we have to at the blue the quest
board let us all me at the quest board
that sounds like a splendid idea if I
can find it oh hello hello are you going
to go on an
adventure yes mayhaps when we gather our
party members too oh do you do you think
that you maybe have some room for more
party members we oh we have four hello
hello I don't think there's a limit to
how many people can join our party they
shall we shall remake of five five yeah
five oh I see so they've already got
their full party party of four so you
two must fight each other to the death
in order to join our okay I'm going to
bed it's
time gone we have oh true this is true
it's nice meeting you today yeah it's
nice meeting you guys okay may our path
cross again good night luck oh thank
thank you we should we should this the
party you can join the call again by the
way I'm a nice person I I'm a great
fighter too I'm strong that's why I'm in
item yes yes yes yes would you be okay
with me joining your adventure yes we
would be okay you must come to the quest
board with us though because we must
remake our our our mind party okay yeah
it's just that I have a question yeah
which Guild are you in I hope it's not
ambercoin I'm I'm with Jade sword we are
strong courageous Fighters good good
Jade sword okay let what are the rumors
flying around about ambercoin oh
ambercoin oh we don't even let's not
start oh you don't like talking oh it's
it's whatever it's pish posh pish posh
yeah yeah we we'll find the board first
let's let's go let us go let us go let
us make haste
except sorry my my horse is very
slow psych it is this
way one of my
people some problems with my map you see
yeah yeah it's uh definitely this
way yeah yeah yeah yeah this is this is
the right way this is uh the the quest
Master this this is the way yes yes this
is this is the way we go this way M oh
did you find the lost Leeson child
ambercoin
uh amber coin I'm on leave me alone I'm
on the
phone see that's what I'm saying
actually sword member though I'm really
yeah that's she lied
oh wow she is Amber coin I don't want to
no it's just
a new people beautiful pink lady wa
beautiful um oh gosh these two are
exhibiting an aura that I've never quite
who are you what is your name
I'm I feel like your legs are calling to
me your thighs th are I don't know why
your thighs are calling to me I have a
on your thigh I don't know why I want to
sit on your
thigh back off now watch you're you're
Jade sword your is so sharp but you
know
likein you
li Amber coin you lied toia okay then
you're okay you li with your stupid
comic large sword you
lied your your weapons are idea told me
to say it is focused on dexterity unlike
yours that is focused on just all bronze
but no brains meanwhile I use a bit of
my
intelligence
to yes indeed leave your party whatever
party you may be in we better than that
I am oh sorry
you swine how dare you say my brain is
Tiny I know this place like the back of
my hand I am very smart how do you know
I've joined your party welcome to know
how do you know this place like the back
of your hand abandoning Elizabeth she
seems to have made
friends
what are not we are not friends we are
not to each other no no no going on
I was about about to hush a traitor she
is a traitor she is supposedly ambercoin
but not ambercoin she's Jade sword I
don't really
know oh my God what was that I just I
just contacted someone she is a harlot
too what what happened she is a
harlot what's a harlot you do not need
to know something wet
what wet I don't know it sounded a
little wet don't you
think wait well you know let's let's
let's let's forget about you know oh
recollection recollection Revelation I
forgot everything that happened your
sword UPG you must be
flustered where do I up wait is she Jade
sword or
amberin been why are you
back back
okay what will you do there or going to
make more money that's what they're
going to do oh I see oh yes I love money
for I am part of
ambercoin you liar you bloody liar you
bloody liar what does she lie
about what what Guild she's a part of if
you guys aren't ambercoin and you're not
Jade sword are you Cerulean cup no we're
we're the we're the best team in the
world you should join you should join
our our our call our call on the magic
radio oh right we have the magic call in
our radio yeah you're not in the magic R
you don't you don't need to you don't
need to possibly drawing what is the
magic radio this this this thing that's
in our hand right here and then you you
click on it right click on it and then
you ring ring with the diamond thingy or
I don't know if it's a diamond thingy
but the thing what is Diamond thingy oh
actually I don't know it looks like a
pile of dust to me where I'm trying to
I'm trying to recruit the pink the
Beautiful pink thighs to join our call
oh I in it yay let us
meet the castle Gates everyone oh the
castle Gates I understand yeah everyone
do the quest up on follow
me follow me up until the uh the ruins
the ruins yes no I'm still at the Smithy
Quest wait wait let me let me finish
that real quick okay definit is there
something we wanted to do after that I'm
assuming we speak to
well like you got to get to the quest
first cuz our quests are not synced so
oh okay okay wait wait wait wait sorry
let me let me do this real quick
uh uh could you bring us 10 Cobblestone
okay okay okay okay yeah yeah it's so
hard talking to these um these leeston
that you have to like you have to like
Crouch like crazy sticky keys the force
of the sticky keys comes on and makes it
very diff why is everyone
falling I think they turned off sticky
keys actually cly people maybe I'm the
only one that gets the sticky keys
prompt we were advised hav got sticky
keys in a long time but if you press
shift six times
though I have not been getting flowers
have advised to turn off those sticky
keys before how do I how do I give it to
them wait true I want to give it to them
help I am being swarmed at the castle
Gates there are so many many STS only
have eight hey how do you get
cobone how to get cobblestone follow
follow me follow me yes my queen what K
Mory is that your name they
hurt what what happened what is your
quest my quest is to exit the Town Gate
head to the Plains and speak to Hest of
the Jade SW okay we're on the same Quest
okay great Iris wait is your name Iris
your name is Iris yes my name is Iris
what yes follow me here this is the
castle gate special okay they're all
very special let us go we are full of
empathy mind you empathy is our middle
name oh my God this world is so large
what all of our middle names Cobblestone
is this
way see over there oh it's minecra I
mean it's excuse me what is Minecraft
yeah
Minecraft I I have no idea what I just
said what how do you craft the mines
yes well yeah bully that puppy bully
that puppy it's making puppy noises we
not bullying him we are freeing him of
his they're quite a different why are
you trying to kill the rabbit yeah it's
a dark one what's wrong with the dark
one I don't
know what the rabbits are fine The Blue
Team no no it's not about rabbit can we
can we can we make meat out of the cows
wait sorry instincts I want to get off
the there we go wait let me re one of
those reation Revelation ghost stories
Revelation the cow didn't die from the
Revelation wow this cow is strong wait
that is a strong cow that is a strong
cow
Revelation
Revelation oh my God I didn't mean to
kill those oh God why did I oh no they
didn't drop anything even drop any meat
I will help help
you
coins there we go hey the monsters Dro
coins they
do we are rich well you can become rich
I
suppose no we are not to be full of
greed that is not us we are full of
empathy yes that is up to the amberin
what empathy means anymore what does
empathy mean can someone give me a
definition of empathy compassion
compassion peace EMP empathy that's what
it means are you ceran cup yes we are
all Cerulean cup we are all Cerulean cup
yes nice to meet you this very ni what
what is Jade all about huh what is Jade
all about hey hey hey hey don't don't be
so
aggressive we are courageous fighters
who fight for what's right oh wow oh
okay you guys seem like the actual good
guys okay what do you mean actual good
guys we are good too the actual oh yeah
oh yeah you're right you're right we're
full of empathy and we force empathy on
people by killing them right no
no what kind of takeway is that taking
things into their own hands I
guess is that oh excuse me sorry my
horse is a is quite a um you know Rowdy
fella you see I I don't know how to
control it who are you talking what a
Rowdy horse I'm I'm talking to I'm
talking to a Amber coin member right now
and who is the Amber coin member this
ambercoin member is the same member that
adopted many children and um and is
money I wonder why
Liz she must love money cuz that's what
she says who is Liz you know the the for
breakfast does
taste you seem to dislike a lot of
people on my team she was very wow what
kind of money do you eat every single
for breakfast lunch and dinner is it
different every single time Iris Iris
where are you are you in the PLS right
now at the Smithy you're at the Smithy
I'll come save
you copper flakes oh yes I will return
what about silver when do you eat
silver hey hey hey stop talking with
that fake Amber
coin hey get out of here get don't
belong you don't own this place you
don't own this place hey cian cups are
here get out of here I was just I was
just asking her NRI was she's really not
bad don't don't talk to don't talk to
her she's like a fake
ambercoin oh she's I mean that's not a
good that's not I thought we hated Amber
coin yeah she's Jade sword
apparently she not is she actually not
Amber coin yeah she's actually not Amber
coin I am oh I actually thought she was
yeah I she was ambercoin too yeah wait
you you lied to me I thought you were I
thought you were ambercoin you kept
saying you loved money that was just
like a full on sign I've been lying to
you this whole time I am part of the
Scarlet wand how dare youare where did
your
teamm I don't eat money for breakfast I
wait where did your teammates
go I have to apologize I was also lying
on her behalf saying that she was a
member of Jade sword yes she is not
no she wants to keep her her identity
not even Jam
sword oh she's a compulsive liar oh I
also don't know where she is from the
first time I I I met the you were trying
to threaten me so I did not get get your
hey hey you don't talk to hey you don't
talk to my gu member like your do not
know how to ride if their horses they
always ride into me not your voice at
have you not seen what I did to your gu
M I'm going to rip up your to stick on
your knees and call you Tony I
swear you put your sword away you put
your sword where it belongs on the
ground there is PVP I can show you where
there's PV there is would you like to
follow me yes there is that's our Guild
the J I will take you to the J I will
take you to the Jade sword Guild
what at the G Jade sword Guild it's
right way so she is Jade sword so is she
Jade sword is she I don't know what's
going on she Jade sword I think she is
Jade sword I should just remember this
stuff welcome to the Jade sword Arena
guys are we are we going dungeon let's
go to the dungeon You're right let's go
to the dungeon you're right we should go
to the dungeon let's go to the
dungeon to the dungeon Arena whenever
it's waiting for you yeah let's go yay
courage is on the battlefield I need to
do my quest you guys can I need to do my
quest wait uh what was the next Quest I
need to go back to the quest Master Miss
ninoa where is hastus at the plains you
can check the map left shift oh is he
onwards I need to get off check the map
and I should show you the NPC you need
to go next I know we've got grave duty
but I
hope I do not see him on my see him he's
very far south oh you are here to get
your started yeah we just go straight
the shopkeeper I think it's just
straight where's the
shopkeeper the shopkeeper is right
across the the Smithy okay thank you
yeah I am here he has been expecting
me is it just straight across what the
oh no what is this Jade sword you can't
proceed yet shopkeeper shopkeeper
shopkeeper shopkeeper or South huh am I
just supposed to talk to the shop maybe
wait don't
across the plains I see
oh hello we must kill all of these ooh
gold do do not be so easily
distracted Jonathan G I'm sorry my my
empathy I must return to kill them all
you have to do is talk to me and I'll
you st like what do you want to buy
isn't that easy my empathy I must put
the stains down do you stop by if you
ever need anything okay hero you are
arrived break and do some okay you can
try visiting the Gill Halls of the four
Great guilds for instance each of them
has an activity
okay the great ruin do I have a lot of
quests I need to do which one are you at
I'm at the shopkeeper well these are all
side quests and they're all repeatable
so
like to go talk to the the kid Park open
the way got some time why not the Gard
the children are attending to them I'm
sure okay the children children
stains I see oh wow wait wait while we
wait for friends I'm going to go ahead
and pin my my jade sword out emblem to
my C where's the children where's the
children lead me to the CH where's the
children it's in the gardens the gardens
there's a child in the Gard is is it the
place with the Amber coin is it where um
Liz was trying to take us or is that a
different
place if you check your map you'll see a
red marker for the next NPC you need to
talk to want me to help you wait let me
see if I can figure this out why does it
say I don't have any side quests huh I
thought I
did did I like where should I pin it I'm
coming to find you where are you I'm in
front of the shopkeeper and I'm just
like okay I thought wait do I so I
talked him he was like oh find the
children but then like now I don't have
a quest and I'm just like where's the
children uh so like just follow me I I
think yeah so it should be I think it
should be around here maybe it was this
way yeah I think are these the children
uh there there's a child like in the
middle of the garden that's a jade sword
yeah there's a garden garden wait maybe
this isn't it oopsie I think it's the
opposite way child yeah it's the Leeson
child and it's in the middle of the Gard
one important child to be called the
Lees child I know right he the child of
the country anpad where did where did
crony
go I thought I was following you wait
very cool thank you this that a pin
where's the sharp part going into my
eyeball best child oh found it I found I
think I see the Leal child wait oh
really okay good I think it's it showed
up on my map now it wasn't there before
God okay good thank you I can't find
I will now make Jade sword a part of me
the bestl
child let me talk to you I just want to
say hi liestal child liestal child yes
the it's the best child ever is the Leal
child wa now I kind of want to know
where it
is oh wait oh yeah it was here the best
of child it looks like any other kid
what makes this one so the
ruins there we go found strange voice
but we know not what to make of it okay
let's see and then go SS of stains open
the
way okay then now I looks like our team
members already figured out the the
riddle there's a
riddle yeah it says oh slay 10 stains
and then we have you want to do some
building or gardening got it leave it to
me I'm
ready cannot proceed yet oh yeah you'll
we'll see about
that I've been slaying stains this whole
time dang it
speak to the best child okay speak to
the pit Dorman okay now I'm at the pit
Dorman okay pit D okay you found the pit
Dorman where was the pit Dorman again
was like in it was in the yellow area
right no it was in the green wait was it
yellow what the heck is
this I remember crony saying she wanted
to see the pit dormant 20 minutes ago so
yeah and I found I can't climb I mean I
mean Tam Tam Tam oh oh okay wait what is
your name
Tam Tam Tam your name is Tam yes oh
where'd that come from oh I me Jonathan
Jonathan Nam me Tam Tam Gander stand for
the Azure Maiden Tam for short I see now
hold on makes so much sense what yes yes
yes I'm so soaking in all this
information maybe I didn't use it right
oh oh no not the map she's not taking a
map I know you could make us room that's
strange that's
me you we have been in the same party
for tens of minutes and you do not know
Ral your name isn't that a bit
a I was told that the
faker are you talking about Liz
yes and you li us her affiliations why
did she yell at me then why would she
lie then but she said doesn't want
anyone we can gamble here apparently
she's in the arena but I can't find her
her The Guild Master wishes to speak
with you please meet him at the where
did she go confused to the p d speak to
the Jade sword Guild Master Okay Jade
sword Guild Master what are you doing
all by yourself maybe after our Quest
hello hello well I'm not all by myself
you're here None Shall
breach don't try to be
so I got I got to drop out of this
excuse me excuse excuse me
excuse
me what is your quest right
now thank you
um who's uh I got to exit the Town Gate
and head to the Plains and speak to um
hastus of the Jade sword good do you
know how to get
[Music]
there do you know how to get there I do
know you know what why don't you show me
you know what
I have fine fine it seems that the throw
youres in my face fake ambercoin needs
my assistance so I guess I have no
choice you follow
me summon your horse there we go at
least you know how to do that at the
very least that's very good for you
anyway let's go chop
chop uhuh let's see okay it's a
I'm just kidding it's this
way okay it's that
way okay and then uh not this way this
way it's this way see see I know where
I'm
going
okay and then we go this
way ah yes very good yes you're welcome
what would you do without me even though
we your
enemies all right now follow me down
this
path down this path come
along
so
no
hey yes and then you keep going down
this path and you'll be able to find a
hus hus this way
ow there we go hus oh very good thank
you yes of course I have to drop this
call to give her a piece of my mind oh
there she
is you what do you mean the loud one you
disgust me yeah what was I
thinking cut her some slack cut her some
slack only I can give
her yeah yeah no I've been bullying her
enough I feel kind of bad she's all by
herself she is she is she good I I have
my guild mates in my heart I know she's
in my heart me let let's all be nice to
her you okay she's she's kind of alone
on it she's in my I love all kind of
friends so yeah of course I'm on it hey
red red thing I am Elizabeth oh
Elizabeth red red thing I'm talking do
you not see me talking to no I didn't
hear you talking red thing can you
apologize to
Jonathan with a G Jonathan Jonathan with
a G she's she's very hurt open you
called her name her war
cry underworld we shall secure the
surroundings undb what am I suppos to
apologize say sorry I I apologize that
you are
sad investigate
theor apologize that you were a lesser
being here have some of my melons please
we all share the same goal where I don't
know I'm trying to it to you supposed to
protect the
land I should leave some stuff here it
seems I cannot give you my melons oh no
it's just what are we talking about the
Harlot is talking about melons now
Mak
me I
tried these melons are sted to my hand
what oh never mind I can't of her melons
I apologize for not giving you my melons
can I have your melons too she lies she
lies I cannot give it to the she just
how can you try and and fail at giving
melons I I I am using the uh the mus mus
Q muscle is not working oh my
God okay I'm just going to pretend I
didn't hear that and just go Slay
Slay I'm going to
slay hey hey who wants to slay with no
way to enter the ruins we are to gu
everyone can use it some have reported
hearing a
strange key oh good you have to slay 10
stains too exit the Town Gate head to
the Plains and speak to okay okay slay
10 SLS then speak to H okay okay I think
I'm almost at the the dungeon Quest
probably you just need to kill 10 10 of
them yeah to kill T of them okay okay
there are more like out in the PLS I
will slay them I will take this corner
Barrel from
me okay I'm going to go slay
ow my horse is a little special in the
head okay let's see I think there were
more lot more around here in the
beginning
spot or not never mind uh they do not
spawn around
here okay it's uh it's
right here nope that's the wrong spot uh
where am I going
again um
H uh oh oh there it is
okay well I have no doubt she could
clear the dungeon by herself okay okay
okay is my skill AOE
Revelation Revelation I can't tell how
far it goes oh my God it barely does you
killed my
prey well I mean I Revelation it what
are you talking about I didn't kill it I
revelation
it
reation I'm
dying okay where is uh where are I
forgive you dearest what is your name
red
thing Elizabeth I am Jonathan with a
G yeah oh ow it's actually Jonathan G we
have we have a Jonathan in our gu too
but I do not know it is with a G oh
that's a Jonathan wa does that mean you
are gathan Jonathan no no no pronounced
Jonathan I think there is it's in the
other
shop okay good prop portional
regeneration yay I killed 10 of
them yes they one step closer to
Extinction to accept oh I don't think so
fashion surprise
box just be that way I'm build that way
now what do I do maybe I can trade my
melon to the where's the dude okay
through the power of my empathy I
forgive you I know it must have been
very rough to have fallen in hard
times oh did you guys make up I'm I've
made up with her okay that's good yes I
got the key I got the underworld key
thing I don't forgive you okay do yeah
show we I'm working through it yeah want
to
see I can go to the D
any does everyone have the
I mean not map does everyone have their
key yeah I think Ena already entered
though didn't she can we go give me a
seconding last minute but I'll be right
there okay water key up
here he has this key the dungeon anyway
I can hear you guys now oh my gosh you
guys can hear me sorry about that oh
this way it's there at the end yeah I
got the key um already enter no I'm back
at the town just chopping how do we know
how many we have slam I see it you have
show up and then you go all the way to
the
end what if you think wooden swords is
enough what if we made two parties of
three you think that would be good H
should we do should buy stuff should we
buy
upgrades well we don't really have iron
you know what let's Let Me Mine a bit I
see gold right here maybe they want to
stay with their
group that's mine no what you talking
about what do you mean that's mine
actually that's mine actually done I was
almost done no no that's mine actually
no get out of my
way I was almost done I was almost done
that's what you did to me you will never
you will never successfully dig that one
out no no you will never no no no no I I
will not allow you no no no no you're
never don't need to be like it appears
there are people in a cut scene in front
of us or they're seeing visions in their
head and they are reacting to it they
must be crazy then they must be crazy
then wait I I think
they uh clear the dungeon okay do two
other people want to enter the dungeon
together maybe let's enter the dungeon
enter the dungeon if five of us go then
one person will probably be left behind
really only four can go only
five yeah we have five yeah but I feel
like we should also what about Liz she
in party a we can go into teams of three
we can s yeah we can split yeah I think
that would be the best way everyone meet
inside are we really going to go are we
going to go in with um with wooden
swords I I think I should probably
upgrade stone sword can I can can you
possibly be kind so oh so kind to um
throw me a stone
sword gathan beloved gathan I will have
to return to town to get you a stone
sword let me make haste let me come with
I think we have to split the party
before going into the dungeon how do we
get there's a area in there that we must
make ready checks I think we are allowed
to oh split the party before we do our
ready checks okay go if you say so away
who there they
go are repeatable I think yeah
oh
okay so I am here Fair Maiden
Iris oh
gathan my lovely handsome gathan you and
your comically large sword maybe after
we clear it the first time not comically
large it is uh
pronoun pronounce many words no that's
comically large please except this TR
this normal sword looks like that's not
even a normal sword yes this is a normal
sword stone sword you may have some raw
beef thank you I will eat it in front of
you to show how appreciative I am yes
please eat the raw eat it
raw slay Liz St would you like to enter
the dungeon with another one of us we're
going to split the team into three
groups or two groups I think of two
groups of three no do not don't split it
do to me it's okay oh you don't want to
enter the dungeon
together I mean
I would be fun if you
want why are you such a loner or you
guys are you guys are Guild
mes oh no one Minds yeah they they agree
that we should do that so it would be
best that way don't be such a loner
freakishly large sword woman yeah no
need to be a loner not alone I'm doing
my quest
Yeah by
yourself I a got to Rel was
behind oh what
oh are you done with your quest now no
are you done
now no are you done about
now we do we have to do this quest to be
able to do the next bit yes yeah or can
we just go into the kill 10 if you kill
10 wa we can go to the next thing yeah
Elizabeth do you not have a normal sword
myal I do it seems my my my my
freakishly large one is is wonder what I
can do with the stone freakishly weak
yes you only use that for an ultimate
attack I see
oh
Revelation oh
boy I finished my quest I'm just doing
it for fun now I love killing
what I love killing things what killing
things sound right I'm a grim Raper not
you guys I wouldn't hurt you wait you're
a grim reaper how do you know that
that's what I did before is what
everybody told me wait really who told
you oh the col people there are these
bone skeletons that float around in my
[Music]
head so
she I think she needs to kill a few
more stain what is a people by the way
Liz it won't tell you you just got to
you just got to know how
[Music]
many there's one over here I'm going to
go dig for some more stuff
while I'll follow I'll go farm
some hey hey pink
thing pink
thing hey what are you doing what are
you doing here huh hey pink hoarder pink
hoarder you hoarder yes what do you mean
hoarder you hoarded my gold what do you
mean hoarded your gold what does that
even
mean I'm speaking to one lady that is
not in our group call for some reason
even though she is why do I keep getting
disconnected they do thing man she she
really likes hanging up on us so you
know I don't know why it get
automatically maybe it's the person who
creates the phone call hangs up and it
hangs up for everyone
perhap I have to test it what this what
my fellow
friends why can I not
proceed
oh yeah so it does get oh so it does
drop it does drop I see I see I
see oh oh I didn't mean to oh I can't
swim wait how do I swim oh there we go
oh there's diamond in here oh what
okay wait okay so uh if you fail to
receive they will be sent here do I have
a storage
system can I like okay let me experiment
can I put okay never mind I can't darn I
thought I was being smart wait it
dropped again the call
dropped
hello sorry here's the party I did not
mean to hang up the phone call why do
you keep hanging up my connection I was
entering a tunnel H the tunnel seems
that the magical connection between our
brains causes to drop the call you mean
this is all this talking is telepathic
yeah I'm falling directly into your head
word oh
wow Sasa magical world well how do I
throw thing oh waist bin okay
yeah recycle lady recycle you may be a
queen but you should recycle copine what
what excuse me I don't think I've ever
been called something so foul hello
cine no maybe I have but that's
definitely very
yucky the Smithy won't let me make more
St have an autograph I don't know what
she talk what a pleasure to see
everyone oh hey we are
incoming what with many people okay
awaiting you I
[Music]
seen yes yes friends are here oh really
what really what
promise okay I trust you as as a member
of the Cerulean cup I trust
easily wait don't do
that I can't why am I a cow
there's a wall okay there's a l i are
you
sure are you sure think she needs to
join the party can she join the party I
can't jump it's not allowing me
to wait how do I throw this away ow what
to her what's under here we'll split
into into groups of three in a minute
we're going to split into two yeah party
is different than the call oh okay I see
okay
also no caps please oh please do not B
have is everyone inside the dungeon my
tamies um oh okay are we going in the
dungeon first and then we split yeah no
we yeah go inside past the bridge and
then we can split our party yeah okay
okay the bridge so around here this area
where we're waiting in front of the
dungeon farewell I passed by something
farewell maidens yes talk talk Tanashi
Ki kiari
K Tanashi this
Tanashi Tanashi
kiari Tanashi Kar goodbye Tanashi
Kiara is it kiar or Kar I don't know
what they're talking about they're
making me really uncomfortable maybe
it Kia sounds familiar can you please
leave me
alone where's everyone
I am right in front of this the Ed at
the edge of the bridge group
[Music]
chat they with my friends please explain
the vision I don't know what you're
talking about please leave me
alone no I don't know what you're
talking about I just want to I just want
to go
question big up I I have I I have
questions maybe I should get out of here
hey what are you guys doing to my
honorary seruan cup guild member hold
on all
right guess that's it for today that's
right I'm in the toilet so away
what no no no just just come come um
that's not the dungeon yet you it's the
are you also P the co
to I
am what is doing in a toilet hey like I
said group chat assemble stop hanging
around in the toilet wherever you are
I'm not in the
toilet how what what what what are you
letting out that you're taking so long
in the toilet just wait where are you
hurry up and hurry up we're we're we're
in front of the dungeon I'm in front of
the dungeon what do you mean you're not
in front of a
dungeon You're the only one that's not
here what AR we aren't we at the
canyon no click the thing to go in after
you get the key oh
okay henceforth okay Enter the dungeon
we must enter the dungeon okay God and
enter the dungeon yeah we got to split
up I don't know Liz knows that we're
here does Liz
know okay okay and then let
me Liz I don't know if she can read let
us go to the dungeon towards the dungeon
if we're in a private call can she not
hear us I let us go in Dungeon no she
can hear us if we are in a radio call
okay yes yes all right let us I am going
to go to page four of my magical to okay
we can make a new room group y disband
this
party yes party
disbanded I'll make a new one then
um who would like claim your three two
claim your two my two claim your two two
my my two two claim your who wants to
join teop claim your two yeah okay yeah
are you guys yeah oh my gosh they're
very frightening but I'll invite them
what do you mean
frightening I inv let me grab Miss
ninoa okay it let me grab Liz who I have
forgiven I mean aren't you also the
aren't you also perhaps like something
that might be connected to this dungeon
we have a cheat code yeah huh I mean I
do get a familiar feeling it's a
competition
now party invite Miss Liz wait we should
probably drop out of the radio then
quick I suppose so a new radio call then
yeah oh okay okay is everyone ready
standing by to enter the dungeon oh
there we go stand by we're going to do
amazing I have we're going to finish
faster than the other teams yeah yeah we
will enter the dungeon no players
standing by you got to stand we got to
ready up do we have to ready first yes
okay all right you're party
enter we're ready yo we made it yay it's
was there something we needed was there
something we needed to kind of like I
don't know play play play we enter the I
don't think so don't worry okay oh okay
the end of world a domain of boundless
oppressive Darkness as feared as it is
unavoidable it holds a final resting
place for every creature that walks the
Earth yet even in this realm of the den
there are those who live and call it
home skipped everything it's okay ready
for you you know that feels very
familiar to me I think you're supposed
to
death that's such a that's such a scary
concept death death also yeah also the
other let me explain to the kai people
the other two are are gone because uh
they're in a different instance we split
they facing in a different dimension
yeah we split oh my God
this oh no no no please hang on you are
bad at should we build a bridge shut
up excuse me I
think a little slip oh there we go there
we go good good good nice nice okay
there seems to be a light over there so
let's go okay that light seems promising
I'll go towards it too um oh wow that's
a b should we make a bridge uh can we
make a bridge it might be the safest
beted to make a
bridge I try jumping they oh yeah it
doesn't no yeah it won't let no placing
blocks huh well then we'll have to be
careful how about maybe over that no
that's where we came from pretty let's
go that
way okay lead the way hopeful let's go
that way and then we go this way and
then she seems to know where she's going
I totally know where oh yeah there's
another yellow thing over
there
yeah
is where are you where are you over here
yeah it's like a some kind of like
Obelisk whatever where where's where I
mean where's Tam oh there we go Tam yeah
that's me Tam Gander oron above head
Gander who's oror
cron okay if you say so I'm a little
confused new checkpoint checkpoint nice
so perhaps if we die if we have't a
perish we'll respond here oh that's
comforting why do you keep saying
promising oh I think we need go over
there that ominous looking Church o I
think that's a castle that's not a
that's a castle I'm sorry in the sky
yeah Okay jump jump jump oh so that's
why so many people were
[Music]
dying oh yeah the mystery is solved we
can all jump we we will not die even
once we are we are better than that
exactly we are what do they call it
Gamers yes we are are totally Gamers uh
person who plays games well yeah games
yeah try not to bring the team down oh
you you're a
gamer new checkpoint heck yeah
checkpointed through it huh I know right
I know right and then we go this way and
then we go this way okay settle down buo
who she's really quick we need know this
place better than me and I feel like
this used to be my home or something
yeah settle down bu oh boy oh she
definitely doesn't know where she's
going no I just it was just a slip of a
slip of a hand I'll be right back I'll
be right slip of a foot more like yeah
that's
true she'll be able to make it back I'm
sure no no I'm right behind you I'm
right behind you are you sure a speedy
teammate would definitely be right back
right Che
maybe right behind
who that looks really
familiar okay it's not this way it's a
not this
way I get the
check man she is not gaming I don't need
it because I'm very used to this I am so
gaming I don't even know what gam what
does gaming even mean that sounds like a
that sounds like a word that's only for
people who who actually games yeah yeah
it's a term that only I know well you
guys don't play games just in your free
time no no it seems like she doesn't
know what gaming means no but I'm just
curious thought everybody has Hobbies
right A lot of people game you know what
your hobbies are you remember what your
hobbies
are yeah they say jumping and apparently
foring I think when I was a oh who told
you you're a Reaper you're you you must
be you're
goddess not not a Reaper you're a
goddess she's a goddess sad makes me
embarrassed say that but why do you
think that she's a goddess how could she
be a Reaper no I I made it to the castle
screams goddess to you I don't know I'm
going to die which is ironic it's okay I
died twice already in wors I never died
cuz I'm the queen well that doesn't
matter that that won't matter you'll die
soon enough no wory take the throne no
no no like the The King and I oh man I
can't believe I have to explain the
story every single time but the King and
I we lock no no well like this lock no
what no we didn't go that far what are
you saying all right I mean hey live
your life no I I don't no wait not like
that it's supposed to be like a
political thing okay oh a a marriage
arrangement of convenience a political
marriage where I gained the throne
because I mean look at the king it's
easy
oh he's pretty old I guess but I I I
could definitely puppet him behind the
scenes man man look at this lady talk oh
we're in the dungeon oh we're in the
dungeon okay this is
oh get in here it's dark it's time to
fight okay I'm ready to fight come our
way
oh my God is that a demon oh yeah it was
too fast Revelation demons everywhere
get them yeah your Revelation is bad
wait wait wait quit my
sword let me get Revelation crits crits
exist
crits okay I think we got to I think we
got to keep I think they keep spawning
so we just got to push through them
maybe yeah do we have levels in this in
this world well I'm level 15 but I'm
level 12 an
item they have triangles they have like
they have rice balls what are these
things no no no they have shapes they
have shapes they have like a like a star
shape and a triangle oh my God they hurt
yeah they do hurt quite a bit they hurt
quite a lot oh my god
oh ow oh my god oh my god wow this is
really tough oh my God it really hurts
ouchie quite a maze isn't it it it it's
amazing shut up it also feels like home
a recollection oh my God they don't die
it's not recollection it's Revelation
it's
reation whoa that area is way too dark
wow wait where are you
guys oh wait I found something oh oh hey
I found a door is it a door a door yeah
I'll watch your back where's the door
okay there's a triangle
key how do I you know some of the
zombies are actually holding these
things Oh yay you must have picked one
up hey there you are you found us y we
unlocked the door y nice yeah let's go I
totally did something I'm sure I did you
found the way o can we ride the oh we
can't ride the horse here okay no horse
in around
been here before ooh so you must be a
goddess yeah if this is if this reminds
you of your home then you must live
in a castle Yeah W look at those
chandeliers oh I want to swing on
him whoa she wants to swing from the
chandelier chandelier
chandelier where did that song come from
I I don't know what I'm sure we heard it
somewhere what do you think this thing
does is this a puzzle I think this is a
puzzle it looks like maybe it's a movie
screen maybe we just jump into it oh no
never mind do you usually jump into
movie screens oh we we're looking at
different things oh it is a puzzle oh
okay wait it's like it's like one of
those things where you like eventually
make everyone everything light up right
by just clicking on it like randomly um
hey I got this side uhoh
but all the the other sides affect each
other oh really okay maybe one maybe one
person should do it then a Boop a Boop a
I don't know I feel like I'm not smart
enough for this kind of thing a Boop a
Boop you're doing good you're doing good
yep y yep yep yep a boop boop boop boop
boop Yep this is hard a Boop a a Bo a Bo
are you why don't you do something
rather than just
usually for these for these puzzles um
only one person should do it cuz
otherwise you're just pressing random
buttons SC each other you do another
side a Boop you don't you boop another
side you know there's both sides to this
right yeah yeah yeah why don't you go
poop another side and do it faster than
me if you're you know I mean I I want to
but you keep messing it up buddy really
is it changing the other side too
yeah
yeah that's okay common mistake don't
even worry about it yeah don't worry
about thought it was one I thought each
side had its own puzzle I didn't you're
cute so it's for yeah it's it's
okay I'm bashful oh no I'm embarrassed
now why did I say that to say beautiful
pink lady likes me she doesn't like you
what she doesn't like you she she she
does it not like that love her not like
that well hurry up and hurry up and
solve the puzzle then hey
man tried to take my time
here this is I will mingle with Pink
Ladies so hurry up me yes oh hi you know
you're pink too okay I didn't know that
I'm solving all this puzzle by myself
hot I'm hot
pink yeah I guess you are really hello
guys yeah yeah I'm hot pink oh oh my God
not just pink oh what's wrong what's
wrong I thought you were going to solve
this I I
am oh she's Violet I don't know it's
it's like a I think yeah like a hot pink
Violet is color it's very beautiful it's
a pomegranate oh thank you a pomegranate
what is that that sounds delicious it's
a really Juicy Fruit oh wow you remember
your fruits I'm so proud of you oh yeah
I mean I remember basic things just not
my history hey guys you know like the
bonding time is great and all but you
really want us to help you with this you
really like you know I mean you know
cron are you sure I think we're just
going to ruin it for you really I think
you're close I think you're really close
so
wait
wait we're really close we are move them
over you figured something out probably
I'm going to ruin it aren't I no no
you're not going to ruin it
you feel like you need to switch it
back hey all right now we're on to
something I got this whole part here
dark okay this this part is filled out
no
psych oh one part is filled out wait how
do do you I I can't see the pattern
honestly okay like that you can't ruin
something that isn't even close to solve
say this says the C people that's true
okay that's good wait wait hold on hold
on hold on hold on hold on hold on it's
getting it's getting
there
okay I think that the way we need to end
it is yeah just one unlit one in the in
the
corner oh
man
huh oh whoops
[Music]
I can't go much higher than
that maybe work both sides to one side
just keep wrapping it around maybe if
you go from one side wrap all the way
around and solve it that way oh no the
one side that was full is no no look no
longer full I wonder if it was my fault
for touching the
cube forbidden Cube forbidden
cute actually can I can I try it again
you guys can can you can you guys kill
time while I try to do this time oh are
you saying are you saying we weren't
helpful no no no no no no it's just that
like you know like uh I I like I like no
no no no like I like solving puzzles no
no I like solving puzzles this you know
like I don't know if you guys like
solving puzzles so you know wait I think
I'm starting to figure it out wait oh
really
okay never
mind that was weird let me know if you
want help I feel like I might ruin it
though no you're not ruining it like
she's she's seeing the way yeah yeah no
she is over watching over us
overwatching us what oh
yeah okay what if we just stay on the
same side and work together on it and
slow name that's
crazy oh
wait yeah if you think it's wrong you
can always switch it back yeah
thankfully that part is
good that's what I'm
trying I think I'm started I think I'm
cooking guys oh yeah oh okay
okay oh no
sorry I'm hearing news that the other
team used to quote unquote bug It Out by
spamming lights oh my God they bugged it
out yeah I think we should maybe avoid
doing that though I'm getting I'm I'm
cooking I'm
cooking
nice I'm cooking just toggles a plus
shape is what yeah it's a plus
shape yeah oh I'm
cooking yeah she's doing it she's doing
it
yeah Iris the
genius genius I was I was doubting I was
doubting whether I was a genius or not
but now I remember I am a genius
remember you must have been really smart
in your past life I know yeah I must
have been absolute like like I must have
won the Noble Prize whatever that is
what's a Noble Prize I don't know but it
must be something special if I remember
do you wi if you're
noble yeah so I must get it soon too I
mean I think you need to be you need to
be smart and Noble and I don't know if
you have both well you only have one of
those at the moment what what you're
saying I'm not
Noble H oh wait no you are noble
oh you're
wait
the hey this way this way this
way there this Hot Topic in there wait I
don't know what Hot Topic is oh
wow that's so
cool Hello
Father maybe not my dad
but I want to be friends with him
oh know why do that what's what's wrong
with your dad why you do that not my dad
I dad a little
angry I just had a weird Instinct that's
all oh boyu here oh no we're waiting I'm
waiting for I may have died oh oh oh
hello hey uh huh this is the checkpoint
from before
Oh Oh wa what is this place it's a
mushroom we fell down do we eat it
want to eat the mushroom strange
mushroom that you
see oit Bone Heads can I eat it no I
can't pick up the bone I cut it no oh he
he
revives yeah that is one very very
persistent skirlington am I supposed to
feed the mushroom him or
something I
wonder ah hey
hey back off boneman oh good your place
the heck oh you're supposed to kill him
okay okay okay
wait oh you're supposed to kill him here
yeah his bone meal will drop and make
the tree grow yeah it all makes sense
yeah yeah it's growing the tree this way
this way you
fiend he is only father yeah for our big
tree yay Y is it done now
so tall are we supposed to climb it all
the way up maybe I think we should let
it grow a little more I think we need
yeah we probably need to grow a little
bit more spr you killed it in a weird
spot I'm sorry my
health come here come here
hi up here up here come here up here up
here come here come here there we go oh
I think that's it I think that's it I
think we can climb it now I'm can you
make that jump do you think no no we can
climb the vines
oh the vines ow I'm bad at climbing
vines how does one do that do you hold
space hold SP you jump I'm going to die
I'm going to die hold on a sec I'm going
kill this
guy don't spam what's what what someone
something okay now heal go go up the
vine first so much for a noble Warrior
all right up I
climb there we go okay here and then
here oh
this is interesting I've never had to do
something like this before yeah first
time for
ah less underworld and tree climbing
first time for a first time for a
underworld I was never one for climbing
trees I don't
think this is not very
familiar he
nice we can make it work oh oh
I wonder did we go here maybe and then
up here and
then tree is hard to climb I know right
I know where to go to next I'm having a
hard time yeah figuring out oh maybe
here did you find the way oh yeah I
think I found a way too here here this
way there are two mushrooms we got to
kill the skeletons really we still got
to kill skeletons here wait wait here
here Cy Cy come here here after climb
the tree don't worry don't don't climb
it all the way to the top oh yeah there
there are two mushrooms here
oh there's not much of a climber you see
you see where I am I'm so bad at jumping
this way uh let's see one moment let me
see where you
are hang on
maybe I should work on the quests while
you guys are this is why the Minecraft
like mcraft I mean you know I have no
idea sorry I don't know what I'm talking
about I must be
crazy I did it I did it um let's see
where cron is I'm
attacking okay oh I see
you they're ahead of me before I Know It
wait wee yay wow you're so quick what a
a gamer thank you what's that about you
not being a
gamer oh I am quite a bit of a gamer Oh
wrong okay work I think I think royalty
should not be playing games true we
should be taking care of you your no no
there's a royalty that plays games no
you shouldn't have time you should you
should be spending all your time making
the citizens lives easier that's what
your job is right as royalty well like
I'm not royalty yet but I will be soon
well so that means you're only playing
games while you're still not royalty
once you become royalty you'll be you'll
be um a slave to all of the citizens
you'll be a slave to the citizens
yes that's that's a very negative way to
look at
it well there's some truth I don't think
you're ready for for becoming a slave to
the citizens a slave excuse me I think
we can climb this now or do we have to
connect the trees like why else are
there too connect the trees yeah they're
still they're still spawning okay come
here come here come here okay come here
probably continue to spawn regardless
though even if the tree isn't complete
do you don't you think maybe but like
why are there two trees yeah I'm curious
about that hey hey hey don't follow me
come here come here come here come here
back way back up back up back up back
up okay I think we can climb it now
maybe is it climbable I don't know I
think we still need a do one
more oh
boy oh
dear can you can you can you kill that
thing this way this way can you kill can
you kill can you kill can you kill the
skeleton kill can I kill oh I can kill K
yes don't spam though okay thank you
okay one more hit one more hit one more
hit probably there go nice good job yay
nice nice nice oh there's there's
there's
Vines cool I'm going to climb the right
side
cuz why not yeah uhoh maybe I'll climb
these this seems right this goes quite a
ways
up oh maybe this isn't the
way
hey this is the way be right probably
this way probably this way lot a
platform then go this
way maybe that's how I got so good at
jumping oh you like platform too I like
platforming she might be a jump King
what what could that ever mean that's
what everyone was saying to me a jump
King but now I think I do oh my God I
almost died if being in
the me too if being in the Underworld
requires this much
jumping perhaps that is why oh I'm
looking up your okay where you're
looking up at what K nothing at your cap
it's very beautiful thank you what are
you guys looking up she's looking
she was she's you know her life is
looking up that's what that's what's
looking up I see yeah oh God I'm so
embarrassed
wait and then okay okay okay and then
fall oh what are you talking about I'm
here already oh okay oh you you know you
you think I was going to fall while I'm
here first oh whoops I was an
overachiever I uh climbed way too high
well you know I mean you did say you
were a gamer but you become you're going
to become royalty so you don't need
those gamer skills anyways you're going
to be a slave to the citizens okay okay
thanks that's the word on the street
what does that mean to the denisons of
the Underworld the light emanated by
Souls was vital they needed it to
survive in this ever cold and dark
environment yet among them there was a
heretic who called their Customs into
question do we really need to take
others lives to sustain our own no there
has to be another way and so she
yeah I know right into the plane
above what a dummy why would you leave
all these people down here to suffer and
die I know that's so silly what a
heretic think it's this way okay I'd
never do something like that personally
if you ask me I know I believe ow
yeah oh shiny it the power of Revelation
is grown stronger yay level up baby did
we get the treasure of this place and
now we sneak again guys we love
sneaking a portion of your memories you
recovered a portion of your memories
nice a memory what kind of memory sneak
am I going to remember how to spell
things now oh hopefully cck here to
watch video
oh oh
what click here to watch video video is
it are you sure you want to open the
following
website this is where we
um can we watch it will it will it
automatically play or do we have to play
oh you have to open chat press t
Okay shall we take a
look yes wait is this is this okay to
show on Screen Pro probably right or
should we
just cuz I security
wait wait let me double check don't do
it it steals your security your social
security number there's a download
available so we can we can play it
ourselves oh I think it is okay to play
it yeah we can yeah we can play it but
the only thing is I
think all right I think I'm just going
to use the one
that I show you guys a portion of my
memories I will show yes we will share
the portion of the memories that has
unlocked yeah all right let me let me
just uh should we should we
mute yes
sure silence myself how do we mute again
uh press
V and then
mute V mute
okay okay there we go and then let's uh
let's see what this is about
guys all right
uh and then do this oh wait no don't
play yet
[Music]
and okay
yep okay let's
see recollection Mory
[Music]
kopy a Reaper's job is to end people's
lives and take their your
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their
sustenance but I keep
wondering
basetable is this the right thing to
do no it's
[Music]
not what's going
on
party look at
that turns out we can also use people's
emotions huh we don't need their Souls
at all
huh Reaper should help the living was
that part of the
video don't take away their future if
the others can't accept that that
doesn't seem good that's their loss
huh I better leave before the others
come back to their sense things they're
seeing the same vision that I saw
I got to
go that that is not I was the
heretic It's All Coming Back to Me Now
that's why I got mobbed I got to go I
got to
run did they all see the same memory as
me wait what if they saw their own
memories
though we were in the
under I got to go I have I have watched
I have watched a p tickle peak of your
memory um Kia borei me are you sure that
was me though yeah you were doing very
evil things but it's okay you seemed to
have learned that it was evil and
decided to do good now so All Is
Forgiven wait so you don't care that I
betrayed all my underw fellow underworld
Ians no you did it for the for the good
for the good cuz I mean look at your dad
dropped us all down down a hole you know
that's that's not good Parenthood you
know sorry I'm sorry
yeah yeah I'm not sorry I'm not sorry
then H yeah do do you guys forgive me of
of course of course you were we we we
went through this dungeon together we
are Nama whatever that word means nakama
friends nakama nakama are you sure
Hakuna Matata Hakuna Matata Matata
Hakuna Matata
what does that mean how we know that
Matata Hakuna means Matata family was
that family Matata Hakuna means
Matas that is not an explanation matatas
oh well I guess it's okay then everybody
seems to be in good spirits so we have
done an amazing job yay I'm in the clear
well if that was my past it is what it
is it is what it is it's all in the past
GL I ended up being an okay person the
past don't matter all that matters is
the present and the future exactly I
feel like underworld definitely don't
like me though hello beautiful who are
you beautiful Raven lady oh you have
such a long spear wow a spear for
noticing such a beautiful spear oh I
just realized guys my My Little My star
thingies are shiny do you can you see
the shine no are they oh they're kind of
sparkly yeah
sparkly too ooh Why pretty is it cuz we
went through a dungeon I think so maybe
wait I mean I don't I don't see any
other reason Cy yeah pull out pull out
your weapon my oh oh yeah yours
sparkling too I can't see it cuz I
haven't done the dungeon yet you want to
do the dungeon I can uh we're going to
me me and beu and and those two
mysterious looking dogs are going to do
it in about 30 minutes together oh
fun that sounds like a fun time whatever
you see in there though you know take it
with a grain of salt is what I'm saying
oh okay let's just say it's a lot of
jumping yeah there's a lot of jumping
and also it's apparently my home oh so I
hope that you guys enjoy your time there
I guess I I'm sure we will it was a
really nice scenery Place yeah I'll take
care of the dogs too
they are also of the Jade sword so I
have a lot of respect for them
yes wonder if that means you ladies
Revelation Revelation whoa can you do a
beam yeah I'm a beam Blas I'm stronger
than Goku whoever Goku is what's Goku is
I don't know go oh I'm going to
experiment on this chicken
Revelation oh did it really deserve that
I saw stuff going on behind your head
when you did Revelation what was that I
don't know I think you your head just
exploded when you did a revelation oh
dang
okay brain do you use brain cells every
single time you re you revelate no no
reation it's just my mind is blown every
single Revelation looks kind of cool
wait why I I missed ity Callie's
Revelation looked kind of cool not going
to lie I miss just need to warm back up
but yeah my Scythe of death and
destruction I will use it as a sword for
peace I'm waiting for my Revelation to
wait
oo hey why don't you revelate again
please revelate for me what no I mean
why why is it all in caps ah what if she
wants to hurt me you guys are a lot
Kinder I
think it's okay so that that one's
really aggressive I feel though the
orange
the good game one she's really
aggressive no no no Jonathan is part of
the Cerulean cup and we are all very
full of empathy so it's okay yeah that's
why we're in the celan cup cuz we're
full of empathy and kindness and we
think about peace of the world exactly
good job guys hey we saw your memories
yeah Revelation embarrassing you
remember how interesting I do but did
you guys just clear or did you guys did
something else after it's a little
embarrassing nobody see myor we quit and
we were just like waiting and we just
having you know just having fun in that
we take that long we were did we take
that long yeah you did oh yes we we oh
yeah we we finished wait 3 hours ago
even oh
wow one what let's go turn in the quest
time flies you know oh yeah we could
turn in the quest flies did you guys
notice that your Revelations are sparkly
now after the after the dungeon they
sparkle oh my God they are oh we're too
far they can't hear guess it wasn't a
bad memory right Sparkle yeah they do
check it out later on they're so shiny
right cool hey I am on my
horse we're out now where do we my horse
is
amazing give it a leg hey made it wait
how do you know is better than how do
you know that song no reason for that
maybe our our
parents my horse my horse my horse my
horse is
better I know right yeah maybe it was my
lullab oh yeah should we rejoin the big
call now maybe oh
yeah oh just like that wait is it the
Guild Master outside or in the place I
want to I I like I want to get hey cell
phone is not what are
you actually this pretty useful what are
you
what what's a crony my name's Tam wait
I'm going to I'm going to quit the call
one second of people are sleeping now
but let me when turn off the
coal oh your secret S I mean I mean I
never saw you before who are you what's
a crony
Senpai is that like a food I'm Tam I'm a
I'm Tam
Gander ah what's your
name yeah yeah your name is yeah my name
is that's a weird name okay well good
seeing you yeah my name is yeah ra oh la
la yeah la yeah la yeah okay yeah yeah
yes good to see you Tam Tam Gander Tam
Tam
tber Tam Tam Gander Tander Tam Tam
Gander Tam
Tam tamam Tam Tam yeah t a m d
Tander not tender
Gander yes Tam
Gander T dander no not tender Gander
dander no not dander g g n d r Gander G
no g g a n d r
it's not it's not tamam tender
okay it sounds like some sort of chicken
chicken tendies or something it's really
not it's a it's Tam Gander I see like
chicken tender no it's not it's Tam
Gander I you don't have to be mean so
yeah like you don't have to be so mean
yeah
yeah got it okay I got it I got it
hello no you don't okay say it again
what is my
name sorry how you doing no say my
[Laughter]
name don't just laugh that's rude heyo
why you just laughing that's
disrespectful same my name the
tender what the heck
what stop laughing that's my name you're
laughing
about t oh my
God or you're doing this on purpose
aren't
you
t t is stand correct t a m Tam yeah t
Tam Tam yes yes tender no g a n d r not
tender
Gander
Banner ban b as uh g g g as in
good Gander Gander yes yes yes yes Tam
Gander Tam Gander yes thank you so much
I got it I got it oh thank you oh my god
thank God I got it okay well I hope you
have a nice
day are we are we talking about pizza
have a good day we are not talking about
pizza we're talking about my name hello
we talking about her name can introduce
you yes Tam Gander her name is t Gander
yes thank you Gander so your last name
is Gander your first name is she kept
saying Tam t peon T tender pepperoni see
even she thinks that we're talking about
pizza no I don't talk about pizza all
the time I love the pizza oh pepperoni
pizza I love that pizza I love the pizza
I
loveza you guys remember this language
why do you guys remember this language I
don't know actually what is this
language remember
anything it's not really a langage
language of love is it language of love
Yeah is it the language of love I
thought it was French that's love wait
what's French wait what's French what's
French what is French the only French
that I I've heard of is is the is the
smooching French is what I've heard of
what what is it I don't know I actually
don't know anything else past that so
wait what's
sming it was very fun not tender Gander
dander Gander you're saying this on
purpose there's no way no you're saying
this on
purpose no she keeps calling me T
tenders it's cuz her name your name is
tender harassing me because I canot see
here I'm not harassing you're harassing
me so I guess I ought to disband the
party so that you guys can get back with
your ceru and cut meat oh all right band
it for now click to disband yes
free oh man you're free of your
obligations to your boy I'm sure that we
we'll Brave another dungeon together
someday I hope
so good luck on becoming
Queen not good luck it will happen after
this journey okay then i' look forward
to you becoming Queen yes thank
you you want to become a queen no not
I'm going to become Queen not I want to
I'm going to become
queen queen of what the queen of
leeston no what do you mean no I will be
the queen what
yeah oh you're the
second oh no no if I build my castle
before you no that's not how it works no
oh yeah no no no no no no no you're a
second I'm the main hey oh God damn it
these enemies enemies around me
man okay where's
the investigate the
underworld then speak to the Jade sword
Guild Master Jade sword Guild Master
wasn't he
here uh oh wait oh wait I forgot to turn
the music back on whoopsie
okay um his guide has also been
searching for strange ruins a guild his
Guild has been searching for strange
ruins in the lands of Libo mayhaps they
have discovered
something hopefully the Cerulean members
can get back together oh hello yeah turn
in your quest yeah turn to fragman I
need to keep talking to all my think I
completed it power of Revelation San
good old days
eh speak
to the Scarlet wand Guild
Master Ruan tears what do you mean my
maid there must be some connection
between the
ruins
Rus his Gil has been searching for
strange ruins in the lands of liestal
mayhaps they have discovered
something speak to the Scarlet wand
Guild
Master okay I guess I got to
well not in the
call I
can can
feel I'm an
empath okay how do I join a party
but where are
they it's okay I'm going to go look for
scarlet wand I think this is Jade and
the looks of
it wait no
uh nope it's just the illusion of choice
once again
ah can I borrow empathy no it's
something that you just have
to learn by
yourself learn to have
empathy learn to love learn for peace
okay there it is rubius I'm coming I'm
going to kill
you where where where where are
you
I'm I'm I'm
looking for the
Scarlet
leader okay let's see
okay this is where rubius is at oh have
also been investigating near the plane
oh hey fancy seeing you here again hey
there to Tam who knows my deepest
memories hope that you're doing your
quest yeah just from verus off the coast
they found something yeah talk to the
leader there's some interesting stuff
going on yeah most
fascinating traveling to the coast
where's Carla one who they're hard at
work just good luck in
exceler go to the coast really like
saying
excelsia should be willing the coast and
looks like that's the next location good
luck and
exceler okay go to the coast where is
the coast I think it'll show on the map
maybe where you need to go
next but probably need to leave from the
main
gate all right
right well it seems we have a shared
purpose so I'm just going to tail after
you uh
okay give up
no well I can't join the
party at the
coast
uh okay so go straight down there
you know if luck will have it I will
cross paths with my fellow and
paaths is it that
one
uh Corin
wait that's not where Corin
is wait no maybe this is no no no wait
Corin from Fire Emblem no no no no cor
Corin oh maybe it's like here this
way who's
crony who join our party T oh yay
yes man imagine imagine having a girl
named Tam in our party right now man hey
what's wrong with the name right Tam is
great Tam is well Jonathan actually
named me so yes yes I thought I said for
the almighty the Azure Maiden yeah and
then Tam said it was too long so I said
Tam is okay
too
yeah it's a good name your last name
Gander right yeah Gander yeah when you
become Queen is your is your last name
going to change I'm going to assume I
kind of want to keep my last name though
I don't know but you're going to get
married to the King right me
tamto yeah well I don't want to be
called like you know Tam
of you're going become
mrsl
nol how would you
hyphenate H you know I I want to I want
to keep my name you're oh you're going
to keep it yeah I'm just going to keep
it I'm just going to tell the king like
No And besides like he's stole my kill
he's he's old he's an old man it's going
to be my kingdom soon mine yeah keep it
keep it between us though keep it
between us yeah but you you do you do
hold affection for him right Revelation
yeah yeah no sure yeah of
course I see it's because of your re
Revelation re
re
Revelation your Revelation I can't
really tell what your Revelation is uh
Tam yeah well I'm going it's really
fast her
Revelation W that Revelation is cool
right that Revelation is awesome man oh
I'm sorry I'm sorry but we are in a
party it's the
empathy we're kind of violent for no
we're not we're not
yeah it's for the kingdom for the
kingdom for the kingdom I think we're
getting sidetracked again my TB Kingdom
Sam isn't in the voice chat
either oh now I'm in okay it does sound
like you need
toath dangerous yes monster from another
life are we going out on an
adventure W the water is so beautiful it
is a swim take a
swim
oh how do you get
up okay we got it we got it this is just
a little it's a it's it's just a little
splash splash in the water oh hello
fine hello you take dipping the water's
cool feel like I remember your horse's
name but it slips my mind oh do you
maybe from another
your horse another time what letter does
it start with an
a yeah I think so I think I feel like
there was a strong connection between
you and the
horse yeah I just can't remember the
name Adam oh Sadler get away from the
queen all the stains she's remembering
she is remembering she remembering she
did see her memories yeah
H I should get more all right are you
guys ready to go to the coast this is co
to go to the coast yes so yeah hold on
how do I remove someone Beach
episode mag tomb magical
Tom I would like to get rid of I cannot
get rid of our offline our I mean our
disconnected um I mean our sleep sing
member our sleeping member you mean our
our banished member right yes our
banished member she seems to have
disappeared I know not where member let
me reform our it is odd yes we must
reform I must reform okay okay sounds
good here are you take shape to a new
form will with curiosity you're quite
certain something of
great I'm just
reading yeah you got to open your mouth
when you speak crony what are you sorry
sorry okay no need for the Sass spicy no
it's okay I get spicy when I make
friends oh okay spicy spicy yeah the
spice must flow yeah oh I left all my
stuff in a different Barrel well maybe
I'll put it in this corner Barrel too if
I'm
allow been speaking a
yeah I always think the corner Barrel
breathe underwater we believe this
anomia rumor is the breathe under water
what does it mean I don't know we're
going to be able to breathe under water
came into my mind yeah I think we're
I think oh next is Atlantis o what what
what's Atlantis I have not say that
properly what tantis a t tantis tantis
something do with it starts
with where you come from Tam oh were you
originally from were you originally a
mermaid
Tim maybe that's that's why wish king
it's like a marriage of different rumor
countries different species you
mean
species different species and countries
lestans and mermaids they are joining
together she's a mermaid can
reproduce I'm sure they can let's go
back guys to think about that if you
talk to the uh the thing we got to go
back to town okay okay Coral shards huh
is what we need where we get Coral
shards it says to gather them and then
speak to the Guild Master do you think
that where we need 10 yeah where do we
get the there is some Corals in the
water nearby I don't know should we wait
why why' we try to go to town are you
leading us to them are you mayhaps
leading us to the coral the
coral are these Coral okay thinking that
you guys didn't see where it was oh I
see
cor I don't know if they're
rainbow you see are we colleting it h oh
yeah I got four oh oh yeah these are
rainbow I'm returning I'm
returning yo I can't tell I have how
many I have I have 10
I I need Coral in the
water yes so
delicious uhoh yikes big at least it's
not dead coral it's not like the coral
is still alive and fresh which means
that the sea is very clean okay and now
we got to go back to Rubi is to
pollution there's no more Coral I need
more Coral they respawn so you can
always go back oh speak to the Scarlet
one Guild
Master I make haste back towards the
kingdom me
too together yes we it's just me
but hurry
up thank you Tam yeah of course what's
your name
Pink huh hot pink hot pink no wait
what's your name though you could call
hot no you're not
hot wait a minute excuse me which
direction oh no you're excused
farewell wait wait only
rubious speak to the Scarlet one is he
not the Scarlet one he is a scarlet no
no no no we have to go see ruus and he's
in the village good maybe Iris will know
way okay okay yeah guide my way Iris
will guide your
Yes she'll guide my way
huh she has descended and she is not
alone alone yeah literally okay that's
crazy you guys know so many similar
songs me go
back yo you guys follow you guys
following uh I'm going I'm going to in a
in a minute oh I see it it's right over
there see
it y it's a path right there's a path
need me to lead you here where are you
no no no there's no you go right ahead
it's a it's a a Sandy path right okay
let's see and then rius is right over
there there's rubius yeah yeah yeah got
it don't worry about
it you guys don't have to worry about me
I'll find my way I have a map right
she'll find her way are you guys
digging you have diging a tunnel digging
a
grave they're digging a
grave could be I think they're digging a
grave heck
yeah yeah I
think grave
diggers would be to explore but I think
our path is blocked you're digging me
yeah it feels like maybe I don't know I
am I am hot if we give enough time the
path will open on its own the path will
open on its own eventually
[Music]
hot pink yes
what fairy well yes the well goodbye
goodbye goodbye lovely lovely gorgeous
ladies oh I guess this me we do a magic
trick and
disappear oh I didn't disappear right
away oh shoot I was I was planning on
disappearing okay exelia he really silly
Exel
Exel okay where's the
there we go all right where where I
should do something that calls my
name what calls your name it calls to me
a small blue
box a small blue box small blue box
what's we're not talking about the manga
right oh wait no no no what's a manga
what is a manga what what is a manga is
that how you pronounce it
I don't think that's true I do not know
I've never seen one before how do I we
would pronounce it mang CRA loop I have
no
room I guess I I can get fin oh what did
he
do rainbow Coral cluster an object only
red how do I use this waste bin oh I
know we become
mermaids just just like
Tam just like yeah just like she didn't
need this item to begin with but can we
farm farm we can Farm yeah I think
that's what the shovel is for right
growing things
yeah we can build at our Guild base oh
yeah we should build something Guild
House yeah and then have some some do
some farming weat so we can not have to
pay gold to make bread right can we we
should do that we should make our own
gig gig we can have like a guil chest
someone is calling me Gigi I am Jonathan
G she's gathan I thought you were good
game gathan what what is good game one I
drop the telepathic call even if she was
G drop it it's now gathan oh it's gone
gathan dropped the call why did gathan
do that oh well gathan it's been fun
though it has been fun I hope that we
our path cross I want our paths to cross
again our paths will cross as long as
the stars align yeah I think so
too goodbye goodbye goodbye a goodbye a
goodbye goodbye
now what where are you off to
Tam why do you keep laughing Tam Tam huh
hello excuse me Tammy Tam Tam sounds
like you're making fun of me no no I'm
just I just wanted to say your name so
so very often because it's just so
appealing you know oh okay okay MH well
we got to go check out the Ocean Temple
dungeon wherever that is I don't think
it's even open is it open H oh is it not
open I guess it's not open I thought the
dungeon open like daily or something oh
okay I don't know I I that's what I
thought but maybe not well maybe we
should just go to where the ocean Temple
is and I think I might go sleep sleep
yeah I need to also go sleep sleep I my
body is extremely tired me too cuz I
don't know why but I think I was having
some upper day you know this thing
called yeah I don't know this place
called the gym the gym yeah what did you
just Tor is that you tortured yourself
today is that what you did yeah I think
so I I think that's what I
did I don't know why I did that yeah
what what happened are you an M are you
on a m what an M I have no idea that
word just came up in the top of my head
but I don't know what it means wow
that's weird I I never came up with that
kind of
well I mean you know you were torturing
yourself and you enjoyed it right so
well you know oh well I didn't know that
there was a term for
that I've heard I've I've heard um the
back of my mind is screaming to me that
apparently a gym is not even free you
have to pay money to torture yourself oh
oh I mean when you put it like that that
sounds really weird right why why would
I do that I don't know I think I think
you should become a better person now
that you forgot you lost all your
memories you know then stop doing that
to yourself maybe you're right that's
Weir oh hello oh hello hello ladies
hello ladies we got horses you don't we
got horses you don't I I think they do I
guess you're just horsing around then
huh yeah oh oh no you're making the same
joke I did an hour
ago nay I disagree nay my hores my hor
is a very on onyx colored Steed look at
how Majestic my my Steed looks mine's a
normal horse but like this just me is it
just me or is ena's horse like like a
pony sure yeah try moving
Ena why are you make full of my
horse to you you're short oh there never
mind never mind it was only pretending
to be a pony yeah Pony want to be don't
listen to them
Pony W to be Pony at all oh is that the
name of your horse you're a wonderful
horse yeah that's J I will find my gem
it was nice to see you fair maidens all
right
goodbye
Exel all right well we're going to go to
the coast the coast the
coast yes the ocean the ocean wait where
did where did
Fair know what the Cho I'm looking for
you oh hello hello hello you have
returned to us a precious Rock I am
suddenly talking to so many people at
the same time wa you know someone was
looking for you yeah yes I am I am
looking for them they they're in the
town you should go look for them okay I
will I will go onward farewell beautiful
you
canwell farewell
that's her name yeah that's her
name I didn't know that hello Fair n
n the stars have aligned
already again oh can we do that dungeon
I think I don't think so no no maybe get
ready to yeah get ready sure sounds good
to me I'll go all right let us ride let
us ride okay let's go like the wind
[Music]
yeah running over cows we are fast and
furious slow I could use some carbonated
drinks now carbonated love some
carbonated food carbonated love do you
love
your I do
indeed I I don't know what that means
but it must something amazing oh wait oh
and we can cook I mean I can cook
investigate you can c i can stained meat
is it actually yummy where is this ocean
Temple I think the Ocean Temple is
somewhere far out in the ocean and you
know we have this rainbow Coral cluster
so I think we can breathe underwater now
my rainbow chloral cluster oh yeah we
can yo I can breathe yeah let's swim
that's awesome do did you find your
Rainbow Coral
cluster sinking Like a Rock was my
inventory
full if you cleared the quest like the
they the rudus gives you one yeah but
put in your hand my inventory was full
my St this is a rainbow Coral Shard
which was used to make the thing do not
hunger
Coral rainbow Coral uh cluster is
missing oh check my check my magical
book ah there it is where where was it
in your was it in a it was in the
magical tomb of greatness oh okay was
that oh
God thought that was an earth shut up
shut up I hate these so-call tamies or
cronies whatever it is I'm so sick of
them so sick of the voices in my
head I do have some left over jerky I'm
wandering I'm trying to wander off to
the to the to the thing on the map oh I
think oh wait there's an arrow symbol
okay we go down like there's a thing on
the map
that
oh you look like
dice hold
on okay D so mean yeah whatever oh my
God there's
diamonds okay I got to I got to get
these before anyone else gets
them wait wait I can't mine it with just
Stone
darn I
can't oh yeah
radio wow oh she's finally joined I will
what do you mean finally joined welcome
back Tam thank you the call I just spok
I
Mario Jonathan keeps dropping the call
so I had to I had to speak with Mario
Mario said that she's the queen and that
you're a liar who's Mario I do who's
Mario she is pink and she looks like a
cat oh that okay okay no wonder okay I
get it why she's called Mario okay okay
called herself not Luigi but Mario okay
yeah her name is Mario okay she was the
one making fun of my name
made fun of your name not be able to get
into the mysterious place she kept
calling me Tam tenders for no reason Tam
tenders tenders yeah that's not very Tam
tenders cam
tenders slender and tender what an evil
she said that she wanted to kill
everyone so oh wow that evil yeah that
is pretty evil that's a pretty Evil part
of Amber coin yeah yeah
I bet I bet she's part of Amber coin we
can't we can't get to the dungeon
there's an invisible wall That's I feel
like time will solve the problem wao
look there's something time this is
Diamond did I just go the wrong way
strong enough pickaxe for this
time I'm going to be rich
oh I'm going to be is high sorry I'm
here
hello oh I knew you were going to say
that dungeon is still
dormant oh is that what it says when you
try to enter yes dorant seems that ENT
just
yet Perhaps tomorrow maybe we need some
sleep yeah maybe yeah I think it's about
time I need to I need to get some sleep
yeah I need my beauty sleep get some Shi
let's meet again let us meet again R Vu
when time opens up a new gate towards
the next when the gate opens let us meet
again I will be waiting
theanu and Guild Masters will make us
assemble right this seruan assemble
right I will a carrier pigeon and
letting you guys know with my pigeon
you're a
loveely carrier pigeon by the way that's
really cool
yes I will send a pigeon to your inboxes
and they will leave a note to you let we
have inboxes you mean you mean our
mailboxes right yes yes your your
mailboxes I will our carrier
pigeon yes yes
mhm I will send note all right be thank
well have a great one
everyone take care take care everyone
farewell again tomorrow
goodbye tomorrow
tomorrow I love you
tomorrow how do you all know this song
very weird I don't know only do we come
from the same world that's crazy I hope
not may maybe we oh why
not why do you hope not I don't I don't
goodbye goodbye everyone her problems
has her problem no no no
heror her name is I named
her hey don't put it like
that hey I don't like I don't like the
sound of that I named her excuse me okay
good night allowed me to a suggestion
farewell
fwell
byebye oh man so guys that was that was
something
um yeah there was a lot of
interesting experiences I
suppose yeah um I don't know what kind
of Adventure awaits us
tomorrow
but yeah remember anything yourself not
really
but yeah I just hope
that it's a
it's
okay yeah did I enigmatic
recollect I'm not so sure
but who
knows
ah okay
but with
that I will have to bid you a
do
um
C
crir have a great one everyone thank you
so much for stopping
by uh my tamies
crownies Crower of
War yeah wh why did I do that that was
weird
what e
I suppose I could have just sent
see you
tomorrow right why did I say croro
what's
croro whatever