[Music]
cakey
everyone welcome to the
babble of the legendary gods
playing
i think the most important question that
i gotta ask right off the bat
do you all have uno
what i mean if i mean we're playing the
game
now callie what's the meme it's a
miguel it's a meme it's a music
huh guys
[Laughter]
joke just with us yeah it was good i
just
didn't realize that that's what we were
talking about
oh kelly swoosh
[Music]
good morning or good evening or wherever
the hell you are hello and welcome
it's uh it's the day the day has come
where we play uno
um we have some rules uh
that i have decided on and together
with my dear twitter replies thank you
everyone
my my chickens for answering um so let
me
let me read to you the following rules
um they're probably not so bad they're
just funny and cute and yeah
uh so now we have we have
a rule for every round
losers and then we have a rule for the
final
rule losses at the very end like you
know
um so i want to one thing i have not
decided on though is that
the the loser thingies
for each round should we um get
only the one with the most cards at the
end to do it or
all three losers who didn't win the
round i'm asking you guys
um it's more fun to point your finger
and laugh at one person
so we got like a few things so for
example
um since we're probably gonna do a
couple of rounds we're just gonna rotate
this randomly so
uh number one end your sentences with
nya
or meow for the following round
sing all your sentences for one round
yeah something like that number three
talk in baby talk for one round no no
[Music]
you know what
okay the next one is that one that
callie is looking forward to
uh speak like a cowboy for around one
round i'll speak like a cat cowboy for
one round i'll do that anyway
[Music]
exactly and now and the next one is try
i think because we all got members here
who can obviously speak decent japanese
especially guru who has now cheated on
me with another bird what the [\h__\h] why
did you die
so try to speak japanese for one round
like
yeah and then we got another one speak
like a graph
speak like a grandma for one round
do you like gosembe
okay so that's that's like the general
like round loser
rules and then there's a final one for i
guess someone has to count like who lost
the most and who won the most uh
i guess yeah who won the most is
important because the winner of the most
matches
gets to do one tweet on each loser's
twitter
so i'm probably if i win i know what i'm
gonna tweet on kelly's account
i can keep track of that if you want you
should buy that
you have to beat her are you sure
are you good with numbers you can't are
you sure you can count to like
five items i agree i am certified it's
in the uno name tenzai
so you can count from one to ten or only
from
you if i tell you that will you count
one and then ten or will we count one
two three five five six seven eight nine
ten
i appreciate the attempt of what you're
trying to do but
i assure you i assure you i am certified
a certified counter true genius
certified tallier tally mark taker i got
this
i believe you well one thing that is
also very important is um
in this uno match we
encourage violence so
yes i wasn't told i mean i'm fine with
this but i just wasn't alerted about it
before
i didn't get to ricky and also oh no
ricky's behind me excuse me
nothing nothing nothing nothing nothing
nothing nothing nothing we're good we
also
are we um sorry
we i we also i think each one of us also
got the the uno flip
uh i think everyone got it right i was
the homeowner
i don't know oh i mean i can get it if
if you want to
if you want to do it but okay what is it
the the one
what is in the flip the one that well
where you see like the cards that
everyone's using unless you
put a card where you unscrew the card i
don't know
but generally you see every time oh
i i mean i got it i don't know
i don't think i have it but i can buy it
if you want oh well oh well i guess we
we can do it without and then another
time we can do a whole uno flip match
yeah i got the i got the whole start
with the basics here yeah okay
so as you can see the current rules i
don't know if you guys can actually see
that well uh the cool rules are just uh
stacking is okay and
uh draw until you have the card that
that matches the card that's on the
stack uh are the current rules the other
ones i have turned off but we can change
the rules every now and then
okay okay well done okay
yeah i'm by the way playing with a
controller so i keep on mistaking
the right button what's the right button
it says here uh
start match what is that is that is
[Music]
amelia suggested it to me it's very
empty it's very
thank you i like it i think there's a
certain there's a certain flair to it
i like it thank you amelia so i think
the viewers can see
partially see my cards but i'm also
partially um
um covering them up on purpose but yeah
shoot okay let me not look at the
yeah don't look at the stream sorry
excuse that was that was totally i'm
sorry
i'll i'll play feather i'll play fair
okay fairman
happy birthday
[Laughter]
oh by the way is the audio fine my dear
audience is the audio fine
is everything cool are you here i got it
i tab that way
the reverse
i was just trying to pop out the chat
hold okay um
hang on hmm
sorry by the way we we just had to leave
someone out and amy said she was kind of
busy anyway but next time
maybe i will not participate but emma
will be there
so don't worry which color
kelly what's your favorite color oh
did you say blue yeah
oh by the way wait can we watch this
card yeah i don't understand why would
you challenge it i don't understand the
rules
but why would you challenge it like what
are we challenging the i mean i don't
understand
i told you i challenged it then that
would reveal what i have in my deck so
i'm not going to say anything hey but i
don't get it it's like what
a reason and it turned out the rules
were not as i thought they were
oh that's all you know oh my goodness
okay oh wow
i got a good color i'm gonna stab
this color all right
down was that good at giving me two
cards for god's sake
welcome teacher
we have to talk about one now
if i might properly put in a card though
[Music]
i know how to play the game
we're still all the friends but let's
see how it looks like at the end
oh yeah what the [\h__\h]
oh yeah wait
god damn my god
we counted we counted okay next next one
nice one
sorry let me just say the new yeah
oh yeah wait wait wait wait wait wait
was it was it kelly
me kelly i thought it was um wait hold
on hold on we stopped
please twist me out
stupid dumb word kelly would you like to
tell us what
what your week was like tell us what you
did this week
[Music]
meow
kelly have you been missing me
give me an answer here um
sure meow uh-huh
yeah thank you have i satisfied you meow
yes yes meow mm-hmm
it's like when you challenge it like in
what cases would you win
the challenging and then yeah
someone in the chat tell me we don't
understand
could they have played something what
challenge equals could they have played
something else besides the plus four
ah you can only play the plus four if
you have no other choice
and if you play it anyway then you can
oh
yeah wow
yeah well then here you go kelly two for
you
say thank you meow say thank you
[Music]
we can we can change the rules later too
so no
problem but i think every time we change
rules we have to
open a new room so it's gonna be a bit
annoying but
no problem um
what nothing until now meow
meow meows when i said meow
kelly do you want the new scratching
pose scratching post
scratchy scratch i'm cool okay
thank you for the membership how many
will you draw
girl sweating i'm drawing i'm drawing
i'm drawing i'm drawing i'm
oh my god
hello dad how are you dad
fine oh yeah oh i didn't mean you i
meant
uh
good to
hmm
okay
someone's gonna make uh someone's gonna
make a mimo do you know that mean that
it's like draw 25
cards four for kelly it's gonna be say
meow or draw twenty-five
you know what let's do it
[Laughter]
okay no no problem for me
this music is so chill it's like saying
looking good like like holiday music
vacation music
inside yeah
the fact that she definitely doesn't
have a blue card right now
because she played uh the the six in
green
so she definitely doesn't have a blue
one
[Music]
she also doesn't have a green maybe not
she does though
okay tina ina anna
don't you guys want to hear cursing i'm
here
no i'm here to sing mine yeah
what is that
[Music]
i'll give it to you later yeah
okay
i am not tripping it means i'm not
falling down at this moment
um
[Music]
you're going to never bloom huh hey inna
stop cook
you're gonna challenge that challenge
yeah
if i can't be first then i definitely am
not going to be less
we'll see about that
[Music]
everything is green now who wants to
challenge that huh huh going to
challenge no one okay
okay go with me
because i'm playing by the rules i'm
playing nice
best color
the best color what say you to this meow
oh no that's okay oh wait oh wait oh i
have to take oh god
[Music]
welcome to the membership we got some
new eggs i'm gonna eat scrambled eggs
tomorrow
with those new members
what does everyone eat for breakfast
here normally
steak um a lot of times
i don't eat breakfast i forget
oh what about guna uh
a uh hot cereal
like you [\h__\h] kidding me yum
ah that's pretty good actually that
cereal is good
hot favorite like with hot milk very
kind cereal
hot meal or just hot cereal hot soup
it's like oatmeal or something like that
ah okay okay that's okay
okay now i understand okay that first
sandwich is really weird as if you just
warm up cereals i don't know hot
cheerios
so i guess that's just uh wait what's
that called like hot oatmeal
iced
orange that's the word oh yeah pork
couldn't actually eat porridge in the
morning here
you know it's a little more flavorful
there you go yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
do it do it do it i don't know
we have to stop here
[Applause]
wait who had the most cards at the end
wait it doesn't even say i didn't
you didn't oh okay
uh in the next round beautiful all right
i anticipated wow the meow curse is
broken
let's do one more and then we'll change
the rules okay we have to make a new
room for that
okay marina how are you today
oh okay all right all right oh no
no is this cheating i wonder
[Laughter]
there's something beautiful about this
i love it can we keep this the whole
time actually
yeah i love these rules oh i don't think
so
[Music]
what is stack and when someone does plus
two and i also have a plus two then i
stack on it and then you're gonna
take plus four unless you have another
plus two oh
thank you for letting me know that
have you ever played uno in your life
it's been a long time
wow i used to play a lot of uno
okay so did you have any weird rules
multiple times a day oh no
did you have any weird rules no i always
played
like classic uno time
of day got that right
you gotta stretch out your nose yeah
long and longer sing longer
sing for me
[Laughter]
keep on blocking her she's about to win
again it's not good
you guys better act faster i'm going to
take this w
no no no oh no
oh yeah it was green the muddy color
how do you say green in japanese
[Music]
but okay funny fact okay i got a fun
fact here for you girls so
in japan the lights right so it's a red
and green like everyone else but
they call when it when it turns green
they say uh it turned blue
only not i think it's because uh in the
past
and they used to be blue probably but
now they're green but they still say it
turned
uh blue is not weird that is weird yeah
or why yeah and probably because they
used to have blue ones
[Music]
we want to hear inna sing more you know
you know what did you do this week
nothing wow that little record scratch
look at this humor i'm trying really
hard to make your girls use your your
bat's game a little bit more
but all you say is like one word answer
is it's not acceptable
you got to get creative kiara
wait oh my god
you gotta
this really hurts oh this really hurts
oh no
wait wait the next round is baby talk
for a round we want
we want kelly to talking baby talk oh my
god i gotta get rid of my cards quickly
i'm cool with it i'll talk baby talk oh
no
i won't be the satisfaction my dog i
just won't
what have i done
[Music]
i'm helping thanks
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
baby
[Music]
oh
have you remembered from your japanese
lesson yesterday
anxieties wow
10 years old oh no she stopped me
you know you gotta explain that joke to
the viewers i don't think anyone
understands that
means 10 years old and also a genius
can i please get rid of this card
what color
[Applause]
you know why
it was worth a try
[Music]
we all love that song don't you we wish
we should cover it with whole lives
english we should cover the blue song
[Music]
damn it oh yeah no angelic damn it
damn it i already got so many guys stop
this insanity
insanity that word yeah that sort of
sanity
[Music]
oh
i got so many cards i got the same
amount as kelly maybe if we keep it like
that we can we can
both be babies you babies
you seem really anxious to be a baby for
some reason oh wow
[Music]
oh my god
[Applause]
okay thank god
i'm free wait who had the most at the
end i think i had like 13.
there was christmas daughter wait how
many did you have kelly
it's me am i the baby but how many did
you have ah
i don't care what the most what chat
tell us
who will they have 12 oh then i am the
baby
[Music]
okay i think that's a sign of it let's
let's quit oh let's get out of here
[Music]
okay
okay okay oh we're gonna add this one
because uh this one is fun i heard uh
we're gonna add the rule
and play a seven from now i think
now we only had one two six right but
now there's a seven and zero
and the seven is um play a seven to swap
hands with someone else
and a zero zero to pass hands around i'm
not sure how that works i never used it
but it's apparently fun
and what let's uh what else should we do
we jump in
play a card out of turn if the last card
is identical to the
what does that mean i don't get the
sentence plan oh so like so like if
someone puts down like a
uh red four and then you also have
[Music]
was it is it the same number or is it
the same color and number
i forget but yeah but you can you can
put it down like even if it's not your
turn
yeah okay well this is gonna be crazy
okay well um then let's
freaking go
okay can you girls join color and number
you can you can okay
i think only my friends can join now can
you girls oh there we go good eyes in
all right okay let me see all right
in the house
[Music]
oh
what
[Music]
oh
that's all right
[Music]
what if someone has not careful no but
then someone
changes the cards from everyone then you
don't have uno anymore but someone else
says
oh my god
[Music]
ah this hurts me i'm in pain right now
okay well
what happened what does this happen
what does it do oh i switch all right
oh okay okay okay
that's interesting are you sure you want
to
i don't want something at least though i
have to i don't want to can i just wait
uh yeah i know i think it will swim
randomly
okay oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
oh another one yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh
my god
[Music]
can i drink some milk i see how it is
i have none for you i want some milk
down
i don't have any forgot to go to the
store
[Music]
i'm hungry
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
all right all right all right you guys
are bullying me huh
i don't really care you wouldn't have
given me milk i wouldn't have given you
two kinds
wait cali but the next one is uh next
one is the uh
cowboy one you want to have powers
you guys when someone wants to go ahead
and win really quick
no
it really can just turn like that oh
damn it
empty i
i don't swear
okay next time
ah
[Music]
you're waiting to press
that doesn't make me feel very good you
have to click first
oh yeah i know i might lose this one
[Music]
oh yeah i didn't give it to you on
purpose it's not worthy of your thanks
thank you small thank you it's my smart
things
one more card for you
all right i want my passive sign
no oh okay that's just the brakes
this is the brakes my dog i'm sorry you
don't have to be dirty like that but
listen
i'm sorry my dog no no oops i missed it
this time
what i challenged
all right well all right
you know but okay you're welcome
[Music]
weird oh
you know it's funny and then you'll like
it
[Music]
no no stop i clicked
the [\h__\h] button
every single [\h__\h] every time
oh maybe i can be cowboy just kidding
[Music]
oh my god yeah one two three
are rich in cars
yes
that is
oh
[Laughter]
no you don't play i'm just trying to get
your hand over to me
slowly but surely
no no i'm playing the wrong i'm pushing
the ramp on them
[Music]
this one goes for cali i do like the
color red
[Music]
and the
sorry all right
[Music]
i don't know xbox buttons [\h__\h]
them
controller yes i am playing me crunch
one
i love you i don't
dance
[Music]
i'm wearing the pants here
i'm going to shake those pants real good
what's happening kyla
what
[Laughter]
don't worry
okay that's not too bad it's not too bad
oh my god
nice two one i can count
better than
you just said you were gonna poop your
diaper on street
that's your mom
i know what color it is don't worry guys
oh yeah of course i'm sure he'd uh-huh
uh-huh i do
i do
is it not red i don't know if i should
say
what are the chances what are the
chances what are the chances
don't do it look at the chances
[Music]
how long will i be baby
now okay now i
am too kind okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
it's like taking me
i don't think i can get up to 20
unfortunately
oh my god
[Music]
baby
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
i have a choice here i have a choice
okay i see
[Music]
okay
i guess keanu is going to be a baby
forever huh
now oh
oh
who's your mama who's my mama um
oh nice
nice huge place huge place huge place
we've got stacks going on here that only
does it once that's the thing
we're so close to greatness and they
don't stop coming
and it don't stop coming and it doesn't
[Music]
done
oh
[Laughter]
press the wrong button on those funny
[Music]
don't stop coming
oh she wants the cowboy she wants them
she doesn't wear a baby anymore
your favorite number five your favorite
number
that's all right and your birthday
number can i come to your birthday
party i mean i won't i won't lock you
out of it you can
[\h__\h] yeah if we were still in the
womb together i think i would have eaten
you by now
wait wait we were wearing the room
together
did you stay still in the womb see i'm
sorry
i think i might have missed something i
didn't listen to the rest of the
sentence
don't change the corner don't change
all right all right karen knows what
color this is he knows
yeah i don't know
[Music]
oh it's a document
you're happy about that right yeah
i feel like you're happy good night
[Music]
oh wait can i no
probably another hour for this round
thank you mama
[Music]
cali wine i don't like green
no okay now i have more cards than you
maybe
good grow nice and fat and ripe so i can
switch with you in the future
yes i become fake baby for you as you
ask me no wait no
[Applause]
take just a couple steps back
[Laughter]
this sure is a special round huh
she's a real special round over i don't
want to be baby anymore
yeah it's been a very long time since i
turned into a baby's real
i must follow a rule
i mean i will follow you know what they
say
children grow so fast around oh
thanks but i'm not growing
[Music]
orange juice that's all we got orange
okay
[Music]
oh
all right we're still in this we're
still in this
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
no i'm sorry listen
immediately
let's make this over please please
i've never played with you ever yet
why did i get two i could have jumped in
by the press the wrong
than it is
[Music]
nice big baby stupid baby
is
[Music]
i'm gonna punch someone's throat
yay
all right kelly next time around i gotta
get free
thanks man thank you looking forward to
your
[Music]
gift
oh gosh i don't have green right now
[Music]
everyone relax
i'm i'm very relaxed
[\h__\h] hell baby well that's someone
yeah
[Music]
baby
baby sorry i'm baby mama told me how to
say
i'm just not gonna say anything
i've been baby for half an hour when new
people join this stream they think i
always speak like this
for half an hour fortunate isn't it
this isn't gonna end
and pay me forever baby phoenix
okay we have to work together
we have to win together next time
someone gets um
we have to let that person win
oh no never kelly
[Music]
you know what to do i've heard
how can you have such a bad hand
wait oh thank god
stop
let me cowboy somebody once told me he
didn't have any
i don't know
kelly what color do you have to see it
should i really tell you yeah maybe not
but give us a drumroll
that wasn't
kelly i could have ended your suffering
oh man
oh god
please oh my god
oh [\h__\h] i forgot i didn't
but i don't want to let me come back
hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
oh my god
no
what's the [\h__\h] point
you can't
[Applause]
okay i will take it from you do we want
to do the same rules again
that was real stressed wait wait let's
how about no
jump in because i can't do that but how
about well okay first place if you draw
a card on your turn let's play
no why how about no bluffing a lot of
draw cards may be played without being
challenged
ah you can draw you can pull
put plus four and so whatev whenever
even if you have other choices
i want to do that yeah chad is saying no
seven zero please no seven seven zero
[Laughter]
then we have but what does the score
limit do it says one round or 200 or 300
500 i don't understand that
what is that that the full score
limit can be lowered can also be set to
one round only
i don't understand that should i just
have no
one round no if we want like
rapid fire matches i guess
so any we have a plus two plus two the
stacking one then we have no bluffing
and we have draw to match
um okay oops uh
okay okay lambie's only lost me
games
[Laughter]
adam sadler sadly passed away he died in
a mining accident
i don't even know how to speak in a
non-baby voice anymore
all right out of class this is my voice
are you okay hello yes i'm okay
enough happy
just kidding that changed real quick um
now as the sheriff with my badge yeah i
feel great you sound sexy
can i can i change the from the sheriff
voice now no
no
might this is refreshing this
could be as a short game again
yes maybe
i don't know maybe short game how are
you all right damn
are you all right wow
just a quick quick quickie a quickie
with
cowboy sarah crowley oh
my god
[Laughter]
i'm looking forward to whatever whatever
um
that guru decides to write for me i'm
very excited
[Music]
this is indeed well this is indeed
oh wow oh no okay
[Applause]
well inna has the next uh finnish ina
has to speak japanese for one round
maybe we can join nasty hand ahead
japanese okay
[Music]
[Applause]
you didn't have to answer that you could
have said i'm i won't answer that in
japanese
but you've chosen
[Music]
what is it
foreign
[Music]
uh
we all can speak nihongo we all tensai
oh what is his hand what is his hand
you got a good hand i have fruit salad
no
fruit salad noise
or food salad did you say that salad or
fruit salad
fruits fruit salad yummy yummy
no no wrong color [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] now where's that
[Music]
okay
you know about the oyster ever since i
came back to australia wink
uh i i start i tried to speak german you
know but
i get these i i have these automatically
programmed words into my brain like
yourself
and i always say that
i i take something up i put something up
from the ground and i'm like yo
even though i'm now not in japan anymore
that's so used to it
yeah it follows you yeah
everywhere i go the japanese comes with
me yeah
you saw
yeah you know japanese friend actually
told me i was like wow
um i really like to say uh kono yaro
right what if there's a yaro over here
what if there's no over there i mean
instead of here so it's not incorrect
it's not incorrect yeah
well kelly how about two kites for ya
[Music]
as a certified japanese language teacher
kelly didn't get enough of the cowboy
about this game and so she wants to
continue with the japanese parts of the
game
yeah that's what it is
this is the best number i'm getting a
rushed my brain happens
[Music]
um
[Applause]
my brain is a little too small for this
okay it's a little too small
your brain can't handle a game of uh
no i've lived for all of existence
oh wait that was my turn
[Music]
yeah you have to laugh in japanese too
yeah yeah yeah there you go there you go
you got it you got it
oh so we're going that way how about we
go that way
to go down
the stage is yours have you have you
guys had like in
like in my country oh in my country like
we had this tv show where there was this
this magician and he was like the stage
is yours
and he checks out other magicians and
stuff i don't know
um
[Music]
oh
yeah i think it was guru
[Music]
back okay one second i'm joining i'm
joining him oh you're generally no i
don't think you can i'll
reopen it's okay sorry
i mean
what was that what the [\h__\h] was that it
sounded like god
that sounded like gold precious
no that's not a grandma a grandma's mom
like
i think this could be the last game
because this is our last batsu game of
ours uh independently okay do you want
to do a number seven zero
i think that let's let's go let's do
another one come on seven zero's fun
okay okay you guys are not tired if
you're not tired are you okay
guys yeah we're fine
the grandma's probably already tired at
this early in the morning so
she might need to go back to sleep early
uh should we no do you think grandma
i don't know i'm cool with anything
i am good right now big round
okay okay one big this is the
one okay jump in
yeah yeah all right all right all right
oh sorry
jumping sorry i had no jump in sorry
oh
let me get out of this i never know
what's the right button
whatever let me get out of here what's
the right button to
leave this freaking lobby there we go
okay it's oh there's i guess i escaped
let's go i'm for the final game
uh yes what so can i tell you the
rankings for this final game to give us
a little bit of incentive to really try
hard
yes collaborate no matches one are you
ready
she's up on the board for ultimate loser
it's going to be a big mess let's do
like double points or something
boom nothing double or nothing come on
go home okay
then everyone please enter the lobby
it's now worth jumping okay
all right all right all right but
bluffing works again and you can
challenge someone i'm bluffing again
and gouda will be our grandma come on
grandma you got some cookies for me did
you make some cookies
cookies can i watch cartoons on the tv i
brought your teeth
can i watch cartoons oh my god
you know it's birthdays yeah i watched
carson's
it's my turn to watch the tv oh my god
[\h__\h]
but grandma should be more accepting and
more open and say yes yes
it's too fast for grammar
grandma do you need your glasses to read
those numbers
no okay should i read them for you let
me show
your grandma voice you're not speaking
in grandma voice come on this is
oh she's my it's a great grandma voice
it's a great grandma voice
my grandma voice as long as you're
giving it your all
grandma this is my grandma
what's your grandma sounds like
i don't have a grandma anymore
[Laughter]
i'm not sad sound like
grandma i'll make you eat double
vegetables next time
i love vegetables your least favorite
with no butter or salt okay baby
um yeah you gotta better watch out
not fried either wrong grandma
could you could you shouldn't you be a
british grandma please be a great
british grandma please
oh wait we have that again oh oh oh i
guess i mean i guess
i'll switch with you i guess all right
you have a better hand than i did
i got there's so this is
[Music]
grandma yeah
there we go it's cool
real quick it's granny isn't it
once upon a time many many many years
ago
what the heck
thank you i'm going to sleep well
tonight
[Laughter]
you know what color
grandma what what sorry i've got some
old age you're going to have to try it
[Music]
it's okay grandma it's technology we
should have played uno with real cards i
guess not with this
ubisoft pubg
[Music]
oh no grandma are you collecting cards
grandma grandma
oh wait a song
grandma is happy about it all those
times yet
i told you i don't want any more food
grandma please it hurts
grandma i have to i have to confess
something
that muffler that that you needed for me
i hate it i threw it away i burned it
grandma's feeling
i thought it was beautiful grandma
are we here granted
grandma my christmas gift you sammy
hasn't arrived did you did you actually
send one
oh did you forget about
does she even know who she is who she is
who are you people
who are young grandma grandma
you know it's me collide marty the grim
reaper
grandma oh yeah i'm just focusing
everybody shut up
oops i didn't mean to play that grandma
it's okay
you're playing the game
i'll send my brother to fix your
computer again gouda okay
grandma
oh yeah oh yeah
oh yeah also
you might have learned something wrong
on the internet you're not supposed to
put the chicken into your pc to grill it
that's not where it belongs even though
kfc tells you so
it doesn't go there okay what that's not
new technology
what's kfc that's where the food comes
from
that's where the food the chicken the
grill stole the fried chicken that's
where we got that from every night
that's what you're eating every night
you don't remember
what i've read
what i'm writing to you she doesn't
remember
unbelievable i'm sick of this grammar
damn my grandma
do that to me
let grandma be happy come on
[Music]
every time i can never jump out of like
15 times of jumping in i got it once
oh you have enough cards already
[Laughter]
no the good thing is that the last the
final
batsu game the last punishment game is
like there's only one winner and three
losers it doesn't matter who lost the
most actually
yeah so that's that's double or nothing
we gotta think of
ah but how am i gonna double zero losses
oh wait oh i'm gonna get like something
i'll think of something i know if i win
this time i got two wins right
because it's one double okay okay sorry
wait did this double zero i meant i
meant double zero wins but anyway that
doesn't
make sense whatever i'm confused okay
maybe i'm the grandma
[Music]
oh god damn it play no it's not just me
okay
no
let's get my cards back oh
[Music]
okay we're leaving this game i guess but
uh wait
wait wait so i had the most cards
yeah but everyone in the last round
except the winner loses well i don't
know how
there we go okay there's really nothing
okay well um
girls so wait who had the most wins who
had the most wins that's important
i can deal with a pun on my
[Music]
of something twitter yeah
yeah yeah
[Applause]
i had two wins done if we did double
very kelly yeah i guess so huh
cool yeah you have zero wins and girl
has
two wins why do i have passions
[Laughter]
okay well then yeah he still did a good
job that means that ina
is gonna tweet something on our account
sometime
soon maybe right away maybe not uh but
look forward to that
we will never know if that coming up
tweet is made by inner or the person
themselves oh you'll know you'll know
i hope everyone enjoyed this we're
definitely going to play uno again
sometime but
next time probably and we can i also
realized one thing
girls there's also we have permission
from monopoly as well i really want to
play monopoly
yeah no no no
the good thing is that monopoly
monopolies it seems like it's for six
players so for opportunity yeah so we
can play it with everyone
[Music]
monopoly
okay i'm gonna ask everyone for their
feelings about today's game one by one
first of all let's ask our grandma
gurantma
please i had a lot of fun i really like
uno and you guys are really fun to play
with so
i have fun thank you
thank you for participating grandma
let's ask kelly how she felt about
today's game
cowboy kelly well a cowboy cat
cowboy cat you had two games i'll
declare meow
um i i it was a roller coaster of
emotions meow
um but i'm glad that i got to experience
it with you fine ladies meow
thank you for inviting me meow i look
forward to our next
encounter meow wow
let's uh ask our singer she had singing
as her
punishment game once ina you were also
the winner singer and winner isn't that
beautiful
sing something for us how you feel about
it thank you very much for calling today
it's a pleasure so much fun
thank you
[Laughter]
i had the punishment game to be a baby
for half an hour and i was fine too
um i did not get to drink kelly's milk
but i am pooped in everyone's pants so
look forward to that
grandma where's the laundry room
like one of my grandma's uh when i
visited her place like
thousands of years ago uh oh my god i
hated going to the toilet there because
it was
just not an automatic toilet which just
was like toilet paper toilet paper and
like newspaper on the ground of the
toilet i don't know i really didn't like
it it was kind of weird
[Laughter]
did your grandma's not have something
like that she was living on the
countryside like on the real countryside
so
old plumbing was not very good back in
the olden days
the more you know
[Music]
well i wanted to put money with human
life exposure thank everyone
for joining this game this was really
fun i'm going to be reading super chats
but we're going to the learning stream
for a little bit because i want to take
a little screenshot
of four four shot selfie and upload it
on twitter and then i'll be back in uh
three minutes to read some super chats
because i've been uh
yeah lacking uh i didn't read it last
time okay
thank you everyone and enjoy
those know what to say and in germany
[Music]
ciao
so
[Music]
do
oh my god okay wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
oh my god hello are you guys still here
why are you guys still here but i need
to fix some things it's a it's a mess
here
it's an absolute mess one second
i have said goodbye and posted a after
stream
post a tweet uh
and now we are back here
wow at some point there was
43 000 people watching us play
what 43 thousand
that was the point
i didn't think so many people would want
us to
play you know i'm very happy
uh everyone was having a great time i
guess
oh okay chad come back to me welcome
back to
i see you now it's not moving yet it
will move probably soon come on come on
yeah there it is moving
no i mean 40 40 yeah it went back later
to 33 000 but it was at 43 000 peak
my youtube says so so it must be true
that's crazy i'm looking forward to all
the memes on reddit oh my god
it's going to be full of uno posts
well i'm so excited to check reddit
later
let me drink something
was it fun for you guys did the rules
make it fun too
next time we can have different roles um
render vlog yeah shout out to the
redditors yeah
there's already many memes really
already so fast and they already climbed
up to the top
not like how long does it usually take
with brackets so that it reaches the top
oh i guess that the people preemptively
already made memes i guess
like before like they already wanted to
make memes before it even started i
guess
they probably did didn't they also
okay um we got super chats to read
from yesterday's stream did we also have
super chats to read from the stream
before
or was it only yesterday i wonder i
think it's only only from yesterday
oh and today right
right am i wrong no not just near okay
near that the stream that that
disappeared because okay yesterday i
streamed near automata
and i had a lot of issues so it was
really really bad i don't know if that
was
it was probably my like a lot of things
like my pc and the near automata being a
bit
wacky on pc and then youtube also being
stupid it was everything together
so i privated that stream after playing
a little bit of minecraft to test
out some more um if it was only uh near
automata it turns out it was own it was
only near automata
what have i heard that uh youtube in
asia is still [\h__\h] around
like they're still um not able to watch
streams like a few hours ago i read that
it was
still that way is it
oh really i thought it was like only
asian countries
still wonky what the hell that's been
like like 24 hours or something like
more than 24 hours
wow also i'm feeling so hot i was
feeling i was freezing before the stream
but now
i'm sweat i'm gonna take a shower after
this oh [\h__\h]
wow that was fun that was fun
[Music]
apparently not in the c s e i r why do i
always read s-e-a
as c-e-a happy birthday
baby voice for half an hour that was
that was difficult
i had i think the longest uh punishment
came
that the last zero to seven
game wasn't even that long it didn't
even feel like a zero to seven
yeah it was a zero to that that's what
you call it i don't know what you call
that um
we we need a few more cuckoo cuckoo
combos would have been nice like plus
four plus four plus one plus one
i needed one more of those
a seven to zero yeah can last much much
longer it lasted so long the first time
holy [\h__\h] it was like never ending
oh my god yeah yeah and then kelly uh
yeah wanted to throw because she wanted
to be sheriff which was i guess helping
though it was helping
but then we weren't sure if we wanted to
let certain people win
i was i don't even i don't care anymore
i don't want to be a cowboy
i wish i was supposed to be the cowboy
but then i gave that to kelly
because she was really excited for that
and i was exhausted from being a baby
for too long
[Laughter]
ah that was so fun
next time i don't know when we're gonna
do it again and i don't know
which channel we're gonna do it again
and i don't know what member is but
uh let's see let's see it's
gonna be a legendary stream again next
time with some more rules
next time some more fun rules
thank you guys for helping me out on
twitter
by telling me what um
what rules you will want me to apply
ah well nothing is going to be happening
i'm looking forward to monopoly not only
i played a lot of times when i was
younger like for example
uh uh like i was to play i
there were so many different kinds of
monopolies people always are surprised
when i mentioned this before on my
stream but i played like uh lord of the
rings monopoly
we had that too did you guys never see
our lord of the rings monopoly
that's so much fun lord as the lord of
the rings bad none of the rings monopoly
was so dope
i know i don't know if they still sell
it but
pokemon monopoly what star wars monopoly
there's really anything isn't there what
kind of monopoly weird monopolies have
you played before
never saw and you got to check it out
there's a lot of the rings but not
bullying i don't know
if they're if it still looks like yeah
it's gonna hold a headphone up
fortnite i have a real there's a
fortnite monopoly what
spongebob metallica monopoly
simpsons monopoly doctor who spider-man
free monopoly oh my god there's so many
muppets really are you guys just making
up things this is for real
shrek you're lying to me there's no way
that there's a shrek
i'm gonna google that
[Laughter]
was the other one that i was so
surprised about i don't know
do you guys are not lying
yeah the four that one fortnite really
fortnite monopoly
there is i don't know i never played
fortnite but i think that's funny that
there's a fourth nine or not point
what a monopoly over everything it's
like free real estate so if there's for
everything in monopoly then we should
have a whole live monopoly what the hell
that doesn't even seem like such a
difficult thing to do
it's free real estate let's let's make
it
monitor you listening maybe maybe we
should uh tell that to the upper other
people
gemma let's let's fetch that idea to the
to the ai people to the
to the most uh to the people with power
and be like hey we need a
hold up hold up bully hold up paulie
i wonder do they play monopoly in japan
because like in japan it seems like
anything is a possibility for her life
they have like collaborations with uh
the biggest convenience stores all the
time
in japan with whole life but i wonder if
that whole life is a thing
wonder if that's a thing there
oh hold up for me
moshi moshi hasbro
[Music]
let's do it
hold on for you might be something
different oh my god let me google is
that something
what is that wayne
when i look that up it's like there's
there's already
interesting what is that
what is that it doesn't the domain name
holopoly.com is for sale don't steal it
i'm gonna i'm gonna buy it it's mine
just kidding just kidding just
just kidding
i guess i guess monopoly in japan would
just be momota
shouldn't have said it yeah oh my god i
think
someone's gonna buy that url aren't ya
okay who's gonna be
the one person who thinks they're funny
and gonna buy that url who's gonna buy
it huh
who's gonna buy holapoli.com
oh anyway we should read super chats
i'm going to check back tomorrow and see
if holopoly.com is uh available still
let's okay scrolling
scrolling scrolling
that was so much fun oh my god
it's such a simple game but anyone
understands it i mean
the thing is like for example with chess
not every country really teach like
not in every country chess is like a big
thing like you might think so because
it's a big and anyone knows it
in your country but for example in japan
most people don't know how to play chess
but uno everyone knows how to play uno
so that's fun it has fun because
everyone can watch and everyone can
understand and it's fun and easy
and you can join in anytime it doesn't
matter if you missed
first half of the stream yeah yeah japan
plays shogi but no one else knows how to
play show yeah i don't know how to play
shogi
did i read the super chats for the heart
challenger choco
street i think i did yeah probably yeah
okay
[Music]
uh
why did it break uh stupid youtube
things
i don't know why it broke maybe it will
come back later
[Music]
you know what i'm gonna i don't know
what does refresh car say of the current
page too i don't know
where it's back
is
pinkies i don't know thank you so thank
you thank you for the pinky
quite late but this is my pinky promise
buzz yeah thank you for the pink super
chat
for the best birth boss and the best
blessing i've received in years never
that i
feel as emotionally connected as i did
with you
i cherish these days with you and i
swear i won't be leaving soon thank you
that's sweet you feel connected to me
that's nice
that's i think important to have like to
feel like you can connect with
that streamer otherwise it feels like
they just live in a completely different
world i mean
i mean i live in this virtual
australia but still
i want to be close to you guys yeah
thank you so
much thank you for a red super chat
mwah and so you and kelly are both my
wife we will be
very happy together
i am first of all what the hell second
of all
i don't plan on sharing kelly so
no no
but thank you for the red super chat uh
you tried you got a sticker for trying
thank you for your support but ain't
happening that
ain't happening
thank you for the red super chat
this person is riding too so we got
kamiyah in the super jump wake up danjo
is my mom
kelly is my dad they will marry me when
i grow up
by dream of pink you cannot
you cannot marry your parents
that is just weird
no even if you send a red super chat for
your parents no
no no but you tried you get a sticker
for trying as well
i need a i need a huge ride sticker
i need a huge ride sticker please
with animation please thank you for the
red super chat though
sending me a pink super chat with uh
what is this like a what is that
what is this two her reverend kiara tv
your vassal and humble servant greetings
our seat on antioch continues
and bamboozled is on the nearest redoubt
daily fry those entering
and leaving the army nft the great
seeing this
took the army and smote 400 of the
bamboozlers
who were lying in wait drove others into
a certain river and led back some
captives
among these captives was albedo who in
grief and denial over the loss of jfp
had found his way amongst the ben losers
and fought his men restored
jesus our vulnerable vulnerable
another bishop is doing his utmost to
bring the albedo of kfp
back to us but until that day he remains
a captive of army
rest assured we will continue to besiege
antioch with all diligence
and hope soon to capture it we continue
to besiege the blessing of you our
attention
and pray we bring honor
[Applause]
[Music]
wow the lord vegans the lord is too deep
man
then lord is so freaking deep people who
don't come here often will be like what
the [\h__\h] is going on
oh my god wow
that's fun thank you asperger thank you
i couldn't join the stream yesterday so
here's my wholesale message i followed
her
live months before ian was announced and
yet you became my aussie it wasn't luck
it was all you
your hard work and your sense of humor
your kindness and your progress brighten
my day every time i won't get sick of
you duncan for everything you do first
that's good thank you that's so sweet
that makes me happy to know that you had
all these choices but you chose me thank
you
thank you thomas not thank you for the
pinky
pinky promised angel here at the
beginning here till the end not gonna
say don't ever change either because
that implies i wouldn't love you if you
did change
oh wherever you go however you grow and
change i will still be your fan i love
you oh my god come this night
why are you guys so sweet goddammit so
sweet
thank you
thank you for the thinking is it too
late to send my pinky promise i hope not
um i hereby declare my eternal loyalty
to the kfb and my undying love for
takanashikiya the phoenix
till my body is reclaimed by this earth
viva
wow you guys are so passionate i love it
thank you
thank you oh my god holy macaroni
wow thank you that's everyone oh my god
i feel the love wow thank you
chat reflects streamer
[Music]
it does doesn't it
sorry for making you worry i'm fine now
i just had some emergencies i had to
deal with
uh your concern was touching thanks you
here's the pinky promise i forgot
yesterday i'll gladly
be behind you on this journey till the
very end no matter what
yay thank you let's go far together
let's go thank you i'm glad you're
feeling better
hope it stays that way ellis
stanley hopkins duncan today's my
birthday oh i guess so yesterday
happy birthday to stanley hopkins
and sorry that i yeah even though you
write that you
love my new automata place i'm sorry i
couldn't play it probably yesterday that
was
sad i was looking forward to it i'm
really into the game to be honest i
really want to
continue the story um as fast as
possible
like i want to do it like in like not
with too much time in between
um yeah thank you for the membership
tassie josh thank you account name thank
you
introducing the new machine burger when
it's time only it can't
be right i don't know i wasn't i'm not
sure what machine burger i wonder what
you were talking about there
some kind of machine obviously in the
stream
oh wait you're just saying
we should sell machine burgers no
no no because no that's not gonna be
i mean no matter how many barbecue
barbecue sauce you pour over that
no did i miss the game yeah but i'm
going to read super chat and then you
can watch the archive
it was fun it's worth watching the
archive
nail matrix 7777
happy birthday to you too birthday
birthday hey i'm looking forward to my
birthday with you guys
still a long time to go but
you're not lagging you're just
approaching the perfection that is
cardboard kiara
oh my god machine burgers aren't yummy
but need for our chickens and eggs i
swear please let my people
i don't know what you're talking about
we don't eat chickens
and eggs at kfp it's in the name
chiato fried phoenix it's in the name we
don't eat chicken
otherwise we would be kfc kiara fried
chicken but we are kiana fred phoenix
okay so
whether shut your mouth or you get put
into the usual room
thank you for the thinking
okay i will literally come to your house
and fix your pc for you lmao you need a
dedicated tech person or something
yeah um if it continues like that and i
don't know
what to do about it even after trying
out everything on my own i'm probably
gonna ask one of my
um close friends here uh who's really
good with pc
who put my pc back together um
i'm going to ask that person i guess and
to see maybe maybe maybe that person can
help
but i hope i can just fix it myself
without the kneel problems but
i saw i saw um some advice that you guys
gave me on twitter and i'll
i'll try those um next week or maybe
before next week
watson can help but watson is not here
and i don't want to annoy
once and she has her own things to do i
don't annoy her with my pc problems
um but yeah it's better if someone is
like actually here you know
a stream about i'm educating kiara and
her tech
no i don't even i don't even know
like i don't even know where to start
there i don't think she knows either
she would she would have to be like here
i think to see what's going on
um and but thank you for the pinky
ellie's move
skill page thank you soon school page
thank you soon thank you again
yeah thank you thank you guys uh i'm a
bit relieved to hear that it's not
not necessarily my pc's fault but more
like the pc port
fault of the game thank you dan michael
tandanka
lock stress
is
thank you everyone for sending my um
ideas in the super chats thank you thank
you
i think right now i i don't really have
to read them because we're not
playing it anymore anyway but yeah i'll
take a good look
later thank you for the membership
junkie
thank you soon
[Applause]
we couldn't be helpful it's okay sorry
that i got so frustrated
and screamed and cried
sorry yeah it was very frustrating
i hate technical issues i just want
things to work is it too much to ask
to have things just work how your eyes
this pretty oh chris
during your flirt
it's hooker papa's fault he drew me this
pretty hmm
is your hair did you just hear my gulp
did you hear it again
yeah goddammit i gotta turn like the the
pick up a little bit
um higher since you don't hear my gloves
that's embarrassing
yes it was sexy oh no
oh no
with no text to it though but i
appreciate the support
and the generous donation very much
thank you thank you always for being
there and always supporting me
thank you soon bread
of beats
thank you for the pinky virtual hugs do
you think you really needed them but
thank god i have my cats now for moments
like these
if that happened in japan i guess i
could have at least asked the
genma to come over and help me
but i wouldn't have any fluffy cats to
instantly
like put my face on guys
last night oh my god like so we we named
uh
the other cat for stream purpose uh
smoothie right
and smoothie oh she's getting so
i told you guys before she's getting so
affectionate but it's not stopping like
last night
the whole night she was sleeping
on top of my head like
like literally her body was touching my
my head while i was sleeping
she was sleeping there for the whole
night it was so freaking
sweet i'm so happy
yeah she really likes that spot
like um it's like this big pillow
comfy pillow did i sleep against like i
don't really use that pillow i use
another pillow but i sleep against that
big pillow
so like she lays on that big pillow
which is like right like on top of my it
makes her
like lie right on fro on top of my head
like
like in front like touching my head like
she's not
she's not exactly resting her whole body
on my head but like
a little bit of it yeah
i'm so shocked because like she used to
be like
i mean she liked me always but when i
when i before i left for japan for a
year she was still like kind of like
she would only um she would never come
like she would sleep
with me in my bed but she would always
be like an arm's length distance away
from me
and um she
wasn't so attached like crazy attached
as she is now
and they've always been very only
attached to me but
it's crazy now they really i think she
missed me
hmm that makes me really happy
and i didn't get catch that fly also i
did i bought the
i bought the vinegar it's not working
though
they don't they don't fly into it did i
do it wrong maybe i put more vinegar i
don't know
i filled up like a third of a glass with
vinegar
and some like um washing
washing thingy it's not working do i
have to
homemade drops now but i i would think
vinegar would work am i saying
wrong or why you guys making fun of my
vin wow
that's that's how you say it shut up
should i just get a proper fly job but i
don't know those things are like
uh like super like expensive for what
they actually do i feel like vinegar
should do the trick
vinegar vinegar vinegar
is it vinegar is it like that vinegar
shut up that's how we stayed in
australia it's australian
accent maybe i put it in like i want to
put it away
from my cats i mean i can't reach it but
maybe i should put it lower to the
monitor
oh well
yeah barely any difference
barely any difference just use lemon
juice
anyway
thank you
is that a song move your body every
everybody wait it's not iphone 65
reference okay
i'm so sorry you sent a pinky and i
don't understand the reference
i'm so sorry
[Music]
but it seems like these lyrics are
different yeah
i agree but i also don't understand
backstreet's bad all right
thank you for the pinky doll
[Music]
watermelon by the way in summer oh my
god
i'll be eating so much watermelon
whenever it's summer i eat so much
so much watermelon
you know what's awesome being like at
the lake or at the ocean
inside for a swim
in your swimsuit and then with your
friends and you bring watermelon
and eat watermelon together oh that's so
nice
oh my cat is missing me
and thank you don't worry about it i'm
gonna check i saw you tweet the the one
of the nine tweets
uh with the instructions and i'll try it
out
thank you for testing it out thank you
even using obs
so that it's like recreated thank you
johnny johnny 2023 thank you
chlorine and translation
oh sorry i didn't copy it no
no yeah
is not letting you stream smoothly we
can always just chat as long as you're
happy thank you
the little minecraft session afterwards
was fun so that was okay
we had a chat and played some minecraft
you guys saw me farming quartz for a
little while
song was all fun that was that was okay
that cheered me up i was really
pissed off but that cheered me up thanks
for hanging with me
man one five one four thank you for a
red super chat
keep on trucking nintendo give them the
old number free special of the extra
crispy fries
is that a reference to something too
is that a reference
the old number three special of extra
crispy fries
hmm
a nice quartz statue of tanjo good idea
no no no okay i guess it's not
guess it's not huh
anyway thank you thank you for the
support thank you very much
i'll do my best thank you for believing
in me and thank you for supporting me
g-man
thank you soon iceborn demon thank you
for the pinky
your local demon just wants you to be
happy please don't fret over the game we
just want
you to be happy funny because uh you
know to be
and near automata
thank you thank you soon welcome
soon
yeah honestly listen to you fight this
boss as a podcast without seeing what's
happening it's just as entertaining
yeah whenever when we actually we're
fighting the bus uh you youtube didn't
let people see it um
so we were just doing but but you could
you could hear me for people who don't
understand
i'm explaining for them uh
you could you were able to hear with no
problems but you were not
able to see anything so i was just doing
near automata
boss fight asmr
top notch account name
skill skill page thank you soon
the fight is too intense it is not meant
for the mortal eyes tenzio it may be
your responsibility to describe the
fight to your employees
i did i did and i think i did well thank
you very much
thank you for your support thank you
soon thank you for watching even though
it was such a scarf
really i appreciate that so much
most people just leave i think
when they
this is because it was such a chat delay
you're the only one that can save us you
must this
this cannot continue i'm so sorry that
robot voice is so loud
why is it so loud this cannot continue
kiara may not play this game anymore
this cannot continue we must make her
stop playing
near automata she will reveal the truth
about everything
she will become as god no we have to
stop harry that's my real words by the
way
didn't i sound like a robot just now
robo kiana
robert roberto roberto
and jason
[Music]
sorry things didn't work out kiara today
you seem really happy when the stream
started and i hope you're doing better
now really hope you don't give up on you
though i'm really enjoying the play
through
and hope that everyone's wrong is an
easy fix yeah i really don't want to
give up
yeah i am i must find a way i must i
don't want to give up
i will find a way do you know that way
where there is a will then there is a
way so i will find it
thank you thank you for the support we
got for free eleven thank you
thank you maybe do what you did with
fire emblem and make the archive members
oh yeah yeah i wanted to do that but
then i
uh realized because you guys told me
that minecraft um
cannot be put behind the paywall uh
so i made the i undid it and now it's
just completely private
but the people who were there um i did
say you're you're
allowed to make clips out of it so
that's okay
uh just don't don't re-upload the whole
stream to youtube
please thank you small cookie bear dream
there's really not much
fun thing and things in that stream
anyway so it's not worth
uploading the whole thing crazy and
lizard wizard
and residency
monkey thank you soon skill pace thank
you
and fight guys thank you brandon welcome
sorry that i'm skipping everyone's pc
advices uh i just uh
i don't think it makes sense to read
them all now
and but thank you i appreciate it all
very very much i'll do my best to find
the solution
and come back with perfectly running
near automata
soon
and joshua fox
i'm a little late but here's my pinky
attenuate our future days be blessed
with your radiant glow
of kitties love you dancing i have been
here since the start and will stay as
long as this world allows me to
viva la quiara thank you
dusty thank you
you've been here since the start it must
be fun to watch
someone you know really for that long
time and really see them
you know grow and improve and all that
must be fun to
to follow all of that
thank you for supporting me for over
half a year thank you i'll do my best in
the future as well
thank you very much looking for the top
donkey shane el cano we are with uncle
sharon character
dr thank you thank you for the pinky
thank you for the stream strong
potential thank you for watching
thank you really everyone who was there
thank you so much this little real thank
you for a rant of attack
please donate to choose to a
hard-working actual i.t staff of kfp
so like uh i think they love 67 could be
one of those
but he already gets enough kisses on his
own also the chat stopped for me
he already gets enough kisses i don't
know who deserves this because i'm just
gonna throw them in the air and you guys
aren't going to catch them
i don't know the chat stop for me did
you get them did you get them
catch them
the more people trying to give advice
the worse it gets uh oh wait
where i moved my eyes moved to the wrong
line that was a different super chat
uh popping back to get some curse
limited edition near craft content
crowdsourcing i see the advice from chat
gets versus probably gets more
open-ended
don't feel like you need to listen to it
well i mean but i know that there are
many people who write like wrong things
but
i like in the moment like when i'm
streaming and i'm like super stressed
out because of tech issues
i i just hope i in that moment i feel
like
i just need help and and there must be
someone who knows what they're talking
about so i just
you know try to get quick advice from
as fast as possible from there
so
yeah i mean but what else am i gonna do
like i gotta try out some things i gotta
try it out
there's nothing i can do i have to try
it out
better than being like okay it doesn't
work end of the stream i'm not
even going to try to fix it i have to
try to fix it so
um anyway for a future new year streams
i'm probably gonna
like when i test it out i'm probably
going to be um
streaming like test streaming i feel
like
just doing it unlisted like private test
streaming should work too but
i might make it public because i don't
know maybe maybe um
the unlisted private streaming just to
myself
doesn't doesn't put as much pressure on
my pc as it would do
if i test stream openly i don't know
i don't know if that makes any sense
also let me turn on the lights of my
room and
uh wait brandon welch or welch thank you
soon for super chat
and as a fellow actually i think person
hard agree with dyslexia the more people
trying to give advice towards it yes but
we will be here for you
so even on the days you want to burn
your pc
thank you yeah but as i said i just want
to try it out you know
so i'll turn on the lights and we
finished reading the new automata
superchat so next up we will be reading
the uno super chats one second
no no no catboy i only gave them five
stats
only only padded them five times store
hello gotta say hello yeah so that they
know that i still love them and i'm
even though i'm talking to a weird
object in the room that they don't
understand what it is even
even then they're the most important to
me only five should i get them more
i'll give it to them later um you know
uh it shouldn't be
shouldn't be that much
oh no wait actually they are a lot
oh wow wow wow wow
well we will we'll we'll go for it
we'll be fine well we're going somewhere
quickly
looking for the top tanker chains lying
down looking for the top tanker
general piccolo and naga thank you i
think that's a red super chat baby
thank you and thank you soon
kiana before i forget you are not boring
you are a joy to watch no matter what
oh remember your core audience is here
for you and not for the game or whatever
so relax to enjoy so we can enjoy you
now i need to remember to not to akka
spell my savings
so i suppose this is a red super chat it
doesn't show the color to me
by the way so yeah wow thank you
yeah i'm glad to have my core audience
who's always here you know
thank you it's it's a big relief
oh very reassuring
like a like a like a safe zone
like somehow you know it makes me a bit
sad that my rpg streams have such a low
viewership but then again
the people who are there it feels like
such a safe place
because i know the people that are at my
rpg
serious streams that those are the
people who really really really really
love
me and makes me so happy to be with them
it's like we're hanging out having some
fun
chilling together um it's like
some quality time with my
with my cuties with my cute chickens
so thank you guys king mufasa
the chat stopped again for me but
i'm sure it'll be bad is this stream
like lagging for you guys
or is it just a chat being weird hey i'm
keeping some bottle
thank you thank you for the rest of the
chat
[Music]
um
am i still streaming fine
is my stream okay
huh
answering me
what
right
oh it's a bag
oh okay because now instead that my chat
lost its connection even
everyone okay
oh good okay i see it again i see
it i thought i lost you oh my god
oh my god okay okay
wow okay i'm back i'm back
is it my internet is on youtube i wonder
um
[Music]
hi back
and may i request a birthday song from
muah from my favorite big bread
of birthday kisses that antiquate my age
now 24 years and still kicking would
also like to thank you and all of her
life for what you do but orange
is my favorite color for a reason
thank you thank you
so you even want 24 kisses or a birthday
song
[Music]
well baby sanders said special message i
didn't see it no is there something new
okay uh let me sing for you
let me sing for you seth blackburn happy
birthday
to you since it's a red super chat i'm
singing otherwise no singing happy
birthday
to you happy birthday dear self
happy birthday to you
now thank you hope you had a lovely
birthday
watching us play uno must
i mean it must have felt like a birthday
party somehow
and hope you will live
long long and stay very healthy and
make all your dreams and goals come true
yeah
noise thank you for your support
jason dreamstockish and bradley thank
you
i love how a lot of people believed in
me winning but i didn't win a single
time
you really expected freedom god of
amiibo thank you
while the jackson died oh my god they're
betting on people on the super shots
well the jacksonville a dirty tristana
thank you steven thank you sn thank you
[Music]
and every other kfp employees that will
that believe in you
you are lucky order i'm sorry for
disappointing you oh
i didn't win a single time
oh
you won my heart
your winner in our hearts oh you went
over my heart
come on guys
time next time but hey um honestly
i didn't need to win it was just fun fun
times run times with
my friends and and you guys
that's all i needed faithful reduction
oh another korean name that i cannot
read is that the same one as before
no how do i say that
thank you soon
xbox
one felix style thank you for the pinky
morning time to hope you guys have fun
playing all together thank you yeah lots
of fun
yeah let's do it again
i'm i'm really sorry to ahmed but like
basically i was like
i i didn't invite them one by one
directly i just i just went into our
discord i was like okay who wants to
join uno we can only have four players
and then you know the girls were like me
me me one after another
uh and then i was like ah i'm busy
anyway so
you guys do your thing so it was not
like i
i i like um chose to not have alma in it
it wasn't like i didn't want her
to participate yeah
because i think she's moving right so
that's one of the reasons
why she sat out this time
yeah next time next time there's always
a next time
there's so many collabs that we can
still do um
show them what the power of a phoenix of
a legion of loyal employees look like
this hurts reading it after losing so
gloriously
reading these super chats of people
betting on me and supporting me
and believing in me streets
my parents i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
not lu thank you for a red super chat a
bit late but thank you for introducing
me to leaving on a jail plane now i have
another sound that instantly makes
me dr cry good luck on una oh you liked
the song you found
liking it because i sang it on my
unarchived karaoke history of kelly
awesome i wonder have you listened to
the to the
female copper version because that's the
one i prefer
uh there's that the original
but there's also a female combo version
that's very popular
and that's the one that i like
thank you thank you yeah from chantal
crevia however you pronounce that name
look it up if you didn't know it yet
you're welcome that was uh it's indeed a
beautiful song that has followed me
my whole life yeah
so i'm glad you like it thank you thank
you eritos defeated
sacred uh sacred edge thank you mike
l v raiders
[Music]
i was swearing so much even as a baby
i couldn't hold back even as a baby
it's my reflexes
but i mean it makes sense because like
as i said as a baby
my argument was callie is my mama and
she
uh she swears in her songs and all that
so i listen to that as a baby obviously
you're gonna you're gonna pick that up
oh not my fault whoopee thank you
sanchez
thank you sgs
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
you're only supposed to play well draw
fours
yeah i was asking about that like
yesterday
i was playing uh to test out the game i
was playing against pcs
and i didn't understand the challenging
thing at all but okay i never knew that
you're only supposed to draw
to play that when you don't have
anything else if a challenge you're
saying
you think the person could have played
another card
now i know the more you know thank you
thank you thank you for explaining now i
know apparently no one in our
girls team knew oh nice that's what also
surprised me
no one knew is that such an unknown
thing does everyone play
the game without knowing that
interesting that crap yeah it's been
really bad
it's been really really bad
mama do you know korean no i don't
but there was this one show like even
though i don't know any korean and have
never visited korea
and i have absolutely no connection with
it i
watched this like there was a time when
i was like so
addicted to this one show um that they
uploaded like
pretty long clips off on youtube um
this korean show where there's like like
somewhat famous people
with uh babies like that the the men
would take care
of the of their baby alone without the
mom
uh for like i think 20 24 no longer than
24 hours i think
yeah return on the superman yeah yeah i
was so addicted to that show
because it was so cute and it made me i
don't know it made me feel so
fuzzy inside like oh my god these
children these babies are so
cute and i don't understand what they're
saying but
there were subtitles anyway so that was
nice
it was so cute yeah
that was a fun show they had like a
million episodes so i never watched all
of it but
oh it was such a cute show
have you i see there's some people who
know what i'm talking about
[Music]
that's my mom's favorite tv show along
with the running man i don't know
running man but
your mom's favorite to me so
baby and baby and at least those babies
are not swearing as much as i do
those are all really good babies
well-behaved babies
disciplined babies
thank you for the pinky at this point
the ian branch
really looks like a sitcom family we
have kelly as the sleepy mother kiara as
the quirky auntie normally i'm the
mother and
and callie is a dad have you missed out
on something
okay you know it's the common the nice
eldest sibling
with almond being the snacky one in the
middle and good at the cute baby of the
bunch
we're not the cute baby of the bunch
oh [\h__\h]
guna is evil yeah a grandma
but guna can be very salty and like like
i can imagine her like
uh having like
funny fights with siblings so
i don't think she's just the cute baby
okay
the halo is a bit broken okay
um we're all happy big happy family
the fighting makes it fun
good eye is a jack of all trades yeah
yeah yeah kelly's a good father figure
[Music]
no i guess so
today she was my mama though because i
old japanese didn't have different words
for blue and green that is so
weird that's two completely different
colors
how long is that a goat how old is that
in fact
tweets my email on the other camera side
i want to see it wait later
let's see
long long oh my god
oh my god
what's going on i understand
i understand
all right so that was that was uh cali
and gooda
oh and now it's only me left you know
what i'm gonna do it now because she
sent me one to tweet
but it's gonna look around in the
timeline because the head comes first
for me and then
kelly's tail and now comes the middle
from me everyone checks with her
it's wrong this is wrong
check twitter everyone i've done my part
i love it this is fun
i was also thinking a little bit about
like you know um
the end battle game the end punishment
game could also be something like
have to um put
um a profile picture on twitter that the
winner chooses
and for example if it would be good ass
you could give us like really really
cute scuffed scribbles of our faces
and we have to use that for like 24
hours that would have been fun too
like they decide on what our profile
picture looks like maybe next time we
can have that uh
it was it wasn't me
tackle his lungs wait oh yes
it's i guess it's supposed to be long
taco is long that tango is long
scuffed it's scuffed
it's so scuffed
it's scuffed enough
it told us what order but maybe this was
uh on purpose as well to have it scuffed
and
chaotic taco is long long
cute okay continuing myself
yeah i'm curious about the blue and
green thing
how long has it been like that you tried
i didn't try that's the thing surprise
mar the fat card
so
[Music]
wow
i hope my roommate wasn't listening to
this
[Laughter]
sucker thank you for the pinkie
thank keep being so good to us in the
girls thank you
thank you i love you too thank you for
watching
hope you enjoyed it space guy right
thank you for the pinkie this is the
best room i've ever seen we need more
competitive halloween yeah we do
you guys should do the monopoly on
gameplay oh definitely oh we will
definitely
have monopoly because that we got
permission for it the moment i saw it on
our list i was like uh-huh
[\h__\h] yes oh my god we got monopoly
[\h__\h]
and i think it's six six um up to six
little six uh people uh
players so keanu training and twitter no
way
you know why and which country
is it really me well not play as brutal
or can be
i mean i don't even like i don't i used
to play monopoly with my family
i was earlier training in philippines
what
why why wow thank you
the name kiana is running
[Music]
it's up to six people but i'm sure we
can only play into five people anyway i
was i used to play monopoly with my
family and it was never like
was never like people we didn't have
fights or so over it it was always like
um how to say
uh
i'm looking for a specific word
civilized civilized
but who knows i mean honestly uno like
i was i was uh picking fights with the
girls on purpose
so for monopoly i'm going to do the same
and jose here
endless baby round eternal
m internal phoenix now i am a general
baby
don't lie then danke says from distant
thank you
wait i cannot read this name let me let
me translate
eugene bientai
um
in japanese it's called yuri
after that magician that i was talking
about
so much when i asked about him in the
stream most people didn't know what i
was talking about only the japanese
people were like reacting
but most of you guys didn't know who i
was talking about oh
they did
he sued them over wait they didn't have
his permission
wouldn't he be happy about it
he sued
what they did not ask him about it i
guess they made just a pun
on the name probably like they didn't
officially give him that exact name
to the pokemon but just like
it was only recently he gave permission
what
[Music]
that's a huge big kusa there oh
that is funny
it seems oh my god that's so funny
what say the night shade
once i was just a shrimp before but i'm
an entdd now thank you
i cannot read your name once again let
me
translate this one too
[Music]
i just copy whatever google google tells
me how to pronounce it
dragon 97
youtube only let me donate half of what
i wanted to the other day
here is the other half thank you again
are you sure yeah what
thank you wow
is it what is it okay is it okay to
accept it
really is it for me
you didn't because it's a collab you
didn't want to like
send it to the other girls thinking that
like it's gonna be shared or something
right is it okay
he's in the chat really
i see him of course it's great really
really do you want me to share with the
girls
that's usually not how it works even for
collabs but wow thank you
wow it's for me this for me is it really
for me
wow thank you so much for your support
lots of kisses
[Laughter]
that's a huge support i appreciate it
i'm gonna invest it into
my my you know technical things and my
youtube things and all that and
microphones and then
all that kind of stuff i'm gonna use it
wisely thank you very much
wow thank you for the generosity
and thank you for watching my streams
more than anything
thank you hopefully you will
continue watching my streams forever and
ever and ever and ever and ever
ever thank
[Music]
kfb investment going stocks
wow so much for bitcoin huh
just kidding i don't know anything about
that kind of stuff we should have
no idea david gonzalez
sacred edge danke soon secret simple
contaction lord reverend
a soul survived mr caspian
yeah yeah i wasn't playing with yeah
exactly to be fair about you when
playing with an
xbox controller for those jumping small
great stream yeah i don't even have an
xbox controller i was playing with a
playstation controller and like
the game only shows you the buttons for
the xbox you can't even change any
controls either you cannot remap them
it seems unless like i didn't see an
option
but my uno didn't come with an xbox
though i had the wrong controller
so i always i always press the wrong
buttons because
i couldn't remember the right buttons at
all that's so rough oh my god like why
is that
why is that okay button on the very left
but then also the lower button was also
the ok button sometimes
that was so confusing
now it's so confusing
if i would have gotten those buttons
reds maybe i would have won
in a different dimension in a different
timeline
uh good game oh thank you for the pinky
by the way good game thank you for this
collab you guys are the best oh i think
we're
getting closer to the end thank you
thank you for watching
yeah it was an amazing collab this is
one that will be in the history books in
the future
and ho live uh ian
generation two that we're not supposed
to call generation two but i don't know
what else to call it
will tell uh
no way we will tell them about these
tales yes yes yes yes
i'm glad you guys had some laughs
hopefully
during these dark dark times out there
i'm glad i could
arrange something nice no actually this
collab was planned kind of
recently i started just blending it last
week so
and for next week or the week after i
have something big coming up too
but first of all like tomorrow i think i
have a day off and then the day after
tomorrow i have a collab with vada my
senpai that was gonna be
fun too we're just playing clubhouse
games but i just feel like
doubles games is just such an easy game
to collab with someone
so bear with me and it would probably
be mostly japanese but i'm gonna try to
get some english out of vata
senpai and maybe translate a little bit
but it will probably mostly be japanese
so look out for those translators in the
chat
look out for the translators
yeah finally mata mikko now
you bring out the best in everyone
except yourself because i did not need
to know about the soiling stuff
i was just joking i was just joking
way i was being a good baby
thank you
uh i'm glad to hear that though that i
bring out the personality one and it
makes me happy thank you
zombie donkey apparel
not to king shame you cannot but for the
love of god stop talking about your scat
fetish
oh my god
i don't like poop i understand a joke
okay i don't like poop
which scat means poop right
that's what it means right i don't
actually know for sure
i'm just going to suppose it does
glitch master 767
thank you for watching
red super chat oh
options
marry kiss side girl pet booba punch
what punch in the boobs and spank oh my
god
so punching the boobs i don't want to do
that to anyone
and the candidates are inaccurate
so what bubba punch is it doesn't mean
bunch of boobs or a punch in it and what
into what
that hurts can i not do that
that's like it's so rude that's so
aggressive
that's so extreme i i will i will not do
that often
no pulling the blings boys are blessed
things on this world i don't want to
hurt them no matter
who the person is ah guna doesn't have
any so it will be okay
oh i
guess so is it okay to booba punch
i don't know about that
okay okay well
mary callie kiss
kiss inside girl huh
psycho like an affair i don't really
want to have an affair
but this is difficult
and so mary kelly
side girl ahmed kiskura
what pets does it mean to pet someone or
make that person into my pants
wait there's piccolo why does this
that's too difficult what the hell
okay since i since i'm not using bubba
puns i'm gonna
double double on kiss maybe
okay cali mary
who's gonna get this bag though i mean
it must be moon up
i mean because i'm not gonna kiss muna
okay
and i'm not gonna marry muna but this is
just a rude like if i say i'm gonna
spank
muda everyone's gonna be like wow kia i
hate smoona
so much oh my god you're putting me into
a difficult situation
that's a really difficult situation okay
you just want to make drama out of this
why did you have to include peculiar
moon on there why could it not just be
halloween
um i'm just gonna do nothing
okay the spank is not gonna be used in
the booba punch it's not gonna i'm sorry
i'm sorry
punchiness you would like it no why what
the hell
i doubt it well
you got some answers and those must be
enough answers thank you
thank you thank you spaniards back to
food soup each other spank for
chad thunder boobs spank
my cat just she was sleeping at the
at the clap she was like
sorry smoothie
i'm going to be quiet again
monochromatic duncan i'm saying ready
still thank you
that was super fun thank you for all the
hard work trying to get this collab
screen you're welcome i feel like you
know
someone has gotta organize these collabs
because clubs are just so much fun to
see like the interactions be
in between people and other than that
you know the other
young girls don't seem to plan that many
like
collabs except like one-on-one collabs
but like more than two people collapse
they don't really
the girls don't seem to plan that much
on their own
so i'm taking that position i'm the i'm
the
winning planner no i'm the clown planner
it's my job
it's fun though it's fun but there's
just not so many games that you can play
with five members so that really sucks
but wait oh my god guys i have to tell
you
um after you guys mentioning it to me
many many many many many many times as a
collab option
i have requested a permission for it and
i have received permission
for uh jack box party games
which gives us i think i never played
that but you guys always
told us to play that so i think now we
have like a million more options oh you
guys are excited i don't even know like
i don't
i don't understand jackpots party games
i don't know what it like what's in
there
i don't i don't get it but we got
permission
yeah is it is it like uh
uh it's like it's like the the the 51
clubhouse games just with more games and
different games
allows the audience to play okay but can
you play without the audience too
we could do like a full member collab on
that
different stuff like trivia cool yes you
can yes you can you can play without
audience oh cool
where you can play with audience too
that's cool though
oh
it's going to be good yeah so many more
options maybe next holo and collab
ufo mama collab will be in jackpots
games who knows or monopoly
or monopoly light audience participation
to vote on stuff
okay hey we can vote on stuff and
interact the squad
no one is going to ruin it yeah we might
just want to test it out without
audience and then you know once we get
the hang of it we might
i'm i might just play with audience at
some point um
is it something like among us where you
can just you know play
on stream alone and just have the
audience join in
is it something like that or can you do
something like that too
yeah not really yeah not really
audience only but like can i like open
like a lobby and then people will join
in
like with among us
and then we play random games or so i
don't know i gotta take a look at it
it's more of a boat thing okay
interesting interesting
okay yeah i'm gonna test it out that's
so cool though
okay cool look forward to it
i'm so glad we got permission for that
as a quiz because as i said it's so
difficult to find games
that you can play with like five members
so difficult
that i mean games that we also have
permission for but even then it's like
even without permissions there's not
much choice
continuing um monochromatic dancing
wait wait was i was already i already
read those oopsies so yeah alex thank
you again
motion function that is slacker
jokes doing very well in fact i record
ah that's the special message you guys
talked about
i recorded a very special message from
him that i sent you on twitter it
surprised us so much
yay i'm gonna look at it i hope it
didn't
i hope i can't find it in in my millions
of replies
you know what i'm turning off the super
chats now and then read the rest
okay turn it off
reading refreshing
refreshing i'm so hungry guys i kind of
want to
get it done and come with my cats
priorities food food food
food food
i want food
[Applause]
[Music]
you're going to eat your cat no i'm
going to eat
and cuddle with my cats
baby sunday maybe
guys can someone tell me why i'mma
didn't join today on a stream it's only
four players
not everyone can join unfortunately
really sad but
yes and i once again i'm gonna explain i
i asked in our group discord who wants
to join
and everyone said me me me and then
ahmed was like i'm busy anyway so you
girls go ahead
okay next time emma will be there i'm
going with muted
now next time i will be there don't
worry don't worry
it's not like we're um how to say that i
can't think of the word it's not like
we're blocking her out of
our group or something like that there
there is no group we're a whole lot of
english we are
we are five members but just sometimes
sometimes there's a
times when it can't be five members
sometimes it's four members
excluding thank you that's what i was
trying to say thank you
master 101 thank you so much
the heart of the cards was not revealed
but amazing fun many loves and such
thank you for putting this together
oh thank you for watching it was fun
thank you
[Music]
roger where has you started since 2016.
where you gonna buy it
where are you going to buy it
account name where you gonna buy it
don't tell me you were gonna buy it
it was so much fun to watch thank you
attention looking forward to the
monopoly club
me too me too i love monopoly so much
yeah
excited for that and also yeah next time
we also got to play uno um flip
the the one where you see the coins it's
gonna be interesting too
i i was like when i i never knew i knew
i never knew about the existence of that
game
until i was looking for steam and i
thought well it makes the game so much
easier what's fun about that
but then you guys were like oh uno flip
is so much fun it's so
so mean and so crazy
but like how i don't understand
how yeah it has two side clients right
it shows on the other side what
what looking through strength
through stinks two side cards yeah it
shows what cards you have and then you
can flip it sometimes with another card
so that they don't sing
i guess it's oh it's not always the same
so you you can yes but it's not
guaranteed that that's really the card
that they have
uh the other side is always a different
card
or only sometimes are they always
different than what's the mean
then what uses that then that's the same
as having no
nose other side at all
oh wait it's uh is it like decided like
uh
each four like each red four it will
always be like a
green five or something like that
you aren't playing two sets of cards
what
you can win on both sides what
what wait that sounds crazy wait okay i
don't i don't i don't understand i agree
but i don't understand
[Music]
i have to check that out
i don't understand that's that's already
confusing
okay and thank you moose
look forward to future monopoly collabs
nobody mother
[Music]
uh hi today is my friend's birthday and
he really likes you very much i hope you
can wish him a
happy birthday his name is lee yonde
happy birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you
happy birthday dearly on day happy
birthday to you
angel vasquez
thank
what the [\h__\h] i'm sitting here in my jfb
penthouse apartment in the middle of new
york eating cabinetry and definitely not
capturing
he's just lying that's what someone
would say who's captured
yeah he's just lying no way he's eating
copier
they don't have caviar in new york do
they
just play along just play along they
don't have caviar in new york
so it's happy
mother content thank you for the pinky
machine burgers aren't yummy but never
to add that one
i will not let my people glove because
we don't eat chicken anyway
no need to worry
why wouldn't they have carry don't
question it just play along
how are you supposed to deny copy i know
you just just saying don't have it
you guys are so good with acting and
playing along this lore
but then now you're failing with it what
the hell you guys are supposed to be
good at this you guys are good at improv
and one thing that i know about the kfp
workers is that they're good at improv
now don't fail on me now
don't question it
what happened to my usual improv buddies
huh
who's acting no no one's actually wrong
these are real
real pirates thank you for the pinky
yellow red gummy red blue gummy orange
green gummy thanks for a funny morning
what i did not regret waking up 7am
today just for uno now i listen to super
chat reading and wait for my co-workers
to get online
what's the beginning about thank you
darling good morning to you
it should be uh what 8 a.m or something
like that now
for you good morning well that's if that
isn't a great way to work out a wake up
then i don't know what is
mo don't count them thank you for
another pinky you deserve a kiss now
you've been sending so many pinkies and
these are like pretty pretty much one
after another room
[Music]
i've never seen you give up a wing for
kiara for phoenix
do i need to silence mutosan
he's trying to expose me
make super chat stream separate i just
want to watch the vlog
no
have patience i'm already almost done
i'll get you
also these are the way the real fun is
at
as many of my viewers say
you may want to consider that for the
future
no i do it my way sometimes i do
separate
um super chat reading streams
sometimes i do but
no what account names depth collector
thank you soon
my resume thank you soon thank you igor
two years ago a doctor told me i was
about to die
i worked hard to get healthy and last
week i got off my meds
i'm glad i got to live to hear your
voice and joining me thank you for all
that you do boss oh my god i'm glad too
and i'm so proud of you for like
getting back on track you know
good job
[Applause]
life is worth it so make the best out of
it
enjoy life watch whole life
enjoy whole life but also enjoy the real
life
thank you i'm so happy to hear that
you are amazing you are strong keep on
doing what you do you're doing it right
um
thank you for your support the rejected
cat dankeshan
um two names in a row that i cannot read
ah
yeah and
pump
h greetings back to switzerland
thank you for the thinking i speak for
all cafe when we say we'll always be
together forever and never to fight
oh you guys gonna marry each other
together forever we do and don't you
know we
would move heaven on and earth to be
together forever of you yes it comes
wow okay wow you really want to be
together with us
what's your problem why was this collab
exclusive to your channel
because it was my idea and i organized
it
and because this game doesn't need four
perspectives
people wouldn't be complaining about
super chat reading if you just let one
of the other channels stream
the una collab no it was not necessary
so
chill for games where there are
uh each perspective of each player
necessary we play on each
channel but it's not necessary for this
one
and if you don't like that the fact that
it's on my channel then
you don't have to be on my channel
my channel my rules my stream my rules
this is kfp this is the way we do it
so stop complaining thank you
sam envy 15.
[Music]
jaywalking
thank you jaywalker
yeah five to eight hours uh for the rpg
streams is indeed a long time so
i understand that people can also just
not watch it because of time issues
yeah that is true
thank you jingle speedos thank you
like wrangling cats now around wrangling
cats is a little bit different
damn it bad is like the present
tense and past tense same thing
cyrux mr caspian finlay maloney tubs
[Music]
uh how much money do you want not to do
the baby
what's your problems my new
why
[Music]
what's your problem huh stop please
what's your problem
piano baby is cute okay
max out my sub accounts if you stop baby
talking
wait what does it what does that mean
you want me to stop or not
ah
you know you don't want me to be baby
why not i want to repaint me i want to
be
cute baby i want to be cute
like lunas i'm fine no no no
why won't you let me be baby
i'm gonna do a whole stream being a baby
sometime soon
like mine said if i did a stream on
being a grandma
i'm gonna be a baby yes
sir against monkey duncan
well he's asking for it with a pinky
what can i do
what
um
i need my milk mama where's my milk
give me milk
baby and why
baby bump
i am sorry
he asked for it he asked for it i'm
sorry
i'm sorry i'm just fulfilling people's
dreams okay
and then following you into your dreams
and never leaving you alone ever again
needs to learn that true gacha could
accept her moshi no matter what even if
she swallows her pants
i didn't criticize potential
after the sims war and i won't start now
well why thank you how
how nice of you
why thank you patrick
so that's it guys uh
we can end the stream so that the babies
can stop crying
um about
not being able to watch the archive dear
lord have some patience oh my god
you guys are going to live like what not
18 18 19 years depending on how much
alcohol you're drinking
and how much uh cigarettes you're
smoking
maybe 17 i don't know but you think you
can't wait like one hour for me to read
super chats and then what's your archive
you think you got
and ain't got no time for that what what
the hell
you got so much time so much time
so yeah anyway thank you everyone for
watching this fun fact
we'll do it again and as well as
monopoly and jackabox games sometime
and i hope you all enjoyed it i'll take
tomorrow
of i think according to my schedule and
then i'll see you
at the bottomless empire club
thank you very much for watching
and
i'll see you soon thank you i love you
all
thank you thank you thank you thank you
i'm gonna go have some proof yeah
thanks guys and in german we say
auf wiedersehen
[Music]
foreign