[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
questions
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
kick
get off get all hello
I am
huh
um
Frankie mama is here oh hello
I have hands oh
I'm already better than that stupid
Kiana because I got actual hands
[Music]
peace peace
welcome to my first stream I'm a bit
nervous
I wanted to show you guys my Expressions
first yeah I can cry
[Music]
yes yeah yeah no don't crank you up yes
hello
[Music]
I can wiggle my eyebrows
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
and of course you know I have the gun
that you saw in the in the
take over video
yes very dangerous kiddo
um
if I see anyone in the chat asking for a
certain Phoenix
I must shoot you
it's not a lava pistol totally not a
water pistol kiddo
do you notice
[Music]
anyway see that's a cute cute frog
sticker you see it
cute frog sticker oh
[Music]
yeah
okay so that was the gun and we saw the
tears I can have tears when I'm happy
too
and one more thinking huh speaking of
frog
what do you think of when you speak a
obviously me
but oh
oh yes yes
[Music]
foreign
to survive a frog needs a strong
strong and preferably long tongue
[Music]
[Laughter]
bye
blah blah blah blah
blah
[Laughter]
[Music]
you like my frog Kettle hmm
did I say you like my frog candle you
like my tongue kiddo
do you like my tongue at all
kiddo
pedal pedal kiddo
[Laughter]
yes I just want to reveal that a little
bit oh oh about it oh got my gun oopsie
I'm I'm already better than Kiara Kiara
can't show her tongue piano can't move
her hands normally
what a loser we don't need her
Nina here can all
right
[Music]
no puffy cheeks also you look at my
mouth
[Music]
I can move it from side to side oh
oh
[Music]
yeah
I don't even like I can't
live one with one normal expression I
can already do so many things
[Music]
I don't even have to switch it you know
with buttons or so because I'm I'm a
real I'm a real rocket
see so many so many emotions so many
Expressions so easily oh maybe you wanna
I'm not seeing me like
and full body
just for a little bit I'm gonna stand on
my Lily Pad oh wait
well
there I am
[Music]
[Applause]
how about that
[Music]
okay maybe I can even only with my hands
I could maybe dance with this a little
bit
uh
[Music]
okay this could be improved this could
be improved but for now this is good
yes I'm superior to Kiana
all right guys
um I take donations of flies by the way
if you feel like
you know donating to your new
smug
frog Overlord then
if you want to be in my favor
[Music]
and give me the goods
give me more of these of these there
um
okay
flies please oh I mean are we I'm gonna
at the end of the week I'm gonna make a
fly to your list where we talk a little
bit about what flies are the best what
kind of types of flying insects are the
best and the tastiest and
um
yes we're gonna make a fly to your list
but for now you just have to you know
give me whatever give me a collection of
flies and I'll be happy thank you
South no morning over that bee
we don't need her to have fun let's go
play a game I like games that have to do
with frogs so obviously let's move I
stole I stole that
is a gaming room so we're gonna go over
there let's go
ah
dinner okay I don't know how I don't
know well how the streams are please be
kind with me
um I'll do my best though
please don't mean to stick and you know
I'm gonna do my best fight oh Frankie
mama
oh wait I actually I made myself a logo
Kettle let me put it up somewhere to go
wait where is my logo
you like Frankie Mama Frankie Mama cute
oh uh yes he put that on top
don't wanna see that logo never again
it's my time now my time to shine baby
[Music]
oh
it's the cutest right I know I know and
then I think I have this game logo
somewhere this is how kiwawa used to do
it right
he would put up the game logo let me do
that too I can do that too here there
you go
time on frog island is what we're gonna
play today
I don't know
okay yeah perfect
it's my channel now kiddo
gaming frog
let's go let's move this over here
um I heard this game is free to four
hours long
so
we will do it in one stream okay
also you guys are not chickens now you
guys are tadpoles okay
hello tadpoles
yeah you only all my babies too bad then
you know for tadpoles it's like you know
I make many many typos in my lifetime
but with one one time
one time of egg laying
oh see come on we have one thing in
common I guess [\h__\h] always said she
doesn't lay eggs but
um nah we do have that in common I make
eggs and then they turn into tadpoles
but unfortunately like usually half of
them half of them like die if not more
so not many of you yeah survive
yeah you either get eaten or you I don't
know just die from being somewhere where
I don't know you're gonna die like at
all very unfortunate kiddo but you know
you have to be strong to survive kid
also in order to become stronger you
maybe should just watch my streams to
learn how to be a good frog
what's tadpole in nihongo
tadpole
nothing okay
what is Deadpool
oh
[Music]
my God
I don't know
[Music]
yeah fifty percent mortality rate is
that for 100 as a stock chicken
you don't even have to think about it's
not a choice anymore you're with Meek at
all okay new games that I'm playing with
a controller
hopefully it goes well cuddle
also I can move my hands but but
I have them under control like you know
whoa
yeah I will wave to you guys sometimes
to make sure you remember I have hands
girl who is this that's not a frog
kettle
it has a plant why does he have a plant
on his boat Carol
unnecessary kiddo
oh we stranded on an island kiddo
wake up
oh
his plant is gone
no
[Music]
oh where could it be oh oh there it is
I'll give it back stupid bird [\h__\h] Birds
don't want Birds bird is a big enemy
Birds always poke me when I'm sleeping
um
oh I can move Kettle let's go what is
this I can pick that up
oh what I'm pressing X
wait it's not it says X but uh maybe
yeah they don't recognize I have a
PlayStation controller because
I had to press um square at all
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah trust me
trust me kiddle
so what is this there's a frog here
hello are you my uncle Carol
[Music]
gumbo
um and that's my plan
you're drawing my plant
s
can I can I have basketball
um
you what can I get my no oh throw away
yes no throw it
what the [\h__\h]
evil okay so many things Carol
oh see that crap is hiding from me now
okay and they're scared
I'm superior after all so what maybe he
wants me to bring him that oh wait
that's something
and take this
um uh maybe and talk to you
oh
[Music]
yes that's right
I don't know why I like it so much but
it's very important to me why what could
y be
oh I can I
I don't know what that but
he's in love with a plant
and we put it back on my boat or what
oh
seems so oh
Brett
uh-huh wait what whoa whoa whoa
what was that button
where's that button
I'm not sure
all right let's continue to explore a is
X B's Circle
Square wise triangle
ain't okay well I might have to pin that
meal pad I I touched it
on the right side this comes up ah maybe
it just wants to show me my achievements
okay because we got the Shipwrecked one
kettle
okay what's in this house Kendall can I
go in I can jump by the way
I can't jump as well as I candle oh
bones oh
I said jump on I'm gonna give you that
um on these mushrooms not dangerous at
all
I can pick up air everything but I don't
know what to do with it yet
well I think I saw someone over here
what are you doing
oh you need the the things that make you
seem very far kiddo okay did I see them
somewhere
maybe not yet did you guys see them get
all anything down here
well no foul damaged at all sick
oh binoculars
has anyone played this game before in
Whole Life by the way I don't know if
the other whole album is know that I'm
taking over I didn't even pass an
audition or anything I I wonder what
they think of it I just kind of like
killed Kiara and now I'm here kiddo but
you know if you want to be successful
then sometimes you have to walk over
dead bodies and [\h__\h] and create dead
bodies and you know don't be like that
so yeah I hope they accept
me as as their new colleague otherwise
I'll have to do something about that you
know
I'm the first of course
[Music]
is first you can call me froggy Wawa by
the way or froggyada or I don't know I'm
still looking for a nickname how about
how about Wawa hmm
no one ever has used that before
I'm stealing her her friends oh want
some people fire you wanna oh you want
to fight okay but stealing her her
friends her family her job her gaming
layout and now I'm stealing her nickname
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
so ah you need oh wait you need some
ah why is it showing me the mouse now
okay here you go you need this I suppose
yeah oh we're repairing the
the boat
here's another piece that I brought up
here
yes oh where's my Wheel I guess we can
make a fire first wait
[Music]
Oh I wanna eat
nah
give me
[Music]
ah wait ah now does this goes here ah
start a fire today
what
what do you mean start a fire today
I don't like fire
Frank don't like fire Frank Frank don't
like fire dangerous get all
I want to hear anything about
fire
oh Birds [\h__\h] Birds
got it
it's not a water today I guess whatever
I don't care
yes let's start a flat today
that sounds more like it um
oh
fire is the water why
wait where the hell is that huh ceilings
well because I walked so much
I'll get all okay no
um
wait wait wait wait wait
start a flower today yes okay took away
so it turned nine times I'm surprised
you can turn 9 10. wow we make the fire
but I don't like it
[Music]
um scary
so I made this okay nicely like can I
eat some bees
[Music]
we should Grill them
they're good when they're grilled
bees grilled
um
I've never eaten Seafood before
okay sleep now I'm ready to sleep what
ah
good night kiddo
hey I don't like fire but you know you
can Grill without an open fire
well who's this girl
Am I Dreaming
you'll make up
at all
was that Kiana
she's still alive
oh no oh no
I thought I killed her properly
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
I will take care of that eventually
I'll find her
oh oh yeah wow
wow you're trying me now and my bone is
so big wow thank you
foreign
[Music]
you used
what what the [\h__\h] is that frog frog man
you used my my sail no wait no you just
parked was it always like this kettle
what is it because I threw away his
other
[Laughter]
is that mine
am I what do you want
hello
and I'll use this instead what is it
what are you telling me
Oh you mean maybe some some something in
the water he's using my my sail oh wait
but wait this is here no that's a pillow
oh
did we see him somewhere Channel
not here
maybe let's go a bit further oh what is
this blue flower Kettle no no blue
flower just water oh
[Music]
scary ah scary birds
Oh I wanna stay away from them holy [\h__\h]
there's so many kid off
oh what the [\h__\h] is that oh is that like
a tadpole I didn't know tadpoles look
like this at some stage what the hell
usually I've abandoned my children after
I make them
so wait what do I even do with you
there's another Franklin let's talk to
him
what you're angry yeah yeah
okay it's a green and where's oh where's
the head
the head of your scarecrow
oh I'll go look for it because I don't
want these birds to be around here
either look
at the rooftop Pokemon
and this Temple is like a like a dog for
him
oh God wait he needs several heads so no
because there's several scarecrows get
all
okay let's let's go look around
it's following me gonna
did I make you are you recognizing me as
your mommy Carol
I've made many many many many many many
tattoos so far so I don't know to be
honest
it could be
you could be mine
perhaps what is this kid all what
whoa
Chloe Stone I can't pick it up kiddo
um more more wood
[Music]
um
hello someone here kid on
es
oh I know
what is this place oh
okay remember this guys will need this
for something probably okay
oh
by the way there seems to be no map in
this game so we might get lost a lot get
off
what do you mean you're rooting for them
Sonic at all
ah do I need to
I guess I need to make use of chiara's
usual room
I have no choice some of you guys seem
to be against me at all
who is against
yeah I'll drown you
or I'll just eat you
tadpoles are small how can you tadpoles
I might just eat you
so who is not on my side hmm
you're not a dog you're not a dog at all
what are you saying
we have a
zigzag
zigzag machine zigzag knife
there's so many Bee nests and lots of
food for me
um
there's no people in this area maybe
they'll come later oh God
okay unlock it all yeah are you also my
chat what what's going on here oh my God
hello frog family you're going inside
are you getting married
what was that oh they went inside oh
what you want a glass okay a cold glass
okay I'll remember that what do you want
you're looking for a tadpole with
glasses maybe yeah well there'll be a
shop here
oh this is like a little village skin
off what anyone
are you talking to me
one of these things called again they
look kind of similar to frogs but
they're not frogs oh crazy man what
yeah you're also looking for that thing
oh yeah wait
I just axolotls and not tadpoles
[Music]
I found the wheel what where
oh I mean this way I can't take this one
you mean the first one wait did you see
it all
those eyes okay okay that's why they're
following me hey I wouldn't make any
other sense otherwise
the red color made me get off but you
know you're not wearing glasses
learn such a language Skittle what about
this one
wow
okay I don't think they want this one
but okay we'll take it we'll adopt it
now
is this kidnapping
no it seems like they were mine to begin
with
[Music]
um
well we got on it where's my red one
did he like bug out somewhere
where did one
they should Implement some kind of like
respawning mechanism if they get stuck
somewhere otherwise I always have to
take care of them oh
[Music]
yummy never mind I didn't mean to heal
these are exactly what I like to eat
how do I wait maybe Apple Apple
I need to
shake down the apples oh
oh here take
take
it off let's have a dinosaur
because I'm here okay so first we step
away okay
and then we attack this one because he's
slower
[Applause]
[Music]
um
gonna have a good good dinner here later
came off
so we're going the right direction I
wonder
do you know
you know that oh yes yes yes
well that was really far away wrong
color I don't think it matters
does it
you wanted this right
oh
talk to me
yeah yeah yeah
I thought he wanted this thing
did I go back to the wrong person
what
they get up I thought we would have no
problems communicating you and me we're
frogs
uh
I straight I scream just like your ocean
you have to forget about your machine
I'm your roshi now
um
when I do this thing I brought it here
now taken
looks exactly like what you requested oh
money
[Music]
oh my dogs
where are my other dogs
oh they're missing two of them
okay I'll try to get a blue one seems to
be very specific
what
I have to make a new fire okay now
I hope the the this will always respawn
because the other one
are you trying to go back to the tree
I'll go sleep
maybe if I sleep my my dog's my dog
poles will re-spunk at all
what is this we're we're building a boat
maybe I was maybe that's my sister Kayla
oh
[Applause]
I heard her again
where is she
should I be worried
did you hear her oh this is just a voice
in my head that I'm imagining at all
can't you save us what do you mean
my frog rain has just begun get used to
me
get used to me
so I'm back I think oh okay oh yeah
[Music]
don't they like rain
okay I don't know
you don't know I love rain and I love
Army
especially amazing
you know
maybe I just joined whole life
so that I can get closer to Imma Be
but who knows I cannot say for shark at
all
a frog has to keep her secrets and her
strategies all there's more apple trees
here a couple more
oh hello
I'll See You Again wait the Crowds Are
Gone you've got strawberries oh and and
blueberries
and no crowds I guess they don't like
rain at all I love raining
you can just in fact eat breakfast
it's okay you guys are tadpoles now
anyway and and I killed Kiana I have a
gun
so let's talk to him
oh sorry hello
yeah yeah they're gone they're gone
oh let me go find the head okay ah oh oh
wait ah what are these called again
we forgot kale
let's go maybe back up where I first
went
where are my other tadpoles
so weird
so I'm gonna maybe I was supposed to go
here first after all
can tadpole jump out
and don't believe you frog going to see
yeah protect
[Music]
um
okay I lost my other dog too
okay so one thing you want
you won't find anything in this game not
the things that I need at least let's go
this way maybe there's somewhere here
me
oh yeah yeah we were here before
sneeze sounds familiar well a sneeze is
assistant at all
no nothing weird about that at all
if if it sounded anything like her
we don't say her name here
then that's just because I'm currently
I had to stay
developing her in my tummy dinner
oh yeah that's that's one thing that's
useful let me just leave that here maybe
that will be useful later
what are you doing in the water canal I
mean I know I know I know I know but you
know
are you even you dark blue did I have a
dark blue one before
hello everybody you enjoying the rain oh
wheel
what
I saw a wheel
I was running here and then I huh
I reacted to a wheel
on the car yeah oh maybe I oh I'll get
it if I help them maybe
for frog
how are you
give me a wheel but maybe wheel is more
for late game yeah you need that Stitch
stupid thing what's here wow
wow oh sorry I also want a glass oh
there it is so
can I have that someone else needs it I
think oh wait wait wait wait there's two
though
oh what about this one like she wanted
one that's called Carol
um
thank you ah come on ah you want them to
you
on the mountain
on the mountain is something that would
help me cool down these
um uh glasses maybe cannot
okay
yes give me what I want now
I lost my tadpole again God damn it all
right let's go up to the mountain
[Music]
s
what does the frog say I'll I can tell
you what a frog says
I can tell you what a project oh you're
a frog too holy [\h__\h] you got a beard
girl oh you want a bell I've seen a bell
around
I can try to get it for you
but I don't think I can currently detach
it what does the fox say
you want to know
that's what frax says
and Frank I'm Frank for real
Pepi
was just you know faking me
maintaining me wishing to be as cool as
me but she never can she can never live
up to this what
is it really okay for me to go
up here right now I feel like maybe I
should have been solving things down
there first of all what is this
well that looks very interesting
[Music]
huh
teleported me kiddo
why did it teleport me to
oh my God where the [\h__\h] am I
where am I
should I do it again
oh wait there's some cool mush oh wait a
second what is that
wait is that
huh
I forgot what we are looking for
it's kind of
interesting
so so
it looks like a runny nose yeah
this is interesting too
very interesting girl oh there's a beach
side
[Music]
I feel like even though it's supposed to
be three to four hours
I'll be taking some extra time with this
game where does this lead
well
we're here again we're okay okay so
that's kind of connected
let me try to use it again
where where do we go back to where I
found it
all right let's go even higher can we
get much higher so high
oh do I need to put that thing in here
[Laughter]
take it huh
no no no no no here
oh what
no one did
it's supposed to go in here I'm pretty
sure but it just flies away
something else
[Music]
my favorite song
do you know my favorite song
[Music]
maybe also need at some point get all
your bone
what is this
what
I made a funny sound
okay
I have another favorite song
no
no and
um
[Music]
hey you know that song
cute destiny
yeah
okay
I can't sing it
I have a lily pad now when everything is
[Music]
didn't you say that whatever he was
looking for was up on the mountain where
the snow is I was there I feel like I
looked at everything
okay my favorite song is do cattle by
fragawa dude maybe it's behind here and
I can't get here yet ah where should I
go fireflies
[Music]
um you need to use your tongue young man
you need to use your tongue
catch the fireflies
10 million fireflies
you would not believe your eyes lit up
this guys I fell asleep
[Music]
also one of my favorite songs
I have many favorite songs
was this thing moving you know
what happens if you kiss frog Rocky
Walla I don't know
nobody ever kissed me so I don't know
what would happen
it's a good question girl I've heard of
the tails
Tales of froggy Wawa
he's frog and Magic happens oh look
there's another one of those
maybe I need to light them up maybe it's
like a like and use a fire or so
frog
can I turn into a princess when I get a
kiss oh
green one
oh where are you going stop
it why are you so green
wait
oh wait they're already following me I
thought it was running away from me but
no kiddo
I was just running ahead of me wait do
you guys change color depending on
the weather
and if it rains you Green Girl
oh
why this one stayed here
even though I teleported no no
[Music]
maybe there was always two to begin with
okay okay I'm going back I need help
though someone who played this game can
oh help me get off
help make it off
what should I do first
it seems like everything I find needs
something else first kettle
focus on doing one thing at a time
I tried
I didn't explore the mountain enough
secure a blueberry for that grub to
change
huh
ah you mean
if I give one of these blueberries to
those of the thingies
maybe it's still over there like it's um
disappeared in the ground though
probably because it doesn't okay can we
try to sleep maybe it's night time right
now
oh the fireflies light up wait he walked
away from his painting that's also
interesting okay I will leave this here
oh he's going to sleep
why can the fireflies not light up my
my fireplace why why
not yeah
one more wood
okay
and
sleep
fire of life no make fire
why not oh they're looking at
a map
on the top left there is a treasure
hmm
is the map of this island probably not
[Music]
she said
okay I'll get on now
oh yeah
should I bring it over there I I think
so
but wait it's still raining
why won't it stop raining
um is it random
am I just unlucky
wait was it more on the right side
okay let's leave this offering here
can we do something else in the meantime
does anyone need mushrooms what did you
need again sir
oops you needed
can I talk of them
no
oh yeah forgot to take the breeze coming
out unfortunately it's not out yet
otherwise I would have played it in this
week as well yeah this scarecrow heads
see any heads around
I can
I can behead someone
ah
these things are in the cave in front of
him thank you
binoculars that was like on the left
side of the yeah yeah yeah oh
yeah cave
you don't fit in huh oh wait you mean
your binoculars oh
We Come Away ah that you didn't do it
before he was too fat to go in but I'm
not kiddo I mean I'm maybe a little bit
chubby but
um that that shop is
huge chopped kettle
[Music]
d one thing
where are you going now oh you can look
into this ah
is there something interesting there
you know
okay well it doesn't seem like he gives
me anything in exchange that's sad
okay
let's see where I can go next maybe the
other things maybe the solutions for the
other things
are not as
far as I thought they were at all but
this thing is mysterious though
um and this thing
there's so many of these
maybe can I jump I mean we can jump so
maybe I can jump on top of the house no
oh there's a bucket candle remember the
bucket remember the bucket
okay oh a rope
ah you broke
Europe
oh it's broken can only want a new one
wrong
oh
bird is it a better problem though
from the crows
okay no you have an eye infection sir
oh you know you have to put some some
honey on that eye and then it will heal
get up yeah I know that from frog mama
put honey on eye and then infection will
heal
foreign
[Music]
where did I not go yet I feel like I've
run around this whole island already
when we're back here oh hello see wait a
second not all of them turned green in
the rain because the red one is still
red
wait so this is a belt I want this Bell
can I take Belle
try tadpole
[Music]
you think that would work but they ran
away from me
all right I will try
I wonder if it also has to be a specific
color
we've gathered a couple of them together
again
that would be crazy
well
no
no it doesn't work
[Laughter]
it up
head to bottom far right okay kiddo
thank you are you playing the game
[Music]
love you
somewhere here
oh
pretty oh there's a hammer
and this rope can I take this rope
no but there's another one of those
things in the water
and I think hammer and then
we'll go on camera
more wood oh wait that maybe something
happens if I make a fire here
or is it just another place where I can
sleep if I don't want to walk all the
way back
let's Grill the tadpoles no no no no no
no no
oh yeah I can't sleep here I guess I I
guess I'll sleep
hello what is this game
look at the bottom left it says time on
frog Island we're playing a little
small
putt puzzle puzzle Adventure what would
you call this genre
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
anymore but my tattoos are gone all
right wait wait wait wait wait wait oh
what is what the [\h__\h] is that what
I feel like I opened
a portal
interesting but I don't know if I found
what
what that tadpole wanted me to find
it
hello Frank
what do you want
[Music]
what what does that mean
we go together over there okay okay okay
okay
one you have here
well there's another big island stop
stop
oh pretty
they look like a maybe
party pizza neither one noise don't get
off
holy [\h__\h] this place is big
gonna get lost again wait maybe now he
tells me what he actually wants
yes sunflower yeah because it's sunny
now
what you want one here
huh
oh
yeah
one
minute
I don't understand I thought we were
frog
family
they're not as making my language
[Music]
wait
this we already had somewhere else
or was I here before
oh
wait that thing over there
it's a different place
is it
plan something in it
that doesn't look like isn't this just
tree tree
um bottoms
doesn't look like I can plant but I can
try
[Music]
oh this one's pink because of all the
pink stuff here get off
wait
a timer
can I Dash
is it a race what to wear do I just go
straight
there was another one but I don't know
was it over there
done
[Music]
I think I think down here
um
[\h__\h] where is that thing
ah wasn't it like here ah
ah
hi
why doesn't continue I don't know where
to go next maybe we can only do this if
we really know where to go next
wait it makes music
hey here it is
I feel like maybe if we activate all of
them in the end it will make a music
a nice sound
oh
ah now it's getting higher so it's like
ah you're losing
all right all right maybe that's for
later it doesn't face the direction I go
next but no I turned I turned in order
to get to the other one
but who knows if that was even the first
one that you're supposed to enter
okay guys
they're trying to run from me anyway we
hopefully hopefully this works
I fed the other one a green apple so it
turned green so if we feed it a
blueberry then it will turn blue kettle
I know where are they
I'm lost who is this
hello
why are you not talk to me
I
whatever I need to focus on one thing at
all
I can't find
I just walked by them
hey
foreign
[Music]
I don't think so
attention span of a frog hey
hey what do you mean is that an insult
okay I found them yeah
[Music]
okay okay
take this eat
come on come on oh it's so fat come with
me
there's still more for the others and
John Kennel
um
so fat I wanna take a bite too
I don't know
the birds are back
oh no
okay after this maybe we can focus on
finding uh a rope maybe okay here take
this
Oh yay it is blue blue color
[Laughter]
oh there
oh it was so alive
and now is this from me you know
ah ah I continue fixing my boat
oh what on it
I thought I could put it up there
no
ah from here
oh he's so pretty pretty I have hosted
the sales so it's the end goal to fix
the boat
we need a wheel in the Rope
no he's chilling here oh
what's your name frog man
froggy froggy long legs
all right
let's get on what about these heads
canal
maybe nice nice tadpole from before can
tell me
help me you know
help me
please be hives
you don't seem to really know it but
that could work far right okay
okay
that is a very very rough
uh explanation
I keep on going right
[Music]
can I if I jump on them oh
I wonder if this has a meaning
and we're just here again
I know I'm so cute I know thank you
Sergio
thank you
foreign
[Music]
have I gone here before
oh it's a dead end
I went right uh
next to the skin across what
so you guys are still loyal to that
being
[Music]
unbelievable
hello friend
thank you
um I'm here again she's got a jock it
all
he's gonna Jack it all
I don't remember I don't think we need a
jar anywhere but maybe in the future it
will be useful you're going to sleep now
huh
but they said go right
he said go around
more rides to the teleporter okay thank
you okay
I was once again but you're better than
her hell yeah I don't get all
I mean maybe I'm currently not better at
gaming than her but we'll get their
candle practice makes perfect
um
right
me collab with her no she's dead
how can I collab with a dead person she
ain't only
[Music]
I'll bring that to you uh where did I
leave that
[Music]
um
oh
ah
did that he was here I mean he's gonna
sleep now but
you're real
oil
[Music]
I'm here here okay I'll bring it
um can I sleep by this fire
nope I can take the gold okay remember
that too someone if someone is a gold
digger frog
then we can have this gold all right
we'll keep this we'll go somewhere to
sleep
I have to do this first because
at least for this one I have a solution
kettle
go home okay no
you know
[Music]
okay no announce
take me home are we back yeah we're back
[Music]
all right put it here
and then we make
fire
ah
there's no one have a lighter you know
what these tiny hands
I I bought a lighter the other day
because I wanted to turn on some candles
I know what's wrong with the liner there
were two in the package but I just could
not turn them on
and if I've used the lighter before but
that one was like
I don't know stuck
I tried turning you know like a typical
lighter
if I buy a lighter another Candlelight I
don't know these I mean I saw it
randomly in the in the store and I was
like
oh it's gonna be good
uh
she's in my brain she's haunting me
okay let's bring this
child safety liner oh maybe there's some
kind of lock
but I looked at the lighter and I really
tried and I didn't find anything like a
lock but
maybe there was
okay now we have to find that dude again
can uh
he was not too far
but when he's awake I wonder if he goes
somewhere else
I just gave it to you did it fall down
no I think he took his kid off
is he is he bringing it somewhere oh my
my green dog's hello
what you doing
that's it
no rewind
come on come on it's gonna work in the
woods now and maybe something will
reveal itself get
rid of this moment about that requires
you to push hard when lighting the
lighter
maybe I should do a hand cam stream
where I like the lighter
oh maybe it opens A New Path oh wait
there's already
oh maybe that was supposed to show me
what I thought is that
what is that whoa maybe this was just
supposed to show me that there's a path
here oh
yeah look
Stone special stone okay I don't know
for what yet oh no I can't see any more
than that
okay
okay remember Caleb yeah kfb okay no
friends Phoenix
I'll show you I'll show you these these
tiny hands uh
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
dancing you always have the best ideas I
say always even though we just met a
plastic baby yes
I'll remember that kiddo
okay okay well we we cleared that but
that didn't help us so [\h__\h] that oh
we're still gonna go to the right side
though
because I was told to go to the right to
find the heads but like where
they didn't say as far as possible
as far as like to the mountain but I I
don't remember how to get there
Stone here Stone
ah
how do we get there before
maybe here oh see there's another one of
those thingies but this one's what's
[Music]
what's do I need a hook shot kiddo
I will buy flies I'll buy really tasty
flies
with the money I think you could all
ding dong
it looks like a wheel but it's just a
window
the Bell they keep on telling me about
the bell I know I need a bell somewhere
someone asked for Belle but
I can't help you with that girl
plant a mushroom there
head up to Second teleporter second
but here is
oh
why I
um
second
that one that we just passed was the
first we found I think what
[Music]
ah there's something where I can plan
something here too
um that one okay okay
so we use it again
what about those flag thingies
use the one on the floor okay
[Music]
okay
and then maybe somewhere here it's what
I'm it's what I'm looking for
hey
what
not here
no for Jason oh
oh look there's one of those here
oh
I can't pick them up the only thing I
can do is knock them over I wonder if
rocket and little wait you're the one
you're the one with the ah I have to
come here twice I can only carry one
thing all right all right let's return
this one first I think the village is
not even that far from here
try to remember the path get off
[Music]
oh
this sunflowers
[Music]
oh
oh will it follow me
oh no it just runs back on its own
[Music]
it was me who helped them
wait if you just run there on your round
and they won't know
[Music]
ah
okay let me go back and get the other
thing you know
I apparently I just needed to free it
from that one spot
I'm sure it will tell them
oh
it thinks it's a [\h__\h] frog
unbelievable
yeah small hands small hands
small hand ah yeah I can do peace
maybe thumbs can I do thumbs
my phone is so small
twinkle twinkle little
middle finger
now I can
too small
you'll be tonight
at least the piece works that's all I
want
um was it here was it here was it wasn't
here I think it was here
okay so one but we need three of them
who
also I saw a lot of you guys changed
your names to something with frog
instead it's so cute thank you for
accepting your new frog Overlord thank
you
thank you
me I don't say thank you soon that's
what that [\h__\h] says I say I say quack
[Music]
where am I going
ah
um let's see if something changed now
that they have their friend and look at
them
I'm gonna put this down for a second
yeah
you happy now what do I get
oh you are he just goes back to work I
suppose because he's done looking for
wait it's following me though it likes
me more than you kiddo what does that
say about how you keep your pet scale
what does he do now that he works oh
what are you gonna make
[Music]
I mean let me talk to you
that's it
do I just need to solve everybody's
problems but I thought some of these
things would be connected at least huh
[Music]
oh well I mean okay let me let me ah
should I bring no he's not asking for
the ore but if I bring it to him maybe
he can make something
for someone else you know
well let's let's figure it out oh
oh we found
we found it okay okay
[Music]
for the sake of all of us we need to get
rid of them here I
I did one of them I have one of them
where's my thank you you want more huh
okay
ah one and two two more
what
okay
this one was already so difficult to
find oh all right all right all right
but we already solved a couple of
um
problems so
it will surely wait he's
he's working now
you need a new one please sell me a new
window
you want a lamp from the from the hairy
frog
he has it
well I saw him somewhere where do
you know
yeah it's so cute that they follow me
get off but I'm just gonna abandon them
eventually like I always do so
well well
I don't remember where I found this but
anyway let me take one of these maybe I
can try to flange them
ah top left I think you are hello and
what did you want again no don't talk to
me first I you want I have for you he
doesn't like the how loud it is probably
so I have to stop it somehow
I have to steal it
I guess
what how
we couldn't reach it before it wasn't
even the one that I saw
so much
oh
my whoever that is sister or friend is
like sick
oh no she did
like Chihuahua
he wants the Bell
[Music]
[Applause]
what is this though
what's this spell ah
I can maybe Jump On It
[Music]
oh platformer let's go
how do I reach dad
maybe impossible now wait wait wait wait
wait wait maybe maybe maybe from there
maybe from here
[Music]
hog
I got it
oh my God
no more of that noisy stupid
oh nobody heard or saw that she
um
No One's Gonna See Me Right
now
I guess you're my little rock champ
[Laughter]
let's go on to the top again
give him this Bell and then he'll give
us uh I forgot a lamp
I think
hopefully he better I want a fair
exchange she's not here though want it
it's daytime though oh he's over here
he's meditating is levitating
and his beard moves
[Music]
not my kind of thing
wake up
wake up stop doing that
give me give me give me the lamp
[Laughter]
[Music]
s
hey kids you're happy yeah
wait what can I
oh God it's gonna fall down
and we replaced it
say no
[Music]
wait wait
is there a good placement I have here I
mean ah
can I place it there
no and that wouldn't make sense anyway
because he doesn't want no no I have to
run all the way around again
but I don't know man I could not pick up
the
look at her
give me that social light
oh you like me you want a ring and you
want me to put your ring on your finger
and then I get the head
girl
look she this is quite the huntress she
has a whole Fox around her neck you know
what frogs can be dangerous get up
they might just
kill animals that you've never expected
them to kill hello everybody is
again
so
yeah
all right what take this
yes yes oh you just wanted me to put it
down okay
I already brought you
the what's your problem
oh the big one yeah yeah I know he wants
that but I I want this first man
he also wants the ice cold drink but for
that I have to find the other thing
[Music]
explore the right side of the island
have you played the game took at all
right sit down
and tell me everything
you must
backseat me
tell me tell me
[Music]
all your nuts and [\h__\h]
oh hello
these tadpoles are so cute
I'm going the wrong way
[Music]
foreign
okay so I'll I'll try to explore more
but oh
but
let me try
to reach New Heights
the reason why I'm singing that
it's because
I heard it somewhere
just just a few days ago but I I knew
I've heard it I realized oh I've heard
it before
is that what Kiana's viewers were always
talking about
is that it
she'll never really understand the real
meaning oh
well then
I never went here I thought it was
here
[Music]
oh yeah
what is this is that the top of the
mountain where we were able to enter in
the bottom
oh wait
there's a whole universe so there's some
in there a universal universe
where does this go does it go it doesn't
look like it would fit into that
hole but let me try
maybe it works oh no it doesn't
[\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
it looks so important
but that was not the right spot where
where could I need this
have I seen where this goes before
[Music]
hmm
the blacksmith
you think so
I'm gonna try well no I couldn't go down
maybe someone reacts to this
oh look at these
huh
okay you are not interested
she wanted a ring
oh
hello hello
what are you looking for
[\h__\h]
why is it the same
hmm
can you make me a ring actually
maybe with the gold
please make me a ring
oh well maybe if I place it on there
thank you
please make ring
I don't know what I was looking for in
the mountain to be honest I'll see it
doesn't work
I saw everything I mean now we found
this thing here down below the globe but
um
yes I know I'm working on that
Santa Island to the East has the key you
want oh
me honor okay
okay East
so we go to Sunflower Island not to the
mountain
okay okay
do I however have to go there if it's
sunny
Pearl from a shell
oh no oh wait no it's different flowers
oh
whoa oh yeah that's unfortunately maybe
these can be used for something else you
know where are you going
to show me something
um what is he gonna do ah he's looking
around oh wait maybe he can can I look
with you
oh hi
no
oh
did I go up here before Oh
[Music]
and for that one door
whoa what is this machine
uh this one I cannot pick up okay
all right
thank you
let's see let's see let's see
uh anything else before I go just
checking
like don't don't think I can go higher
than this kid all
right okay let's go
let's go kiddo what is this sorcery
where's my angel I can't wear it
like did you not see the video
she's done though
she's Danny with that funny
no more no more quinoa funny no no
let me see what's here though on it
more mushrooms
and then I guess it just leads to the
same path
just making sure let me what if I put
this here oh oh oh oh never mind I'll
take it with me I think I can climb this
maybe
no
dunk
oh there's more
no uh is there
all that kind of is
oh oh wait that's teleported I've used
that before okay that's connected to
where we found
the
um uh the head and the tadpole with the
glasses
okay
all right then with this we go up up to
the mountain
don't mind the timer guys
are cute actually I was thinking you
know originally now I kind of regret it
I recently thought maybe I should do
like a w stream
but then I for some reason decided
against it and now I'm kind of regret it
I should have done the debut stream
beforehand
oh well we're going straight into gaming
because Frankie mama needs no
introduction
oh wait wrong path
a little bit up higher
yeah that would have been uh oh you want
to sleep what if I don't let you sleep
what happens if I don't
know
well if I find the fire I'm I'll guess
I might let you sleep
ah of course well
um the design is made by Mama Luni it
was just originally just a fan art
and I wrote all the credits already in
the in the video that I
uh uploaded yesterday
so the design is by Mama lonely where is
some wood and uh the modeling is by
preaching
again who made on the other
um VR models from Kiana
and
and then husk
did like the
um no
helped me to make
my face move
yeah and oh Haskell also made the gun
yeah
my cute gun I'm surprised I didn't know
husk can make
uh on like like 3D and stuff too there's
one for the fireplace and then
say I guess yeah somehow Mama really is
now mama
where is Wood I've seen ah there
foreign
[Music]
how sad he is no
oh
sad
it's gonna be okay don't worry
we're gonna I don't know make your life
it's gone
[Music]
oh I didn't know I should have just went
up first
he died
wait
um should I walk there or yeah
because I think teleporting
can't speak close to there too but then
first I have to walk there to the
teleporter and bleep blah blah blah
songs
[Music]
[Laughter]
not that this was ever planned but the
first time I saw that cute kennel kennel
quinoa design I was like ah I am
beautiful I am cute I am Divine I am
exquisite
I am the most gorgeous thing I have ever
seen
so
obviously if you know
one thing leads to another
and I became disconnected it took me a
long time
to reach this ultimate form cannot
what
none of them finally here you guys don't
have to worry anymore about that
[Music]
no no no no
I know she was she was um like a tyrant
to you guys
now I might be even worse but um don't
worry you'll you'll reach Enlightenment
and salvation
through other ways
yeah
it's in the in the end it will be better
trust me
this is the best thing that could happen
to you is this even the right way up or
was it that way
ah no it was not that way
am I going the right lane get all
she sometimes would pay as an ear let us
go outside for now
and that is true I looked into the
documents
and I only saw payments incoming but
never outgoing so you're just coping
there's no need to cook huh that tent
was not always there was it
here
sunflower man
he knows what's it's opening let's go
I'm way faster than you get all
well platforming I wonder if he can do
that yeah I want to see you do that
you can't
leave it to me
I'm good at jumping Channel
oh oh
yeah
oh my God so good oh
that's what they want maybe it didn't
look like you know they just wanted a
cold thing but
another bone too okay we'll knock this
over because I have a feeling that we
have to knock all of these over
okay
okay oh bone bone goes bye bye
so we bring it to the kitchen
to the restaurant colony
[Music]
took me long enough man
Mario
of course
no no don't
actually I don't know man I I
there's some [\h__\h] oh
it's getting dirty what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
wait no what there's the head coming out
of it
there's a frog
was this not
what
this is not
what am I supposed to use this for
foreign
[Music]
help
I want to know what I use this for
statue at the top of the mountain
yeah right you wanted the flower
I'm putting this somewhere on the top of
the mountain
for the Scarecrow I think
take a sunflower up
what about this body though
ah she's just so much to do kiddo a holy
frog really yeah pray pray at the Frog
Relic
it's my
my relatives from many many years ago
hi guys
okay Apple
if I leave it I wonder if it will
disappear and respawn like the other
things
or if it will stay and where I'll leave
it
but I will go
up again ah if I really need a sunflower
I'm gonna be so mad
when I reach the top and it says I need
a sunflower
I want about you don't you like this
meditating statue I feel like you would
like it
no
no no
[Music]
I thought you would like it
okay I guess not
yeah if it responds it'll probably be
frozen again
but it doesn't seem to be the purpose of
it anyway
but I wonder if I find the purpose for
it up here
um
[Music]
he's gonna drown it was near where I
found it okay okay okay
higher
and we got much higher
oh hi it's a nice song
I don't know what you guys say it's so
cursed it sounds really pretty
higher higher higher high
oh what is this
is this a reference to
um that rock climbing game because they
look like them with long long legs and
long arms and they climb up a mountain I
saw the game too I considered it for the
Frog week but I don't have perms perms
for it
there's another Cube
ah I looked into so many frog games most
of them are
kind of lacking oh wait there's there's
so many oh
there's several ones that I need also I
think I just sound like like a oh
interesting
like a like a plant over there
hey there it is
um
ah priorities all right I don't know
we'll bring the flower first
and
we'll eventually figure out what to do
with the Statue
maybe flower is important now but will
this also melt when I go down
there do it first
what
oh gee
oh no that's just a stone
okay let's go
down to the level
maybe maybe maybe maybe
hey
here here
okay I think I have to go up here okay
thank you
[Music]
I was thinking maybe here but there's
nothing really here
but
jump oh
but does that mean I have to bring the
other ones down too so that they can
melt first
there were several cubes though
I only need two more are they like
um fake ones too much
[Music]
okay
oh
so we bring them down quickly let's show
are you the one
are you the right one I hope so you
better be
don't act with me I got a gun
oh
yeah the door
and here it will start melting
let me pour some water
while it's melting
you know in Japanese the way you write
Kiana and the way you write frog kaido
if you combine them I become quieter
[Laughter]
it's written the exact same way as Kaira
is written in Japanese
I was I was thinking about whoa how can
I combine up
it was fake what is
I was thinking how can I combine
kaido and Kiana and then I was like oh
I don't think I can use this there are
fireflies here
maybe maybe kiaru
but now
um
for now I'm going with froggy Wawa
thank you
Keanu Reeves
the only one who thought of that
Toad's rule frogs drool
yes no no I don't draw
I don't I'm more sophisticated I'm a
pretty sophisticated frog
foreign
beefy frogs
yeah I'm I'm not dead I'm cute bubble
bubble frog
eat
so great
okay the other one was fake so let's try
this one I have a feeling this one's
fake too but who knows
take
hi let's see is this a bug though
maybe if I sleep at night it will be
gone but looks like a bug
how old I am uh
I'm On Top
Pokemon one too
I don't think it's it that's not it
look at them look at them falling in
love with me
okay okay
no
home according to cake
all right all right all right if it
wasn't those two then hmm
it must be you and where's the last one
that's two statues
let's only ask you ice cubes I got
or do they only melt into what I want
during the daytime no way
waiting wow stretch stretch
[Music]
hahaha
what it is
all right maybe all the other ones are
somewhere else
[Music]
you're two hours late what the [\h__\h]
and let me get the flower for now
um
[Music]
welcome new Temple to Kettle Fried
Phoenix
for breakfast I eat kiddos
headaches
get it
thank you
[Music]
see I'm funnier than her
I'm funnier than her
even
is this melting it doesn't look like
it's melting hot it's just gonna be
forever Frozen nice so exactly what we
need but oh they're not gonna be there
too
but this maybe will not respawn maybe
this will not respawn but let's see if
he's in here because it's open it is
open oh
oh
I got it
okay okay I'll throw it in there
oh
hey
[\h__\h] no no let's try on this is
dangerous
I mean maybe get on the on the stove
uh-huh
[Music]
who wants a cold one
Ice Ice Baby
make it cold yeah yeah oh
can I turn it on
not yet
do you need more
no he seems to satisfied ah he wants me
to sleep okay
good night I guess you need a break too
from working
I sleep sleep don't go
where
uh I'm looking
looking so cute there your tails are so
cute you know
how are you
actually got Toto
I guess I'll go all the way down here
somewhere here should be
Maybe
huh
huh huh
I'm lost again kiddo but keep on going
down eventually there you go I got a
real uh saw realized notice that you had
like a a rooftop balcony
fancy
how to make a fire with
froggy Wawa
when you're scared of it
don't don't get too close to the fire
otherwise ah
you'll burn
Phoenix Lane frog is future good for
everyone
now
Phoenix sucks
Phoenix very much sucks
don't like Phoenix
make fire phoenix Phoenix eat frog
[Music]
um
[Applause]
foreign foreign
[Music]
workplace why what place this this is
not a workplace
um
I'm not giving you a job
you just abide to my wishes because you
love me and you see me as a god it's
that easy
now you can work elsewhere I don't care
as long as you bring me flies back home
you're free hey sounds better now huh
oh can I turn it on
whoa
okay okay okay so first bring it to the
yoga guy
Ana
[Music]
took me so long to work on that now give
me thank you
ah finally
ah
we got the lamp so uh who wanted this
again someone in the village right but
who
are the market guy maybe I think it was
the market guy
the whale guy
oh welcome now give me wheel yes
[Music]
wow well don't really you don't need the
wheel
you don't need it
now now you can never move your store
again but thank you
[Music]
somewhat easy yeah I guess not really
everything's connected this took quite a
while
but this means we're only missing one
piece
can we get more tired no sorry I'm so
sorry
we're just missing one piece for the
boat and that is the Rope I know
with this thing in the back there too
we'll figure that we'll get it
eventually
already did quite a few things here
yeah I know it's from Lumpy's now
but I don't know why you guys think it's
so cursed I don't understand that yet
coming to me
hello
is real I am real
you like the model yeah yeah
[Music]
I like it too
okay okay uh someone else needed the
drink too I remember someone else asking
for the drink
[Music]
who was it she wants to ring
you want that
now you want something more
what is that
[Music]
change of plans guys
thank you friends
uncle and get the stone because I know
where the stone is
oh that's the ah he'll make
[Music]
it if I bring him that thing
see friends are so nice that's why you
guys should subscribe to my channel
because I'm not certain than the Phoenix
did you notice I even burp burp beep my
Christmas
Chris and beep burp now I don't burp I
beat my curse words that's what I was
saying
I tried
I mean the sound of the frog makes I
guess sounds a little bit like a verb
Maybe
I burp my keys words
I burp my cheese Sports
I chirp my
beads words
right
oh
wow
there you go do I place it on top here
let me put that away yeah I got it
now I am making it here
I thought so
okay I waited today okay thank you but
maybe I can do something else maybe I
can find the person who wanted to drink
oh yeah
am I remembering it wrong but I'm pretty
sure somebody else wanted a cold drink
um
[Music]
you're wondering about the Bell well
you're not getting that one back I think
or do I have to bring it back maybe I
can find a new belt but then I mean I
guess we already have what we wanted
from the other person
the chef oh I mean maybe he just wanted
maybe he has something to say oh
is that what's this thing
oh
what just happened
that that that was like a toilet
flushing sound
but that's what a drink came from
[Music]
huh
jump higher oh
frog
okay
um
but that would be like forever or only
for a certain amount of time because I
don't really need it now maybe there's a
place where I will actually need it
um
oh
can we talk much higher jump high
yes release my full frog potential
proctential Rock show what
you you need one I think I found one at
the top of the mountain I think I also
saw when someone somewhere else but um
that's the one I currently remember I
think that was that sort of hammer right
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
she told me when she thought I was her
friend which I never was
she told me that around debut time
she was thinking because you know she
finds it really cute to end sentences
with something get off like I do get off
because I'm superior girl but she
couldn't think of anything that would
fit
her you know as a phoenix
so there you go I'm once again Superior
in every way
oh the cubes are back
or maybe now maybe no they will give me
this one looks stiff no whatever I
wonder if I try again if this time they
will for some reason oh
this is new no is it not new
[Music]
anyway I was wondering if they gave me
the figure now the statue but anyway
this is the hammer
step by step
the person didn't think of anything for
you was an attempt but of course it
doesn't really make sense so she
couldn't use it forever
well
unfortunate
but I'm having fun kiddo I hope you're
not annoyed by the cat okay now but I
can't help it I'm proud kiddo
um
[Music]
foreign
they went to the same school as me and
those frogs why are you sleeping
or not all right let me find a place to
sleep again
yeah yeah we went to the same school and
we had a school reunion
uh like a couple weeks ago
yeah and I met them
back in school days they were kind of
mean to me
but now suddenly you know they were like
suddenly so nice to me I wonder why
maybe they know maybe they heard that I
I'm acquainted with
takanasikiana but little do they know I
was only I was only giving her attention
because I wanted to kill her and take
over her Channel
which I successfully did
Papa
and if I met them again now they would
probably be like a yo we found a new
respect for you wow you have your own
Army now
it's like this like suddenly when you're
more oh oh it's a grave ah
that's why he likes the plant because it
grew from her grave oh I didn't know
humans can can grow plants
when they die
shut up bird
anyway what was I saying oh yeah yeah
it's just like when you when you are
suddenly like
successful or so
that people suddenly nice to you
um
I thought this was only a human trait
but then I saw these frogs doing that to
me and I was like aha I see how it is
we're all the same in some way we have
similarities
cannot
oh wait what was I bringing this to
not to you right okay wait you you have
something else for me
aren't you finished with my thing
um but this this goes somewhere else
wait let me leave it here let me bring
this to my phone I wasn't to the wood
Chopper to chop chop chop
okay
oh
what what what
the wood cutter yeah yeah yeah
I feel like it makes more sense of this
guy though because you know
the other guy chops wood wouldn't he
needs like um
like a zig attack zigzag machine
[Music]
oh we're so close how long have I been
streaming two and a half hours but then
I messed around in the beginning a
little bit so more like two hours of
gaming
I wonder if now maybe I caught up a
little bit with the like the the game
progress get up
and see nothing's done up
ah
you know
they're supposed to bring this to the
right person
in all kind of
knocking this guy looks a little bit
like you know from from that golf game
lamb called game
because of like he looks kind of like
you know crazy
what is he doing
is he throwing up Kayla
you cannot let's get away from there
quickly
oh no he's froggy he's frogging I'm
frogging too we're all frogging are you
frogging
stand back he's frogging
where is he
what
don't go
okay no
[Music]
honey
what
is daytime Wednesday
morning
yeah he keeps on moving around
[Music]
yes yes you're gonna make something for
me now
um
[Applause]
and what is that oh a statue a ring and
is that a scarecrow head maybe I don't
know what do you want for this
gold coins gold bar gold bar gold bar
gold bar gold bag gold bar
can we please
there's true now was there always two
can you please make
gold coin what if I just bring the gold
coin no the gold bar probably not enough
I would think
on Instagram
foreign
[Laughter]
he made another one
did he make a new one in case I lose the
other one where did the other one go oh
what are you making how long is it gonna
take
okay
what are you doing
you're making the bridge
for a bird no
no
okay well do you need something what
no you're just gonna do it on your own
all right all right all right all right
all right okay
please tell me how do I get gold coins
how to get gold coin
someone wanted the feather ah baby from
that bird yeah
[Music]
tell me
tell me how to
get gold coin
nope Matt the belt
why if I have gold bars here
let's see it all
right
maybe oh Merchant will give you gold
coins for trading items with him trading
when he was asking for coins though
well let's ask him again sometimes
sometimes Maybe
[Music]
something all right baby
it seems so so in reality we're not
buying the things of gold coins or
buying them with sunflower maybe he
wants all the flowers
one flower one coin
so we need the
[Music]
um
maybe he wants the the sunflower when
it's like um nighttime
the non-sunflower and then maybe the Ice
Flower but other than that I can't
remember any other flowers
at least the ones I can pick you know
these ones like in pink
yay ah zombie on Yolanda oh that game I
know that game I played it a few times
when I was um
one year old
one now I'm two
[Music]
what's the color you know
wait this is this comes as a flower too
um yes okay
so first of all I want to buy
uh the ring thank you
I take
yes
I take this thank you
thank you can you make it okay
I don't think so
I mean do you see it say open hand
and it closed
okay and then thumbs
ah
[Music]
my thumb is too small there's no
difference when I move it
um
[Music]
maybe height
hey
[Music]
guys
I'll I'll work on it I won't work on it
I'll try experiment a bit more
uh where's the lady
I know I know they're so cute you know
you know
um you know
when amen was doing
uh let's remove that small model that
she had with the hands I was like holy
[\h__\h]
I couldn't stop watching her because the
hands just off yeah let's take those
well you want me to get on my knees or
what
yeah keep
um
the new one ring though
are they you be welcome
oh what do you think
[Music]
what am I supposed to do with this now
what
did I buy it for nothing did she change
her mind
[Music]
foreign
uh a woman like her
okay I'll put this I'll I'll put this
smell here for now nobody's still mine
ring also can I turn on the lights for a
second it's getting dark or this dark
and I'm scared
[Music]
okay okay
ah
yeah
[Music]
I got night vision now but
um only two years old I'm still scared
who says that even if you have night
vision you shall not be scared you know
that was a danger wait I thought you
would want more flowers
[Music]
with a puff of wish once
and it did not end well
dear Lord are you for real I haven't
even seen one before
do I have to go swim swim
mer for the purpose
how deep can I even go can we get much
deeper
I'm drowning
foreign
what should we do
half a fish she didn't like the ring she
now wants uh the bee the the honey but
can I get it from
if I throw it against something so that
it will break sometimes things break but
like
this one will not break
come on oh yeah
easy easy but
she's probably Gonna Wanna kinda want
something else now
let's sleep first because she's not
gonna be awake anyway
for you like what I'm confused lady
it was frog ladies man they don't know
what they want
they don't know what they want
I sleep next to my honey
ah
fine okay
oh memories
what you already did
yeah hopefully we'll have another huge
[Music]
um
stop now I don't want to hear you I need
your ear thingies
I need to put something
you guys stop saying that your tadpoles
now you cannot say that word
it's forbidden you say okay okay no
where are your ears oh
um behind
my hair
I got ears
[Music]
let's see where did where is she right
now she always walks around too
I don't know
there you go take it take it
take it take it
she wants a pearl now
foreign
do we just break one of those uh shells
like we broke the beehive
I picked those shells up before but it
didn't give me you know unlike this one
for example
it doesn't look like it has a pearl
inside
of course I beeped it what do you mean I
just beeped it
ah
hey
[Music]
you need to I need to give her the ring
no no no she wants the Pearl
I don't know where the [\h__\h] I get a
purple hair though
it's the thing yes yes it's a pink
I beeped it on time I totally did get up
she always says she wants something else
how do I push it onto her to like force
her to take it
well let's talk to someone else maybe
I'm sick of her already what do you want
by the way get off
nothing oh he's happy wow at least
someone's happy and you wanna throw the
other fish
yeah we we were supposed to sleep and
then come back to him took it all
you know I
was telling me about that no no never
mind never mind never mind at all
I wonder look at the bridge
um
which Bridge get off
I am
froggy Walla get used to it or else off
or else
[Music]
you can get Pearls by picking up and
throwing clubs oh I was trying to hmm I
guess I was just not doing it the right
way
thank you dude you can stop now
oh oh look at the amazing progress I
guess with every night that I sleep he
will make more progress Maybe
no no no there's two more heads one the
lady has and one is in the shop
no
um
you want a glass bowl
on these things
what okay I'll try to remember that oh
oh I don't think we've been here before
no no no we've been here before oh hello
you want the
I want the feather oh yes
what does that mean
that way
frog froggy Mama emotes
oh I don't know man
I wish I wish I could have prepared so
much uh
foreign
begun
it will take some time for me to draw
them maybe I can try to keep drawing
some scuffed ones
ie
[Music]
now
oh
[Music]
and mold limited I would have to replace
the others I mean I can always bring
them back but you know
wait I thought never mind I was I was
imagining that this one is another one
of those heads but it isn't so someone
said they saw another one wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait
where did you see another one of those
heads
said it when I was walking around here I
think
one yeah even one single one I okay okay
um
even one would be good I agree with that
under there oh under a bridge yourself
oh oh wonder wonder
well
under
[Music]
ah
what are you saying that I don't see
wait
I'm stuck okay
oh thank God
that thing in there
you think so
[Music]
um not it
doesn't it kind of look like all the
other things
there but hmm
let me try let me try
I mean there must be a reason why they
put so many things here it looks like
they're telling you to try to get on his
house
[\h__\h]
what
yeah
but then from here on it's kind of
difficult
yeah yeah and the rope and the pole you
must still get oh okay okay
I may be then it's not that
mmm uh what should I do next
some things I don't know how to do the
jump up ah for that
the other one is at the beach to the
east the other
frog head
okay I'm gonna go look for it thank you
to the east
Gandalf never goes to east
but froggy Wawa is not scared
which means I am Superior to gandal of
kettle
believe it
oh
um
I am able to pop my cheeks yeah
look
um
where am I going
[Music]
is this the East Beach it feels more
like the South Beach
should I sleep maybe let me sleep first
Marty Monty Texas
[Applause]
please don't make French frog legs out
of me please
I've seen
I've seen things
look at me
you know I've seen [\h__\h] man and I can't
forget kettle
yeah one time one time I've been to
France
and I've seen that's why I'm scared of
fire to be honest I've seen them
burn
frogs
alive
and make them into delicious frog legs I
know we're delicious but ah
but but please have mercy actually let
me try again with this because someone
said I can't break then leave me I'm
just too clumsy
hey
don't have to come on
but there's no pearl inside
oh is there a special one or is it
around just random
[Music]
maybe that one that one
that one is flavoring
oh
huh
no this one I broke and it didn't come
with a pearl never mind
ah
oh let's go around here
don't ever know
I mean no no I don't
I do
ah look
I
[Music]
nose
you see it's hard to see maybe here
[Music]
I have a nose it's just hard to see
oh
oh cute cute little frog
[Music]
pick me up pick me up
pick me up
[Music]
wow
chunky belly hey
mmm
what did you say about my belly
I know I'm cute thank you thank you
I'm cute
so tell me what is the deal with the
with the pearls Kettle is there a
special one and a special place
and I have to break going to just random
kiddo
what
Is Random
it's so hard to break them
how do I break them efficiently
where did it go
down oh what is this one no oh yes no no
no
when she says she wants the pearls you
need to give it a ring no way girl
what's the name
you're funny
how would I know
and if I bring a pearl to her would she
say no
but then I kind of need to
read her mind oh is it like a thing like
eventually you would find out oh okay
when she asks for a ring she wants to be
high thing but when she wants to be
happy she wants to Pearl so if you bring
her a pearl when she's asking for a
beehive you win or when you bring her
the ring when she's asking for the Pearl
you win or soak at all
oh
[Music]
somebody else made
Sam
why why why my nose sense quite so I
want a diva
yeah
where am I bringing this again
here oh okay bye
we're back at all
right one more
one more
yo this is a big request when I finally
finished this one they better give me a
good reward candle
I wonder what they'll give me again one
more one more the last one
the last one I don't know I don't
remember any
locations get all wait
foreign
don't go away
okay East Beach someone's at East Beach
and I'm looking for a lot to get on
[Music]
when you say eastbridge do you know this
one is more like a southeast Beach dog
at all
what am I looking for
[Music]
um
I've been up here before
nothing here
wow
I mean honestly I'm surprised you can
even do that and there's not just an
invisible wall there at all in a lot of
games they're just lazy they're gonna
put an invisible wall there
this makes you just yeah it spawns you
all the way back in the beginning and it
kind of sucks but allow neon wait wait
wait
right there was the first one what
convenient respawn is it so what what
what what do you know what I don't know
nickel what am I
what am I currently
hoping to find
[Music]
go down okay
okay
oh yeah we know this place already
[Music]
we know this too
oh chocolate wait is this a flower no
I can't pick this one oh yeah and then
here I drowned myself get off
if you go to the Easter Island you have
to head to the most often but okay yeah
oh okay
okay
[Music]
having hands is so nice
it's such a blessing
oh yeah
I thought I could jump on the stone it's
okay it's not that far
oh what
oh
I thought it was a fish
we got bad
go back it off
[Music]
okay
am I going this way
well froggy shirt drowning
it's because I'm playing a human kid of
course I could do better
of course look at him he's not a frog
the game I would not drown
did you get that one already apparently
not
what what am I trying to get the head
I know that the first one was somewhere
else was not here no no oh wait up here
maybe I can go up here there must be
something there oh there's nothing there
foreign
guys I did go here before
did you just join the stream later and
missed when I went here
um
[Music]
go to town enter the fort fort
all right I'll try to go to the most
southern part of that place
meet you right for this one
meteorite
and don't don't don't don't don't don't
don't
Rose whole life
you know
I'm sure that they eventually want to
reach this level then froggy Wawa is on
but currently obviously froggy Wawa is
superior Kettle I know you're excited
but
you know
what fourth are you talking about I did
not say a fort I mean this is a
restaurant and I went there already oh
wait you mean this place
oh wait no no the guy is still there
Gaga
let me why not
wait
what what does he want from me
foreign
statues and [\h__\h] but why why is there
this oopalupa
is that your painter Quest he still has
something for me to do
what did the painter want from me now
is that their God frog is it implying
that frogs surf the oopalupa axolotls
what is he doing
oh he's going to sleep probably ah we
have to sleep again
hello oh maybe before you go to sleep
tell me what you want
no
okay maybe tomorrow then candle
froggy froggy got Street
oh
yeah I've been wondering if I can change
some songs up a little bit and turn them
into Frog songs
sleep
the more we sleep it's good anyway
because then the the bridge will be
created and then we can go over to the
other side and get the feather kettle
foreign
good morning
how can I help you sir
no what do you mean with his quest he
doesn't want anything from me
what's up
yeah wait a second
wait a second the Southmost did you mean
this part
wait a second you don't get off
hello
there's nothing here
no
I thought there would be something here
he needs it to deliver a letter
he didn't give it to me though did he
okay
Frankie llama mate you know like what
gouda has her
um Dino dinos dinos
[Music]
um merchandise maybe maybe we can make
me as a plushie but even if then we
would probably have to wait a long time
and
go to fisherman fisherman
fisherman
fisherman fisherman
left oh
ah
ah what does he want
s
just ordered small Kia there's gonna be
so many forms of small quinoa ones but
you know I'm not really koala I'm froggy
Wawa I'm different
so it's worth getting me
um
I want
[Music]
from I know where is he
wasn't he here
you said left oh wait no no no no no no
no no no wasn't it here on it
on it
[Music]
but there's something here there's like
a there's a platform I'm really like
hidden one
I wonder if those really matter at some
point
up and left I
assume
[Music]
up but I can't go left here so I assume
you mean this way first ah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
he just want some better
oh what do you mean
what do you mean
he pointed at the Axolotl statue
[Music]
and the guard wants that thing to be
gone while he wants to get he wants the
statue for himself
now go back to the Fort okay
the first time I talked to this guy
though
does it have to be in direct connection
at all
oh there's one inside is that so
hi Google gaga
oh
[Music]
love it
you in love with the pain yeah
oh sweet
okay
I am now Postman
[Music]
Postman Postman yeah
oh St man that makes no sense
and so that's a Christina Aguilera song
but I thought for a second I thought it
was post but then when I was singing it
I realized it's candyman candyman
candyman
oh wait a minute Mrs Postman yeah
oh a letter back it's invisible though
it's kind of see-through why is it
Seafood
why is this April
that's weird
but Super Chat bunny
okay okay
no candy candle froggy wow I heard you
turned old tense into swiss cheese my
suggested side of fairy to go down with
your Phoenix movie
Cola for a while and I heard they taste
like flies
you know I'm quite excited to meet her
tried to
meet
Palmer
that chick for such a long time
and she's never accomplished it but
but
um
easy Sanji
and the whole arrived again
management talked it out over a long
long time and finally finally finally
she could
Cool Math but
you know since they always wear it kind
of like a Romeo and Juliet
of the Beethoven world I was like
no pure and then I killed her so
it's even more like Romeo and Juliet and
I'm I was like is this not what you
wanted
is this now 21
think
it's a tragedy
It's Entertainment oh he's walking away
yay thank you
what the [\h__\h] is that is that a
H wait it's a frog then
has a mask on oh that's right it's a
frog with an axolotl face
oh you wanted to be protected ah you're
faking
bacon oh are you oh wait that's better
it's not from a bird okay
oh you want to replace it
oh is it like you know they they pray to
him because they think he's like
something he's super special but in
reality he's just a normal frog candle
foreign
let me get the flower first
um
but for the flower it needs to be night
time right
or is rain already helpful enough
a Lotus well we'll get there
it's [\h__\h] already
this is always following me so cute
look at them
that works I no I didn't swear what do
you mean
what's swearing get up
wait purpose
it's a beep
ah
you know yesterday before before right
before I shot
Kiana
um
uh
she was on the phone
with her mama
and I listened a little bit into the
conversation
mama told me it was
like praising her endlessly that GTA was
such a perfect fun playthrough and then
she did such a good job and then she
thinks now ukiwawa is ready to you know
play more of those kind of games
thank you
yeah she was going on and on and on and
on and on and on and and then Kiana was
like I need to I need to make food mama
I get it I need to make some food I'm
hungry
yeah yeah and she was like you have to
play Mass Effect you have to play this
and I will not give up
and uh
uh what else yeah she was just like
pushing up the bridge is finished
pushing and pushing and pushing but you
know Kiara seemed a little bit flattered
uh actually you know she was like
watching all the streams no matter how
long
um she really enjoyed it good for her
what
you you're giving this to me I thought
you sure
[Music]
my ship needs it
I thought he was gonna tell me that he
needs a rope and I'm like I need a rope
too though
let me just move myself a bit higher
okay
okay yay and then we take the Hat
and now we have all the scarecrowds
so so so so so what are we missing now
nothing
the plant
secure the sheets you want the plant in
the boat
oh that's so this is so emotional and
sad oh there we go no rain yeah yeah we
have to but we're not done yet
can I
uh I finished my boat
but there's still quests it's just not
frog race is this not it
why do I finish the boat before
finishing all the quests am I done with
the game
or I sail around the island but I feel
like the character would want to like
you know go somewhere else because he
just stranded on here it was not never
his intention to come here
hmm
[Music]
oh he lifts
no
wow
I got the last head candles
frog real
what are you asking
oh where where where where where where
where
foreign
oh oh but they won't react until
tomorrow
[Music]
yeah I get it I get it
are you on like a
I
in the night you're going towards the
Frog's ass
hmm
are you gonna go inside oh
I see
where is the wood
dunk
look at my eyebrows kettle
they're making taco
[Music]
that's right
oh
cute
I'm too young and I'm only two
two
not like really small children that like
they're like one and two or so they also
first they have to like so they look at
their hands and they're like
um
[Music]
they try really hard and sometimes they
have the fingers wrong
it's like me but I'm like really
struggling though
[Music]
oh man
Chinese
[Music]
hello do you have anything to say for
yourself
but now okay it's your business I I
don't I will not disturb you guys kettle
he would do you or you do him I don't
know man Carol your business your
business are you happy
oh
you're gonna make a plant that grows
these oh someone wanted those okay I
want to sleep can I sleep when it's
already daytime or maybe I can do
something else uh I cannot go over the
bridge let's see
let's see once you're at the bridge
foreign
[Music]
up again
oh wait it's not here
ah here here
oh
I said all of those portals oh
it doesn't have like a door like the
others
but I guess maybe this is the goal
well what this place is big
whoa
he'd only knock you know oh this one has
again this one's green
well how do I know where I even start
is it really a race around the whole
island kettle
another flag
Wicked
whatever what is this this looks special
too like I could blow it up with a bump
I can take this Stone okay
did you see one
and there's probably one seller here
I didn't see one though oh
more of those fancy stones
yeah more of those hmm
[Music]
okay
what blue with blue what do you mean
blue and blue
that was Green
what do you mean
tunic yeah I'm getting a small tunic
Vibes but that's just because of a big
world that I have to explore that's
filled with riddles it's I guess that's
a lot of games do that oh
is that looks like it would grow into a
bomb but what that what do I know
w
Wilson
what's that
what
[Music]
I'm scared
I blow up the bird
it's a dodo
drown the bird try the bird yes
[Laughter]
trying to be
I'll show you I'll shoot you
[Laughter]
and they've seen they seem relatively
peaceful
oh
green oh
wait that's the second green one I found
so is it green to Green
ah and you mean blue the blue and so on
but what to do with this thing
um and the birds the feather I thought I
would get from them but
um but so can I plant this one here no
huh
oh my oh my oh my
God yeah he carries it kind of like link
yeah yeah yeah
hey
whoa what
blue
[Music]
oh that's still that's the bridge
the white ones do you have the blue one
I only saw okay both green ones are on
this island at least
oh
on it
hmm
sass
by the way this there's a pink portal
also here
no
um a egg
Yoshi egg
oh no there's a Derek's wait didn't
somebody want one of those eggs
and feather but I don't need another
feather do I
oh my foot is sleeping it's like
tingling tingling tinkle tinkle
[Music]
what do you mean I look Shifty
replaced egg with Wilson
you think that will work
okay
no money I don't remember anyone
specifically asking for the ah
don't take my ink my egg
wait where do I bring it though
wrong way
you guys know where to bring it
okay ah
oh I lost two of them yay
oh they all gave up nice
grocery store
ah will that be the item that he wants
after the puffer fish
and I need the puffer fish first I
wonder if this this one will disappear
after I leave it's somewhere
where okay I really need I think a hint
where do I get the papa fish
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay it's fine we found a lot of
new things over on that side now
egg Broken Eyes too
you guys know where where can I find
them
from cage wait wait now he wants a
strawberry
wait does he also have the same problem
as this lady he asks for something but
he wants something completely
differently
quick let's get the strawberry
no problem though
changes every day oh no oh he resets
oh oh gladly wait do I maybe never have
to give him a puffer fish or once I give
him one strawberry it won't be an option
anymore
[Music]
Well for now I'm glad and I'll take this
and then I don't know what the other
thing is for this this one on the right
I don't know what that one is for right
now so I'll take this first Maybe
although it will not solve anything
because I still need one more of the
statues
feed my pets no
I'm gonna bring this
dinosaur
let's bring this up up to the mountain
holy [\h__\h] I'm getting so many meters
today
running so much this dude oh my God
must have
sore muscles after this adventure
I'm just running running running on The
Running Man
[Music]
okay don't kill
him
wait kiddo not here Kettle somewhere
else kettle
here kettle
I forgot
okay though
what was that
was it in uh was it in the ice region
I roughly remember I think it's up here
somewhere
I go up and then I go left and kind of
down I think
[Music]
uh what was it here
oh yes yes yes
[Music]
one more
I wonder what this will give me after
I'm finished
and which what comes first
ah maybe the jump I need for this one to
jump item
hey oh no I don't need it
but magical space
hmm
cute creatures bottom right you're
talking about me I
[Music]
mean
so what next
[Music]
um
in one of the NPCs tell me to come back
to him after one day and I said let's do
something else then I knew I would
forget it it's the one that I was
planting oh yeah yeah yeah yeah oh oh oh
sheesh
yeah I would hope that we're close to
ending it's that four to five hours so
since I'm kind of like probably slower
than good Gamers
um probably gonna be more than like more
like five hours Carol
um
[Music]
catch fish with the with cage at the
fisherman house
oh
okay
he's telling me
I will get more coins
at
whose house is that
but you think he will run out of does he
not just mean I didn't I don't know what
does he means oh
nice in a row you guys should get
married oh
it's not very Christian of you guys but
I guess you guys are not Christian
s
[Music]
congratulations
more memories
well these are memories that this one
we've seen before I think so now they're
just repeating
hahaha
it's ribbon and then kick any eats like
a collaboration
of chicken and frog
and okay
so what happened
it's not growing yet what
you told me to come back
down
oh yeah no no bears yes exactly that's
what I did for you
oh
you're still working on it how much
longer
oh Rome wasn't built in a day again
yeah oh
wait maybe that Wilson plant that I
picked up maybe that's what he needs
and now this guy
I'm knocking I killed her with this gun
did you see the video from yesterday you
should watch it it's 45 seconds or so
and then you will understand everything
and reach enlightenment
yes
it's my
Turtle I'm your new frog Overlord and
you better
support and believe in me you know
I can do many cute things I have fingers
see I'm better than Chihuahua I have
fingers and I can say I'm two years old
[Music]
cute right
uh what should I do first
um oh no next I guess
um
what can is there something that I can
solve right now
let me talk to you
[Music]
[Applause]
stop wasting your materials please get
off
yeah you missed you what one stop
missing her I'm back down
ah
I can do the gates
um
this is blue I don't remember what the
colors were of the ones that were I
guess it was one pink one
but I didn't see him
all right so we have a blue one and two
greens ones okay let's try the green one
then maybe
I wonder if it matters where I am too
maybe from the one with the door where
was the other green one
was like up up up up
we'll check it out
we have to have a feeling we need to
understand where are we going kettle
and just blindly run towards nothing
oh where was it
okay yeah if I saw the door triggers so
so the ones without the doors are always
the goals
maybe so the blue one is the goal so the
other blue one is probably not here so
okay this is the side
and I wonder if it's true that is this
straight Direction let's see
I was the other one
so froggy Mama turns Seth realm and of
Freddy like small amen
that would be amazing
[Music]
do they remember that I broke their egg
okay so I don't think it was this far I
remember it was a bit closer than
nothing
okay wait that seems like it was really
that direction
roughly at least
more or less but it's not like you can
actually just go straight can you
maybe you can
let's try let's try
get up can we jump there
get up there just have to walk around
or is that not enough time is that what
matters
do we need to jump much higher okay
let's try it once
how much time does it give us
and free I don't I want
[Music]
one [\h__\h] I already messed up
yeah
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
does this make me faster when I jump
okay I forgot where it was but it ended
that's here it's here
oh
do I look faster when I jump
on
all right I'll try to do it with them
with the frog jump potion
this human will become frog
or at least partially I see the broken
egg shows
so I remember he wanted a green apple
and something else let's bring the green
apple first
I guess we just have to throw it into
the big pot kettle
miles
green apple wasn't even here was it it
was over there with the with the bugs
and mushroom oh easy
they were like everywhere
oh
I'm lost it was close to this place
[Music]
huh
hmm
on it
[\h__\h]
um
[Music]
these Hold the Line south east south
Southeast
uh yeah probably more this way
nice jump six jump Kittle
oh yes yes here whoa they're eating
everything
oil and leave something for me
yeah I know them I want the green up how
do I pick a green apple
there you go okay green apple
and then
see here for example there's some
mushrooms let's remember that
I'll be looking all over even though
they're everywhere and I'll be like oh
where are they going
on
green like
nipples are the best so I'll leave this
here sir please wait
hopefully that
and then frog lady
won't what
eat my
Superior
green
Apple
no she's eyeing it where did I see the
blue mushrooms
well it was close to the water I think
here somewhere
Somewhere
Over The Water oh mushroom screw
yeah
but make sure to not eat them or you'll
be feeling blue oh
I went to five
y'all like this place wow wow I can
enter from here okay so do I just throw
it in there
let me ask you again
uh-huh yes I want to only
Prague
yes okay okay that's what I thought okay
[Music]
one
oh there's like a slot machine
don't gamble don't gamble guys make
make juice do I have to sleep over it or
are you gonna make it why does it take
so long
and you like your apples with mushrooms
um zombies and their weird taste I
prefer it without the mushrooms I just
want my green apple or or mix it with
some delicious fireflies
oh that's a good stuff
[Music]
are we doing only do a flip
oh they're sleeping by the beach oh
this was me I did that
this is the works of yours truly
we haven't talked to this person after
they made love oh
I guess I don't get a reward for it girl
all right
she was a skater zombie
okay
[Music]
drink
ah
it hurts my ears to hear that
suffering uh it's so painful to hear
that every [\h__\h] time every morning I
wake up one day I will straggle that
[\h__\h] chicken
and then there will be no mercy Kitty
key no no
more
all right now stop [\h__\h] around with
me give me that juice and please tell me
that it it's
it works for a long time and then I can
use it for my Marathon
if ideally it would be nice if it works
forever and I don't have to keep on
recreating it
huh you made it
huh
let me try
yeah oh oh can I drink more than once
maybe
oh [\h__\h] how long
huh
am I faster
oh no it doesn't feel faster it doesn't
feel like a jump higher either
don't drink immediately
I don't even feel like it's like
am I faster do I have to make it again
and then drink it when I'm there
okay
let's bring this summer thank you
and pay attention to how fast I am guys
and see if it ever wears off you're
flying faster when I get slower
I guess I
faster
I still need I need another item to make
it in time
and away
what do I need
I don't want to change the drink now
try it anyway even though you're already
telling me it's not enough can we get
much faster too fast
I'll play so I mean I feel pretty fast
right now but let's drink this
foreign
but I won't be able to jump fast at like
High Enough
maybe if I really only jump It's jumping
at least doesn't seem to Slow Me Down
okay I think I think
I think I'm faster
ah
close Okay no yes see never mind I
really won't be able to reach it unless
I can jump high so that just makes me
jump further perhaps but I need
something also that makes me jump higher
it was better that was for sure
can I do any of them
right now kiddo
and then
drink more
more flat mushrooms and the brown spots
to make bonjour
okay
any which which ones any of them
uh
uh let me find the mushroom
huh
I wanna I hope I'm close to the end I'm
I'm getting a bit tired of it
because now like I solved everything
that seemed relatively easy
what is that
oh
it's just the eating apples oh come on
now the game is four to five hours
supposedly
I still need to go to the top now
blue
okay so this one all the way until
oh the other side of the bridge
[Music]
now
you can just skip all this stuff can I
how
this one had a long one yeah yeah you
can already get in the book yeah I guess
so I guess yeah let's see what happens
if I get into the boat
is that the end of the game
but then what about what is the meaning
behind all the I guess maybe just for
completionist but it feels like
I was
I don't know it's too easy to
achieve this
foreign
love you oh no he did
well I mean it's it's raining okay well
we can solve that probably
well that's ridiculous
okay I said I'm getting bored of it and
I would be happy if it ends soon but
that would be like I don't know it feels
it feels
feel some
incomplete like to his sudden so sudden
too easy
there should be more like
oh big celebration I didn't even get all
the shop items
and I still I just don't know what
I didn't even fill up all the statues
what about the statues
I don't want to go yet I'm still curious
about some things
where do I get the how do I get the last
statue do you guys know
foreign
right side whoa you did you do the whole
thing did you complete everything
I want a girl but not really yeah I
don't know this is a weird ending it
doesn't feel right
[Music]
right side right side
um near the teleporter
um which one
which one
the one on the beach
let's go to the beach beach no need for
beeping that one out because I said
Beach b-e-a-c-h
so
that's okay
so yeah that was a teleporter uh up here
yeah
I said Beacham so what what what I'm
here
do I use it or is it somewhere
and I've already got one the one from
here you know that
should I use this
I have to do four gray spots
uh four
these ones these ones
what
hmm
and then
mushrooms and she told me to bring a
mushroom
was there any mushrooms here
um but that's why there's like tiny baby
mushrooms growing around it it's like a
hint
Italian to the plants more
mushroom foreign
[Music]
no
don't like mushrooms
[Music]
mushroom down oh thank you
I'm fascinated by my face oh and here's
the red one I never I don't remember
seeing the other red one the other side
okay one here hi oh
hi hi
I need all of them it feels like I can
already reach the top though but okay
let's do all of them
okay no I'm not gonna do the race I I
want to complete a few more things if
possible but wait foreign
[Music]
but not the race also there's just three
mushrooms here
where did the other one go oh
I need one mom grow faster
one more
yeah it moved right oh my God you know
everything in the game
you're amazing did you did you play the
other frog games too that I'm playing
[Music]
oh
up a bit okay
maybe they're secretly to developer yeah
I wonder I wonder you know maybe some of
these games they're pretty small this
one is maybe one of the biggest games
that I've chosen
and turn himself like
how much exposure they have
ah there you go
I wonder if any of the games Developers
see this and they're like oh my God a
frog tuber is playing our frog game
let's go
I did it another one
oh suddenly oh really oh really
okay thank you
foreign
now I'm really curious to see what
happens when we put that in the spot
where it belongs to kettle okay no clock
Ribbit rabbit
this one is kind of a broken eye
crab Army invading the island
who is this new fresh Rocky but who
started out with 1.4 million Subs
fastest growing Beethoven in the world
one day 1.4 million
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm not surprised I always expected this
at all
so does this mean I can make them
everywhere oh oh
wait where does this lead
great oh Nani Nani
hey do I get something like a hook shot
at some point because I still wouldn't
be able to continue from there
well now I think the thing that I
learned from this is that you should
always be carrying a mushroom around in
this game because
uh it's just a shortcut
you should always carry one around so
you can plant them everywhere once you
see one carry it and the next spot where
you see
a place where you can plant it and plant
it
well don't be tired
no time to rest oh
I'm gonna you know since Kiara is dead
I'm gonna eat her leftovers from what
she cooked yesterday I'm gonna eat that
today I think
oh also
oh my new I guess not mine but Kiana's
new hello fresh order
should be arriving soonish so I'll see
what she ordered and then maybe I'll
I'll give him don't give it a hand at
cooking what
it's like a diamond here
yeah I'll um
I'll try cooking I don't want to waste
food right you know I hope they send
something with flies or bees or or
fireflies or anything really and if any
bugs sound I don't care Oh pink
I'll be lost
don't worry I'll get there I'll get
there
not the bees well don't worry don't
worry
don't worry about me I'm hungry I have
to eat something
here
oh what's gonna happen
oh
what
what do I do with this I don't remember
anyone asking for this is
I ran
um frog
family no don't play this jelly I think
it's um
like Ruby or something
oh well I want to jump over there
ah it's just decoration for if I build a
house
oh
and how hard is it to build a house in
this game
is it quite an effort for me now
one coin what
who do I bring it to
I need one more coin now let's ask the
dude what he wants for a coin tomorrow
[Music]
it's the pink oh oh I hope it won't
break oopsie oh I don't know the oh
where is this oh he's inside probably
huh
oh this place is way too unprotected now
it's not one more round
you know
look at his eyes bouncing every step he
takes it's kind of creepy
[Music]
all right I'll I'll put my statue to
where I sleep I think a fire should be
ready for me
[Music]
unless it's disappeared
still there nice
and we'll put this
here
sleepy time
[Music]
strange
um
froggy cute I want to be forever
[Music]
foreign
okay uh let's ask what he wants for the
house for the coin I guess
oh should I bring something just in case
maybe he wants a strawberry again
probably not that's that would be too
too lucky
though
tell me
Leaf juice
no I don't care about doing that no no
one more day
oh is there one novel thing I can
fulfill your
the belt let's try to bring the Bell
back I guess
um
[Music]
am I able to bring the other one and
it's been four hours now
no
oh
no no
hold jump for frog jump
I'm holding
oh wait he's he barely reaches me oh
look
this way
I don't know how helpful that is
all right
um this is so weird that I'm able to
take this away from him
that's so weird actually
oh and that in combination with the
speed potion
could be pretty good oh
Nana sorry I killed your friend Kiana
but and I I don't really like boots very
much they kind of you know they scare me
because they wanna you know eat me
um but if you swear to never ever even
think about eating froggy wow then we
can be friends together
how about that kiddo okay
[Music]
and I have hands
Kiana did not have hands
so I'm better than her
and then you're gonna take this where
are you not yeah yeah you were you're
the one you take it oh sorry
do you want me to place it
she'll be remembered I guess rip yo wow
thank God Kiana is not alive anymore to
hear how
how surprisingly un worried and
unbothered you were by her death
when was this I hear here was it here no
no no no it's on top of the house right
on it
[Music]
am I bringing it back to the same place
where is that place
oh yeah no
it wasn't here
was it on on that thing no
[Music]
on top of the church what is even a
church like nothing here really looks
like a church
that's not a church maybe this ah okay I
mean yeah when you see more of the roof
I guess it looks oh a bit more like that
do I have to enter from the top again
[\h__\h] look at that
break down
just need to be able to jump a bit
higher because okay I am a leapfrog now
okay no but
it doesn't go very high
oh yeah I wonder what Kobo will think
about this
hmm
okay so from here
oh yeah oh yeah
there it is
back I saved this city you happy oh
blah blah blah you want an uh a frozen
drink oh but then I have to bring the
frozen flower and down again and then I
have to but okay I won't do the race so
I don't really need
oh yeah I don't really need them the
drink that's there currently I guess
yeah all right but I kind of want to see
the
in combination okay well now you know
I'm curious God damn it
they got me
this is not this the speed potion
[Music]
huh
does this look different to you guys
than before I guess
a bit it goes a bit further
[Music]
Yeah by living here he's more than
worthy coming in front Canal he's sat
back he's frogging
I saw
terrifying question in the chat I can't
even say it out loud
I don't even want to think about it
what
okay now I feel like ending it
is the question but now hmm yeah
unless we wake up and then he wants a
night and then I can deliver to him
easily
[Laughter]
yeah
wants to oh he wants to do something
else
also froggy Wawa actually needs to stand
in for Kiara and record some things
I finished some things
all right oh I wanted to tell Arena
something
but I'll do that though off screen then
I when are you going to sleep are you
still watching are you really gonna go
to sleep now
[Music]
for sure okay let's check one more time
I didn't know he would be asking for so
many different things
[Music]
[Laughter]
I guess I can she already yeah I already
recorded it so I guess I can just use
what she recorded uploaded and then take
all the fame and money that she gets
that I get from her singing yeah why not
I mean I'm ruthless like that
huh it's the same thing
ah [\h__\h] you
oh
what what did Ollie write
well now I remember what
thank you
I start reading today
let's get out of here
oh hello
[Music]
bye bye bye bye thank you frogs ah it's
so nice but I have to say goodbye froggy
wobble goes on her own Journey now
[Music]
[Laughter]
quinoa
[Music]
okay this is like a frog head on my boat
is that a living frog or a dead frog
[Music]
uh hi
hi okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
I guess he wants to become a pro
playing
[Music]
yeah that was fun
that was fun
[Music]
cute frog game there needs to be more
frog games
let's go to my lily pad
I [\h__\h] wrong no
oh
[Music]
hello thank you for watching I guess
I'll read Kiana's Super Chat
I mean for me now right because Kiana
finished all her super chats before
she left she died and so
I didn't say I said f e q
ah
okay
I guess I'll read them here
how are we gonna read them though I
don't know German kettle
soup
okay
okay let me see him
you know
I'll say quack
I'll say everybody's name and then quack
how does this work again with
um
it's my first time using this
also it was my first time playing a game
first time doing anything
wow I hope I hope I hope this was
um
a good introduction to froggy Wawa
[Music]
I'm a streamer now you
know you're very cute froggy and Mama
I think everybody is convinced of their
new RC
oh
frogs speak Spanish in Germany
what no that sounds like a whole load of
[\h__\h]
okay though
[Music]
oh by the way apparently there were two
super chats in the video
of kiwan was
demise open on Mike and Jacob 47 at
quack
what was it life when I type in
real time right real time instead of
something else
am I doing this right candle
oh yes it worked
okay okay let's go
Skye quack
it doesn't sound perfect okay it's okay
okay okay okay
I see I see a bunch of you have
um frog hoodie on in your profile
picture now very cute kiddo
I've long hoped
oh you missed out on a ponder it should
be hopped
I've long hoped for at least one frog
stream but he blessed us with a whole
week
ah who knows maybe it will be forever
because she's dead now no
aren't worthy of this much cuteness now
I must make a humble request my own frog
still doesn't have a name
do you have a suggestion
oh
what it doesn't have a name
um
[Music]
if you don't wanna you don't have to
look at all
you don't have to just letting you know
[Music]
the name of the fly in my class
Jonathan
he won't be there for long now it's my
dinner for later so tomorrow it will be
a different fly
run the Flies barely enough for one day
come here January
come here oh
I don't know
okay go back go back
go back go left go back
no that was good
um
[Music]
that was just me eating my dinner what
the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
uh you know what you guys don't get
kisses you get licks
[Laughter]
don't say gross
the house yeah
[Music]
I don't know
you don't know
foreign
[Music]
went to Austria for a couple days and
just came back to Japan and I'm asking
them what they ate you know
you know
tell me
now let me get off
[Music]
the song I finished
foreign
[Music]
um
where was that when I lived in Japan I
found this Austrian restaurant that had
really actually legit schnitzel there
and I was really excited and I told you
guys about it back then so you guys must
wasn't a funky really
quick that's the only good thing they
have in the Bungie then
really
I told you guys about it and I showed a
picture and I brought jenma there to
look at all
um
[Music]
because
I I was thinking I can't be in a fungi
because if I if it wasn't a fungi I
would remember it was the fungi because
I don't like the fungi's atmosphere it
was Ginza so uh
thank you
foreign
[Music]
at all
that place you know I was really
surprised when I went there that it was
so empty and it was
I know the food was so good so I was
surprised that it was so empty
um I wonder if it's still like this now
foreign
[Music]
I was the only one eating in the
restaurant but I guess it was kind of an
early dinner anyway when I was there but
still I would expect some more people
the only people that came in they came
in to pick up some pick up something to
go I think they picked up bread
I think
or something you can take quite a things
quite a few things uh with you there
when I found that place when I was
living in Japan for a whole year I was
like oh this is my salvation because I
I lived there
um for one year I mean I lived you know
in total I lived there longer but this
was one year in a row with no break I
was planning to go back to Austria a few
times in between but then I couldn't
because you know if I left I wouldn't be
able to have gone back was terrible
timing
so I had to hold back
and that was difficult and at some point
I really want to eat some food from home
and I was looking and looking for
a place that would make decent Austrian
food but yeah and then finally I found
that place I was like oh
[Laughter]
let's go real real Austrian food yeah
um I was so happy I remember how happy I
was back then finding that place
and I had to bring Jen my Derek you know
Tony honey is
[Music]
the Moon restaurant
when would you think what would Gemma
think about you killing kiwawa though
well it's very much
um supportive of it because
um whenever she is not
I just point this gun at her and she
understands what's up
and then he gets it
of course she's supportive of it I have
a gun
hmm
come on you'll just support whoever
takes the crown you know if if I assert
dominance over a [\h__\h] mythical
Phoenix and I'm just a simple frog
then I think that tells you
who you should be supporting
yeah
okay okay
well well well do I spot a challenger to
my title of most famous frog
listen tiny I took down Frogger took out
Fiona's King dad and bodied the 73 other
characters just named Prague honey if
you wanted to surpass the Kermit you're
gonna earn I have to earn it
I have a gun
a Kerman Kermit that mother
you're going down you're gonna go yeah
oh no he's dead
[Music]
we're finally free from Kermit the Frog
okay okay
[Music]
you're welcome guys I know I know I know
you guys wanted to get rid of him
because he's the most annoying frog in
existence
but he no more existing
he tells me I like to be you know for
Android with my other frog mates but
if you challenge me then then we have a
problem
It's Not Easy Being Green
yes Kettle
um you know
there's definitely like quite the
barrier between green frogs and the
other frogs because the other frogs are
very dangerous and poisonous so normally
we green frogs we like to stick together
and work together
and don't be like them
in Alabama no
no
[Music]
I like pears yes because they're green
those are the friends they're [\h__\h]
toxic so oh and toxic so we wanna
stay away from them you have to let go
of all the toxic things in your life and
one of those was those other colored
frogs
some people might call this um
frog discrimination but it's only for my
own good they're toxic
for real
yeah
it is what it is
looking for the Frog no looking frock
the top and you wasted
wasted an opportunity ah looking frog
the frog frogging frock the frogs
[Laughter]
now I should just be looking for the
Frog what are you doing
also frog is here now
no more looking
found frog found frog founding for the
Frog
yeah
okay
it should be dead okay
it sounds so cute how did you not come
up with this until now what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
yeah okay though
[Music]
it has a nice sound to it doesn't it
change your name
no now
[Music]
uh for the pinky I'm very sick at the
moment high fever and all body hurts oh
do you have to
the kiddo no
I'm so sorry but I can't interact much I
promise to stay loyal and still watch
stream from start to end there's no
typing also I love your PJ voice pack oh
yeah that's perfect for that kind of
situation
that's actually perfect that's exactly
what it was made for get all have fun
get on get well soon
but yeah take time to rest and sleep and
drink
water hydrate yourself you know
yeah don't force yourself
[Music]
um
thank you
perfect
[Music]
for two pinkies Skye frog
hi froggy mama please give this message
to Kiara attention in last two months
I'll get transferred to a lousy post and
your stream gave me so much fun in those
times the next week finally I will get
transferred to a much better post oh but
in the meantime I will start being busy
out there that is a 24 7 post
of course I will try my best to watch
your stream but if you are aware I show
a bless that is because I'm working
love you Kiana
now let's fight you chickens ah
are you living in the past my friend but
and wait to let you oh
next week you get transferred but until
then
you're working like 24 7. okay so it
won't be for long you're you're missing
out probably
it
terrible terrible
terrible I'm so sorry
oh well
oh wow wow
this just acceptable yes
yes
it looks much better now
[Music]
thank you Skybox so here you get a lick
look
out
okay
[Music]
47 out kennel okay now for the red super
chat
belated congratulations finishing GTA 5
yeah I don't know if Ariana will ever
let her read Disney
but it was one of her finest flavors in
two years and uh Joy all the way through
I I will you know I'm I like taking
credit for things I didn't do so thank
okay you and uh yeah she ran the
feedback from many people
um
a lot of people said this was one of her
top three playthroughs ever best one if
not the best one yeah and she was very
happy until I killed her so
thank you
[Music]
old old debits Die Hard yes old old
habits damn can I dab
[Music]
its
damn hard oh man
okay
other length
hey
also I'm not playing music because we're
hearing water sounds but I guess I
should maybe be playing a little bit
music
I like this one
I thought it's fitting
you like it
boom
[Music]
everybody get down the floor and tweak
and twerk and twerk twerk twerk twerk
little candle
[Music]
okay
Redlands
[Music]
okay okay no the Frogger Creek
I think even now
when Chihuahua is gone you still support
this frog yeah perfect perfect
just how it's supposed to be
[Music]
so frog twerk was also in October
oh my God
where have you been my whole life well
have you been
all my life
oh my life
where have you been all my life and
where have you been all my life
where have you been all my life okay
thank you for the pinky Wiki Tunes
I'm here now so the waiting is over your
whole life you waited for something you
didn't even know you were waiting for
eign
[Music]
what's frog sound in Korean I wonder
do you have a special
[Music]
oh
I'm so hungry I want to eat some flies
I'm so hungry
[Music]
yeah it's a delicious fly right in front
of me when I'm saving it for later I
need to win you don't want to see how it
happens you don't want to see them
snack
I need heart eyes
[Music]
I'm answering some messages that Kiana
got
people still surfing does this go into
account belongs to Kiana well it really
doesn't
I really know he does but um I guess for
some of them you know I'm
I'm I don't want to shock them just yet
so I'm still making them believe
continue to believe that I am Kiana
[Music]
I'm like her assistant okay I'm
answering her messages she should be
thankful kiddo but she can't because
she's dead
so and thank you for the pink Super Chat
oh wow from you all his hands I'm no
longer Temple yeah I never was scared
okay I was born like a frog because I'm
superior
yeah I was born into this body
thank you um
[Music]
I mean if you read it for like two years
like that of course
be hard to brush off
[Music]
um okay
oh wait oh
[Music]
did I just hear oh
let me check real quick
okay okay
[Music]
thank you
Kayla
Williams
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
my God
[Music]
mama
I need a I need a pacifier
okay okay all my food is here
[Music]
I need time
[Laughter]
[Music]
no let's see y'all
foreign yeah
[Music]
I don't want to continue annoying
preach you and ask
because
um yeah they work they both work so fast
but I feel like I could ask for a
million things because froggy lava has
so much potential but I don't want to
like ask for too much but a pacifier
Imagine The Pacifier with
you know actually moving along with my
mouth like this because it doesn't do
that for Kiana
right
imagine when I finally talk or anything
most ideas
a rattle yeah for the other hand
because I am kind of like a baby in a
onesie
um
[Music]
can you use PNG as my oh I guess yeah I
can't um yeah yeah I am
to be able to I haven't tried it yet but
it should work yeah
[Music]
I'm gonna experiment a little bit like
tomorrow or so
[Music]
I'm done in one hand and then the rattle
the Rattle and the other hand
cute
okay let's continue I wanna go eat some
flies
foreign
[Music]
it's too perfect at all
okay okay
let's go
[Music]
can't open up or else I kind of want
glasses you know I'm already smuggling
this but oh sunglasses sunglasses and
the bubble bubble
mouth thing and a rattle oh I want so
many things
[Music]
um are you okay Lorna or perona
candola if anything
Carolina oh you can call me call me
but I mean oh honestly wow wow
it's fine too and I don't want to make
you guys get used to too many things
it's hard to adjust I understand
was your go-to all the streams and then
you go then you don't need to get used
to it
[Music]
I'm not making progress okay at all
where I was like I know
look s good okay
[Music]
okay
dangerous
also artist can knock it off
fried frogs
um
yes
most of them should transfer I guess but
as I said this is not a job anymore for
you guys
you volunteer too
support me
as you should
you're volunteering aren't you
all are volunteering right volunteering
[Music]
I know I know what you are
Jerry couldn't understand I'll get all
frog frog get out there you go oh I
didn't even think of that one for you
thank you
for the pink okay oh maybe I need to
wear flies oh
um that's um yeah that would make you
look quite Charming to me kettle
maybe a little bit too much
Charming okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
looking frog the top okay
huh
um
foreign
of course I'm
[Music]
going to see Frank and I'll get on
don't you see it look at me it's so
obvious
is my wife yeah right now he's dead Give
Up
give up
[Music]
you know
Juan Carlos Rodriguez
okay
the middle of reading it
that's taking okay
yeah thank you thank you
I never thought I would have to watch
this I can't decide which side I'm on
frog yeah maybe the absolute cutest
being in the universe but quinoa was
also just ask you oh thank you but she's
dead you both are just the two perfect
this is way too hard I can't decide you
don't have to decide I took the decision
upon myself and decided for you okay
oh yeah
but you're lucky to have a replacement
like me okay no
other people are not this lucky girl
[Music]
I didn't watch you can knock it off
flies oh
come on
[Music]
random collusion can look it up with a
red Super Chat uh hello fraggiana I'm
Fabian oh
hope you have a fun time this week and
get to eat a lot of delicious bugs
thank you I hope so too
I wanna I wanna eat all of them now now
with this much money I can like import
the most most
Mmm delicious luxurious
[Music]
um flies that there are
you now it's better
[Music]
random collusion come here
Shawnee
boy can look at all for the pinky Toad's
rule from Central oh yeah
[Music]
knock it off foreign
you'll get you'll get some Kettle points
yeah the bigger and the crunchier the
better
crunchy fly good fly
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I think you know on
um Saturday
uh I'm you're gonna see froggy Wawa in
full maybe not only on Saturday I'm
gonna try to which game was it VR Rock
brog now
I don't know how to do it but I saw
other members when they play VR games
they have themselves like their full
body
somehow on the screen right
uh I'm gonna ask how to do that and then
I'll try to do that so you see my frog
body
moving a bit more
um
[Music]
um I don't know what what model of
Palmer Williams I don't know
she may have told Kiara but Frankie Mama
doesn't know
you know
but at least for a while I want to show
her
froggy Lala but we might have to
interrupt the lore for a little bit for
that stream okay no
I I don't want anyone to make weird
comments about that kid on or else oh or
else okay
[Music]
at the Lord
my version ah you know I would have been
[Music]
like
um biting myself in the butt because
when I think that if I put the VR collab
with Palmer on Sunday as my last stream
then I could create a lore where she
kisses me I turn back to normal for Wow
and then the week is over and hooray
while once but I'm just saying that here
this is just you know off of the record
that would be so good
but it's too late but maybe maybe we'll
do that anyway and then we'll just act
uh well we'll continue Sunday as normal
and then we will act as if the thing
that happened on Saturday actually
happened on Sunday okay
[Music]
it's it's kind of like all over the
place
and mixed up and that is a whole mess
entangled but
yeah yeah Sunday is pre-recorded uh yeah
yeah yeah yeah remaining content so
froggy Wawa before Kiana returns yes yes
yes yes yes yes
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign foreign
[Music]
and what was I what was I what was I
where was I where was I
oh I got here
frog gardening
plus welcome back to celebrate your
brand arrival what dishes may I prepare
for you frog legs lasagna fried frog
legs or your favorite butterfly cake
I'll go for the flies like what the hell
obviously
I don't eat my own kind no
[Music]
I read that one that was funny
into swiss cheese I'm a chick
look at all you should change your name
to
ayama hmm
wait but I'm proud of being a frog me me
reading I am a chick at all oh no I
guess it wouldn't be that but you have
to think of something new this is your
chance it's been a long time since the
last time you thought of something new
I'm I'm not gonna you you're way good at
that kind of stuff so I'm Gonna Leave it
to you have fun
I'll leave this one to you
surprise me I probably won't even know
that's you because it will be the first
time in a long time and you'll Bumpus on
me Evans
foreign
[Music]
good morning and maybe good afternoon I
have a good friend who has just passed
to fight by an exam
oh I want to be a firefighter oh I can
fight the fire I would like to ask Angel
to bless her before she goes in for
training she has only just started
watching videos so I will recommend
tattoo first oh interesting timing for
her to start watching me
hope she will become a Carefree citizen
in the future oh thank you thank you
fine good luck and everything I'm not
Kiara but I hope this is good enough I'm
better than her anyway
fight to fire today
Let me refresh
okay
[Music]
I think I already read this one just she
had a wonderful GTA play for her and she
deserves to be remembered did you just
say the same thing as someone else
look by the way insanely cute and
looking forward to the recipe
[Music]
[Laughter]
so much I'm glad you enjoyed today I
really
um I'm thinking about what to play next
but for now
I mean we have a little bit of a buffer
now until Pokemon is still one month
left so either I play Fuller games all
the time or maybe maybe we can revive
Minecraft a little bit but I'm not sure
I can team up with oh did fun okay
asking the people who know watch
everything
say anything about plans of killing the
um what's what's uh it's been a while
what's his name
the wizard The Wizard
[Music]
she wants to
what did she say like if she's planning
it anytime soon oh they're gonna do it
with Council
she did it with Council she wanted to do
it with console oh
[Music]
mmm
um
[Music]
okay all right I'm asking her if they're
still like really planning on doing it
um with Council and if not then I offer
my body to you for now I'm green now
Philadelphia how long but I'm green like
you
[Laughter]
[Music]
you we're green bodies
let's see I mean I totally understand if
she's like so
you know since maybe they made a promise
or so and then you know I understand I
understand if like you can't you know
but then I don't know maybe maybe I can
ask I don't know someone else I don't
know I don't know I don't know but but
maybe I can fill up you know a spot you
know okay okay they're only four now
ah I can be the fifth one you know I
don't know anyway I don't want no
pressure you know
[Laughter]
foreign foreign
[Music]
and I came on just to say hi but instead
of found the cutest
green frog ever a thing ever where have
you been my whole life or you're already
sang for you okay okay no I'm here
you seem to for one welcome your new
frog overlords
[Music]
of FBI Original London puts it into my
room captured me now I'm in a cell
message well of course this can't be
serious but if it's not serious and I'm
not sure like what kind of storyline
you're going for here I'm confused
should I be worried oh no Mike
let me worry
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
what was I have a double Jones
thank you
now partially the reason why it took so
long was because I was like I have no
idea how to like
um get around doing this
like how who do I ask for like I mean it
was clear for me who to ask for the like
creating the model preach you she did a
great job normally she does like Little
Pony stuff but everything is perfect
yeah
and then but then I was like how how do
I how do I get it to move and then what
what program and how do I set it up and
all that and yeah because I'm I'm using
it with like completely different kind
of you know Logistics and
um
and it took a while for me to figure out
and I was like I I was hoping uh I was I
was planning to get help from Ahmed but
um she was very busy at the time so I
I watched many tutorials but then I
followed the tutorials and then some
things just didn't work even though I
didn't exactly like the tutorials it was
like why
why not I always
when they do something Technical and
never works
and then I I continued trying and trying
and trying
and at some point it just randomly
worked I was like eh
why yeah
and then I tested it out and then I got
some fixes so the whole process actually
just really happened between a pre-chill
husk and me kettle
so I'm quite proud of myself I I knew
that I'm probably like relying on or I
used to rely on Ahmed a lot for many
things but I was like maybe this time
see I don't wanna I wanna rely too much
on other people but I had no idea where
to even start but
um I figured it out
I figured it out and
this what I'm using here for the hands I
actually
I had that lying around for even before
whole life
and this is the first time I'm using it
um
I don't wanna like break the immersion
or itself but yeah I was like I was
watching tutorials I wasn't even
expecting to use my hands you know but I
was watching a tutorial and and then
they said oh you can also connect your
with this program I don't want to like
say it to exactly because it really
makes it too real you know
um immersion perms lost
like for ages and
yeah
and didn't ever do anything with it you
know
and now I'm also this works and then I I
went to my box of many things get off
and I searched and searched and I'm like
oh yeah
it is no way it's gonna work that easily
right so I I connected it and I watched
another tutorial on how to make it work
properly
and then I got it to work too and I'm
like really surprised
LeapFrog motion
yeah I was really surprised
I was actually at this moment I was like
so glad I still had this ancient thing
from the past at all
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
set up and working I was really excited
to show you guys everything you know
yeah I normally a relationship with
technical things but makes me really mad
when I do things exactly according to
the tutorial get all and then it just
doesn't work for some reason there's not
even like a good reason for it at all
um and at least this time I figured it
out fairly quickly
but there's many other things that just
never work for me
it's not fair also my head starts to
hurt so ah let's end it
[Music]
um
yeah that does sometimes just likes to
not work yeah
so mean
[Music]
I have a lot of it hey what does that
mean big cat is cute
tonight
[Music]
okay
yeah I'm gonna Zoom from the for them
with me okay now get out for the rest of
the smallest froggy ones
oh they look delicious
and we're gonna talk about the different
types of flies and other flying things
and bugs so I'm gonna it says live
review but I'm gonna make some
bugs I think in there too that probably
don't officially count as flies but you
know for example ladybugs I love eating
ladybugs
so
yeah they're like tomatoes of the Frog
world
yeah they're they're the tomatoes of the
Frog World frog culinary choice
okay
yeah anything in that kind of category
[Music]
yeah I guess I should have done it in
the beginning I don't know I have some
regrets about the order of things of
this week
oh well
um
[Music]
I don't know if it's a big eye or a
small l
okay okay
[Music]
further on your schedule always match
with my work schedule but for the last
couple months I can't culture catch your
streams live I miss you and always
throwing me in the usual room oh I'm
sure the rise of Cafe is looking after
you okay well forever
boom
well
[Music]
I'm trying to stream as late as possible
for you guys like I'm starting some
streams like after 8 P.M I'm really
trying at least on the weekend you
should be able to watch me and please
watch my archive schedule
[Music]
please
it is the perfect time for me oh that's
good
yeah well I'm always trying to mix it
you know because I I can't abandon like
all of like a big part of you
yeah and I have to start some streams
early anyway if you know because some of
them are longer stream schedule
like RPG streams
um
so that'll start here's a pero pero so
you're staying with me
now you have no choice
[Music]
I'm freaking okay all right so if we can
hook it up
Crews get all get off for the pinky
loving this froggy Mama looks very cute
and Bob's birthday I can't think of
frothy names for myself got any
suggestions
[Music]
cruise is not much to go
off bye
you know like for example
with the kettle Creed or Froggy Fresh
and so on you know that's pretty easy
frogs
that's really difficult
[Music]
um
I would just call you frogs l
and it was the first I kind of like
fruits
fruits it's only like one letter changed
but at least
at least you got the F
all right well you have to add something
crucial
Cruise the Frog lover
[Laughter]
that Frogger oh yeah for you that works
[Music]
girl
um
it's the fake one again
before Shake It Off
yeah this one says frog leg cook Tango
[Music]
and uh
okay we're done
foreign tomorrow as well we're gonna
play frog game I think we're gonna play
uh Rock detective one and frog detective
two
since both of them seem to be kind of
like one hour
one one
one hour
one hour um
so we should be able to finish it fairly
quickly hopefully but I don't know how
smart this frog brain is
I don't know yet I have to do some
some good thinking use this brains
oh yeah I think I scheduled it one more
hour earlier than originally because I
added the other frog game just in case
but still even then it should not be
very long
look at all and
um
[Music]
ending green thing and all
um
[Music]
maybe something with ribbon like a pun
with ribbit
[Music]
rabbit
frog because no no German
[Music]
let's get off
you'd probably say rivet okay that's
cute too but there's not so catchy I
repeat
[Music]
the banana
and uh
I remember dancing
you know
enjoy your flies
everybody what do you mean you don't eat
flies
[Music]
I have no ending stranger let's go back
to the loading screen
[Music]
foreign
questions
[Music]