foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
no
[Music]
Okie
laughs
[Music]
yeah no bgm yet
um
is it bgm lagging there is no bgm
up fix wig
you you
witty little chicken you thought it was
so pretty
damn in your soul
oh
you guys not
ice something
um
hello
[Music]
oh that's not really a good thing
yeah I'm using a different mic
a really good one
nasal voice
um well
I don't know what to say about that
I just woke up so I still have a
oh frog in my throat I think
um
I'm a bit tired too
no
I
um
froggy Mama clap
uh froggy mama was very very
trying hard last night no last today
she right before the
stream started the 3D collab stream
right before
what the [\h__\h]
right before she she I noticed something
was stuck in my throat like 20 30
minutes before the stream it was really
really really really
strongly stuck in my throat
I just couldn't get it out like normally
all the previous days whenever I coughed
I easily got
something out
but this time you know
this time it didn't come out
and the whole time I was like
and the other myth girls they were like
do this try that do this I'm almost like
do a do a really low Grumble something
sound I'm like
well it didn't help
didn't hear it in the Stream yeah yeah I
mean I could still talk uh normally but
it didn't feel uh quite comfortable
um
it didn't fix itself unfortunately oh
well so I don't know yesterday we uh
um I wanted to get the girls to go to
them all you can eat
strawberry sweets
buffet with me but it was quite
difficult to find
um
a place that has enough for five people
like space for five people especially on
some short notes because oh Emma
mentioned it yeah a couple like two days
ago
when I was at Kelly's Place three days
ago maybe when it was a callous place I
was looking up some places and they all
said that they're full
thank you Alexander
also they were full and I was like okay
I'll check when I get home
and then I forgot about it one day yeah
but then I checked again eventually and
I checked for like because this is a
really popular thing
well
well perhaps uh
uh well whoa whoa wait wait wait wait
wait wait for it so ah what was I saying
oh yeah it's a really popular thing in
Japan like all you can eat buffets in
hotels and so on fancy hotels
and they always have like some kind of
campaign going on where it's themed
after
something like strawberries is very
popular and then they'll make everything
about strawberries but also sometimes
they have some other stuff depending on
the season yeah but right now everything
is uh strawberries
um
they always have something going on this
was one of the things you know back in
the day that I went to with Marine
zenplay
yeah
um that's that's right
and then thank God I found a place that
still had space for five people
uh and I reserved it it was kind of
pricey but you know it was the only one
that seemed available except if you want
to go to sweets what was it called
sweets Paradise
but it was close with spirit
something like that there's like a cheap
one that I've been to many times myself
too
um
on my own or my friends back in the day
yeah sweets Paradise yeah yeah yeah yeah
that one is like the cheap one where you
don't need a reservation either you just
go there and then you okay oh did you
hear from Ahmed yeah I think it was
around 80 because it was
9600 yen
per person
uh for the buffet and the one drink but
but it was not only sweets though
uh
yeah yeah
it is better but it was an extremely
fancy place too and the food was really
good and they had like French dining and
sweets Buffet so
uh I don't know how French that really
was but
um
yeah per person I know
I think back in the day I wouldn't I
wouldn't be able to afford that
yeah but hey if we were celebrating more
or less
forget level French well I'm not sure
there was a cheese corner with lots of
cheese I didn't enter the cheese Corner
though maybe there were baguettes in the
cheese corner to eat the cheese with the
baguette I'm not sure but then you know
there was other stuff like there were
some really good uh beef stew uh that
had a nice
uh wine Aroma to it because red wine
and there was some nice chicken uh
stuff and what else oh they had um I
wouldn't say this is French at all but
one one of my favorite foods normal
Foods there was some noodles with salmon
[Music]
creamy noodles with creamy salmon yum
yum yum that's one of the few times
where I like eating fish
little salmon bits in the sauce right
the white cream sauce or something like
that um
Alfredo I guess something like that what
do you think of the crab ah did she tell
you
yeah I know everybody was uh taking some
crap because there was a lot of crab on
the buffet too
I'll hook you up in a moment
I'm tired
uh but yeah there was a lot of crap but
yeah I didn't want to but everybody was
eating crab and it looked so fancy they
were cutting through everything and
cracking open the crab
uh uh so I got curious and I don't know
if Emma told you that part
but she was breaking it open and then
one time she kind of like went breaking
it open she slipped
and the like or like it it broke open
really
like an explosion
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah she flung some
pieces over to my side because I was
sitting across from her
and I was I was like oh well no problem
it almost landed in my pumpkin soup
that's pumpkin soup was really good I
almost landed in my pumpkin soup but
anyway I I thought you know it's just a
tiny Pizza I put it on my plate just to
put it somewhere I wasn't planning on
eating it but then I considered it a
little bit I was like
um
I wonder
so I gave it a try eventually and I
think this is not the first time I gave
crab a try though
I think I may have tried a tiny bit
before
and the tiny tiny tiny bit was okay
because it was so tiny we were we were
maybe experiencing the durian situation
again where it's okay when it's so tiny
because you can barely taste anything
when it's so tiny
oh thank you thank you thank you
uh and then she Emma was like do you
want to have some more taste some more
I'm like um I guess
who goes
and I tried a little bit bigger piece
but it wasn't I wouldn't say it was
disgusting
but I did not really like it
and Emma said it would taste really
really good with like butter and I'm
like oh well yeah I can imagine maybe
butter garlic but a garlic would make
this a lot better no there was no sauce
it was just like like that
but with butter garlic I can imagine in
a little bit more just like that it gave
me too much like
fishy Vibes but not the good fishy the
normal fishy that I like more like uh I
don't know
I'm kind of fishy vibe that I don't like
garlic butter crab pretty common you
guys yeah that's something I could maybe
get talked into because butter garlic
yummy yum yum
are you guys still trying to give
memberships to a specific person
[Music]
I mean now
remember she poo
okay
[Music]
dining good
um
yeah
so I got uh some some Savory food first
I got some potato Grotto so the chicken
stuff and a little bit of the beef stew
and a little bit of the noodles or the
salmon and a little bit of like carrot
salad I love carrot salad
I think that's
very much all I got for the saber stuff
but it's really only filled out one
plate so only a little bit from
everything in case I didn't like it
and then I was like I can't hold back
anymore I need to sweet stuff because
of presentation like they had two
different chocolate fountains big
chocolate fountains one was normal
chocolate and one was like pink
so it was I think I'm pretty sure it was
like strawberry chocolate
strawberry
was pretty pretty uh pastel color it's a
pretty bright
um
yeah you can dip stuff in there but then
that's for me the chocolate fountain
it's cool it looks nice but uh I feel
like all the other desserts were nicer
they had uh all kinds of I actually took
photos and videos let me show you
just the photos are fine probably
let me send them to janma
I have not checked for Reflections so I
gotta do that real quick
for this microphone
bam it picks up a lot of sound but what
do you think guys do you like it more
than my normal one
I mainly at like uh have this right now
because I asked the girls yesterday on
the table I asked Ama uh sounds pretty
good
that's pretty good
um
well volume a bit low still okay okay
raise it a little bit
I don't think it's as equalized as I
normally have it
uh what was I saying
I always always lose my friend a thought
trainer fun
there's a person talking into it thank
you
wanna hear compared to the Austrian
that's the one I've been using the past
weeks days I brought it uh to Japan
the microphone but I'm I've been using
um
the like a go XLR and the cable from
them but so
you know it was bothering me too that
that noise that high-pitched noise was
bothering me too I was trying to uh like
kill it by lowering the high frequencies
like completely almost to zero
um all of the high frequencies and I
think in my ears it did a relatively
good job it was not completely gone but
I don't know what it was auxiliary
interference maybe I don't know anything
about this kind of stuff but I asked
them like what do you think it is
because I think I had this already in
Austria recently but I'm also having it
here and I don't know what it is
um
can't catch any immediate difference for
real it should be a big difference
huh
interference but I don't know why I
would have it in both places too
difficult two completely different
environments
it's not like that is like default with
the show sm7b but we were discussing it
a little bit and the other girls jumped
into the discussion and then gouda
offered uh me to try out her microphone
um
uh
uh so I'm testing it out right now and
if you guys like it I can buy it but
um
that's good this mic doesn't have this
issue because the other mic got picked
up more as you turn the game up yeah
yeah yeah
goodbye
for some reason my uh wake up alarm was
at 1101 one minute after 11
.
and I told Google to just uh oh yeah
before she goes out to do her thing
um drop it off
okay
and she it's really not a fault like she
was so close to my alarm I didn't tell
her when I was waking up but I guess she
you know I don't know
and then she Rings my bell at 11AM and I
was in a deep slumber
I'm like
who who is who Could That Be I'm like a
zombie I'm like really I don't know
where I am who I am in that moment and
I'm like [\h__\h] uh doorbell ringing what
do I do I'm naked I'm literally naked in
my bed
okay so I I felt so out of it that I
didn't think I could put on clothes
properly in time without putting pants
on my head or a shirt on my buttocks
so I was like
I guess I'll wrap my my whole blanket
around myself
in the hopes that it I mean I
I'm thinking it uh could be uh Post
delivery mail delivery because I'm still
waiting on something that I think got
lost
I forgot my
I forgot my um
my coat in Indonesia I can tell you did
I
and then I had the hotel send it
to me they were really nice and reacted
quickly and I said oh no problem we're
sending it to you
uh but I brought two coats uh to Japan
this time so no worries of course
um I have I have another one but I
wanted that code back but anyway that's
been like
how long has it been since I left one
and a half weeks
I think so
wait how long has it been
it's Sunday now
maybe it's been a wait did I come back
last Monday
it feels like two weeks I'm not sure
anymore
oh no it's been two weeks yeah I came
back before in the week on my showcase
yeah and nothing has come so I guess it
may have gotten lost and I'm like
until
annoyed I don't know I don't want to be
I don't want to follow up on that [\h__\h]
it's annoying I don't know
and it was a quote that I at least in
Austria I haven't been really using it
recently I've been using a little bit
more
just because I wanted to learn a
different coat that doesn't stand out so
much
I I don't think it would take that long
but this was my last hope I thought they
did now it was arriving so I was like I
have to get up even if I'm naked I have
to get up so wrap the blanket around me
as I opened the door uh really confused
and there stands
she gives me the microphone she's like
sorry just it's just me
here's the microphone
okay thank you
I did not know what time it was in that
moment either I thought I still had time
to sleep but then I checked my phone I'm
like oh it's 11.
oh and then a few seconds later my alarm
pops off
oh
well thank you
we're gonna test this microphone out and
why am I so tired wake up
wake up Chihuahua
[Music]
um
also what the hell
when I went to my PC
an open Discord
you know what DM
well you know what DM greeted me which
DM greeted me
okay I'll read you the text so you can
guess who sent this
hey cutie wink Emoji they say the early
bird catches the worm but girl you can
show up anytime and still get a bite
I've been thinking about you all owl day
long
who is this
nope not you know a lot of people saying
Ollie that is indeed something I I would
probably normally get from Ollie
I saw one right answer in the chat
it's pomu
I'm so confused probably what
you're good
she'd be flirting with me out of nowhere
[Music]
checks out
horrendous
responder I did
I didn't float back though I said
what a DM to wake up to beautiful I'm
excited for you out for revealed foreign
[Music]
you crazies
gulp
um
oh yeah I turned on subscriber mode
um because I see everybody else is doing
it everybody else is doing it for weeks
months now and I always kind of like
resistance resisted because I thought
well I don't want to force people to
subscribe to chat
especially for collabs I feel like
people would get mad at me
but even for collapse people are doing
it so
I guess why not make use of this
function and maybe maybe some people who
were on the edge of subscribing but
weren't sure about it maybe it will give
them the push that they need
it's already super short it's just five
minutes people can't just subscribe and
then unsubscribe I guess
yeah
um
well
[Music]
it's kind of the expected Trend right
now
I don't mind the Bots
I don't really mind the boss they don't
even show up that often
you're still trying with the memberships
uh is Taco not even here
I missed the part but you know who I
also miss who has disappeared even after
such a long time of
being here takuma got it
yo
so if it stops now then I will know
you were you guys were really just
sending it for daku mode
yeah
what was I saying
was I just about to say
oh yeah oh the baby
kanoshi
um
no the baby the dead baby
who's been around for such a long time
[Music]
and it's been a long time since I last
saw a baby
um where's my baby my dead baby
[Music]
a bit sad
oh yeah let me check the photos
this score did a good thing
finally pictures are uh
you know shown as like a gallery
right when you send several ones
[Music]
this looks fine
oh this
this looks fine too yeah yeah
do I see my reflection in the chocolate
fountain no
do I see my reflection here no no
no no no okay
this one is good
this one
oh yummy
yummy yummy yummy yum yum
looks fine too
[Music]
on this one
so many strawberry knees let's go
strawberries everywhere
Anna was eating some macarons and she
was like this is so good and her and
Google
we're saying that it tastes like some
cereal
that I've never heard of ever before
no idea what they were talking about
all the photos seem okay to me
tricks uh-huh did she tell him she told
you about that too didn't she ha
but I just thought it tastes like a
really good strawberry macaron
um
eight Wawa thank you
except for kids it's for kids
she tells a lot of stuff today
there you go so this was like one look
uh
let me put it here
overall look as you see there's like
fountains and at the fountain station
around it where like waffles and some
other stuff
um also there were some Japanese style
sweets like uh
mochi
strawberry Mochi and stuff
a few a few uh
but it's a really fancy hotel
um it was so big it's so nice
too bad we didn't just stay in the rooms
horses were definitely Japanese what do
you mean these are not what do you mean
portions you can decidle your portion
portion
you're the one who decides how big they
should be
so that was that and now we'll take a
closer look
so for example we have we have
strawberry diet coku and oh I can't read
the one on the right side that's also
something Japanese foreign
[Music]
should be like something with strawberry
no no
um
[Music]
you see my credit card information in
the fountain
don't look
looks good yes uh here's strawberry what
goody or something
yeah so and then here's some strawberry
cakes over there and then on the very
back
there's some more
some more strawberry stuff
the tart at the top there I think that
was a a lemon heart mini mini lemon tart
with strawberry on top so good I love
lemon stuff
um
I don't even have a credit card
I only have a debit card
that's impossible
um
some more strawberry stuff although that
there's one thing I was surprised that
was even there there was one thing that
was not strawberry you see those little
cakes
in the I guess I guess there's two the
left side that looks like a moonburn
style thingy
but the other thing the other thing
looks like uh I tried that one
because it looked a little bit to me
like a creme brulee cake or something
like that but no it wasn't
a more strawberry Stuff strawberry with
some cream
cheese I think it was
and oh this was also an ice cream
station so if you wanted some ice cream
you could get it here so there were also
I guess some stuff like sprinkles and
cornflakes and so on to top your ice
cream with and on the very left uh
corner you see there's like just pure
strawberries too
and I got a lot of those too because I
just wanted strawberries
just strawberries
I don't know
so one more
one more
um
okay which one
ah this one okay
one more time here are the macarons and
on the left side to it those look so
good those are chocolates in perfect
strawberry form and on the right side we
have strawberry
and on the left side very left side
there's like
um
how do you call it
in in in German we say confection I
guess
it's kind of like chocolates on the left
side not quite but a little chocolate
tea cakes yeah confectionery cakes
thingies
um
I tried one of those
um oh that's that ah the top one that
might be the one that
um I kept on saying that's the best one
she had one uh thing as whole buffet
that she kept on bringing back and she
was like you guys gotta try this one
this is the best one this is the best
one and it was just like a little tiny
roll
um of a soft
soft cake sponge rolled up
with some
you know
strawberry cream inside top of a little
strawberry
but she was so into that one she kept on
selling it to me
I tried it and yeah it was good I
wouldn't say it was the best thing no
but I didn't want to disappoint her
so I said yeah it's really
it's really good yeah cute I'm glad she
enjoyed it too she ate a lot of stuff
I'm glad she ate a lot of stuff
um
this was my plate
uh my my sweets plate some some of the
things I got
oh some strawberry shortcake you know
some of them no the one thing under the
strawberry shortcake at the top
that there was supposed to be a
strawberry on top of that but it fell
off but it looks better when the
strawberries on it
um
no some of them are a little bit broken
because when you pick them up they kind
of Fall Apart
yeah that's my sweets plate and I I
think I got a second round with a little
bit more
of sweets but for Savory food I didn't
take a picture of the Savory food
oh wait this was one more
this is one of the things I got
yummy this is just strawberry custard
pudding and then get that
strawberry roll cake
no that's not the one that I'm liked
it's another one strawberry shortcake
yummy and Ah that's the strawberry lemon
tart I really like that one
yeah yeah
what she saw the show
yummy
looks good right so that was the main
reason why I wanted to go there yeah bgm
right now is like on vacation
[Music]
so if you ever come to Japan
they have something like this going on
at all the nice hotels at all times so
you can make a reservation online you
don't even need to buy uh to pay
beforehand or to use a credit card for
reservation or so no oh no no
yeah I don't know even like 80 dollars
per person is definitely kind of crazy
but if you're feeling very hungry and
you're the type of person who eats a lot
then I think you will get your money's
worth but
if Emma said I didn't eat much then I
have to say though the others also I
think gouda maybe also it's about as
much as I did
um I think Cali ate a lot of crab
uh
I did say to everybody yeah yo we have
two hours
to get our money's worth so eat as much
as you can
I'm definitely
tried her best
as she said she ate the most and you and
good I didn't eat enough well yes
she also said good I didn't eat much
um
possibly I don't know like I when I used
to go to these things earlier back in
the day I think I ate way more than I
would nowadays
uh
I don't know she's a nervous either yeah
I think I also like have that a little
bit
um
and on some days I eat more than on
other days
it depends
um
wow was good good uh I was just happy
being there together and eating together
and that the others enjoyed it yeah we
had some chit chat about this and that
um
we talked about all kinds of things
together so that was good yeah
oh I don't like seafood with my boys
well
I don't know if I ever said that
does she have a voice recording to prove
that I said that oh
it do be true
yeah you know Cali we're also there
we're all right we're all of them I made
a reservation for five
what
um stretch huh
what was I saying
oh
oh yeah so after the Showcase
um
we didn't immediately go home uh like I
asked if I can record something small
for a YouTube short that I then uploaded
but when I did that uh the others like
you know originally they wouldn't have
asked but they got inspired and they
wanted to take some videos and photos
too so for like 20 minutes or so we were
doing that and then
um then we went to take off everything
uh one by one we changed out of the
stuff and then we uh talked to a staff
about something uh important and then
and then we were advised that the pizzas
have arrived
so in management not Yago I know Kelly
said thanks Iago but this is on Ian
management
um they organized a [\h__\h]
to us for the staff and for us
how many so everybody
walked over to the pizzas and got like
some pieces but now here I have to say
I ate the most
because I ate a whopping
drum roll
two pieces while everybody else from the
girls only ate one piece and the tiny at
that they were cut into so many slices
so
redflex I know but
wow wow wow
but again
um I I would definitely say that I'm a
nervous eater too because like uh also
for my showcase for example they brought
um
[\h__\h] hell why are we dancing almost
for an hour again I said
have you noticed guys have you noticed
oh whatever let's just get it over with
let's get the tensions
I wanted to say yeah so at my showcase
you know they brought those um fried
chicken and karage and stuff and I ate
one a fried chicken oh no yeah one like
fried chicken leg thingy and
um
then that of course that was nothing not
enough to fill my belly but
I I don't know
it's not that I feel full in that moment
but I just don't feel like I want
to eat in that environment
yeah so I said I'm gonna eat this Bento
at home and I brought it home and then I
ate it at home
no so again with the pizza also
I guess normally maybe I would have
eaten more pizza slices
or in this case no but I have to say the
others only took one piece
but there were so many different
varieties
but those Japanese pizzas they're very
different from
hmm
[Music]
oh yeah no they actually you know it was
nice uh
so they said oh and then Gemma comes in
with
um
a special special box smaller looking
box and like a whole pizza box uh and
gives it to AME and this is for you
because they they were so considerate
you know
they remember they heard that when Emma
ate pizza in Japan before uh her stomach
was kind of messed up [\h__\h] up
so yeah she basically got a rice Pizza
it was like rice apparently with on top
of it was like typical Pizza stuff like
the Tomato stuff and the cheese I guess
stuff like that
um
she said it was okay
but at least she didn't have to eat the
pizzas
yeah yeah yeah she liked it I think
yeah but it's thoughtful right and I
don't think this is like information she
told them directly I think this is
information that came from her stream or
her Twitter or so so
see how considerate they are our
managers are so like thoughtful and and
they pay attention to you know
what's up and what we're doing
so I thought that was really sweet
um
stuff's on the clip watches
but I went up to the pizzas and I was
like because there were so many pizzas I
was I was thinking there must be at
least one pineapple pizza right because
pineapple pizza they have it in Japan I
think so I was like pineapple pineapple
pineapple pineapple pizza pineapple
pizza there was no pineapple pizza
what
[Music]
I heard the Japanese staff that already
were eating some pizza around the tables
uh were like kind of like chuckling I
noticed that I was looking for pineapple
and they were like ah ah wasn't there
something about like pineapple pizza
being very controversial
well well
[Music]
nothing controversial about pineapple
pizza
oh yeah oh yeah and then the en staff
apologized to me sorry takanashikiwawa
we didn't bring any pineapple pizza
they didn't have caught in tuna even
though
no pineapple no corn no tuna
none of that
sad
so sad
even though they loved uh corn on pizzas
oh oh it's nothing with corn oh well
yeah everybody was enjoying the pizzas
um and then I I brought my sock puppets
so
I brought over the sock puppets to the
staff and lined them up and told them
how to line them up and and told them
which puppets to be careful with because
two of them are kind of falling apart
um yeah and how to treat them and gave
it to them but I gave it to janma to
then give it to the staff in charge
whoever that is so I hope that will work
out well
um
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] that reminds me I was supposed
to
fill in a short
thingy can we do that really quick
because I'll [\h__\h] forget again
uh
please enter your talent names
enter title of work
um
hold on live English sock puppets
uh
a story behind the creation of work as
well as your photo should I write to
some Japanese because it's gonna be
mostly read by Japanese people
now I submitted already before but this
is like some extra submission to like
you know they're gonna put like a little
plate in front of it that explains who
made it what it is and so on
yeah all right in Japanese
100 to 250 characters maximum 350
characters
let me open up
character
count
online character count tool there we go
uh
[Music]
um
Thomas
[Music]
she
being none of that hi
hi
foreign
[Music]
um
uh
no no no no no no no no
um
[Music]
no
ending
story monster
[Music]
um
what else was there to say I said uh in
December I got sick and I was really
lonely so I made some sock puppets but
uh they are new so I've never worn them
before okay while I was creating them it
got it became more and more fun so I
made all of them
um
uh I also use them on stream so please
check out uh check it out on YouTube if
you want and I also
made the use them for a final finale
video uh
in for the Advent calendar that I Advent
calendar that I have organized in
December as well
is there anything else to say
they are new songs
good summary yeah
she mentioned that what I wasn't
hysterical
well
people were saying that I know I've I've
become crazy or so the voice is in my
hands
[Music]
no wait well it's more than me just
getting sick I think I want to add
something
foreign
okay and
[Music]
um
foreign
uh
quarter well
um
[Laughter]
okay I added I added to it in the middle
that during this time not only me but
also other Indian members were mostly
like taking a break or sick and nobody
was streaming so people were thinking
that I perhaps have gone absolutely
crazy and am seeing these as my new
friends so they were worried about me
but I am fine
hahaha
I am okay
nice
nice why couldn't you come out when I
was when I was
here when I was um
right before the 3D cool Upstream huh
okay let me add this there we go
this should be okay
okay
submit
I did it
done
okay maybe it's now time after an hour
to read some simple chats
this was warm up
foreign
this was warm up okay
warm up this
a little bit of super chats in my life a
little bit of reading and more life
nice warm-up yeah well I want to talk
about remind me to talk about uh
choreography learning process and also
the choreography uh you know things I
wanted to say about that next time I'm
looking for a tangent remind me of that
please
um yeah
that's important
I want to flex what parts were made by
me because I made I came up with a lot
of things for our songs
actually
um
so I'll talk about that another time
what was the number
uh 86 I remember Mist fist 86
okay
you know
[Music]
oh yeah that's why the thumbnail was so
up
there you go
alrighty
ah yeah I mean
some part of me does want to
try choreographing a whole song at some
point but
you know I always thought it wasn't very
realistic to for me to do a good job at
the choreo for like five people because
then you have to think about formation
and you're not only thinking up one
corner you're thinking of like five
people's choreo because they're not
always they're not they shouldn't always
dance the same thing because that will
be boring and that's a little bit too
high level for me to start off with so
unfortunately I didn't do it this time
but I did add a lot of things on my own
but in the future maybe in the future
okay so there's a bell thank you for the
pinky so happy that you your 3D showcase
is finally here you're one of the most
hard-working and creative people out
there you're one of the biggest
Inspirations and I'm so proud of you so
proud to call you my Cami Aussie can't
wait to see what you got
what I got congratulations what do you
mean what I got you mean like
but I have to author
well well well there's a bell
was it was it satisfying did it make you
proud
thank you for calling me okay I'm very
happy that you say that and you think of
me that way
God or she
I hope this will not change
I'm glad to be your OC
and I'll continue working hard thank you
deza thank you so much for watching
thank you for the recipe Chad kfb
assemble it wait I should probably turn
on BTM or have you guys turned on your
own bgm by now
maybe you know what I'll have you turn
on your own bgm how about that
how about today is
use your own bring your own bgm to work
day
bring your own bgm to work day
but don't get too distracted okay
if it's songs that have vocals you
usually get distracted by them
hmm
don't bring out the scream all
[Music]
ah
rip phone uses yeah
yeah sorry I know I'm not feeling bgm
right now
I mean I can turn some on if you really
want
if you really want
[Music]
death metal black belt
no it's fine but it's okay
it's fine dig into the voice right
sometimes it's good to have just nothing
else
I'm okay the bgm imagination okay
PGM of your private jet also known as
PS4
well you you're very positive
person aren't you
you must be a glass half full person
if you see your PS4 as a private chat
I mean it can probably take you on a
flight simulator
uh so yeah thank you Jackie Chan 3D
party time yeah yeah yeah thank you for
celebrating together and being there on
a very special occasion thank you for
the red super chat
[Music]
I appreciate it
and I will put in a fruit candy
thinking that I already talked so much
protort is not far away
[Music]
because it's loud as [\h__\h] oh that's why
does it make sounds like my airport
laptop
well it's been pretty quiet these days
all right
I have to use the background anyway
though because otherwise I feel bad
have we even gotten out of pre-chat no I
don't think so
it doesn't look like it
but I still think I got far because last
time I read other stream triple chats
too and I finished them
hi
hi [\h__\h] I can't yawn properly Brad thank
you Diego Vans thank you
Super Chat yeah your streams have always
been a wonderful Journey for us we're
grateful for every moment your hard work
talent and dedication is valued and I
want you to know that you're very
special to us keep shining bright and
bringing happiness to everyone around
you
[\h__\h] you
um
uh
I appreciate that thank you for
believing in me and supporting me for
such a long time thank you I hope you
enjoyed the Stream obliga
[Music]
hi Rohana thank you for the words of the
chat I'm sure this was a glorious super
special party kiwawa
I'm sure you were amazing why are you
talking in past tense
trying to repeat what I'm sure everyone
else has said maybe you could say some
say variations
of praising some chickens or just some
variants of your little [\h__\h] kisush
United
you don't want a kiss
oh because they're already like
anticipating that I will be obviously
reading it after the Showcase wow
that's some thinking
no kiss for you
um
variations of praising some chickens
you guys are so fluffy and cute every
time when I see like fan art uh of me
with chickens with employees it makes me
so happy because they look so cute like
sometimes they make me hug you and Fan
Art I love seeing that kind of stuff
it's so cute
um you know it makes me makes me you
know feel like a mommy or a very proud
boss you know you guys are so fluffy
and chunky and cute you know so adorable
more more what I want more of is Fan Art
of me with my cats and me with my
chickens
mama mama
just got here no medium look here it's
bring your own bgm to work day
yes
I can't [\h__\h] breathe I think today I
have a problem with breathing
definitely feels like I can't get a full
deep breath in
it's one of those days
let me try
I'm lacking um
I don't have an inhaler but
um the other day actually the last Japan
trip I don't know if I told you about
this but I was like doing a rehearsal
um and I saw Japanese members
like one Japanese member
had this
you know those air horn thingies that
look like spray cans
so she had something like that and I I
was like what is this and then she puts
it on her mouth
and uses it to inhale and it was it was
yeah like an oxygen bottle
does that count as an asthma inhaler
because she said that in Japan you can
get it without a prescription I was
thinking like oh damn that's good I wish
we had that in Austria
it's just oxygen
that's not an inhaler
type of fun in hell but not with asthma
medication oh
foreign
[Laughter]
nebulizer
Canada Placebo it's a placebo
sounds like an inhalers
to
canned air no chemicals good for
migraines
uh
[Music]
what's your brand function optimal well
she was saying you know it's for it's
for you know
yeah basically
she did say she has asthma and she uses
it for that
so
it's your net Souls
I should try it out
um
there's oxygen tanks all the time Sports
athletes in the hail using oxygen tanks
on them I should try one I'm I'm I'm
um I have some dancing coming up this
week
I should try to get one of those and
test it but
I know do they have those everywhere in
the world I wonder if you could get
those over the counter
in Austria too
because I don't think you can get asthma
inhalers like the typical ones over the
counter but if this would help and you
know I can get it anywhere then that
would be so cool
order from Amazon really
um
can you guys remind me on that rehearsal
day I have in the schedule
oh can you remind me like you wanna try
getting that oxygen bottle
that air horn
but try to not get a real airplane or
air horn and then stuck it to your mouth
and then let go
your mouth okay that will be a problem
you
you just air with increased
concentration of oxygen
I'm gonna try it out I've been wondering
about that since then
I do recommend getting an actual inhaler
to a point well that would need me to be
taken seriously by a [\h__\h] doctor for
once when I say that I have breathing
difficulties and that my tight chest is
up then my chest tightens up
then my chest tightens up sometimes
out of nowhere and sometimes when I am
doing something
huh
now
maybe that's the problem I said my tight
chest is up maybe that's why I didn't
understand
women had similar issues with her doctor
for real
like why why why why why why why why
don't even test me they don't even like
try to see it
I don't know ma'am
what else like I don't know
okay I think so far they've like been
trying to push it on the fact that
I have a bad poster
I don't know about that
hmm
chest x-ray no not I never had a chest
x-ray I know
I need to do like Raven tests yeah but
then I think back to my Lufthansa
um
health health check that I did which was
very intricate right I think I told you
before that they did test my breathing
there and the Doctor Who was doing that
with me was very confused because
I just was incapable of doing it
correctly
and we tried again and again
um but I just couldn't do it right
because I I really lacked the ability to
breathe properly
but she was just like I guess thinking I
was stupid or so and gave me the benefit
of the doubt and just said okay that's
fine
let's let's move on on to the next thing
but doesn't that tell you something
but but that was not you know that was
just for the Lufthansa thing
um
My Whole Health checkup
it's not like their problem that I have
asthma so
um
anyway I should be reading super chats
right
ah stop me from tensioning for God's
sake
um thank you I gave you a kiss anyway
but you got also tension so can you
really complain I don't think so Robin
Hood thank you for the rest of the chat
one hour left until the Showcase oh I
can't wait to see the result of all your
hard work tender I'm so practical in my
coming
[Music]
oh no thank you
thanks for waiting for me being excited
for me supporting me celebrating me
thank you soon
ah finally I could show it off all the
things I wanted to do for such a long
time yeah
thank you
please continue supporting me well Chuck
1001 thanks for the pinky get ready
chickens this will be perfect yeah yeah
I think it was pretty perfect yeah yeah
I agree
thank you thank you no song for spiders
soon
for the recipe Chan I'm so happy to
finally be here at your 3D showcase
stream kiwama it's been such an amazing
adventure from late 2020 to now and
watching you grow has brought so much
joy to my life yes I've seen you already
at fruit Fest and your third birthday
concert but this is special right I
would say so too
yeah first class was just one song and
then for the birthday concert was
different environment
so
this was finally you know full kiwawa
hour with high quality Freddy so
good stuff
thank you for watching and thank you for
supporting me dezavold I appreciate it
thank you so much lovely chicken
foreign
hello there this is a message from kfp
2023 2ksp 2020 oh
there's one thing I'm pretty sure kfb
keeps winning myth girls keep winning
today we have our 10 to 3D showcase and
next month we have fourth fest concert
what are you waiting for just join us
join kfb
thank you yeah it's an exciting time
uh four Fest is so soon
and yesterday you were able to hear a
little bit of a sneak peek from my uh
song with mumei my song cover with mummy
for the decor 27
concert thingy
a little little taste
oh [\h__\h] help can you breathe
[Music]
ghost rule yay goes really it's a really
cool song
um
are you guys
planning on
watching that one too
because I must warn you like
there's
um
not much koawa there
but if you have more than just one Oshi
which are performing at that concert
then I think it will be worth it if you
only have me then I don't know how
boyfriend it is
depends on how much you love me
you bought all the tickets thank you
I only have day one ticket that's fine
too there will be much kiwawa on day one
now we have to go that's not how I
manage you don't have to prove me
anything but I would be happy if you
guys at least watched day one because
there's much Wawa
on day one
no I wasn't trying to pressure you
um
[Music]
man they won yeah they won
of course they won I've told you day one
day one
oh
day two foreign
I wanna see
the one day one
she's the only day two bird
[Music]
I'm really curious to see everybody's
reactions
so
thank you thank you hakutsu for talking
to past kfp I hope maybe past kfb will
come back to us some of them
thank you black rich and donation for
the recipe for my beloved ocean it's
been long overdue but we're finally here
you're gonna sweep us of our feet like
you always do you're simply amazing and
I can't stress that enough a cute dog
with Incredible Talent dedication and
ambition you wonderful kind stop
stop
stop oh thank you good night
stop black freak John
no you can't be so nice to me
you're so sweet
you can't say all those nice things
I'm gonna get cocky
thank you
so sweet
thank you shrimp like fridge
laughs
we could do um instead of kisses we
could do blow noses
no I will not get anything on you
feathers don't worry
no
[Music]
I'll get a nosebleed no honestly
how much I was
as much as I was blowing my nose in the
first like
couple days
it's probably as much as I would
need to if I wanted to blow my nose for
every red Super Chat
it was really not never ending
um
you were so goddamn cute in the 40
showcase like man
I do feel like
I still can't quite get out of my shell
like I see someone like Cali for example
yesterday going crazy all the time
moving her body like she
like I feel like normally she only goes
that crazy when she's in 3D
um
when I'm with her under normal
but in a normal situation
she doesn't like
how to say move her hips in a circle
movement constantly and and swing her
arms like an octopus constantly
she doesn't grind on the side even no no
yeah she like yeah gets totally unhinged
and pretty
absolutely
hmm
I
guess I am bravocom
maybe even
um calmer than I am in real life
um I don't know
I I wanna
um
become more unhinged but especially in
that group situation I would feel
awkward about it
hmm
uh very dignified and pretty I think
it's all the cameras that and also the
people around
if I was completely alone in that room
maybe I would be doing more
[Music]
um
but yeah
you had to be the responsible MC
I guess so
you wear pretty unhinged on a New Year's
special oh that was really hyped there
too yeah well that was because I was
really excited being with Japanese
members there and like having one of my
deaf first opportunity to be on a
program like that on such a special day
um
I think that played into it and was just
so hyped
as long as you talk of your arms I'm
happy hmm
thank you
on top of that where you were still sick
no yeah for the showcase for my for my
well for my solo 3D showcase I guess I
was sick but not in a way that I would
say it really had a big impact on my
on my body movement
only really on my throat
hmm
the New Year's one
um
[Music]
I was like pretty much recovered right
it was pretty okay during that time
I think
wow wow wow
thank you Blackberry Channel
thank you
also thank you for the recipe
I'm so proud of you I can't see it I
can't wait to see the show thank you
well you were so close to it you were
half an hour away I hope you were able
to wait
because there was no other choice than
Gotta Wait for great things like that
thank you so much
I know you've been looking forward to
this for so long and all of your hard
work is about to pay off so proud of you
boss you're going to absolutely rock
this
I appreciate it Jim Tracy cutie
thank you for being here again always
did I rock it I tried
I tried very hard to make it into an
interesting
perfect beautiful showcase
thank you for being there Jim Tracy
I hope you will continue supporting me
[Music]
I did I sure did thank you thank you
thank you
Luna shine Crow dancing sir 956
greenwilder thank
howdy hot wings what a wonderful day it
is to finally see you get the free debut
that is long overdue
and how for two we choose that I can
actually say it live I haven't seen
anything live in a while oh you're going
to be an amazing I could couldn't be
more excited for Moshi thank you I'm
glad you were able to make it live thank
you soon so happy even if you can't
watch me live much recently I hope
you're able to catch the vods though
[Music]
thank you thank you
thank you Alistair Kane thank you for
two weeks till forward two weeks
fortuitous
is that right
there you go
that's that's about as close As It Gets
thank you greenwilder or Wilder I always
forget
I'm never sure
I'm sorry I hope I'm not insulting you
with the pronunciation of your name
thank you so much for your support
[Music]
rad thanks for the pinky release
unlimited viewers unleash those hot
wings and reawaken in a way that only a
phoenix could I know you've been holding
back for so long and now it's time to
see the world Ablaze like no other
campaign
[Music]
um
you guys almost sound more motivated
than me
if those phrases you come up with
thank you so much
we love you afterwards
[Music]
estamos motivados
thank you you just read
and when you say sounds so cool
but I would feel bad to set the whole
world Ablaze
let's let's hold back a little bit
it's only set
the stage Ablaze okay
let's contain it a little bit
hmm
it makes sense that Cali
the Kelly showcase was after me because
you know her stage was on fire turns out
that is just the aftermath of me
performing Sparks on that mattering
stage
so Cali basically reused that but it was
well it looked completely different
because that's what
it looked like after I was done with it
I accept this lore
I had to set the stage yeah yeah yeah
yeah
oh man no no that wasn't the underworld
you may have thought so but turns out
it's just not to this stage set on fire
hmm
let's go down the world don't worry
about it
hmm
uh
for the pinky 3 40 AM wrapped in my
kiwawa blanket can't wait for the
Showcase extremely happy that the Third
Article of the rhinocch's golden
gazettes came true Emma
um
Italian
[Music]
it makes no sense what does that mean
probably
this is barely sounds like German
is you waking up
you're waking up is that what you mean
also who is that in your profile picture
I've been wondering
what anime character is that
are you here
ah me being sick oh yeah
that was such a close call
Carl I was crying out of panic before
the day
yeah
and I was still not sure if it would
work out
um
man
I was really scared I didn't want to
move it
it worked out but not really
I wasn't healthy but
you know
it was about you being sick
wow wow wow the backup option was moving
it but I had to give them early enough
notice where I was still like seeing
improvements after every night but I
wasn't sure how well I would do after
the coming night but the other options
for days they gave me were weekdays
and
wow
I didn't want to do it on a weekday
um
especially not only because people can't
watch on a weekday but also because
it was announced with this date so
you know
I think like a lot of people would miss
it completely
if the date was changed
[Music]
well we all know Chihuahua
never gives up kiwawa
comes back even when things are looking
very dire
so that's what I did I guess I willed my
health into existence
very stubborn yes
Never Surrender
[Music]
little baby
oh Five Guys yeah
good song
hmm
oh my God you know Foo Fighters well I
know that song you should always know
that song there's certain songs that you
just have to know
yeah the Lord of the Rings watch Vlog it
was nice indeed
[Music]
sorry I'm very dramatic today when I
stretch
foreign
I can hardly believe that we're now able
to watch your 3DW kiwawa but now that we
are here it honestly feels like an
eternity waiting during those last
moments I'm extremely happy to watch
this live and I'll be looking forward to
all the good days ahead of us
it felt like an eternity for me for you
it felt like so short to me like those
hours before the Showcase
I was so scared
I was screaming before it happened
screaming
staff we're like it's okay it's okay
calm down
it's just the pressure in general would
have already been a lot
but the pressure when being sick
uh was even better
um
I was scared my voice would give out or
that I would have to run to the toilet
in between
uh imagine that would be the first
Freddy showcase where the showcased
person
goes to an idol meeting in the middle of
it
crazy
way like for real though
it's not that easy you have to take all
of the finger trackers off
unless you want to be disgusting
um and then you have to put them back on
and it takes quite a while
putting those finger trackers on takes
like
I mean they're pretty faceted because
they're good and they're used to it and
they do it with like two people
so it takes like maybe
five
five six minutes
to take them to put them on
but it's kind of like they're using some
kind of tape so taking them off also
takes like two minutes
I think it was memeing
so
that's like eight minutes or so just to
take them off and on
yeah and then you have to check the
calibration
it adds at least another minute if all
goes well
how many sense to annoying she's just
held in all day yeah yeah yeah she did
and then well the act of going to the
idle meeting depends how long that takes
but so it's not really something you
would uh do on stream
you would want to hold that back at all
cost
s
we're diapers ill
he's known for it so who knows where
there's
uh will after all
uh really
I have to look that up
and see how much time that took so
one second ah thank you so much
[Music]
yes well at this point you were looking
forward to the pretty uh showcase collab
as well but now there's still things to
look forward to next is the four Fest so
oh it's never ending we're riding this
big wave right now let's enjoy it padaya
um
production for the pinky it's so hard to
believe it's finally happy but here it
is you've made a Chihuahua your
performance is both in 2D and 3D always
have so much power it'll be incredible
to see you with Limitless off-rooting
for you boss enjoy that Limelight
what about lemon light
well
I know I know I know I was hyping it you
know to be like oh oh
finally high quality limiters off but
you know I still felt a little bit
limited but you know
it was as good as it gets as we've
talked about before so
yeah it was pretty decent but yesterday
I watched my choreographer Kiana putting
out a video a dance video of Sparks and
ah yeah that's how it's supposed to look
I mean even in reality I can't dance
that well
as she does
[Music]
but I would say I do dance it
a little bit better than it looked like
but also some of the moves she does man
are really difficult
so
it kind of changed them up a little bit
I guess she killed it she absolutely did
I'm glad she brought uh Sparks to New
York that's New York right the backdrop
was New York
look there's some famous square that
people take Kpop videos at there pick
K-pop dance videos
she does that too
Times Square nobody gives a [\h__\h]
some tourists maybe watch sometimes but
nobody gives a [\h__\h] that's just New York
I've heard
New York
[Music]
Spider-Man's gonna go after her
the man
[Music]
yo I should sing that in karaoke
sometimes
remind me
I have to learn it though
[Music]
oh there's a Jay-Z part oh
can you do it the wrap up I don't know
how it goes
I remember that at all
lights will inspire you
thank you there's a version without him
too
oh it's called Empire State of Mind
where's that part
in New York
Concrete Jungle where dreams are made of
there's nothing you can't do
it
now you're New York
the streets will make you feel brand new
Big Lots will inspire you hear it for
New York New York New York
hahaha
what those lines there's so many words
in that line what the hell
okay kiwawa okay chill I will do that
now take a chicken thank you for the red
super chat you've been a busy bird
lately hopping from country to Country
and meeting so many people yes there may
not have been many streams but it's been
fun just hearing all those Hollow mems
and some nun holes talk about and praise
you and now you're free to showcased
let's go yeah it has been a lot of fun
and it's nice to hear
um others other other members or
non-members
talk about
that kind of stuff too hmm
it's nice making memories like that
but I am so ready to go back
yeah I also mentioned yesterday to the
members that I'm like so homesick I
normally don't get homesick but damn
it's been over two months
and in between
in between I've been
home for like two weeks
but one month
away two weeks back one month away again
is just
I'm losing it I'm
I wanna go back to the usual Rhythm to
my usual environment to my kitty cuddles
it's been long way too long I want to go
back it's feeling so long it feels
longer than a month
and my mom watched my solo 4D showcase
as far as I know yeah yeah
I guess
um
yeah Kura told me she's also homesick
so
we we feeling it
we're feeling it
I locked arms again with good yeah
yesterday last night
you know before we
basically we went back to the heat and
house together
in a taxi and we got out and then we're
like
um you know I feel like I'm gonna get
hungry later should I should I maybe go
grab something I'm gonna also felt like
grabbing some stuff she might be more of
a sweet tooth than me I think
I catch her so often
buying like chocolate and stuff snacks
from
I'mma said that did she
snacks from the store
yeah way more than me I think she eats a
lot of sweets
[Music]
yeah I My Sweet Tooth kind of
disappeared a lot
um
between Cali and gouda I think uh
yo yo so we walked I mean I'm I locked
into her arm again we walked to the
market yeah got some yummy stuff
and then at the when I was cashing out
at a supermarket
that's when I
realized that when we walked back
we could have a door Showdown again so
at the cashier already I was thinking
about that and mentally preparing so I
took my keys into my hand already at
that point
[Laughter]
yeah
oh but I made her buy ice cream because
we were at the ice cream cone and I'm
like do you like ice cream because like
oh they have some good ice cream here
that I really like
um especially Haagen-Dazs because we
don't have much Choice much variety of
Hagen-Dazs in Austria but they have so
much again that's here and I really
recommend you this one and this one and
this one and this one and she's like
thinking I've seen I see but she wasn't
gonna buy it and I was like but you
should try it you should try you have to
try she said she never tried Hagen-Dazs
before I think and I made her buy one
she got a coffee coffee flavored hug and
that's I'm excited to hear her thoughts
about it
is really good really good ice cream I
got myself a cookies and cream one but I
didn't eat it yet
hey
and she got another Pepsi and I told her
I hope it's okay that I told my viewers
that you're a Pepsi girl
she said yeah no problem my uh they know
they know
I was like I told her that for some
reason like she seems to me even if I
didn't know this she seems to be to me
more like a Pepsi girl than the
Coca-Cola girl something about her tells
me Pepsi
I like I like them both but I guess if I
think about it maybe Pepsi is better I I
could agree with that
I could agree with that yeah
Ben and Jerry's uh I think they do yeah
yeah I think that's happened in Jerry's
in Austria before
Mountain Dew I haven't really tried that
before maybe once in my life
um
go ahead and we walk back we walk we
walk and the whole time I'm thinking
I am mentally prepared for what's about
to happen but let's not make her notice
okay I even notice I even opened like
uh the door
um at the you know at the ground floor
so she already saw me with the keys
there
but she didn't realize what was going
down
so then we go up
elevator
we get out of the elevator
and I take
the thing is like her uh apartment is
like hers is like closer I have to walk
further than she has but I didn't want
her because she would be closer if she
saw me running already she would
immediately like you know understand
what's going on so I took some normal
steps
like two normal steps out of the
elevator and then I ran and then I
dropped all my stuff on the floor and
then I immediately opened the door
it was like so confused I caught her so
off guard she was like no
[Laughter]
I was in before she even like
put in the key in the key lock
I was already in my room
[Laughter]
it's free versus one now hey
but she was already standing at the door
and her door she was just very slow
very slow
[Music]
yeah she had no idea what was coming
anyway okay where was I ah
ah thank you naked chicken
noise
I'm so happy for you you've worked so
very hard for this moment I want to give
this prior to the Showcase but because I
will be sobbing tears oh happiness won't
be able to type during the show can't
wait to see your wings when you fly no
[Music]
really cry
yeah if I sang like an emotional song or
so maybe that would have you know made
me squeeze your tear buds
but I think it was more like a exciting
thing overall
um
[Music]
sorry I knocked myself out
yeah
I stretched into the void
no no no Country Roads no thank you
Over My Dead Body
roads anyway thank you Studio rap for
the sweet words
thank you so much
I hope you didn't cry too hard
you can use my leftover tissues that I
didn't use only the ones I didn't use
it for the rainbow
let's go pretty party time
[Music]
it's a hello project sub unit song
life kiss delivery
you can have it fresh
and warm and toasty
thank you Ricky
beautiful rainbow
Over the Rainbow
there is
[Music]
supporting me like a good chicken that I
know you are
laughs
I still feel a little bit stuffed here
and there well
thank you
the kisses hit different now do they why
really
what's that Genie does a bag
you did like a bam
you guys like talk about this
after Fafa has read fafa's rainbow GT
did a backwards rainbow
[Music]
to follow it up immediately
did you plan that
sick
it's a rainbow Fusion between two
different chickens teamwork
impressive congratulations
thank you
road yeah
maybe this is the new Rainbow Road for
the next Mario Kart nine next one would
be nine right
most recent one is 8dx or is it
this will be the new Rainbow Road
I hope I don't fall off this one
wait double
oh no no
Oh you mean double with father but you
did send another ah a pink a pinky that
you left out
why did the pinky come after the red one
interesting
it's been a long time coming I'm very
happy for you that you get to finally do
this showcase light up the stage my Oshi
very proud of you thank you
I wish something like this could be done
more regularly but I guess then
I guess then it would be so special
I hope they let us do more
often at least for birthdays and
anniversaries would be nice but you know
we had so much fun yesterday with that
one hour thing
that afterwards I was like I'm so sad
this is already over this was so fast I
wish we could do more
and everybody seemed very motivated to
do more like this together
and I brought up like you know I was
originally hoping to maybe
get a 3D stream for my third anniversary
um but I I told the staff
that I for the sake of having a
like any 3D stream at all in the first
place but also to do something together
again
I would like sacrifice the chance for a
solo
anniversary
anniversary if we can do one together
better than nothing though
that's that's my point like if if uh
they turned down me having a solo one
then I'm thinking well
don't turn it down one so five of us
right
but
I've never done a 3D anniversary stream
before so
yeah it's just the chances are not
looking good
um it's not really
realistic looking
of doing a solo one at least so I'm
hoping for um being able to take
one together
well six months of prep it would be
enough it would be enough it should be
enough
and yeah please at least for the five of
us together we want to do more together
we want to do more together please
yeah I'm gonna mold too
so true
together
please please
please
thank you Genie again Elvis
thank you for the recipe chat
Elvis obligada thank you for coming to
the special occasion it has been years
of waiting for this moment I'm very
happy for you kiwawa
thank you I'm happy too we're happy you
are happy I am happy thank you soon what
a happy day oh happy day oh happy day
when Jesus was kiwawa oh happy day oh
happy day
we were enlightened Oh Happy Day
Oh Happy Day what
I was Jesus
Christ kiwawa okay I shouldn't make any
claims like this
always has been
makes sense Jesus did it rise again
Jesus is a phoenix
um
reminds me uh I've watched
oh my God
um sometimes I watch some channel that
does
um some kind of speed dating uh videos
sometimes but also other videos like uh
like where people have to guess in a
group of other people
which ones are what whatever with the
button yeah the button one and the other
day they released a new video
I kind of want to show it to you guys
because it's so ridiculous
uh I released a new video we have one
guy was just so
oh
oh oh oh
[Music]
that's my stream let me
let me show you
is it which one is it is it this one
this is two days ago
no it's this one
oh yeah it's this one
oh my God
as soon as the girl said she didn't
believe in God he was like dubbing her
but then it got man he put so much value
and pressure on it it's like asking
things about I know the Bible and do you
believe in the fact that Jesus came back
and so on
oh
please watch it
that was so cringe
that's so cringy
it was just too much like there's
there's like decent people who are
religious but but this guy oh my God my
God
little did she know the Chihuahua was
Jesus the whole time
I am Jesus
um
have you seen the rehearsal what
what there's rehearsals for this
I hate these
um
most of the time these videos are very
painful to watch because
they walk in sit down
and you know you can only press the
button when it's red and like even when
the person barely said anything
they immediately push the button
they don't even give them a chance and
then people keep on requesting that they
do it blindfolded or that they do it so
that if you push the button you yourself
have to leave not the other one
um
my God way more worse than this
yeah
it's called speed dating sure but
they don't even give them a single
chance to like introduce themselves it's
so rude it's so stupid
so this again is just one of those
things you watch even though it's
painful just because it's like watching
a car crash you can't look away
you cannot look away
I like uh
some of their uh
some of their like lineup videos more
yeah
more interesting
laughs
they have a lot of weird videos
women rank other women's attractiveness
those are really Tater though maybe that
sounds [\h__\h] to you at first but those
always end up so titty they like
appreciate each other so much
so sweet guess my credit score
oh yeah guessing videos lineup and
guessing videos
also like sometimes they do these videos
where uh two people sit next like across
from each other and then uh they drink
every time they don't want to answer a
question but uh one time it was like
boss with employee
oh oh oh that was one aphis and
Christians play true for drink that one
was interest too interesting too
basically it was always an aphis sitting
across a Christian but they they had
good conversations like you know
wasn't so bad
yeah it's not like they were like no
[\h__\h] you you believe suck blah blah blah
no no no they were like respectful and
all that so all good
ah pregnant woman play Truth or drink
that one was also good
I think
you say aphids in a cute way hmm
why in German you say artist
so I thought in English you would say a
fist or so atheist
oh wait no they don't actually drink
though it says in exclamation marks
drink uh exclamation marks it was a
thing is they're not actually
it's not real alcohol I think
I know I just realized that that's that
sounded uh wrong you didn't have the
whole context
okay I got it now okay back to Super
chats
[Music]
oh
blue that looks
amazing
[Music]
wow
yeah so I asked blue for last minute
um acid for
tomorrow's stream
and she's doing such a good time it
like it
cute okay
where are my super chats they're they're
there Alice thank you
thank you for the pinky it's been a long
time coming I'm very happy for you that
you get to finally oh wait I already
read this is
[Music]
perched out waiting for this moment for
so long I honestly thought the
excitement had passed and something like
this showcase wasn't going to be so
special but after listening in on inas I
felt it I felt that spark so I know I
know your showcase will be epic and that
it will make it the most flocking
incredible
thing you possibly can because despite
any setbacks and surf roads will
preserve very like always this will be
amazing because you are
[Music]
oh thank you [\h__\h]
it's been a while since I've heard so
many beautiful puns in a row thank you
did I say that correctly on on Twitter
was that you who got uh five of my
famous bottles thank you so much
[Music]
thank you
so oh I probably
I'm probably only getting one so if I
lose mine I know who to hit up if I need
another one because at that point it
will not be on sale anymore
I know who to get it from
thank you please keep one um very safe
just in case I need uh an extra one
okay you know thank you so much for the
support and the sweet words
[Music]
hope you enjoy those bottles yeah
I have one like just a sample but I'm
not I'm not allowed to keep it I'm
supposed to give it back and I wasn't
even allowed to use it I asked if I
could use it for the time being you know
when I was sick because a furnace would
have been really helpful and they said
no
um
I was told to get destroyed but if they
get destroyed anyway can I
couldn't I have used it why did they
even give it to you to look at it
yeah well I looked at it I've been
looking at it
so instead I bought a furnace cup which
I've really been enjoying
to use
um
Elvis sent an episode of chat a pinky
which is an addition to the other one
you sent I guess which says but I still
love janma well I love jenma too
I guess we'll have to share
but I don't really want to share
[Music]
JMT 80 20 split us 80. hey no way
you 20.
it's not fair She's Mine She's Mine
yesterday she was really not feeling
well
she got hit so hard from uh allergies
foreign
so I don't really know how it feels
but
um
she was swollen
no
she was swole
but she was not feeling well last year
are you okay or do you just not look
okay but you feel okay but she was
definitely not okay she said she was not
okay
she's doing really miserable I hope she
feels better today
um
apparently um
it's called Poland Poland are really bad
in this season in Japan and a lot of
Japanese people have uh pollen allergy
no it's very very common here way more
common apparently than for example
in Austria
spring is here almost yeah it's been
getting warmer for sure
Poland now I'm not talking about the
Polish people again
[Music]
you guys were saying that in the chat
weren't you
pretty aura
it's kind of hard to say
well I guess okay
thank you thank you love you too
thank you soon for watching I appreciate
it thank you so much Sean R sent a pinky
it's been a long time coming congrats
Daniel I'm at work but I'm secretly
wanting thank you appreciate it hope
that you could focus
on me this time I'm not gonna say focus
on the work no you had to focus on me
this was a special one
thank you
and if you couldn't focus and you had to
watch
again after it was over okay
thank you simply thank you for the rest
of the chat we are finally at the
beginning of the stream guys
uh the weight was long and agonizing but
it's finally over you've worked hard on
this and I'm elated to see you get your
due reward enjoy the Limelight you've
earned it yeah I mean
just simply by the sheer patients that
we have shown
in waiting for this
we definitely deserved
we we should have even gotten two hours
of showcase
oh
but you know
this might be even louder than normally
there's no different microphone
so sick no not really no no no no no
[Music]
thank you ziply oh it's not only us who
are patient but you guys as well thank
you so much
also you seem to be European gang thank
you for getting up at such a shitty time
for me thank you soon
I just know you'll do an amazing job
showing everything off I tried I tried
my best yo yo yo
I think I showed my assets off quite
well
thank you and I also got to show off
some fighting skill
that turn didn't look so bad did it huh
I think it looked pretty decent
I stayed up and said oh
hope you weren't too tired spin move was
sick right
we need quality one fan yeah I regret
not doing it as a as a YouTube short by
the way my God can you please remind me
I forgot doing the chicken dance
but I want to do the demon thing demon
Fang double demon Fang and I want to do
chicken chicken
um
there's still so many shorts I want to
take
I might get a chance at the rehearsal so
sure
note I'm also gonna write it to Jenna
cheeky cheeky Bang Bang YouTube short
and
bang if possible
okay
push
it should be remind you you know on the
rehearsal day maybe
um
I went to oxygen
try
oxygen thing from
and
Pharmacy
okay
yeah many reminders
[Music]
oh wait that wasn't even a double thank
you for the double red wow effo
therefore thank you
so generous I appreciate it thank you so
much
on the green screen okay okay green
screen
I'll try
uh the camera alone
Jimmy Sullivan thank you for the recipe
chat congratulations on 3D I have been
here since you wanna remember since day
one but this is my first Super Chat ever
thank you for being the best ocean a
chipkin could have what thank you
oh yeah this is definitely the first
Super Chat from you I haven't
seen one before from you
wow
for supporting me for such a long time
and not giving up on me
yo
it's hard for me to like look at old
stuff from me it's so cringe
hmm can't believe you are still here
then wow
you already finished chicken
congratulations
[Music]
thank you for supporting me out of all
the people you could support
no what a lurker you're such a lurker
you can come out of the lurking Shadows
a little bit more often if you want I
would not mind it at all
thank you
okay
dumpster fire dumb thank you for the
recipe chat it's finally time it's been
a long time coming
thank you yes it has been a long time
coming thank you so much for waiting
dumpster firedom
[Music]
that dumpster fire was also set by me
hope you're enjoying it
Alexander babsky thank you for the
recipe chat
can I sell your fruit pics
hmm
I'm gonna skip the rest of the sentence
but I'll read it after what comes after
uh
you're an inspiration for everyone in
your branch keep up the good work at
being a shining example thank you
um
why is the rest of the Super Chat so
nice
um uh thank you uh
I don't know what to say
you're confusing me
um
she doesn't know the meme even if it is
a meme I can't read this
just because it's a meme doesn't make it
okay okay it doesn't apply always
from a manga by junji Ito
wow
I will not read that nonetheless
thank you though
for teaching me enough of me my guess
yeah I will continue working hard Alex
thank you very much we please continue
supporting me
um
thank you soon for watching my super
special Freddy showcase mwah fried Squad
um
[Music]
foreign
because you can't send the super chat
but you're trying to tell me something
Ah that's probably for the best thank
you
about me not reading that
it's so good it's all good now that I
know it's a meme I at least am not
totally freaked out by you
if if it was not a meme then I would be
a bit freaked out
okay we're good we're good
all is good
uh
yay more memberships yay
sometimes better to not know in this
case it was good to know
thank you
um
[Music]
day one is
thank you for the red super chat I'm so
happy to see all uh your fun events and
achievements thanks for being the best
Oshi I could ask for much love from a
fan from the beginning of Ian oh wow
yeah this if you were watching from the
beginning
man you guys are real patient and this
must be finally such a nice conclusion
right really necessary
thank you for being there and not
leaving before this could happen but
hopefully he will continue staying
anyway yeah would be nice to have you
around Nico thank you so much
[Music]
kfb for life thank you soon
been watching mips and debut thank you
for the light to follow you since the
beginning wow thank you
so many of you
it's been an awesome Journey looking
forward to the next Milestones indeed
indeed
next is for Fest after amigatu your
dream I was already happy but this was
even better yeah I really appreciate her
making that possible
because that was already like incredible
that was incredible
did for me
1.5 Subs this year yeah yeah two million
no 1.5 yes yes
still gonna take a little while maybe a
couple months maybe in the summer would
be nice
and we made it in a cave with a box of
scraps yeah
she did I get that meme
I get it now even more than ever
Iron Man right
that was Iron Man
[Music]
I
think amazing
Bruno thank you again for another recipe
we all have been waiting a long time for
this but seeing you persevere
the setbacks makes me even more proud to
have yeshi congrats on the Showcase Plus
oh boy
well quite a couple of uh Brazilian
super jets on that day my Brazilian Bros
are still there that's so nice
I like having Brazilian Bros
thank you so much hope you enjoyed it
and we're partying with me
during Spark's favorite night and do you
thank you so much for being there
ah 100 I've been to Brazil two times
they're so nice and welcoming
it's like every person from Brazil
is like I don't know part of the
marketing team for the country because
they're always like 100 percent
oh
you're so enthusiastic
they have a good marketing team yeah
tourist ambassadors
laughs sir 956
Marshall Marshall
yo
finally there was a stretch of non-pinks
or Reds now it's over again
it's over
pong thanks for the pinky finally
Britney showcase we've all been waiting
for you went through so many obstacles
to be here when I run into obstacles I
think look at Wawa and where she is now
with the power of Phoenix I can do it
too love you and let's have fun you do
you the best bye
[Music]
that's sweet
that is too sweet
thank you for sharing that with me poem
you also the best thank you for
organizing cool things over there like
the advertisements thank you I really
appreciate it I hope I can get to see it
when does it start
when does the the uni coffin when does
it happen is it on the day on that
weekend
13th
[Music]
I hope please somebody take a video and
and pictures okay
I don't think I can see it
foreign
I will take videos
wait no
maybe maybe you can't see it
[Music]
wait a second
um
is there like special times during the
day there must be right special times
where it's happening
can you tell me when
it's always on the same time each day
eh it's just a really normal keyboard
uh
no play for one minute every hour
oh oh
well update on Twitter okay tell me like
which which hour at which which minute
in the hour
I might be able to see
yo imagine I go and then I'm like
waiting I'm on Standby and then like
a second before it happens somebody Taps
me on my shoulder and it's like uh sorry
do you know how to get from uh here to
this place and like you know ask me for
help or something something and I'm like
totally distracted and don't get to see
it I'm like [\h__\h] I missed
to wait an hour but maybe I can't
oh
thank you you also helped out thank you
13 to 19 at every hour thank you wow
such a long time
yeah nobody tapped me on my shoulder
when I'm on Standby waiting for my
advertisement or whatever that is
foreign
[Music]
video
window
confused
this one
yeah
yeah that's it okay found it I reopened
it
um
I will put like studs
spiky studs like Cali's I will I will
just borrow her cape
and I'll put it on so people cannot tap
my shoulder because if they pat tap my
shoulder
their hands will be well
on spikes
[Laughter]
cute fan art idea
but it's gonna get kind of bloody but if
you think that's cute
sure
impaled
for trying to distract me
a mohawk too yeah in case of yeah that's
how I can protect myself from people
trying to pet my head when I don't even
like that
I need a mohawk for that wow finally
no I was never really into the idea of a
mohawk but now you finally have
convinced me
thank you
yay
[Music]
wow
good idea okay that will be my next
hairstyle
oh thank you
rare find it thank you
it's confirmed now yeah
whole burp approved
wow smart
uh um anyway thank you pong I'm looking
forward to seeing it I think I have a
chance at seeing it
Tech thank you for the pinky
I'm so happy to see your 3D Live let's
go oh thank you
I hope I hope I really want to do 3D at
a Korean convention please
please please please please
please please please
I heard of some
uh I heard that in Korea uh motion
capture is actually pretty cheap
so
um
Maybe
yeah
it's way cheaper than elsewhere
totally like for an event I would say
that's totally affordable
because they do a lot of they they do a
lot of motion capture recording in Korea
or games
hmm
you know like I guess
uh
LOL
which does not stand for Lord of
something look League of Legends
too deep into the Lord of the Rings
right now because I just watched it
League of Legends yes yes stuff like
that
um
uh yes a trip to Korea motion capturing
there would be cheaper than doing it in
Europe but
I would still lose money from it if it
was just for the sake of a pretty stream
a one-time 3D stream I would probably
lose money from it unless
uh the company pays for it which I do
not believe in that but for an event you
know I think it could be considered if
they want it to be in 3D
foreign
[Music]
let's share even louder well the great
late birthday present this is a dream
come true for all of us keep up keep up
and never be afraid to make your dreams
come true thank you
wait wasn't your birthday recently
maybe I already told you a happy
birthday but in case I didn't
happy birthday
[Music]
belated I wonder how late it is hmm
it'd actually be easier than using I
don't know about that well
but it's definitely worth looking into
I would say
yeah
you got older congratulations it wasn't
a 19th oh
what was I doing on the 19th was I
streaming
or was I sick or was I in Indonesia
where was I
hmm
was I in Indonesian or not
a pen
well well well I hope you celebrate it
well and yeah you're welcome to see this
as a late birthday present you're
welcome hope you enjoyed it thank you
millions of them thank you
action
I want to see pen lights
looking forward to four Fest
it's about four hours less time to Seoul
in Tokyo
you mean from Austria
um four hours really I don't remember
how long I think I had a
diary did I have a direct flight
I think I had a direct flight to Seoul
uh in that case it was definitely
shorter than what I'm doing right now
because right now there are no direct
flights
so that [\h__\h] sucks
I keep a set of pen Lights by my
computer for such an occasion really
you're always ready
seeing all those pamelites in third Fest
was amazing hearing them shared the
cereal being Brown yes like a while ago
when I was asking they still told me
that no voice
uh uh no code no cheering allowed
so yeah
I shouldn't ask them to cheer either
but
things have changed and now it's allowed
us yeah
yeah
oh already lost all hope but see see
there's always hope
there will always be hope
thank you thank you
foreign
just take my money and let me cry and
happiness
ah three years that's insane isn't that
crazy man
thank you for such a long time together
believing in me staying with me no
matter what happens through ups and
downs
yeah
we went through a lot of things thank
you you're the best
[Music]
you can cry it's okay
cry it out
I would give you my shoulder if I could
but
she
don't don't cry uh yourself out on my
shoulder when I'm wearing Cali's Cape
okay
um
we're getting all together
yes
[Music]
you lose an eye worth it maybe for some
of you
if you get to crack my shoulder worth it
Anton M thank you for the pinky I'm so
happy for you thank you the long-awaited
3D showcase is finally happening you're
the best I can't wait to see your Divine
and exquisite skits
skits or did you mean skills and I
wonder if I'll see it working people are
like kind of saying I was twerking when
I was hatching the egg but I was not
I was not I was not trying to twerk
there
I was just trying to
um
you know spread the warmth
throughout so that it wouldn't be too
focused on one spot you know
now I would I just had to
I had to spread out the warmth
it's very scientific yellow
when when I talk you will know
imagine
you know how we talked about major scent
by having Collision on her boobies
imagine if I had collagen on my butt
[Applause]
[Music]
that would be too evolved we're not
ready for dead
what
Collision I guess oh
Collision Collision oh okay yeah
Collision oopsie
you talk funny no you talk funny you
Australian little [\h__\h]
I like it though
thank you Anton M again for it
celebrating together
shots fired
yeah I don't want to hear that from the
Australian
W thank you for the rest of the chat you
look so good and pretty Kiana
congratulations oh stop thank you
I remember when people first saw my 3D
Japanese members also were saying oh
it's like exactly it looks exactly like
her life today but in a good way like it
is perfectly recreated
and put on a 3D body
I'm glad you guys like Freddie King
thank you
W thank you cute dog by the way
give me a donkey a notorious BSG danke
schoon izurusan pinku super chato thank
you thank you
spankenheim thank you for the rest of
the chat happy free detention been
waiting for this for so long it's
finally here I feel so proud to be a
chicken thank you
yes yes I'm glad if you guys were proud
of me I tried to do my best to impress
everybody
you know make the most out of the
opportunity
if you guys were proud then I am
satisfied thank you well
thank you spanking Heim I hope your cat
also enjoyed
my 3D showcase
um
mission accomplished yeah
Justin Lambert passion Galaxy wolves
[Music]
looks amazing now that you can actually
join us on the cashier restaurants I
promise to work as hard as the other
chickens and will definitely not be
distracted by looking hard working in
front of you
um
in hindsight I would have liked to add
even more chickens to the
like default state of kfb
but
I think it looked really good
yeah it's good that I could also go back
to the kitchen and all that
too bad that there that we can't go
inside the usual room but I think in
hindsight it's good that we couldn't go
in because
yeah they probably wouldn't have been
able to recreate the whole currently
Canon uh looks of the usual room that
would have been probably too much work
but um they would have probably turned
that down so I would have had to be
really simplified
maybe just simple back room for brooms
hmm
but I think yeah just the door with the
sign that says the usual room is already
threatening enough yeah the the picture
yeah
it definitely is a door you do not want
to open
[Music]
maybe it really is just a broom closet
and we just hallucinate the rest out of
fear
I like that idea yeah could be
um
uh where was I
ah I am Benjamin thank you for the pinky
sir 956
thank you for the recipe
yo I'm like uh my scroll bar tells me
I'm in the middle already how is this
possible
I'm doing quite well I would say
nice
red
right
thank you for the recipe chat thank you
it's been a while two and a half years
but we finally made it here work and
life keeps me away from your live
streams most of the time but I'm always
rooting for you as a vault Watcher keep
on shining brightly and wish you best
for the future
watching the Vlogs uh you guys are just
as important
um
I'm glad you still try to be here even
if it's not live I hope you enjoy it
thank you thank you thank you maybe
sometimes every once in a while you can
make it to the live streams
so you made it to this one to the 3D one
thank you
and greetings to vodkang
thank you for the support
counting chickens dancing
um
foreign
[Music]
hey
Argo now
again soon double was that an accident
high fructose corn syrup
um thank you
for the pinky now
cute Hannah finally made it the Phoenix
always runs towards her Dreams Come
Sunny down
cute cute cat cute wild cat
what kind is that is that a
hmm what cat is that the face looks so
cute
I've said it before it's not is it that
is
chica I don't think so
I need to learn more about wildcats I
guess
links oh yeah it could be
wild cats was Ned from
uh High School Musical
anyway
thank you thank you thank you please
continue supporting me in Korea so maybe
I can be at a Korean conventions and
again okay I can't speak English today
oh my God
thank you
hope we can see each other in Korea okay
I shouldn't have done this one too I'll
have two number nines and number nine
large number six with extra dip as
number seven and two number 45s one with
cheese A large soda I remember when you
guys were spamming me with that back in
the day
because it was funny then
people had this one phase where they
responded me with this
in super chats
I remember that
and I tried to read them all
okay
dragon's fire thank you for the words of
the chat Kiana's so cute my heart
and are you saying your heart hurts
because I'm too cute why are you saying
I am in your heart or are you saying
you're giving me your heart maybe I'll
apply
I'm guessing all apply right
okay I take your height you can have
mine
all of the above
I thought so
Deadpool five thank you soon candy
stamps thank you soon ultimate
thank you for the wordless red super
chattel well I've I've seen you I
noticed you were sending I think also
wordless red super Chats on the collab
stream I noticed in the chat
thank you for supporting I don't know
who those super chats go to but probably
to a management projects so
thank you for supporting them too
I've noticed you thank you thank you
thank you pay for the pizza possibly
yeah
General budget
hello
toilet paper thank you for the pinky
Mama 3D let's go indeed let's go let's
go let's go more more more please more
seventh evil Danke Schoen uh
total
s
foreign
um
so stay full face
foreign
[Music]
honestly really
ah thank you so much it's not a given
it's not
something that just I can expect from
you guys but you did it anyway thank you
really
I hope you were able to fix your sleep
schedule after that and then ruin it
again for the 3D collab as well
HP 22 hours
thank you
and
I might leave it at that yo I am at 25
minutes now not bad and way past the
middle in the scroll uh bar
what
I might keep it at that that's fair no
no you guys are so sweet
I love you guys
recently people have been saying more
and more that I am parasocial
well
okay
I accept
[Music]
is is it wrong to feel like you guys are
very important to me
hmm
I'm just thankful for you guys being so
so supportive
you know and I don't know I want
everyone to feel special and I want
everyone to know how much I appreciate
each and every single person's support
individually
and I I mean I can't say
that to like every single one in almost
1.5 million subscribers but I'm trying
I'm trying
see seeing those
that's fine
it's um it's impossible to watch someone
for so long and not get attached in some
way same for the streamer yeah you know
more and more it's just I mean I feel
like I've I've been always appreciative
of it since the beginning of having such
a special chance but
time passes and I'm still doing this and
I mean
um more and more I appreciate especially
the people who have been here for a long
time and don't give up on me you know
stuff like that it just means so much to
me and it's a long time you know
it's just special every day is special
and we I don't know it's just nice to
have people who believe in me
and want to spend time with me
[Music]
um
no I don't know I don't know I don't
know if you could really call it
parasocial and that sounds like so so
negative
it's a joke right it's a joke probably
because it can't be
I feel like however I'm feeling
well you guys
very understandable and a human reaction
yeah I think it's a meme
[Music]
yeah but it's funny
oh Azuka I want to try that yeah yeah I
saw I saw because Senpai doing that
before
yeah I mean right now in this Super Chat
reading stream obviously there's not
that many people here
but I kind of want to try it
well what am I saying my Super Chat
reading has
the same amount of viewers as I had in
my last stream what was my last stream
uh
what was it
check Fire Emblem
Man Poor Fire Emblem
it's such a long series I understand
it's okay it's just you know
a long long RPG series but I will
continue playing it I don't care but
okay
uh members okay here no wait subscribers
I I can't do it with uh subscribe with
members but I can do it with subscribers
or I guess with members You See It
Anyway by the icon okay okay
let's say
um okay everybody chat as much as you
can so we can see a difference in the
you know amount of people
say hi everybody
this is normal this is normal wow
don't be shy don't be shy lurkers come
out of the Shadows come come okay and
now we're gonna do
six months continue continue
six month subscribers
hi everybody can you chat
hi it doesn't look that different to me
to be honest
so let's do
one yeah but I know that isn't there
something like where YouTube or is that
other social media
some places they have like bugs where
they unfollow someone even though you
didn't do that I wonder if YouTube has a
problem hi
hi
again whoa hello hello
[Music]
probably my last yeah you think you'll
you'll be bunked out of this group
soon
hello hello hello hello okay okay are
you ready for the next level
oh I will go
um oh wait I can only go I can't do like
1.5 I have to go up to two years what
that means for years is impossible
until September
okay
ah maybe with months I can let me try
later that's still two years
24 months of subscriptions
bye bye no no
bye bye
hi yeah papaya
hiya papaya thank you for staying
subscribed for so long wow
thank you
yeah I don't really notice much of a
difference still unless you're just
chatting harder to flex
um
open substance debut thank you
Still Standing hey what's up oh now here
comes oh Lord evoke
what would you remember for 29 months
only my members chat can persist because
if you're unsub and resub you lose the
streak did you lose the streak
Erica 19 months no
still in yeah but then you don't have to
send the members in order to communicate
with me
but unless you're under two years you
could communicate with me through
members messages and super chats
in substance December 2020 I should be
here but I'm not
yeah see that may be one of those
instances where YouTube has unsubbed you
once and you subbed back again
or you just had one day where you were
like I'm breaking up with you kiwawa and
then five minutes later you're like
never mind I love you I'm sorry
but someone like Evans L obviously
cannot
um chat right now because
it keeps on subscribing and
unsubscribing and subscribing and
unsubscribing every day
I would be funny
actually able to chat and then we'll be
like wow what does that tell us huh
everything until now was a lie
it was our lives
is he here
and just
subscribe
strike two years with no break in
between
and we all knew it we knew it
and for in case you don't know evanzel
is famous for being tuned and always
saying hmm oh she's she's so cute today
I might consider subscribing
it's so funny to me
caught in 4k it's a bug
uh the bluff the bluff
pretty sure I accidentally unstuck but I
can chat what the [\h__\h] hmm
maybe it was too short oh I Luna of 20
rib ships
thank you eluda ah you were here and you
heard I saw you in the chat yesterday
thank you for supporting me
we appreciate the pizzas
okay let me try can I do the
um
so two years is 24 months
can I do I can how much is
20 24 or 30 is uh two and a half right
30 months is two and a half let me try
that are we really passed
two and a half
let's see
who has been subbed since debut
only Channel subscribers
guys
talk to me
okay I guess we were not quite past uh
two years and six months
subscribe I'm subscribed at some point
let us in
okay maybe maybe it was a
miscommunication maybe it hasn't quite
been 30 months maybe it's been 29 months
so you just disappeared immediately
sad as Dad
how sad man my membership was not open
yeah but this is about subscribers sorry
it's about subscribers not members okay
here we go 29 months can you come back
to me please go
foreign
guys guys
[Music]
map let's go that was scary I know I
know
especially for a parasocial voila
yeah had to ABS unsubscribe and
resubscribe from time to time to keep
you at the top of my list oh
oh some people do that huh
I guess so you might not be the only one
yeah welcome back okay
it was really weird yeah the chat died
so quickly that I thought maybe my chat
was lagging
okay thank you for this fun experiment
yeah I I know yeah I have a lot of loyal
viewers but not so many new ones give me
a chance guys
need to spread kfp
okay well I mean
there must be a reason why these people
are so loyal right
and that is because kfb is the best
kfp cycle
okay go back to normal
it's only been a year and four months so
it's okay we're going back I just wanted
to test it out it's okay no matter how
long you've been here
doesn't matter but it's cool to see that
so many stayed for such a long time
because you know other people may have
left but you stay
and I love you for that thank you
we were able to know that finally I had
that on my mind for a while
back welcome back
that was two years and three months
two years Phil to me no I'm here for 1.5
years now thank you
thank you thank you
excellently press the answer button half
a year ago oh no what the [\h__\h] no oh
accidentally
one year nine months counting yeah let's
go two months two years soon
thank you I've only been here four
months thank you for finding me and
giving me a chance
you guys
the ships holy [\h__\h] 20 memberships I
don't know if there's even that many
non-members in here at this point
thank you
wow Jesus
Jesus Christ
I found you last year that's okay thank
you
are we getting close to another emotes
love
I feel like it was like maximum already
and it didn't matter how many new
members would join
what happened what
yeah
yeah they cap at some point yeah and
then you have to like this I think it
said something like please discuss with
us directly
I don't know if I ever did that though
I remember you promised to marry your
cats when I subscribed
so what what are you trying to say are
you expecting me to follow up on that
anyway I am
I'm gonna prepare now I guess for my
recording I think
let me see my schedule
okay
oh
well it wasn't even my fault oh my God
okay
oh I I just looked on my schedule and
I'm like I have plenty of time right
because um it was supposed to start at 5
p.m uh in the schedule and
I I have that too sometimes it's okay
um turns out it started 15 minutes ago
it wasn't my fault
but it's okay
quickly
I was gonna end my stream
anyway
uh I'll be there bye
turned out it started at uh you know 15.
um
primary
military time or something like that you
know what I mean and I also made that
mistake sometimes it confuses me too
when I say for example
9 p.m sometimes my brain thinks I'm
saying 19 so 7 P.M
yeah it was put into the schedule
wrongly but it's okay it seems okay
because there's plenty of time okay but
that even more means I should go now
thank you guys
if
I gotta run
ah
[\h__\h] good good that I checked the
schedule and Discord now oh my God
[Music]
okay okay bye