Cinderella,
a fairy tale by the Brothers Grimm, a rich
man, his wife became ill and when
the filter that we came to the end called
her only daughter to the
bed and said every child stay happy
and that's good, the good Lord will always be at
play and I want from heaven
looking down on you and wanting to be around you
then she closed her eyes and said
goodbye the girl went out every day
to her mother's and
cried and stayed pious and well
winter came the snow put a
white table on the bike and when it
came  The sun in the spring has
gone away again, the man had taken
another woman, the woman had brought two daughters
into the house who were beautiful and white
in the face but spiritually and
black in the heart,
on the other hand, a bad time for the poor
stepchild. The stupid one should be completely
Sitting in the room with us, they talked about who has to
eat bread and earn it from the
Mitterkirchen market. They took his
beautiful little clothes from him, put a
gray old coat on him and gave him
holding his shoes
took her to the church and
she had to do hard work from morning to evening,
get up the day before, carry water, light the fire,
cook and wash, and on top of that,
I know everything, she gave her godfathers, and then they
mocked
her and poured the peas and lentils into
the ashes so that she could  She had to sit and
read them out again in the evenings when she was
tired of working, she did
n't go to bed but had to
lie down in the ashes next to the stove because that's why
she always came out strong and dirty
Wanted to have a fair,
he asked the two stepdaughters what
he should bring them, beautiful little
fine pearls and precious stones, the second one,
but Cinderella, he said, what do
you want, father, the first live one that comes to
you on your way home,
the one that stands out for me is him  Now he bought
beautiful dresses for his two step-sisters,
beads and precious stones and on
the way back
he took a green book and touched him with hazel rice
and knocked off his hat. Then he broke the
rise up and warmed it up with him when he got home
the donors what they
had wished for and to
Cinderella fork the raise from the
Haselbach Cinderella thanked him went
to his mother's grave and planted
the raise on it and cried so much that
the tears fell on it many universities
watered
it but it grew and was a beautiful
branch  remedy for all days we
cried and prayed three times and every time
a white field came along the tree
and when it made a wish
and deduced what it had
wished,
it came to pass that the king
made a feast for the three  It was supposed to last for days
and to which all the beautiful young
women in the country were invited
so that they could be and a woman out of
hunger we hired two stepsisters
when they heard that they were also
supposed to appear there, Cinderella had been in good spirits
and spoke can give
us the hair
he is for
We're going to the wedding at the
royal castle
Cinderella said rumors but because
she would have liked to go to the dance
and party Stepmother she wants to allow him
Cinderella said she's full of dust
and dirt and she wants you at the wedding  you
have no clothes or shoes and want to
dance when
it stopped with requests,
she finally spoke through the clean key,
lenses poured into the when you have read the
springs out again in two hours
you should go with
the girl went through the back door after
garden and called you farm
doves, you lovebirds, all the birds
under the sky come and help me
read
the good ones in the potty, the bad ones
in the croplet. Then
two white cakes came in through the kitchen window and then
the turtledoves and finally
all the birds
under the sky buzzed and swarmed in and
The US fans and the great mickeyed with their
head and started with a picnic
and then we also bring it up and
let all the good guys in the
shots. It was barely an hour around 20
and finished and everyone flew out again.
He brought it  girl the stepmother's bowl
was happy she thought it
should now get on the skin
but she spoke a Cinderella
you have no clothes and you ca
n't dance you will only be laughed at it
now cried she spoke at the end with two
keys of lentils in an hour
from the  If you can read the ashes in,
you should go along and thought that it ca
n't be more than a victory. He
had poured two bowls of people into the ashes
against the girl through the back door
to the garden and called out numbers to
deceive the lovebirds, all here,
little birds under the sky, come and help
The good ones read into my potty, the bad ones read
into my head. Then
two white potties came in through the kitchen window and then
the turtledoves and finally
all the little birds under the
sky came in and swarmed around the
alchemy and the little pigeons nodded
their heads and started
and then the others catch up and
let all the good ones into the
bowls and he had been around for half an hour,
they were already finished and flew
all sorts of things. The girl took the
bowls to her stepmother and was happy
and thought she could now go to the
wedding, but  She said it doesn't help,
you can't go with me if you don't have any
clothes and you can't dance,
we'd have to get your beautiful ones
then she turned her back on him, the old one
with her two proud tech land,
when no one was at home anymore, against
Cinderella to his  mother digs under
the hazel farmer and calls little tree shakes
and shakes you like gold and silver
over me then the bird brought
down a gold and silver dress and
with pointer and silver from embroidered
slippers in the hall she put on the dress
and went to the wedding of her sisters
And the stepmother could
n't do it and said it must be a foreign
king's daughter. She was so beautiful in
the golden Cinderella dress.
They didn't think so and thought about it
at home in the dirt and looked for the lentils
from the ashes. The king's son can
receive it from her  hand and
defied him,
he didn't want to dance with anyone else,
so he didn't let go of his hand
and when someone else came to
ask for it,
that's my dancer, it's you,
it was evening, he wanted to go home,
but the king's son spoke  I'll go with you
and accompany you because he wanted to see
who the beautiful girl belonged to,
but the judges told him and jumped
into the pigeon house. Now the king's son waits until the father came and told him that the strange girl had jumped into the pigeon house.
The intended one was already Cinderella
and she  He had to bring him soldiers
so that he could break the pigeon house in two,
but there was no one
in it
and when they got into the house, Cinderella was lying in
the ashes in her dirty clothes and a dim
oil lamp was burning in the chimney.
Cinderella had quickly jumped out of the
pigeon house at the back and
There was also a hazel tree running around,
he took off his beautiful clothes
and laid the grave and the
bird took them away again and
then he quickly sat down in his gray
coat in the kitchen
the next day when the party started
again  ohb and the parents and
stepsisters were gone again in
cinderella and hazel tree and said
little tree shake and shake you like
gold and silver over me then the
bird threw down a lot of proud year clothes
the day before and when it was with
this little one at the wedding
You were amazed at the beauty of the
colexon, but he waited until it was there,
you could have it at your fingertips and you could
only be alone with them when the others
came and asked him to do so
The king's son went after him and
she wanted him to go into which house but it
jumped away from him and in the garden behind
the house a beautiful large
tree arose on which the most beautiful pear
lines climbed like a
squirrel between the first and the
king's son knew  Not only had I gotten there,
but I waited until the father came and
spoke to him. The strange girl came
to light
and I think it was spoken to the pear tree.
The father thought it should be Cinderella. He
had the ax fetched and turned
over the tree,
but it was  nobody on it and that's where
the kitchen came. Cinderella was lying there
in the ass like one of the other ones had been spun
down from the tree on the other side.
The bird on the hazel tree had
brought back her beautiful clothes and dressed her gray childishly
on the third day  parents and
sisters were gone, Cinderella went
back to her mother's grave and said
to the little trees, little trees, shake you
and send you joys of silver
over me. Now the bird threw
down a dress for him that was as splendid and
shiny as any it had ever had before
and the  The slippers were completely golden when
the act came about in the dress.
They all didn't know what to do because of their astonishment.
The king's son could be all alone with
him and when someone asked,
he said, "That's my fighter. It was now the evening of
Walter Cinderella Ford and the
King's son accompanied Wolters
but he jumped so quickly that he
couldn't follow. But the king's son had
used a cunning and had the
whole staircase painted with bad luck.
When the credits came out, the girl's left part of
the girl's left part remained
the king's son ruby ​​on and  He was
small and delicate and very cold. The
next morning he took it to the
man and said to him that no other should
be ground mine than the one that
fits this golden shoe on the foot.
The two sisters were happy
that they had a puddle for themselves, the
eldest  went to the room with the school
and continued to try things on and the mother
stood there but she could
n't get in with her big toe and the
slipcase was too small for her so the mother handed her
a knife and roughly spoke the cere
off when you're queen you
don't need it anymore  to go on foot
the girl ran the therapy one foot
in the shoe doggedly in pain and went
out to the king's son then he took her
as his wife on the horse and rode
away with her but they had to just
pass the one who sat there on the hazelbock for two days
him and called good team
stuck it ended up too small the right
breast three more public who on her foot
and saw how the blood came out used it to kill
his horse brought the wrong bride
home to them and said that it
won't be the right one the other sister
should  Put on the shoe and they went
into the chambers and came with the ten
lucky ones, the shoe but the verse was
too big so he handed the mother a
knife and addressed a piece of the heel
when you are queen you do
n't have to walk anymore,
the girl  wrote a piece of the
heel branch, put the foot into the shoe with
dogged pain and went out to the
king's son, my name is she, as his
bride, got on the horse and rode with her ford.
When they
passed the little hazel tree, the two pigeons sat
on it and called rookie the cuckoo
The shock is stupid, the shock is too
small. The right bride, now still at home,
looked down on her foot and saw
how the blood was pouring out of her shoe and how
red had appeared on her white stockings.
Then he turned his horse and brought the
wrong bride back  home,
that's not the right thing either, he said,
you don't have another daughter, no,
the man said only from my late
wife, there's still a little one suspected of being
Cinderella, because that can't possibly
be the bride of the king, and said
send it out, the mother answered,
oh  No, that's far too dirty, it
shouldn't be seen,
but he wanted you out and
Cinderella had to be called.
First, she'll put her hands and face
in, then go and show herself in front of
the war, who handed him the golden
shoe and then sits down  The first person to make sure
his skull pulled his foot out of his
heavy neck and put it in his
slippers.
He was like a glove and everything is
safe. He adjusted the height and the king
looked them in the face. Then he recognized the
beautiful girl who had danced with him
and called out  That's the right bride, the
stepmother, the two of them had fun and were
frightened and were immediately in front of him,
but he took the Cinderella unlocked it
and scratched it with the Ford. When they
passed the hazel tree, the
two white bags called rocket ebook
Bürgenstock the shock is not too
small  the right bride the publishers and
when they had called that they
both flew off and sat
on Tim Cinderella's shoulders, one on the
right and the other on the left and remained
sitting there when the wedding with the
king's son was held on the side.
The false sisters wanted to
ingratiate themselves and  share and take his club
when she stepped people now went to the church
the oldest was to be calculated the
youngest to the left side there the
pigeons grabbed each one's one eye out
afterwards when they went out the
first was to be directed and the youngest to be
erected there grabbed  Each one's dreams
turned out the other eye and they were
therefore punished with blindness for the rest of their lives for wickedness and falsehood.
Why
[Music]