[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
Kat
k k
[Music]
man
man I don't
understand I hate my audio
mixer it's doing this thing maybe uh oh
maybe it's not doing it for you guys
because I have a
different way of capturing the audio for
for you guys
AKA do you hear this like fade in fade
out right
now that right now it happened after he
talked H this it's
happening it's happening I think you
guys don't hear it yeah yeah if I
switched to desktop audio you guys would
probably hear it that's okay I I can
handle it but I just don't [\h__\h]
understand why why
I set up my mixer which is a
roadter Duo um yesterday from scratch I
did a factory reset because I just felt
like everything was messed up and I
didn't understand anything
anymore I generally already had a pretty
low understanding of how this [\h__\h]
works so I did it again I did a factory
reset and I just um watched it tutorial
again on everything all the features and
everything and even while watching [\h__\h]
like that it's still confusing and
misleading and weird I just hate it so
much it's so hard to work with this
thing I want to
switch I personally would love to go
back to go
XLR I would love
that it's just so much more user
friendly you know
but they don't have software support
anymore I mean isn't there maybe like
user uh how do you say that user um oh
shut up I don't think the people who
complain about the golr have really any
idea what they're talking about there's
no difference there's so many other
members who use
goxlr it's not the fault of the goxlr
whatsoever
um but yeah I was thinking like maybe
there's like like because like hundreds
and thousands of people am I peeking
today oh yeah I might be hundreds and
thousands of people have been using let
me turn it down um the GH L right and so
if there if it's suddenly abandoned I
would I would think that there would be
yeah like an open source project like
people who use it decide to continue
making software updates for it or
so there is open source programs for is
that what I
mean there is I thought so it must
be H there is that been using
it much is it is it
useful I just can't [\h__\h] work with
this broadcaster [\h__\h] I'm sorry but I
hate it it's so stupid
yesterday when I was doing the Koke I
was um I didn't hear the music at all in
my that was one reason why a lot of My
Singing was off um although in HIDs side
listening back to it it wasn't even that
bad but it sounded way worse in my ears
but I like barely heard the
music now I sound low what do you mean I
sound low an OBS it shows I'm in the I'm
in the yellow
but for the average person it might be a
p pain in the ass to work with you know
what's a pain in the ass to work with
this roadter Duo thing I'm
using I might I mean okay I found out
one cool thing yeah while I was like
setting it up a new
yesterday one cool
thing hey
I found like built
in
[Music]
a I finally found these kind of things
um and and these are these are built
in I mean the
W might just be worth
it
woo
[Laughter]
hello you don't like it what what what
do you mean of course you like it
right ah I thought
[Applause]
[Laughter]
so I've always wanted to have stuff like
this but I was always too lazy to set it
up and also like I don't know copyright
sounds you know I don't know if some of
these sounds are copyrighted but if
they're built into the mixer and I'm
sure I can use
these let's
[Music]
go I might just have to get used to it
um for the sound
board
gross you're gross St shut up
can you copyright sound effect I
mean I don't know like somebody came up
with this first right and then it was
like I don't know it's some TV show
probably or so and then everybody copied
it but cuz somebody must have come up
with that and then everybody must have
been like oh yeah that does sound like
the perfect sound effect to you know
Express
like a [\h__\h] up situation where you
[\h__\h] up do you disappointed or
somebody's disappointed I don't
know whoever came up with that
genius
oh um yeah there might be there might be
like yeah I know I can probably buy all
these sound effects somewhere but
they're in here and already on the
buttons I didn't even have to put them
on the buttons after I did the factory
reset they were just
there updated my firmware and did a
factory reset and I suddenly had these I
don't know if I had them before it feels
like I
didn't now see I can edit the volume of
some of these things but I still this is
again a a thing that I wonder why cuz go
Sal you could easily do this um I cannot
change
the
volume of the megaphone even though it
is significantly louder but at least it
seems to be like capped at a certain
point as I can just see right now but
it's it's it's
louder right and I can't change it
that's so
stupid m
it's only capping actually because I
have my OBS
lowered yeah I can change the volume on
other things on some of the some of the
sound
effects only some of them but
yeah sorry I have um I have a healthy
snack
today
uh Vine
Robin
[Music]
oh what's it
called grapes
[Music]
yeah we love Graves
woo with no
seeds
[Music]
wo um
green yeah [\h__\h]
yeah no
it
um yeah and uh I did play a little bit
off screen the only thing I was able to
do cuz all even that just took me two
hours was going through the dungeon
again and but it did gain me like five
to six levels
and I got some cool equipment and I got
a lot of money yeah I didn't I didn't um
I wanted to do the other
stuff that has been recommended might do
it tomorrow before the stream today I
woke up like a
12 and and then I just went to buy cat
food cuz I ran out of cat food and I I
bought I bought I bought a cherry tomato
plant really really nice because it's
already like it already was carrying
fruit so that's
exciting
whoa let's
go
cool I saw you staying
up
yeah for me it's with double n these
days in my brain that's how I say it I I
really wanted her to like I wanted to
watch her cuz like when I joined in she
was already playing for 8 hours I'm
like playing for 8 hours and honestly no
hate just made me realize uh that the
game is really difficult but I I thought
she wasn't like it it just seems like a
game where you can't really get that
good because even after actually she did
a stream before that as well even after
over eight
hours uh there's not much progress to be
made in your skill it seems it's just it
gets chaotic yeah you can't most of the
time you just die because you got
unlucky or it's just uh
unluckiness and the weapon gotcha is
really important like what weap she was
also I I I felt so connected to her
stream because she was also struggling
so much uh with the frisbee getting the
Frisbee like several times and again and
again and again especially with a boss
and then it's like [\h__\h] uh oh I'm
talking about the Kon booku game that I
played the other day Cora was doing a
Endurance on it and I was watching it
for a few hours
the I was watching for 3 hours or so and
then yeah I didn't see it until the very
end but then I watched archive ending to
today when I woke up and I saw ah she
didn't make
it whenever she got the frisbe she just
stopped shooting and went for the next
weapon immediately but not always like
she died a lot by shooting herself with
the Frisbee for example or just you know
the boss killing her when she had the
Frisbee just because she couldn't really
do much with the Frisbee but she was
still
trying but
yeah she only endurance for her when she
writes into the title yeah but like that
was obviously endurance she was
obviously enduring it and oh my God I
can't believe like even me watching it
for 3 hours I felt like kind of like
like it's so it I can't believe she's
been playing it for like eight to 11
hours at that point because I'm even
getting like kind of sick of the like
repetitiveness could have you know if I
if it was me like I would maybe at least
change the map but you don't want to
change the map because like you're you
want to beat the [\h__\h] game and so you
need to you know get good at that
particular map it's better to not switch
it but then again it's like
oh after after you should not play it
for 11 hours
hours that's just I was thinking when I
jumped in at 8 hours yo she probably
should just like call it the day you
can't play a game like this for so many
hours you're not going to succeed I
think but I understand the feeling
completely that like I've already come
this far I need to complete this game
now in this one
stream it was funny I was commenting
quite a lot in her chat and and uh she
had to focus on this on the game most of
the time so she couldn't read my
comments most of the time sometimes she
picked it up and then and then she she
was she was making me go doky doie
again she was making me go doy doie
guys I think I think probably right
after her stream she must have gone
straight to bed because I didn't
get here let me write to her I didn't
had a message about Among Us she said
she might invite me to among us cuz she
was also saying oh I feel like I always
invite the same people and I'm like yeah
yeah you probably do invite
me Among
Us I write a message I think she just
went straight to bed among wait let me
write a full message
[Music]
okay for
among
among get energy drink no
you okay I told her I told her I can't
participate in getting drunk among us
but I be I'm being told that when I
drink energy drinks I'm almost like I'm
drunk whatever I am like when I'm drunk
we don't know
that but if if you really wanted to be a
drunk episode I I could I could
perhaps yeah the participate while
drinking energy
drinks good
point I told her yeah about what on the
game it's not your fault that you didn't
make it it's the fault of the Frisbee
[\h__\h] the
Frisbee you've been drunk with power
many
times true
but I might act differently if I'm drunk
with
alcohol also you guys towards my tweet
of we're so close to the
end you guys are so mean so many of you
guys were like Ki you're not going to
make it and I'm like just be positive
just think positive just just whatever
also yeah whatever like whatever it's
it's okay like
I didn't say in the tweet that I intend
to finish it this week I do intend to do
so but if it's that difficult then
whatever that's not what I said in the
Tweet um but but then it's okay then we
finish it next Saturday
whatever actually not next Saturday um a
girl talkers next Saturday I
think you might have to do it on Friday
cuz
I'm busy on Sunday
might have to be a Friday late night
Friday we can do it pretty late because
the uh Saturday girls talk will also be
late schedule says
finale
yeah yeah
well at least I have good levels
and
uh
I I mean we also finished last week
giving them good equipment
and I got these
shoes out of the
dungeon and I think the life jacket as
well is
new it's a other stuff but that was not
important and I used a lot of items so I
kind of want to I feel like I need to go
shopping let me
see uh two out of five 3 out of five 9
out of
10 I want more of these and
oh yeah oh actually I didn't use that
much it feels like I used so
much mango had a had a really good
mango the other day the first time my
mom bought a
mango and then she cut half of it and I
thought she was going to eat the other
half cuz she cut one half for
me and she was like so excited because
it was a ripe mangar she was like oh my
God
K look it's a right mango oh my God how
lucky we are and I'm like huh I guess
because I never buy mangoes like that
like uncut but I guess usually they sell
them like not ripe here and it's not
good but she was so
[Music]
excited and she got so excited that it
was a r Banger and then I gotc had it
too because it was really yummy it it
tasted really proper mango yeah it's not
so common here because um usually they
sell them
unripe and then I thought she would eat
the other half I put it in the fridge
the rest she she cut me one half right
she leaves one half on the kitchen table
I put the rest into the
fridge
and she just leaves the next day and
didn't eat it I thought she got so
excited about it you would think she'd
want to eat some of
it I would have had no issue with her
eating some of it then she just dis
disappeared I don't know if she forgot
about the
mangar or she just thought oh this
delicious mangar I shall give to my uh
to my precious
daughter so she will grow strong and
powerful seems like chat on screen that
what the what are you doing
what are you doing fix
yourself why must I always do
this here I fixed you right it's not
[Music]
working what's wrong with you why you
why you acting like this why you acting
like a like
a rebellious teenager
H
move move
refresh
cash there you go what's wrong with
you
huh it's just a face yeah yeah that's
what I think it
is stop stop
phasing I fixed you once again it's
going to be a day one day where you have
to be a [\h__\h] adult okay and I'm not
going to fix you
anymore I'm not going to help you with
all your issues
anymore you have to grow up it's time to
grow
up oh God the music is like constantly
fading out and in and fading out out in
out in out in out in out in for me it
look it sounds really stupid like
there's noise cancelling on it I don't
understand
why it wasn't like this before I left
last time and for two or three three
weeks was it what the [\h__\h] did they do
then I couldn't even fix it after doing
a complete uh factory reset
man we for the game
yeah I'm
[Music]
on right all
night all all night
[Music]
L I'm want to hi what am I doing I want
to buy some stuff um
I'm on a
hway I'm on a
hallway I'm on a h way how do you sing
it no I'm not trying to be British I'm
trying to be like you know we need Five
Star Equipment now are you telling me to
go buy
it
where I aren't they like they they're
like spreading [\h__\h] all over actually I
guess in the Super Mall super
mall shopping center
Supermarket plus mall is super
mall they probably have some
stuff get count
count on the hell away how do
you please help me you always just laugh
at me but I never you
never help
me I'm on a
hway I'm going to ride it ride R it R it
all night L the L the L is pretty good I
think I wanted to look what do you
have Aloha blonde Aloha to you too I'm
orange
though I'm on
a I'm on a
high I want to ride o professional board
bir professional
professional
professional uh but I don't think I want
to buy these
weapons because I want to make the
weapons myself for this
team um but we can go a floor up and
buy hi
think I want to buy some clothes right
might want to buy them for
[Music]
later
question yeah what side do you stand on
uh escalator in Hawaii H the trick head
177,000 I'm on a hway
aberant jacket 30 this is going to cost
a lot of [\h__\h]
money a lot of [\h__\h] Mone press
Triangle Well like where
where left side right
[Music]
side stand in the middle if you want no
almost no one walks
really do people in Hawaii just take
life easy
huh away
[Music]
no no not
those that's not even worth my
time speaking for all the US what do you
mean no Escape if they're under my level
almost 10 levels you should just let me
go it's not even worth my time you're
not even I'm just going to attack
normally King cover wi you know I
already did a king cover oh you
know what's what happened with the combo
attack dude it's that combo
attack I'm going to forcefully break
maybe I should have used this
skill yeah K's favorite Pi
cover okay he doesn't have a
grapple again where is the combo
attack why are they lying to me like
that
games say combo attack delivery
[Music]
when back attack has been
properly
exed what was I talking about
anyway what was I talking about whatever
who cares I'm talking about a lot of
things you said triangle what do you
mean triangle I press triangle here and
there's like nothing you mean on the big
map or
what pointed toe 17,00
177,000
peets what does it
do okay I guess I'll buy the shoes
here and the
jacket and the trick
cat and that's all right there's no to
just buy it here or are there better
items elsewhere
maybe we don't even need it for Ichibon
he has something
else recover HP when you that's actually
pretty
dope it's
okay
equip I think I think I'll have enough
money I
guess what is the ich bun wearing thank
you very much Mahalo 17K is nothing yo
okay look just because I have
$329,000 doesn't mean that I will just
carelessly for about
177,000 at [\h__\h] Louis V of
Hawaii because that still is expensive
doesn't matter how much money I have
that's still unnecessarily expensive
let's be
real ooh free pack croissant S I
actually don't like cro did I say this
before I feel like I said this before I
don't like qu
sandwiches quas but at least you guys
can use the quas
emote on this
[Music]
occasion oh that was pretty
good no it wasn't no it wasn't k
thank you for stopping by sorry I'm late
no worries
hello am on
way I'm on the
cross I want to eat
it
chocolate where is the other store is
this one that I wanted to go
to
yeah yeah no you know it's just uh
unreasonable I don't like unreasonably
priced
things I still
shop as
relatively realistic
places this doesn't even have a special
effect that's so
lame is there any jackets elsewhere that
have special effects at
least same me nether very smart mhm mhm
mhm
boo boo boo boo bye
[Music]
Sweet Home
Alabama where the skies are so
blue you're so freaking based on for
that thank
you you get some good gear when you move
on with the story with story yeah but
like usually they only give like one
item that I needed for
everybody it's good investment okay I
just thought maybe elsewhere I could get
something more worth the prize
tag you know with some extra stuff I
maybe I can't I'll leave it for each one
I feel like I feel like at least one
item will probably pick up somewhere and
I'll give it to each one he's still he
still has some some gear that's a little
bit better than everybody else's well
until now but you know you know what I'm
you know how I'm thinking you understand
how I'm
thinking think like me think like wa
[Music]
[Applause]
uh thank you thank you thank
[Laughter]
you oh I supposed to go in
here hi
Oliver and I can I can do how many we I
want I can do two or
four or
endless I'm
sorry okay so what are these
what oh it's a weapon for someone I
thought it was an accessory well it
really is an accessory but thank you for
stopping
by four is the best 1 2 3
4 1 2 3
4 four Bri Squatch and
then
yeah uh hello hello shoes
please oh
M okay yeah yeah I already have some
good shoes for two of
them uh let's give them to her the
pointed toes and again might not give a
to
each also has like decent stuff oh
somebody needs to be rescued Let's
help you might need the weapons too no I
already have sick
weapons I've been doing so well in the
dungeon
too level 12 oh my God
collateral damage kills
[Music]
him oh you guys should not be picking on
the weak people when you yourself are
weak you have nothing to show
for now get a Sher and go drive to
hospital shur shaur Sher Shaffer
hello yeah how do you say
it so you're saying I need to buy the
weapons or don't you just think I should
just make
them oh but I need need to probably buy
them
to are those necessary to craft
with the ones I can buy Here
chur aha so it is PR similar to the
German Way
Sherer
[Music]
Sherer buy the base craft the up ahuh
okay where was
it the uh the axes are maybe in here I
don't even know which one I need though
maybe I'll just come again when I'm when
I'm at the point that I feel like my
weapons are too we I'll just come
back I'll be back don't
worry I already like started looking at
stuff last time when I was crafting and
I was like oh okay you get this stuff
here you get this stuff
here so it's good it's
good Aloha no you I'm right in front of
you always just buy them it's easier
no no not easy for me
no let's go get that conversation shall
we
I'm on a
hway I'm going to ride it old night
long if you're going my
[Music]
way I have I have a bigger repertoire
now if you speak my sophisticated langu
language
huh in in road trip songs hello who the
[Music]
[\h__\h] did I
accidentally drive into main
story what
oh but it's
[Music]
here do they really want me to hurry
that
b
c they can talk to each
other te can talk to each other
that was good to
know good to
know you don't have to go over there now
though oh what else should I be
doing I need to do main
story I'm on a
highway I'm going to ride it all
[Music]
night going to R it
night s where I don't see them see I'm
not trying to avoid them but I I legit
don't see where they are I'm doing
everything you know I'm doing the side
conversations I'm doing the the links
the drink links I'm doing uh the picture
stuff but I just don't see any side
quests I'm doing the rescue
[Music]
missions I don't
see what where
I don't
know the only thing I'm purposefully
ignoring is that stupid like battle [\h__\h]
like the raids and
stuff speech
bubbles that oh I haven't been avoiding
that what speed you mean the the the the
the blue
ones I've I've been running into those
every once in a while but that doesn't
seem like a side quest but now I don't
see any at all
ah wow there wow arer that's a nice
icon wait there they're in blue though
right the
pink yeah these but that's just the the
bonding
bingo I think I you think I toggled them
off oh
interesting oh I can have very specific
ones no I don't see
them oh
where where do you see one
here or locked because of the plot oh
okay so there right now there's none
right um I only see these like pink ones
but those are
different story locked off sub
oh okay well it was never my intention
to like uh just ignore them I just never
saw
them I
swear than baby I swear Baby I
[Music]
swear where my kop
stands something like
[Music]
that that was a sister I think I love
sister I wish they were still a
thing you seriously messing with
me you
know you know pretty okay okay I mean
that's at least something
[Music]
classic group I miss them you
do they were amazing also just because
they
were so different you know they weren't
scared of doing
Concepts that are just more
sexy and that may sound weird to you how
that's different there's a lot of sexy
K-pop but it's different of sister they
still
differently especially with uh what was
her name
Hing like tanning so much which was like
against the beauty standards mostly the
the the biggest beauty
standards in
Korea she was rocking it and honestly I
feel like she was like a fashion icon
with that starting some
[Music]
Trends what's the group name sister s i
s t a r but they're not active anymore
but they're having some solo careers
I'm
Charmed I'm Charmed not so unfitting in
my last dream I have magic powers this
time they actually kind of
worked I was able I was able to maybe
it's it was the effect of yesterday I
was able to like point at
someone with like a gun
finger and say gun and then it shot
them there and some other magic like
like teleporting and stuff pretty sick
pretty
sick cuz I was doing that yesterday in
the K
too not teleporting but the
[Music]
gun
yes yeah okay maybe afterwards we can
still do some sub stories after going
moving on with this part here whatever
you guys are doing
here Pon is making another play for
aanan damn it there's no avoiding a big
fight this
time oh Five Star Equipment Plus
recommended level 35
H
wait I mean it's pretty much let me
see okay five star four star four star
but it's not so bad
bad and it has some special effects yeah
yeah yeah yeah his life jacket and
there's a KO with one HP I found this in
the dungeon and thought that's actually
amazing because you know when ich dies I
go game
over so that's pretty
amazing um but my weapons are so
cool I just made them
recently that's why you I
said you might need new ones right away
I'm like no please don't say that to me
now I'm having fun making new weapons
it's fine with my year I think so too
because it's not just level five it's
also upgraded to 10 plus 10 yeah and I'm
level 36 and 37 let's
go after this
maybe confidence
confidence confidence
half confidence half
confence sorry I was trying to co boss
kasuga's here good kasuga show my
face is he streaming live again oh he's
zooming Zoom
call yeah oh hello oh bastard
[Music]
I normally don't use that word but like
holy [\h__\h] he deserves it so much is
dreaming for a son of a
[\h__\h]
for yeah yeah [\h__\h] bleach Jaan
going to kill me
okay Quint
essentially Quint essentially
you okay what that's just what weird
like what Quint essentially you I mean
yeah that's Quint essentially what he
said in Japanese but I think there's a
better way to say that in English no not
like an easier way yeah that's like
that's totally a kasuga moment right now
right there that is so kasuga of
you quintessential that's so long in
Japanese you just say when you want to
say like that's just like you you say
the name kasuga and then say that's
that's how they said it in Japanese so
Kash or kfp Rashi that's very kfp
like you can trust me
oh you could say like
that for
so you just want me to
suffer
trouble I think streaming someone's like
the murder of that's actually so
stupid you want to stream how you murder
[Music]
me okay do it then you'll be certain to
go to prison for death if it's live
stream I don't think you can ignore
that I don't think no matter how corrupt
the police
[Music]
is there's no way around
that okay let me turn this back down a
little bit for
myself Peak content for
them all right let's see it's kind of
bright I can't see the markings on the
floor so
well I guess work
[Music]
yeah and in the dungeon I usually
started my battle like this those two
skills usually already killed like a
bunch of zackers
[Music]
I could have gotten closer oh well don't
know if it matters oh my God see I'm so
strong things is a great opener I just
when there's so many enemies I just like
to start with an AOE and that's like a
[\h__\h] one of the best like I can use
because of the terization
a why are you all shooting
her
[\h__\h] yeah I tried the scattering of
flowers once I
think I don't want to waste his skill on
an almost dead
enemy what do you
[Music]
got you weak against fire
no h oh
[Music]
well I forgot no you're also not dead
damn it this game looks fun shout out to
the Hat the hat which
hat thank you though oh let's try to get
the one behind as
well almost
time to clean
up she has short hat hair in the eye
cont yeah she got short hair now since
last
time she has been reflecting on her
actions see I I don't
remember when I was writing the tweet
and I'm like thinking what did we do I
just forgot but I generally
remember it was pretty dramatic but I
just had a brain empty
[Music]
moment nice block
Wawa what do you
want you you can have a burning
Arrow I love this
attack nice BL up one more HP with would
have been nice
though character
development oh nice 37 okay I was like
so close to 37 with them
[Music]
huh wait maybe
there's
noise I think there was noise cancelling
on my
out I figured it out
I didn't know I could put noise castling
on my
output
[Music]
hey oh well anyway
yeah I thought you were going to
dodge yeah this one's also quite
nice easy prompt as well if you remember
it but even if you forget it the first
second you can still follow up soon
enough
yeah I think it's back to normal
now but still I'm having problems with
like
balancing
everything like the balance of
microphone versus
my
audio it's okay
though it's okay manageable
guys what that's like bilard bilard is
an English something else
right H
Bard that was like
um pool why the [\h__\h] is it called
pool the English German name is better
for that doesn't even sound like a
German word I think it's like a foreign
word maybe French or something
[Music]
oh you call it
billion
in wait wait wait wait wait don't stop
moving guys
yeah what I
want ah J
always it's such two different games
we technically use Billiards 2 but
nobody says casual oh really yeah I
think I hear pool more often in English
so I thought you guys don't use
bilard
R who is a type of I didn't know there
was different types of
that sport g
sport game sport sport game game
sport sport or game both depending on if
you're playing it as a hobby or as a job
maybe snooker snooker snooker
snooker what the [\h__\h] is that that
sounds
cute that's
cute but I pick up the P for more fin
right here we go it's too late to Circle
back to the entrance upstairs take put
we only drain us so we have to keep
moving wait that I should put that on
the next list for my car K
car I like to move it move it I like to
move it move it like to move it that
would be
fun it looks like conr it might be worth
checking out why am I feeling so hot
maybe because I have a blanket wrapped
around me but just
generally let me turn off the the
[Music]
heating it's just kind of CAU in my
working
room m
the other rooms are not so bad I
think he a gamble okay same here let's
head
[Music]
up
construction
C what is
this Jazzy saxophone trumpet whatever
going on in the
background it's not quite Jazz
though hey y what's
[Music]
up I wish those moves were circles to be
honest this is a bit hard to use
[Music]
triang a a don't don't question
him he's a suy
baka everybody moving out of the way oh
no no we good we good going to say that
might have messed things up but no good
ooh weak to
thunder ah okay I thought that would do
[Music]
it I do really really really hate him
still don't worry
[Music]
ah come
on it's always just a little bit
more my inputs
are so
Point yeah I think so too I never had
such
strong clear ha thread for a game
character before I think so
too might be wrong maybe my memory
is you know misleading
[Music]
me mhm
oh wow that was enough
nice nice
nice yeah Kum was a piece of [\h__\h] too
but I feel like a I just ha a little bit
more personally from a very person
person
standpoint standpoint standpoint did I
just say something really German in
English or do you guys say that too
please tell me you say that
too St
pun do you guys say St yeah you do okay
cuz in German it's also just St Punk
standpoint stand
Point see the different uh the the
similar
yeah a actively causes harm
inent he's a psychopath I mean Kuma is
also a
psychopath I
think thank
[Music]
you was more
ptic oh yeah
yeah wait are we fighting the whole
machine again
oh that is so ridiculous like normally
it's like rafian or like rude people I
don't know it's like heavy
machinery I just realized how ridiculous
that is on its
own two of them um nakima and suda oh
dear it's a [\h__\h] machine how the [\h__\h]
do you fight a
machine can I get both of them or so
stupid maybe I should just boost my
agility for
[Music]
now can I get both they resist
guns
oh oh and knives don't work
oh are you saying I need to do magic
actually
indeed I'll
trying it
both a grapples don't work
okay can you even paralyze heavy
machiner and blind them I feel like no
fire
breaking Master oh they're weak to
thunder let's do this this might be
really
[Music]
useful every
turn okay this is so good we also have
this one what was this again there some
magic damage to enemies with a high
chance area
attack power light power medium let's do
this
cute
cute yeah he has a good weapon for this
oh you can't what [\h__\h] psychop have
attacks people with a heavy
[Music]
machinery I don't I
I
you watch
[Music]
finally learned that song properly just
for that one
[Music]
stream that so funny the clips are so
funny you killed it I can do it even
better it was just I barely was hearing
the
music I had so much fun though in
hindsight right somehow I had I had a
lot of fun more fun watching the Clips
than actually performing them I was like
pretty out of breath most of the
time so good I'm so happy you guys
enjoyed that so much cuz I really
enjoyed it
too and I uh I think we we'll have more
of that more where that came
from what should I
[Music]
do I'm still in that but Ichiban is
not yeah I can't believe like I already
said it when I first thought of it I
can't believe nobody thought of this
before here go in there
it I think we're
in no no
iton please ichan yeah stay no ichan we
both need to get
it your [\h__\h] surf for is in the way
okay maybe look at me look at me
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
I keep on getting away with everything
just like with the Rick Roll I
purposefully put Rick Roll at the very
very very very end of my playlist so
that I would sing it last for you guys
and like give you one big bamboozle at
the very end and then I get so much
karma for it oh my God but then I got
away with it and then I got more Kor but
then I got away with it too
a I was so
happy should I do
this it's AOE but you know it really
only goes uh to him so maybe not worth
it I don't know the lion one no
tag
team I mean I guess one is fine but just
which
[Music]
attack my driving was so [\h__\h] but you
guys don't understand I had to have the
lyrics right right above the gaming
screen so both were windowed and both
were pretty small um if it was on a
different screen I noticed later on
anyway uh the that's like so difficult
and and oh my god there was just so much
to focus on the road and and uh the GPS
and the lyrics and everything oh my
God insect
Army agility currently only one up
then let's but grapple doesn't
work damn
it all right I'll I'll try
this I can't get both can I stop
watching
[Music]
me
okay con by fear
no well understandable who who would not
be consumed by fear except
Lin
luin they
F K-pop
reference I want to watch the wa a
of course you can let's do this I have
everybody ready except for Ali should I
wait for
him should I wait
for oh I said stop watching did I don't
remember what I said 2 seconds
ago wait
okay H yeah okay electricity I think
maybe we can get both
yeah I think this this can get
both
Bo
[Music]
nice you guys making me so aware of this
skill has been incredibly useful you
[Music]
know boyie
Bo I could do this one too but the thing
is only the boogie wogie board has the
range to get both you
know wait I'm so excited today I didn't
even take an energy
drink why am I so
excited I don't know man your skills
like they resist both you know this is
kind of shitty I can I can raise
everybody's attack in critical chance
even more but really only matters for
[Music]
ichibun should I buff
again well I didn't what I didn't drink
Red Bull last night what are you talking
about I
didn't might need he ah true too bad he
does not have a healing
skill I could use an item that heals
everybody a little
bit what do I
have 400 is a bit too
much is that all I
have a you know what I might have an
attack of electric Dam yeah but only 150
[Music]
wow I'm thinking too much about what to
do
huh
maybe this one is okay is it too
little no that was good good amount
Dynamic
combination
okay
[Music]
okay Divine
lightning oh only on one of them oh well
that's okay um we're going to do mask of
fertility although we're already
quite
through with the
uh
fight better late than never then I
might heal or
or wa I didn't realize they would attack
again right after that oh I was going to
even substitute or do a Aloha
dance oh what I I didn't realize they
would do that I didn't look up to the
next
[Music]
thing um that [\h__\h] up
everything it was going so
well I guess it's time for that item
after
all that was I do look at it yeah but
not in that moment cuz I really didn't
think they would get another turn right
away
damn [\h__\h] stricken with fear as
[Music]
well my best
fighter ah
man should be way easier to beat up two
excavators this isn't very realistic
yeah I mean first I was going to say no
you're wrong but actually you're right
because you can I think cuz they move so
slow you can just run up to them to the
person who's inside and punch them in
their face
right yeah I need to revive
actually damn it I I think this is the
first time in the whole game
possibly and I'm Reviving
someone h H I think hop is all
[Music]
right
okay and you know what I'll do
now and H he cannot attack at all when
he's in fear so we will give him um
something to get rid of this here for
ichan
I need him where is uh here Burns
cold what is
fear what I don't have an item that is
particularly for
fear so I have to take
this well
[Music]
okay but I have like everything except
fear the full Party attack
H oh wait can I do it when I'm when I'm
on
him no I
can't wait if I press X I'm getting
sometimes this makes me confused I have
to press Circle right not X if I want to
cancel
it yeah asked e one that was what I was
thinking
yeah Circle right Circle full party
would be Overkill
now
really I know start go okay wait no I
don't think it would be that
Overkill we'll
see I want to try
it oh it will be only
Overkill if it kills them like
twice
which honestly if it kills them I'm I'm
satisfied
already you almost one shot at this boss
of power friend what when they still had
full
HP Overkill sound yeah I mean when am I
going to use it when not in a boss
fight ultimate
[Music]
te oh
yeah I was just waiting fori to load it
up okay chill chill
chill
cusa big cusa can't believe we pulled
through that I'm not seeing anywhere
else to
Runa I say we get a Breo in while we can
more bound to show up more more bound to
sh
up
uh
yeah air horn the air horn is so
good there we [\h__\h]
go that's exactly what I was saying
why I'm not going to buy anything for at
least one person in the team because
they're going to get
wait I already had
one I forgot I had one from the
dungeon
oh is it
better oh it's quite a bit
[Music]
better
H
huh well
we can do the thing where we give it to
someone else from the other team so I
don't have to switch it out the whole
time
nice all right um I think we're good to
go good you want me to talk to you
mhm
yeah no wait can I still pick up that
item well like I don't know maximum 10
hours we're going to ride it
he's saying shut up and drive drive
drive
drive no no no no no are you
stupid no can you even go that fast that
it that it makes
any impact okay oh
wow what the are you
stupid um there were three people
hanging onto this
thing outside of
it oh that's how we get
[Music]
here and then they all died
freaking
crazy are you
okay mhm mhm good
question how the hell did you get out of
that
alive oh no split
Team all right don't worry
BS don't worry BS
where's that noise what the [\h__\h]
happened
here no
um this is awkward I don't
sorry you [\h__\h] K kill
them bring it
on we are
the you're ever going to
meet that's what I I need like some sexy
music something like that I need that on
my sound
board all right here we
go Oh that's oh he's strong ah he's the
strong one out of the bun makes sense
makes
sense we broke
you think he's going to be mad wait we
are both
team no
wait it shows a full team on the bottom
right we're in the same fight in theory
but we have to clean up these enemies
first okay
it was a rough fight doing two fights at
once yeah well saves time I guess
maybe why is the circle so it's because
that's kind of where I am oh this is
kind of interesting the circle
is like trying to capture me and the one
I uh I
select I suppose if that makes sense
yeah yeah
yeah the spin to win
yeah thank
[Music]
membership
ow welcome member you
have uh selected the right choice in
life you're welcome to catch up on the
archive of 2 days ago no 3 days ago my
members only stream in 3D I was
dancing I was dancing I think that
was that
was a really good
M
I have been on a
road yes you guys always are like oh
this is the best member stream now like
this is the best stream ever but I feel
like you guys say that a lot but you
said that about my member stream and you
said that about my Koke yesterday best K
ever you just generally say that a
lot it's just it just means that I'm
always amazing
okay I'm always in in
Innovative and always you know r
oh but I think yesterday with the K the
good thing about that is it it creates a
lot of funny
clips people might come more people
might come to the next car how Okay
because they saw those clips because
they saw how genius I
am shut the g w w w
yeah yeah I'm I'm proud of my content
creation you
know I'm quite
[Music]
proud think I'm just going
to nah whatever
still good
damage thank you guys flight Sim would
be fun too oh you know what I'm going to
sing cuz I'm
living on a
dead I don't know when I'll be back
again
oh I hate to go
you are going to bring it upon yourself
my friend upon
[Music]
yourself need the good songs for flying
but in flight simat flight s simulator
flight simulator are the
flights uh RAV short or r along or are
they like comparable to the driving
stuff that I did
yesterday do you guys know does anybody
know anybody who played
it oh well comparable to your
Tru they can be the equivalent of real
time depends on how fast you're playing
this uhhuh is it more difficult because
there really like less things to [\h__\h] up
in terms of like crushing into things
what are you going to crush into except
you got to nail The
Landing but like there's no traffic
really
usually unless you're
[Music]
reckless but for now I want to focus on
car um Trucking because I'm I'm thinking
of
getting uh I'm going to get the
wheel the wheels on the bus go and and
round round and round the wheels on the
go round and round watch the rest of the
lyrics ow shut
up you guys already sent me some
recommendations I appreciate that for
[Music]
M for uh Wheels I appreciate
that
uh I've seen some nice ones now but I
might actually cat the one that's from
Nintendo if that's okay because I can
use it with my switch with Mario
Kart that sounds like fun
and it looks cuter
too you being but then then
again you
think will I play much more Mario Kart
8X until a new Switch console comes
out you know why why why is he like the
only one with like full HP besides okay
our lady but like I want to use these
skills and it just makes no sense to me
oh well I'll do it
anyway I want to play with you Mario
Kart and Beach
you why do you desire such a
thing with America is a huge
disadvantage I can
imagine okay maybe
maybe what what are what are racing
games that are on
PS5 is
fora one of
them then I maybe get one that's
compatible with PS5 I've
also gotten recommendations no Grand
Turismo
okay I I don't really I don't know I I
mean I'm not going to say for sure but I
don't really care for racing games right
now but
okay we'll see we'll see we'll see
[Applause]
[Music]
wait I should heal
him now everybody's together so let's do
the Bro
face can you do a c I don't think so
it's too stressful too
fast too
Speedy I just want a truck
in peace and in harmony just have a good
time you
know agility is too up
so
[Music]
um maybe one
more is that still going to boost my
agility yes okay
it's going really fast
in yeah I wonder I wonder if I'll be
better at Trucking people said that that
game is
easier when you have a wheel cuz the W
ASD it works but it's just not as
good is
this sick
steering is
tough that's of any car game Wheel is
easier if you drive a if I have
experience IR I
don't ah yeah that makes sense though
that makes
sense I feel like mask of punishment is
actually pretty
weak sadly
[Music]
maybe I'll buff but everybody's so far I
can buff
um Us
free there we go the three of us
no driving experience at all no
nothing
nothing Split Second is a fun racing
game that feels like a big budget moveie
Chase SC oh that
fun we can treat this as a practice Yeah
I'm going to go to the driver's license
off office thing and I'm going to be
like they're going to ask you didn't
have any um you know actual practice so
far and I'm like yeah I do I even
practiced with trucks so far and they're
going to be like what what do you mean
trucks you shouldn't be driving trucks
and you don't even have a license even
for practice like that's kind of unusual
and I'm going to be like
well don't worry I learned a lot from
[Music]
[Laughter]
it
uh I don't know let's keep on buffing
for
now why
not I'm going to rely on the gun
people
and yeah better to crash in a game than
an IRL crash crash crash so difficult so
confusing here another one another
one and then with poor agility I'm going
to do a non-un move I guess that's okay
double
block let's
go that's why simulators exist do the
kfp pilot I suppose you have flying
simulator
experience oh wait she she get another
turn oh her agility is so high okay uh
then I guess we're going to do
illusionary SL or should I just continue
because she doesn't care about non-un
moves really
but this one actually maybe
[Music]
Dam what C afterward either illusion
stash which also on the number of hits
Rises or this one I guess it says light
to extreme so it should be even
better Shadow
clone okay it's really fast probably so
I'm going to miss every single [\h__\h]
PR
I'm so dumb but okay a thousand I
thought it was going to be Bam Bam Bam
like the other one no it's just one and
it comes really slowly I pressed it way
too fast once I saw the triangle damn
it a man oh but she still has two
agility that's pretty good pretty good
pretty good
[Music]
H
500 still good damage I didn't expect
her to have actual clones to
yeah oh okay so burning Arrow raining
Arrow maybe not worth it if it's just
one I don't know this one is fine it's
[Music]
heavy 722
how you like
that I'm doing a lot of K-pop references
these
days
nice last P where we
are been listening to K actually when I
was doing uh Polaroids I was listening
to Ariana gu's new album because I
finally have Spotify
guys I finally got myself
Spotify because a friend was like oh who
wants to join my my family account for
like three bucks a month I'm like oh
well maybe actually sometimes feel like
I wish I had thought
F now I can finally listen to music and
that's what I was using when I was
practicing for the cuz they have lyrics
built-in
lyrics Let's
Go ah yes
the we are close friends so we are
basically a family oh she's out of uh MP
no let's raise her oh he's almost dead
anyway but let's raise her agility one
more
[Music]
time oh that's 600 for a 10 MP skill
guys I'm telling you there's no need to
sleep on the weaker skills I'm so happy
and satisfied with
them 600 yes she's strong and she's
buffed too but you
know damn oh I sh your playlist
so far I don't have that much save but I
save I saved um Arana
gu and
Tak a really really good
singer yeah she has a really good song
new song out that I feel like you guys
would like it's
called wow it's called
Kima yeah maybe look her up on Spa
she has a lot of fun songs yeah that are
really epic yeah oh you like her too
you're also a fan of her oh do you know
her she's actually one of the most
listened uh to on Spotify out of her
company right now I checked it these are
the things I couldn't check until
now but I was actually really surprised
I saw um of course cie has like Ci and
sus Senai have like the highest you know
but my monthly listeners probably right
now because of Chima are are pretty
high yeah pretty darn High one of the
highest in whole life I'm so proud of
myself yeah I don't have a a label and
like like a huge
discography like some others
and I'm just doing my own thing and my
own pace so I'm pretty proud that I have
you know accumulated a good amount
of listeners to my music thank you so
much guys thank you it means a lot to me
I was actually moved when I saw
that may it be Spotify may be other
music streaming services but I really
appreciate it thank you you like check
her out yeah yeah yeah you should
Tak she's she's
amazing you deserve it thank
you can you even get paid on Spotify I
hate so all our music services are
probably
really um but
still still I still want to push it you
know because
I mean I don't know maybe maybe
sometimes it does get recommended to
random people
maybe maybe not maybe yes wait now I can
go down here right can
I or do I have to go like around
somehow can I go
no here no no I still can't go down got
to go around
probably congrats on your music thank
you Grand
me there's absolutely no downside to
pushing it it can only help yeah I
mean it's it's um all everything
together you
know even if one music streaming service
alone maybe doesn't pay so
much it's everything together
[Music]
he's
fine can you press four on
Spotify no for that you have to go on
YouTube I like people's reaction to that
we need more like that we need we need
to bait other members into pressing for
but I think like a lot of them already
saw it like cie surely saw it right I
think so she at least could not escape
the ass load of asses on
Twitter surely she must have seen the
ass even if she didn't press
four press for challenge I even almost
want to do like a YouTube short about
it without even showing necessarily what
it does in the YouTube short but like
just like
hinting or be like oh my God you can
win1 million dollar if you press four on
Kima and then
bz maybe that's
illegal maybe that's
[Music]
illegal sorry I'm in
I this doesn't raise my agility this
raises my agility but and this needs
agility but I want agility
for what do you think could this KO in
one go let's give it a
try yes that my ability and I used
something effective let's
go I like to be efficient min min max
Minx we love the min max we just love it
so
[Music]
much so are you all only weak to
water
maybe what it still kills okay maybe
that was totally Overkill what I did
with
Chan Chan
I think that may have been Overkill if
he can kill him with a weaker skill
that's not
efficient then that was probably very
[Music]
Overkill oh but this didn't kill really
efficient but relatively weak attack I
get it
okay uh
multiplayer I I think I saw videos I saw
videoos um it may have been Microsoft's
slide simulator I saw a video of a pilot
pilot there like people actually role
playing there in in the online
servers and a pilot was there and like
the the kids who were role playing as
pilots and stuff were like having a
blast being Guided by the actual pilot
whose job is being a pilot IRL but he
was like sitting in the Watchtower I
think and yeah he was just playing
around together and he was giving proper
commands and stuff and then the the non
real pilot who was in the plane the kid
was like doing flips and stuff and the
pilot was like hey yo you probably
shouldn't do
that it's cute yeah that's kind of cute
for
[Music]
real don't do this in reality
yeah traffic control
person I have so
many what did I tell you guys what did I
tell you
oopsie but he yeah that's the thing he
already has I wanted a new Bootsy and a
new helmet life jacket I already have I
should have just not bought a jacket for
the others
oh well I'll give it to
him greatly reduces chance of receiving
damaging status ailment
amazing what did I tell you what did I
tell you what was likely going to happen
and I'm going to get these items in the
dungeon but only one of each
[Music]
yeah I have so many
keys it's like my name is kiata or
something that would be so fitting
wouldn't
it I always miss it in the beginning I
always
forget oh nice oh Tommy finally able to
kill people after all
you coward never mind you're not a
coward for not being able to do that
you're actually
based dop blit super base is what you
are 7 [\h__\h] hundred oh my
God can I say one thing guys on Twitter
you may have seen me interact with a
company that makes Ramen and knif just
because I said 6 months minimum
production uh time doesn't mean that I
have a deal or any contact at all yet I
actually don't I just said that because
that's just how it works usually if if
we were to work on something it's going
to take time anyway um but yeah I I
would be delighted to do something they
were already following me so I was like
[Music]
H
yeah I'll do this one
I did not get him it looked like he was
in the
range the OKO dude he certainly was in
the
range they seem super legit and well
regarded yeah the knife they made for
girl DM just looks so good so sexy and I
always wanted like knives and stuff but
that I don't think we can do it as merch
in like our usual merch plan so I'd have
to do a tie up like that you know so I
was like oh my God wink wink i' totally
love to I got something in my eye wait
wa I totally love to do something
[Music]
to and then they immediately were like
let [\h__\h] go DM me now I can't just DM
them like that and be like okay no uh
has to go for
our our management properly so I told
Gemma I was like I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry but this would be so
cool can we look into this no promises
guys there's you know these kind of
things they're always
um more
complicated it
might so
if you don't I'll make it myself no no
no no no no no no no don't worry I I
have I High Hopes I I swear I had no
contact
whatsoever and I I don't have any reason
to have high hopes I just uh I don't
know I think it could work out I don't
know I don't know I really don't know I
don't
know no
promises yeah we could have it look like
the popsicle knife or not or we can
maybe have several things you
know and maybe while we're at it we'll
make a k Ramen as well cuz that seems to
be their main thing it kind of almost
feel bad like that I jump on the the
knives rather than the ramen which is
their main thing but I mean the knife
just look so cool and I need I'm I'm I'm
a chef I'm a chef
you
know yo can they make my cutting board
dreams come true maybe
yeah that would be so cool cutting board
shield and kada popsicle knife oh [\h__\h]
can we put LEDs into the
knife the front part that's
um but still LEDs but also Damascus
steel of course how do you do that I
don't know we'll make it work
no RGB
knife oh
wow you're so lame for hiding behind a
screen just like
me c me
eye how about that
[\h__\h] is he still calling him
a I'll bury you what are we going to
fight the screen that would be so funny
no we're not
okay G
oh let's
go
oh oh [\h__\h]
oh
what let's
go
OMG min max oh perfect min max found
it good though very
good oh
calm the down it's so
sick clap clap clap clap clap oh sh
[Music]
me meow
meow they're all too far apart I hate
this H this
work
[\h__\h] can't see
[\h__\h] if I were the kind of person who
goes into
clubs I I I I would love to hear this in
the club [\h__\h] but I'm not the kind of
person but I
appreciate the sickness of
this anybody who doesn't like thunder
you I'm to hurt on you more distance
more damage can I go behind
you I hate myself
oh nice thank you my eyes my eyes
M oh W saw that one
coming out I didn't see that one coming
oh it came from
behind you think I'm stupid I can't see
[\h__\h] oh my god oh
he's just in a screen y guys are
motivated by being on the screen you
guys should be pissed off because of
that you should come here and not
hide
behind what a
[Music]
coward wish I could got all free of ah
maybe I can little bit of
[Music]
pushing yeah no
no now I can't push him anymore oh
wait yo move move back oh he
[Music]
I'm getting motivated by a certain
person on my screen right
now okay yeah I
guess I guess that is what the effect
that I have on you guys
partially oh
[\h__\h] this goes so hard oh my God
kak I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready I'm
ready I was so ready for
that I was so ready for
that
baby thanks for the membership
gift m H you're awake to
fire fire breaking
maybe oh he's the
boss woohoo well not so
much there's a cowbell on the song hurry
up let's go
that one you think that's a cowbell I
guess it could be
you let's
go that skill is honestly kind of
difficult to get the prompt right
because
the special effects
are misleading my brain
we break his
grapple if it kills it will raise my
agility doesn't that
sound
kill nah that is so scam
me oh that should have totally yeah
there's so much blue on the screen yeah
that's what I'm talking
about time with the sound effects on the
F hey
oh well I mean I still got it ride
but
wow okay calm
[Music]
down oh my God this is such a [\h__\h]
oh not going to help you now
[Music]
well only two left
yeah I feel like at that
moment when it's like the the weird
voice that says something it should be h
f stars
like
stars hold on live
stars hold
on sorry it's so loud
from Blue
Clapper we are wait we have no agility
right now
[Applause]
[Music]
A
H all right got to build it up but by
that time it might be too
late that's okay
[Music]
H that reminds me I
should team I left them on the
[Music]
red why did I leave them on
oh ich couldn't wait
anymore
impatient what
now
mhm oh all right you got gas Mas then we
got to be fast in this
battle oh no
are was going destroy
them I they
are
Target thank you for the membership gift
do
your how strong are the units maybe they
can go down with one hit but they're
also level 47 but maybe they still have
really low
HP do they have a
weakness not that I can tell okay let's
try a they are not that easy to
kill to take
down I should have done it
a here I can reach quite a few with this
fight smoke can't see
[\h__\h] why not why not I blinded two of
them sorry I'm late I love you welcome
no
problem level 37 generator how many
people did it kill for that yeah I must
have gotten that exp from somewhere
oh did that voice just say
Barracuda I didn't properly hear it
until
now go oh kind of want an AOE don't
[Music]
we you're weak to it you're also weak to
it
okay
[Music]
let's yes I still got it it was gy gdy
last moment
well you just realize on that loud cuz I
still want to hear my own voice louder
otherwise it's really confusing in my
brain what if I kill all the enemies
first uh before the poison gas
generators does the battle end
uh Godlike armor
hello but the poison could be the end of
him so let's let's heal him right
now uh how much uh HP does he have at
this moment let's give him maybe this
one you good
bro you
good
okay Mom Mia that's why we need to uh
have him wear that armor with one HP
reev uh
survival what was that line in that one
song that has survive Sur surv tell them
we're survivors I love that line let's
go that one's fun
grapple but the poison we need AOE
oh
nice yeah one more chance in life
ability AR
paruda this
there maybe the stronger one that even
is
aen but
yeah okay okay okay okay
okay ah the Regent counter pois D would
have been what a smart person would
do I wish I was smar baby smarter
smarter baby
[Music]
smarter
baby
[Music]
baby I just want to kill the stupid
generator
okay of course you want to see me dance
at
Julia everybody who knows that dance
wants people to dance
it even girls with no ass can look like
they have an ass so imagine this
girl okay so yeah my model maybe doesn't
have the best ass so maybe it will do me
Justice shotgun dude May kill wait no
please don't please don't will
he he'll be fine right
um what what what are you going to do
sleep grade this is
it he
missed what song are we talking about
is it smart or smarter smart I think
smart is a relatively new song from Luc
serim Julia write the name down for our
cultured
friend what am I doing I should who am I
other next is her
[Music]
let's go come at me
already let's
go
you be right
back maybe just go straight to the dance
version they usually have dance
versions or a live performance of it or
so although even in the MV they are
definitely showing off that dance
move can I one shot the machine with
this what do you think probably not
doesn't even have a
weakness press four I don't know where
it will lead you but I don't think you
need to press four there's there's a lot
of ass in that
MB just accentuating the
CH one
is I have a girl crush on CH one so bad
she's so cute it's so pretty and she
slays like every [\h__\h] concept they
do [\h__\h] I don't know what to do I could
heal everybody or I could wait for Cheto
to heal everybody and I could do damage
with him now but like on whom can't
decide k
come
[Music]
me I do want to get this [\h__\h]
down almost seems like a
waste let's get these
two maybe I don't know focus on the
machine [\h__\h] I was considering it oh but
he that wasn't bad that was good
damage all right and now we
heal oh but that I have enough for the
coconut shower thank God it's so so low
low low low
low hi
guys hey
guys hey guys hey guys hey guys hey
guys hey no how to
cor okay you piece of [\h__\h] I'm going to
break you with fire breaking me no that
sounds so
fitting can I get HP out of the poison
gas
generat let me
try machine heal give
power yep yep okay it works I stole the
unit two Soul it has no
soul they did not think about that one
did they
come at me
already a robot of a soul that is very
concerning that is very
concerning keep finding out on this
skitt [\h__\h] I really need uh some
freaking or we Tango a little bit into
the direction of move back back towards
other to you little [\h__\h] right
now right now I say yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah wait we miss the [\h__\h]
machine it didn't look like that
before what the
[\h__\h]
uhoh okay nice I oh I block it twice
she's on 23
woohoo
um all right
uh 300 100 might
be it's going to be okay although he
still has a lot of HP but we're just
starting to focus on him now what even
is his weakness I don't remember fire
no knife yes knife okay perfect then
give
me I want I want
your come at me
already should we steal it
again it's not his turn next so it could
uh we could also leave it to H to
destroy the machine I think ichun does
not have an effective attack
anyway I missed but yeah maybe that's
better just to be safe I'm going to use
an attack cuz I'm I'm scared that it
won't be enough
okay we're free finally from the
poison it didn't show water as a
weakness but it totally should have been
yeah okay uh nice agility oh I have
three I can do Shadow clone just okay I
remember it's a slow coming one slow
slow cooking slow cooking
how much
damage
[Music]
1,200
oh yes I think I got
it push harder
come on who's number one me
[Music]
me
mhm oh yeah we're wrestling we're
totally
wrestling
suplex saturation bombing oh no oh no oh
no oh [\h__\h] dangerous
[\h__\h]
dangerous [\h__\h]
dangerous just [\h__\h]
[Music]
dangerous still not that much HP and
honestly he needs more this and there
actually yeah he really does should have
just healed him with an item I
guess wait he has the Bret too though we
can do
the and heal oh so many people
actually that looks better we're looking
better we have no mp on him but we can
tack him let's do that
okay they're so cute together love
them yeah I got it under
control this fight is so long isn't that
it's
learn
bar
Barracuda I know this one
I'm so
useless I could do another Shadow clone
Jutsu even though I have only two
agility might still be worth
it need to learn the way of the
sword I only know the way of the
popsicle Roo splitter is pretty good but
it's not going to kill him but it might
still be okay uh that's just
five five uh MP
difference it's slitter I guess by the
way let's save some
MP okay okay 600
okay
stop shut
up he missed
againa you think I'll level up that
would be nice I think can we finish it
can we finish it with other two
together
power he's a he's a he's a
beblade did we just use Adai as the
Beyblade oh we didn't finish it but it's
okay I'm going to finish
it
easy oh yeah he Sanic
who
Okay
ni nice nice
nice
fore spee
[Music]
[Applause]
I reminds me cuz he's in a suit uh it
looks good in a suit my
brother whoa my brother my
unan okay he sent us in our family group
chat a picture of him in a nice
fancy uh like blue grayish suit
and I was
like whoa Myan looks so cool in a suit
he suddenly looked yeah so Dapper and
like so stylish and I was like
[Music]
who suddenly looks like way more mature
the suit really changes everything he
also had proper shoes on and all that
but yo I didn't know my bro could look
so
Co I'm so proud of him like I was like
damn my bro my
[Music]
Onan
yeah what you wear really changes can
change your appearance appearance so so
greatly it's actually
insane does he usually not have proper
shoes well no yeah he has fine shoes but
the combination of good somewhat pointy
shoes with a nice suit that's not even
just like I like basic black suits too
you know they can look good too but he
was wearing like some non- black suit
that that added to it I think he also
looked so I don't
know
mature I was just amazed because I don't
ever see my my brother like this like wa
oh my brother can look like this I'm so
proud of
him I'd rock my Converse in the honestly
I dig that too that that's cool you can
make it look cool I'm sure we got to get
you and suit me Po talk hosting suit
little baby bro is growing up yeah he's
not my younger bro though he's my older
brother by a year but I feel I was shook
seeing my sister and the wedding stuff
right probably that that must have a a
similar
effect yeah yeah yeah yeah clothing
seeing your family and like clothing
that makes them like glow the [\h__\h]
up
waa crazy as a Grims man at a wedding
and we rocked converse with a s that's
cute that's
cute a
[Music]
so
fore
foree a man for
real
for for
Fore yes please more
[Music]
mm we could have lost her
already so yeah you better use your
chances
[Music]
foreign
spee speech
[Music]
foree speee
speee speee
[Music]
fore
fore yeah so
foreign
foree
foreign fore
[Music]
fore foree
he's so
positive
[Music]
damn
for I knew he was going to say that
[Music]
please call her
mom fore
[Music]
that hits hard for her
oh she going to break
[Music]
down oh [\h__\h]
oh
R my original
song oh
[\h__\h] no stream wasn't lagging don't say
that maybe for you oh man yeah you have
to hug her oh my God he's such a
positive happy doggle type of person
oh I'm wiping my
tears but
he's
H and then the one I find [\h__\h] up
though no not [\h__\h] up but like come on
ichan you're calling that [\h__\h]
psychopath
[\h__\h] son of a [\h__\h] a Chan still but
you're calling your mom a still
I mean he I guess he was still like just
as he said just now he's still not sure
if she birthed him but I mean I think
we're pretty certain about that if she
says so too then call her okasan at
least I
mean like a lot of people in Japan call
their mom okasan or okasama or so like
not even okan or OK or mama or so but
least
okasan just switch out the A on it I
know yeah
like she's more the woman the boss of
yeah but like you're making this
connection here and like I I feel like
ichan should be so hyped that he now has
a mother in his
life it I feel
like I get what he's saying when you
don't know actually you know what never
mind I mean it's hard it's hard I can
actually relate to this like
meeting a
parent like for the first time in many
many years but for him is like even even
even even even
longer so of course you feel like this
kind of Disconnect right and you don't
know like you don't feel like calling
them like Mommy in that moment but he
does seem to immediately like connect
with her like now they had a really
wholesome moment so maybe maybe at least
after that like after this wholesome
moment maybe he could like I don't know
does he not want
to have her in his life I wonder from
now on is that what he's thinking about
at all because I'm sure he would love to
have family in his life
again I would think
so like why not why would you not want
that like he loves his mommy for sure
right I think he already loves
her he just ich he's such a dogle he
mainly trusts everybody even if it's
[\h__\h] strangers so if then there's
your mommy who's really nice to you even
more so you should trust her and like I
feel like they're already connecting so
I don't know I feel like uh he's going
to get there hopefully I would hope so
but then again it's dumb H he's just he
he seems like he's stuck on being extra
respectful and keeping the distance from
her but he seems the kind of person
who's craving who would be craving to
take a um to to have to build this kind
of relationship now that he finally
can you know what I mean even yeah even
if there's so much time in between if
anyone ich seems like the person to
Crave that and want that and then work
on that and so please each F
please
please yeah I know I get it I get it's
weird and all that but like they already
like you know
vibing as a family in my opinion that's
how it feels to me as a
Observer M M
M yeah he even exactly he even proposes
to his crush on the first dat
give it time they just met like two days
ago for me it feels like 5 years ago no
but like is it just two days in game
it's a bit more no I don't
know we've been chasing her for a bit
more than two
[Music]
days how
we're back in
Tokyo let's
go yes it is the first moment where they
got to talk to solo that was important
that was something also that I've been
hoping for it to happen ASAP cuz the
talk in the taxi was kind of like that's
it we need more like they're finally
reunited we need something more
here best chapped in the game this
coming
one this upcoming
[Music]
one yeah yamay was also listening while
they were in the taxi
yeah and the taxi driver
this one is Kino Kino
[Music]
Cinema We're All in This
Together mhm which means we're just
switching
equipment huh preparations huh it's a
long trip so it's probably a good idea
to St up right plus this is the toal
clan royalty we're dealing with you
never know what will happen come on
don't make it sound so
OMS he right there's no guarantee to S
of words we should be ready for anything
all right we have time to stuck up and
maybe even get some training
in well he think she was fine but K
might be the best nothing you can't find
there plus it's basically K son's
Hometown walking those streets again
might be good for
him although I guess we run the risk of
him being
recognized maybe but it probably is the
best place for us to prepare we'll just
have to be cautious if we keep our heads
down it should be all
right that settles it then what say we
grab a taxi um not a uh that means
probably I need to drag you guys through
a dungeon uh I did the other one off
screen I wish I could do this one off
screen
too but it seems like we're not getting
around
it need a sword for
him but okay are we going to upgrade
stuff for them now or are we good with
this for now
Highway there's a good chance to show
off your
strength the dungeons are a great place
to listen to the in-game
podcast I just the other day off screen
I was when I was doing the dungeon
that's the first time I realized I can
switch to the like Kadoka
songs I didn't know that was podcast to
to switch
too hero battles those work too now I
did that last time I think we can go to
the
dungeon then we can get probably some
extra items as
well um anyway what am I doing
uh oh look at that strong equipment
[Music]
I could repeat that forever it
seems we are living the Yellow Submarine
ah they at least already have five star
weapons those two and then I was like
what I do for the other
[Music]
ones maybe I should give the this jacket
to K
just so he doesn't
die K's fists are 10 St
weapons yeah but right now we got to use
a
sword
[Music]
um I always have to think like are you
in my team right now or are you in the
other team can I take this from you or
can I not think think think think
think equipment
wise we're good except for some weapons
maybe I just constantly have to switch
things in and
out
yeah uh now him I don't think I'll be
using him so he's
good m the reserve some lowest star
stuff I mean I guess
so no want not you're right you're
right survival boots
yay I don't know um have this oh that's
yeah that's perfect for you
actually I lasted end game with just
five star weapons worked for me oh okay
can't believe n about disrespect That's
my
boy I love him I love him actually but
yeah when they give you so much choice
so we need a professional better whisk a
better
whisk for our cook and perhaps another
new
sword uh do I craft the sword or do I
buy it I gu I have to buy the
base it's all about that base base thank
you for the membership gifts uh hello
work no uh here I can walk there if I
don't get
lost all I'm just going to to check if I
were to craft something
something what I would need also I just
realized this side of the team already
was in level 36
47 that's good but I wonder what they
what level they want me to be for the
coming
part even
higher or do I need to go to dungeon you
can check what you need on your phone ah
oh well
so uh
what five star I need a secret long
sword lava geod I have
enough
mhm secret long sword or should I just
make this one I don't know if I can six
star
I don't know if I
can that's Z's Katana hold up dancing
Gods Katana is
it protection of a war
god uh ah
Chef my
grader food grader so what was the other
one we need a food grader
[Music]
a
seashells wait then I can make this one
right cuz this one doesn't need the
seash
shells I should have gotten them while I
was in
Hawaii but I forgot about it I already
like last time I checked I was like oh
seashells okay
seash shells let's make this one
stainless Li doll lid doll and uh a few
more ice GEOS five exactly stainless
Ladle and secret long sword and Ice
secret long sword write down
please stainless
lightle uh some L long sword or where do
I buy it
like for
example wait like this
no dancing stable
no
no I mean they might have more stuff
right uh action star some this story
might have it it's just not listed I
guess
yeah
K I don't know how to say the X actually
okay we go
here
uh where am
I
[Music]
far [\h__\h]
where
[Music]
we yeah
picked it from the oh
my oh my
God can't believe he did
that that is
Savage uh is that the
store you guys are kind of in the
way they're kind of dangerous ooh
o I remember those from the dungeon I
think I saw them before
[Music]
ow don't hold back it's
hard oh okay I need to think reink my
whole system cuz this is different we're
we're dealing with different people now
uh a
[Music]
M Small smaller smaller small
smaller line okay
maybe
[Music]
maybe that's probably not even going to
get the one behind
him SM
[Music]
SM I
love we can do the gas grenade going to
get two
people the chance of poisoning them I
don't know if it's worth
it that's okay
damage like to pick some little
nightmares
a a little
bit
yeah and there's a little bit of a level
Gap
[Music]
maybe let's debuff
them en lo their
attack area let's give him a
coal
two all right let's buy these
too shake shake shake oh I have to press
nothing like the Buffs and debuffs
usually they don't need you to press
anything they're weak to electricity woo
do I have anybody who uses
electricity I should do damage yeah I'm
kind of lost like I'm like what I do
this team uh oh they're weak to knife
okay that's good um High chance of
making them bleed and then I have a a
followup that is stronger when they're
bleeding right
yeah uh yeah this one the wound opener
so s slides and then we follow up
afterwards I think that
was one good
St but he's going to die anyway oh nice
follow up and his
b the the wound opener what do you mean
oh yeah right okay he's not confusing to
me cuz he has the same attacks as what I
was just dealing with a moment ago
anybody anybody
no okay knife weakness is Tas I'll go
for him what is this one
uh or can I go like in a line do
something useful here no they staged so
stupidly oh
[Music]
whatever
here they so spread
out of course I'm saying wound open her
but I okay with the names of the attacks
and all that in this game I guess
they're
a a a w
opener maybe that's realistic why does
he always bu the same dude we have to
kill him
quickly
uhoh oh that wasn't that
bad I only said that made to say
it thank you for the membership for you
[Music]
wait I made them weak to electricity
uh which
one oh this
one
okay
M yeah thank you kid you oh that was
otherwise really
unsatisfying that was the strongest
buffed one so got to get rid of him
um I should probably
heal s needs it the most where is he ah
look like them cuz you also got a yellow
like okay just because it's the same
color of yellow okay I think this
works please reach reach yes it
is
it no no back
up
a oh
no oh no
no I was just trying to get in there to
buy
[Music]
some oh man greatly if they're bleeding
we have a bleeding boy but it's not even
necessary maybe we can
do this one like goes from one to
another to another right we can do this
one
okay okay I got two I got
two say I'm not tou which one they all
look the same is it is the red one the
the boss right that's
I guess we get more uh XP that's right
true got to see it in a positive
[Music]
way Warhead as a
weakness to electricity so I could kill
him take him down
but enemy is next I hope K is
[Music]
okay uhoh get out of the
way oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah we we needed the
most good
you please wake up yeah wake the [\h__\h]
up now is not the time to have a nap in
the middle of the
street it's actually never the time to
have a nap in the middle of the
street where cars are passing and where
people are fighting what do you mean
you're still
stunned get a hold of yourself
no should I focus on the boss now
[Music]
uh is the boss the boss is
bleeding so it will uh damage him
greatly that is exactly what I
want only
397 what ah he was guarding I didn't see
it I'm blind this oh oh no oh
no I didn't see that's
why ah you didn't
e better than
[Music]
nothing what what what can we do the
grapple let's use the grapple on the
boss okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
G oh yeah good good
[Music]
reach they always do the same attacks
man a just stop cheering and cheering
and
cheering you shouldn't be in that outfit
you should be in a cheerleader costume
that's all you can do with show me that
you're the boss show it to
me uh is he ah he's not bleeding
anymore ooh actually they stand pretty
nicely for this one right
now yeah I fre
people
woohoo 350 plus damage from Free People
what a
deal what a deal
[Music]
[Applause]
this may inflict
pleased I think I may inflict some but
no I need to take down the
dle H but oh this is good this can get
three of
them but now maybe like this this is
better with the
boss but I did get four I got four
[Music]
woohoo
yay no my summons are [\h__\h] because I
didn't get
any
yeah oh there's a another one with a
grapple
request all righty I'll give it to
you I'm giving you exactly what you want
I know I know I know
Oh you mean the T team the TX team I can
do should I do a z z is the only one who
can't do it yet a we need to become
besties I got to look out for some Z
conversations I need I want to be
besties with
him
ow oh he's got just resarch I didn't
look at that thank
you I
[Music]
[Applause]
forgot
[Music]
say
more oh well still only four I guess
I'll even
more what the [\h__\h]
man this is so
stupid
[Music]
um remember to go to D for new summons D
gives me new
summons he
[Music]
does what am I going to do uh wait is
anyone bleeding
no uh
can we do this again no not
[Music]
really my game
lags the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
wait should I do a big tack team or solo
tag
teams not just the game uh I don't know
if it's the same today but apparently in
my Koke yesterday uh the the chat was
making people's streams lag not you I
mean yeah that is YouTube but I guess
you wouldn't even think about
that um so I don't know maybe now it's
the
same I don't know what is this what am I
using oh that was the tack team should I
use it was super laggy what the
[\h__\h] I want to take down these
T I'm just going to do
it TOS
in huh
huh take
the [\h__\h] did you see that it was
supposed to hit all three of
them
[Music]
what yeah I'll break you stupid ugly ass
mask and then I'll break your face and
you'll need a new mask because you
broken face will look even
uglier foul at
400 let's go that was
good I'm leaving the play
[Applause]
area we're leaving Japan with this
one ow
I need MP for like
[Music]
everybody I need more
cheese I need more of these These are
good
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] thank you camera for not
supporting me
here if it's
spicy is he bleeding he's still not
bleeding that
bastard
well medium medium light well I guess if
it's if they're both medium then I can
just continue you're using this
one green tea or black tea I prefer
green
tea okay bleeding
Woo which is not only good for uh D but
uh was also good I think for
K I was about to sayi but no k
[Music]
can I KO him with this I hope so cuz
then it would boost my
attack I like te like yeah generally my
favorite are like fruties sweet peas
sure she did the unhealthy ones um but
if we're talking like real like hot tea
not the cold
ones then uh well still I like fruit
teas in that case too and green teas and
sometimes a nice uh herbal tea like
chamomile or a mix of them or so you
know good stuff good stuff are you still
bleeding yeah okay
[Music]
okay almost
900 cold bottle green tea so refreshing
yeah when I'm in Japan I like to uh
drink the cold green teas as well oh my
God he never stops okay I'm taking you
down I am 100% focusing on you you
little piece of
[\h__\h] but first let me sing a
song uh
[Music]
stop walking stop walking although he
has full
[Music]
HP I would have liked to
heal uh the other ladyes
son a little
bit Yeah green tea is good hot or cold
all tees are kind of good both ways
but fruit
tea
like when I just make fru tea from a
bag and then cool it down that's not
enough it's
just you need to have all the sugary
stuff in
it otherwise it's just like M and I'd
rather drink it hot it's better when
it's hot if you're not going to add all
the factory [\h__\h] to
it what was I going to
do I have no
idea but my strongest attack is either
this or that
[Music]
but
let's try no well I don't think I can KO
him but just in case
why is this why why the [\h__\h] is he so
strong why
happening finally no more backup
now do I really need to go to the
dungeon if this is what I'm dealing with
right how many enemies am I fighting
here in total
is this grapple no grapple grapple
grapple grapple grapple grapple gra
grapple
[Music]
grapple power heavy power
heavy but
not oh
[Music]
well I didn't see that one coming
can't wait to play this game oh you're
planning to do so did you play the
previous like of dragon as
[Music]
well going to have
fun that's how I think people when I
realize my people are lost like me so I
might as well laugh on the way
out what what are you talking about I
don't even
remember h
[Music]
where is that one we need a heal over
here my Bros
no I still have to play yaka 2 to7
before I can play this
game okay but you're already spoiling
yourself about everything
here but okay you want to play it in
order that makes sense you just already
are completely spoiled for this but I I
appreciate you being here
[Music]
oh thanks wow 281 as a
followup now you can call for backup too
oh this
nevering I'm going to throw up
you're pissing me
off what did I choose a skill by
accident
oh oh no that really wasn't my intention
I was going I was going to go back on
the manual
no I was just going to do a normal hit I
accidentally chose a a weak
[Music]
attack yeah I guess she it's like a
dungeon die please
m m
[Music]
Mia I'm even going to attack with her
now cuz I'm like so pissed
off or maybe
normal help
me backlog has been killing
me game backlog H what about uh ba like
I guess because she was playing like vcr
and stuff is she in the middle of a
uh of a Yakuza game right now or did she
just finish
one [\h__\h] I missed but it was still
strong she's just finished me she wanted
to play like all of them
no I guess she's too busy to play
another one now right now
[Music]
there should be a Max to how many
backups they can
call it's going too
far she's planning on starting K soon
wow wow wow wow wow wow wow it's so
funny like the moment she plays a little
bit of yaka she's like oh my God like
opening another whole world for her and
she's like I got to play them all now
but it took her so long to get into it
it's going to take a long time if he
wants to play all of them on stream from
now
on en enemies enemies okay careful for
real that is absolutely
perfect you recreated that
perfectly the rabbit hole is real
[Applause]
[Music]
how we strong with
this 200 400 okay with some help and
another one
nice don't you dare don't you dare call
anyone she wants to beat them all on
stream this
year
um
all all of them in this
[Music]
year all of
them I don't know how realistic that
is I mean that it would have to be
everything she plays like like look at
me these games are
long long as
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah seven and eight alone would be
half the year I don't think but but nice
nice
[Music]
dedication is
that is I don't know if that 53,000 is a
lot
or well yeah um I'm happy to see other
people play Yakuza I'm not going to go
as hard as her and play all of them I
don't feel like doing
that oh
but if you guys want to see more and
more and more Yakuza you can go watch
Bales the whole
year should have known Chinatown would
be a good place to find
souvenirs oh
cute is this Uno merchandise who knew he
would end up in a place like this with
his head cut
off the first time I put on that suit
and he put He you wore this before
that's him
I never thought he'd end up a nationwide
phenomenon guess it's due to all the
love that was put into him by his
creator hironaka and the people of Ono
let see all that hard work pay off
interesting
interesting yeah he I mean in all those
games surely he must have done a lot of
stuff which one were we going to get the
secret long sword I think
right 3 million yeah
okay I could also afford this
one but yeah let's get
it and
then
uh what's the other thing some cooking
utensil uh that took us so
long just because because they were
camping right in front of it oh my
God uh weapons just let me
check where could it
[Music]
be
no
no Aqua not ah this one host and Chef
yun's Foods
are there going to be people camping
here too you're doubting we can finish
this chapter in this room come on be
positive oh it's out in the open there's
no
campers uh stainless little I
remember I remember
nice that's already quite a good
Improvement the com headquarters are
just up
ahead my history of Kil goes way back to
my connection with the parent
organization the jingwan mafia and now
son is not only leading them but after d
seated power to her she's also in
charged to
liong powerful lady it would be no
exaggeration to say that son has the
entire Yokohama underground under her
Thum and that's kind of sexy isn't it
she must be under a lot of pressure
still what an impressive feet even
though it's only been a short while
since we met I'm in love with her I can
now she was born to be a leader she has
the potential for it seeing the next
generation carry us into the future
fills me with hope I sounded like a Jer
just
now big fire some ganging mmm
uh saw this in there I was going to
go wait let me get this
thing this
memory Thanks for the Memories even
though they weren't so
great
[Music]
t one night yeah one more
time why they oh I was like why they so
expensive no we're back to
Yen uh
conversion
Pepsi
okay hey Mountain
de right I wanted to get like bom stuff
with
fore
[Music]
there so this area is Korea Town
now reminds me of my history of the
jinguan
mafia our few dates as far back as kazas
son's
time we I was thinking e we've had a
number of conflicts with them in the
past it was kill or be killed but I here
I am now fighting alongside a remnant of
the jinguan
J
alongside not really we left him behind
hey if you told me this years ago I'd
never believe it guess you never know
what life's got in store the future's
always
unpredictable
gu the J One
Mafia
no yeah go organized some kind of event
in Minecraft that they uh announced
today as you may have seen no Wawa is
not
participating I did
not decide to participate this
time I think I'm I'm either not
available at the time or I just thought
nah for whatever
reason yeah yeah yeah but that's why Hol
talk can't work next
week because of that event also being
that
weak yeah I don't know if
is
also in that
[Music]
event oh there we go
nice yeah um so next week is because of
the event that it's not going to work
out and then the week after
that uh yeah I the week after
that wait a second next week is yeah the
week after that I am not around so that
doesn't work either but Hol talk is
going to
happen for sure for sure the week after
that so for fifth that week
finally oh I should go here and is this
this is
[Music]
sunny yeah we have set the
date so it's pretty
much certain
how important is it that H talk needs to
be in order well at least uh I would
like to finish that generation first
though
fourth fourth generation yeah before I
jump to fifth
generation he wants to meet an alien
mhm
okay
[Music]
and oh there's a social towel let's go
let's go let's go let's
go you plan on doing well eventually
yeah oh all of
them got to do them all got to catch
them all although like I would also not
immediately go
[Music]
to cuz I feel like I think after fourth
gen I might try to do members or ID
Members First
because although yeah fif gen fifth gen
and myth are pretty much sameish so if
we go by like time then it would have to
be first gen of ID
first right
I think I might do that oh my God Pony
pony
[Music]
grapple so I I don't know if I'm going
to do
it that that brings up the question
should I do it in English and then
translate to Japanese or should I just
do English only or
[Music]
H but the one thing I can do with myth
and ID is I can do it in VR chat in
free that'll be
fun cuz they all have
V
yay I'm excited for that
I can finally use the VR version of hog
again that I had commissioned for my
[Music]
episode oh there's one back there
too oh no the suicide s by
Kik speak ID we all will be
confused yeah of course I mean we're
going to speak not ID because I cannot
speak
IDE you have time to learn skilly shoes
X excuse
me
chicken okay then you learn too you do
it in
Japanese oh my God that would be so
funny if I do Ana in the classic like I
do all of ID and myth in English but
then Ana in Japanese translated her to
English but it won't happen it's just a
imagination because I hate Anya I will
never do a one-on-one collab with her of
course
not just kidding I love
her I love
her totally
totes
totly I got to go
there just getting that Bond going if
you let me into your party
I'll fin your income
taxes fight fight
what what did you just
say Ana replacing my popsicle sword
interesting really
fore okay
yeah we we struck a nerve she reacted
very sensitively about the age
thing game
center and then I don't want to fight
that dude
so close to a
bingo okay we can go uh oh from here to
here
yeah then we can wait let me get the
memory though then we can continue with
the story and get another towel
conversation on the
way looks like an old fashion arcade
guess it's what the kids would call
retro yeah it's it's
uh that pyura as you know for sure is
very
retro oh
no I used to frequent arcades like this
back in the day had lots of fun playing
games
there the fs behind all these games must
be incredibly creative and unique come
to think of it most of what I played
were from a company called
Sega they always seem to innovate with
every new game they put out
[Music]
[Applause]
wait no
makes me wonder what other kinds of
games are out there waiting to be played
if I could live forever i' play them
all
[Music]
Okay
no Okay I think they're low
level thir
one damn
[Music]
it this should be a breeze w
a he's weak to fire but that attack is
so weak let me see if I can do at least
an
AE uh oh that
area very
[Music]
interesting
grapple oh there's more oh [\h__\h] oh oh W
strong
okay
[Music]
interesting I don't because I don't
think I or did I I might have used a
attack before but
I really only used it once or
twice two weeks
ago maybe
[Music]
[Applause]
not bad for
we
rude pay back you bastard with the
pepper mil blow okay what was it
triangle and then square square
square
662 but he's a bit uh Stronger should I
use the dragon
thingy yeah for
[Music]
fun I can't see
W more
[Music]
more
2,000 oh my hard work
[Music]
man don't
on oh he's way too
funer now I know you're
[Music]
[Applause]
weak what
you can do
that what was he in a counter
stance what the [\h__\h] is that
[Music]
emote the [\h__\h] is that
emote oh is it because she was drunk or
he was drunk the [\h__\h] is that emot why
is that a
thing who is that I don't see that in
the YouTube
OTE where did you get that
from that's like a twitch emote there's
some secret
emotes what is
that BTV what the [\h__\h] is
BTV that some famous uh big subscriber
YouTube channel looks like
IR yeah I mean the cap yeah
secret what are these secret
emotes emot expansion DLC Jake Peter is
the name of
it who is
that CH ad oh who is Jo who is Jake
Peter some like like like you famous
YouTuber oh yeah he's drunk so he's like
fighting back wait being drunk has that
positive
effect now he's not drunk anymore or was
that even being
drunk I don't know but he stole the's
head we must retrieve it and give it
back that is rude you cannot just take
too
much she only has one I have two so I
can I can get rid of one you know
especially the
one it's from the Adam this just
the like those are hidden I love them
they're so
cute 1 million
from okay okay okay calm down calm
down we got a go hard on the story
now wow wow wow wow already B level
23 let's go
he using a
dream I know I don't know about that
time machines you know I like the do
post about the future and Ai and all
that but I don't know I don't think time
machines
will really exist in a in a way that
is we
because that's like magic I know
like we I I think I saw a video on
something that's like hinting at time
traveling but it's not like significant
like impossible in a significant way I
think I don't think so I don't know I
don't know I'm not a scientist I guess
yeah anyway I guess we're taking a taxi
are we good to
go wait I want to still uh I want to
still like um craft I didn't get the ice
geot I might need some right where can I
get them here
um it would be at the dungeon was there
a dungeon on this map where I can go do
I even have what I need no can we visit
that at his bar first
his
bar uh you mean in the in the in
here wait no this is not the
one I survive
[Music]
uh God the maps
are yeah
okay M it's out talk
mhm
uh oh
wait I have to
do a little
detour I spy with my little
eye that's not even what I attended
foree
fore h
fore
foree
foreign
[Music]
fore
foree spee
tech oh can we get akiyama as a summon
fore
[Music]
foree
for
for changing
topics that one's
TI and now kiss
[Music]
come on K you
think
for charlot
try
[Music]
right foree
that
[Music]
ISE not potato chips by the way it's the
the peanut
fluffy M
flips
again the one I ate
before
peanut if I have this around maybe Anya
will Ana we'll show up
baby got to be careful don't want her to
show up
here wait wrong
Ona but maybe she likes peanuts
anyway do you guys want to hear the
whole conversation with
d we have one with him too oh my God
oh with all of them oh
my I'll I'll Zoom for a it
okay read
fast oh he's also
fanboying for
[Music]
I know that story
line looks like a
festival
[Music]
foree I
know uh
for
what
what I want to go
now he's
[Music]
F kind of rude kid you what the hell
what's wrong with you
what that's so
rude that's Prett
nice you you caught that right
right frying
Inferno finally we got another
one you
did oh now we're sitting
[Music]
here what is
it something's bugging
him his whole conversation is going to
be about
his
[Music]
restaurant that's not
really
me good for have rest I want him to do
well I agree but I also don't
understand it's surprising how how often
I can use that phrase I reuse
it that good old famous phrase
really like a nice quote like like
a like a freaking poet quote or ven VII
it's on the same level I would say as
ven VI vichi
well that's not
good wa is it
true probably for the other like was he
giving it out to homeless people
he
[Music]
drinks he covered for someone
else and then they accepted it and then
they fired him anyways two years later
[Music]
thanks for the membership game
that's so [\h__\h]
up
yeah we becoming
a yeah I think we're in resolve so we
should resolve
things oh are we in wait a second where
are we
uh are we in survive or in resolve or
revolve that's revolve not
resolve right oh damn
it I we're in survive so it doesn't work
out at all anyway damn
it she staring at the wine bottles or is
she staring into the air
not to the point to the where you would
embarrass yourself like
well like every single day is
weird I
know every day like
Overkill ity catching
St I
won never forget that
[Music]
mhm
yeah good for
you good for
you good
for
whatever I want to hear your love
stories
there's another one we're going to hear
even more about their love
stories what's the point of doing that
because they they going to help more out
in the
battles oh no Mar
[Music]
spe
first world
problem you have to marry Ichiban don't
even think of
it so
oh she's like one
young eating and drinking with
two tad bit
hostility no no no no no not at
all okay so I found it funny that she
was like asking him have you ever given
anyone anybody of flower bouquet and in
theory we I think I think we already
did now I have no bouquets on me but I
could have totally given them flower
bouquet oh wait oh my God you're over
here I didn't see
you my
girl what is
it
faster what is it about still fan girl
what are we
doing you don't even know who's calling
turn it
around no maybe they stop calling
because they're being held at gunpoint
right now and you know shit's going
no no no no pick the [\h__\h]
up pick it up pick it up
[Music]
well that's
n some Rebels is there some
[Music]
Rebellion as Nesta would
say it's call the night I need to
continue the main story
[Music]
H okay are we done here final oh does
she have another
one oh she's she's fine okay I think
everybody's fine
now uh
then wait I can sleep and charge my mp
right
oh we're also getting a call
[Music]
oh yes I guess we'll do that you guys
want me to do this kind of stuff
right that b stresses me out every time
in game you
mean it doesn't come that often come on
get
out okay uh he said
uh I should go here
right I'm on my
way I'm on the highway to sub
stories
[Music]
high save me
that
save ready to go let's
go um
[Music]
that's a cool name at
least te up on this one
[Music]
but you probably
know the back story right you played the
other games probably
huh
fore
[Music]
fore ow
I felt
that but my reactions are so
late the cowboy music
[Music]
[Applause]
what was this
again
for these guys are all around
damn fore
[Music]
somehow May because I'm playing it in a
game
seemed like a fantasy thing to
me just
surreal telling me this was a
thing
IM maybe still
nowwhere so weird
I mean gangs as well but gangs is more
realistic to me gangs are more realistic
to
[Music]
me I mean this is nothing else than a
gang I
guess it was a news article on some
no
he's right
there I guess you didn't see the video
the viral video yet
damn do me again wouldn't they recognize
him but I guess he's just going
to hi
MH M oh it's right
there where is Old
Arina
for he's back there
[Laughter]
foreign
speech yeah we saw
oh
you don't take my soundport away unless
you going to
um replace it with a better
[Music]
mixer damn he look so
different I mean the the
[Music]
others wait did they not see the video
that go supposedly
[Music]
viral I it's
about like she always
covers about Yakuza you would think
Yakuza would pay attention to it
and they would like even if they
personally don't watch YouTubers surely
you know the people around them would be
like did you hear from this video did
you hear that like they would talk about
it cuz K is
legendary yeah it would spread I think
they aren't no I guess
so I still think it would spread in this
area cuz he was famous in this area too
that's like his his hood the
for right
[Music]
fore
foree foree
[Music]
got their hopes up
no you can't take
[Music]
it I feel like
KYW a very recognizable cologne and they
could just smell him
he looks like I can smell
him why are we still hiding it
when there's
videos of us out there
and aren't we mostly hiding the fact
that he's dead just for the sake of
Yakuza not finding out about it a few
hosts and like normal people at this
point doesn't matter does it if vaku
already
know yeah I I I guess you could still
claim it's edited but wasn't it like
everybody believed it
[Music]
already for his family's
safety like I said in Canada probably
plays plays after the Koka party oh oh
like before the video even comes out I
was supposed to see this hm
okay okay that makes more
sense but they should consider that that
can happen that you watch it afterwards
[Music]
clandestin the [\h__\h] are these
words a there we go new pound mates to
pound they come together in a
team but then won't they see kid
you kazuk has been added as a guest of
Dondo island yya has been added as a
guest it's pretty good one M will it not
be as useless as the other ones I
have we ain't pounding the
homies why
not they are my pound mates don't they
deserve it a little bit of pounding you
know don't they deserve it
too why do you want to take that away
from
them kinky
Bridge let's go on to the kinky
bridge I guess we're not doing much main
story today it's okay I guess we'll do
whenever stream
next week on Saturday no
Friday
on next one I don't know man can I do
those off screen it's going to take so
much time to do them all on
[Music]
stream can say I have the greatest
memories of the highways no you don't oh
you should have gone on the highway with
me when I was trying to rescue hukai was
ambushed by the snake flower tried which
led to a car chase or looks like a truck
Chase to me once I was even attacked by
the jingan mafia and had to fight them
off on the cargo bed yeah I've had
nothing but dangerous experiences on the
highway
H My Stream yesterday must have been
very very
traumatic
damn life is a
Hardway if you're name is
k he's on the highway to hell yeah yeah
literally probably felt like hell to him
hi way to
Hell me
hi welcome
back it disappeared when you heard my
vocals hey there stranger me is this a
side quest y if you got some money on
you I run a couple games here but I came
for a memory are you some kind of card
shark just a humble gamer kooy and O
kabu as you please consider yourself
welcome you never know might walk away a
little
richer I don't know
man Dynamic
kugu t
going to get scammed oh wait a second I
feel like I'm having a d
Vu it's just down this ladder whenever
you in to move down this ladder if you
don't mind me asking why did you say I'm
welcome you're are you inviting anyone
who passes by actually I keep a very
tight list of clientele it's just you
remind me of a kid I once knew when I
was running games out
of the West Park in C
do I know this guy from the previous
game I imagine that sometimes that's all
it takes good luck to you
stranger kamaro is scam
City wait but yeah I came
for a memory there we
go yeah we oh K was in West Park a lot
uhuh
secret
[Music]
weapons did
we what's his what does he have in stock
also down
here what is it with this
ladder oh there we go we got a Side
Story Quest
thingy but I don't want to
gamble
who what
what oh oh oh wait it's a different oh
May it's different are you bringing me
with a boat to somewhere
else I guess I remember
him might want to
[Music]
save do I have to fight
him mhm have some respect
[Music]
a number didn't even matter
one strange as it sounds I feel like I
know him too
what what
could he be LA but that's impossible the
LA I remember was the head of the
snake where he was shot to death a long
time ago I saw it happened right in
front of
[Music]
me yeah well I guess he was a fake name
too
well but I also know a lot of Suzukis
that's why there's so
many because there is so
many wouldn't be surprised if we start
seeing
nishiku I doubt
that oh don't want to have to silence
him but worst case scenario you come
closer let me see your face wait why am
I reading them we're not thinking it
do we get straight into a
fight
no for real
though should have done that moment
ago
foree wow okay
[Music]
mean yourself or
him y have
[Music]
guess I can't just walk away fine by
me thank you
thank you
thank
y are we going to have a
problem no
[Music]
problem um maybe we can charm him I
don't
know I
miss nah he's he's weak no
problem no
[Music]
problem they probably giving them a cold
Mele charm or reduce their defense let's
try
[Music]
this damn it not even defense decrease
all right he
resists um nice
onal okay let's try the
pepp that's okay thank
[Music]
you your F was on a high level I would
have been in trouble but this is okay
what about guns okay you don't care oh
you don't have a resistance so that's
good wait
[Music]
uh I guess we can also do this
one
[Music]
sick W baby a triple
is this an OS
from the first Yakuza Yakuza
fre use the new palmate right away H
maybe it's not that necessary I
[Music]
think critical hit
please I what is wrong what is wrong
with me
now but it's still high damage
whoa dude calm
down is the one person heal
stronger I think it wasn't right not not
really oh no it's good it's good it's
[Music]
good let's do it again let's do it let's
do it let's do it do it let's do it
let's do it let's do it let's do it it
let's do it let's do it do it oh but it
costs money
guys a lot of
money you'll have a night of a lifetime
in the capable hands of stardust's
number one host as well as its owner
these club scene veterans will ravish
all enemies with a th000 base damage and
increase the party's magic doesn't cost
a turn
okay
yes all
righty th000 sounds good
actually you have like 38 million do you
understand we already had this
today waste money
everywhere you're going to unre yourself
[Applause]
[Music]
oh wow this
experience oh my God
stop Mak me unable
[Music]
alluring
[Applause]
to oh no I don't think I'm coming again
to you thank
you oh I thought base damage man it
could be more but it was exactly a
thousand
Jesus what an
experience there is a reason why I don't
go to host clubs I
guess uh uh
[Music]
damn benefit increases the damage Ah
that's what they
mean
nice the mic guy was overkilled
[Music]
I know we can't charm him or whatever
[\h__\h] the I feel like it's always only
her attacks and maybe this one in
particular is we got to check in the
archive if um the other lag I had was
also a this
attack I feel like it might have
been it's a small lag but it it's throws
me
off
damn you Ed to go to host club in the
best no never honestly like I I
wouldn't first of all like why why the
[\h__\h] would I pay money
for like
some like chai flashy Gody dudes who
think they're so cool to like fake
flatter me when I know it's all n I I
hate the concept of these kind of
establishments it's just not my
thing I don't see any charm in that when
it's fake
anyway and even if they have some sort
of genuine interest in me in the end
it's still about money and it's still
like if I want food I go to a proper
restaurant and if
I want flatter then well now I can
stream
I'm going to pay for that and then it's
usually Crazy Prices
too really
expensive so no no no no no you can
probably go to the main story now I I
will do that
yes looks like I passed
don't worry
Sans the girl that scammed people to pay
her host was funny and
sad
who
for w he's still not going to
was on the
news well well well you better have some
good stuff for me that fight was easier
than some of the other fights like the
one that we've done in front of the
other weapon
shop this one was
easier wait we got to go down
again oh or did he open his jop up
there
upstairs I think I saw it on the map
just
now you think I was supposed to discover
it earlier wait where is he I'm blind
I think it is
downstairs I took that one earlier than
I should have it was hard a a there he
is it was so dark I didn't see
him well I guess an underground weapon
sealer has to be underground what do we
have
ooh used to Ladle out eyes should I just
get this for him
I didn't craft the other thing
yet 13 million
14 wow I mean might as well already get
it get the mall get them all that's
afraid of your cash
right I mean I'll just get one for
those the others maybe later
he already does a lot of good damage so
we want to improve that uh but then um
brain I cannot upgrade these right and I
don't think they were the a base to
create any other weapon
either yeah but you can do good damage I
mean if I craft one or if I buy
these you could probably use those for
the end game and be fine h
but not use those crafting material ah I
can upgrade it okay I'll buy one
whatever no need to think too much about
everything there you go have fun with
that we're going to come back and get
the
others wow enormous
spender see this is an investment this I
will spend money on pound mates you know
I can do that damage myself no but uh
every once in a while yeah they're good
pal and damage is good but I need to
save my money for these
weapons I'm going to quickly get this
and then we go main
story I went to K collab Cafe do you
mean the that the start end myth thing
that I guess they did it first elsewhere
and now they
are like Reviving
it right that one right
well wait keep reading it
uh what is
it it's not that there was a collab Cafe
yet I just found at the cafe in fact I
didn't go to a cafe I just drank coffee
at home in fact I didn't even drink
coffee my state just
k w cute
[Music]
oh my
God
cute that
is
cheeky but in the cutest and most
positive way I thought it was going to
end like oh I went to the cab Cafe where
you were at but I I was only uh eating
and drinking like stuff from to by or
whatever you know like
but H isn't this T I
guess that's
good that's good I appreciate that uh
wait so you guys said I can check on my
phone what I need I just want to check
it for k at least I can finish what I
want to
do
um this is what I want okay I can make
it dancing God
honolulu's account got hacked on
Discord be
careful
woohoo there it
is no
nice
upgrade let me upgrade
you upgrade you let me upgrade
[Music]
you I have 100 free pure
steel that's still plus 10 for
[Music]
now nice 10 memberships thank you so
much oh my God we are so generous at
kfb I think whoever gets those
memberships should go and watch my most
recent membership stream and all of the
others actually
too okay this one maybe we can put a a
better I I'll put this one on there
yeah I guess I don't need it anymore it
hurts because it's still so
fresh but I don't need it anymore
goodbye mm that
five I have a five star what is this
what detective why do I have
this why do I have this Ana weapon I
think I remember picking this one
up
Desperado guess we're not using the
stainless light how much should I spend
on this
I hope not too
much cuz I just
bought and all I get it's [\h__\h] pure
steel time
one can I return what is the return
policy on this stainless Ladle please I
didn't use it yet it's still in its
original package you would sell it for
money yeah maybe I should sell
it if I find the place for it oh the the
the I know the recycle place right but
whatever we're going to go to the main
story go go go go go
go shiny thing go go go go run run run
[Music]
everybody
to
right yes
[Music]
SNSD that's
right it never changes does it
cute son you must have a million
memories here eh yeah I was here just
like a few minutes ago I suppose a
couldn't Hur to stop by some places
while we gear up I'm already geared up I
don't need to gear up anymore right we
can eat somewhere though oh great
memory so many
memories the ten kaii Street G you could
say it was a symbol of the city a that's
a nice picture every time I pass through
this gate I get this feeling that I'm
either heading off to or coming back
from a difficult battle maybe because
this Gate's always been there for every
major occurrence in my life really next
time I pass for this gate I wonder what
kind of battle awaits me a Oh Come
memories yo wait there's a lot of food
places over
there what are we feeling oh yeah uh we
have
sushi and
H what's
this ah
Seafood all
right
ooh everything waa why am
I it's so sad that the thing I'm like
most excited about is the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
OMG how much is this in total 11,000 Yen
oh that's so
cheap actually no wait 11 is like
yeah 80 bucks maybe that's that's
actually good for all of what we're
ordering yeah I made that before I triy
to I should try it again it's been a
while but like I
I have to get the all the ingredients
again I don't know if the one all those
like liquids that I bought for it like I
think meting was one of them if they're
still
good
wow I proba
still it's been a
while okay we're all drunk exciting that
is the best state to be in to do the
main
story wait one memory over
there no now why would they build a
police station this large here it's
giving off and I've got my eye on you V
you need that don't you that looks nice
though the cops and I get along like
dogs and
cats but the detectives I've encountered
were all guys who would die for what
they believe in h and I've been
influenced by the way of life Time After
Time time after time that is sound
especially I owe that man a great debth
I doubt I'd ever be able to repay if it
weren't for him I don't know if I'd
still be alive to this day Strangers
think of a a former Yakaz a detective
would wind up being friends that's kind
of cute cute combination and one of the
only ones I've got at that
[Music]
a hi Tony wony she's running around I
know she's walking around
running
memory
inside
ah what do you
have I can sell too yo ah but I have
sell equipment uh
separately hi hi hi hi hi hi
uh o that's actually not bad
money why is this ah they're still
what have to switch out their
hats also the music is
cute do you hear it a little bit
what is this
cute nullifies curse and instant
KO ah
huh were there instant KO
attacks or is that just like if I were
to die from any normal
attack it nullifies
that they're rare but it's useful to
keep
accessories m
do I need this still no
right I hope
not yo 350 I get some okay money back
okay okay I probably spent way more than
that because look at this 1 million
versus what did we spend 13 million yen
but let's not think about it too
hard I don't know if I need these
things I think
not not
anymore 10% back oh my God but 3.5 3.5
million I guess at this point is not
that much anymore so it's
okay okay whatever buy but I also wanted
to check what you sell
AB from family heirm seized as part of
death collection to a ring being sold
the F same day it was given to a
Hostess the pawn shop is a place where
all kinds of things gather each with
their own history but for some reason
this place always struck me as a weapon
and
army I don't think I've ever never been
in a pawn shop they've got Japanese
swords and even chain mail armor strange
as the selection is I have to say I do
like the variety I really appreciate
this job for helping me get this
far oh I have a I have plates to
sell
[Music]
probably there we
are paper plate 10
Yen 100 yen per plate
th000 Yen oh there's more 10,000
Yen [\h__\h]
microwave what is all this [\h__\h] in my
inventory we could sell some of these
like
stupid useless things that I'm not going
to use
am I going to use these I don't think
[Music]
so okay
got to
work work work
work looks L has to work work work work
work work he's going to work work work
work work
work even though this is also his work
work work work work
work uhhuh
[Music]
oh she's still drunk she's like oh the
world is
spinning you good
[Music]
for
oh it's a Side Story a
memoir so
hey she's
[Music]
from oh he knows her
she said she like un I teared her up by
wearing un costume pretty sure her
[Music]
name up to be
interesting are we going to stalk
her you got to put on the costume
[Music]
again she heading towards pink Street
that's not good especially if she
doesn't know she probably doesn't even
remember me still I should probably make
sure she's all right that's kind of
creepy be
K I don't
know I don't know
K maybe just leave her
be send the other on me to Cafe Alps
this place has been around for a
while looks nice it was even well
established before the bubble area era
era I spent hours nursing a cup of
coffee here before
nursing nurs
sing what got to say I'm pretty fond of
this place if memory serves all sorts of
dangerous things went down
here I even remember completing my first
ever job training session at this Cafe I
once worked somewhere called the
tachibana real estate in the
past and my instructor was a man named
OD he drilled business etiquette 101
into my head here wait I know this he
was an [\h__\h] though never liked him
much at all hold I liked him Ki
banana but thanks to him I remember the
proper way to exchange business cards to
this day kind of a ESS skill though and
I have no reason
to
banana but yeah this was from the game
that I played right this one I know
right I feel like I do that sounds
extremely familiar to me I know those
people
H I know touch bu a real
estate I'm going to go that way but the
enemies are there I'm go this
way
ah
o number one I believe the like how a
family office was around
here kasuga the man who was instrumental
to the dissolution of both the to Clan
and the OM
Alliance and now I believe you to be a
man I can trust to do whatever needs to
be done wow this might be the first time
I've ever entrusted someone with such a
big tat he really is one hell of a guy a
this fight we know
ichun I think I know him
I might be wrong but I think I know
him okay oh what is this
some is this just a where is the main
quest this is the main quest now even
though it's a
[Music]
memoir
for
[Music]
nice did she ever see him out of the
costume before
for [\h__\h]
[Music]
ah does she watch
vtubers
no I thought she only knew him as
Mio I'm surprised she recognized me
still she doesn't know much not about me
nor who I used to be and I want to hurt
her feelings I should be honest with her
oh
finally two different
[Music]
people nice
she only cares about
Meo no she thankful to him
too Cafe
[Music]
helps it's really cool that they're
bringing back a character like that
that they grew
[Music]
up that's such a [\h__\h]
mascot
har don't this
are take those
slander yeah but it's hurt
that's
true
a is a place in hirosima and hirosima
was the
uh place that they used in yak
six I don't know they went
[Music]
to hey what what places have
the go to
[Music]
oh that's so cool I didn't know they
went all around Japan
already slowly regretting skipping no
it's just um like there's some like this
game and the previous we played and also
I think in uh the one where majima was
in that I played uh zero I've seen like
a lot of overlap Hawaii is new now but
I've seen a lot of overlap in locations
so I I thought it's just always in these
areas didn't know they
went here and there
[Music]
get to visit Japan from the comfort of
your
home locations don't get reused because
after five they swapped to a new engine
and they didn't remake all the maps from
free plus ever
oh that's
unfortunate
better
for girl girl what a girl
failure oh my God
[Music]
does she realize that she's delusional
now it's better actually
[Music]
go let's show him who the
boss anyone
guarding oh the music is nice here
kind of cool Cool
vibe oh was that one fighting people
what damn let's go was too drunk to
[Applause]
care oh look ato's HP
weak level 36 was so weak what's going
on too drunk to care to fight or what
drunkenly attacks oh my
God they so drun w but nice
job oh that dude's name was like
she wait their drunk voice lines are
funny I need to make them drunk more
often D they must be really drunk I
can't control them oh
look did you see did you
see I can't even explain what I just saw
follow
up I two
defeated
no oh oh she's back to
reality let's do it together yeah
sick team work team
work are they only going to play this in
this
fight except the only reason they
brought it back
[Music]
8 million
yen was this just a normal reward and
Yen I peppered the [\h__\h] out I think it's
fights in this map oh a
battle okay
nice it's pretty sick I like it
I can get used to
this she
[Music]
go
for she probably has ITA bags of
[Music]
don't
worry wor K FES from helping people
[Music]
K such a
s spe
[Music]
oh wait that place behind him feels so
familiar just from playing the game
before this area is
[Music]
familiar good old times and
C which one was C so the one in Tokyo or
in
[Music]
yok okay
okay sounds
[Music]
like she knows oh she gave him the one
that was on her back but it's okay she
got 50 more at home
yeah it is
yeah what time is it we can explore long
okay so the game wants me to do side
side stuff right now huh I can't even do
the main quest so that means it is the
main
quest take a look
around Okie
doie well
do oh this place used to be a huge bath
house back in the day I guess they shut
it
down you saw no hot springs it was a
nice spacious establishment hot baths
aside I had a lot of fun playing table
tennis here even though it's a smack dab
in the middle of com every visit felt
like going on a vacation a that's nice
that you can like just with some
establishment like this you can feel
like you're on vacation I I don't think
I can feel like that I need to really go
on a vacation
didn't like getting all sweaty after so
but you know going on an actual vacation
doesn't sound half bad yeah for
real go to the
males mes all the way moldes
[Music]
hooray didn't I get hit by cars
constantly in my previous
playthroughs are the cars
more careful now in this game I wouldn't
mind getting hit a few
times and seven I got hit constantly I
swear it
hurts did they just change the the
amount of cars or so or how aggressively
they drive I wonder Millennium Tower
it might be a symbol of this town
nowadays but it actually used to be a
filthy shopping
district
oh wait it looks
like huh but then a large scale
development project started and the yaka
spoke blood hiding over this empty plot
of land I was right in the middle of all
the action if everyone involved in that
conflict would could see this View today
I wonder what they'd have to say maybe
something along the lines of you can
make good money with
this ah the empty
lot first empty now beak as
[\h__\h] what
what no but I was about to say like it
reminds me of a building IRL
[Music]
another
one well the Stars trying
again he was a h
of course he
was how could he not
if MAA can pull it off surely K can as
well I guess so
[Music]
qu is just civil and she has no idea who
I was or what I've done and so
fast
for
Fore
fore fore
[Music]
you calling her an Old
Tag there's only one way we can
clear thise
only one way I know that's
[Music]
true going to be m
really
[\h__\h] that's so
true one single
enemy he's going to be
fine I lag again yo it always this one
always lags for me I but I don't
know anybody who play plays this game
before does the same attack lag for you
too it's always the same attack for
me that kick remind me to never use that
that kick again cuz I always mess up the
mess up the prompt because of the lag
it's not a skill issue trust
me well this one I missed just because I
suck same timing for
me you don't think it like for you it's
it's a pretty um
what's the word
subtle
lag so
weak ooh oh yeah we we have a all fire
element
now no more
water goodbye water
okay he's
[Music]
bleeding Agy no no no it's really it
feels
like it slows down and and like lags for
a split
seconds that was not the like no I'm
also just right
now I'll admit
that she's pretty free
now
well it it depends how old this guy is
calling her a hag
[Music]
yes let's
go let's go
inside is that supposed to be K that
golden statue
what the [\h__\h] is that
pose is the old one not
I'm ra a woman I don't have a
choice she's at least
50 the old one right so she's PR free
the other one is
wow I mean yeah that is
h
a fore
[Music]
membership
I guess we got to help out let K and
work
[Music]
for that that sounds like that sounds
like a
uh a not like a way of saying yo we
couldn't uh get her to voice act again
in this game uh so she
just is fulfilling other dreams in her
life right now because that's what she's
doing IRL or so I don't know she say no
she's here okay
[Music]
for
okay
cute I'll give that to her but
[Music]
I
for and I swear if I played the other
Yakuza games I admit this would probably
all of this would be so much more
special to me so I'm sorry I I can't
yeah I mean yeah it's the main story as
long as they don't let me do the main
story yeah I've been saying
that but yeah it's like it feels like a
Side Story and I don't really it doesn't
hit so hard for
me um I mean yeah I I still get the
sentiment like oh meeting people from
back in the day but
[Music]
yeah where is why I should play them I
ain't got no time for
that it's
okay it's
okay doesn't matter this was good for me
I'm glad I came back here all right once
everyone's
right what we're already going
back
we're we're not that's
it oh but like there's so much you could
do
probably if you
stayed wow okay
n the right book on the right side of
the map is
good this
one or the upper one you mean this
one the light one in the
middle ah
ah oh
okay kfp recommended me
books
unbelievable as if you didn't know
better
champion
[Music]
wait that's the name in one of his
skills
[Music]
I don't remember him he was in
Yak I don't remember
him
n you want to fight
okay oh we don't have
time they won't let me
go all day yapping yapping yapping
before getting into a battle just get to
the
point okay just get to
it do I love I got time for
this it's
already time is passing
so
fast nice follow
up I have a better chance to cook knock
you out with words
yeah if anything
[Music]
that
voice old man Kaki In the
Flesh wait you should recognize him
right away
[Music]
say it say
it come
on
you why not tell him
that gives me a skill that I've been
told to
do on my off time wait no I couldn't
have have I could I maybe not couldn't
have come here
probably something else I got a pound b
oh more
pounding yeah you
missedi or the the fan girl of
[Music]
oh
wow me to sensei
realize you think he knows he's
pretending playing
along I mean he
doesn't look such a dump
person
[Music]
fore
foree 38
no
problem let's
go
one1 would make sense but they always
bring my whole party
back oh it's
101 I can't block him at all
dude can I do that
what's his
weaknesses he probably doesn't have any
huh what if I use the Kaki Master
Essence will he
react kick his ass I'm
scared oh
there's a single part I yeah this one I
guessing a critical hit what what kind
of probably was really fast right oh
[Music]
God missed
it and he doesn't even
react oh damn I'm so scared
[Music]
kak style has no
weaknesses Co
bleed please why you no bleed
uh-oh okay oh my my f
activated
yo th damage minimum I don't accept less
oh we already wow oh we're going to get
to 2,000 at this point H
almost
1,883 is probably when you
were emotional damage
she wait I'm
dying what do I
do what do I do I can probably take at
least one more hit right should I get a
pound mate that would be so oh so
embarrassing it's going to need a burn
heel I should have
done
[Music]
this uh I guess I could also do I I get
still I still get a turn right if I heal
but no the 100 is like weak I'd not risk
it maybe he has a strong attack up his
sleeve but I still got to turn if I call
them right they don't take up my turn
yeah it doesn't cost a turn I'll do it
cuz I'm I'm a scared little p SS
Y no problem Violet to duel they let me
do
it they let me do
it and we all want to see Kaki and join
The Host Club don't we
[Applause]
[Music]
so
confused why am I here
I'm so
[Music]
sorry and now I'm going to
heal
um
500 what's my Max I think 500 brings me
up to full like
800 I'm so
[Music]
scared okay not too bad
224 what what how much damage which one
was the best so
far baby
let's
[Music]
do I don't
know nice C thank
you should I do the pine burning error
always I like that one too
[Music]
yeah and these ones the the prompts are
so difficult that's the
thing yeah I I think pistol generally
578 y That's exactly I did as much
damage as I have HP
heo
stand so it's better if I don't attack I
could have healed in this turn huh but
then I'll I'll
[Music]
boost
yeah we don't want to attack when he's
in counter stance range ah I
forgot range works
too damn
it okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay I'll try but
then I'm like out of MP let's do the 20
that's better I'm going do that
twice
waa 1,100
just one more just one
more is
that that was a strong crit yeah my crit
is up that worked
excellently
Divine what a challenge
[Music]
the crit caused the wall Bal and de
damage yeah that was some double damage
yeah
mhm but do you want to become my pound
[Music]
mate come
on Straight
Talk why talk around
it you both know
[Music]
any other
guy just wants to tell him how he's
[Music]
feeling
understand I think that's their theme
song
he did a good
job
foree
[Music]
fore first
that was so
[Music]
[Laughter]
soft I'm
sorry not sorry
[Music]
nice do I get a stamp there we
go
nice there he
is he must be really strong when we call
him oh okay we got to go for real for
[Music]
real he can
get what do you mean of course it's a
coincidence that has nothing to do with
it
what you got a main quest to
do is important
over well that about covers everything
guess it's time for the big meeting geni
station once we take off from there
there's no turning
back I feel
nervous so right in
here it's yeah which conversation is
this number
Z oh
oh I already have like five of those I'm
a whip collector NOW Watch Me Whip watch
me ne ne watch me whip whip watch me
neigh
NE watch me sing that song while I'm on
the
highway riding in my truck
honestly yeah they got so much to do
oopsie oh
Dam
sorry but I no this last time I went to
Japan suddenly there's like so many more
maybe already the time before I don't
know so many more self checkout
registers so I've been trying to use
those too in convenience stores there's
so many more wow it's kind of
fascinating when you see like changes
like that happening with your own eyes
in real time
[Music]
M but I can buy some stuff here it's
actually good glue is faster than
standard Super
X damn
it they're everywhere in America yeah
generally self
checkout
wait no wait in Austria a few here and
there
but not
everywhere not definitely it's a thing
everywhere yeah level 41 yeah
B am I
okay am I going to be
that let LEL
41 it's pretty difficult for me
uh-oh hard content
uh-oh
Shield I mean if I
do another side maybe I'll get another
level
[Music]
up this may be the most exciting one for
old Y what which
one this plane
I'm actually just going
here cuz I thought I could get food here
but I actually I don't know what I was
looking at I guess I was
[Music]
wrong oh the upcoming Story Part ah yeah
I wanted to go to a food
place to heal kidu
up without using my
items CU I'd have to use MP
[Music]
[Applause]
items yeah let's go let's go let's
go do I walk in
here no
[Music]
oh wait these
are
CH that's not what I mean I I need a I
need a
restaurant now I'm going so
far
Walmart yeah places like that really
need self checkout
Target in Walmart I can
imagine I don't know which one it was
but the one I
saw was proud of this [\h__\h] oh my God
remember I remember this
place this is where my gambling
addiction
started right
here thank
you bless you too guys
bless you
too let's get drunk let's get
drunk in the middle
of no let's get [\h__\h] drunk let's get
drunk I don't even drink alcohol I am
straight and for real
for I didn't drink
red
oh I went or
rapping G helps her think things
through I want to learn how to make
gilar I love gilar especially the
crunchy one so guys what do you
recommend should we go or should I do
like some of the hero quests
or should I
go oh we got
drinklings you dip kills and anything
yeah this in the what is it
soy sauce but it's not just soy sauce
it's like
different trying to get some levels any
way to level
up the white
book do I get I get I guess usually I
get into at least one fight so I guess I
get some exp out of
it
Shina h
H probably not like that
much right first drink
links it's above it behind the back
uh-huh above it behind the back okay
it was
AR self
[Music]
report self report disc
fore
fore fore
[Music]
do you know what I'm
laughing feels too
[Music]
familiar you're just making face like
you have no idea brain empty
[Music]
moment scary
dude you
don't and then you roast me for not
reading
wow subtitle is hard to
read okay then I'll just have my
thoughts on my own with me myself and I
H I'm getting pissed just listening to
this you should talk it out you should
compromise I got why you didn't want to
talk about it
now damn
lots of
Y
like I was going to tell you because I
only wrote it in the memb only
post when my mommy came
over
besides we to
a and I never went to a with my mommy
together
before so that's
special wow wow wow wow wow wow
the P made her was
nice
yes I felt like a [\h__\h]
even much
older sorry fum
um I think it's from the
quing quing a little
bit uh I'll be thinking
too let's do a
think I was saying my mommy and I we
[Music]
went and uh
I feel like in my childhood whenever we
went to like swimming places usually
they also had like a SAA and then my
mommy she would go to the
sauna but then I asked her when's the
last time you went to a sauna and she
told me like at least like 20 years ago
what
so I
thought this must have been kind of nice
and relaxing supposedly but then again I
don't know how relaxing it really was
because like she was like a little bit
suffering from the heat she couldn't
like we we had like pretty much the same
tolerance of it we both got pretty
exhausted from it and then
uh she was yapping the whole time mostly
I was just like mm
trying to like uh keep my
energy reserved just for enduring the
heat but she was she was not just
yapping she when my mom yaps she yaps
strongly and with a lot of
energy and
and when she was getting more and more
exhausted I was like Mommy maybe you
should stop yapping while you're in the
sauna and you can Yap outside of
it cuz I feel like this is is draining
you no she was yapping aggressively very
much so so I don't know how relaxing it
actually was but I feel like it was a
nice little
activity for us to do because we never
went together before and I was always
like I was just too young for that
activity I just wasn't interested and
now now I'm
old so now we can go to the sauna
together
I think she enjoyed it too oopsie that's
not what I wanted to do I wanted to talk
to you dude no ah
yes yapping is in the
blood yeah
yeah I guess
so okay yeah sorry his story
is unless it gets
deeper he's just getting slandered by
reviews
[Music]
for in German we say
SAA too probably
in finish too
probably my God there's so much side
stuff today I'm sorry guys I'm kind of
rushing through it just because I'm
scared that everything takes so long we
will never make
it and I just want to do main
story I don't care about the guy who is
like throwing roses at her
[Music]
talk about each of
them thanks for
drink for
for
I want to run
for distribute
some some
[Music]
ouchies yeah I'm All yapped Out cannot
listen to this yapping anymore I'm so
sorry you don't have anything to Yap
about right
good you have a tobacco
assortment I don't think you wait do you
I guess does he I guess he
does you're good right yeah okay
byebye
yeah oh
um uh well
oh so H you said
behind above and
behind above behind above and
[Music]
behind this is what you mean
right wait there's nothing here where is
this
look at this look at this little
egg that's what you mean ah Ki said Yuki
place was around here there better be
some experience points to be gained from
this
cute must be hard to get customers from
there girl probably no one's hearing you
usually from 90% of the
time yeah that's what I
thought H you're telling me she's 50
plus they did not bother adjusting her
model I will tell you over and over
again gladly how Japanese people don't
seem to age
but this lady she's not 50 plus m- no
she
is 30 at
most you
say they really adjuster model
today oh same reaction
[Music]
she is very
energetic what is
this it's a cute mask though better than
the a
certain Rin orange
person y yum y yum
statue how the [\h__\h] she has a [\h__\h]
baby
face
small how is she 50 plus
I need to know
oh
I don't think C takes 30 years off don't
they drink alcohol all the
time you good
girl drinking alcohol every single day
probably makes your age a bit
too
for are you going to go and help her
please no business
e
[Music]
for I feel bad for her too though
she
own
[Music]
restaurant in a place that you only
really would go to if you know the
address and you know where you're going
to you don't stumble across
we got to make her famous on
y or at least the Japanese equivalent
there was no experience to be
[Music]
had s this in that
Cas
[Music]
um right there there is
no like dungeon in this map
right there
is but we're already it's already be so
late I might as well just grind on my
own um
instead yeah just do something more
meaningful on stream ah wait there it is
North oklahama underground
huh I don't know do you want to see
me doing the
dungeon I
mean go for the fight if you pull off a
win then it's high if you don't we can
try
oh you want me to H I don't know about
that nah that's off stream stuff well
the thing is also tomorrow is the other
stream and so I'd have to do it before
stream I don't mind doing some stuff
before the stream
but you know it's going
to take up some
time know what to do
[Music]
um should I do some hero
classs should I do more of these
memories but I feel like you guys you
guys are many many of you guys are
saying you didn't read you're not
reading
along
so who Am I who am I doing this
for H
well the small memor is are actually
fine cuz those are just like free lines
of like oh this is this and I'm actually
interested in
those this is this kind of place and
this is this kind of place let's go
here
oops my goal is never to 100% any any
game I don't think I ever really aimed
for that in any
game it's a bit Overkill usually in most
games in my
opinion what's down here that
I
what what's that book about
what
what go back and go inside I can go
inside inside
here
e ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew
I thought it was deeper
though had no idea there was a gambling
then in here actually kind of comfy
those lamps are nice Ambiance all the
enough gambling dance always remind me
of
H should gamas Instinct one that's
strangely good at that her predictions
were always right on the
money interesting T sign gambling
genius after listening to her I ended up
winning too much and a huge fight broke
out you purchas you PL W gu you flying
over thank
you thank you that's
exciting memories never fail to make me
smile nowadays I feel a bit sorry for
those gamblers
though
interesting so much gambling
potential but don't worry I'm not going
to gamble
here I only do
blackjack
for
well yeah we haven't done it
yet and it's probably better that
way I know is there a black check
in the
[Music]
game hi who are
you wait the curry look good
too
wait wait where are we going
where where are we going I guess we're
going to go let's go well wherever we're
[Music]
going let's go
I don't know these names
D during my I joined forces with the
hero and family humble little we all had
each other's backs caught up in the
conflict surrounding their
hometown uhhuh
foreign speech
[Music]
his face looked familiar I was
like they mod his face after him right
and had him voice
act that's
why huh
maybe it's better if I don't listen to
all of
this kind of spoilers if I want to play
the other
games come spoilering any
everything I shouldn't be listening to
this at all thank God my brain is mostly
empty when I listen to
this I'll forget
[Music]
it fore
all right
guys let's hear some more
[Music]
yapping nice glasses
foreign
fore
for
what what
IR the
actor the main guy of the HS of family
nagu does not appear because his actor
was a comedian who unknowingly performed
at a Yakuza sponsored venue so not this
game sponsored it but actually Yakuza
sponsored it he was dropped by his
agency and the irony of it is that due
to that he will he's not included in the
Yakuza game
[Music]
anymore what which there is a sub story
in this game what what do you mean uh
what does that last sentence mean
there's a sub story about that incident
or or
like that IRL incident was made into a
sub story or do you mean what what does
that last sentence mean the rest I
understand but damn like
what dropping him because of that did he
even know he was performing at
a also the agency isn't the agency the
one who's in charge of keeping tabs of
where your your contracted Talent is
performing at and usually you're also
the one organizing that anyway how the
[\h__\h] do you fire them then or drop them
what the
[\h__\h] there's a sub story about oh there
is one about the irel incidents
what
H yeah he must have done it behind their
their back then
but I don't know maybe the sub story
would tell us more about it there's a
sub story where a guy gets dropped
because he was accused of doing a job at
a Yakuza own
place it's like kind of in honor of him
then what's this what what's that guy's
name
nagumo in the game is
Nago it's one with the sub store in
Hawaii
ah yeah that's wild wild
all yeah the agency didn't check hard
enough on the L blamed him yeah that
could also be the
[Music]
case
for why is he so hostile
[Music]
ACC new
jerseyy
[Music]
for that's how people say
that new
Joy
for new
J I got to learn
that I don't like
are they likeable in the game where they
show
up they stink
it is a weird situation
can we
[Music]
fight oh yeah we're going to
fight we have been
ra thank you
nobody
cut
ball
huh
for need to
EXP
for no it's my I
don't we're cashing them outside how
about
this go
[Music]
ow one
and
and never
mind never
[Music]
mind best
girl or is she honestly if I have to
give the title of best girl to
someone we have a traitor and uh
Ino I I
know okay but like think about it she
she has been spying on us and
stuff
what
[Applause]
dam what
did you see this just now what what what
what it didn't even show like like Miss
or anything like
that I would say son would be best
girl she has yet to do
anything to where she would have to
redeem
herself us you know
totally understandable her
reaction towards
Ichiban but then I will not get
that pretty good yeah and I have
absolutely no issue no beef with her at
this point in
[Music]
time time to end it B you
know she she did it and that already
brings her score
down oh nice 17,000 than New Jersey has
the most diners in the United States oh
I love diners I think wait I mean well
I'm only thinking about family
restaurants in Japan if there if there's
a lot of places like that then I love it
also I've never been to like the typical
American Dina kind of place except for
you know what was it at Wendy's or so
but I'm thinking more more like diner
diner more like like a like with the bar
counter and small and the checkered
floor and waitresses on roller skates
and so
on was a Denny okay okay
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
for yeah family owned I want to go to
one like
that I'm going to become America
eats I'm going to become the America
version of Japan
eat I'm going to report on all kinds of
American random hidden familyowned
little little restaurants tiny today
today he uploaded one where he ate in
like a garage of this tiny random place
he's doing really random secretive
little spots recently that
dude can't can't lose to him I have to
go what guy fear who the
[\h__\h] who
[Music]
I have the
shirt
huh
flavor I only know flavor
[Laughter]
FL TV show where he does something
similar
uhuh I don't have TV and I don't have
American TV even more so so no idea what
you're talking
about looks like K fights like
K name sounds like k
k how many brain cells do these Yakuza
have
knocked down prob many times
[Applause]
[Music]
before I wonder why how that comes out
how that
[Music]
is
for the way he looked at him for
real oh you want to hear more of that we
for for
[Music]
what
in this picture he just looks like an
old and Japanese
version of Dewey from Malcolm in the
Middle oh my
God I have opened your eyes to something
that you will never be able to
unsee please bathe your eyes in this
[Music]
F damn who is
this all
gold malol in the middle they played it
all the time and oh German Austrian TV
[Music]
that what have
you is it is it that Kido sitting right
next to you and he still doesn't want to
reveal himself to you is that what still
hurts you after all this time I that's
kind of hurt hurting me right
[Music]
now he not even looking
at awkwardly sitting next to them
[Music]
maybe that's a good
thing if I can't see them they can't see
me
[Music]
fore
spee fore
[Music]
if they're playing
along it's kind of awkward that they're
like raising him to Heavens while he's
sitting there and like I mean come on if
you know then just just don't
[Music]
huh yeah they they don't know right cuz
otherwise I feel like this situation is
extremely awkward like you know the
person that is even kind of like he
asked for all this information you're
sitting right
there you're like praising like his
legacy and talking about all the
legendary things he did he's just like
like not even looking at you
like I wouldn't I don't know I guess
they are oblivious about it they don't
get it they know but again K made a
promise soon no no they you think they
know I don't know they seem like they
don't they don't
know they but K you how much more
obvious can you make
[Music]
it foree
uh because that dude is making it super
awkward that's why we're leaving
[Music]
the guy who got
fired
[Music]
for you're a drunk and stupid
D I am kill
you but if you tell
anybody I'll kill you
[Music]
no not the Crickets
no only
Applause
foree
[Music]
for good for you
maybe we need another protagonist like
ichan to follow up kuu but like as a
side the SE sequel side game thing
spin-off in
[Music]
Hiroshima
oh
so I
am wondering now don't tell me
but the fact
that uh neither in zero nor
in what was it seven what I
played did I feel like
I don't know anything that they're
talking about and they are obviously
like going really hard on relieving
millions of his memories like everything
his whole
Legacy they didn't do that in just like
as a catchup in zero for
example or the previous one seven so
what I'm thinking now
is he might just actually really
die CU why else would they do
this why else would they spend hours and
hours and hours hours and hours and
hours and hours and hours of
content uh discussions and
yapping with
kido's story from Z 0 to
7 so 0 to six I don't
know he is so
dying can't believe
it but this is like making it more and
more clear for me that they are killing
him off
which is I mean fine you know after so
many games it's fine to proceed and move
on to
another another protagonist that's fine
but it just made me realize in no other
games that they try so hard to give you
so much like Recaps and closure closure
so much
closure
no took it you want me free
what does does kiw me free play
after this
game oh it doesn't exist it's some thing
okay
yet ra setting him up to die in a future
game he could die here but I don't think
he necessarily has to yeah well he's
certainly going
to die tly like would also be kind of
crazy to like cure his cancer now when
when they make such a big deal about it
being so serious and too late and not
worth treating and blah blah
blah and then obviously all the closure
and all that that they're trying to
get uh they're not suddenly going to
pull out some
magic healing potion
[Music]
and it would be like kind of like also
like if he actually of course we don't
want K to die but on the other hand
wouldn't we feel so [\h__\h] dumb after
doing all these like closure things and
and meeting older people from the past
and bucket list and this and that and
the whole time we talk about him having
cancer and him dying and all that and
then he doesn't die I mean that would be
stupid
too that then I would feel
so so fashed in
German very very bab
Boozled it's make yeah yeah we do we do
be trying to do these things to make him
want to keep on living but to me it's
just like it's just like a nice goodbye
letter to Kido the
character
weird I guess I'll find out either by
the end of this game or if there's
another
game but we'll
see but I
mean there there's so much
buildup but then also how can you kill
off such a legendary character just let
him go to I don't know Hawaii and like
die 50 years later as an old dude just
let him retire for real for real let him
why why why
why must you
script cancer it's so serious
too
man but it's like maybe it's like you
know like how kings in medieval times
felt and Vikings felt it was more
honorable to die on the
battlefield and
even
desirable so rather than just dying
quietly off screen or so not an actual
game just like being written off and all
that maybe it's just like to pay
respect to let him die like this back
from retirement fighting once again
while having
cancer but then they could have then
they didn't need to give him cancer if
you want to make it like that you could
have died protecting someone I don't
know Ichiban taking a bullet for Ichiban
oh my God if that actually
happens
oh quote me
now um
[Laughter]
but the cancer is unnecessary a little
bit they could have just uh had a very
dramatic like but then then if it was
something more like taking a bullet or
so there would have been no reason to do
all this bucket list stuff and like let
him meet all these people and all that
with cancer you know that he's going to
die and then we have a reason why for
many many chapters in the game we can
lead him yeah through this like trip of
memory
Hall so it has to be something that is
cooking and that we know is coming
slowly but
surely so that we can do this oh so he's
definitely going to die
it's just making more and more sense in
my brain more and more sense in my
[Music]
brain not even natural cause
yeah I don't know I still find it weird
to like kill off a character like this
though like would they really do that
but then all the signs are leading to
it but that's just a theory a game
theory
whatever we'll see we'll
see oh wow
Fury
so I have to cook something
and I must say I'm disappointed in hello
beep
because what I have three recipes all
with meat this
time and one was a fish recipe I should
have cooked that first but the moment I
opened my
box a pungent fish
smell met me in my face and then I was
like hm well I guess
I don't understand if it's some like
airtight package how that smell would
leave the package but okay and I I
opened the the like ice bag that has all
the stuff that needs to be
cooled I open it and I I take all the
all the ice thingies out and I take all
the meat out and everything and I touch
the package the plastic package of the
fish filet and
it smells strongly like fish and it's
really wet but sometimes those icy
things they just make everything even
though those are also
supposedly like air what's the word air
TI I don't
know packaged without any openings
somehow it still makes things kind of
wet but I thought this was suspiciously
wet and the wetness also smell like the
fish you know airtight
M but I was like okay weird but I just
put it in the fridge and then the next
day yes today when I opened my fridge I
noticed where I put the fish there was
like a little baby
puddle of liquid and I I pick it up and
I
notice H there's still liquid coming out
directly from a corner of the fish
package and then I I I I Tred to like
touch it with my finger everywhere to
see if there's a hole and yes there was
indeed a hole and that's why that's why
it was smelling because the fish was
probably already bad if that fish is not
air tightly packaged and I I Googled it
too if fish really smells strongly like
fish then no don't eat it so I threw it
away I was like no I'm not eating that
I'm not risking that that thing is
open yeah I I did send like you can um
send like a not a complaint but like a
an update on your package if anything
was damaged
whatsoever you know when I got refunded
free bucks like dry oil free
Euro can I even
buy another fish filet with fre
euro is that
even
enough I thought it's not enough so I
went back and I wanted to do another
complaint cuz you can do a complaint for
the food being off and you can do a
complaint for the packaging being open
and so on but I just did the O package
is open one because I thought that's
just like it makes sense obviously if
the package of a fish is open then the
result is probably that the fish is
going to go
bad yeah you can't buy anything with
free yeara
nowadays no it's like two fillet like
for two people but usually I mean the PO
portions are pretty small but I don't
think I don't think I
can buy such a yeah like Frozen is like
less quality so maybe Frozen I don't
even that I don't
know yeah I don't think I could buy that
from that price so I wanted more money
out of it I tried and then then I got a
message like Mrs takik you are kind of
like complaining a lot these days aren't
you so we want you to like oh you know
just to make sure everything's okay AKA
we want to make sure you're not
reporting everything even though there's
nothing happening
like fake reporting but they write it
like oh we just want to make sure
everything's okay so please talk to the
like
staff uh
whatever yeah that that was like
uh yeah at a time where just it it led
me to like an online chat nobody showed
up so nobody was available I was like
whatever
whatever yeah everything is not okay I'm
reporting because I don't even know how
the [\h__\h] you damaged that somebody must
have like cuz that's it's pretty thick
plastic I don't know how that happens
when you're just throwing it into a bag
somebody must have like knifed it or
so how does that even happen
man I've had that happen with the the
ice bags before the ice bag leaking
because the ice bag had a hole in
it but not with the meat before
so I'm going to make one of my other
dishes not the fish
one I have one that's like uh Korean
meatballs apparently but you
know probably not 100% accurate but
something like that inspired by that and
then some other
thing I should cook but
I don't want
to I'll think about it I think
about
yeah
yeah the Korean meatball slab yeah it's
like meatballs and they have some Sesame
topping a little bit little bit little
bit got a planty planty is the frozen
pizza or something like that H yesterday
I ate more of my my soup soup is
finito I ate soup twice yesterday for
lunch and for
[Music]
dinner uh I wouldn't mind some meat
now let me cook before the next room
like today I was kind of
tired after I woke up I just couldn't be
productive it's SA Pizza
H it
is what Saturday is pizza day or what
who decided that
you I alert cor yeah but no I I still I
still went to bed to a time where I
normally kind of normally go to bed at
all not really un
but sounds like a day for takeout it's a
bit late like at this time only like
more crap happy stores are open I
think main
story tomorrow hopefully we'll get more
main story and frozen pizza is good I
don't
know
recently I just had it recently I'm not
I'm not feeling it right
now I guess I'm feeling shitty delivery
pizza even more than frozen pizza right
[Music]
now is the Korean style meatball with
green bean and
potato uh I don't remember but you are
you looking up the
recipes that I could have right now it
probably is that yeah probably
I I literally you guys even you guys
even monitor what recipes I have from
met
fresh and you call me out on stalking
you
guys I couldn't even eat at this time e
it's all about just your general
although you stay up late too don't you
but I think it's all about your like
sleeping cycle Rhythm
thingy we learn learn from the
best chat reflect the streamer how fan
Bas is
concerning talking green meatbone sounds
good yeah but meatballs I don't know
they're like they take a lot of
effort and I have to like form them but
maybe actually might not be so bad
actually might not be so diff What if I
just I still have
shuta I still have EA
meatballs maybe I just don't take the e
meatballs and then glaze them with the
sauce from the Korean meatballs and the
Sesame and call it a
day
nah I'll go now and see what I can do if
I feel like doing
[Music]
anything
yeah uh sorry for a lot of skipping
yapping but don't worry I wouldn't skip
main story just the thing is I I will
admit it's just um basically I just uh
can't really relate to a lot of this
stuff and that's just because I didn't
play the other games not all of them at
least I played two other ones you know
it is what it
is yeah there there was a lot of yapping
I just got a little bit tired from the
yap yappity yap speaking of yappity Yap
you know when I saw like couple of the
girls playing Monster Hunter in a collab
you know what I was thinking g h Ina
[Music]
bi Grand blue Yap toy what did I finish
it
for are we going to collab or
what
yeah where is the Grand blue you have to
see
collaboration this was expected to
honestly yes it was to be
expected that I finish the game and then
it's just not
happening did Z catch up I don't know
did she she didn't finish the game but I
feel like even if she did nothing would
happen well let me let me ask S if she
plans
taada do you still plan on finish ing
Grand
blue then I'll if she says yes then I'll
I'll say go go go do it do it do it do
it do
it you're kind of going to push for
people and you know are bad at starting
collabs are
they is
people like bi boo I don't know can't
judge h no I'm not going to get into
Monster Hunter you know I tried that
before aesthetically I like it but uh I
didn't really ride with the game play
[Music]
GAA G Gula
goua Gula playing other monster hunter
games Well everybody's playing the new
one Gula
Gula
G
Gula why is that so funny to me goua I'm
just going to call her that next time I
talk to her hi gula see if she
reacts
goulash welcome to the
goog it's going to be
confused I'll just say sorry I I bit my
tongue I can't pronounce ours today I
bit really hard into my tongue so today
you gula
my favorite R
Gula
Gula oh imagine if she was a gal vtuber
called gal
Gula
G Gula Gula it's still a weird
name golly
goulash G
fan out of GA as a gal even I I didn't
see any even when you
know when she
became
student she dressed herself up as a go
oh really Alo for today h it was a lot
of yapping but it's still fun great job
with the soundboard thank you you were
killing it video you
woohoo there you I like it too it's
great
okay see you tomorrow for hopefully some
progress did I save I think I saved but
let's do it let's do it let's do it
let's do it let's do it
again but yeah just wanted to say one
more time thank you
for you know
being around and having fun with me also
yesterday and the member stream we're
really hype thank you for um even though
like I personally for both streams right
after I was
like maybe that wasn't so good oh man
I'm sure they're like kind of
disappointed but then everybody was like
wa this was so good this was so fun so
I'm really happy you guys are enjoying
my content right
now yeah polar roids by the way are up
on the community board and I think Jim
Tracy are you
here
Jimmy Jimmy are you here I think you are
the one are you here so let me tell you
uh I think you're the one who sent a red
Super Chat and said I don't need a polar
um now you may not know but I made one
for you anyway it's also in the
folder just so you know I think you were
the one right who said I don't need a
polar Ro I already have one I made one
anyway sometimes I do
that you you knew how did you
know how Oh no you're saying yep because
that was you you didn't know right you
didn't know that I made one anyway can't
escape from the
Polaroid cuz I want to say thank you you
can't just send a red Super Chat when
all you need is a pink Super Chat and
just be like here take my money
check my
money yeah I chose for you
though slaps you gently with
Polaroid getting bullied with love love
love love you love love love rush I feel
it every every day hold you TI never let
go cuz I have you in a choke hold and
I'm going to choke you until you
faint and then I'm going to grill you
and eat you and we in
[Music]
good night W me
wo
wo is this what Bing looks like I just
opened
my YouTube Studio
[Music]
I
saw something that looks like
[Music]
Bing
shees I was B today
yay Y
no that's weird body looks like Weir
yeah cuz like it just suddenly goes down
in like 1 minute seemingly
probably like
[Music]
what what let me do the
math almost
3,000 it's mostly done with malicious
intent well if you're going to bot me
bot me all the way
through to the
end cheap coward
[Music]
stay committed to
it so that it's not so
[Music]
obvious Bots are everywhere first the
Twitter
Bots you know what the [\h__\h] is up with
that BS are everywhere they're taking
over the robots oh be careful guys be
careful
be careful of the
robots even my coffee machine is a bot
throw it out throw it out and grind your
coffee with your own hands
[Music]
please yeah yeah yeah I know others have
been getting boted and then I was like
oh seems like
I'm being bought it now
too but yeah that's like such a weird
like it doesn't really do anything
so it's like spraying me with uh water
with a water spray
bottle what does that hurt you does that
hurt must
hurt like no what
unless I'm a cat oh my I was kind of a
cat anyway see you tomorrow
[Music]