than
do you see you who are
you e
[Music]
there
L to see see you who are you
[Music]
lovely to see you to see you who are you
h
than
see you who are you
for
sh
lovely to see you see you who are you
is for
hey hey you
yes you do you know
me who are you no I don't think so wait
hold on you smell kind
of why does your feet make dingding
noises as you
that's very
strange I can't remember
anything do do you live in a pineapple
under
huh it seems I have been pulled into a
red
void how
strange move
[Music]
interesting all right cod's down oh what
has happened
legit all right out of character what
the freig
has this happened for anyone else or is
it just uh Elizabeth Rose blood
flame cards down everyone cards down
Elizabeth froze blood
flame it's
[Laughter]
confused that's funny
man I set up the ambience and
everything oh my
[Music]
God we'll cut it in post guys we'll cut
it in post cut it in the cut it cut out
this bed all
right
where
[Music]
ah it's cuz I made fun of a feet isn't
it
all right one sec we'll go BRB
[Music]
for
okay who am I the world I live
in and more than
anything the people I hold most dear
faced with Oblivion I feel
empty
relieved
perhaps distraught
I do not
know so much I don't know and
yet that bright light it calls to
me is anybody else concerned about
this who are these people
I I'm want to follow the light I mean
everybody's going so I
guess seem drawn to this light over
here I can't it is very beautiful
wherever we
are okay okay
than I don't feel very powerful with
this
I don't like light I don't like
that I take me take me aliens is this
they are very brave to suddenly walk
into this
light whoever they are can we go up can
we can we go we don't go up should we go
towards the
light really what's that that looks like
an
[Music]
egg that
like a broken
egg is this a hole but what came oh my
God like a broken egg oh it's not a hole
it's not a
[Music]
hole does anybody know where we
are huh
[Music]
huh the bestle
castle
huh you there what are you doing
here you have the look of an Outsiders
about
you quick send word to his majesty
[Music]
but the heroes have arrived at the
sanctuary right
away
whoa ra audience
chamber oh welcome Heroes this is the
kingdom of lior and I am its king
[Music]
he's really
cute I like his
mustache the guards who brought you here
have informed me that you remember not
but your own
names h a side effect of travel between
worlds no b no
doubt H this must all come as a surprise
to you but H but here can well it was I
who summoned you
here you see an
unprecedented Calamity now threatens our
world pause for dramatic
effect
what it has Z the other Earth will with
corruption and driven us from our
homes this blant land now gives rise to
creatures of Shadow known as
stain this Kingdom of Le bestto and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us
Leist but should the Calamity be left
unchecked is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire world
[Music]
faced with this Prospect I showered the
ancient texts for a way to combat the
Calamity and therein I found
one and that
is yes king of this
land the ritual of hero
summoning hero you who hail from another
world have been summoned here by me to
become the saviors of
listo right only you have the power to
save our
world and so I ask Will
You
Huh your your
majesty what is it a great host of
Stains have broken through our defensive
life
fine
no we are rushing to mount to to mount a
def defenses defense but the situation
is D Your Majesty we must get you
somewhere
safe he looks
cool I mean he looks cool who are these
strangers what say you Heroes will you
accept this destiny
to save there is a great power within
you will you use it to save us to save
our
world so sorry I'm so
sorry
huh
yes strange horn
I am
am
are fair
Maiden Nissa apparently that's a a very
odd C name
[Music]
apparently I
see just Nissa apparently right I see
M I
am here Elizabeth is my
name
yes what is above my head well E I guess
is for Elizabeth and blood flame is my
surname of course
[Music]
what's it says raven
Croft yes seems like a very long name
yeah come come here come
here oh are how very forward of
here I realize I'm in
I'm very
Predator you at any moment at any time
can you Pur okay yes Fair Maiden you are
speaking quite quietly is there a way
that you can raise your
voice I I know we have just met but uh
with so many voices around it is quite
hard to hear you I might I might die if
I much higher but I can I that that's
probably as good as I can do is that any
better
um one moment I must go look at this
wall and ponder over at the Horizon
hello yes please P the wall stop leave
me alone
[Music]
I don't know honestly oh my goodness
they're speaking to us what huh who is
speaking speaking why does this this
using so many difficult words I don't
understand these words I me come from a
land of simple
words it's too late to save this world
Perhaps it is too late to save this
world from destruction nevertheless it
is our duty to defend our King and our
countrymen to the very end Brave Heroes
From Another World let us go forth with
Valor and fight
[Music]
together is that the
enemy I don't want to fight I'm a
pacifist I thinkk
these girls are
strong they're going to battle straight
away I will observe for
now
dear we have to kill
interesting guys
first what's that
[Music]
what you are dead die in this world
huh I'm back I made it I'm okay you have
been
reincarnated battle oh I think this is
all a simulation wait you got even
bigger M kill the K the stain King where
is he gone he's over
there h
got but big head and a big heart and I'm
a get away from the fair Maiden you
stain thank you my beautiful
night is that's what you are
oh dear
maybe why do you keep
spawning help
it hurts oh God got look out for each
other nice one very good
[Applause]
Revelation I shouted
it
Revelation it's amazing I'm reading the
words and they are not coming
maybe I I need dramatic music
again maybe it's not maybe that's
why
[Laughter]
Revelation wow
all right cod's down that was
funny
[Laughter]
[Music]
Revelation oh that was
great that was a good timing eh all
right be right back I'm going to sort
this out
[Music]
oh e
monkey s that
let me move myself no
M I didn't set this up to
chat okay okay there we are that'll do
for
now you guys are
[Laughter]
monkey yeah we're going to just have a a
little out of character break
out a character so it's cards down at
the
moment cards down and then we'll have
cards
up again real
soon I'm just going to plop you guys in
the
thing there we
go there's my sweetheart look at
that I return to Monkey no
you're not
[Music]
monkey actually you know what I'll
do actually no I won't do
that I'll do it when I switch
screens I want to make my Minecraft
smaller not full screen just in case
there's a another
little little hiccup cuz then it's
easier for me to see bits and
Bobs yeah how you all doing that was
cool what we saw thus
[Music]
far
H sorry you guys are over there so I got
my back too at the
moment so excited
I guess we found out in
character
that within this realm we can come back
to life
[Music]
wow oh I love that little mustache King
I love
him out a character I love
him I gave him this
voice I was bit confused at first what
voice was going to give him I was like
I want to be like cute
Kawaii yeah it's so cute I love his no
mustache
wow yeah end of episode one thanks for
[Laughter]
watching n this is really cool I mean uh
you know technical hitches are going to
happen especially when this is the first
time something like this is
happening that's how some Productions
are you
know and that's okay if anything it
makes really you know fun moments I
guess funny
moments
yeah let me just check I'll check my
audio whilst we do this
my shell
[Music]
music
hopeful and then Wow music wait is this
the same I put the same music on two
different
buttons wait a
minute no I think they're slightly
different but they're they're just very
similar funny
um
[Music]
battle it is an RP without scarf
Cho I mean especially as I said when
it's the first production and all that
it happens happens in the
theater happens on stage you
know at least we get to chat in
between why is this button not letting
me Fade Out oh there we
go am I late n we're just having a
little a little mini
break uh for a
[Music]
moment okay that one's that one
oh yeah I like
this this tune all these Tunes um all
this music is from epidemic sound
epidemic epidemic sound epidemic
epidemic
EP epidemic
sound
[Music]
uh
epidemic that's
cute gives me Shy Vibes that one
and this one is
[Music]
spoopy Hash not sponsored yeah true
hasht not sponsored thank
you I think the Ser back up all let me
see let me
show me look at the notification
oh yeah
true okay let me just do that I'll just
do it in the
background um
H let me just plop it back to this
music it's
[Music]
po uh cuz I'm going to slightly change
my
Minecraft I'm not going to have it full
screen
anymore I'm going to have
it uh semi full screen I don't
know I think for
now
start Go
Minecraft wait am I already on oh no oh
no I don't want two Minecrafts
[Music]
no Minecraft
doer re yeah got to shout Revelation
[Laughter]
again
[Music]
ration all
right wonder where we
go where are we ending
up is you back to the
Revelation the
revela holy moly this is
[Applause]
loud me out of this box video
settings I don't think I can not make a
full screen
[Music]
us out of these walls man hello
beautiful hello the voice is in my oh my
God oh my God okay we
can't I'll just have to change this
[Music]
here
okay gaming
sorry uh
[Music]
uh we're starting again I mean I don't
mind
rewind Echoes of Forgotten
memories who am I
the world I live
in and more than
anything the people I hold most
dear faced with Oblivion I feel
empty relieved
perhaps
distraught I do not
know so much I don't know and
yet that bright
light it calls to
me go toward the light
oh yeah I remember this look at those
pretty
lights it's beautiful why do I feel like
I've been here before strange what kind
of name is go yeah that's a pretty bad
name very rude kid strive to not be so
rude that was very rude and you said it
out
loud I guess I'm being
ignored that looks like the pink one I
met that pink one is very rude that pink
one is quite rude
saying someone's name out loud and
dissing it and then ignoring me how very
[Music]
nice no wait let me turn you up uh you
want you turn me you want to turn me
down that's what it is rejection
rejection at first
sight it seems to be fair I also cannot
hear that
flirting of place is
there it's a floating
egg
strange I'm sure let me here fa I don't
know why but the word lesbians comes to
mind the Privacy hello the privacy
H bestl
Castle you what are you doing
here look of Outsiders around you about
you
even just suddenly
goes wait could it be
SH word to his
majesty the heroes have arrived at the
sanctuary R
away he's so
cute this is the ruler of this
land oh welcome Heroes uh the gods who
who brought you here have informed me
that you remember not about your own
names
a side effect of travel between worlds
no
doubt uh This Must ALL come as a
surprise to you but harken well it was I
who summoned you
here you see an
unprecedented Calamity now threatens our
world it is so Earth with corruption and
driven us from our homes
this blighton land now gives rise to
creatures of Shadow known as
stains this Kingdom of liist and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us
leiston but should the Calamity be left
unchecked it is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire
world faced with this Prospect I scoured
the ancient texts for a way to combat
the Calamity and therein I found
one the ritual of hero
summoning you who hell from another
world have been summoned here by me to
become the saviors of
Libby only you have the power to save
our
world and so I ask Will
you y y your
majesty what is it a great host of
stains is broken through our defensive
line
no we are rushing to mount a defense but
the situation is D Your Majesty we must
get you somewhere
safe honey who are these
strangers
oh oh what say you Heroes will accept
this Des
Desy there is a great power within you
will you use it to save us to save our
world oh I
see
the sound going to give
me ring n
r it seems these maidens are following
me Fate has pulled us apart oh I guess
they same path why you got a zipper in
your back he being R
and
your I will you to the
king you're unlike the other great great
great
grand
[Music]
will
Captain call Captain can't hear you all
the way down here
[Music]
just call me Shakira just call me
Shakira my
goodness that
[Music]
one Fair M and how have you faced
through that
theol do you mean I am you are one you
are fused I was about to say SMS I am Ru
trigger something ru
right you are rubius it seems you have
eaten a fair Maiden
with
newbies the dialog
is I came here to tell you that you yes
are The Lost Child of her of our family
what I mean I don't know who I am you
are my my father who are you
mother the
daughter
that
grandmother's second
cousin who's this little guy
daughters I think you your I I all I
know is about my name and and now I have
found family this is glorious I know how
they move you must protect the I I will
for you father
cousins I will do it for
you K The
Bu
it's could I potentially be
a ah yes a
foe ow that hurt just put a bandaid on
that boo
boo got
silly Arch silly AR ah well done blue
Maiden a very large
vehicle down you
go
ah that one that one is strong it
seems let's
go I'm Tiding him I'm Tiding him worry
not
be there small ones
too be careful I'll protect
you no no no no you don't yeah I can see
why you might feel bad aren't you also a
dog
yeah good oh gosh we must
help defeat the
king I'm smack watch watch he's jumping
in the air watch out okay okay okay I am
moving back
in I must go over this way I have been
injured away
fou yeah get
him
huh I am I am alive or maybe not maybe
I'm dead
Revelation
H what is this weapon I
[Music]
hold revelation
stain host has been
rooted
routed
uh you fought Brave bravely kind Heroes
I pray you are not injured
that Mighty armored one must be their
leader the stain King that guy has a bed
I'm going to give him a
wizard that be his voice
now if only I knew what his line was a
moment ago I would have give I would
have said
[Music]
it well I see why they call you Heroes
we'll be in the right pickle without
your help wow
well I'm glad I was here
H we sustained minim minimal damage
thanks to your Valor our kingdom is in
your deth thank
you I must hasten to inform His Majesty
of our Victory will you accompany
me
sure I
[Music]
shall we should have a royal audience I
heard the news though we called upon
your you suddenly uh you Rose to the
occasion you have my deepest
gratitude I think he is invisible this
king is mighty
powerful what interests me most however
is the strange strange power you
manifested during the battle with which
you are able to defeat the
stains where is he is he behind ch
that power May well be the key to saving
our world from
[Music]
Annihilation Accord to Heroes the power
came from them like a forgotten memory
when they spoke on a word
revelation but once they use this around
the state host it seems that power
vanish Without a
Trace well it's a bloody brilliant is it
so what are we supposed to do the next
time the stains attack
revelation we must uncover the secrets
of the phenomenon if we are to Prevail
against the
Calamity many questions remain but the
one thing is certain the kingdom of
listol still stands today thanks to
you here so Heroes I ask of you once
more will you lend your strength to save
listol from
ruin
sure Mars on behalf of orist I thank
you we are blessed to have you your Aid
kind
Heroes allow me to introduce the four
Great guilds which are responsible for
ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity The
Haven nobody there The Haven for Curious
where knowledge and creativity are
valued above all the Scarlet
wand everybody's invisible they're all
quite powerful
the
home the
FR my they are Mighty I don't I sorry I
just couldn't pay attention cuz you guys
just appeared from
nowhere the sanctum of healing where the
spirit of empathy and devotion thrives
the kulan
cup the beacon of righteous and loyal
where great threats are faced an even
greater courage the Jade
sword one of these guilds will become
your home during your time
[Music]
here Beyond this door lies the room of
Truth therein the will of the ancestors
shall decide your
guild introspection is a a vital step to
the road of Enlightenment Exel Ste as I
always say ever higher
a time to roll the dice eh been seeing
some of you locked down at the chamber
coin Guild
all let us save this world
together the room of Truth awaits go
forth with
Valor it seems I am
moving the room of truth I see step on
the platform and
receive the will of the ancestor
I
see
okay what is your will great ancestor
amidst the Raging currents of the heart
seek the peaceful Cru and
flow Jade sword
[Music]
wow armed with thee an noav will seek to
defend the soul of
Jade I
shall if that is your will
mhm enigmatic
recollection yeah little bit I like you
talking a little bit
hello yes I Elizabeth and you are my
enemy enemy enemy I don't know my wait
what an enemy what's your
name I guess I I got to pick a name hold
on let me ask the voices in my head
what's a good
name's what's a good name guys I got
friends and stuff
so are you also part of the Jade sword
Jade sword that's
me and you are fair
Maiden Fu waa mhm I see I see and you
all I got a name what's your name John
Watson you call me Watson
John see wat it's from earlier is it
name wait are all of you oh yeah I met
you both of you that's a big knife oh
it's not a knife it's called a
scythe Callie has a
farmer uh farmer no I think Reaper so
yeah farmer but farmer of souls maybe a
sweaty Reaper spooky sweaty hey I'm not
sweaty jeez Out Boy Oh you guys have
really long
fingernails yeah you're right you going
to clip
those're shs oh oh I see so they all
your weapons I all I have
is wa how' you do that
strong oh it won't use again I guess the
magic is only 10
place that was a big sound wow
and this is Jonathan
uh this is your weapon
Jonathan don't watch it's a bubble
blower or something who are you going to
hurt with that a bubble blower uh I can
smack people in the head hey I will
defend myself nice Dodge that was a
test I'm a Reaper so I'm strong too a
Reaper I see yeah and your name is
Reaper
no my name is Mor K but you can call me
cie that's what the the bone people in
in my chat say the Kia people yeah
that's what they say stay back
though should I give them my true name
well when I came here
these do anything can we to
them imagine it does I mean never
show Scarlet
[Music]
nice it was indeed cool I'm GL I have
you guys on my team you're so
powerful well I imagine you are also
powerful Jonathan if you are part of uh
the Jade
sword yeah maybe I think I have to level
up a little
bit you can challenge your friends the
walk DS here at the arena I don't want
to fight yet we work SP might be fun
[Music]
aain yes that could be cool test our
strength against each other very true we
could we could
[Music]
train I suppose we're all in the same
Guild since we're all here in green so F
oh yes the
ancestors bestowed upon me the Jade
sword and we have to I imagine that is
why you here too but your sword is
red yes uh that's kind of weird
maybe
sword uh maybe they ran out green swords
maybe that is why I mean red quite suits
me I think uh so I think so too but I
guess if it was green it might be like
uh Christmas colors or something gu that
might be weird you look nice why why do
I get excited when I hear the word
Christmas am
I arena live together now we live
together with people we don't know
[Music]
we live together we y wait where's our
beds yeah do we have like a a place to
this
is
wow
amazing Quest board right he said yeah
we
got maybe it's out
here du
yes we shall defeat the sa using the map
I'm going towards the quest Master did
everybody sorry we're trying to look for
the quest board but I have the map here
we could go this way oh you do all right
the way Jonathan wower woman all right
yes Jonathan wait I think everybody
else's
names I am
Elizabeth oh Elizabeth
are you bow
bow I don't want to be on my own don't
know I don't like it it makes me upset
do not worry Fair puppy I shall protect
you we will never leave a guildmate
behind I will not leave you
alone on the oh you only but a few steps
away do don't worry I want to be a few
steps away I want to be by your side
okay okay from here on out
I will promise you I will remain by your
side bow bow okay oh it's morning wait
where's kie did you find the quest board
oh find the quest board I don't
know that was very
cute I can you want me to fluffy fuzzy
ones are very
sweet my heart hurts me because I can't
do
directions I really
can't
wow this
place
people thiss like a
quest oh
yes a good
eye a good eye you have what what is
your name sweet one fuzzy one theying
look at
that look at this look at this oh my God
your sword is way bigger than mine I
don't know I mean it's not about I think
it's not about size I imagine I I don't
think I was supposed to find you guys
it's about how you use it of course in
battle for the sake of improving our
relationship going
on her life
speak to your gu I mean I I I've awoken
only an hour ago I don't really remember
what so Jonathan you have spoken to
the The Guild
Master sound not I want to help
people reapers are supposed to help are
what team are you guys
hello there we of the I must go back to
our Guild and speak to the Guild Master
I don't
know
Elizabeth yes that is I Fair
[Music]
Maiden she's quite
beautiful whatever
[Music]
I'm glad I know the
way I was nearly
trapped is this you for the king for
leesta yes I
agree where's the Guild
Master oh there you are you were here
this whole time
sir you were here this whole time I
think it's because everybody was
surrounding you that I did not see you
not not calling you small or anything
uh I mean you're all quite small you're
all anyway
anyway greetings Brave hero this is the
headquarters of our Guild the Jade sword
and I am the Guild Master
veridus though you had barely set foot
in our world you agreed to lend your Aid
to the defense of liista liista pistol
for that you have our deepest gratitude
henceforth you will be working with us
to repel the stains and save the
world but first you ought to familiarize
yourself with this Kingdom and learn how
to accept and perform
Quest out in town you'll find a quest
board please go there and speak to the
quest Master mayhaps you can explore the
town while you're at
it right I sh oh so that's what you said
to the to the puppies and the uh and
Jonathan yes and and
such I
see
my guess we make our way over here
again this is a very nice
town that arena is gosh
H I'm going to put these over here I do
not want these
out a radio in my
pocket I see a map a magical
toone I
see I see I see summon SE to help you
Traverse long
distances I see
oh press T and then hover
over now press t
t I do not like tea how do I
accept think I don't
[Music]
like post Js andest
I have to talk to the GU master I ski
them wa wait wait this is I
just do you know how to can you tell
Nissa how to there we go I don't
know I have done it correctly but I
missed what he has
said don't I'm so sorry I missed what
you have said guil Quest
Master maybe F us
Maybeck complete the quest and sweep to
the quest complete the side quest and
then speak to the quest
Master how does one find our
Quest um I don't I'm not sure I couldn't
find oh wait I see it I see it now we
got to go this way
I think we're going to use our horse to
get there faster nice idea horse let us
ride Elizabeth is
[Music]
happy
a some reason I I have memories of
riding a horse uh yes same problem but
she got in somehow
right over this this way Elizabeth do we
do I not need to accept a Quest from the
board or is it that we are I wonder
because we all accepted the quest but
does that mean that well maybe you
should go ahead and accept the quest
just in
case is there just one up
here if you if you do the the uh the
right click on the board it should come
up if not you haven't finished talking
to the quest Master
then oh yes I see it materials needed at
the Smith see I see the Smithy and my
master says we're running low on raw
materials
okay ah Quest accepted I see great let's
go to the Smithy then
right away we go um who's the one with
the map it's not
me
yeah
so well we shall Venture forth and
see uh where it leads us
yes where is
[Music]
Jonathan
Jonathan sorry something came over me to
say it in that manner
uh oh yes so fast oh there you are you
got to talk to this guy here oh let's
put
is this the Smithy how does one
do how does
one how does one put away their
speed ah yes I see now we got 100 coins
just for talking to this little can I
talk to youin Talking
cool wow easiest cash I ever
made Rich I'm sorry
s do not worry about the horse that just
appeared in your face what's this what's
this what what's this oh great you saw
the question I posted well the St could
you bring over 10 oak logs there are a
bunch of trees not far outside town that
you can
chop what you're the
apprenti I'll wait outside getting busy
hello not a fan of big crowds
Jonathan let's the I think me and
Jonathan are going to be good
friends all right shall we go to the FL
I think the gate is that way right we
have to go to the that does look like
the
exit wait where did they
go what go to another location yes go
yes oh
yes oh we're outside now go to another
vation oh hey enemies enemies enemies
out oh my
gosh
this not the bread use
this get
Theon I'm not sure I like the way they
they
cry we shall rid the lands of disdain
the the St clean the stains C yes we
should have
I yeah get get some
exp right getting exp what is exp we
need Oak
right yes we need need
materials seems these trees grow very
fast again uh Fair Maiden maybe uh using
a sword for a tree might not work uh yes
that is a good I a do be here I still
figureing it out sword is good
mhm well you're very very brave to use a
sword on a tree these trees seem to grow
back very fast Fair Maiden they do trees
where have the logs I don't know where
the logs are are we getting logs H I'm
going
to he scared
me of course yes the fluffy one is The
Fluffy one is
confused the tree has consumed
me uh they not get anything for
that get
anything probably not need I
would stain is quite cute and it is
sleeping
[Music]
oh I have I have a work in
it where's my
sword my
sword
my will you die
I'm
sorry it also seems I am not I am
further away from knowing who I truly am
I was told that rubius was part of my
family and I am not part of Rubio's
Guild I'm going to
[Music]
die I must eat I must consum this bread
I just get
these
wonderful all right is a battle you
[Music]
want oh gosh there's more of
them there is a lot of them uh the
stains
uh a fair Guild
Mates is still stronger
I I'm sorry that
sheep yes nice we work well
together nice job though very nice
job well I I have 10 I have 10 logs do
nice yes all right let's turn it our
let's let's go finish this
Quest wonderful
[Music]
right over here this one wait who is
this look at the
map ah this
[Music]
way Hello whoa cool swords
is this the Smithy
yeah I am can't get to the
door you're not wait you brought the
logs
yeah bring you bring you more materials
he can make all sorts of tools and items
for you I can't talk to
him I
see complete this craft a wooden pickaxe
at the SMI I'm sorry about why won't you
let me talk to him stone
tools you brought the stain I have
stained
slime how do I give the planks into SS
from your invent
how sticks seem
useful make all sorts of tools and items
for you
wooden
shovel okay you needed certain things
like 20 coins three Oak planks and two
sticks what do I
do um
H oh oh oh maybe I can make the sticks
myself
now we can craft them from inventory
what was I supposed
oh but said did I make it
PL somebody else just
did all right green
if you bring over 10 oak logs there's a
bunch of trees not far outside the town
that you can chop outside of the to okay
let's try all right I figured out how
you make a stick uh well I have a
crafting table if we would wish to use
really oh that might work too but you
can also do it in your inventory can you
that's not planks first and then sticks
planks first
sticks I made a pickaxe I made a
plank and then two planks makes a
stick so they wanted us to make the the
axe and the shovel and you got to make
it in your inventory and then give him
the materials does he want the planks
make it in your inventory you can make
sticks in your inventory by using two
planks yeah just them on top of each
other like one on top one on the
[Music]
bottom I don't think I can fight again
until I have something to eat though we
should definitely eat
something like bread sticks they're very
excited about making
sticks well they uh puppies do I feel
like I should move here I think I got a
stick and yeah true enough how many
sticks does he have I am a member of
Jade's sword after all so I'm going to
put this here what do you
want Jade sword huh inventory is very
full now I don't know about my
place those two are very
silly that one's very
smart wonder
she's hope we can be
friends okay
I bought one sorry that's supposed to be
in my
[Laughter]
brain I also bought one I thought I was
making it I thought we were supposed to
make
it I feel like we can actually use
it maybe we can make one how do I make a
pick I have a pi I
maybe not uh yes it seems we
cannot you got to buy things fair and
square got to buy them from him like
normal humans yes humans buy things with
money
oh this I know is a fact our Quest or do
I don't
know
well I maybe I have to turn in the quest
then do we go back then
oh yeah to get the coins huh the side
quest and speak to the quest Master I'll
the quest master I need to
get we
Cobblestone how do I make
ax I purchased
everything oh that's fun that's
fun in my brain laughing
does anybody have any more
Oaks especially if you need
coins everybody have their
pickaxe complet I
see so confused one
[Music]
second oh you have to trade oh yeah make
sure that you trade with the the uh the
charge Quest trade I thought we had to
buy from him we have to trade too I
understand yeah both you trade your
coins you have
enough every time you buy
something you are
conducting the voices in my head are
speaking to me I wonder if they could
tell
me all right Quest Master but maybe we
need to do another Quest I'm not sure
okay
at
thise if you bring
theal wooden I
made it seems I should talk to the
apprentice
TR is this all of our money am I am I
using all of our okay I do not think so
my money has not decreased I think
that's your money want to talk to me I
have your wood how much money do you
have three craft a wooden pickaxe at
the I'm richer than you three
ha build a purchase don't have the
required
materials collect 10 Oak speak
to create a
Wen that's what that means that's so
shallow is so shallow
it seems I have been
forgotten
know Elizabeth did you finish the quest
I have traded oh
hello hello I'm not I'm supposed to get
cobblestone now yeah let's go get
cobblestone
puppies Fair puppies have
you have you been asked to get
cobblestone and
money you have not we can use so have
you traded I'll talk to The
Apprentice wait
no oh oh oh speak to the
blacksmith okay okay okay he gives me a
new Quest I've created the wooden
pickaxe from now on when you find new
material
stop are you okay now fuzzy one I think
so I don't know though brandish your
pickaxe and let us see oh yeah let's see
your pickaxe
now swing it from side to side side side
to
side pickax
pickaxe oh no that's that's an
axe that is an axe it's a different
weapon of mass destruction what that is
an axe it is a different weapon I'm
going to trade with you that is not one
you pick your nose
with is quite foul it's quite foul I
don't really like
I have the pickax oh okay is it in your
inventory I but then it didn't work I
feel like there is a saying to do with
picking your friends nose or you're
picking your friends but not your
friends noses I don't know something
like that that's okay we got get
cobblestone to finish the quest follow
me follow me I I
don't Scarlet
wand Scarlet wand they'll figure it out
I don't know why but when they say
Scarlet it makes my ears perk hm oh true
is that part of your name red one I
don't know maybe it it was a
nickname cuz it says e blood
flame above your head but you aren't my
friend blood flame H people keep riding
their horses upon me oh I wish they
would
cease but watch where you going days no
manners watch where you are plopping
your horses
something something defer you must
respect those legendary horse girls oh
wait they don't hear us do
they hey I'm just saying I've heard of
your
kind excuse me you picking a fight you
must Spar if you would like to spar you
must come over to the Jade sword area
okay they're gone exactly you're gone
that's all right you know people talk a
big game I was getting excited to defend
themselves I thought they knew going to
SP yeah some people can can talk a lot
of s word but they can't actually take
it night
time I'm ready to M
whenever oh that's okay this F will have
enough materials by chance to make a
trade box oh yeah Quest Master she can't
open Quest
master master you know
how you should just write uh let's see
right click when you talk to the quest
or the blacksmith
person fluffy one the
Smithy where did she I thought I heard a
bow bow from
afar this little guy where she oh oh it
seems I heard the bow bow from afar
inside the fuzzy one's
brain it seems they are connected so
like so well as a pair that I can hear
The Fluffy one out of the fuzzy one as
well I have I have wow such power I
wonder if all our Guild could be able to
do this one day that would be very very
helpful so with oak logs then you make
Oak
planks I'm not hearing voices voices in
my
head do not be
silly brought some talk my mouse you
should be able to make you stone tools
give it a
try yeah talk to okay
talk to him she has a lovely voice
Cobblestone and sticks okay will to them
the blacksmith's a
prin oh I see okay now I can talk to I
do not know why but I wish to monitor
this one now you okay I think I finished
complete the
quest for some reason I cannot take my
eyes off
there finished the
quest I don't want to talk to him then
right right as we were losing
hope I need stop looking I wonder what
would suit you best cobone next I'm
probably use your I not blushing voices
in my head I I it I'm observing ah
another one that has caught my eye for
some reason I just really want
to monitor this one this
one those two fig out what is wrong I do
not understand okay okay why was I
supposed to talk to the blacksmith then
to buy the this is
more okay why can't I just use this on
the stone maybe it would get let's see
your pickax let me see that thing that's
oh that's not a pickaxe it's a horse are
we going to go somewhere can unless the
horse's name is pickaxe we're not
leaving until we see your pickaxe we're
not leaving until you show us your
pickaxe young
lady all right we're ready let's go get
cobblestone off we go
[Music]
[Laughter]
onast you got to beware the enemies
though because I haven't had a meal in a
long time okay I'll get off my I'll
protect yous like it isn't oh that stuff
can't be
broken away with me oh it's turning into
a different color it seems you can't
continue to line
it it sounds like it's going to blow up
it does doesn't it I I hear the too and
it it does frighten
me
[Music]
you up here what that can we get that
get get get
okay okay I now I'll use my pickaxe okay
o lots and lots of
Cobo I think probably 10 once
again if only we could uh have this
stain as our Noble Steed it is very
cute although I do not like it when it
cries gosh
[Laughter]
ah it's it's war cry Jonathan it is but
its war cry think of it that way it is
trying to attack us so
cute it's his war cry rabbit
[Music]
perish what Jade sword is all about we
shall become
strong yeah
together if if we survive we will
survive and as long as I know how to
love I know I will stay alive I don't
know why that came to mind
strange oh yes it would make good song
lyrics I
[Music]
agree why was this one so
difficult my goodness I need two more oh
there's a rabbit
cute
ooh one more for
luck let's
go they so
cute I want one look over here
let's
go my St
woo oh my God three
is what what what wait that's my
name fiden you seem to want to have a
fight with everyone you come across okay
do I look cool like
[Music]
this thus far we have known each other
you have always seemed cool or looked
cool
yes did you guys turn in your quest
no that's the voice
okay oh
nice oh well that's it
then well
oh it seems they are gone
againa seems my guild mates have left me
you have your Cobblestone we can go back
to the Guild Master get your coin and we
can be rich it's not like I miss the bow
bows or anything yeah I still have I
still have a lot of cobblestone that's
all right we'll need it later maybe
maybe I'll find him
oh
hi oh yes I I
yes have you got another another
Quest oh we're going to go to the shop
keeper but beat it has to be after you
submitted the quest at the quest oh I
see
I don't know why that sounds familiar
but which way was the oh there it is
right on my nose it's right over here
under my
nose come find out yeah we speedrun all
of this I bet maybe we could go to a
dungeon how you accept a dungeon you
please don't accept yeah I want to fight
in a dungeon with you guys and see how
good you are did you pick up another
Quest
oopsie
that's can you deine it accep
it I was going to pick it up after
visiting the shop buy bread from him why
don't we pick up the
Elizabeth something for us I'm a little
confused because it just gave me the
option of getting another Quest unless
it's oh the quest Master sorry why do
you have a raw pork
chop
I talk to the quest leader
now we waiting time when I have a look
around town there's money find shoping
items
start
500 500 every 500 500 smackaroonies
wanted to go oh
yeah time to buy something okay I'm
hungry let's go I'm going to die if I
don't eat something oh please don't do
that that's bad for you kill the king C
considering
[Music]
I hey leave my friends alone she wants
to kill the king Jonathan would never
kill the king Jonathan is part of the
Jade
sword talking about
teamm excuse me small one stay away from
my guild
member
EXC excuse me your gu excuse me excuse
me excuse me excuse me excuse excuse me
excuse me you don't talk to a GU member
like that your guild member was talking
to my guild member
first friend
that my guild member wanted to hurt the
king my guild member would never want to
hurt the king we are part of the Jade
sword and we are
loyal
loye your father's a hamster and your
mother smells of
elderberries excuse
me vinyls hey
[Music]
hey it seems they're
crying listening will they even find
me I am from I can't talk about this
right now why don't you guess
I don't know you are too
evil Amber no Amber you are correct you
are correct I am from
Amberg disgusting yes disgusting I am
from that
place disgusting yes Amber is
disgusting yes do
not do not ever interact with Amber I
agree don't talk to us don't talk to us
do not shush me fa maen or else I will
shush you in a moment don't I know a way
to shush
you excuse me the air is very loud what
you guys from what you guys
from you
are oh okay thanks now I can report you
guys it looks like there's just a barid
selling potions I love
I love these seats they are made of
chair these chairs are made of
doors I want these chair doors for some
reason I really want to steal them but
that is not the way of the Jade
sword although we are just loyal to our
King I don't think the king will mind
bartender who wants youo if you like to
order something ask to buy made over
there right I
shall
hello instant Health the freak
regeneration speed that show night
vision
cool I want strength
H jump boost
whoa Fair bade do are quite
powerful I will see you
later if you go to a CO swim out 100 PES
dive down until you see the bottom and
then count to 1,000 you'll drown
wow what is up
here
oh that is not what I wanted to click
hungry I'm so hungry maybe we should
[Music]
go it seems my kmes are gone again we go
hunting bring the food back and use
their in there is
I was thinking maybe we could cook us
something have you seen what this B made
sells it is is amazing yeah potions only
potion so I bought that oh well done I
got strength I'm going to go hunt did
you find the shop saw some
food yeah yeah yeah let's go hunting
together shall we I saw a bunch of them
out there y here I wonder if we have a a
a chest that we can store our food and
such in back at the guild here I to
steal oh oh that's probably not a good
idea I'm not sure I'm not sure the Guild
Master would approve stff huh yeah they
might kick us from the kingdom to be
honest huh but we're here to protect
them taking a couple things
as probably continuing the
quest oh boy do we want to go to the the
child I mean do you think there will be
food
there maybe there will be food there
your horse is quite
Gardens I have a small horse
oh where did you want to go cie I I
apologize let's go to the gardens okay
yes lead the way I just wish I had a map
to know where they are Watson was the
map holder I mean we we all have a map
do we not oh yeah that is true I know
how to read
it I have to pull it out let me oh thank
you for saving this town welcome to my
humble little
shop what can we get what can we get all
right all right just give me give give
me the gun give me the gun give me the
gun give me the
[Music]
gune de I didn't ask you think I'm a
free what the heck wait why do I have to
talk to a kid I just want the goods oh
so look for the some of
these people are quite I don't like this
the
blackith you child I see it on the
behind the blacksmith you
guys I just want to buy
stuff you think they know where it is
it's supposed to be here
right hey found the same way from A to
point B I'm embarrassed uh you both
found the way you think they have any is
here are we
allowed what heck berries berries I I
think I hurt a lot now goly you're one
of the heroes boy this must be my lucky
day yeah go could you're free to come
and use them whenever you like what oh
the child pry aces in it my dog to keep
an eye on scare away birds and Stu let
me know if you need more bread you're
one of the heroes boy this is my lucky
day
this
is free to
come building empty you Heroes can build
whatever you like you and can work to
build a right to
stay building or gardening say can I
tell you a secret did you know there's a
place called The
Pit mom says that's allow to go but I he
you can play a really fun game there
you're here I've been to let you in
maybe you can check it out tell me what
theit can I tell you secret you know
there's place called The Pit isn't that
where the Amber coin people
go go to the AR so
away okay did did anybody else just get
a of bread see
what to
Theo what this child is speaking to you
maybe you can go check it out get anyone
else bread no I didn't get any bread I
would have loved to have some bread huh
yo kid where's my bread huh excuse me
did to see you again did you speak to
someone else to be able to speak to this
child I got 64 bread too I did I did
threatening violence does
work why did you hit this you hit this
child and got bread I think no I didn't
do anything like the kid gave me the
bread out of their own free will that's
a lot of bread oh
yeah I will give you head Pats child
what's going
on
best is it that
easy I don't see
anything what are you doing are you just
fing the bushes I thought we were making
a salad yeah Mak so s hi do it really
okay wa where's the
salad
berries what the
heck hey did someone take my berries I
don't get any berries they're for my
salad salad I
scavengers
I salad hey the salad good for you
Violet on
[Music]
the violence all attacking at the same
time it does seem kind of
fun
potato ah yes there is
a much food out here
too
sustenance taking a bath this is the
public bath house uh I'm not sure about
that I'm pretty sure it is but you look
like you're
flying Jonathan yeah you're
flying I'm taking a bath oh is this how
clean that I'm ascending is this how you
take baths in your
realm yeah isn't this normal
um I mean it's
different feel so clean now you should
try it try it
[Music]
ah yes I feel Mighty
refreshed y that was quite dangerous
that was fun was
it
yes oh
melon nice melons
this where we Farm can we Farm here I
don't know I mean I'm uh you know for as
we are you know part of the the Jade
sword and we we protect those in need I
think we should uh you know we're in we
should get our take our sustenance and
uh return yeah I think we have a plot of
land where we can grow stuff oh there we
go
H oh oh oh Jonathan Jonathan Jonathan
careful oh everybody went to the pit
shall we go to the pit yeah I I shall uh
join you okay the pit I think I have
enough o Jonathan Jonathan the berries
Jonathan Jonathan
Jonathan I might die don't do that
Jonathan that's bad for
you and I would be
sge from just some berries I'm a
hero that's
true Jonathan is a hero a very good hero
indeed I've seen her
fight and I've only known her for what
wait is that
5 minutes and I would give my life for
Jonathan
oh here we
are it' be a lot easier if you had some
extra coin is all I'm saying Master
wishes to speak to us oh
don't you again hello come down here to
the pit and play around or
two ever walking out here Penn don't
worry about it is this are they asking
us to do something
shady I don't know like roll the
dice we're going to do like underground
fights I don't know Guild Master wishes
to speak with you please meet him at the
Jade Guild Master that's where we're
from right
yeah maybe what
do not worry voices in my head I've I've
already
realized is that you guys yeah oh oh
looks are you sure that sharks can drown
though that seems
confusing I feel like that's not
something that should happen to G I must
go my own path for a moment
I must get out of here first damn
horse are you sure you do me
okay
goodbye freak out of
here need this potato
I guess I'm on this lonely path
again but this is fine I will see them
again for we are linked
we have a
bond that no one can break but we are
part of the Jade
sword and I have a big
[Music]
sword I don't know where I'm going this
way this way
[Music]
is my sword named
Jade I do not
[Music]
know does it
say thorn of
order
wow it's amazing in this realm the way
they write the names on the
items it's very
convenient Elizabeth pend dragon that
does sound like a nice there has a nice
ring to it is this where the shopkeeper
[Music]
keeps that's
s oh Brave hero thank you for saving
this town in all of our lives
welcome to my shop I've all sorts of
items here I might help you with your
adventuring While others are just nice
to have all you have to do is talk to me
and I'll show you what I've got in stock
and just select what you want to buy
isn't it
easy now I'm afraid I can't just give
you everything for free there make sure
you have enough coin
okay do St by if you ever need anything
or if you just want to keep me company
oh
and there is one more thing I'd like to
tell you about I'm sure fighting stains
all day will be hard on both your body
and your heart so when you're feeling
weary do remember to take care of
yourself have a break and do something
fun you could try visiting the guild
Halls of four great guilds for instance
each of them has an activity you can
participate in many of my customers are
regulars at the arena for
instance when you're tired from
adventuring or simply looking for a
little diversion maybe give some of
these activities a try take your mind of
your quest now and then it'll do you
good if you've some time yet why not
visit the
gardens the children are attending to
them and I'm sure they be joyed to me a
real hero such as
yourself ah
yes yeah right
I shall bid these children hello
[Music]
again I shall bid these children hello
once more and they shall be incredibly
happy of my me I
hero Amber Amber amberin ambercoin
you're right ambercoin disgusting AB
coin I agree e icky don't like them why
are youy why are you doing that you
don't need to be so negative about that
yeah it's only okay when we say I'm just
I'm just so negative about myself and
the Amber Koy I just man I wish wish I
wasn't part of Amber they're poo poo
stinky wait what's wrong you want talk
what's wrong yeah yeah yeah we can we
can we can we are full of empathy we
will totally listen to what's
wrong do you want to join us join
you but I must go speak to the children
the children I go speak to the children
in the
gardens they have children in the Gard
know where they are yeah take us to the
children they're at the gardens this is
this
way do you know do you know how to find
your way of course I do I am of the
Amber coin I
am I know my way money yes I love money
I can't get enough of the gold I I love
it so much Le child does not have any
money
oh well as I am part of Amber coin I
would hate to give them my
money what the heck is this place
anywhere is this your CH is this your
child uh yes that is
Henry
Henry I adopted
Henry ah pit door man that much money
it's easy to adop so many
people p dor thank you you are you you
meant pit dor I'm so happy for you she
likes to bring her horse
inside oh this is interesting
coin h a
bookie do you think they like books make
a bet not today thank okay now you got
it now to the
Gardens do you want me to help
you
bye I must take this PA alone
why did I say out loud that was weird
I'm turning into these people who talk
to themselves out loud where the freak
are these
Gardens yes I feel like gambling but uh
but uh that we'll go
back gambling does sound fun can I go
through here oh my God the whole time
here's me wanting to walk all the way
around like a regular
citizen yeah the freak are these G
freaking
gardiens you know I'm going to use the
horse Noble
[Music]
Ste acknowledge the
voices should I really should I really
acknowledge the voices in my
head I mean
they are the
company that I treasure at this very
moment whil I find these
[Music]
Gardens
gosh I glad
that none of these Fair maidens have the
power to read minds
Garden
D wow nice nice
structure I was there about a moment ago
and I have
forgotten yes
[Laughter]
hello
child ho you the heroes boy this must be
more lucky day all right well the see is
the garden feel free to come and do some
whatever you like I putes in
it in
it in it
what strange wording I but I I like
it don't like Gard you can also try
building there empty dots just pass here
where you Heroes can build where we like
you and your guild mates can work
together to make a white sfty place to
say stop by any time if you want to do
some building or
gardening oh s can I tell you a secret
did you know there's a place to in town
called the
pit yes Mom says Us kid on now to go
well here you can play a really fun game
now you're a hero so I bet they let you
in maybe you could go check it out and
tell me what you
like anyway hope to see you
again speak to the pit
Dorman
well voices in my head you have one
today as we shall be going back to the
pit but
first I Shall
Gather some
Necessities to the pit
H this
way one day I shall know this place like
the back of my hand and it shall be a
glorious
day I think I've taken a long way around
but that's
fine must be the guild where my my
family member lives
that's where I got
stuck
aha I have found
the we shall go to the pit
more
energy lucky lucky lucky lady
oh I got a game for you oh say you're no
no
face H don't tell me you're one of them
Heroes uh what save the town aren't
you want to get rich I know uh uh how
you could uh make a
fortune
uh uh wait don't go I promise ain't
nothing Shady look how about I tell you
something oh I tell you something useful
see I used to run with the Jade sword
before I join the Amber
coin I yes we are alike you and I but I
I tell a Porky pie that I am part of the
amber amber
Guild I know it is quite quite an
amusing Gest
yes ah uh well when when a girl M took
us out to uh un some stains they uh also
taught us how to work as a team
uh just point yourself at the your mate
and right click on uh from there and you
can select whether to invite uh to your
party or trade with her now you can
adventure together or swap items and
coins I see see T is useful didn't I
you'll thank me for it when you're out
adventuring uh I know you you got a very
important Mission and we're all counting
you but it' be a lot easier if you you
add some extra coin is all I'm saying
so if your pockets are ever feeling too
light or too heavy maybe uh come down
here into the pit and play a round or
two and if you ever see some poor s
walking out here penist don't worry
about it that won't happen to you hey
lucky
lady uh are they trust you've had the
opportunity to explore the
town The Guild Master wishes to speak to
you please meet him at the Jade sword
Guild Hall
oh yes yes
sir and that
was ah this
way hello
huh hello M
MOS oh hi oh did you find the lost
Leeson child Amber coin I'm saying good
night to my guild members good
nightwell I'm on leave me alone I'm on
the phone I'm on the
mobile goodbye Jonathan fairy well bye
Elizabeth thank you you too good luck
thank you thank you for for for your
your your your your your your greatness
and your heroicness and
such you too you are
pogi byebye
bye I don't know how the [\h__\h] she did
that red
I have a scythe I want to sit on your
side I don't know why I want to sit on
your
side
what now
what you're you're J
is I am Amber coin amberin yes I a poopy
Amber coin not amberin you lied to me
okay then you're okay well you threaten
your your weapons are uh different sizes
you told me to say it is focused on
dexterity unlike your join you for your
focused on just all bronze but bra my
fair Maiden can you open your magic
tombs and go to
page what a woman and leave your party
whatever party you may be in we are
better than that oh
sorry you swine how dare you say my
brain is Tiny I know this place like the
back of my hand I am very
smart welcome I've joined your
party welcome how do you know this place
like the back of I'm not abandoning
Elizabeth she seems to have made
friends what we are not friends we are
not friends we are not friends so
closely to each other oh no I was but
about to hush her gums she's a traitor
she is a traitor you can hush gums is
supposedly Amber coin but not Amber she
Jade
sword oh my God what was that I just
onward that's how
one I got them I don't know where I'm
going I mean I know this place like the
back of my hand oh yes I need to go to
the
thing it's
fine this
way
onwards H I'm
back I will I'm going back to our gu
sword okay what will you do there our
more money that's what they're going to
do oh yes I love money for I am part of
ambercoin what the
[Music]
ah yeah I was
just tricking the voices in my brain I
totally remembered that the guild was
within the confines of this big circular
Arena ah of course I
knew yes I totally
remembered and didn't just go past this
building a million times because
I totally knew this place was the place
where
I
poofed hello gu
master I see you are returned Brave hero
I hope you familiarize yourself with the
towns and learned about adventuring we
all uh uh lament what has befallen the
lands outside our kingdom the Calamity
and the stains it has born have turned
most of the world into a wasteland you
must be shaken so to suddenly find
yourselves in another world but I pray
you will Aid us in our fight our first
priority is finding a way for you to
regain your powers of re Revelation to
that end I have just received word from
one of our Scouts regarding a possible
lead while investigating the Calamity
near near the plains our comrades
charged Upon A mysterious ancient ruin
moreover they observed from the ruin a
light akin to that of the revelation
which you used to repel the stain
King your words your words St disappear
so
fast Scouts from our Guild are already
stationed at the ruins for further
investigation I asked that you might
join them there and lend them your Aid
go forth with
Valor all
right
one one moment Guild Master I must go
talk to your friend here whilst I
hydrate
oh you might be right voices in my brain
that is what my
guildmate cie spoke
of ah yes the
ruins she do did speak if of
this but I was too busy with those rapid
scalling accusing me of
lying it was but a pory
[Music]
pie ringer on the mobile
radio private
[Music]
it
seems she's but in a core right
now it's fine it's not like I wanted to
call her or
anything it's not like I wanted to hear
my guild mate's voice again
what a beautiful night it is the stars
in the
sky in this realm they
are they are
square everything is
square
even I am
square but do that make me a square
[Music]
I do not
know I should go
Yonder I mean this is a way to check out
the place okay you guys see like that
she just runs at me with a horse every
time how
rude ma'am do you not know how to
control your
horse oh excuse me sorry my horse is a
is quite a um you know Rowdy fella you
see I I don't know how to control
it
obviously I'm I'm talking to I'm talking
to a ambercoin member right now
and this ambercoin member is the same
member that adopted many children and um
and is and loves money I Love
Money loves money she must love money
cuz that's what she says like I eat
money for breakfast you eat money for
breakfast does it does it taste good H
yes that is the uh ambercoin diet oh wow
what kind of um money do you eat every
single for breakfast lunch and dinner is
it different every single time oh yes I
mean uh for breakfast the Smithy I mean
for breakfast we like to have uh uh
copper flakes yes very good copper
flakes yes oh what about silver when do
you eat
silver
Tuesdays B Amber
coin hey get out of here what do you
mean you don't own this place you don't
own this place hey huh hey stay away
from her here stay away from who I was
just I was just asking what her what
nrio was the small one is loud don't
don't talk to don't talk to her she's
like a fake ambercoin I am a real
ambercoin that's not I thought
we Jade sword I
found yes she's Jade sword I
am oh I actually can you read the
room dude you lied to me I thought you
were I thought you were ambercoin you
kept saying you loved money that was
just like a full on size I've been lying
to you this whole time I am part of the
Scarlet wand how dare you dare go I
don't eat money for breakfast I eat
magic coin wait where did your teammates
go oh I have to apologize I was also
lying on her behalf saying that she was
a member of jade sword
yes no she wants to keep her her
identity ambiguous it seems classified
no oh she's a compulsive no oh I also
don't know where she is from you look
the first time I I I met the you were
trying to threaten me
so get your get your hey do you know how
to ride your horse you don't talk to hey
you're gu mate you're both your guild
mates do not know how to ride if they're
horses they always ride it into me you
has your I will make you have you not
seen what I did to your guild mate you
what I'm going to rip off your toes
stick them on your knees and call you
Tony I swear alone you put your sword
away alone she is you put your sword
where it belongs on the ground PVP I can
show you where yes PVP there is would
you like yes there is that's our Guild
the Jade sword I take you to the Jade I
will take you to the Jade sword Guild
what your at the G
it's right this way follow me it's the
big circular place would gu what's going
on all yes what what yes let's
go if you would like
to what
fire fire light the
fire oh they went did they go
in the
freak vo is in my
head I'm pretty sure I'm at the right
place
I guess I'm alone yet
again Elizabeth bloodflame is my name
and I
am the Lone Hero of the Jade
sword and I have big
sword
well I'm pretty sure this is where we go
to spar ah but alas nobody's
here left
side I shall Journey this
[Music]
way
oh I am intrigued
[Music]
wow I said wow
that's better that's better music
[Music]
what a glorious
Place
amazing it must have taken them a long
time to
build imagine this place filled with
people
[Music]
but why even when I am around my
guildmates I feel alone like I've
left a large Arena behind
myself an arena of people
of
roses why do I miss something so much I
have
forgotten maybe one day I shall find
out for now where is my goldate gone
[Music]
why are they already in a
call every
[Music]
time seems there's invisible
barrier my guild mate is always on the
phone
the oh it's cuz I'm opening it with the
thing hello
voice is in my head you are right
[Music]
I'm sorry I didn't do that
sooner with all the hustle and vessel
life
for nice
cloak the voices in my head think I look
quite
daer you know what's funny add a
character though cards down add a
character
um I think before all the hiccups I was
ready in my mind I was like okay I'm
going to put this clo on at the when we
get the
cloaks and
then just
went just went out the
window it's an invisible cloak hey
hello what are you doing all by
yourself well I'm not all by myself
you're
here don't try to you said and you said
you were smart and you said you Excuse
excuse me excuse me yeah you're excuse
what is your quest right now
um who's uh I got to exit the Town Gate
and head to the Plains and speak to um
hastus of the Jade
sword good do you know how to get
there do you know how to get there I do
know you know what why don't you show
me you and your gildo throw your horses
in my face a fake
Amber my assistance you are the horse K
I guess I have no choice you follow
me summon your horse I have summoned my
horse at least I don't at least wow at
least I don't summon my horse in your
face you need to stop horsing
okay I'm just kidding it's this way
uh-huh ah yes yes uh very smart uh okay
it's that
way okay and
then not this way this I actually think
I do know the
way and then we go this way ah yes very
good yes you're welcome what you do
without
ha fools ha I knew the way
here it's true
right I am following Fair
Maiden
no
hey yes and then you kick and then you
lead me to the loud
one test this this
way oh very good thank
you I have to drop this call to give her
a piece of my mind oh there she
is you here what do you mean the loud
one you dis yeah what am I yeah what
what was I thinking what was I thinking
thinking you were the loud one cut her
some slack only I can give
her yeah yeah no I've been bullying her
enough I feel kind of bad she's all by
herself she is she is she good I am not
I have my guildmates in my heart Callie
is in my
heart me yes I'm honored thank you see
she's honored she's in my heart to I
love all kinds of friends so yeah of
course I'm honored hey red
red thing I am
Elizabeth oh Elizabeth red red thing I'm
talking do you not see me talking to
this no I didn't hear you talking red
thing can you apologize to
Jonathan Jonathan Jonathan
with she's very hurt ah it seems she's
making her war
cry underworld we shall secure the
surroundings what am I supposed to do
say Sor I apologize that you are
sad
inv apologize that you were a lesser
being here have some of my melons please
we all share the same goal where I don't
know I'm trying to refer it to you we're
supposed to protect the
land I should some stuff here a it seems
I cannot give you my
melons oh no it's just why are we
talking about the is talking about
melons now
me I
tried these melons are stuck to my hand
what oh never mind I can't I apologize
for not giving you my melons radio in my
hand can I have your melons too I would
try but I cannot give it to
the why why how can you try and and fail
at giving melons I am I I am using the
uh the C muscle musle muscle is not
working oh my
God I'm just going to pretend I just go
oh is this a shared
chest do you have do you see my stuff
initial
for my melons
inone can use it some have reported
hearing a
strange oh good you have to slay 10
stains head to the pl speak to slay tens
then speak to H okay okay I think I'm
almost at the the dungeon Quest
probably corner will be slay 10 stains
ah yes I will slay them I will take this
corner barrel for
me
what I cannot proceed yet just kill more
Corner Barrel is mine
stop okay stains come I
wonder they must have entered the
dungeon
already where is this dungeon it seems I
have some sort of ping slay enough
enemies lag Oh we must I cannot hit them
is
ital oh my gosh
will Dodge and wave Dodge and
wave where's my battle music
[Music]
ah
yes
ow the thing is you have to be in a
party
[Music]
reation
H I forgive you dearest what is your
name I am Elizabeth and you are
Elizabeth I am Jonathan with a
G
yeah we have a we have a Jonathan in our
Guild too but I do not know if it is
with a G
oh wait does that mean you are
gathan no no no it's pronounced Jonathan
maybe
we I
see well gathan I shall give you my
melons another
time I will learn to accept oh why are
you eating your melons in front of
me I just be that way I'm build that
way maybe I can trade my melon with you
to
thee through the power of my empathy I
forgive you I know it must have been
very rough to have fallen in hard
times
ow I've made up with
her ah yes I got the key I forgive you
the underworld key thing I don't forgive
you do yeah shall we what
should yeah i' like you fo I did not
need to forgive you
does everyone have the map I mean not
map does everyone have their key yeah I
think en already entered though didn't
she can we go in I think she's doing it
alone who's doing water
alone up here uh oh I did leave the
party call let me get back
in where is the dungeon anyway oh I can
hear you guys now oh my gosh where you
guys can hear me sorry about
that yeah I got the key um doesa already
enter no oh how do we know how many we
have
slain uh it shows up I think
uh what if we made swords is enough what
if we made two parties of three you
think that would be
good should we buy stuff should we buy
upgrades well we don't really have iron
it shows
up it shows
up
F character what happened to
Kiara what happened to kiar Senpai I can
of
proceed dead
magic T oh the book yeah you're
right okay maybe
not okay do two other people want to
enter the dungeon together
maybe let's enter the
dungeon probably be left
behind only
five yeah but I feel like we should also
what about is she's not in our
party it is
okay yeah I think that would be the best
way I'm A Lone Hero freaking these
little
things I'm tired
this hero is
tired you know I'll come with I'm dying
I'm also dying this hero is also
dying there's area in
there
oh are you with me okay go you say so
way who there they
go okay
okay how many have I
done I'm breaking the four4 how many
have I
done oh
wait you and your comically large sword
it's not comically large it is uh the
right
size no that's comically large
this is how a normal sword looks like
that's not even a normal
sword this is a normal sword excuse
me by I still have
uhit the call hold on a second I need to
slay stains would you like to enter the
dungeon with another one of us we're
going to split the team into three
groups or two groups I think of two
groups of three no
don't split it due to me it's okay oh
you don't want to enter the dungeon
together I mean I I I I I mean be fun if
you want I'd like to enter it with you
but I do not I do not wish to intres no
oh no one Minds yeah they they agree
that
we don't be such a loner freakishly
large sword woman yeah we need to be I'm
doing my
quests Yeah by
[Music]
yourself I was
behind I just
can't are you done with your quest now
no are you done now no she's still slang
I don't know do we do we have to do this
quest to be able to do the next bit or
can or can we just go into
the no if you kill 10 then we we can go
to the next thing Elizabeth yes do you
not have a normal
sword I do it seems my my my my
freakishly large one is is wonder what I
can do with this freakishly
weak yes you only use that for an
ultimate attack I see
Revelation stone sword it
is this one look cool with my my big
sword oh don't go that
way I love killing what why is the one
so weak s right I'm a grim reaper oh but
not you guys I wouldn't hurt you wait
you're a grim reaper they keep killing
them I can't kill I can't slay when they
keep killing them told you oh the Kaya
people we are trying to
get
enter I think she needs to kill to the
guy again stains outside by the way Liz
it won't tell you if you kill 10 you
just got to you just got know how many
you
wait there's one over here I'm going to
go dig for some more stuff wow
yeah I'll go I'll go farm some more
coins while we
wait yes
okay I do not know if I have
slain how dare you hurt my new friend I
have no idea if I slain them I do not
know if it counts when another person is
helped
slaying the stain
I'll kill this one up
here mother
[Music]
trucker now it just told
me ah a key finally
[Music]
there we go
finally oh yeah so how shall we split
the groups the whole
thing I are we all in a
call yeah it might be in a
call where everybody
go I'm sure they'll be
back I was told
I had one more oh one more yeah no i'
I've done it I've done it now but uh it
did the gods did tell
me in the end that's good yes I'm glad
to hear that
yes nobody's riding off into the sunset
oh maybe they're going to shops to
prepare ah that is a good idea
sorry here's the party call I did not
mean to hang up the phone call oh it's
cool my connection I was entering a
tunnel uh the tunnel seems that the
magical connection between our brains
causes it to to drop the call oh
telepathy yeah I'm talking directly into
your head that's a new
word
uhoh yo more enemies die
it's amazing how I can hydrate in my
brain thank you for the head
Pats I'm head the voices in my brain are
head patting my
[Laughter]
brain join them
should I hey should I join them
okay okay awaiting
you yes yes friends are here what
what
what I don't
know the blue Maiden appeared and just
said what what what
what
uh the voice to say yes she needs to
join the party can she join the party I
don't know can six people
join only available to party
leaders party leader would need to
invite
her we'll split into into groups of
three in a
minute party is different than the call
oh okay
I
see also no caps please cly people if
you use all caps I have to get rid of
you it gives me
anxiety and then we split yeah wait I
think
so that's what they say yeah why do they
make such a HS sound when they die where
we're waiting in front of the dungeon
pink lady
red CR lady we just saw we just saw you
pink lady this no we just saw you were
doing something oh yeah I just saw your
most inner thoughts I we saw the inner
workings of your brain know what you are
I don't know what they're talking I know
who you are I know what you are I know
your deepest darkest secret people
watching know everything about I
know all right good night I'm going home
goodbye goodbye I shall as well hello
good night get out of the call hello
signature saw you in a
vision a vision I just want to go in the
dungeon with my friends please explain
the vision what does it mean
talking
me can can I can I can I talk to you
from me why are you hassling my guild M
question stop hassling my guild M you
will understand big up SZ I I have I I
have questions I should get out of here
hey what are you guys doing to my
honorary all
right that's right I'm in the toilet
what do we not know why
after my guild member who is this
pink hello
hello are you also a
puppy I am not a
puppy what are you I am a big cat very
one of those Dangerous Ones she says
dangerous her cat phrase
is a strange
cat I I I'm a I'm a big cat a big cat
well then make a big cat noise then
prove
it wow you are
ferocious I know the rumors is are
true yeah I kill everyone and everything
enter the dungeon if you can enter the
dungeon Fair cat where is the
dungeon oh go oh this is this is this is
the dungeon go oh this is the dungeon oh
oh
yeah that fair cat is
correct okay okay and then we
just Liz let's let us go to the
dungeon you Lett us is in the dungeon
that is
strange okay yes yes all right let us I
am going to go to page four of my
magical Tob okay we can make a new group
and disband this
party yes party
disbanded I'll make a new one then
um who would like to claim your three
two claim your two my
two who my my two CL who wants to join
team claim your two yeah okay oh you
guys yeah oh my gosh they're very
frightening but I'll invite them what do
you mean
frightening I've invited
them
okay Liz who I have forgiven I mean
aren't you also the aren't you also
perhaps like something that might be
connected to this dungeon we have a
cheat code yeah huh I mean I do get a
familiar feeling entering competition
now
invite Miss
Liz out of the radio I suppose so a new
radio call then yeah oh okay okay is
everyone ready standing by to enter the
dungeon oh there we go stand by we're
going to do amazing guess I will see
this
stand faster than the other teams yeah
yeah we will enter the dungeon no
players standing by you got to stand we
got to ready up do we have to ready
first yes there we go okay
oh underworld dungeon let's go it'll be
so
easy this underworld a domain of
boundless oppressive Darkness as feared
as it is avoidable it holds the final
resting place for every creature that
walks the Earth yet even in this realm
of the Dead where are those who live and
call home I see Naro
do finding the final resting
place
uhhuh guys GG
I'm entering radio call yes enter radio
call so we're not lost pull your your
radio out and join the party call dear
Liz yeah we're good okay does not look
like it is this
way we must go forth this way
wow I've seen a lot of people die
today have sensed it I've sensed in my
head run let's go we are not going to
die
wait is is that one of those transport
teleportation things we got to go to
then looking things maybe we reach it
over here let's see yeah someone can
Photoshop underworld dungeon bracket
svage
yeah everyone rank whoever did the best
new checkpoint on checkpoint
oh
okay they're going to is there going to
be
there going to be monsters I think so
like this place seems like a good place
to fight wide open space I guess we
should go
open oh she was behind us I'm here go
towards the oh you are up there no I am
I am down in the
lava I am perishing jump off oh yeah if
you're on the lava block you can sneak
and you won't take damage what unless
you're in the liquid one then
pray and then you can get this
[Music]
checkpoint this wonderful beautiful
checkpoint and then it seems that we are
going to engage in
parkour I am now going to engage in the
art of
Parkour I cannot I can't click this oh
you have I think it's just activated on
my team basis probably I see it
activates in your brain
[Music]
waves horrible Lantern very
nice got a portable Lantern yeah I
bought it at the shop oh what a good
purchase I will have to check the shop
next
time are you okay I'm fine of course I'm
fine I am a a hero are you frightened
mayhaps no I am never frighten
you can make this job I'm hungry I
believe I'm
hungry hello hungry I thought your name
was
Liz all
right let's
go this way ping
and and
up and H
and you're doing very well I do not need
to hear that from you loud
one no what thought that we have made up
we've made a men no you are doomed to
fall you are doing so well we're almost
there yes we're almost there wait if we
at the next checkpoint does she revive
at the I am at the
checkpoint I wonder if she has to unlock
at her does if I get this do pop up on
your screen
too new checkpoint
unlocked try try dying dear dear Liz oh
okay if you say so try try dying and see
what
happen ah oh hey hey this is a Str you
are
magic we don't need this as a Strat I
was just testing your heroicness that is
all your
strength it was du to our strength that
this was possible yes I was seeing if I
could trust
you worry not I see it I see the
checkpoint Over
Yonder that was almost
dangerous danger is my middle name is it
maybe I don't know what my name is
you which way is it this
way I'm trying to make eye contact with
our next I think we're supposed to go
towards the
thingy so this way this way
yes can I make a job
no it hurts it's like you
never was just right behind Castle how
sad it seems she has perished in the
cast won't know what hit it once I'm
done with this
Castle oh it's going to regret standing
here in the name of
empathy oh we got to climb from this
side this
way
woo this way
where is it where's the entry point I
see it I see her see
empathy where are you oh my God that
that was almost y
okay it is safe up here there is nothing
to be scared
of I'm Not Afraid here we good yes not
be the checkpoint yeah yeah checkpoint
obtained so worry not okay we good you
do not need it though you are so good at
climbing like a mountain I've learned
well Channel your mountain goat Channel
your mountain
goat is that good make sure you're not
hungry I'm eating
bread
oh man I love bread all
right ready let's adventure oh w oh
checkpoint do you think something will
kill us in here where shall we
go oh zombie oh my be gone foul Beast
what is this very dark room they red
zombies is this a
maze we lost a knife what is that no we
lost Liz I'm behind go okay
okay I secr
[Music]
zombies oh I found it I think I lost you
guys uh no you are closer I'll go back
to
you don't worry I'll make sure these
zombies don't hurt
you this
way oh my God the hold thing same
frantically oh they have different Stars
oh are you okay wait they have keys
maybe I have to collect them I'm
hurt are you okay I'm getting surrounded
by zombies there there there's many of
them I got
you it
hurts wait I think we're supped to
collect the sh Keys which one how many
should we collect
um so far I have star triangle and
circle
okay and where do we put
them it
burns I also have a star two triangles
in a
circle okay I don't know how many you'll
need so maybe we can no I'll throw this
out okay all right you guys
good um I'm okay I do not know where you
are
what does this
say this is
nothing oh there's a keyhole okay okay
okay wait I can't put oh oh I just got
to click the thing wait we got to find
Liz though I'm here I see her name she's
right behind us okay let's go to the
next
area hello oh the recycling V chest I
what a joy
day wow thing great what is your name
waa me um
n
Nino yeah can call me Nino
Ena
[Music]
n Nina
Nina n there's a beautiful name thank
you we just call you li you may okay
okay do you prefer something
else
um
H oh oh is this a puzzle as you are
offering
[Music]
H oh nah just Liz is fine no just Liz
okay yes I don't know why but your
majesty came to mind but oh supposed to
light up everything every single one if
we click frantically this is what I
learned in my my my past is that a
puzzle can always be solved through the
bruest of forces
[Music]
umm you know
yeah you know what I
mean this is going my tummy is
shook oh I did not mean to kick you from
the party you stood in front of my face
rejoin come back
please please rejoin the party I did not
mean to I did not me
do that I was so please please G well
gin for the first time and then they
leave me alone in this click any of the
blocks is it only you who can click I'll
accept oh for now maybe it is only me
that can click it
well I'm I hope you can click it I'm
clicking I'm clicking it I used to be
able to but now I can't oh why exiled so
you were clicking them yeah I I can
click it oh maybe maybe it's a party
thing maybe cuz I accident did the
thing do we even know what we're
supposed to do
here apparently other my I think after
that parkour my my T is turning the same
thing happen
oh why would they who would put a puzzle
inside of a put my on a
bug who would dare do such a
thing well it's all you let
see oh
no oh no
wa you know we need your we need your
Superior brain
power should I maybe get out of this
world and then return maybe maybe that
over work I don't know if it maybe
return to your world of the of this
world hopefully it does not okay
hopefully it does not I'll be right back
crossed
[Music]
oh welcome back I am here can you click
it hold on it's still
loading
okay oh I can click it now y
huzzah
huzzah thank
goodness hold on should we just have one
person do it at a a yes I I entrust this
to you you can do it I entrust this task
I don't lady
n not
smart what you are so wise
why is beyond your
years I think you would do better than I
did the
first I don't know what happened so much
was
happening so close I see it in my mind's
eyee I see you solving this
yes you are getting so close to solving
it
I was just out of character I was just
switching my top just
then for
uh something lighter I'm just too hot
because right now the music in my my
brain wav is making me Jolly but this is
a tense situation this is very I put my
fan on now so that that should be better
it's annoying because the with the
motion sickness
because
like I really want to join
in I'm having a lot of
fun but then half the time I'm like ah
my tummy my
tummy be scared to take a break ah yeah
I mean
I'll do I I'll I'll finish up after
this add a character I'll just finish up
after this
yeah not this dungeon is done if it's so
close so much of it is lit up my brain n
you are of the biggest of brains you are
you are so I believe in the believe in
me who believes in
the you are this moment
oh oh oh my gosh what did you work so
close lady Ena what lady Ena what did
you what did you work out oh I don't
know oh you don't know okay I thought
you worked it out I believe
not thought I
did okay feel like you it
better I don't know
is this the part where people took the
longest
probably this must have been what caused
people to falter for so
long I think I'm I'm just trying to
figure out
like what
is what is the what is the connecting
thing cuz I just I mean I just realized
you can you don't have to click one
that's not on you can click got this you
can click one that's
on you get
it vo is in my head how did how did you
figure it out going on in your
head
nothing it is so full of thought that
you only think that way but I'm sure
that you are thinking many things I am I
can't yeah you you are thinking so much
allowing me I cannot
join H it seems I cannot help with the
puzzle you may have to disconnect your
Consciousness and come back just as Ena
did oh what
completely yes well you will have to
return to to your
conscious your default state of mind and
then return to this body
okay I'll try as
in
um
in appar according to my scriptures that
it reads disconnect from the game and
and return and re Rec I'll be right back
and reconnect to the
game whoa
what what do
[Music]
that I'm starting to remember
yeah but did you work out how you how
you solved
it we saw Hollow live and then it was
solved what I think H live is a big clue
yeah it made the letter H and then she
solved it immediately after
yeah well I guess we can go ahead I do
not understand now we can continue we
are's is it telling us we are Hollow but
we are
alive yes maybe we are alive the maybe
we'll find the answer at the end of this
place
yes there must be something
here join my telepathic radio channel oh
yeah we to get l oh we're here
okay I ins your brain you're in my brain
I'm in your brain bring
wa W what is that
skull what does that mean I don't know I
feel looking at me like feel
danger oh no whatever is ahead of us
wa what the what huh run happening Oh we
must run turn around run run run run
turn back around oh there's no Rock oh
no oh no what's happening ah
where
fall I
fell what was
that I would to us why does that skull
attack
us
oh what is
mushroom there's a mushroom D the
skeleton are these the skeletons that's
your SK I thought exploded no it was to
survive this is this a waves of
enemy the survive those skeletons are
they're really hurting
us make sure you keep yourself well fed
oh I am very hungry thank you for wa
does it come back alive growling do we
have to do something with the
mushroom how do we feed it we let it
have the
mushroom beautiful now what I did
something is there another
mushroom we just keep killing it I don't
know
I felt the need to chop it what the
oh oh well done oh I feel like it comes
back alive we need to bone meal this yes
yes you're right you are right yes yes
yes we grab those I could oh I
see so we got to kill it here and then
the tree will grow cuz it drops B meal
when it dies and it doesn't like us
picking it up die on the
platform oh oh it's
[Music]
growing and soon we can parkour
yeah all
right nice okay we're getting closer
come here
skeleton do not come here
skeleton come closer skeleton come to
this middle platform with the tree I
need you to take root I think we can
already go maybe there's like buttons
here what do the buttons there's buttons
yeah I've grown it a little more okay I
think we're ready to go
okay
maybe I'm un sure
way oh yeah we can totally jump from
this let's go okay okay okay on my way
up but make sure you're well fit there's
more more
trees to kill the skeletons I'll wait
for
everyone I
can't I will distract you you guys can
climb the vines too at the start
oh so it's easier yeah
yeah oh gosh there skeleton there's two
trees
next no
skeleton is too powerful that's the
thing we we it's hard to go up like on
your own with the skeleton
attacking all right maybe I can shoot
down from
above uh I wonder if it
reaches
oops who okay go go go whoa oh you're
going that way climb the
vine how does one
climb oh there we go
nice good job
Nino all
right all right keep going
guys I'm a bit
stuck you good good yeah I'm always good
I am of the Jade sword I
am
yeah uh uh anyway uh are you
good well I was almost not good but I'm
good oh I'm glad you are
good I
guess it's not like I like you or
anything oh you good yes okay let's go
there is another another mushroom here
hope there should be another oh there's
two all right draw it here get rid of it
with this first no more
trees oh it was a little
far I'm going to die it's okay I'll come
back alive here
hello
o nice okay there's another one here
should we grow one first do we only need
one my biggest
weakness only spawns one at a
time
ow unhand me foul skeleton
Beast where is it
oh it still has
not oh oh if only I can push the item
it's if
only do they do they both have to do
both of the trees have to be up I mean
let's start with one maybe and see where
it
goes maybe it's a mechanically need but
I'm
not okay got one here
I see there's another
spawn bring it here come bring out
your oh Jesus on there
buddy over there come here you want to
hit me on tree trunk so bad I don't know
what I'm allowed to you are OB switch on
and
off I'll check
we can just for next time I'll
ask like what settings am I allowed to
unset leave me
alone all
right yes give give my brain head
Pats okay thank you voices in
head and then and over
here oh that's how you do there I look
like
this we got grow it one more
or oh maybe maybe we have to grow it or
we go over this way potentially over
here and up and then down oh yeah yeah
yeah
yeah I don't think I can make this
y y y y y y y I'm sorry I'm not talking
much okay okay out of character I'm
sorry I'm not talking
much
nice the
tummy okay it's
poopy oh
goodness this this tree is in my
way I'm kind of in concentration mode
now to to kind of get to get this
dungeon done
more I'm like let me get me out of
here okay okay I will kill the skeleton
what
okay skeleton will kill me did it grow
did I make it grow no I think this is
the maximum
then I wonder if we do have to grow both
of them and and then it links to the
other side yeah
maybe that could be a unless unless
unless I'm killing it worry not stay up
there where do I find bobbing if I do go
into settings where do I where do I find
the
bobbing okay I've grown up
more oh you
have is there a new pathway yeah
ah ah yes good job have you made there
nearly I've made it you may die oh new
I'm I will die I will die I will I will
die but I don't want to
die but if you die you may
live
no quick I ref to die in video settings
okay let me just
I want to just look at this how amazing
this sculpure is to the Denis of the
Underworld the light emanated one moment
teammates I just want to look at this
tree and Ponder it's just so amazing
what are you
pondering I just need to have some
thoughts to myself for a
sec yes yes oh if you see over here this
[Music]
above
all the plane of Life the plane we call
life oh there we go thanks sweethearts I
think I turned it off ah yes I saw the
meaning of life in this tree
what did you see what did it
say
42 42 42 yeah I counted 42 blocks I mean
tree
leaves tree leaves she count only 42 she
can count yes kind of
a mine
eyes mine mine
eyes your power re has grown stronger oh
wow you recovered a portion of your
memory memories what did I remember Hol
memory Hol live is this the timing to
Hol
live play the thing oh it's the
time it's time to play the thing
a all right guys I'll get the
thing and we shall watch it
together okay I am
ready
[Music]
Soul a Reaper's job to end people's
lives and take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their
sustenance we're going to start again
cuz I didn't see the start okay let's go
3 2 1
[Music]
go a Reaper's job is to end people's
lives and take their
souls wow that's that it's always been
the spirits of the underworld need their
sustenance holy
moly that's my guil but I keep
wondering go
get this is the woman who joined our
party is this the right thing to do
no it's
not memory was
that the's memory those are her memories
it was kind of
like she did say she was a re what's
going on when we met with her maybe she
remembers more look at
that turns out we can also use people's
emotion you don't need their souls at
all h the
underworld so does that mean if Reaper
should help the living if we go ahead
and clear more take away their future if
the others can't accept
that that's their loss I wonder
who unlock
[Music]
NE I'll do things my
way so
cool H my
goodness oh
oh that's my
guildmate that's your guildmate it's
true that was your guild mate
wow my seems there's a lot more to her
than meets the
eye yeah well maybe maybe the Jade sword
Guild Master knows more maybe yes we
must we must ask let us to the Jade
Guild Master find more of our own
memories H oh it's time to play the
Happy adventuring oh yeah happy happy
music once more uhuh wow
okay yay now it's no longer ambient
noise wow great job guys hey we saw your
memories yeah reol do you remember me
interesting I do but did you guys just
clear or did you guys did something else
after it's a little embarrassing clear
clear we cleared and we were just like
waiting and uh you know we're just
having you know just having fun in that
last room did we take that long we you
did oh yes we we oh yeah we we finished
Way 3 hours ago even 3 hours 3 hours ago
3 hours ago what let's go time FES you
oh yeah we can turn the quest did you
guys
notice they are yeah oh my God they are
sparkling what is our Revelation
Sparkle oh they are so shiny guess it's
time to test them
out I am on my
horse we're out now
look at my horse it seems the
same like raisin wait how do you know
that song I don't have any memories what
maybe our that is a very strange song
When We Were
Young maybe it is it maybe it might have
been your
lby yeah May was my lullabi maybe a
damage but but maybe we'll
see oh just like wait is it the Guild
Master outside or in the place I want to
he's like underneath the
thingy cell phone is not very so the one
in the
arena what what's go in the little wait
I'm going to I'm going Tock the one
second let me let me turn off
the hello S I mean I mean I never saw
you before are you what's a senpai what
is a
senpai are you
have I even ever had a
p i don't not
know there's a Senai
maybe it's codee for
[Music]
something a secret
language between that Guild
[Music]
maybe you located this might be an
acquired pie
they were Master speak to the Scarlet
okay Scarlet
Letter the loud one and Nina
were good teammates
dear
sidus I apologize but I am about to Bath
all over
you I'm kidding I would never do that I
don't I get am sickness but I don't
actually do that thank thank the gods
anyway what were you saying I see the
SEC the RS held such secrets that was
your
[Music]
voice a crystal deep within that when
touched returned a fragment of your me
memories to you memories which in turn
reawaken the power of
Revelation Al
albeat only fractional
potential that your summoning and the
discovery of these ruins should coincide
so
closely there must be some connection
between the ruins and the power of
Revelation Brave hero seek rubius The
Guild
Master his his gu was also is searching
for strange ruins in the lands of liist
mayhaps they have discovered
something it is
complete ah Guild members I am going to
there that is a fake fake ah you guys
are sneaky that is but a fake place to
go I see I'm going to hither over here
and leave it to that ah
I wonder if there are any if there is a
room in
here H
interesting there's like rooms down
here
freak well
guess I'm sleeping here hon
Sho card's
down I need to
[Music]
end we need to
stop or else I will perish all right let
me just quickly disconnect
that was
fun despite feeling Sicky through most
of it half of
it it was good I really enjoyed
myself and I hope you guys had fun
too with
[Music]
um
the odd version of myself we've created
[Laughter]
thank you for streaming well thank you
for watching it was you know our first
time doing something like this so I
appreciate y'all hanging out and uh and
you
know just having a good
time I need bed myself #
relatable I think uh once I hit the
pillow I'm just going to like
freaking con out
[Laughter]
but yeah let me just uh show you a
closeup
of the
cloak before
um before I hop uh you know what let me
just let me do this
properly if I do this there we go that's
better look at that
I love the
brooch it's so
pretty it's like iridescent look at
that it's very nice very
nice
[Music]
wow I think it's quite
suiting it fits with uh with the rest of
my outfit quite well don't you think
[Music]
hope you had a good time I had a great
time yeah very
nice yeah it fits along with the rest of
my
outfit
yeah yeah it's real
cool um okay let me see who we shall
redirect
to let me see what happens where with my
missed off what it
says my tummy just went
hello Remember
[Music]
Me Maybe if I
wear my my my travel
sickness like cuz I have these
wristbands
for like traveling which like press
against your wrs maybe I should wear
them next time see if that
works I have that
somewhere like the sailors do you the
sailors do with their
seasickness uh redirect let's see oh
there's a lot of people there's a lot of
people still
trucking uh you know let's raid
Mory Mory
[Music]
Senpai give her lots of
[Applause]
[Music]
love lots of
positivity and
also by the
way this is role play I would never ever
forget you
guys okay you got that
never all
right cuz you will mean the world to
me so don't forget that it's just role
play
[Music]
okay okay
it's not like I like you guys or
[Music]
anything I love you guys all right let's
H let's go over to Mor Senpai have a
great rest of your day make sure you
hydrate eat good Noms get good
sleeps I am definitely going to sleep in
a
moment and uh yeah keep an eye out for
more streams these are going to be
because of you know it being a a sand
sandbox Adventure you know kind of thing
it might be a bit sporadic the streams
but as soon as I know I'll let you guys
know um and I still really want to fit
in uh the like a a membership unarchived
karaoke as soon as I can so we'll see
what happens when I awake from my
Slumber all right first Peak first
episode I'm glad you think
so I'm glad all right right I'll I'll
bug her off now uh yeah uh yeah have a
great rest of your day and if you're
going to sleep have good
sleeps and uh yeah parting is suchly
sorry but I will see you on the tomorrow
let my voice be your
strength bye-bye
[Music]