you
[Music]
so
hello everyone kitty kitty king
geek girly key what up everyone
hello can you hear me
hello nice to see you on this lovely day
get good again
we're here live everyone
i am doing my first ever touhou related
stream today
uh i'm being uh sponsored for the stream
but
i love touhou uh in general since many
many many
many many years so i'm actually really
really excited to do this
uh i think like the normal total
games the original ones the ogs
are
definitely a bit too much for me
uh but this game i played it already
before the stream yesterday and a few
days ago actually and checked it out and
um
i already like really enjoyed it because
this one has a lot of music
in it that i really enjoy soho project
um since many many years has been a
source of
many many amazing songs and
one of the touhou artists
which are included in touhou spell
bubble is actually
sync arts by the way which is the circle
the touhou circle independent circle of
gojo sound who made my song hinotori so
there is a connection even
but my song is not in here but there are
a bunch of other songs in here
and i wanted to before we get started i
wanted to tell you about some dlc's that
i also got
uh the dlcs let me let me show you
number one i got this dlc
it's the side story bag juno arg oh i
love
she's so cute she's so swelt
she's a very funny character um
yeah so this one has three new songs in
it
that are also very very very popular and
uh it came out three days ago as well as
the other uh
dlc still came out three days ago this
uh
it has a side story in it
[Music]
i knew what you were gonna say how did
you know
i i tried to not say it so in this one
chin overcomes
the trials laid down by romeria but can
she become a professional spell bubbler
we will see we will try a little bit of
the 3 i don't know how far we'll get but
we will see
next one i think this one is familiar to
many of you guys
because mighty senpai has recently
released um in collaboration
uh uh a whole album
with touhou songs total arrangements
which i absolutely love i love them so
much it's not only her in that album
it's a bunch of other
uh whole life members in there as well
and this dlc
yes this album is now included
in the game oh my god
that got me really excited even more
connections
so this one adds six more songs to the
game
and some challenges i suppose and
there is one more that i also got so
this is the third and the last thing
i'll see that
i got it's the special music pack volume
two
also released three days ago it adds uh
six more songs and six more challenge
stages
and it also uh features two new artists
uh that weren't in the game before
digital wing and r note maybe you've
heard of them if you like touhou music
you possibly have heard of them
[Music]
it's very close to the holidays
the whole spell bubble is now since
three days ago
on holiday sale yay 20
off between december 17th and december
28th
so don't miss it if if this stream if in
this stream you think oh this is fun
then you should probably get it before
the december 28th um
it's a switch game in terms of switch
games so get it get it at the nintendo
store
of your choice which is only one but
please be careful uh
there might be some differences in
discounts possibly depending on which
country you're in i'm not sure
but check that out so yeah now we got
that down
i will get started i love touhou songs i
mean i i have to say that
the most of the tour songs that i know
are
from back in the days
[Music]
i think we will listen to a lot of
amazing songs today
so i told you i played a little bit of
the tutorial
music already going going crazy do you
guys um
feel like the audio is too quiet or too
too
too high anything like that
let me know
a little bit loud okay
got you a little five percent i don't
get donkey
thank you guys um
i'll i'll probably have to focus a lot
while playing this game because i only
have one brain i think many of you have
more than one brain or like brain cells
at least
so i'll probably be focusing a lot you
guys are welcome to cheer me
on while i'm vibing to the songs that we
can vibe together
um i want to try a bunch of things but i
think first we will get started
like continue with the main story um
yeah let's get let's start with the
story i already started okay
but it's okay not a big deal
i didn't do too much i did like the the
you start out here in the hakurei shrine
and it gives you a tutorial of how the
game
uh works it's really easy and easily
explained and the forest of magic i
already did
and now we're in scarlet devil mansion
best place ever because i love sakuya
[Music]
see i already played these three uh
these two so now next up is this one
wild exorcism dance
are you guys ready i don't know i don't
want to pick favorites i love all of the
characters i love tattooing as well
i love i love uh madison i love all of
them goddammit but
we will also be able to play um
different characters but i think
for the story mode generally you always
play with ramo
so we're playing now against romania
scotland
and the song that we'll be playing is
scarlet bad vampire ramp
vampiric knight oh no the song is
vermillion air earth
okay okay that was i think her skill
that was that i was just reading out
let's go first game of the day i might
still
um not be very good at it but i'll do my
best
amazing voiceover in japanese as well
team scarlet devil mansion general
manager ramirez scotland
good morning sorry we want you well you
should be biting in like that making
a make an appointment next time come on
don't blow your top we heard spell bubba
was trending hard here at the lake
so i brought super rookie with me we
wanted to check it out
stop calling me super i'm just a noob
yeah that's right
that's that's me we were watching the
fairies playing by the lake and we were
stunned by how much fun they were having
we hear you fox have had a hand in that
maybe pulling the strings behind the
curtain
pulling whose strings i appreciate not
being
accused of mischief i'm merely
by aiding in the promotion of gensokyo's
culture as a noble woman does
cultural promotion is it really that
legit
i'll decide how legit it is you cannot
deny that it was
we who made the game popular among those
fairies at the very least they seem to
like it for one
for what a game created by science
replicated by magic that's a very
interesting venture
games and children's games and
children's interests
sometimes breathe life into new waves
and culture
since fairies gave around the lake if
they create a new trend in gentle kill
it won't present that at all i assure
you
i'm not scheming shimming screaming
anything
okay i couldn't put my thing on it but
it did since i did send some sort of uh
nefarious undertones
familiar sauce very much
but looks like i stand corrected i
really need to stop
being so cynical not everyone has a
hidden agenda
i just wanted to show it off to everyone
and i'm honored to help
though i don't know what motivates you
it would be funny if you
just wanted to fair one of the fairies
to think you're cool
yeah like show up the game and then
smile and take all the credit
just stop looking for false already like
maybe you just wanted some friends
hey i have friends at the start i used
to be an active player
but now i prefer to watch it's quite
thrilling to watch two top level players
duke it out
is that also a thing a noble woman does
well despite my outward appearance
appearance
i am a vampire if i really tried i would
probably be
quite powerful oh let me guess
you quit because you sucked why must
you always assume the voice
wait this voice actor
oh my god this is who i think it is
if you insist on patronizing me i
wouldn't mind proving you wrong
oh we got a live one okay super rookie
now's your time to shine
is it is it is it why me
okay let's go
let's go sorry i just woke up a little
while ago so
my throat is not very um greasy yet
i need to grease it all up
i don't know i don't think it's mine in
sci-fi but she is indeed very good in uh
uh impersonating voices
sound holic is a very very big name
let's go okay so basically
you gotta shoot the bubbles to the right
color
and then oh my god okay focus and then
sometimes
you get something like this ribbon
thingy activated
sometimes you get longer ones and
something something
sometimes something special happens
i'm not the best at ribbon games but
this is fun because i
i love uh wait what is it oh my god i
can't talk so much
[Music]
yeah sometimes some special attacks can
be activated as well because i have some
ultra attacks and stuff
oh my god oh my god okay we don't want
to lose this
let me show just this watch okay just
watch guys
okay this is uh i talk too much
that is for sure oh god oh god oh my god
okay oh my gosh
[Music]
it's not over yet
oopsies
[Music]
okay probably maybe we shouldn't have
activated that now
are we losing we are
by the way there's different
difficulties as well
i think i have it on normal
[Music]
hi
hi hi
that was birthday
night again
okay i think i'm not supposed to hit the
the the bats that she sent over they
will probably disappear eventually
oops oh my god pink
hey we're not losing oh my god i somehow
managed to
catch up uh go away
there we go you're gone now
[Music]
believe in me who believes in you or
something like that
believe in me you believe in me don't
you
[Music]
oh we're ready yeah
you can by the way buy more songs like
in game you get
coins after you finish battles
and with those stopping with those coins
you can buy more songs and you can buy
more like special attacks and stuff oh
god we're going to shoot
there he goes here we go
so with whip time you get more and more
songs to play with a lot
just what is she doing what are you
talking about no it's not second
[Laughter]
[Music]
remedy
that's okay with me there's your game
well
[Laughter]
i i would probably do better if that was
a bit more focused should we try it
again
let's try it again i will not accept
defeat
remollish mug
we already heard the story so let's uh
skip that
turn bgm higher now you want to hear
more
there you go i i i turn it up a little
bit again
you can do it tenjo we believe in you
thank you maybe
maybe if you guys would pull out the
chicken light sticks then maybe it could
maybe it will help me touhou music is
great yes
[Music]
focusing
come
[Music]
oh on she's already sending me over
those bubbles
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
foreign
though
[Music]
hi hi hi here we go
are we doing good oh i think we're not
doing that bad right now
[Music]
oh
the good thing with doing arrangement
songs is like
you always hear like a familiar mute uh
oh god amelia
so you can always survive
[Music]
uh alone have my own ready i don't know
if i should use it right now though oh
god
uh pink oh yeah i should
that's up
[Music]
okay
oh
[Laughter]
ah that was fun though it gets um i
i have to say though i didn't have so
many issues with clearing the previous
levels
you know what i'll show you i'll show
you
something that i cleared before
hello alice market joint uh oh my god
yes
i love this song marisa madison stole
the freshest thing
i think you'll know it it's really old
but it's a classic let's try this one i
already cleared it but
it's already cleared i'm also going to
skip the story we're now
up against alice the puppeteer
i think here we should be able to do it
it has some this song has some german in
it doesn't it
it's fine guten morgen yeah yeah it's
it's it's history
a very quick song so the rhythm the
woman gets faster
[Music]
this song is
come on
[Music]
thought
it's over
[Music]
oh we are waiting by far
it's going beautifully
[Music]
you cannot control me
oh that was different
[Music]
hi
yay
[Music]
look at this stop changes is already
done no you gotta do it until the end
applying 270 coins so with these coins
by the way i will show you what you can
do with those by the way
that song is so good
[Music]
sorry we only streamed for one uh hour
so i want to show you more
uh contents of the game so we're
probably gonna skip some more
story here and there i wanna show you so
basically the coins you can use here in
the corindo
so here you can buy new music
b and i
already bought two guess it doesn't show
it anymore since i already bought them
i know see i bought that apple
and what the one song from sync arts
which is uh
as i said before in the beginning of the
stream the guy from sync art is the guy
who made my song hinotoy
and then you can also buy extra spell
cards you know those ultimate weapons
you can buy different ones
so i want to play bad apple so i think
if you go into solo mode
and then uh i i tried both of these
versus cpu i think that maybe we should
go for that one
i probably lose because i also lost
privately when i was playing this but
maybe
maybe if we change it too easy
we could win but here you can choose
your opponent and the one you're
fighting with so i want to go with
madison
she has master spark as her attack of
course
and we can choose the opponent as well
let's give her a flamo
[Music]
maybe someone else actually because we
want to see more characters
now that is fine and we'll give her
poison
[Music]
although she already beat me many times
should we go too easy
i mean it doesn't matter if we lose it
doesn't matter if we lose but
should we go maybe normal whatever
and we want to go for better
let's go
apple oh my god oh i have to hold myself
like if i sing too much i probably lose
focus
but bad apple how can i not sing with
along with bad apple
it's too long ago
[Music]
sing along
so good what a classic
[Music]
oh
oh god you're sending me so many bubbles
[Music]
[Applause]
bye
[Music]
when there's more on the field because
my master's back pretty much oh yeah
this is probably where we need it soon
oh god
[Music]
hey
could you please not
[Music]
oh
uh
[Music]
oh my god
hold on
[Music]
it's not over here
[Applause]
[Music]
the salt the salt i was leading the
whole time
it's okay at least i got to hear an
amazing song again
um okay
now wait i want to play one more
different song one second
how about let's see let's see what you
guys want to hear
i want to play mazda again i love her
maybe she is my favorite maybe she oh
let's is
against sakuya although i'm scared of
her
yes let's go easy
one time easy okay so we played bad
apple
[Music]
[Applause]
this is one of
[Music]
bye
let's see if we can win this one um
uneasy i'm easy we should be able to win
there's so many songs in here and i love
them all
uh it's so nostalgic too
[Music]
let's go let me show you what i can do
nice one
[Music]
you
winning
[Music]
i'm not
i think i understand i would like to
stay away from those but
we don't oh we don't have much
[Music]
but not yet i will keep it a bit longer
hold on okay maybe now
[Music]
oh my god
okay place your best now who's gonna win
i think it's me
but we thought so the last time
[Music]
thank you thank you for believing in me
i'm a big blow though i think probably
if you get used to this game you can
play it much quicker
with much more speed
[Music]
all right i forgot this was easy mode
that's probably why i will win
[Music]
the rhythm is a bit hard to figure
let me use my my spike one time
is it maddie and senpai's voice
beautiful
isn't it beautiful oh
there's no blue there's no blue oh my
[Music]
god
oh my god
no panic come come always stay calm
we made it yay
but that was easy mode
okay next thing i want to show you
guys there's the challenge mode as well
and there's a side turn we'll go to the
side story because we downloaded the
side story
but i never opened this uh this one
before so i don't know i don't know
what's going to happen
team scarlet double mansion trial
general's flight arc
oh general overcomes the trials laid
down by romelia
let's see lunatic
we're not so crazy and we'll go for
a go for normal hopefully
this will not be too hard in the
beginning
whoa whoa
they came to the lake it was quite some
time ago
i created this new toy they told me then
handed me this
and watched as everyone playing they
showed me how it works
lake very soon become hooked on it
they've never played
something that much of course i'm the
strongest one
out of all of us and it makes me the
strongest water fairy in the lake
qq 999 yeah i
won i i lost but it was fun
you know you were awesome next time play
with me
merry mel come at me
that was a heart stopper but the wind
was mine
i haven't had a loss since yesterday i'm
totally on fire
and took your 999999999 spell bubbler
channel
okay i'm not losing next time very well
come at me
good luck excuse me i'm sorry to
interrupt you journal oh who's dad
who are
what's the tangle doing down here
avoiding work
no not at all i'm doing news reporting
reporting it something here caught your
eye
don't be so rude i was thinking about
asking you for an interview
don't be so silly are you saying there's
a weird rumor or story going around
about me
no no not that kind of interview i can't
believe you lost it
today it's an interview nothing vicious
just an interview
that toy has been actively pushed around
by magic folk
it's become quite the hot topic in
gentle kill
people have been talking about the
famous spell bubbler in this area
famous me
of course that's amazing channel
how cool are you famous
i suppose around here i am but that's
because i haven't got any proper
opponents
famous i suppose i should be
famous smart strong totally makes sense
how wonderful so speaking of now
you know the famous channel
i wanted to ask you the ins and outs of
the game and why you got stuck into the
game
that's what you want and sure
let's jump right into it the famous
channel will give you a match
[Music]
is a journal against tell my mother i'm
linked to
yay
wow it's winter against
autumn i wonder what song we'll play
which song which song it must be a
popular one a famous one for sure
nine plus one is gentle oh we
got girls i don't think i've heard of
that one before
maybe i did definitely know the melody
okay
[Music]
really fast
oh my god
[Music]
oh my god oh my god
i'm not sure i don't have time to look
[Music]
over
[Applause]
hey we should have gone crazy
[Music]
oh my god
is
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
okay shoot everything down
[Music]
she is um destroying me very much i feel
it
oh my god
[Music]
again
why are we here just a summer
[Music]
oh
again
[Music]
oh okay
i would say if we practice this a few
times
we can do it i mean not on stream but
i would probably practice her on my own
[Music]
but
what are those numbers
not 1k well
i don't think we're gonna win this uh in
the stream cell
we're gonna go back to our
versus cpu mode
and oops what not change anything here
[Music]
and we'll try one more character how
about we try it
uh puccini i really like pachini as well
she knows a lot of things apparently and
her opponent will be
nitori so cute
okay guys now help me choose a song are
we gonna go on eating we want to win
some more things
[Music]
oh this is from pink eyes
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
so many good songs in here
[Music]
oh my god these songs are so amazing
perfect let's go for this one and then
do one more
marine senpai song
i love this i love it i love these songs
so good i listened to these songs
so man so much when i was a little bit
of a younger phoenix
show me what you got
[Music]
oh my god this is coming too close
oh
[Music]
in a it's game of this show but i don't
know if you guys got it from somewhere
else
this is what i think of when i say nice
boat in minecraft or whatever
[Music]
now we're talking
sing along
[Music]
again
wow
[Music]
now this is what we're talking about
love it all right why did i go out i
want to do
i want to do one more one more let's do
a money
song again
i like patchouli i need
oh maybe we should choose someone else
how about
i can't stream one more season one
i think this will be the last one though
because we've already reached one hour
one hour goes by so fast when you play
these games
so wait time
which one do you guys want me to play
[Music]
it means happy bunny and i am a shia
massive phoenix
after playing this game
[Music]
the rhythm in this song is kind of slow
so
we should be able to stay calm
[Music]
fan going hard let me run
give me a blue one
[Music]
oh
yeah but depending on the song the
rhythm is different
so the rhythm of the game of the the
rhythm that the game will give you
will also be different doesn't make
sense
[Music]
it does something on the enemy's side
right
[Music]
oh yeah sometimes um you're not able to
use it uh i'm not sure if i can explain
why
because i'm too focused
[Music]
right now yeah now i can use it she
blocked it before
[Music]
hmm
um
[Music]
there's a bunch of special bubbles every
now and then that do some special
[Music]
oh
we did it she got wrecked
yeah so that was basically a one hour
over your
overview of the game and i couldn't even
show you everything i mean there's a
challenge mode
um which what
what exactly is the challenge mode i
think i tried i did i did try and yeah
you can balance varying difficulty
levels as indicated by character sheets
and spell cards i did try one
already you see clear clear i cleared it
uh this one phoenix rebirth i was
wondering about that
okay one last thing since i want to show
you more of the game
i'll i'll i'll play this one against
mogul
and we'll see if we can win this one we
are playing as
um what's your name again
there is a few uh portions of the game
that are yeah
yeah i think you just saw a little bit
of texture voice in japanese not sure
why that was
but mostly like if you have your switch
set to english
then the game will be in english
[Music]
oh this song is
okay come on come on
[Music]
is
i messed up
[Music]
what her auntie does not sure if i
should use it now
i should use when i'm in the kids
[Music]
okay i should probably now use my outfit
soon
now what does it do what does it do
oh it does something on the enemy side
oh
[Music]
can't really look over there please
don't win
[Applause]
i cleared everything
no giving up
[Music]
right now
oh i can ask she's in a counter mode or
so so i think
that's when you cannot use the opening
oh god help me
[Music]
do something do something amazing
oh my god
[Music]
ah close close
i will practice i will practice and one
day i will win against her
so yeah that was
the hospital
that was a fun game yeah it's a
ripple game where you have to destroy
the bubbles and you have a lot of
amazing touhou songs personally now you
have uh
songs from marine senpai and some other
whole life girls in there
so i think it's very interesting if you
i will repeat if you want to get it you
should get it before the 28th of
december because there is a 20
sale going on as i told you before
but that was a lot of fun i will
probably play it probably every now and
then i'm not the
i haven't until now i haven't really
played uh ripon games not much
but this one is fun because i love
touhou project
thank you guys i hope you enjoyed it too
and uh enjoyed vibing to
some of some old uh toho songs and some
of the newer ones as well
thanks for watching today
[Music]
and in german we say auf wiedersehen
thank you to hospital bubble for
sponsoring this stream
[Music]
bye
you