[Music]
What's wrong Kia-
chan, it's embarrassing, it's embarrassing
, that's how it started. Comments too.  It's
okay if it's not the first time. [Music] So, let's introduce ourselves. Let's go. Yes, let's go. Commas Noel Shirokane, a member of the 3rd generation of Ruful Live. [Music] Why are you so embarrassed? Um,
Hololive English.
Fujina, I'm Etaka from Austria. I've
never done ASMR before.
Thank you very much. I've never done it before
. That's great.
There's something to teach me. I've been waiting for that
. Today, it's that Kia-chan.  Hey, I asked the group leader to
tell me
about ASMR, so we came up with a collaboration.I don't know
why, but I always wanted to do SM,
so I guess it was just an off-collaboration idea with Noil-senpai.
Well, I thought it would be no good if it wasn't this,
so if
I had to do it, I'd do ASMR.Well, I don't really know if I can do it that much, but I
might not have any plans to do it myself.Yeah, but just in case.
Well, I think it would be better if Nol-senpai taught me that.I'm sure everyone is
looking for it, and I'm sure there are people who are looking for it.When the
group leader set up this frame, it was
amazing.  I'm
already looking forward to Kiara-chan's AS. There's already a lot of stuff like that. I
used a foreign language to say something like "bar," so don't get used to it.
Wait a minute. That's right, the comment
is dead. It's been a while since I was a regular person.
When it's erased, it's
like, if I change just one pixel, it'll be weird.
Now, it's healed, it's healed, it's okay, go home, okay, okay, go
home. Okay, that's
right. I'm wearing that Liandre costume that looks like it's going to be hot today.  Please
try saying it in German with proper pronunciation.
Diandru diandrua
dean
guesu Ah yes, today is Mamoru Anoma. It
's been 1 year and 5 months since I last attended the ASMR course.
Who was it, Rene or something? I'm pretty
sure, so after that, I continued to watch the birds,
and as usual, I taught Chiara-chan about things like how to clean her
ears, and then I taught her how to clean her ears, and after that,
Chiara-chan was on her own.  Yeah, yeah, we're
going to try it out, but after that, the
two of us did a lot of things with Chiara-chan, and
while she was teaching us those words, we thought, ``I wish we
could do SMR together,'' but
actually, we did some ear cleaning.  Actually, yes,
if I were to get hit with that stick, I'd be
really bad at it.That
's right.Yes, that's probably
true when it comes to Japanese culture.However, when I
stream ASMR, it's seen quite a lot overseas.
But it's special, special, special, and so on.It
may not be only in Japan,
but at least in Europe, ear cleaning is
n't like relaxing.It's
just for cleaning.It
feels good.  I don't have anything to say
about it. I don't like it at all. I'm
making some adjustments. I don't know if it's
okay or not. I'll
give it a try anyway. Let's give it a
try.  Well then, this is always a tradition,
but please try cleaning your ears with this cotton swab.By the
way, I would like to
tell the listeners who made that comment
a little bit about today's sound.
Hmm, I wonder what they say on the left and right sides of KU100,
so the
leader may be on the left on the screen, but for
KU100, the right ear is in charge of that.
Please,
please use the k100 standard. I see. I
don't understand what you're saying. Yes,
there's left and right. Why is it the other way around? Because it
's facing that way. Yeah, it's facing this way. That's
right. Oh, it's the other way around in OBS.  It's fine if you
do it. There are so many things. Let's
do it as it is. Let's do it as it is. Yes, yes, uh, put it in, put it in, it's fine. Will
cle not be too strong.
Don't break it.  It's like a little bit
[Music] I
'm being lured in, but I'm in.
But this is it. I was called by a doctor the other day,
but he's really saying this to my ear. So this is
it, this is it, this is it. It's a cotton swab.
Um, if you put it this way, you'll naturally say, ``This isn't good,'' and say, ``You should take out the trash.''
Okay, this is JMR. It's not
real. That's right, in reality, listen to it on that SMR.
If you were a normal person, your
ears would be damaged if you cleaned your ears like that, but you're right. It's a
world of imagination, after all. You
shouldn't let your imagination run wild, so it's a little
different from reality. Noel,
have you ever had your ears clogged?  I've been so
stuffed that I had to go to the doctor. I've been
so stuffed that I couldn't hear anything.
I had no choice but to go to the doctor. What do you
call that floor?  What's this? I
went out to clean it, and then I took a shower. They
showered my ears in a small shower. They showered
me really hard. It
was a very strange feeling.  Why don't you give
ASMR a try?
Yes, it's probably too sensitive, and the microphone may damage everyone's ears. I see, there
is such a thing. It's a good
learning experience. Please have a chair.
Please come in. That's right, Kia-chan. I
'm feeling her ear picks right now, but I can feel her gentleness. It
doesn't feel good at all, it
feels good, but after all, Kiara-chan
herself is the type of person who doesn't pick her ears up in moderation. So
what should we do about this?  I don't know what to do,
huff, but maybe it's about time. The
comment section is a little bit deeper. It
seems like it's good. I think it's really going to come out.
Seriously, it's so, so, so, so so so so so such,
but it's so noisy. It's not so loud, it's not noisy, it's okay.
By the way, the cat in this ear is
It's white, it's white, it's that microphone part, so don't
push it too hard because it will break a little bit.
Oh, here and there, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah
, that's dangerous. Eh, okay, okay, I'm sure there
was something on Dada-ki.  Chi,
red, red na
bladingOhmyLetmerid
oftheBL stop chi,
stop it Kira-chan, yes everyone is crying in the comments section
Don't say that, it's just your imagination Yes yes, it
hurts, everyone is in pain It's okay,
I'm your nurse  I'll heal your ears, I'll
fix them. I'll
heal your ears that I broke.
That kind of
thing By the way, besides cleaning your ears,
can you also scratch your nose? Splash your nose a
little bit, by the way, just a
little bit more like this, like this, no
, is that really okay? Even if I go, it'll be too much.
Hey, yeah.
That's right, it's probably a place name, but Hara-chan herself is not
good at it.I don't like this when it comes to things that I'm not
good at.I like how everyone likes it.It's ok, it's gori, it's
gori, it's deep, but it only sounds like noise.
What is this?
There are all kinds of sounds, but
when you're a baby, there's something in your mother's womb,
in the water, in the water, that
low-pitched A sound.  Ukada, it's
not completely silent, right? Well,
even though it's rusty, it's
almost like it's so comfortable
that I feel so handsome.
[Music]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  It's
like,
it's my first time making music, so I
can't get the idea right.But you should clean your ears.I'm
sweating so much, you can see it, the
sweat on my face is so sweaty.I'm so nervous, but
wow, I'm so sweaty from the wind on those hands.  I'm
not the writing type, but I was sweating so much. I'm
nervous. My heart is pounding. Well, yes, I
should have gone first, but then, Hara-chan,
since I'm going to do SMR this time,
what do I want to do?
Yes, I guess I should clean my ears.  I said I'm not good at it,
but I'm not good at listening, but
it's okay to give it a try.Actually, let's
try something gentle.The
only thing left
for me is to make a sound that everyone will be happy with.
But, no, I make a Sound
that you will love
very
much. I'm going to open up, no, no, no, it's
coming. What kind of sound does it make?
Um, what?
Change it. I never thought that the K100 was a little
too big and in the way. I
couldn't see the face.  Do it one more time, do
it one more time, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look at
it.  I'm
doing it, but it's completely different.
Yeah, let's do it. It's close, it's close, it's close. I never thought I'd be able to teach you how to make a frog cry. I'm good at imitation. But this is one of
ASMR's strengths. That's right, other people
can't do it.  Because I don't have it, Chiara-chan, I'll
do ASMR.When I do it in the future, I
wonder what it'll be like.If I go overseas, I'll probably hear things like frogs crying at night.If I live in the countryside, I'm sure I'll hear all kinds of things.It's
just like Japan.  Even in the countryside, the sound of frogs
makes a lot of noise.It's like a summer thing.That's
right, I can't make cicadas.Well then, there are no
cicadas.Labora
collaboration.Here we go, on a
summer
night.If this is ASMR like this, I'd
like to hear it a little more.Oh, I see.  It's
refreshing, I don't know anyone, but hey,
Kira-chan, there's a Chinese word for demand and supply in the world.Do you
know the word demand and supply?
And
what I deliver
seems to be in agreement with each other. I get
it. I get it. I
get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I\hget it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I\hget it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I\hget it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. It's probably
not a frog. Yeah, I get it.
Yeah, I
think I'm probably not going home.
So, let's take a look at that Brahma just now.
Yes, this Brahma that that leader is holding in his left hand.
Hey, it's cute. I'll give it to you.
Now I'll clean your ears again. By the
way, yeah,
with those eyelashes.  Yeah, you
can hear your ears with eyelashes that can be made with eyelashes that can be made.
Hmm,
what's this? It's called a butterfly kiss.
When a baby's kiss rubs against your skin, it's
like a gentle butterfly kiss.
What is it? I've never heard of it, no, I've never heard of it. Yeah, yeah,
myes.  Give me a little kiss, give me a little kiss,
now I'll give you a butterfly kiss,
yeah, Butterfly Keith doesn't look like you at all
When I woke up, I got butterflies in my ears. Oh, this is it. I
'm going to go with that one. Oh, you're so kind.
Okay, okay, okay, I worked hard overtime today. That's amazing. In
reality, SM overtime might be good, but it
's still work.  You worked hard at work and at school,
right? Kia
is the type of person who only talks about practical things. I'm sorry about that.
No, that's fine. That's part of her personality.
So please don't take the last train home today.
Please come early.  Let's go home early. The
weather wasn't so good today. Yeah,
but I'm relieved that summer is finally over.
I don't like summer in Japan. It's hot. Hello, hello. It's
hot. I'm glad it's over.
Akia-chan,
Kiara.  I understand, too.
Yes, Chiara-chan does some creative magic,
but even though I don't like it, the whispers are
really good. Thank you. Just one time last
time, just as a joke, I
played ASMR on that computer with specs.  That's right, I
read out the specs of that Minecraft computer and said, ``I
don't know what that means,''
but I read the name and number of the graphics card and
so on.  I
invited her to the SMR course,
and Sayaki Kia-chan is really good.
Thank you, Kukuku Marine, and Hanesake. Her
voice is a bit quiet, but she's so
loud, so I
had a hard time, but Chiara-chan
is amazing.  Yes, that's good.
Thank you. Noel-senpai is also good. Thank you.
Well, both of you are welcome.
Collaboration collaboration bofu size bofuen
[Music]
E
like
here
Sue. Isn't there this Brahma in other countries
? I wonder if this is a cat toy.  No,
there's something like this, so I
don't know what to say. I don't know how to say it. It's true, Ponte Ponte Ponte.
For the people overseas who are in the comment section right now,
Noel is holding
this fluffy thing in his left hand. Do this now.
[Music] It's like
that
[Music]
I'm going to say that sound now
[Music] I'm
going to go with it
[Music] I
'm going to say that.
Okay, okay. Ah, what's that? Noel-senpai.
Yes, today is my birthday from last year.  I was
surprised when you brought it up. I
got it, so I put it on the sofa.
Thank you. By the way, the
leader was the one who was making stomach noises earlier. I
couldn't hear it. It was true, but it was found out in the comments section.
Seriously, everyone's ears are so good. It's because they're like this. Surprisingly, everyone's ears are
n't dumb, so they're sensitive. I
haven't eaten, no, I've eaten. I
feel hungry when Mamoru is with me.  That's right. That's how it is. That
cat's
making that noise. It's so good. It's amazing. That cat is making a lot of noise. It's like
that. It's making
a lot of noise.  Yeah, I'm
doing it behind the scenes.But when I
heard my cat impersonating me for the first time with an ASR microphone, I got a
totally different impression of it with an ASMR microphone.Oh yeah, it's a bit different.Yeah, it's
different than usual.Drink some water.Yeah,
Papa.It
looks like a daddy car.It's an engine.  Sounds like an
engine No, a cat is an engine. That's
right. Yeah, it's better than the bridge. Nemi-o, cat-chan, Mio. There's a cat in my left ear. I'm hungry, and there's a
tulle. It's a cat. It's a cat.
It's a cat. It's a cat, my senior.  I can't do
things like dollar rolls, so I
probably can't do that either.
Yeah, I thought if I was Japanese, I
would be able to pronounce that R because I couldn't shake that bell.
Well, I'm a bit short. I ca
n't get it out either. I can't get it out. Wait, I can't get it out either. That's
right, that new En member,
Nerisa-chan, can't get it either. Lately, I've found out that she can't get it either.  I
was really happy, but I can't believe
there's another person like me. I'm so happy that I
can't go this far. It's the
first time I've ever heard that. I
took voice acting lessons with a Florive member.
At that time, we were talking about the length of the tongue.It was
embarrassing, but the captain was short, but that's why he was
shorter than everyone else, so no one was the
same.So we're the same.I'm so happy.  When I
go to the dentist or something like that, they
ask me to turn on the bell, but I try to give out more,
but every time I get asked to
give out more, I
can't.  If it doesn't come out, let it
out.It's
hard to eat ice cream.Yeah, I know it's hard to eat.I
know it's hard to eat ice cream.But I know it's too late.But
Kiara-chan moves a lot, so don't
let her get too close to the microphone.  Oh, you need to
stretch a little more when you move. Your body is
stiff and stiff. Oh, let me help you stretch.
If I try it here, you'll start screaming. So, it's
stiff, it's hard, it's stiff, it's stiff. Should I
tweak it a little more?  I
went for a massage today.Massage,
oil massage, oh, it was really good.I
tried massaging my ears too, and I got a sore.I
had to put it in that white thing, so I got it out.I
got a tissue,
too.Hey, wait a minute, sweat.
Isn't it okay just to lie? What's this? It's oil. It's
hair oil. Oh,
put this in your ear and say something like this. It's so
sweet. It's like
that.
Ah
[Music] Oh,
how are you doing?  It's so arrogant, it's so good, so it's so delicious. I
did
n't want to be massaged with oil like this. I was asked to avoid my head.
Normally, I would massage my ears and my head, but my
shoulders were massaged really hard.  But I got it
Oh, it's so
strong, it's so strong, I can't
hear it anymore No, I
can hear it, but it's sealed up, so I'm like,
Wow,
what was I going to do if I couldn't hear it? Hey, hey,
just that Noel-senpai.  Yeah, I'm going to
tell you a lot of things, so please don't listen to me, okay? Well, I didn't have
anything to say. I wanted to
see it or try it out. Oh
yeah, you all couldn't hear me, right? No, that's
amazing, Chiara-chan, by the way.  You know,
there's a trick to covering your ears, and
right now, I feel like I'm a little disappointed in the book, but
right now it's too much of a secret, and the
feeling of not wanting to hear it is too high,
too much...  If you apply too much force, this
KU100 is a precision machine, so if you
apply too much force, you'll end
up applying pressure and making noise, right?  I
really couldn't hear you, how did
you do it? It's difficult to do it like this. It
's difficult to use enough force.
[Music]
It's difficult, but this is how I
feel.
Noel, you can't
hear me, my senior.  I can't hear you, I can't hear you, it's
okay, it's okay, I feel
like I'm in a swimming pool, I know, I feel like I'm in a swimming pool, I know, I feel like I'm under pressure, I know, I feel like I'm under water pressure
, I'm starting to feel like I'm drowning, I'm sorry, I
didn't want to
drown.  What does it mean in Japanese
when you go into that water and can't breathe? I mean, I'm
drowning. I'm sorry for spilling on
you. I'm
sorry for spilling on you. I didn't plan on hurting you, especially.
I'm sorry, I'm your nurse. So,
live and live, but this nurse just
does funny things like the frog croak, so that's okay.
That's that entertainment program.
I see, I like all kinds of programs, so it's time for a massage and ear cleaning.  Oh, tissues, here's a tissue.It's
pretty.The trash can is in the back.Okay, that's
nice.It's already time for today.The
leader of the group noticed that he didn't need it.No, the
leader is here.What are you saying?What are you saying?  No,
that Kihara-chan can stand by herself. Yeah, it looks
like it's her first time doing errands. Without the leader,
she usually whispers to that KFP-san,
or rather, that kind of aiming feeling. Yeah,
try it.  I
'm watching you. I'm watching you around
here. You're not leaving my room. It's okay. It's
okay. I'm here. It seems
like I'm left with only Kia-chan. I'm sorry. I'm on the
channel.
From today onwards, that's
my channel. I'm
about to cry.
What should I do
? You can only use the winning one. Yeah, hello. I'm here too.
Hol Live
English's Hol Listening book
came out recently, so yeah, it's
really good, I recommend it,
and I'm
sure there are some mistakes in the book, so please
refer to it.
Tai,
then that's what I'm saying in SMR, but it's
great to be alive, oh praise, praise,
English, praise, praise, hom, home,
praise, praise, oorets Do Insh,
praise,
nobi, you have to get into the e zone, enter the zone.
Good luck Zon
IAMSERNOWLET
SER
YOUDIDSUAGREATJ
TODAY
Beauty Beautiful
Beautiful
Beautiful Beautiful ASEYOUSUAGOOOD
PERSONGMAYBEIFYOTO BEG OODMAKEYOUFOOD LATER
OK SOWHATWOULDYOULDYOU PREFERTOJUSTGO
Outtoa RestMaybeweshoudgo Yakiniku
Yakiniku RFORME Bake instead of me  Can you
help me? I'm not that good at it, so I'm not very good at Yakiniku Yakiniku. I wonder if Senpai will cook me some Yakiniku.
Little,
little, thank
you foring me, thank you, Rescue,
Noel Rescue,
Okay then, I'm grilling
yakiniku, so please leave. Yeah, I can't do that. I want to ask you something.
Hey, it's
delicious. Let's
bake it on high heat. Let's grill it on high heat. It
's
okay. I'll leave it to you. Yes, it's delicious.  I
wanted to hold my hands together, I wanted to hold them together, hold my hands, hold them together, it's stiff, it's
sweat, it's oil, it's oil, it's
oil,
it's a mixture of various things, that's it, it's amazing,
moist, moist,
oh my  Sweaty spaghetti
means sweaty spaghetti in English.
Sweaty spaghetti, spaghetti yes. Sweaty spaghetti.
So,
uh, I'm done eating. I'm done eating. I guess I'm
done. I'm going to eat yakiniku. Thank you for the feast. It
was delicious.
ThankyoufortheF
Dessert Dessert
Dessert Dessert Is there something wrong?
What kind of technique is this this time?
Okay, let's see what's out. I just made
this last night. Try it. It's
Japanese, it's Japanese. It's
scary and scary, so I
think, "Yeah, it's
okay."
Yeah, I'll eat anything. It's
delicious. It's
delicious.  This is a Japanese sweet that many people chew and chew at ASR.I
see, it's a Japanese snack that many people eat.
Thank you for the meal.Tayamiyamiyami Well
then,
what should we do after dessert?
Before I go and pay, I'll
take a look at that leftover drink.Okay, I'll drink it at the same time.Yo, it looks like it's really rich and
rich.
I can't do it. I don't know if the Adam's apple is big in my throat,
but it's amazing. I can
hear mine.
Ah, I'm full.
If I'm full, I'll have to pay.
Please go ahead, Mama, I'm a senior, so I guess so.
Credit card.  Or cash.
Well, I don't have a card with me right now, so I'm going to use a
passmo. Is it
okay to use a passmo? I don't know what to do with the passmo. Yes, I don't know what to do with the passmo. I don't know what to do.
Pipi, ah, maybe this. If it's an SMR, I'll pass
it.  Tapping
Tapping Ping Yes, but Nol-senpai is paying
for it, so I can play with this?
Well then, you can use Pasmo.
Are there any other point cards? I
don't have points saved up. I see, I
only use Pasmo.  Yes, I'll ask you once, then I'll put it in here. Wow, it wasn't here. Yes, it
wasn't here.
Yes, I hit it with Pasmo 100.
Now, please be gentle, be gentle, okay. Pipi.
Well, I don't have any money in it. I have
n't entered it.  Do you want to do something other than that?
Well then, on your smartphone, on your smartphone, on your smartphone, on your
smartphone, on your
smartphone, okay, okay, on your smartphone, there's no sound on your smartphone. There's no sound. I'll
press it again and make a sound. It's
scary, scary,
scary. No matter what kind of sound I try to make.  I wonder what's going on with the explosion
? But this one isn't even making a sound. What kind of sound is it? The smmr isn't making any noise. It looks like there's going to be some dust to
commemorate. To commemorate it, let's
go, let's go. Yes,
smile, smile, yes,
pause.  I
did it, I did it. I
have great memories of Japan. Noil, I'm
probably doing something that I've never done before today. It's
more like I was imagining something that I've never done before.
I'm sorry, I don't want to say this, but it's good. It
's fresh, it's very fresh, but there's just one thing. Um,
I've probably done it many times before, Noil-senpai. There's something that I thought I had to do too. My heart is
pounding.  Beat heart beat oh heart beat yes I
want to do it but that means I have to take it off
No I don't have to take it off I
can do it
okay if I touch that chest I can hear the sound of my heart in your ears
oh my stomach is getting hungry  I'm getting hungry, so it's delicious.
Acha,
my. You should
listen to the beat. That's embarrassing. Where's your heart? Where's your heart? Where's your heart? Maybe it's not pounding too much. First,
Chiara.  I can hear your heart, I
can hear it, it's dead, I can barely hear it
, I can't hear it.
Please release my heartbeat, Eeeno-senpai.Okay,
IARanything.By
the way, I'm usually alone, so I take my clothes off.It's
different than usual, so I
guess that's okay.Oh, I'm doing it.You're all
doing it pretty loud.I'm glad to be alive, I'm alive.  I'm glad you're doing it. I wonder if Tae
will do it that way or not.
Her face was the same with Marine. I
wonder if it would be better if we could do this and that in turn. We're together. It's
embarrassing.  Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, yeah, it
smells really good, right? I do
n't know who is who, but I get it
. It's happening, it's really happening.
Noyle-senpai was so excited, but
hey, I learned a lot.  You know,
when we were together with Marin, we were so embarrassed that we
tried not to touch each other,
but Kia-chan
hugged me and put her arms around me all over her body.
Otherwise, it's difficult.
No, it's amazing. I'm so sweaty.
I'm sorry, that hot Noil-senpai. I
turned off the air conditioner, so that's what happened before. I
also have an air conditioner AS to prevent noise.  I think so,
but Pipi, it seems like it usually comes out.So let's put
it
back.Okay, let's go home.Well, I guess I'll
take it out, take it out, or take it out.Also, it's going to be a little
more, so don't worry.Hey,
Chiara-chan, you're good, but I also have wind in your ears.Everyone is
happy.  I'm thinking about it, so I'm listening to it.
Yeah, that's amazing. [Music] I haven't seen it before. Why, I
feel strange.
It's really good, but it
's so good. It's so good, but it's so long. I
did my best. Request, request. Um,
chair.  I
said, ``Okay, I'll give you my ear,'' and I said, ``OK,'' like before.
Yeah, I'm going to give you my ear. Why are you so embarrassed? Oh, I'm going to give you my ear.
Wait,
oh, it's already over here. That's
too bad.  It's so hard to go all the way to the A, but in
reality it
's amazing. Oh
my ears, too.  Is it
true? Yes, it's scary. Is
n't it scary? Why is it scary?  Okay,
so this isn't really that bad. It's the hurricane that everyone is talking about.
What is Chiara?
If it were like that, it would be
stronger. Yes, it's quite difficult. I
think Chiara is good at being able to constantly negate.  Yeah, that's amazing,
then that thing is running, yeah, yeah, that thing is running, yeah, I'm
dying,
oh, then I'm a little embarrassed, I'm
embarrassed,
let's stop it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's running, yeah, yeah, that's it, yeah, that's running.  I've
done that before.It's
not a marathon, but
after doing 10 squats, I
asked you to listen to the sound, and it was so loud that it was so
loud that I knew it.  I
want to ask you,
Is it now?
No, I don't care if you're acting recklessly. I'm going to do some squats, squats, squats, etc. Anyway, I'm going to do a cask cut form. It's okay if I don't wear a short skirt, because I'm going to be seen as a mess. Yeah, for now, my heartbeat.  I want to increase the number Yes, yes,
but I wonder if I can do it? Good luck Shehas
Naiform has a really messed up shape. I
wonder if I can understand that the form is good. But
now, slowly, slowly, slowly, fasta, fasta,
fasta, fasta, fasta, fastaaaaaaaaaaaa,
don't go fast. I should have counted the red.
Okay, wait, the finesse stuff got really fast. I
heard it was dead.
But oh, it got a little faster.
[Music]
definitely got faster.
But I don't want to scut. I
don't sweat.  It's hot, it's already hot
. Ah, there are some classic sounds that I haven't done yet.
And then there's the gel ball, and
there's this, and it's amazing. When I put it in my ear, I
have
something.
[Applause] Oh, it's
delicious.
So, go on the other side.
Okay. If you're a first-timer, you'll do things so
vigorously that you'll get angry. You'll
break them.
But you know how to do it and you're good at it
. [Applause] It's
like you're washing your ears.  I wonder if you can hear it, but Gel
Gol is like the sound of a massage in your ears,
so this was a comment in English,
but yeah, it feels like it's in a flyer.The
sound of my Niflyer is burning, it's burning,
Hue.  Lakspicy Chicken Crispy Chicken
Yara-chan looks delicious SMR is good,
but everything goes in that direction.
My audience is M.
This is your fate. Fate, oh, get burned.
Okay, this will happen eventually.
I
[applause]
Even if I eat, I can't watch Chiara-chan.
So, yes, yes, I turn into a tile and come back to life. That's right,
yes, that's right. What about everyone in KFP?
Kepi was originally a garden chicken, but that one time.
If you put it in the fryer and it dies, I'll
give you those wings. Yeah, yeah, it'll
come back to life with that short-haired chicken hybrid, so yeah, it's
okay. Oh yeah, it's okay. It'll come back to life as many times as you like. It'll
only come back once, just once, just once.  Ah, I'll
revive you. Ah, I'll revive you the second time.
Yeah, I can't give you that. Well, that's right. The
second time, I won't let you do that kind of work again, so it's a
job. Well, I
used to work at a fast food restaurant.
Eventually, if I wasn't old enough to work, I'd put it in the fryer,
turn it into rice, and feed it to the customers.I'd
revive it, and by that time, I'd be
fighting that battle.  I also worked as a part-time worker,
and everyone from there was there to
help me out, after all.But you
know, I
guess you can't go into battle unless you experience the fate of being eaten at least once.I see, that sounds
really good.  I don't know
what to say, but I
guess it's to prove my own worth.
That's kind of how I feel about myself. That's
how far I'll go to try out Chugami.
When I heard KF
KFP, I said, ``Everyone is having a hard time.''
Everyone is happy. That's why I want to
be burned, and I want to be burned.
Nice nice. Yeah, it's
amazing. Even now. Yes, I remembered it when I didn't watch it.
But yes, I recently bought a cat chime.
Hello, this cat has a theme. The
theme of the cat is Hinahi Hinamatsuri Fire,
Faa Fire, so it's
perfect for Chiara. Chime Chime Tummy.  I feel like I want to
go to sleep, but I go back to praising my baby when I was a baby.
Yes, I did my best today
. I'll do my best today and tomorrow too. Let's do our best. Let's do
our best.
Well, the time is right, so
that kind of music is true.  Yay now, Kia-
chan, I'm so happy.Oh yeah, and it's
like a school chime.It's
different overseas too, but
when I was in Japan, I sometimes heard
all kinds of noises in the streets.Children are confused, so
please write them down.  Yeah, that's true. Yeah, I'm worried about the
leader even though it's like an announcement here. It's
okay, Kia-chan. I
wonder if that SMR teacher was able to do it. I was always asked to teach him things. I feel like it's international.  In terms of exchange, that's right.It's
international exchange.I think I've learned a
lot of things, such as those sticks, and things like that.Yeah, yeah, it
seems like it's okay to put in more forcefully.Somehow,
surprisingly, that listener's ears are
kind of M.  That's why I see so many
people who like it stronger.If you
do SMR, make it a little stronger.I think KFP probably
likes it stronger.Ah, at the end, there is
one thing that KFP can record so that it can be recorded by yourself.  Is it
okay to do that?
Of course, it's okay, use the left and right, right and left, it's okay.Oi,
yo,
have
ThankyoufortheR
Super
Chat
thanandmanwe
say,
bye,
bye, even now, I'll keep it forever.I always
tube when I'm Aspa-chan.
That's the version. That's right. I
received it. So next time Chiara-
chan broadcasts it, I'll thank you in Chiara-chan's frame.
No, no, I'm not going to invite you. It's
not like that, but
thank you very much Noel-senpai.
Yes, Chiara-
chan.  So, in the end, it's just the two of us. So that's it,
listeners, LINE
and kfp,
no way. So, will you send a message? Message? I
thought you'd say, ``Would you like to play together?'' So, uh, that's
it.  Hey, wait a minute. It's
really hot. It's really hot.
Well then, the leader
always says thank you for your support.
Yes, Kiara-chan, say yes, I love you. Let's
finish this later. Okay. Message. Oh, then let's
go.
Yes, thank you for always supporting me.
Bye-bye-bye I'm sorry for bothering you. See you bye-bye
-bye bye-bye too.