[Music]
he has a widow, two daughters,
one of whom was beautiful and hard-working,
the other
was ugly, but she was fond of the ugly one
because she was her right-hand daughter and we all
loved it much more and the other had to do all the work
and be the Cinderella in the house,
poor thing  Every day the girl had to
sit down on the main street near a house
and had to spin so much that the
blood jumped out of his fingers
She wanted to wash
her but she got out of her hand and fell
down
[music]
it seems she called to her stepmother and
told her about the misfortune
The girl went back to the apartment
and didn't know what to do
and in her heart's fear she jumped into
the well to get the school,
she lost her senses and then woke up
and came to herself again  Suddenly it was
a beautiful meadow where the sun
was shining, there were many thousands of flowers in
this meadow, it went on and there could be
an acute anarchy that was full of bread as bread,
as if
it was a I was already booked out for a long time
hepp and took
everything out one after the other with the pro room after
the now further and came to a tree
it was full of apples and rain to breathe
I shake myself who apples are all
together at the ship first  tree
first the apples a lot of them it's raining and
shaking them there's no one around anymore and
when they were all put together in a pile we
went on again
finally we came to a small house and
an old woman looked out of it because she
had such big teeth  him afraid
and follow it fold forward the old woman
but row by price are you afraid
love skate stay with me if
you don't want to do all the work house ears you
should be fine
you just have to be careful that  you
make my bed well and do it diligently so that
the feathers fly, snow is in the
world in the woman because the old woman spoke to him so
well, so the
girl took heart, agreed and went
to her service, she also took care of
everything  her satisfaction and
always shook her up so much
that the feathers were re-educated and the snowflakes
had a good life with
her, no bad word and every day
sank and fried
[music]
now it was one  For a while with Mrs.
Holle it was sad and
at the beginning didn't even know what was missing,
finally realized it was homesickness but
I felt four times 1000 times better
than at home
so it had a desire and finally
he said it to him  I've brought the misery
home and no matter
how well I feel down here,
I can't stay any longer.
I have to go back up to my family.
Mrs. Holle said it's good for me
that you want to go back home because
you  served me so faithfully means I want to
hang pictures for you myself
[music]
the name is on it at hand and
led it was a big one in front of
the goalkeeper and as the
girl stood just below it wanted a
huge shower of gold and all the gold
stayed on him  hang so that it
was covered with it
as if you should wait, keep it up 30 who
in reading needs the woman Holle and
also gave him back the spool that had fallen into the
well.
The gate was then locked and the
girl was there  Up in the world
not far from his mother's house
and when she came to the yard the hair was sitting
on the well and then she went in to
his mother
because she arrived covered in gold and was
well received by her and her sisters.
The girl told everything
met him when the mother heard how
the great wealth had come about
today, the other eastern and
full daughter sees care with the same happiness.
She had to sit on the floor and
jump and so that her coil of bloody
practice didn't get into the  finger and pushed her
hand into the thorn hedge then
she threw the coil into the well and
jumped inside herself.
Like the other one she came to the beautiful
meadow and continued on the same cadre
when she got to the oven
the bread was pretty out of me again
from otherwise burns I
broke out of the
sauna for so long to be answered because I felt like
getting dirty and went
away soon she came to the apple tree that
called shaking off I felt like
apple are all together
she answers the work
You're coming to my right, it could
hit me on the head and went on with it,
she stopped in front of the woman who came to the house,
I was afraid that she didn't know, I
had already heard about big teeth and
immediately hired myself out too empty
on the first day there was violence  was
busy and followed the woman Holle
either said something when she thought about
what she might want to
give her as a gift
on the second day but was already starting
to hurt herself
on the third day, she didn't want to stand upside down even more in the morning,
she also did
that to the woman  don't like it
Skibbe didn't shake it so that the
feathers flew up.
Mrs. Holle soon got tired and
gave up her service. I was probably
happy with that and said whoever the golden rain was
coming. Mrs. Holle also led her to
the gate
when she was standing underneath it. Barth, the city
of gold  big cauldron folky
poured out on a Tuesday Baghdadi
woman hell and go castration he can
the laziness
but she was completely covered with pitch and
the [ __ ] on the well was the first
our dirty mv is bad luck again
but stuck to it and did
n't want to end what had been experienced for too long
[music]