[Music]
yeah it's like
opera or something i don't know
what the hell is that
i got something else
i gotta uh no not really i don't think
so it's like a bum bum but i gotta have
like a kfp chicken nugget in my hand
chicken nuggets in your hand
yeah
oh wait ammo is a bit too loud well
that's that's that's a first
[Music]
opera i smell like
did you hear that or the discord muted
i heard it it was good that's just
random
okay
well we're back wait did you just sing
as well i didn't hear it
no i didn't you should try to recreate
that sound go
beautiful
beautiful oh he stopped saying though i
think he was like
you know i've lost my job i'm just too
good at opera i'm out of here
uh i found some uh crack rocks here
rocks
yeah
today guys we're doing it a bit
differently we're uh just gonna do like
we're gonna talk to one another the
whole time uh because i think you guys
kind of requested it so instead of doing
the walkie-talkie thing we're just gonna
be talking constantly
uh hopefully
so
please enjoy i hope you
uh like it that way i hope no one has an
issue with that
and we're supposedly finishing the game
today
yeah
supposedly i can do it wait how many
chapters are there chat well then uh
sorry if you guys in my stream hold on
one second
uh
how many how many oh candles
where am i
i think i started you know it's okay
though because uh
at this point it doesn't matter last
time it kind of mattered but this time
it doesn't matter um i think we switched
rose again
oh
okay
it doesn't matter right yeah it doesn't
matter but i i started out uh somewhere
else than where i left off last time
like last time i was oh instead in front
of some kind of oven where i could put
in stones so i think you're there
yeah
i swear i am
i'm still i don't remember so
okay how about now is i'm not so loud
anymore now
let me lower all of this
because i
i i lower in obs
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
well
okay can you just say something normally
not not not screaming
oh uh testing hello test no wait can we
switch because you wanna have all the
potions and these are like you're the
potion lady
you're the watson concoction manager
okay
you'll be fine we'll figure it out
together amen
so i'm in a
church
looking
place
uh oh
uh okay oh yeah and i remember
i see
i see weird
drawings with
weird names i see uh uh mushrooms
mushrooms i don't like it
i don't like mushrooms either but i
think they're cute
cute yes yes they look so dumb or indeed
cute i have to agree with that
uh
and wait i have to turn myself a little
bit up in obs
okay
uh tell me guys is it better now i don't
know it's only a little bit
[Music]
you
have to deal with it
i should be fine
and i see a blackboard that has
um
[Music]
oh sorry i was just i ran into something
i thought i got electrocuted i have a
blackboard that shows me
[Music]
letters and their connections but the
letters are like always like two letter
combinations
what like what like
uh
o h o l p f o t p a and like for example
o h is like
a creator or or whatever by
hello otpa and then out of ot is
facebook and pajamas
what okay yeah i see it and stuff like
that maybe you've seen it last time when
you when you left off when you before
you ended the game maybe you
saw this room anyway oh no i don't think
so but i i do have um like this little
a potion turner where i can go through
different potions and their different
colors and have different pictures on
them i also have a book um
that sounds like the letters you're
describing but instead it uh it just has
the letters and then like the full name
next to it so like uh
eric savor babe
what parix of four bay
yeah i didn't say that right uh and then
i got another book it's got some rocks
in it
and there's a blue rock a blue rock uh
and then plus the kfp chicken nugget
rock and then if you put those rocks
together it makes a red rock but then i
put my rocks inside the oven that i saw
and i can't take them out and it says i
need a third rock but i only have two of
them
ah okay i found the one you just said
paraxial berates uh i have that written
on some of my posters
and one of my posts
um
yeah so i
[Music]
what does it look like
uh looks like an animal like a cute cute
animal um like a crab with a shell a
shell crab oh is it purple or yellow oh
i don't have colors on them only like a
drawing and and the name
is it like a pointy shell or like a
round shell with a flower a round tub
with a flower
okay i have that potion but i don't know
what's good with it so it's called
hermit crab
or is it oh yeah is that h silent in
that word
no no no okay
english inconsistent language
maybe somewhere because like you have
those thingies connected no
maybe somewhere there's like a
a guide on what to do with the potions
maybe you have to make the wrap
you said you need yeah you need a third
rank
all of this is like
on my blackboard it all leads up to
one red rock so i suppose we're making a
red rock
yes okay
and on my on my recipe book it says
the blue a blue a dark blue rock plus a
light lighter blue rock plus the kfp
nugget rock equals the red rock so i
don't know if maybe like one of your
combinations makes the blue rock because
i already have the other two
uh yeah yeah i have like
three three uh combinations make the red
rock but uh the three or like each of
the three um combinations is made out of
other combinations and that combination
is made out of undercover and so on and
so on so i think we have to start from
the bottom
uh um
which
says
p e and f r or is it d e d e no that's a
d e i think or is it is it a d e or p e
it's a p e p e and f r
uh pr priests
aha wait
chris taxio
felix
forex
i have that in my book
and it's uh it's a it's it's like a it's
like a flower that's like bells like a
but but ah the others also look like
bells this one has
two
two leaves
uh two small leaves on each flower
and there's like
uh
on on each bell i guess and they're kind
of like
how they
where's the difference between those two
they look so similar um on the very
bottom of the flower there's like two
round balls
they're like
hanging down like grapes
oh
yeah you do maybe do you think you got
it
um
or like your chair i see it i see it i
got it yeah i see it
that's the pristoxy forex
okay and then the other one you said was
what do you what
ah the other one was fr like france
hungary promise
fungi
[Music]
barrex
promise
promise oh okay all that one looks
um
is it has one big body that's made up
out of three umbrellas
and then at the bottom it has like a
a handle
mushroom
yeah it's a mushroom yes yes
triple triple decker
yeah
rain feels so big they're already doing
so good
i think
do i like mix them yeah you should make
some and that turns into
pb peanut butter
okay and got it yeah with the
butter
if we can make a ammo in the am
um oh
but for that we need ox
okay that is
oxymericosaurus
oxymeocsaurus
wonderful i see it it's um
what do you call those screaming plants
screaming
plants what are they called again but
they look like they look like um
um they look like a carrots ah mantra
agora
mandra
yeah they look like mandrel gourds
because they have a fake
yeah yeah yeah
okay i mixed that with the peanut butter
yeah but this is like there's several
ones there's one the one that i mean
like a fin solo one
oh okay and it has like uh one leaf on
the left that's higher than the one on
the right
no no it has three leaves coming out of
the head uh
three leaves yeah
and they're like the first the one one p
pokes up to the top the other one
is like in the middle and the other one
goes i don't have that one i think we'll
have to make something like that is
there like
i don't know this one is
uh one is only used to make other things
but it does doesn't show
like it's a basic basal component i
think
um the ox yeah
um pb was made out of p e and f r but o
x is
is like a base component
unless we can do it the other way around
like
going both directions
like like making out of pb making p e
and f r oh probably um yeah there's like
an extractor yeah there's an extractor
oh
oh you could split it into two in that
case
if you have because we are trying to
make
am right now i guess i don't know if you
even have am or po that we would be able
to extract ox
i don't know what those are well we need
this we need ox but no we need we need
pb and ox in order to make am
so rx is part of am and ox is part of a
different one p o okay
what makes ox again
uh
i am and p.o
okay wait what makes the ones
uh
what is that
wait when you say what makes ox um like
there's nothing here that says ox is
made by this and this but you can split
um away out of two other ones
okay so what
what are the two other ones that you
could split it
um
uh
am and po
so basically there's a tree here and
from the very bottom that it was p e and
f r we did that and we got pb and then
if we would move upwards um if we
combine pb with a certain ox we would
get am
but
yeah but i don't know what like that i
don't know what the image is so i don't
know what to grab to try to split so
what are the letters again so i can read
you the full
[Music]
i don't know
the ones that that splits from
am
and po
okay two different mix
prima
philipso
primaxil that sounds like a harry potter
spell
[Music]
uh
oh yeah yeah i have that promaxial feel
like so it's uh it's a cute one it's uh
it's like two daisies um it doesn't have
a color so it could also be not a daisy
but
um
if we ignore the color it looks like a
daisy and it has two legs
and two leaves one on each flower
uh
neck there's two flowers yeah it's two
that connect to one
body
and it has really hairy legs it didn't
shave for quite some
time okay um
prima
primoxio felix so is that actually like
a name like the latin name of these
flowers
probably not i think they made it up oh
really
not very educated
do you think you can plant the flower
okay so you're looking for the mandrake
one
ah
no this one
is ox
oh x uh
probably yeah yeah yeah yeah cause like
all of the all of the mandrake ones no
no not all of them almost all of them
start with ox
i have a
oxymoron rate and
roxas and an
oxymoroxaurus which we
already
wait what did we already make that one
no which one is the one that where we
need to make the next one
now that we have the the one to mix with
pb or something
oh wait we have it what
oh we have it we have the
the you mean wait oh x was uh
oxymoroxiris
i don't know if that's the one if that's
the one that you described as a mandrake
then yes well yeah there's several but
this is the one that we first
tried yeah yeah that's that's the one
that one together with pb is am
you still have the pbe right
uh yeah
okay
then if you combine those i think you
can am
i'm in the
air like a really old looking mandrake
no
it has
all in all it has a very fitting body
and
like i see one that you probably mean
when you say old
where like the eyes are really big
no that's not the one the one that i'm
talking about it has like
um two arrows facing inwards as the eyes
and it has kind of a mustache
but a very thin body
free leaves
um
i mean they all kind of have not all of
them two of them have free leaves yeah
there's two
two mandarak mundo drag case that have
three leaves
and it's the thinner one out of those
two
uh
okay
one second
[Music]
all right can we start again from the
one that you said looks like a dandelion
oh yeah
uh
that was
what was that which one what which two
letters without supposed to be p p
i don't know because the the potion
bottles don't have like any of the names
on them i just have the translation for
the
um what is it called like when you
shorten a word
abbreviation oh yeah yeah
abbreviation yes
abbreviation key
but not like what potion it corresponds
to
uh
wait so i think we're yeah that was p.o
primoco philexo
and that that was the daisies yeah one
has a
leaf on the left and then a leaf on the
right exactly on the splitting stems
exactly and long hairy legs
and from that i'm supposed to get
yeah if you split that one you should be
able to get ox and one that is like
censored
okay that i don't know what that's the
only one that's censored i have it says
pl
which is just
paraxi
pressed exil prestaxio luarboret
a uh
crystal philoxorate
chris
axio no
uh prostaxious
i do not have that anywhere interesting
oh i guess it's like the secret yeah
that's why it's censored i guess yeah
okay okay so uh from the daisy uh
besides the pl one so the other one that
we got oh can you describe how that one
looks
uh
wait what wait which one do you want me
to describe
i i split the daisy ones and then there
should be other than the censored one
there's the other wicks yeah oh x uh the
mandrake
with three leaves
yeah it has uh it has free leaves it has
a face it's a
thin carrot
[Music]
and i mix it with what i mix ox with
what uh well uh you mix ox with pb and
then you get am
can you confirm the uh
identification of peepee
pb
was uh
peepee
pb was
wasn't that prestaxiophorics
um the one with the three
bell flowers and the cherries at the
bottom
okay
i think yeah it must have been that one
[Music]
what's the triple one
plus that one plus ox is a um
okay i think i need to make the kfp
juice again which is uh
oh
because i used it and i i got the wrong
thing apparently oh
because uh when i mix the things
i think you told me all i got was the uh
blue well you can't tell the color but
it's a old looking mandrake with two
leaves
that's not the one right oh no it
doesn't look old no i mean i mean if you
only see that one maybe you you do think
that one looks old but
out of all the ones i have it it looks
like more of the younger one
um well well
the one that you got do all of the
leaves like stand up straight
where are they
two leaves two flopping down ah you have
that one you have oh wait you have the
ali or mignole
oh that's the right one
um i
i don't know does it anyway say what
ally will make now what the abbreviation
for that is
are you saying with an o or an a
uh
a l a-l-i-o
i only have o through
[Music]
um
i only have things that start with
o-p-d-f
that's it
i don't know
i can't tell you
wait but you said two leaves that are
flopping down
yeah and that's this one
i will well that would probably be a.m
wait sorry right now you
well yeah and you can you can make like
that's a wait sorry i need one thing for
clarification the things that you carry
like for example the the flower is that
an actual flower that you're holding
no it's a potion
okay so a potion that's made out up out
of that flower i guess or something like
that okay
so but it has like what like
how do you recognize the the plants and
stuff on it
ah because the potion has it just has a
picture on it and so i'm just going off
a base of what like based off what you
describe
okay
and there's a name on it as well right
no there's no names on them i only have
a book that has the abbreviation and
then the full name next to it but not
connected in any way to identifying the
potion oh
okay uh and in that book
does it say anywhere what am stands for
no huh
okay well let me tell you that one is
elio mignon
and that's the one we need at like we
are pretty up high in that uh
um
yeah in the chain we need a we need to
mix am with po
but i suppose wait do we have po or not
i'm i'm confused i probably gotta start
from the bottom if it's one of the top
ones
or ask everybody oh let me check p po
would be made out of like one of the the
censored one and ox
so okay i don't think we can create it
the lick so oh but i have the censored
one
oh you have it oh yeah which one is ox
again oh x's
uh
oh x is that
the the the fin
the thin carrot
you have one of those
oh yeah oh okay then combine the
censored one with ox and we should get
pio
uh p.o is just it's the dandelion one
okay i think it's the dandelion oh the
daisies sorry daisy one okay so you have
that one too then we have am and po
okay so i just mix them yeah then we get
pf which is one of the three components
the main three components for the stone
so that one will already be finished and
we only need to do two more
okay i have pf
pf nice
nice nice good job you're saying no
no no it's noise
yeah okay then put that one on the side
and we start with the second one
okay
okay let's do
um
let's do i guess i'll start with the one
that's right next to it p-o we need p-o
and f-a let's start with p-o
p oh wait we already have p-o oh wait
already
where it one p-o is the the flower the
two flowers
ah but i used it can we make another one
yeah
which means we need the censored one
again
oh uh i have another one of those oh
okay then p o with f a f a do you have
the name for that
uh funky barracks funky funky town
fungi barracks
yeah this one okay i see it this is
already going much better than last time
i think we talk much more it's good just
good stuff
i think manga is like funky down oh
funky funky with those funky you're
gonna get really funky amen
chad are you following are we smarter
than you this time
the funky funky it looks like um it has
one two
three four big ones big um
heads
of
umbrellas separately
and a lot of small ones sticking out on
the side as well
uh and one relatively big one in the
back but it's like shaded out like it's
in the back it's dark so four big main
ones although one of them is
rather small
so rather small one on the left yeah
yeah yeah yeah
okay
i think you found it okay so that one
combined with po gives us
d l
down low it didn't give me anything i
think i have the wrong one so we'll
probably have to make whatever that one
because i mixed it together but nothing
popped out of the thingy what
yeah
what p p o and f a didn't give you
anything
and yeah fa okay so is there like a
chain for fa
uh no
both of the ones that i told you oh i
think you said pf no p oh
oh which one is that again p.o is the
one that has the censored one in it um
p.o is the flower okay the double flower
the double flower yeah we need to make
that one again we used it before but i
thought you had another one of that no
i think i used it
oh something else
um okay so if we need to remake it then
um
do you have
the censored one from before yeah the
the the the the fourier er
the old the old carrot that you said
that had two floppy
uh
leaves one to the one side one to the
other side that's the sensitive one
you don't have that one anymore
wait how how did we get that before
uh i remember oh wait no that's a.m i
didn't which one was the censored one
e-l-e-l
e-l was a censored one
i didn't i thought i thought it was pl p
l p l
p l
p l was p l
price tax c4 no wait for sexy for works
at the um
[Music]
uh prestaxio lorbrate
pristaxi ah yeah that's the one that i
don't have written anyway right right
right uh
but wait you have access to the censored
one
to p l
oh yeah i mixed it with the with the one
you told me i think and it didn't give
me anything
maybe i don't really have the
or umbrella thing that you're describing
we have we have pf right now right
that's one of the three main components
okay
but in order to make that
we used
am npo and for po we need an ox and
sensor that the po one we need again for
the next one
uh
wait do you have dl
anywhere wait no wait i need to first
ask what's the abbreviate i think i
already asked that what was the
abbreviation for dl
del follow just kate
d can you say that again
l follow this kid
alpha logistics
what is the first letter
e d like uh the
dolphin dolphin
d
i will have any of these
nuts
but
you don't have anything wait wait what's
here nothing
[Music]
do well
do i have anything here no
no extra recipes
no
okay okay thinking time
thinking thinking time
thinking time
something is missing maybe we can start
with the one on the very left first
maybe that helps us
um okay
okay that would need
sb and pg like facebook and pajamas
um
[Music]
okay that one
looks
uh like it has only one big umbrella and
only one
big handle it's a very
nice simple
true my nice mushroom nice mushroom
looks very simple
okay and then uh you said pa
pj pj
oh uh
peroxiophelix sorry all right that one
is a cute crab it's super cute
it has a flower on his head it has no
flower but it
looks like a [\h__\h] pile the shell
oh okay
i see it
you're just like okay
okay don't
come back
and it looks like it has a
butthole eyes
but that that's that's ot that's ot what
does ot stand for does that say it
anywhere in your thingy
uh
oxymerotoxis
it's okay we got a new one
okay
uh
so
do we need that one later for the middle
one no we don't need it okay but with
that we can get away h okay so with ot
and
p a that's the next one you need to make
uh we can get o h which is the next
opponent of the main three ones p a
what's the what's the full writing for p
a please
chris taxi oh philip sorry
prestaxio feel like sorry okay
that one looks like
five pieces of garlic
on one stick that has two big leaves
going on to the right side
perfect perfect explanation
all right i got it nice then combine
those two and we get the third the third
the third component
wait what i'm combining the garlic one
and then then ot the
mandrake yeah the old one yeah yeah yeah
that whole one
yeah
yeah yeah
butthole
[Laughter]
nice
okay now that didn't i feel like that
didn't help us for the next one that the
the one that we were first working on
but okay we got we got two main
components out of the three ones
then let's just reset let's reset our
brains
and start all over uh for the middle uh
uh component we're trying to get ol
a cute
cute ol a girl worker
um
p-o and f-a is the one that we're
starting off with
remaxiophalexia pimp for
maxillophyllaxia
maxi yes those are the two flowers we
have that currently right the two
flowers with one leaf each on one side
one to the left one to the right
uh
the daisy one the daisy one yeah
no i didn't have it okay yeah that was
our problem before
um
okay in order to make that one we need
ox and the censored one
uh
[Music]
ah
we we made peel before
um
we had we had ox before as well what
does ox stand for
um
oxymerc source yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
so we need that and we need the censored
one which was
something i didn't have written on here
so i don't know what it looks like
how did we do that before
what
[Music]
wait
you have
you do you have
the censored one you don't know which
one i mean when i say the censored one
right i have it oh you have it okay
and ox
oh
oh umbrellas
ah no oh
four umbrellas
waxes uh
oxymoroxaurus that's that's the fin
mandrake
that oh yeah yeah oh we have to remake
it okay
we we made that one by splitting
a.m
i think
no there it was a different one that we
split wait this is weird
we split oh wait no no i don't know i
didn't how did we get that one
we split
do you have p
do you just have p o lying around i'm
sorry if i keep on
um
asking the same thing
but then i'm gonna get it
p.o was
one of the flowers
uh
do like
um
we had p.o before and we split it and we
got the censored one and ox out of that
but like can you get the same one again
okay wait i have the uh i have the
daisies now
the daisy where premaxio philexo
which was was that p.o that was po right
then
that was that was peel before right
pramaxiophylexo is peel correct
uh
yes
okay okay
okay uh
split that one
no wait no wait don't split it
you have p.o
uh-huh oh okay keep that one safe we
need f-a-n
f-a stood for
uh
one of these no yeah probably what does
what does fa stand for
[Music]
did we not use that one before f a no we
didn't okay that one is the the one the
mushroom that has
um four big
umbrellas all separated and the small
one looks to the left side
and it has a lot of that's what i did
wrong tiny tiny oh okay has a lot of
tiny tiny tiny um heads sticking out as
well
you got that one
uh
f yes but
it gave me okay yeah i got it okay that
one combined with p.o
uh p p o was
the one you just got before that
combine that to get dl
what po is what this is that what pio
was the one that uh
should
be
the
two flat ones the daisy one for maxi
over alexa
for maximum that the double flower one
with the
one with the leaf to the left and one
was the leaf to the right
uh-huh oh that one is it i think it is
yes yes yes you must be
oh you did it already
chad says he already did it
you got the you got the dl already
you already combined them we got the
thing we need
good job
okay
yeah okay then we need the for the last
third beak component we need to combine
dl the one that you already got with pl
but pl is something that's
it has
no no daughter and no um
sun
it's it's just exists existing on its
own so i suppose
oh i got it i got a big uh mush ball
with like
eyes and symbols and arms sticking out
[Music]
but what
what
eyes and cymbals and mushrooms sticking
out
yeah
that's that's pl
or wait what oh i combined pl with the
one you told me too the l
oh and you got the next thing oh that
should be what does a whale stand for
can you check for me
you're working fast mrs watson
oh well
uh oxymerotoxis
no wait uh sorry oxy lure boy yes okay
yes let's combine that
with the other
main big ones that we got do you need to
me to help you recall which ones they
were
uh no but i only have like
okay we have we have o l we have o h and
we have p f
and those three make the stone
okay those three potions
you you have we have them right
let's go
oh i did it we did it we did it
i thought you barely slept how are you
able to use your brain so much
i don't know maybe maybe it helps my
brain function yeah maybe
you work better on on
a lack of sleep
it's a detective life you know
tell me more about detective life
oh so i can't get out of this room
though
and then i just gotta put the stone in i
think okay
yourself you were doubting yourself
why would you do that
i mean you're perfect with the potions
i couldn't have done it any better
i never picked a rock
oh what
i get a cutscene
are you seeing the same i is a sword
coming together in your scene
no oh
guaranteed
entire life no
i already have that i don't need it
[Music]
my father
my papa
i'm confused ami
i've been trapped in a cage no
i'm going to rescue i have a sword
no no it's disappearing nope
oh oh no there it is oh a woman came out
of my sword oh it's skyward sword all
over again you've restored the blade i
guess i did
and
and with it my my essence is your
cutscene done
no
oh he's here i've met a ghost
oh a genie a genie and a sword
you're gonna steal my soul they're
sacrificing me no what the [\h__\h]
is this a cult
[Music]
that's because they mean they're gonna
break
a curse and now they're talking about
tick-tock
desire for a lasting legacy drove him to
desperate measures okay well i'm in a
cage now so by his most trusted servant
thank you thank you thank you ghost is
that
is that cute maybe i'm angry ghost
my mind feels clouded
i don't know what the hell she's talking
about amen there is a power in me i
[Music]
oh follow this path and do not falter
still the cutscenes
waiting faster
okay i'm out of the cutscene uh weird
ghost this is getting spoopy
uh uh uh i'm gonna go left because i'm
left-handed are you left-handed or
right-handed i'm in
i'm right-handed okay i expected nothing
else
um okay
uh what is this
see i'm in the room i uh with uh
what do you call those
like armored puppets
and leathers
and arrows
oh
i'm quite crazy in here i need to break
out of my cage
oh
huh thank you oh you're welcome was that
me i don't know
i just turned around the leather and
then it made ding dong
oh you you let me out yes
baby
okay what was in the other direction
there's so
that was that was easy
yeah
okay then you got out what do you see
now
oh i'm in a throne room uh there's these
mannequins uh four of them which are
standing in a default position uh one is
turned to the
right and then there's a king sitting on
a throne
uh and a big red button i'm gonna press
it oh and it's turning the okay it's
like a puzzle
oh well i have four mannequins as well
um they look into different directions
and
yeah they're also in default poses
i don't know
one of them has an arrow to the right
side but he's looking frontal to me and
one of them has also an oh this lever is
broken what the hell
lever is broken but he looks
it looks uh backwards to me
i wrote hmm i went to the right side
this doesn't make any sense to me not
yet but we will figure it out amir we
will figure it out
uh and the others okay one looks frontal
to me
uh arrow to the right one looks to the
right arrow to the right
okay
does this have any meaning
no
[Music]
oh is that the throne are you down there
no
uh
okay wait well i'll just i'll just try
something i'll pull over
did something move
do it again uh
pulling again
[Music]
yeah
oh
what if i pull
this one did something move some
mannequin
uh no i think the cage moved i heard
something move but
um
oh one of them is moving i think again
again i did it again and again
and again
is he moving again
uh
i don't know i hear something moving but
i don't see anything moving
i i do hear like something constantly
moving like
um
one two three
every four seconds in between like every
five seconds i guess in total
oh there's some some clock or
like it sounds like a
a chain
um
like being pulled up something moved
something moved just now i'm pressing
buttons wait wait wait wait keep on
moving that keep on moving
nothing happened in that one because i
have two different rooms and they're
pretty step pretty far apart from one
another keep on moving keep on moving
okay now nothing
i hear something moving
[Music]
what what's moving
it sounds
it comes from that direction
it's moving
it's from here maybe you're above me and
maybe you're in the room above me or
something like that
yeah i think so because i'm hearing
whatever you're doing
you hear what i'm doing i'm not doing
right anything right now we hear this
like uh
this
did you hear that
uh i i heard when you were like
triggering stuff before but nothing was
moving because yeah i hear the clock so
it was a different sound
oh oh what about this one what happens
if i oh i can't move this one anymore
okay because i already moved it okay
[Music]
tell me about the knights again because
the only thing i have to interact with
is that button which uh it rotates the
knights
in a uh
clockwise
uh rotation
um yeah my knights i have four of them
one looks straight at me and i have a
like a lever in front of every knight
but when i pull it
the only thing that changes is an arrow
uh that is like sticking onto the
pedestal where the knight is standing on
so it moves from right to left right to
left every time i move the lever but the
mannequin himself doesn't move and
something just ding-donked
why people running out of time what
there's a time
i think so no way
no way i don't understand this puzzle
last one the one before was easier
yeah um is there anything else that
sticks out to you in your room
uh there's a king sitting in the throne
who's a mannequin and he has a big it's
a big red rock that we made in his chest
oh
did he steal it
other than that uh there's another round
room before the throne room that has the
two cages in it and then like a little
chair for somebody to sit in to watch
over the
room but uh that's it there's nothing
movable the only interactable things is
a big button which just wait a second
hmm
and uh
i found symbols hidden behind
behind each night
oh symbols oh wait what the hell
there was
just did you just in a moment i said
what the hell did you just like one
second before do something
uh probably can you do that again
i'm moving uh different
legs that are showing different
the lights just turned on here like the
oh i guess i'm letting light into your
room oh
yes like you like um
in front of
in front of every statue in front of
every mannequin i have a window
and oh
only in front of one mannequin
only that window
um now has light shining through
okay so try turning it uh what that
lever that's that's the only one that
has a broken lever um okay well let's
move to a different one okay uh
this one
okay yeah yeah yeah okay oh
interesting
um i moved that one but i don't know did
that do anything i'm moving the lever ah
do anything one thing that just stood
out to me is when the light was off they
all have like some kind of flag behind
them or or curtain or whatever
and they look black to me when the
lights are off but now that the lights
are on this one looks yellow to me and
the other one looked blue to me
the one that i couldn't move but this
one
um i guess like
maybe the colors have some significance
as well
yeah because um
so like the fl the flags that i'm moving
out of the way each have like a
different color to represent like each
night and so the one i just moved out of
the way to shine the second light
was a green checkerboard and then i also
have the first one that i moved was a
yellow one and then there's another one
across which is a
red and white checker and then there's
another one that's just blue the one
that you
the the one where you um turned the
light on for me like most recently
what's the color there
oh uh green
okay for me that's yellow
[Music]
um
by the way when i want to ask chad one
thing that's been bothering me is do is
are my fps slow my
my own body's fps is is that really so
am i fps though
yes why
why
but the game is fine
a little choppy okay but it's not a big
deal okay
okay okay anyway back to the game thank
you chad
um
the one let's go to the one
where you turned the light on for me
um
which
i guess which direction does the
mannequin look
too
uh
well i can move the butt when i press
the button they all rotate clockwise but
none of them are
sorry uh two of them are synced up but
uh the other two are looking in
different directions
they could look in any direction because
i can spin them
okay i cannot spin them but the one
okay maybe you need to have them look in
the same direction as they look for me
but but this one's yellow and it's green
on your side maybe so maybe it's like
maybe
maybe i need to find one um
i still lever for that one
the lever on the lever i have the lever
for that one it's
like i can move it from oh can you do it
okay well the arrow looks real okay okay
okay oh all right i see
uh so when you trigger the lever what it
does is it does correspond to like the
yellow one like you said oh it
corresponds to it but what happens is
that um
it switches the
rotation so
now instead of turning uh clockwise it's
turning counterclockwise
now i have three of them facing the same
direction and i suppose maybe i'm
supposed to copy
like uh
you think they should all be facing the
same direction
okay
um
oh
so
[Laughter]
all right wait i have i have three of
them facing the same direction if we
want to go to the other room or the
other side okay okay okay other room
let's see what the colors are over there
red blue and yellow and i guess maybe
here's red and
green okay one light is on right now oh
i see
i see a little lever for that one okay
it's red but wait wait wait don't pull
it
did you on the on the other one did you
um
just check oh
oh i guess it's fine okay it's good all
right uh yeah for the
this one the arrow right now looks to
the right side i don't know if that's
like
does that move that doesn't mean that
yours will move to the right side
whenever you do that
um maybe yeah let's see i'm pulling the
lever and i was looking to the left side
okay uh can you do it again okay now
let's look into the right side
arrow
you do it again wait
i don't know
uh
um
[Music]
when it moves right now which direction
moves does this one move
uh
clockwise
clockwise okay then i think mine is
currently set to clockwise as well
oh oh does it if i okay now does it
still move clockwise
uh no okay okay okay so i control that
okay which
oh we did it
[Music]
i didn't even touch the last
oh my god i knew exactly what was going
on of course we both knew
oh
i'm gonna go with stories yeah i see the
ghost too
talking to a jester
oh you see the same cutscene oh you must
find the way
oh
is there pointing at you
yeah she did
we'll play this
hey
oh is this a boss fight or what
this game is more
like magical and
fantasy like than i thought it would be
oh okay so i don't know about your room
but in my room now behind the king there
are four different knights and one is
holding a hammer one is holding like a
bath sword one is holding an axe
[Music]
yeah i see the knights too but i have
shields
okay okay
oh i can take them yeah yeah me too
oh pretty shield
what should we do with them
there's a text in the middle so maybe
that gives us a hint do you do we have
do you have a text yeah good night
knight closest to the king's left hand
side wields the sword closest to the
left the king's left
and where's the sword okay i put that
there oh wait i see more text
the dragon can be found somewhere to the
king's left hand side
dragon i guess that's a shield
oh yes i have a shield with a dragon
uh so this one over oh
you see where i'm jumping oh wait uh
where are you wait wait wait wait
would it be like the king i see this one
this one
yeah the last one okay
um i have a shield that has a a bear and
uh
i suppose uh
big burp slash phoenix
oh and one is uh what do you call that
again a deer deer with corn
you put the you put the dragon one on
the last guy
yeah i i put it i put it this one here
the dragon one is okay okay
it says the deer cannot be found at
either end the ax wielding knight is
somewhere to his right hand side
the ax willing what
[Music]
oh then i'm putting right there oh it
says for the shields it says the deer
cannot be found at either end
somewhere in the midnight
yeah
uh what are your texts day
my text says the boar has the mace
wielding knights somewhere to his left
hand side
boar the boar the boar on the left-hand
side wait i have a boar
oh there's a bora bear is this a
is this a board
does that make sense if the dragons
the boy has the mace willing knight
somewhere to his left side and then it
says the hammer railed in phoenix
stands somewhere to the deer's right
hand side
peanut okay wait can you put the dragon
one on the first one the dragon one
on the first one and the guy next to him
yeah on the guy next to him okay
or bear whatever uh on the last one the
bear on the last one
and okay
well the boar has the me smelling knight
somewhere through his left hand
also navatek says the knights at both
ends do not wield the hammer
okay so it's this guy
okay so we have all the weapons in now
it's
the rest what do you have left i have
put the dragon in the board so i guess
the deer and the phoenix
wait wait wait wait wait uh
though
uh
the the hammer whaling phoenix stands
somewhere to the deer's right hand side
the hammer yeah the hammer's here uh the
one closest to on the other side
okay
and then the phoenix the other one on
the other one okay let's see if that
works it would be a miracle
i thought we did it right oops
wait
wait wait wait wait do it
we can't try
to a lock strat again
no no that was not it
wait i i i can you read your texts again
yeah uh the knight closes the king's
left hand
wields a sword maybe it's reverse
because i did it i'm like uh
oh yeah yeah i know kiara has an echo i
think it's just i've been acting maybe
we should change everything all right so
i'm gonna put it
i'm just gonna swap it around just in
case so do the same thing like take it
from the first guy on either side and
then swap it oh okay
[Music]
now um
on the wherever i'm jumping the one with
the mace that one should have either the
board the dragon
right these here uh this one has oh it
has wind
the boar or the dragon evil one
uh
i don't remember which order the boar
has the mace wielding knight somewhere
to his left hand side
why is your echo on yeah i don't have an
echo one
i'm not using the in-game audience
i think i'm bothered okay well it
stopped now all right quick okay
and then
whatever is here the deer in the phoenix
somewhere i don't know which order
four drag
wait let me read this again the hammer
wielding
phoenix
stands somewhere to the deer's
right-hand side
so the hammer should be where the
phoenix is
right yeah yeah yeah okay is the hammer
here no no
the hammer is to the phoenix right side
so the phoenix would be on the axe
phoenix would be
uh right side from your side
you need a rest uh oh here okay
uh okay well that that might have been
what was
messed up on the last time because we
switched sides so
oh
oh we'll try it like this wait the boar
has the maze
knight somewhere to his
left-hand side
the boy wait the mace
the mason the board goes on the sword
the boar
what the board goes on the sword
that's what how i would maybe understand
it too
wait the board before the board
the board the boy
the board has the maze swimming night
somewhere
[Laughter]
whose perspective are we talking about
the knights perspective so it'd be the
same it'd be your perspective too since
the nice the night is facing outward so
oh
the boar has to miss one two
night so much left so the board the boar
should be
the bush so
so the board should be to the left side
of of of the so somewhere on this side
right
is that that's what they mean i guess i
can swap
them and then
the banner wielding thing what else is
on the left side that's what i want to
know
i think we're messed up
i think we're gonna have to start again
okay no problem the knife circuit
everything you cannot wield the hammer
the hammer is currently uh
nowhere okay
chill princess june
i'm so dramatic
oh um
let's start over yeah uh
let's start with like figuring out your
first text
like oh it was actually oh time limit
oh okay yeah oh oh dramatic
retry
is it echo again i think it's in game
that's weird
i i don't even use pushy talk right now
eh
release me from my cage
i will do wait
i need to release you from the cage
again
probably hold on wait another cutscene
i'm skipping
skip okay
[Music]
wait what
but we we did this one
no
we didn't
[Music]
it's like a pretty good probability of
us getting it again
cause it was only the one night so
and
[Music]
oh no why don't they make us do the skin
make you suffer
what the hell game
what okay which one are we starting with
let's open some curtains i guess uh
yellow
yellow i don't know where which wherever
yellow was once again let me see was it
here
yes okay
but i don't know where i left that one
off last time no way
[Music]
okay i moved it
it's to the left right now go to the
other side of the room the other room
there's no way we can do this like so
he's
the probability is so it's so easy there
are all the other three already lined up
it's just like the other one okay
um yeah red red okay i think it at the
end position was this don't know
is this not the end position no maybe
not okay i moved it i moved the leather
um
how's it going
uh
move it again
okay
what
because there's only so many
possibilities it would be easy to
replicate it skipping skipping
what
okay okay i am shook okay so going from
the left
the king's left king's wait which is
also your left okay yes i'm taking all
the shields
yes okay well it can't one thing for
sure it can't be this uh order can't be
dragon
and elk here okay
um
so
uh on the very left side the board
the board has the mace wielding knight
somewhere to somewhere to his left hand
side
so what even one of those
yeah somewhere to his left-hand side
yeah where you put is that the main snow
that was the hammer the mace maybe put
it here
yeah and i'll put the board wait where's
the bullet right the board yeah the
board the boar
[Music]
and
what's your first text
uh the knight closest to the king's left
hand all
side wields the sword which i have there
and then it says the deer cannot be
found at either end the axe will deny is
somewhere to his right hand side which
means the axe is at the end
right yeah this is right so then the
deer would be this one yeah
and it says something about the deer
here too the hammer wielding phoenix
they have a whirling phoenix stands
somewhere to the deer's right hand side
so the hammer should be here
on the very right no but it's your left
the the knight closest to the king's
left hand side wields the
lord
wait what wait wait what what what what
does it say to say again
night the king's left hand side wields
the sword
the knight closest to the king's left
hand yeah that's that's the sword yeah
that's correct but the
uh the hammer wielding phoenix stands
somewhere to the deer's right hand side
we have the
yeah i would say the hammer would go
here yeah you put it there that's okay
okay okay okay yeah we we did it right i
think
the knights but wait no
wait but the knights at both ends do not
wield the hammer
even though it should be standing
somewhere to the deer's right hand and
the hammer wielding things anyway the
phoenix goes onto the hamper but the
hammer can't be
oh maybe the deer goes on now
oh wait you put the
and
uh
the deer on the sword wait a second here
does it say the ears right
is this it
come on give us another lucky try
nope
um because the dragon can be found
somewhere to the king's left hand you
put the dragon there right on the left
side
uh
dragon dragon is on the very
right
and
what does it say about the dragon in
thingy yes i know chad there's double i
are your
know i have ears uh the dragon can be
found somewhere to the king's left hand
side oh then it must be on this side
and some somewhere on his left hand side
oh then it must be somewhere over here
[Music]
what does this say about the deer
can you read the daring
uh it said the deer
it says the deer cannot be found at
either end the axe wielding knight is
somewhere to his right hand side
the axe is on the right
[Music]
the phoenix stands somewhere but now the
phoenix is next to the theater as well
so no this side must be correct yeah
i mean it could still be on the
i don't know
here's writing
the hammer wielding phoenix
somewhere
ham wait what that's that's an axe
though the phoenix must be on the hammer
what is this what is that the hammer
the hammer whaling phoenix
stand somewhere on the deer's right-hand
side
but the hammer is also not at the end
but the if the deer is on the sword then
that still makes sense
because it's to the right of the sword
regardless of the space between it
wait the deer is on the sword why did i
switch it out again then
that's it
it says this is the axe
[Music]
uh
what's next to the axe
wasn't there one i don't know
well then
the boar has wait what about the board i
haven't switched out the board in a
while the boar has the may swirling
knights somewhere to his left-handed
side
oh i mean that works if you put the deer
on the sword it sounds like
wow
wait wait wait the deer and the sword
the deer is on the sword right now
okay yeah the boy has the maze-willing
knight
somewhere just left in this yeah but
then no then the board since the since
the mace is on the very left now
well it could be any of the nights then
because it doesn't mean it has to be
directly
okay bye we're running out of time okay
so the board is not on the very left
no wait no wait wait the board has the
mace building knight
so okay okay okay so the board should be
on the right side
yeah because the le the mace should be
on the left side to the board okay okay
somewhere on the right side so which one
of these two is incorrect um
board
need a rest
oh
[Music]
nice
oh
[Applause]
we found each other
yeah
[Music]
no can we just get out of here now
choose quickly
we have to choose who dies why
why
a good question i don't know
okay i'm just sacrificing myself
well you're phoenix i guess you'll get
revived in the end even if i don't
revive i want you to leave
okay
we'll meet again
but wait why
now why
how's
i don't understand what what what why
did we get into this [\h__\h]
i'm fine chad i'll revive don't worry
[Laughter]
what oh wait oh the end of the cutscene
what is this story i don't understand
dude
i focus too much on nothing about the
story okay it's about the journey though
it's about the riddles
yeah
i think the end and the ending is also
part of the riddle because
i know what the [\h__\h] happened
what what what's to read on here i think
i think somebody had to sacrifice
themselves to
i don't know they like set that line so
fast i don't remember what she said
so that the world doesn't
you know
crumble and this is here
[Music]
peace do we do all of that for that one
gun
uh yeah for the flare gun so now i can
escape and
what
will remain we got a flare gun from dad
that's
that's all we got
i don't know i don't think it's supposed
to like really make sense you know it's
just
wait but this was much shorter than i
thought it would be we were the last
riddles were kind of easy or like easy
to at least like randomly succeed in
yeah
well we only had we only had those two
chapters left so i guess wow
wow
yeah that was fast um we're like pretty
smart so
i
i didn't even bring up my talking topics
today um i had talking topics
i want okay let me bring them up now
okay okay i'm it
what did you eat today
um
[Music]
the key you brought the king back
by sacrificing yourself i think oh okay
my dear friend
you never
cease to entertain
you've played the part of steward long
enough
it is hard time for royal commands to
resound in these holes once again
oh yes my liege but
you're
your last remaining inferior is punished
you are keen
on a good sign
[Music]
i need to look up the meaning of this
game
[Laughter]
the gesture sounded a little bit like
you but you'll sound much cuter
oh thank you wow thank you thank you
steam for doing that you stupid [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] whatever i have i have many
steam accounts okay just shut up
[Laughter]
now i'm gonna get a million friend
requests there as well great okay oh
it's okay
uh so okay what did you eat today
oh uh i had um a like one fourth of a
chocolate chip pancake and then did you
make that yourself
no i i ordered it okay and then um
i had some
eggs with spinach and ham
i don't like spinach
oh it tastes good eggs i like it
and then i had some fruit
so everybody only really sounds like
breakfast
yeah i had breakfast oh yummy
i'm gonna make pizza now
i was really excited for my pizza oh
shoot you just find me i have to
order pizza i'm gonna i'm ordering you
have to order pizza yeah okay like
i was gonna send them breakfast today
but um what they were like oh we're not
gonna be there so can you just send us
we want this pizza at this pizza this
time so
do you just send food to them every day
uh it's because it's someone's birthday
so oh
oh
only today food delivery by amen i might
eat yeah
well when it's like when there's like a
holiday or something i'll send them food
or like somebody's birthday oh that's so
sweet
how kind of you
you haven't eaten anything today you're
just gonna have pizza later oh i had i
had i had breakfast cereal and then i
had before before dj kami which was
before the stream i had i made soup i
made noodle soup with sausages cut up
sausages
oh noodle interesting yeah
was that so interesting it was a pretty
basic never heard that
soup with sausage and i don't think i've
ever maybe like an italian soup i've
seen like a sausage in it
it's like super a super basic soup that
you make for children here yeah super
basic children what kind of like egg
noodles oh
normal soup noodles like fancy really
tiny noodles
and
fin really really not not like the ones
that you use for like a pasta spaghetti
or whatever but
yeah like soup noodles
and then and then cut up sausages yeah i
made that because i had cut up i had
sausages left over now i'm gonna make
pizza and that was my motivation for
playing the game today pizza
nice but it's not ordered pizza it's
frozen
oh that's so tasty sometimes it's just
better isn't it i i love this one frozen
pizza i'd say with tuna
oh
yeah
that i'm like eating tuna pizza and a
lot of my viewers i think mostly from
america they were like
red tuna pizza wood but it's so common
here it's so good is it like the kind of
tuna like from a can
i mean like i shred it up tuna yeah kind
of yeah all over it and then like onions
and stuff but it's so good like i'm
usually not the type that eats fish a
lot but tuna pizza is so yummy it's
super quiet um you should
a fish is really good for you it's you
know yeah a lot of things that help your
brain so if you i think if you go to an
italian like a really authentic italian
restaurant where they serve pizza i
think that would maybe have tuna pizza
as a choice on the menu normally
but i was so surprised to hear that it's
not very common outside of uh
europe
oh no i think i think in japan
i think of yeah yeah definitely because
but they make it like they japanize it
by like adding mayonnaise to it which i
don't agree with
no that's like tuna salad that's like
tuna salad pizza i guess so but they
just put mayonnaise on everything over
there
i like how you say it i like you say
that word mayonnaise mayonnaise
uh i love mayonnaise but i don't think
you should put it on everything no i
don't agree with that
that doesn't sound too bad to me male
pizza it's it's edible that's for sure
but
it's not my my first choice of topping
yeah no no
and like olive says topping i don't like
black olives but that's good because
i'll give you my leftover olives oh yeah
yeah
okay amen i'm going down my list i
wanted to say because i never thought of
it today at digikommi
you said amitori like
like
rainbird or candy bird and i would like
to say if anything i would prefer to be
called candy bird because
you are
you're sweet and enjoyable and desirable
like candy
while rain is melancholic and you're not
that easy oh sweet and enjoyable and
desirable so candy bird must be good
that's so sweet and
like cute
would you read that off a script you
wrote that down in your notes too i
wrote that down and it was like i gotta
tell that later to amen because i
thought of it and i wanted to say it
smoothly but
that one was like a scrape
i didn't want it
it's cute a candy bird it's kind of cute
yeah but but
that's just the official translation but
it will yeah don't call us candy bird
that's kind of weird i think it sounds
like it sounds like a
like a
70 or no like a 60s rock band or
something
oh
yes
rainbird could be like the melancholic
edgy emo version of that oh yeah
yeah
they sing like songs about
how how
they're all alone and no one trusts no
they don't they trust no one and it's a
sad sad world
okay well candy bird is more like
yeah i am
candy
candy candy that's my candy bird
yeah yeah yeah
that's cute
let's make a song called candy bag
okay okay one day one day candy bar
releasing soon tm
did you guys enjoy uh did you call me by
the way was it chat here were you there
were you there
it was like you guys have fun spamming
in the chat i actually didn't have the
twitch chat open i had it
yeah i wish i had seen it
i just i don't know why it doesn't think
of it it was it was very sweet very
supportive thank you guys for being so
supportive um
yeah thank you i
i believe you yeah a lot of people
apparently don't have a twitch account
though and that's why they oh didn't
didn't like read it all but thank you
for still showing up thank you
um yeah
yeah it was fun it was um
i i think from all of the
panels we did this year
i think this was the one i had the most
fun at
um which is a good day and good good
questions good yeah interacting thank
you ami for being seriously
[Laughter]
you did not only advertise
sparks
randomly during the panel but you also
put it uh put it in in the description
of the
stream of your uh was it of the waiting
room or of of this this stream which one
was it oh i think it was from this
stream that's because i had it in the
last stream
i just went i just scrolled back and
used the same uh i didn't even know you
put it in there last time i just noticed
it today
because it's because i went to your
channel originally to like copy the
like your channel link but then i i went
into your description oh as it was i
copied the permission text from your
channel and then i also highlighted the
sparks from your channel and i
i like by accident i was like i'll just
put that in there too
but you kept it on purpose
yeah
i'm it
i
i i feel like
you're so amazing
because
you always
think of like
others like me
and the others in myth like rather than
being selfish
and putting yourself first
and only
advertising yourself
you were your retweet so much on twitter
uh i always wanted to say i really
appreciate that because you you're so
supportive of everyone in her life you
you think of like instead of like uh
having to succeed or wanting to succeed
all alone you think of like the bigger
picture you want to succeed with all of
us together
i like seeing like you guys i mean not
to say i don't like seeing myself
succeed either but uh you know
i like that i like seeing you guys
succeed
more
i guess
yeah
but that also shows like fulfillment
from that you know yeah but it also
shows like in in the way you try really
hard to make stuff like the one year
anniversary great like you
you you do your best to
put something great out there that
involves all of
it for us it's fun
yeah but you could have done it alone
and made it fun but you involved us in
in this and following things that
are in the works now of course could it
be more fun with you guys
sweet almond
you're so sweet
you you make me wanna better myself
yeah really good person shut up
you know i'm i'm always very nervous
when i'm around you but
um
i don't keep talking and goes doki doki
but because i
i want
i think i think
well it's only when i'm on a one-on-one
collab with you
when it when we're surrounded by more
people then it's like whatever but when
it's just us i feel like i
i
this confession time today this is being
honest today but i
this is like in a little it feels a
little bit like in school where
um
i kind of want to impress the cool kids
and you feel like the cool kid to me
so whenever we're one-on-one i am like
nervous because like
i would i mean i mean to like me
you don't have to worry about that oh
you know i told you in the past before
anyways
[Applause]
[Music]
i love you love it
i love you too
stop
i mean you're going on vacation soon
right
oh yeah for a few days oh i'm happy for
you because i also just came back from
my vacation
huh
yeah it looks really nice yeah did you
see yeah you looked at some of the
pictures that i sent to the discord but
i saw them i i showed even more like on
my i'm backstream but
it's like it was really really nice it
was like in the mountains
yeah i want to see that
it was on the countryside yeah
yeah yeah it looks really pretty i
originally wanted to go like to some
beach but in europe
uh
i would have i would have probably had
to go to like spain or greece like italy
would have already been too cold i think
but italy would have been the closest
but yeah
and all the flying around would have
taken up too much time so i ended up
just staying in my country yeah it is
yeah it is a little bit stressful for
such a short vacation
um because it was only like
three nights four days um
yeah yeah anyway
um i don't know you probably can't uh
say where you going on your vacation
until maybe afterwards i don't know
after yeah okay looking forward to it or
you can tell me in private
yeah i will i'll tell you after we're in
the stream
i'm excited i'm happy that you're taking
a vacation when was your last vacation
i know it wasn't that long ago i was
like uh a week i think it was during the
council debut so oh you're right you
weren't there yeah yeah
oh
well it's good that you're taking them
like every once in a while
yeah i'm already planning my next
vacation
good
i wanna go skiing
it's fun because then you know like part
of a lot of our content has to do with
uh telling stories or you know like our
experiences and talking and yeah yeah
yeah and you can't really gain like
anything new from
uh just like sitting in
the game and yeah exactly in a chat like
you don't get any new experiences to
talk about exactly that's why i kind of
i ran out of things to say
oh yeah guys in chat there was somebody
in the chat like a few days ago and they
said blah blah blah blah blah like
that's the only thing you get which you
know sometimes it's fun but
brain needs more
yeah nourishment yeah yeah yeah yeah i
agree after i came back from the
vacation i i still have some things to
talk about i hope i will
have some for a while but i'll run out
soon again and then i'll need to go
outside again
yeah gather some material
[Music]
did you sing that before in your kadoken
uh no maybe it will oh but i did because
i had a version of the song stuck is
like uh
wait how's it go oh
that shakira song oh yeah
[Music]
i always thought those lyrics were a
freaking joke but i realized they are
real why is she being like mikasa
that's like the easiest spanish that
people pick up out of
like granted
probably yeah my house your house is
catchy
[Music]
yeah she's singing about like my house
is is your house
i don't know actually i've never really
listened to the lyrics i don't know if
they're like coherent like that oh
oh i need to look deeper into it
yeah but if you ever see material girl
and you need some some backup
uh vocals i already sang it in my most
recent karaoke unarchived
and you can sing along with that because
you do that and yeah i have a i have a
lot of uh karaokes to catch up on
because i haven't i haven't i don't
think i've done any duets from your
newest one and then there's also like a
i don't think i've done any council ones
yet and there's a lot of people
cali did a
really edgy karaoke recently oh yeah
yeah yeah
there's so much material for you
material
to sing along with
i want to listen next time you do it i
want to listen again the bee kyoku just
it got me good it got me good ame
i would say for the next karaoke it
won't be because it's going to be this
coming week uh
it's not be
a small ame but it is a regular small um
not in the b
not as a b
okay just regular okay that's fine
i i like any kind of almond i was
thinking because you did b
i was thinking i kind of want to uh make
like a frog kiana
[Music]
yeah
because that's kind of been like uh
a thing at kfp and i don't know i kind
of look good as a frog
i don't know why but it looks good
that's the contrast of like your hair
like orange and green because they're
uh
they're not exact opposites but um
but i need to go together by the way i'm
just saying it's not my it's not gonna
be any like halloween costume guys i'm
not going to be a frog i don't want to
do that i want to do like a wrong
costume some sometime in the future i
want to commission it
okay
there's some very specific things if
well i'll tell you afterwards oh earlier
yes
i'm curious but i also
want you to sleep because you barely
slept
oh yeah
are you tired
well you know how like when you get
really tired and you don't really feel
so tired anymore it's kind of like that
oh yeah i i know that feeling oh but you
should make sure to get enough sleep
anyway when is your next stream
uh tomorrow
i oh well it's not confirmed yet but
it's a collab in minecraft so i don't
want to say
ah
oh i see it on the schedule i'm not
gonna say it then
oh you have enough time to sleep for
like i don't know
did you always put out your schedule no
so are you going to make it now
probably not
i think i will make my schedule now and
put it out there yeah oh cause it's like
monday for you already huh it's uh
no it's still sun sunday yeah it's still
sunny
oh but we're getting closer to monday
[Music]
um oh oh we'll have a ttrt on tuesday
again yeah
i think this time uh wait who it was on
whose channel was it was on inna's
channel so i think it'll be on gooda's
channel oh this time well yeah i don't i
don't think we have really like decided
on it yet but it might be a good channel
yeah
oh we were doing it in order of uh
the tutorial oh is she next okay i think
so yeah
no i don't know next
i felt like we did gouda's channel
fairly recently maybe i'm confusing
things
we will see oh it's my turn it's your
turn
yeah why why why why you don't have to
do anything
kelly is doing all of it
i know i had to press i had to press a
button damn add all those damn buttons
fm
it will be fine you just have to lay
back and be water
we're going on a new mission this time
oh yeah right because she's just
listening
she's gonna gonna put us through for
hell
again
yeah
i have a bad feeling i feel like we got
out really easily we got out really easy
because inna had like some really good
roles
and last time
both
both ina and gooda and then us both of
us were like like getting there
and we both like even if one group would
have failed the other group would have
kind of found a way to
uh
get the solution last time yeah at the
same time but my rules were so
so
to
last time
yeah we got screwed over
for real it was so unlucky like we were
trying so hard and i was like doing the
same things over and over and over again
like trying to try to look into a
freaking drawer i was rolling for dad
well it's a great time fighting a
vampire so whenever i fought off the
vampire i was like okay i want my next
role to be looking into the drawer and
then i failed and then the vampire had
enough time to get back up and attack me
again so i had to take care of him again
and i had to look into the drawer again
and i failed again and
i think he got off pretty easy because
there were like a few turns where callie
was like he's preparing to pull his
knife out he's pro he's approaching you
with his knife he's holding his knife
above you
oh yeah but his he can't do anything
against me when i shoot his eye out
yeah
that's a good point maybe what happened
with our rolls we didn't like uh which
was like blowing the dice or like kiss
the dice or something
we should blow blow onto the dices and
kiss them
yeah okay i'll remember for next time i
did indeed not do that last time yeah
yeah that's probably why
goddamn by the way i roll some [\h__\h] oh
it's rake it's ironic it's all right
it's a wig
yeah cali it
she had yeah on the contrary she had
really really good uh rolls throughout
the whole thing
yeah
suspicious am i
suspicious i have to investigate yeah
invest speaking of investigating i
i am
maybe maybe it's because i'm looking up
to you but i'm just recently
recently um really into
investigations
oh like a true crime stuff yet
yeah
i'm constantly watching that right now
i'm like it's like my new netflix it's
insane i'm like watching that before
this stream and before did you call me
and yesterday and every time i wake up
everyone watching there too
wait wait which specifically i don't
know any of them did you watch them oh
um i haven't really been watching them
too much but i've been reading some like
true crime stories like i read a book a
book about this lady serial killer yeah
when when did you read a book
uh it was like last week only a
different one this week she reads books
ahmed ahmed we have something in common
i recently read a book too
oh
you have a kindle
no um they're really good i mean don't
get me wrong the book that i read this
week was the first book that i read in
like um
six seven years
oh
what kind of book was it is it like uh
oh no it was a tolkien book
okay nice those are pretty big huh those
are meaty it's it's not like a lord of
the rings book because i already know
i'm sorry i wanted to pick up something
new to read like during my vacation so i
went to the bookstore and i looked for
any book but i didn't know any of the
recent offers and what books are good
right now and it was kind of a time
pressure so i just went to like an
author section that i knew that i was
talking and then i chose like one of his
like
um one book only um
like books like not not a series so
um yeah which one was it the one that i
got the
you probably don't know it have you ever
read talking
uh no i i i haven't i think because uh
my aunt like collects books and stuff i
think i've tried at some point but i was
like this book's too damn thick
do you not like the genre or you're also
like i don't like the genre i just have
never like gotten into it but i probably
would like it i think
i still think though that that you read
a true uh crime book
it's so funny yeah you're still in
character i shouldn't be more in
character too
it's a little surprising because usually
i like like fantasy sort of books or
like whatever like uh young adult novels
they used to read those a ton but i
tried reading and i was just like i
can't do this and now i'm for some
reason my brain is like yeah i want to
read like either
you know non-fiction or like uh
like recently i've been reading a book
about simulations oh and like uh
simulations
the world building is pretty intense
yeah it's about building a simulation
that
is complicated but essentially they're
like creating these virtual building
blocks of life where they go through
explaining like how they make a from an
atomic level create atoms virtually and
how they kind of
uh evolve into you know like more
advanced things from there and i guess
yeah it's
it's a bit much sometimes that's
that's probably not something that i
would pick out of the shelf
i'm just trying to get through it but
it's kind of interesting because i i
like reading it because it talks about
like some time relativity stuff and like
going through experiments because when
you're uploaded to that virtual world
like uh you experience time differently
so
that's pretty interesting you know
right now when you're talking to me
oh my
oh
all that goes through my head is like
cryptic signs
i didn't understand english it was just
like cryptic cryptic signs and stuff
i didn't
understand but we used to get a kindle
they're really good reading no but i
don't i mean i don't read that often
that was this was just like one time one
time only um
got it yeah
but maybe maybe we'll pick up
another book after that one and then
another who knows who else maybe
maybe i'll
get caught in the web of books
maybe because i'm running out of netflix
so
oh
you can't run out i mean if you run out
of netflix you just go to another
subscription service yeah i'm running
out of all of them no but
i do have i don't have a one two ten i
have a i have a disney u plus
subscription that i
have since like three months and i
haven't used it once
oh
yeah i usually i'll do that i sign up
for subscription and then i i don't end
up using it but then my family is like
oh do you have a subscription for this
yeah guys please use it because i'm
paying for it and i'm not using it
yeah i mean why not share because you
can usually usually share those so why
the hell not yeah share with friends
why not why not i'm gonna
watch some crime stories after this i
guess
yeah
i'm in the middle of one right now i'm
not gonna mention any any cases
because i guess that's maybe problematic
but yeah uh it's very interesting
i think the algorithm got me there was
this i think this one this one i can
maybe talk about but there was this
video that got a lot of people in the
algorithm the one that explains like how
you can tell uh like a real
uh
from a fake one like one that's faking
it
oh yeah yeah i know you're talking about
that channel that like psychoanalyzes
like criminals yeah those are really
interesting
ics this one yeah yeah
it was very interesting to see uh
how how um how ridiculous people act
when they're trying to get out of it and
try to act like a psychopath well yeah
very interesting
yeah
i've been watching a ton of those oh
and now i'm in there too are you
sneezing
no okay you look like you're about to
sneeze
me yeah
oh no
i'm just looking down at something
i'm playing with this little screw thing
screw
a square
this little adapter for a microphone uh
mount
i mean i'm i'm mad
yeah you know i remember remember when
we set up
on the
the small 3d
oh yeah yeah and i asked you like we
talked a little bit about cable
management
and how my room's freaking mess and i
was like yo is yours also freaking mess
with creators
and you said yeah right
yeah it's really really bad i have so
much [\h__\h] like so many cables for
everything
so bad but i actually while i was gone i
had someone um
take care of my cats and that person
also did cable management and now i'm so
nice it's so clean i'm not tripping over
cables anymore nice yeah
i told you you could hire somebody to do
it they'll do it for you i didn't even
have to hire anybody
it was done voluntarily yeah
it's cool yeah i'm glad it's all cleaned
up now it looks really good now yeah
i remember a picture of mine
oh yes
maybe you should hire someone it's like
i don't know how people do it it's like
magic like how can you not end up with a
big big knot of cables
how not how how is it pretty planning
but then more and more you buy more and
more things and you add more and more
like equipment and then more and more
cables are there and it's just not all
there from the start so even though you
planned from the beginning to have it
all clean the more and more new stuff
you get the more the more chaos you get
especially now with the with the new vr
stuff i have an ex extra amount of a
[\h__\h] ton of cables thank you ahmed
i hear um
oh you sent me a picture oh my god
only for my eyes it's kind of bad
because there's like a it's like trash
oh my god
i'm not even gonna judge you because
that's how it looked uh here as well
until a moment ago
it's just a napkin and a
it's like a
collectible twitch card that i i
kicked out of for my ukulele on the
floor
oh there's a fork
you cut
because i have a ton of packs in them
you have a ton of what
packs of those cards oh yeah i couldn't
find a pick that's why
i see the cut out of the card it's the
shape of a ukulele pink
well when you don't have what you need
you gotta create it out of other means
yeah
oh i'm i feel
a bit more um relieved that i'm not the
only one with such a freaking mess i
didn't quite expect it from you though i
felt like you were you would be more the
argument organized type of person
because you you know your stuff you know
you're
everything else
everything else aside from like my my
desk and my office is organized
this is like the only place cause
sometimes i'll just like sit here and
like work on stuff or stream and i just
eat and then put but i'll just put it to
the side for later oh
man we'll deal with it later
and then my dogs end up trying to climb
on the desk and knocking stuff over and
my cat knocks stuff over oh no
yes my cats are a bit more well behaved
because they don't really knock things
over
they're not little shits
no the only thing that is like
a little bit like um
triggering but still i forgive because
cute as hell is that like when i am
laying in bed i often have a like uh
my laptop open in bed
and then chunkers will deliberately
um to in order to reach one point when
like the corner of my bed like right
next to me she would run
over the keyboard of the laptop even
though she has more than enough space to
go around it even when i stop her she
will jump on the keyboard and just run
over it while smoovie
always makes a huge curve around the
laptop i don't know why trunks just
deliberately walks over the keyboard
every time yeah sometimes it's just
attracted to it maybe it's the heat they
like the heat but she just wants to like
quickly run over it she doesn't even
want to lay on the laptop although she
did that today but generally she just
really wants to trigger me by walking
all over it maybe it's an attention
thing because my cat like i'm i'm
looking at my phone and he's he
headbutts my phone out of my hands and
he's like no look at me oh maybe maybe
or she likes the sound when she walks
over the keys
or she's trying to tell me a message
oh
maybe something she's trying to tell me
give me snacks give me chinking
oh yeah usually that's that's when cats
are like really kind of annoying
sometimes in your face they're like my
football is empty it's been empty for
two hours i'm gonna die
you you got that a lot
uh yeah my cats yeah at any time or only
like in the morning
ah
any time well i feed them like two
two times a day like a little bit uh in
the morning when i wake up and then like
at night but then there's definitely
times in between where they're like
hey hey i think it's because maybe
they're
really playing run around and stuff but
i think they just get bored sometimes
you know oh
i need i need to give them some more
enrichment i got to get them some more
toys yeah i want to do that too
enrichment but actually like jonkers
doesn't ever annoy me about food ever
she's she just
she just like always just chills she
doesn't ever ask for snacks or whatever
and then smoovie only asks for food
really annoyingly in the morning because
she knows in the morning she'll get wet
food but besides that they're both
always really really chill and quiet
they don't annoy me with it that's cute
my cats are kind of good
your cats are very young right because i
have a i have like a kitten i think he's
like five months older six months old
and whenever i i'll like be eating an
avocado and he tried to steal the seed
the avocado
he eats melon i have like a video of him
like licking the inside of a melon
because he just eats anything he's crazy
he tried to bite a pear he took some of
my pizza he was eating
yesterday
that's so cute
he's trying to be healthy he wants a
healthy diet
i don't know what's up with him i feed
him like a quite a bit i feel like i
feed him too much and he still just
wants more maybe he doesn't see it as
eating though maybe he sees it as a
attacking prop
cry
yeah maybe yeah he just wants to attack
whatever maybe
maybe he thinks that the melon or the
whatever the peach or pear is attacking
you when you're eating it so he wants to
attack that fruit because he wants to
protect you
sure we'll say that
attack
it's so cute he's just playful hey i'm
sure he'll stop eating fruit when he
grows a bit older
he wants those nutrients
he'll sit under my monitor and then like
put his paw underneath and press keys on
my keyboard and i have a picture i have
like a picture of him doing that and it
was when i was playing uh
oblivion that's like a skyrim type of
game so it has reloads and
also
oh no
oh no that's so cute though i would
forgive
big forgiveness don't don't don't be mad
don't be angry
no i don't get angry with him now that's
good good good uh cat mama maybe i
should have watched cats with you
ah
oh oh god actually it's funny that you
say that because i think it was i think
it was yesterday i was trying i was like
looking for something to watch and like
oh they added cats oh my god the hbo app
and uh i was like i tried watching it
and i i just i couldn't repeat after
yeah after like a minute i was like yeah
i'm not watching this why not it was
really good
because i don't like the way that they
make the cats look like humans and then
like they get used to it
is all messed up like they look really
tiny like i just imagine somebody
walking out on the street and seeing
them and they're like the size of like
not ants but like really small yeah i
mean that was funny to me but that
didn't bother me at all i didn't even
notice that
oh
wait uh you know maybe i'll give it
another try if you've asked for it yes i
don't know why people don't like it it's
a good movie 10 out of 10.
actually i grew up like listening to the
musical because my my aunt really liked
it so i've seen like the stage play of
it before oh
you should want you should give the
whole movie a try it's it's it's worth
it trust me trust me i you know liked it
too i watched it together with inna
and she liked it she gave it a 10 out of
10 being polite no she said best movie
she has ever seen in her her life
yeah okay
i see
i did i did uh i did a quiz today
uh which cat's character am i
did a buzzfeed quiz
and i came out as the the character that
taylor swift played
his character
and that weird kitten that they threw
and look like it's not a kitten but it
says um damn it wait i'll read it to you
go ahead uh you are bomba lurina you're
flirty and full of mystery you like to
have fun and it and will risk everything
for a good time
you're confident and won't take no for
an answer
okay that sounds i mean that sounds like
a pretty accurate yeah do you want to do
it too i'll do it for you wait and are
you usually i just ask you questions and
you give me the answer one second
all right which
dad's character
okay let's do this uh
okay choose
a disney villain you can pick between
scar
from uh the lion movie
lion king lion king i know or ah
from
ariel i think
and crap the ville from the doggy movie
uh i think um
uh
hades okay
okay
choose a fictional dog clifford snoopy
goofy or brian griffin
clifford
cliff clifford who's clifford what is
that it's a big red dog
from where it's from like a cartoon i
think it's originally from like a
children's book that got turned in
yeah and then uh it's the soup i used to
like to eat it always had like clifford
branding on it i feel like i want the
clifford soup i don't even know that
dog it's a big red dog i looked it up
but it doesn't look familiar to me at
all
okay okay which member of the mystery
gang are you
shaggy
scooby
daphne or velma
uh
i don't know chad what do you guys think
kiara what do you think what
maybe you're shaggy i don't
i don't really heard okay
i don't quite know their personalities
like at all i didn't really watch it but
uh chat is mostly saying okay yeah
there's no freddie
i just talk like this all the time
that's good i like that okay
pick an art form dancing acting
writing or painting
um
i guess acting sure okay
pick an andrew lloyd webber musical
uh from the following jesus christ
superstar
evita evita
a phantom of the opera or cats
[Music]
i uh i'll pick a phantom of the opera
okay okay i picked cats but
i have i wonder why
uh choose a type of milk whole
almond two percent or soy
uh
two percent two percent okay
pick a vacation spot
new york city
hawaii
paris
or rome
right
okay
i think i picked that too yeah uh pick a
female star
lady gaga
rihanna
beyonce
or ariana grande
brianna a nice good choice good dress i
would have chosen her too by that she
was ariana so i couldn't i almost
couldn't choose between between those
two
[Music]
this one i was struggling with i wish i
had input with that one i didn't know
which one to choose i'm sorry just
choose randomly but how would your
friends describe you
loyal mischievous
fabulous or funny now what would you say
i'm pretty loyal i'm kind of like a dog
you know
really you would you think that your
friends would describe you could ask me
right now i would probably choose funny
otherwise
what do you think funny or mischievous
mischievous
funny or
okay chad also says miss chivas
at least on my side what does your chat
say
uh they're mixed
uh like
you guys have to pick between funny or
mischievous they're your friends as well
so teammates get to choose
other they're they're choosing
mischievous okay good okay
okay i'll send this to you as a picture
for
[Music]
[Applause]
would you like to read wait wait it's
not fully i'll show you
the full uh description
yeah i was watching like the first five
minutes of the movie and they had like a
really cool
uh part where they showed up you know
like a
very important plot device where
obviously this is like the evil guy
because they had him
parallel with moriarty
would you like to read the text
you live a secret double life nobody can
figure you out because you choose to
hide who you really are once people get
close to you they love your personality
but it's not easy to get past those
walls you put up i feel like this is
kind of accurate though
wow you guys should all take the cats
quick i'm so
[Laughter]
or am i going crazy here come on i guess
yeah yeah i guess because like the
secret double life is kind of because
you know you're like a good
you're a detective and detective
often live double lives and you know
it's true and yeah it was also for me
like i i feel like i experienced those
walls with you
uh before but now now that i got closer
to you i love your personality so it's
exactly as it's written here
i have an idea
shall we do in the future
uh
a chit chat stream where we do buzzfeed
quizzes
okay i guess it's fine as long as we're
not showing it yeah
i mean maybe we can get uh permission
for one website also but but generally
we can just read out the questions and
the answers and then explain what we got
and we can do it all together
yeah i don't think we can call it
buzzfeed though i don't know yeah it's
just just genuinely
cool
personality yeah personality quiz stream
taking ding thingy like stuff like
uh
this these even quests even seven
questions will reveal which disney
character you most similar to
oh or which character from the
aristocats are you based on this quiz
[Music]
oh i got one for everything huh
answer these five questions and we'll
tell you which lindsay lohan character
you are
that's very specific okay
or take this quiz to find out which
underrated disney villain you are most
like i kind of want to know this one
right now
okay okay okay this is the last one then
we end the stream let's do it together
oh oh okay i'll send you the website and
we'll do it together at the same time
okay this is a test run
okay stretch okay so pick an animal
goldfish
rat cat oh of horse cat cat cat cat
which one are you picking
uh i think a goldfish
why i like cute
i like the ones with the puffy cheeks
so much for being loyal oh my god
okay read the next question please
oh um pick a sandwich oh there's um it's
just pictures yeah one looks like a
grilled cheese one looks like a grilled
cheese with more stuff in it one looks
like a very healthy with avocado green
yeah with sprouts and stuff and then one
looks like a sub now i'm going for the
last one because it has salami and ham
and potatoes and salad and everything in
it eat any of these potatoes and then
i'll put the almond oil cheese what the
hell is wrong with my brain right now
i'll go for the green one because i like
sandwiches that have like avocado
lettuce or sprouts
healthy wow let me okay next is pick a
sport baseball soccer football or tennis
to watch or to do
probably to do right tennis
tennis two
i'm not good at it but i i kind of like
um tennis like being bad at it i don't
enjoy that oh we have to pick a singer
again we're gonna read the options
adele camila
i don't know who this is
[Music]
and taylor swift or rihanna
you're not picking ariana even though
you picked rihanna last time in this in
this selection you would choose adele
yeah
i like adele but i would choose rihanna
here
understandable okay
the last one is pick a subject math
science english or history which one are
you choosing science
i don't know i always like english or
science best i guess i'll go science
i'll go with english because i was the
best in class at english back in the
days who are you
i got randall boggs for monsters inc you
are cunning and intelligent i want to be
from monster inc too
what'd you get i got someone who i don't
know
i'm edgar balthazar from the aristocats
oh
wait there's a lion here what the hell
you're organized and well-spoken but
you're not fond of cats what i even
chose
as the as the animal
what
it's broken it's raining
i chose cat it's my favorite animal
maybe it misclicked no i didn't i looked
back up its own cat right now
oh
what
yeah that's that doesn't make sense that
kind of destroys the
um
authenticity that i believe and on this
on these quizzes but we're still gonna
do the collab
the hell buzzfeed i expected accurate
quiz results
i like that uh you hit the table for
your in order to let out your aggression
[Music]
all right let's do that like after your
vacation
what oh yeah quizzes i'm excited
more and more quizzes
yeah
yeah i used to take those a lot it's
pretty fun
all right then thank you guys for
watching today
thank you for hanging out yeah and also
thank you for joining us at did you call
me and supporting us both there thank
you sir
and we'll see you guys soon and in
german we self identify
the same
goodbye
[Music]
you