[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
okay
uh
sorry i was in the waiting screen for so
long because i was looking for some bgm
to fit
today's
purpose
hello good good [\h__\h] morning
[Laughter]
[Music]
how's it going
okay
[Music]
yeah i want to go back to bed
i've got an energy drink and i'm
drinking it
yeah
i i woke up um
early
because um
well
several reasons
i woke up before 10
uh uh-huh
yeah
even though my stream is at 12. why
because
no because um
i
uh
there was like um
well
generally the reason i'm trying to wake
up earlier was for the stream and
because also i
need to
like sleep early today desperately
for the sake of popcorn
and then
uh i needed to get up like one hour
earlier because one hour before the
stream
me and bae did a little bit of a tech
check
so that was
my minus one hour and then i
i was gonna wake up like a half an hour
before that or so or actually 40 50
minutes because i wanted to get
breakfast
so that was another minus one hour
but
i woke up even earlier than that
at like i don't know
9 30 or something
because a [\h__\h] smoothie
that little [\h__\h]
she just wouldn't stop meowing she
started around 9 20 or so
i was hoping i was hoping she would shut
up
so
in the end i think i got like
not not that much sleep
[Laughter]
woke up unnecessarily
early again sometimes you know she will
start meowing but then after five or ten
minutes she will stop and go back to
sleep because she notices okay this
[\h__\h] ain't gonna wake up huh
yeah but uh
this time she didn't give up she made
out so long that i had to get up anyway
at some point
my alarm started ringing and i was like
great smoothie thank you
thank you very much
[Music]
and then
[Laughter]
oh man you know
um and we did the tech check and i
wanted to see like um if i play music if
you know we're doing it for zoom if i
play music if if um they can hear it
so
uh let me see if i can remember i
started playing sparks
let's see
i was like [\h__\h] tired okay so i
started start sparks
ready wait for it
this is what i was singing
but
lying down on the bed late night
[Music]
wait what was it what was what what did
i come up with wait lying on the bed
late night
i forgot it was something like
something like
here comes
here comes my cat meow
waking me to [\h__\h] up up or something
like that and then
yes
she wants food but i want sleep
i made up the most genius lyrics now i
can't remember them
but it was fitting so well
uh
and then staff were laughing
manager sounds
plural they were laughing
i was really not in the mood but at
least uh
it worked the audio worked
i'll i'll try to remember the lyrics and
i'll come up with a new
i'll come up with a new um
version
so here we are playing rust with an
energy drink um
i will have to later
uh
practice
and sleep and so on so
won't be too endlessly long
let's see
[Music]
a lot of people online i don't know how
to
start an interaction though i want to
show you first
look
what i've been working on
[Music]
i unlocked a lot of things
let's do this one too
yeah
inna is online dana is online i watched
your streams a little bit
yeah i worked on this
uh
and then
yeah i needed a lot of scraps for that
holy [\h__\h] i got a repair table to repair
my axe i got this
look
i actually had two of those one i
recycled oopsie
let's turn off again
then
i i i put the window thingies on the
windows in the second floor i put down
the table
i'm gonna put another um
chair here
and then this is this is new
just putting some more stuff in there
that i need and then i i i realized oh
these things aren't necessary i i
recycled them before but then i found a
car
that actually you could still drive if
you put these things in
um and i was like damn i recycled them
the last time i saw them
uh but then i went looking again and i
found some more so now i'm keeping them
and oh you can see here i got some cool
stuff because i i
i found some crates in random places
that were not mapped not marked on the
map so i have this the c4 i heard i
remember muna the other day in the chat
she was like
i got c4 uh
for sale in my shop or so so i remember
it's probably pretty
pretty
you know
valuable
it goes boom
and i got some other
i got shotgun trap i got
this is the weapon i had before i think
but then i got two new weapons
and i found
and
my clothes have improved i've crafted
myself some stuff but also um found some
stuff
uh
and this one this one i found roadside
gloves what the [\h__\h] this one i made
myself you know that from danny's stream
maybe
found some medicine found some ammo i
really needed ammo because i wanted to
be able to craft ammo
but i i couldn't reach the right
path yet
so i was lucky to find a lot of ammo
yeah
and
uh
i got some night vision goggles cool
stuff huh
yeah a country has bullets i don't know
why but apparently not
weird
weird game not very realistic
um
one question
do you always have to like stay by
um
like the fireplace when you're cooking
to make sure it doesn't overcook because
like
if you let it leave it in there it will
always overcook right so you have to
supervise it no
oh you say no but like when you leave it
there
oh i'm feeling too hot really
but when you leave it there it just
overcooks
oh
thanks for gifting the uh
memberships
thank you
you can split the music so they cook
quicker too hot 40
40 damn 40 degrees
split them
see no oh [\h__\h]
and there's no space to really split
them
unless like um
like this
i guess um
you just know when to take it out
[Music]
well i i i anyway it you're saying this
will not overcook
i'm i'm worried i'm taking it out anyway
nice btm yeah i prepared some bgms so
tell me when you get sick of it
ah
it's charcoal leave the room only for
raw meat and cook me ah
ah
it will just pop out then
interesting that that's how you do it
you force it you force it out
oh
well yeah
cozy house right yeah too bad it's gonna
be destroyed
soon it's good to know
okay there you go we have some food
so
and then uh down here
not much change just like i guess what i
have
i got
oh where is it where is it where is it
oh there's a crate here i wonder who's
going for it
there's so many people online the
chances of me getting it are lower than
zero oh i got the chainsaw i got a
chainsaw yo
damn
are very effective at cutting trees in
addition to soft fleshy objects like
humans
requires low grade fuel to run oh
uh a wetsuit
yeah i got i got everything for diving i
think i have a wetsuit i have a diving
mask i got two diving tanks
what else do you need
oh down there
i'll turn up oh yeah
what's up
[Music]
is coming over just say hello
the crate is yours
i'm i'm too intimidated by all the other
people oh
it's coming
and then i got a [\h__\h] ton of materials
oh wait i still have some some scraps
but no
i put them inside
um
yeah i've been running to the
convenience store a million times
yeah and then are we safe
is it gonna come soon
i'm so scared it's so fast
yeah it does remind you of the beetle
still
okay it's going up and as you have seen
in the stream or on the stream perhaps i
now have
levota
goku goku
the raincatcher
i also know how to make one
and then i have this outside now and i
want to
um start planting some stuff
so
what's that sound
you guys will teach me how
how
[Music]
dana has been using my why it's like
half more than enough
[Laughter]
she's welcome to do that
anything in here no sad i wonder if if
nana she saw my note because i know
she's been playing at least once
since then oh first things first
oh my god two days huh
i mean
and we can go chops we can go chainsaw
some woods
don't you wanna go
chainsaw some wood guys
let me put some stuff back that i don't
need let's make the chest upstairs a
clothing just
need some organization
it's it can't be a clothing chest it's
already something else let's make a new
chest
let's make a new chest that will be the
clothing test
merry christmas what
i would rather once you chainsaw someone
now we have to start with the trees
uh blocks not chest
i mean i want a metal fragment
i have more than enough
another chest another box
wait look
we can make up
a camping vehicle
but
does it already
does it need to be attached to a car
probably
[Music]
well
i don't know what inna is currently
doing i was watching her a little bit
running around but i'm not sure what her
goal was
[Music]
so i don't know
i i i purposefully overlapped my stream
to have something happen but now that
i'm here like how do you make it
naturally happened
it was on the way to gambling oh i
wanted to try that too
oh look good on iris
how does the gambling work
maybe i just walk in there with my
chainsaw and kill everyone
how about that
granite park thank you
oh
self quarantine oh nice
eh
wait where you gonna be at popcorn
that's so sad
i hope you get well soon that's so sad
safe zone no attacks well try me
don't let your dreams be dreams guys
sometimes you just have to
make it happen
[Music]
place that [\h__\h] place it
papa
[Music]
what do i need to be able to gamble just
some scraps do i gamble with scrubs
i don't have that many now
[Music]
but you know you have to make something
big out of something small right
just scraps
scraps and i lost everything well that
was fast what the [\h__\h]
i'll make more but i only have 29. i can
quickly go to the convenience store try
to get some more
[Music]
get here
no well i mean i have gambling
experience what do you play to gamble
there
because i don't play cards besides
blackjack
is there what is the game
i've worn another chest oh
[Music]
roulette
relax
polka slots
oh that's quite a choice
interesting these these they don't take
the muscle fragments right
so many of them
oh
okay well what are we gonna bring over
we don't
we don't need weapons i guess
i guess
okay where do i put all my [\h__\h]
i don't need anything
okay
uh
um
okay let me put the ammo here
is all of that ammo yo
i have lots of ammo
yeah
i don't wanna lose
my precious weapons
[Music]
away
i actually have the game sound pretty
low like i should probably let me see i
actually have to
fix
the audio too
why is the
why is the one setting so hidden why is
it not in audio the one setting that i
need you know all the transmit voice
that should be an audio
[Music]
i hear a helicopter
it's probably really far
i don't see it
the crate is still there
but i've learned that it takes 15
minutes
okay now it's loud
oh i heard it takes 15 minutes i need a
weapon i have a weapon
well i was also told i don't need a
weapon so
you guys are giving me mixed
information
let's have some food here
this is what we're bringing
this one we're bringing uh do i need to
take off my
my clothes when i get there
because it counts as a
high
because it counts as a weapon
take at least one gun okay
bring the other scrap wait wait
okay uh
other scrap ah oh
oh i did have a couple more
do you guys think i have a chance of
actually getting something out of it
oh wait no
wealth
gamble time
i don't want that just throw it all in
there
it's coming back it's so [\h__\h] scary
these look terrifying
be prepared to lose all of it
uh
where is it by the way
local
is it
here
or is i is it here
m8 uh-huh yeah yeah okay we're pretty
close pretty close
okay um can someone shoot down the
helicopter please
wait what did you say now about the
about the about my um about my clothes
will they consider that
a threat
no my clothes are fine okay because
somebody said you know about the
helicopter
maximum three pieces of clothes or
whatever it was at the safe zone i think
it was the helicopter
okay but you guys did say bring one
weapon
[Music]
i guess
i think that's the one that has the
light attached to it
yeah okay
don't need any more ammo six shots are
good
six shots are enough
wait that's not the one with the lights
or does it only turn onto the knight
ah it's the one with the light okay
okay
i guess
i guess i'm gonna go
press f ah
press f to pay respects
oops
close
now
four
uh kind of does if i died because of the
helicopter
okay we're gonna go
i feel like when i go there it's gonna
be awkward but yeah
let's go
let's socialize
how does roulette work you just put your
bets on one number
and help oh god
i'm scared let me
three pieces of clothes right uh
there you go
i had no weapon
no weapon
is the is the axe considered a weapon
i'll get the hotbar too right
is this considered a weapon
huh
sharp axe is a weapon
the only wheels the weapon on
otherwise i will shoot yeah yeah like a
safe zone that's fine that's fine i'm
more thinking about the helicopter
because i don't hear it so well because
of the music
[Music]
you know in other games i also
tend to enjoy gambling quite a lot
i uh i have to admit it
get that one
like in yakuza
it
is
whose house is this
oh
um
oh god i
i i isn't good at streaming
it's not enough streaming
don't think good as streaming
[Music]
they're both not streaming
interesting oh they're already there
what
they're so [\h__\h] fast
don't shout i have no weapon and no
armor
god damn it
oh
this thing is flying here but that one's
friendly right hello
hello
where's the campbell place
where is the place of campbell
i wish i had blackjack
hello and we if we hear some voices in
this
and that's the gamble place
maybe the colorful house over there
that's not it right
probably that colorful one
they have blackjack really
oh my god
hello
yeah i saw she was killed once
well oh this is it
oh no one here
they probably heard i was coming and
left because of that
they just left
wow
wow can i play alone
oh who's is that a ghost
um five
almost
wow
how do you play this on
mount uh mount my
mount
i'm mounting the couch as one usually
does how do you play this
oh
time we're writing until next spin
well if
are my chances higher when no one else
is playing let me put this in
and then i'm gonna bet on
i don't know what's a good number wait
how do i how do i how do i
wait i can't i can't push the numbers
the real lens i can't select anything
is my bed too low
ah to the color
okay but can i do it now
not too late okay
okay uh wait let me take a look
is that is that the same amount of every
number i guess one is the most but one
gives you the least back or so
let's try
[Music]
three i don't know
so is it then what i get back is what my
scraps multiply i multiplied by frame
did they know i was gonna come is that
why they left
i'm so
sad all around me in a million places
[Music]
[Applause]
did i get it
wow
first time winning wait let me switch to
5.
[Music]
oh this would be fun with other people
what if the same what if there's like i
guess they can use a different one right
when like when there's more people
betting on the same number and they put
it on top of that does the game
recognize that someone put it on on top
of that
the sense to addiction no no no no no no
no no no no i'm gonna try the other
games too but this is fun
five five five five five five five five
five five ah
oh
[Music]
this is when i get back for being alone
here at least i'm lucky with my bets
i'm saying it's gonna be um
one this time i might be wrong but you
know
wait right now it's like in between five
and one would that mean that both people
who bet on five and one
are gonna get
the win
actually it might not be one but
whatever
i have a feeling it might not be one
wow too late
no only five
there are no inventories it was five
yeah it was like in the middle
and that's 20. holy [\h__\h] i should have
bet on 20 i should have believed
oh
that was clearly twenty though
i say ten
i say ten oh there's not many tens on
there though there's only two only one
twenty holy [\h__\h]
hmm
what 10
10 and 20 are
oh
really low chance i think this is my
first time in my whole life that i'm
playing roulette
all in all 20 no head hell no [\h__\h] no
i'm not stupid
no chance hi everyone
let's see let's see i'll bet once on 10
and then maybe we'll go lower again
see what happens to chihuahua give me
the pink one
give me the pink
pink super chat let's go
oh
ah so close so close
so close
well you know we won so much in the
beginning we have yet to make any losses
so it's okay to try again you know can i
do two bets at once
is that crazy
it works
oh
wanna make my chances higher
oh yeah oh yeah
you're smoking like a true gambler
whatever i won already
we see that as a different allowance
and uh
use it as much as we can
oh
what did i bet five and ten right five
and ten five and ten
where's my beginning look [\h__\h]
it's gonna be five i'm telling you
but just in case
just just in case
let's put one on free
come on
are they gonna come back
is inna gonna come back
lena should come
my free trial has expired that's how
they get you that's how they drag you in
they make you lucky in the first one two
three tries to drag you in and then you
keep on failing and you're like there
must be a way to repeat what i had in
the beginning i'll keep on trying it
will come back to me eventually what did
i bet on
point five oh free
hmm
did it go into my inventory
that's three right or is that considered
one ah wait that might be one it's a bit
more on the one
[Music]
go now go with lua bets
three and five
three and five i'm telling you
the red arrow um
yeah now when i look very closely i
guess i can see it
honey guy
please
let's get some music
i don't think the other ones were
fitting
for this
we should play kakegurui opening
i did watch kakagurui by the way when it
came out
now i'm losing everything
okay three times 20 will be
[Music]
a lot
so let's hope for the best
now audio stock
i did i did like kakiguru by the way
even though it was so crazy i did
actually
kind of enjoy it
it's actually pretty fitting but we're
gonna get sick of it
come on
[Music]
what is this [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
unbelievable but we still didn't make
any losses i think i came in here with
how much 150 or so
[Laughter]
what is that one character who was like
i
it's a long time ago but something
happened with nails they even
did she bet her nails or what was that
did she
tear off her nails
oh no no i didn't go all in what are you
saying five and twenty right five and
twenty
no no no no
no
what's going on this is rigged
unbelievable
ah
[Music]
what if i do one one one one each
when i make a loss
or a win
depends i guess on
[Laughter]
if it's if it turns out it's 20 then
it's 1 times 20 right so that at least
would be a win
please
be kind to me what did i do five and 20
again
[Music]
okay now we're using my own
money i guess
10 on free
four um
five
now i'm losing everything
ah
[Music]
please i need something back now game
you know it right you know you have to
motivate me this is your job
i lost
everything that i made now so
it's your job to motivate me to keep
going
right you understand that
what did i do i don't remember
friend
what a [\h__\h] hell
i can't believe it
i i cannot
unbelievable
you'll not be [\h__\h] kidding me
ugh
the only reason i'm so energetic by the
way is thanks to my red bull energy
drink i'm drinking um
what's this what's marilla in english
marilla i think is an austrian
word isn't it i think in germany they
call it something else or today
apricot uh apricot apricot strawberry
summer edition red bull do you guys have
that over there
because red bull is from austria so we
have like all kinds of [\h__\h] you
ah
not sponsored however aklas empire and
bhutan senpai got sponsored by red bull
it should be me i'm the austrian yo just
kidding
red bull austria should sponsor me
i'll kind of [\h__\h] you
what was that 20
no one hey
it's only landing on one
what is this uh
[\h__\h]
five on five maybe going double
is
they don't like it they sense it
go
give me the blue one give me the blue
one
give me a blue one
ah
so close
[\h__\h] one it keeps on going to one
scam
who bets on one
i can't win anymore
[Music]
um
it's really sad right it's so sad
everything about this stream is just sad
we're we're only gonna be sad but thanks
to my energy drink i i can't actually be
sad right now
i'm physically
it's physically impossible for me
break free
i think i battle free
i just went straight into it right i bet
like a little bit on free like seven i
think
[Music]
gonna do the same three fives the way to
go
five one three five one five
take the scraps what do you mean take
the scraps
oh my winnings oh oh oh
oh there that's where they went okay
real guys are they
you'll make yourself miserable
what by gambling oh freaking
no not not all of them come on
[Music]
no no
dammit i keep on doing it wrong
there you go okay please
or 20 this time
don't force it
don't force
it's desperate to ask
oh it's coming yeah i got the
my luck is back my luck is back they
they know they weren't they know they
were losing me there
they felt it
nah
ah it's gonna be a one
it's probably gonna be a one
oh [\h__\h]
it's gonna be a one but i'm going for my
three five again
nina what you
up to
see
i'm just desperate now
all right i told you it's gonna be one
i see i know it
killing wolves
[Music]
what's the end goal
of killing wolves
food ah
um she liking food so much
she can just have mine
go
what's my end goal and gambling my goal
i came here because i heard there were
three people here
and now i come here and gone
oh
no i i was i did 5 10 didn't i'm
gambling
in tears
ah
oh is eena done
[\h__\h]
did she end her stream
see i didn't get to interact with her at
all
ah
that's [\h__\h] free it's haunting me
maybe we play a different game you said
they have blackjack here hmm
i'm good at blackjack
yeah she streamed for like three hours i
know i i was hoping to overlap in the
last hour
uh to see her
no all is left is her ghost
give me a sign ina
give me a sign where are you
what's your name
forever alone yeah
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] okay let's play a different game
ah
i get off the
couch okay is this blackjack there's
slots too
do you want to play
oh you're wearing like samurai armor
what's up you want to play i'm alone
play
how do you play slots i guess just like
oh
deposit
wait 10 scraps per spin
and it's so expensive
i
spin
and then how do you oh it just stops on
its own are you [\h__\h] kidding me what
a waste
no
no hell no
okay can we play blackjack please
makeup with hundreds
hell no
was this
that's also roulette
motion blur i don't think i have motion
blur on where do you see motion blur i
don't know what you mean
where is that
i don't see motion blur
oh
oh it's off
no it's all
i don't know what that does though
okay well um
this is sad
i didn't at least i didn't really like
i don't know i don't remember how much i
brought here but i don't think i really
lost anything significant
um let's do one more roll
let's do one more
much better i don't see a difference
go
oh
[Music]
last one
last one last one last one last one last
one
last one
roll that [\h__\h] roll it roll it
roll it roll it roll it roll it we
should put a body
on the middle of the roulette
yeah and then throw knives at it
reina's coming and think really
really
she should tell me because otherwise i'm
gonna leave
nina what you doing now
i was checking in every five minutes
what are you doing now what you doing
now what you're doing now what you're
doing now hey what are you doing now hey
what you up to hey what's up what's up
hey what you doing hey where are you
okay i'm i'm
i'm at home
okay
she's at home which is basically my home
because we basically share a home
because we live so close together
oh thank you nina for telling me that
because that will that gives me an
opening to leave this place wait where's
the where is the opening though
are they
that's not where i came from
which door did i come from that's not it
wait oh they have more stuff oh they
have a different table here
which one is this one how do i know
just just checking
more play is necessary anyway
oh recycle machine
interesting interesting
okay uh
uh
god i'm so confused
home
[Music]
you guys just wanted to be super quiet
or as long as i'm alone i feel like
playing music is the way to go
hi why does he why did you wave at me
and just keep out am i also not allowed
[Music]
okay where's my where's my marking on it
what horse can i have
oh that's someone's horse huh there's a
saddle on it
who's horse
that's inna's horse you just left it
here
she she logged out
you can't just leave your horse
does she not care for it does was it a
throw away one time only horse
a one night stand a one stream stand
wow
did she forget maybe she just forgot
about it she's gonna regret it isn't she
so what if i take it to keep it safe
i can try one night stallion
or is she maybe still online now she's
just going straight to bed right
i'm riding you know's horse does it even
listen to me
oh it does
oh god this is hard to control
oh my god i'm i'm gonna come there with
a horse like on the knight in the
charnet shining armor
knight in shining armor
where is where is my [\h__\h] marking
turn around toys
i don't know where i am
ah okay there
a little bit more to the right there we
are
oh
whoa
i need to prepare food for him right
well ivina's looking for her horse it's
going to be at my house now
[\h__\h] this is good practice
oh god
oh dear what is that oh dear don't go in
there
back back
[Music]
oh god even if i accidentally kill it it
won't make a difference because it would
have died anyway just standing there on
its own
i mean like literally like it's just
true it's just the truth
i'm doing everybody a favor
[Laughter]
okay okay i'll get good good good horse
good horse
good hoisie
what do we need to feed it i saw the
feeder but like what do i fill in
anything
or does it need like something specific
meat any food okay
oh
i feel like i'm on a roller coaster
ah
oh i i thought i could make a horse jump
wait wait wait wait wait wait
it went so far
okay horses and rust don't jump
ah
unless it's a different button okay oh
wait okay wait uh
oh whose house
[Music]
what's that marina's house but she has a
horse now
the [\h__\h]
reyna
all right ain't it
oh that's enough
she's at my house
why does why does elena have a horse now
[Music]
oh wait when i played music accidentally
uh okay hello
i know but that was you i thought that
was i thought i fixed my mic
yeah nice i fixed mine too
play again play some music do you want
to go to the supermarket real quick wait
there's definitely a delay sorry there's
like a
2 3 second delay
[Laughter]
um
i took inna's horse because she parked
it somewhere and logged out and she
forgot about the horse so i took her
horse i have to feed it um
but i need to figure out how
i mean
your horse now right
well
for a while i guess until inna remembers
that she had a horse
yeah uh yeah we can go on a horse stage
we can go horsing coursing around
we can we can also i also found one
actually
gave me one but um i then lost and then
one in the wild today oh maybe it was
your horse reborn all over again
yeah reincarnated yeah different horse
okay i'm gonna leave the house ending my
stream
you're ending it you want to go to the
supermarket with me i just yeah okay
yeah i played from like
two hours ago yeah i saw you
eh
i'm just leaving the horse you think
it's gonna disappear immediately
no no no no no it's fine okay
okay horses
[Music]
what are you trying to do
beautiful
i can only play one note because i'm uh
i don't have a numpad
there's like a full keyboard option but
i forgot how to press it ah
that's what the numpad would be useful
for huh
ah goddammit but it sounds stupid yeah
like why would i be needing a numpad oh
to play guitar and rush
all right can i feed the horse directly
without giving it the the thing
the feeder
really
drop it
okay
eat this horse eat it
oh oh it's eating it
somebody's like nice okay we can go to
the supermarket yeah i have a gift for
you thank you thank you
what is it
uh
i think i know who that is from
is that i was watching the stream a
little bit is that the npc that you
killed
uh oh no i got wait i got killed by a
bear and then i retrieve my uh my dead
body and then it's your own skull
yes oh my god that's uh i guess i can
make my own uh reina ducky makura with
that
that's so creepy that is very terrifying
but you gave me that hungry do you want
some meat oh yes please i gave all my
meat to the horse
don't give me go don't give me your meat
meat
uh it's just you own meat isn't it
well i guess that's
kfp
it's style
but okay
but then i won't eat this i will add it
to my daki makura yes good morning yes
let's go
although wait uh
uh let me put on my clothes properly
again
okay
okay okay
supermarket
you tried gambling already
no i'm concentrating on like i'm
gathering straps for like because i
think like because this isn't resetting
but the tech trees they're not resetting
so i'm like
you know yeah me too
me too me too
maybe if i want a gamble i'll do it in
season three yeah
let's gamble together i want to play
blackjack i went there because i thought
there was three people there but when i
got there nobody was there so that's why
i said i was gambling in tears
supposedly there's polka roulette
blackjack and uh slots
me too
it's the only card game that i can play
besides
understand the other uhno like
blackjack's the easiest oh wait you guys
don't hear her so well
here there you go
okay okay
sorry guys
wow
reina i also noticed you got very very
good very fast
i missed though so sad i still need to
figure out like the whole aiming thing
with rust oh yeah i saw you struggling
recoil
yeah
it's
yeah i don't know how to like aim
properly because i guess different games
more scraps for more gambling
oh i should get some food
i'm gonna grab some food
what should we have for dinner tonight
your body
like literally like you know
i mean i wouldn't really recommend it
but
i mean
what you're the one who gave it to me
my body
no my body makes it no if you look at
the description like even the cooked uh
the cooked version of my body makes you
dehydrated oh my you know
yeah it makes you i think it's good
interesting revelation exactly
i'm just gonna take like the beans or
something maybe
[Music]
i feel like oh my god i'm looking like
everything
oh
pump shotgun
pump pump pumping oh nice
little little pump pump
oh god i just found out about it
yesterday
from
uh from youtube
i just found actually no i found a tweet
away um i found a tweet that was like
okay
making fun of little pump
[Music]
reyna i think like i think i i looted uh
of this place
sorry there he is here's the box here's
the box here's the box
yeah i'm gonna go upstairs first
electric heater
that was electrocuter he
had a cute electric heater
electrocuter would be good too
okay
maybe you can make an electrocution i
heard that wrong i wouldn't be surprised
sorry
[Music]
i need to um
oh did you put something in the recycler
uh yes i did sorry no problem oh i'll
get it real quick
okay you can use it
thank you should i keep this i mean i
don't even have electricity
[Music]
i was just like looking for stuff like i
like using the torch because like if you
use the flashlight
the flashlight from the gun it's so
scary it feels like a horror game yeah
it's true
i hate horror games
are you using it still
uh yeah
[Music]
okay
no problem
oh just a little bit
how do you drink again
okay uh i'm i'm done
oh 69 nice 69 scraps
nice
[Music]
how do you it's not left it's not right
click it's
not e it's not the number
do i have to go
okay hello hello
feel free to use the yeah
okay
[Music]
lunch lunch lunch lunch lunch
[Applause]
i'll give you meat to the horse
okay then
i think the horse won't complain about
it does the horse drink water too or
does it just need yeah
i i think i don't i don't know they
might just need food or something
okay yeah i think i only saw it ever
being in front of a food source never
over water source
there we go
okay i'm done
then
let's go home
and yeah let's go home and then you can
uh
log off
is home this way
yes uh i think it's uh yes it's kind of
that way
[Music]
[Applause]
a warning please
oh sorry
i thought you suddenly wanted to shoot
yeah like i don't know how i should aim
and rust
get good exactly i need to figure it out
but you're
already like getting much better at you
yeah
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] how am i
missing
[Applause]
[Music]
right it's gone
okay let's just go it's fine yeah
did you have fun today
yes i ate lunch i pretty much did
nothing
and
i screamed
wow
i have another stream later at like in
like three hours though or like two
hours
oh yeah
these ones by the last song than before
but like is this just decoration or can
you
oh wait there's no there's a bag i think
you can like put something
yeah
can you use
it you can fly it
really is it not broken do i just have
it
so how do you fix it need fuel is that
all i need i want to try
fuel i think
no great fuel good good
i'm gonna do that when when you when you
yeah
i'll continue walking you home
yeah thank you
oh my gosh
hot air balloon
yeah i'm generously yeah tell me your
experience with the hot air balloon once
you get it running yeah okay i'm really
scared because there's like what if i
see the helicopter
when i'm like riding the hot air balloon
as long as you don't have a weapon it
should be fine
if you don't have a weapon and your
hotbar yes so oh yeah by the way i stole
your water like three times today i have
so much
you also have water though okay what you
have a full container i do that's the
problem
i do i do
i'm like yeah you know your house was
like
very very
close by explain your house i thought
maybe he's also close
yeah true but your house was closer
interesting all right then um elena
thank you
uh chilling with me it's nice to see you
wow yes yes yes nice to see you
i got like a bed and a
table randomly today
yes do you have plans for yes
[Music]
no minecraft summer vegetable
oh no when is that
then 29 for the 30th
[Music]
from the 30th
japanese prime time
it's a 29th 29th
okay i mean i don't have plans
do you want to go can i be your plan
sure sure
let's go
[Music]
thank you
okay
yeah i haven't really checked out the
place and stuff uh yeah but yeah i just
saw yeah we can talk about it later the
trailer on twitter pikoda uploaded the
trailer and it's happening on the 29th
and i didn't make any plans
so
oh
yeah okay okay okay
thank you
okay
okay take care
bye bye
[Music]
i got a date
it's like i got a date for the prom
[Laughter]
[Music]
spoof what's that smooth
i mean i don't think it was
special or anything
poor's still there where is he still
there let's go okay let's build
something to keep you alive
i've got enos horse hostage
i know that i shouldn't put it inside um
so let's see
i got those horse feeders before but i
always recycle
them
i guess i gotta make you though my my
own one how how is it called
feeder
no
what is it called
[Music]
is it even can i even build it myself do
i have the recipe yet yeah there it is
hitch and through
200 wood
okay this means ina owes me 200 wood
[Laughter]
for keeping her
200 you know with this we can we can
have her um
so that she owes me something
for keeping her horse alive
yeah
food and and wood um
fruit fruit
oh troph troph
ah i read it wrong
okay so we put that just
like where the horses right
uh
[Music]
where do you want it horse
maybe we should go up
because there's placing it here is kind
of tough
you know who do i have this platform for
should we put it on here
it's such an awkward platform but you
know what i could build
uh like
i could make them uh not just one square
but three squares maybe
and then it has some
some space to move
okay this is for you horsey
uh let me get my blueprint out
do it for the inna
do we have some chill music
yeah ooh baby
at least i got elena interaction
that's all i need uh what am i looking
for i have blueprint where did i put
that
here
no
yeah like jazz it's tropical jazz
some food does it have to be cooked or
can it be raw i don't really have much i
guess i gotta go farm some food too
but can it be raw
or is it better to put
uh it has to be cooked raw is fine this
cooked feels better okay
let's do that trick how much does it eat
like
per
day per rest day i guess
let's do like do it like this
yeah okay
this should work
they eat stupidly fast
uh what about
like tuna cans and bean cans and all
that does that work i guess not probably
not
is there like
uh what other good what what other
food stores they work it does so also
like mushrooms and so probably as well
wait why did it stop
continue please
corn or pumpkin
fruits
ah that's what i okay we're about to
build my crop field anyway i wanted to
do that today
no free space for the cooked meat
but wasn't that
someone said if i leave no space for the
cooked meat
ah then it won't overcook but you also
have to keep it keep on turning it on
i just want to find a way to just do it
without having to pay too much attention
to it
ah what if i buy a barbecue or get a
barbecue or sauce is that maybe more
functional more more
more effective more
better
barbecue vespa cooking can split food
and cook tons and lunch oh okay okay
i'll remember
that cooked pork i think one more
okay
any other food in here
no ah my dad those are empty right i
wanted to recycle those empty can of
beans
yeah
just a normal day in rust
like any other oh wait we can
to stop me from
oh i have 232
to stop me from wasting all my scraps
let's let's go uh
i have completely ignored this path but
maybe i should work a little bit on that
too
unlock
block
i hear footsteps
[\h__\h]
who's outside
is my horse
or c
stop horsing around at once
hello
nice unlocks yeah i did that in my
offline time
a little bit just just a little bit
okay so let's put this in and listen
will it come automatically over here
i still hear footsteps oh
ah meat
[Music]
[Applause]
my mcdonald's order has arrived
pork
yum
make pork burger
yo
this takes a long time with this weapon
maybe do i have something better
i should just use my chainsaw huh
anyway
got some pork out of that i think
seven
nice horsey uh do i have to like
lead you the way
let me
let me finish building it first
i guess once inna retrieves her horse i
can try getting my wait a second
does it work no wait i i used um
floors there we go
will you accept my offering
here uh so so gracious of me
to prepare that for you come here
come here
oh it's a climbing horse
what's up
here
you even have some shade
here you go
oh also
okay is that
you're gonna
are you are you able to
need a ramp
you're kidding me
a ramp i can't make it
[Music]
i wish i could jump with the horse
okay stay here horse i don't know if i
can build your ramp here
oh would that would that work
does that count
that should work that should work
okay okay okay feeding time feet in our
horse oh [\h__\h]
i'm really bad at writing this voice
is it like in minecraft where
different horses have different like
strengths
and are better some are worse
it's eating
so let me
i want to send a screenshot to ina that
i have her horse
okay
i took a screenshot
it's so early yeah i was i'm streaming
early today to have some interactions
uh
[Music]
you mean your horse and my horse
my horse is amazing okay
you know i have your
horse because i saw it
um
alone
uh
and thought you
may have forgotten it so i built
a temporary home for it
um
you're welcome
it's being taken care of but i expect
um
payment in
food or scraps
uh 20
um
50 scraps per rl day
[Music]
pieces of meat per rl day
[Laughter]
okay oh i also want to learn how to fish
yeah
is that a good
income
source of a food
out of the goodness of my heart yeah
[Music]
15 nuts
okay i'll lower it
a little more to
30 scraps per rl day
because because she's a gen mate
would be more expensive if you weren't
my gen mate
wait wait you know
this time i really just saved a lost
horse but i could like literally steal
horses and be like hey you left your
horse somewhere i just i'm just taking
care of it so it doesn't disappear you
know because it didn't have any food so
um yeah it's in my house
50 scraps per day
just retrieve it whenever you want
and i could continue stealing horses and
people are like that's weird i'm pretty
sure i
i brought my horse to a speeder when
when i logged out
she wouldn't just steal it would she
[Laughter]
okay um i want to learn how to
do this
corn
we can plant all of that right
blueberry seeds red berry seeds corn
seeds hemps ah hemp seeds don't do i
need that right now
uh why have i received yellow berries
nice
nice extortion
agriculture time yeah
man let me see how much food is left did
you already eat everything oh
holy [\h__\h]
it pooped
what
it can poop
is that now does that kind of help me
with my farm
can i use it on my farm
fertilizer
okay horse dung oh
wait it doesn't it won't take the horse
down
what do you want
human poop
money
oh
i can be a corn farmer let's go
i love corn corn is like my favorite
thing on the earth
some
i berries food
what's moving
would boars attack my horse
hi
[Applause]
there you go
no they can but no most people say no
hello
give me food for a horse
maybe you should have attacked the horse
because now you became food for the
horse
that's how nature goes
ah that's life man
sucks to be here
nice
i'm a farmer welcome to my berry fields
[\h__\h]
sorry i don't like using that word i'm
just doing it for the memes oh yeah i
can't oh there you go
okay
okay now i have to put water on it
oh water 71 though
how do i give it water do i pour a
container of water over it
should i keep it at hundred percent all
day
water intake five milliliters for 60
seconds what about raindo does rain help
i mean water seems fine at the moment
health tendo what the [\h__\h] health 18
how does it go up
brain helps right click up
right right click does nothing but um
opening also is just for fertilizer
water sun and thyme okay so can i just
leave it now
i guess it doesn't need my water
70 seems totally fine
then i guess i urgently need to go get
some food for this stupid horse
yeah goddammit it's gonna eat all my
food
[Music]
maybe i shouldn't have rescued it
maybe the whole was a mistake
oh well i i did have i did get some
let's get some of this let me let me
build a barbecue then um
does it have to be on the workbench or
oh there it
is okay
barbecue time baby
i'll have to charge him can you guys
keep keep track of how much meat this
this little [\h__\h] is eating
because i think
it eats more than 20 pieces of meat per
rl day
consider our l day
real life day
holy [\h__\h]
i think i'll have to up it to 50 pieces
at least
can oh can i check the horse's health
eat the horse
now problem solved
how about i check your help
can i check your help hold down use to
open menu
salmon
ah it's pretty healthy
pruning 60 out of 400 i wonder how fast
it uh goes down
pay me or i will eat your horse
that is actually a good
a good um
what's the word word
solution result no that's not the word
i'm looking for
it's gonna eat health is full okay okay
okay uh
let's
go oh yeah i built i built a barbecue
does this have to stand outside
can it be inside
surely right
let's put it next to the fridge
good motivator a good no like um
the word i'm looking for is
not blackmail
outcome
i don't know whatever okay so we put
uh wood inside right
then turn it on
but then still there's a chance it will
overcook right
what you guys doing out there
don't shoot on my lawn man no guns
allowed on my lawn
who the [\h__\h] was that
i have a weak heart
my heart is weak as [\h__\h] please don't
challenge my heart
that wasn't even on purpose
i think the energy drink is doing things
to me
oh my god
sparks
[Music]
split the meat okay
there we go
and there we go and then it just will
fall out right it won't stop cooking
when i
when i do it like this
uh
here now it should fall out
no it's
it still
stops keep two slots you have okay
[Music]
there you go
ah then at least
if i only leave two slots for the cooked
meat
then there will be no slots for
overcooked meat
but
can it overcook them in this when it's
in there like this it will stay it will
stay this form right
well now now there's a spot
unfortunately
whatever i'm watching it
it does cook very fast though oh
oh well now i'm in the mood for some
barbecue oh i didn't have like
our western style barbecue in a long
time
just recently i had korean barbecue but
i mean you know
western style barbecue was nice too
especially in the summer
oh bye bye a pool also or a lake or i
should ask my friends we should go grill
grilling
oh actually my mom
my mom um she when we uh
the second last time i was at her place
we did like a
low-key barbecue but like she doesn't
have a grill or anything
she basically she just built a fireplace
on the ground and then we just put it on
on top of
on top of a
uh
like a
metal
something
which in theory it works but
it does get a little bit
dirty like she we also for example we
did oven potatoes
there what she did was we buried or she
buried the oven potatoes wrapped in foil
into the
bottom like into the ground of the
the fireplace
at some point we took it out but i think
like one or two we're actually like
i don't know overcooked or
they were like
they were like super dark i don't know
so that was too much but
um
yeah if you guys ever do
like a barbecue on a fireplace
then uh
remember you can do oven potatoes
by just burying them in the ground
[Laughter]
okay how fast is this by the way how
long does it take
eight nine minutes half hundred oh
[Music]
he comes it down
water ad75 a light oh
light is bad for those that are in the
shadow but maybe depending on the day
time
it will have better lights right
because now the sun comes from there
you can get cooked potatoes
no no no no okay that's what i meant
you know what i mean
you can have
buying potatoes by putting them into the
ground where they came from
you know what i mean
okay now i go bring and go get some food
um what should we go for
i guess
go to the convenience store once because
then the more i go there the more scraps
i get anyway
and then on the way maybe we find some
boards and then and then we can go to
i should leave some stuff here i have
too much stuff
and then we go
maybe try to find
uh some other food sources what was it
pumpkins and
what was the other thing you guys said
keep that i guess
what do i do with the horse dumb
fresh and fertile
well i couldn't use it as a fertilizer
maybe now maybe it was an issue of time
what was the issue
i'll put the
i'll put it in here
got that
composted oh do i need the
composter that what i need
sorry i'm so slow i'm trying to sort out
like
ah but it's confusing because i don't
know where i where i'm putting what my
brain
can't comprehend it oh god let's put
this stuff in here for now
have this here
um don't need this
recycling this
scraps
scraps for safety let's put them here
safekeeping
in case i die
and
okay
i don't need ammo i'm not really
planning on fighting too much uh
yeah
okay let's let's go
some wood would be nice too
some wood would be nice
get it closed though
so one thing i did offline
was um
i logged in when was it two days ago
it was
around
midnight my time
i think it was after my stream 11 p.m or
midnight or so which is like 6 7 a.m
uh japanese time so i would think
who the [\h__\h] would play at that time
and the server said one person online
so i was hoping that whoever that one
person is wasn't gonna go for the crate
but so i said i was i logged in and
there wasn't one immediately
i waited a little bit and then it was
there was one
so i made my way to the crate
and
i i wasn't sure
how to
deal with it i thought i could just open
it i thought it was like one of those
crates that you see oh hot balloon i
forgot
that you see at the convenience store
that you can just open
normally
but wasn't the case
i went there and
uh i i was hiding from the uh helicopter
several times
really annoying really frightening
and i saw the crate and i was like yeah
let's go no one else is here i thought i
thought i had to be really careful i'm
gonna be shot by npcs or something i
expected at least npcs to be there
but no no no
no npcs
[Music]
and then i went up to it and you know it
was my first time seeing one so i didn't
know what it meant but i saw that it was
something like three four minutes
remaining
um
yeah
[Music]
it was like okay
then i took a screenshot and i asked in
the in the community members only post
like how
how do you open this and you guys tell
me to wait until the end
so i waited a little bit but then when
it was time i looked again and it was
gone immediately and i didn't see anyone
running around but it was kind of
stressful but because at the same time i
was still doing my best to hide from
the helicopter it kept on circling the
area really dangerous
and it was just fun i'm like what what
is it that normal does it just disappear
or did someone take it but yeah
apparently
someone must have taken it
you guys say it was choco sensei i guess
she did start a stream or half
i'm pretty sure i checked
paula's schedule and she didn't
there there was no stream there but
maybe i overlooked it or maybe she
started like a minute or so after i
checked
weird
really weird
so
yeah i was hoping to make use of my time
zone
this is the second time
last time i tried doing dance
i was online for like
i don't know an hour
and
no crates were dropping which was
[\h__\h] weird because you guys told me
it's like every 15 minutes or so
the hell
no
no crates at all
and they i would have seen them
because they are there for like 15
minutes right i don't know why i didn't
see them
[Music]
so anyway now i guess just focus on
scraps and
um get as many scraps as possible
to learn recipes
yeah
but when i when i'm stronger in the next
season
we can go fight for some of those crates
[Music]
normally japan members they stay up late
but they never wake up early
[Music]
it's pretty active
i wonder if there's any days where she
doesn't play
like that that time when i checked i
would say it was a good time
like no en members online
or streaming
what surprise surprise
did i get everything
i feel like there must be something else
i feel like there should be something
did i miss something
okay
that's um hmm
i don't need
any more tuna can lamps oops
what is this little quality carburetor
low quality covered for combustion is
this also mixes air and fuel
do i need this for the hot air balloon
no right you guys said only fuel
what would i need this uh maybe to
repair
the hot air balloon or this is also car
part
am i gonna be repairing a car
before the server gets
killed
i don't think so i was collecting them
though
i heard people say something about
research
i can't research items just like click
on them research and learn the recipe
right that was
a weird comment right i just i need to
go for the tree right
[Music]
oh there is a research table
so if i put that in the research table i
can research
the recipe for this piece specifically
or is there
a catch
i can skip the tree
oh so everything i find i should bring
to the research table first
[Music]
if i create a weapon like this
do i actually need the body and so on to
build it
like these pieces
it costs oh i need scraps for that too
[\h__\h] wolves terrify me they're pretty
strong
ready to go
[Music]
[Applause]
you know on that day when i was looking
for the crate on my way back i died once
by a wolf the hands of a wolf
i was trying to outrun it but i didn't
realize wolves were much faster than
oh
oh yeah
wolves are much faster than
uh
the boys and then it killed me and then
like [\h__\h] hell so i ran back to my
body
and it killed me
a again
time
[Music]
oh
so i i revived again it looks like it
has feathers
i really revived again this time i went
with a proper weapon
and then i killed the [\h__\h] wolf
meat is back on the menu how much did we
get only five
okay would you guys say it's worth
like researching everything or should i
just go with the tech tree
properly
it's worth it
absolutely worth
okay what about my other question um do
i need like this if i want to build the
actual weapon
do i need the separate pieces bodies
yes
can i build the body itself too
yeah what the hell is those shadows i i
lowered the quality a lot thinking that
that was the reason why i was lagging
uh
oh that doesn't really help
i can research the body okay let's try
to research the body
body is loot only oh my okay let's
research the body i guess and
i want to research that too right um
okay research research
i should have done that earlier huh
oh i heard like a grenade or something
i can research that too i hope
what am i gonna
recycle i'm gonna keep that one
ah
this is where the wolf killed me by the
way
yeah there was a explosion
i don't
know
eat that
uh
drink
recycle
don't care ah each
i think i'm keeping those because i
think i don't have them
drop horsepower
okay
keeping
ah
okay
i think what about this should i
i guess i could research that too i
don't think i have this in my tree yet
okay unless you branch power off from
mainline oh
if i want electricity this will be very
useful right
i hear footsteps
i think
maybe maybe my imagination is running
wild
okay i think i know what that explains
explosion was oh
maybe some
someone's stream
by the way if you stay at a place like
this
will it still refresh or do you have to
walk away in order to make it refresh
and
bring some goods in
it still refreshes oh
interesting okay but let's go back and
figure out that research thingy
uh
[Music]
and bring some
meat to the horse once again
horse for the horse god no meat for the
horse god wait we have some berries here
okay now i'm gonna pick up
everything it could be food for the
horse
i mean we could also offer a horse to
the horse god no problem with that
it won't it won't differentiate
mushrooms
mushrooms mushrooms are
there's plenty of mushrooms in the
forest so
that's a good source to also need some
wood
but you know what for the wood we're
gonna use our chainsaw
yes
okay sorry the word chainsaw
makes me call
wild
oh pick it up
i hear
my phoenix ears here in footsteps
is
[Music]
all my animals animals like animals yeah
have you guys noticed the difference in
me today
do you feel the effects of the
didn't you drink
because that in reality i should be
really tired
[Laughter]
if i maybe maybe maybe it helps me to
you know become more normal
and in reality i should be
tired where is it where is it where is
it
don't come here
very energetic yes
hyper hyper
it's making me anxious
what
you know
there's enough food
horse
did i do something wrong
was it considered indoors
it's not indoors someone stole it
who took
my horse
both languages my horse my horse now ina
didn't write me on discord so i don't
think it was her
it's my horse
as long as it's in my care it's my horse
maybe it's like horsing around maybe
it's on the
on the trip
horsey
hello
it doesn't just walk away does it
no it had more than enough food plenty
food
oh [\h__\h] no no no push no push
okay i can fix this uh
and fix this
i could fix it
what the [\h__\h]
someone took it or at this point
yeah someone fought my extortion scheme
what the [\h__\h] it was a master plan it
was a genius master plan
now how do i tell inna that i lost her
horse
oh
full inventory
how do i tell her
maybe delete all the messages act as if
i've
i've never
never been in touch with the horse i
mean it would have despawned anyway
on its own
she didn't pay on time
well
your payment was late so i ate the horse
i don't think that will really um
help me with my
relationship with ina
what the [\h__\h] i was determined on my
business man
man okay well at least i don't have to
[\h__\h] babysit a horse anymore
and waste all my
freaking food on it
ah
[Music]
let's steal another horse
um
[Music]
i had plenty of food
in it but somehow it still despawned
sorry i couldn't save your horse after
all
um
your
total
um
bill comes out to
3.5 scraps
due in
ribbon two days thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
i'm still trying to get her
stretching her baby horse sitting rent
it scared me too yo i need to go to an
idol meeting my my energy drink makes me
want to go
pick my mailbox oh maybe maybe she
really picked it up and left me
food and scraps
but
could she have really
nope
can you leave other things besides notes
in there
ah
wait what why did i keep oh yeah it's so
still doing it
you're gonna leave any items like what
skulls no no no no no i mean like scraps
not so
that's so happening
not that it's not that bad
um
mushrooms
i really need to i really need to
uh
i have so much food now
mama mia
okay
let me sort out some [\h__\h] and then we
also
we're going to build this research table
or is it research
research table ready
research research
ah that's what she had that's what
i thought alina had in her home 200 wood
i really need to go shopping somewhat
no idle meeting i'm i'm holding it back
[Music]
39 hours upkeep time
what
huh
didn't i just take something out
it's 330.
oh that's
sorry
concentration
failure
metal fragments oh
oh
for some reason i thought that was wood
i might be hyper but i'm also lacking
concentration
okay
don't hold your idols holding an eye on
me that could turn into a full-blown
item conference
uh
i see
that's so
there you go
uh
we still have space here
ah
nice
this thing is fancy
okay so let's say i want to research
this thing
and you kind of cannot create this item
out of scrap no no i want to
oh ah cause that was luke only oh yeah
okay
do i
if i already have the the recipe it will
tell me will it
electrical brands let me see
how far am i away from the electrical
branch
locker oh there it is
[Music]
twenty
a 40 40 total required to get it on my
workbench
here it's 20. oh
because i'm skipping one
but in the end even if i were to go to
the other path like i'm not i'm not
really losing anything
i'm just skipping
oh well let's let's go with something
that's really far away though far far to
reach like i don't know when i'm ever
gonna learn how to make this
begin research
will i lose this item too
that's it
does it disappear
learn blueprint
oh okay it disappears
well okay
i don't need it anyway
i hear helicopter
please don't shoot me
it's wrapped one intro not this one i
guess there there's a crate
there's a crate
i want
i wonder how long that's been there
oh god
and
saw the snare
oh
god i'm terrified i'm terrified i'm
terrified
ah
okay
i know meeting time
so
oh
okay
i still hear it so loud and clear thanks
for the super chats
okay oh
okay
um
it's coming back
go go go go go away go away
you know it shocked me for the window
before so i'm being extra careful
i can't put that in there
put this in there
okay what are we gonna do next now that
we don't need that much food anyway
after all
what are we gonna do next docile
i need more scraps
i want more scraps
[Music]
balloon
yeah
balloon uh fuel fuel fuel
fuel
crude oil okay i think i have i have
fuel in my inventory how much would i
need though i have 10 should i get more
[Music]
ah here's more
37.
[Music]
now you know what i'll recycle that
oh
sorry i'm like so all over the place
oh wait why did it not go in there
what's that in there
and then we put this in here
this in here can never have enough of
those suits right
i wonder if it's hard to control
recycle oh no wait maybe research that
i don't have enough scraps why did i
i hear
research
research leads
begin
what else useful uh maybe the weapons
how about
researching
weapons because i don't know the
chainsaw
oh yeah oh yeah on the seat the c4
and my bullets ah
there's lots of research now
oh
okay
learn
oh what's the best
oh
mamma mia
[Music]
what about the animal
what one item at a time oh
because okay
[Music]
they're all 125.
this one's 75.
begin
is this
for the pistol yeah ammunition for a
pistol okay okay okay okay
good
then realistically that's pretty much
all i can do right
what about this one
i mean probably don't have enough
75 though but now i'm like kind of out
of out of uh
i'll leave that in there
um wow
wow
that's tough
oh wait let me keep this so i can cut
down some trees
keep the body and now restart recycle
the body
okay
i will
i will go
cut some trees and then we'll ride the
hot air balloon
maybe someone wants to ride it with me
maybe
anybody
i'll ask in the chat if any ends are
online
yeah
[Applause]
okay
i need to put in fuel
right
oh how
it requires low grade fuel
how do i
how do i put it inside
all right
oh oh i put i put all of the fuel in but
i can unload it too right at least with
the
ah
with the
weapons it's possible
oh wait i can make a lot of
fuel easily fast i think i have you need
to use the fat for it right
[Music]
wait how do
wait do you actually get more wood out
of it
i'm yelling
down
[Music]
wow
oh
that is so effective
[Music]
deforestation
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
holy [\h__\h] how many wood does a woodchuck
chuck when a woodchuck chunks wood i
don't know
because i don't chuck it
i chainsaw it
okay that is very satisfying
what
have a place got a lot of unusable
vertical you may farm over there to get
scrap if not wrong what
what does that mean unusable vertical
what does that mean
upgrade the house
with wood
uh it's not gonna be
i don't need it that long but okay it's
just my
my wood storage i guess
there's no point in upgrading it and all
that so anyway
um
yeah
that was good
let's make some more fuel this was it
right that's how you make fuel
no
ah cloth as well okay
leather club okay
[Music]
okay
fauna will remember this no she won't
because she didn't even see it happening
hi joe but don't worry about it
don't you worry about it
i'm gonna put this back
my my sacred chainsaw my new best friend
i was such a lucky find that was one of
the things i found in those random
crates
let's go fly
into the convenience store
as well
while we're at it
only two bullets it's okay
i'm not planning to shoot anyone should
i
where am i gonna shoot from the hot air
balloon
i just i just wanna fly
there's only one horse here right
[Music]
why did why did my horse
disappear
what what what
i should say this word
nah
i'm not going to do that to lena she's
my date for the festival for the summer
festival
i can't do that to her
yeah you should bring the chainsaw
where was the hot air balloon was
somewhere on the way
is that
it
yeah that's it
just gonna go quickly to the korean
store
making longer fuel
and then i also kind of want to learn
how to fish but i don't have a recipe
for
um a fishing rod yet and i don't i
haven't found one randomly either
i didn't see one on the tech tree either
i wonder what's up with that shouldn't
that be a recipe that you that you get
early on hmm
fishing village sells them
oh
it's hard to see
ribbit
ah there you go
that's what i was looking for
car parts i forgot one
good morning from europe yeah yeah yeah
good morning morning it's not morning
anymore in europe i'm from europe too
i know you can't fool me
how fast 2 pm here
i actually woke up before 10 a.m today
so i think
i
i could say good morning at that time
that counts as a good morning
[Music]
i hear
where the [\h__\h] is it
there it is but you're not coming here
are you
you better stay away
or you're just asking to be killed
it's here
[Music]
ah
i can't do it from the chat can i no
wait i should be able to do it
[Music]
because i wasn't hyper chat i wasn't
able to
wait i feel like i hear no way
[Music]
oh
my gun shoot this far
it's relatively long
but that poor piggy
oh see i missed even though my the cross
thingy was on
on top of
blue pig
sorry
sorry oh god i'm not feeling so well
either
close range shotgun but it's long
and i thought the general
measure was
if
if it is long
it make long pew pew
if it is short
it makes short pew fuel
it's not how it works
why not
make it easier to comprehend
[\h__\h] all i see is blood
[Music]
have you seen my horse the horse
t-spawned even though i gave it plenty
of food i feel
scammed
i feel highly bamboozled
usually it's like that but shawties are
different you gave it a nickname
cute
yeah i feel like i got everything did i
miss something i think i got it all
i think so oh my poop not mine but
the horses put this is evidence that i
had the horse
it's still there
[Music]
time to recycle
i don't really need it
[Music]
i'll get rid of all that i don't need
that oh wait
just give that to ina
do you want the last piece the last
remaining piece of your horse
yes
hands over who is poop
are you happy please appreciate my
offering
remember your horse with this piece of
poop
you're welcome
you are so welcome
honestly i don't want that either
can i get something out of that
oh
then i charge her exactly that's how it
goes
crafting a minus hat gives you
visibility a knife without a gun
a miner's head
i don't think i have the recipe for it
yet
unfortunately
i just throw that in as well
wait i'm gonna throw this one in here
i hear footsteps
or is it just a recycling machine
horse got recycled nope i definitely
hear footsteps oh there it
wanna is
it's so cute though it looks like my
cats
oh it runs away you're scared well you
should be
hold on hold on
okay
can i is there a chance that i'll die
when i'm in the hot air balloon because
if yes then i should return first to
bring
[Music]
bring my belongings to home
thank you thank you
oh thank you
[Music]
not really
yes
[Music]
should i bring you
thank you oh thank you
check it's health with hammer oh should
i bring a hammer
do i need anything else to repair it
besides that
hammer and cloth to fix it okay okay
okay i'll bring cloth i already have
cloth in my inventory
metal fragments too
okay i'll just keep what i
have
we also have the whole snake three times
with a nice weather the next day no no
only thing we have is like when somebody
sneezes when you sneeze then that means
that somebody's thinking of you no was
that the hiccups
was wait was that hiccup so was that
sneezing
i'm not sure
i forgot
is that sneezing
i don't think that's particularly a
japanese thing
um
okay no leather just cloth
cloth
fuel
some of these parts and then we'll put
the scraps in here let's put the tarp in
there too
okay
and i'm gonna take some meat
why can't i put the radiation panels
only in certain places
it's confusing
not counted as food
okay
let's see how my crops are doing
please don't say they despawned as well
oh look at them go wait how do i know my
corn is ready
i think it's not ready though
[Music]
the hell is the coin doing
it doesn't show me the info anymore
on it
hi rusty are these fibers the ball they
don't look like they're carrying fruit
i think we still have to wait a little
bit it doesn't look like they're caring
for it but they're definitely growing
eat growl
oh wait i forgot the hammer
i put away weapon ah
i forgot the hammer
do i have a hammer
hammer probably not there i'm not
[Music]
a hammer
okay
let's fly like a phoenix is supposed to
fly i wonder how hard it is to control
the thing
if i can make it land
wherever i want
gives me the power to fly incredible
where where am i going it was somewhere
over there
mama told you ever tried playing this
game before i'm not sure she didn't
mention anything about it
oh
[Music]
but
i could i could wait for iris
should come online
i mean isn't she again anyway online
she's not just not streaming yet
i always
wasn't she gambling
[Music]
okay i'll wait for eyewitz
and in the meanwhile
uh let's
uh do something else
and then we fly with iris wait let me
repair it i can rip but with some if i
repair it and someone steals it until
then in those 20 minutes
of course you will recognize that
she's a smart cookie
i'll write her on discord
iris
i wish when you start streaming do you
wanna
fly
around in
a hot air balloon with me dot dot dot
um i'm gonna repair
it it's close to
uh p8
okay i asked
i i wish i was
i need to get more than just one
interaction out of this stream you know
i i scheduled it purposefully at this
time for a reason
if i want to play alone i could just
play later in the day
sorry guys if it's disappointing
i might like people say i'm such a
social person at all but i may be social
but i'm also like
very aware
of
awkward situations
like
i find
you know these things aren't they better
when they happen naturally but how do
you make them i would have to run in
into them
but if i run into them purposefully then
that's not natural weaver that's just so
desperate but you know you know um yeah
i don't know it's kind of like i'm
begging for interactions which is so sad
ah
[Music]
i will i guess i'll try to research a
little bit with the 121 scraps that i
have
oh
[Music]
oh i'm like i would say i'm doing pretty
well in terms of trip this is my second
stream my second time playing rust
oh i can get the revolver
nice
a fire arrow oh
cool
interesting
what else did i get
oh that was by accident it just happens
[\h__\h] hell
spare gun spare
ah spare guns spare oh now i understand
it oh that's that's sick
empty propane tank oh [\h__\h] i keep on
recycling those well i don't need them
this time okay i need more scraps
i need oh i should have thrown them in
here i forgot i still
still had some in here damn it okay
ah you know what i'm just gonna run
around a little bit and hope to find
some more um
[Music]
stuff on the roadside because usually
i can get quite lucky by doing that when
i found those random crates they were up
that hill over there
are those locations where they spawn
do they repeat themselves
this is [\h__\h] gay
i swear to god my heart
my heart
my [\h__\h] heart it just spawned a
[\h__\h] car right here
oh my god can you not please
oh
no loot inside
oh my god
did you guys not get surprised by that
oh man
that did permanent damage to me
is that the one i just saw yeah
okay let's run up that hill
see if i find something
you usually there's like a lot of like
um
[Music]
like those those uh those containers
there we go
don't always have to
go to the
oh empty propane tank
i can build the the spare gun
you should try to fix up the car and
keep it
but now i already recycle wait uh i
still have some parts in my home
but maybe someone will steal it like
they stole my horse
but okay i do want to try that
how do i know what it needs it um
this is so cool these are growing even
you can
this is wonderful you can like
take cover in here too maybe
oh
so much storage
yo i want if i ever get a car
i kind of want like
something like this wait you can bring
people with you and go on a trip
i guess if you're going to like raid
some place then bringing this along is
pretty useful for like storage and all
that and
moving together
wait that sounds like fun
this sounds like a lot of fun actually
smack it with the hammer eh
ah
oh it just needs wood
uh
no no don't don't push it don't push it
don't push it sorry
sorry wait
oh it goes really far
all right
ah i always said yes
okay well then i first should repair
goddammit so much to repair
how do i
how do i give it wood i guess i don't
have one so i don't have the option to
keep it wood wait wait let me go get
wood uh
here is
here is the
car
it's a date check engine two okay i'll
just bring all the parts i have
no
time that was not my home that's my home
building blocked
i mean building blocks
the new senpai building
okay some wood
and um
i do have some
hearts i kept them
stairs
here i have these parts
let's see
i don't know what this may be useful
here's some functional some
metal fragments
it's enough
should be enough
okay
there's my car
it's like it was ask it was spawned
there because it was asking me to fix it
it was like please holy quick off the
fixing
please
fix me
oh it's done it's done already
can i just drive it
what about
high quality
okay the front part needs something
different
but that's it which maybe should i check
the back too is it three parts to fix
middle front back
it's two pieces of high quality metal
which i'm pretty sure i have but then
[Music]
okay now that's it
it doesn't seem to need engine plugs
good check engine
ah
[Music]
i had that and i recycled it but i never
saw this thing before never
i wonder if i can quickly get that from
the tech tree this will take a while
fixing this thing
maybe i can find it inside a different
car
dana picked it up
i can build that one part push it home
okay let's push it home
that should be possible
and push and push
and push
oh [\h__\h]
i'm not that close
it just goes back and then it hurts me
honey food
ah it's fighting back
i'll just
i'll help you
weren't you
brought to life because you wanted to be
fixed by me um
okay
let's eat some horse food
i'm the horse now
[Music]
i can't drive it yet right it needs to
be complete
did you guys remember what that one part
was called
let me see if i can research it
right here
here
rocks
[Music]
car carburetor
car the word car isn't it
[Music]
i don't see it in the workbench level
one
but i have to finish this in order to
get to level two workbench now
dropbox
no
oh
work
ah octane's level two
high quality metal and scraps
500.
okay i don't know about the uh
car right now this will take me a while
to get 500 scraps
okay
you know what well we'll take the parts
back for now because i don't want anyone
to take them
instead
and then when
when iris is online we'll fly the hot
air balloon
once we're done with that i'm gonna get
some try to get more scraps i try i will
try
there's multiple ways to get those car
parts
well for now we're gonna keep what i
have and then remember we need we need
this and this
remember
the car
will surely stay here for a while right
or will it despawn
i mean knows how to make it
oh man
i mean shouldn't she be sleeping
there's another car there maybe it has
some
some of the parts that i need
wait didn't i already
i checked it
okay nothing
oh [\h__\h] sorry okay
five parts
oh
that sounds expensive though because
everything needs scraps right
road sense
oh
can be yeah yeah i know i first tackled
them before
what i thought that was baklava
what
balaclava
you called it bala clava
i thought it was the food back lover
ah have you guys eaten it before that's
yummy
pretty yummy
yeah rmt used to love that
she ate it a lot
it's um i think it's
turkish i could be wrong but i think
it's a turkish
oh wait these signs i can ah
[Music]
are you alright i did that before
oh okay okay road signs oh
thank you
[Music]
i don't okay the other thing
maybe we're lucky and we find like uh
a car piece in these is there a chance
to find that
there's another car over there
no
i can still fix it huh um
what can i use my hair
i need to fix my axe
that works too
that works for now
it's very slow
uh
there we go
[Music]
are you always shocked
are you sure that takes ages
[Music]
let me check just the car
nothing i feel like i saw one before
that actually still had
one or two parts
inside
maybe someone put them in there are they
always emptying normally
are you always so
[Music]
you junkyard
what is
junkyard
wooden barricade
let me in please
let me inside
i thought you could get inside
get the rest oh my scraps
okay
i'm going back
oh there's a oh junkyard
since crap car is for scrap at the
junkyard
doko is written the dome junkyard it's
over there
maybe with the hot air balloon my gold
can be e7
but that would mean i would need to
bring a car
or can i just generally
are there like cards there that i can
you know
are not eaten
a uh [\h__\h]
i think you're so funny
oh i skipped the stone on purpose
[Music]
oh wait i'm not using my axe
off to the comedian store
first
there's a crate still is that still the
same crate is nobody interested in that
one
should i go
maybe i should
i wonder if anyone's
did i say comedian store
nah i said convenience store
ah
should i stop at home first
this sounds so close to comedian story
welcome to hollywood
um
go fight for that box you know what that
might be the last thing i'm doing today
uh fly hot air balloon check out the
junkyard
come back
again maybe with the hot air balloon
and then go for the
crate although maybe i should go for it
now
before iris comes
i don't know what her plan is today but
how much for a comedian junkyard not
worth it
was he dead
oh yeah super chat reading is planned
yeah
wait
am i going to wrap it yeah
[Music]
she wants a rocket launcher
that's very
ambitious
does she have the recipe
i feel like i saw a rocket launcher
somewhere
maybe just in someone else's stream
i don't need
ah
ah the
energy drink is
calling for an idol meeting again but
oh man i think it's making my tummy
horde still
i have one i bought like normally i
never have um
ah well
um wrong part
so close ah wait no i'll pick that up in
a second normally i never have
uh energy drinks
at home
when i bought two because i have to get
up at like 4 a.m
so i'm ready i'm ready for popcorn
more or less
[Music]
springs
who is it
boring
iris is live okay okay
okay
i will keep those parts
um by the way i have a little surprise
next week
i mean i guess it's not much it's just
uh
i have a special
arrangement
[Laughter]
you know how
uh
that's one of the parts i need
yeah
[Music]
the update is releasing next week
i was sneaky
and i asked if i could get early access
and i
am getting indeed early access i don't
know how early
um
so i'm probably gonna play it on
tuesday perhaps i guess since monday is
minecraft uh summer festival
i [\h__\h] have no space uh
it's so dark again
yeah so uh look forward to that
they are adding not only
uh gamers
but some others as well
[Music]
okay i don't need so many of those i can
i can get rid of some
maybe two
right
and some more scraps
i don't need two of those either
right
gamers and jen zero yeah
it's not that i have a way with them i
just ask
you know just ask it doesn't hurt to ask
questions if you want something
that is actually so
easily in reach don't be scared
should i keep it
i'll keep it
oh i should research it
uh okay but i think
ah damn it whatever yeah
uh at least i have one each
um
what else what else what else what else
i think that's it
oh this one maybe
[Music]
two yeah opens many doors
can i have a race no
no you have to be realistic yo
whoa
how many scraps 177
wow okay
not so bad
we are gonna go back home where's home
yeah i saw the green bar um
my brother's in town next week and can i
get a day off
no but you can bring your brother to
work and let him work as well
i shall remember that if you do that
well i don't think you have to unsub but
that's not really the only option if you
don't want to spoiler yourself not not
like the game is has anything to spoiler
really
it's just there's no story what are you
gonna spoil
yourself with
no you don't have to unstop just because
you don't want to see it first
[Music]
yeah i guess okay i will if you um you
can have the weekend off if you let your
brother work instead which makes so much
sense because you want the weekend of
since your brother is coming right well
yeah you can have a day off if your
brother works instead
what a deal oh i kept the door open
let's see
oh okay let's see
research baby ah i should research um
i wanted to research that
but no that's not so important now to be
honest it's not that important
i wanna do the car first
did you run out of fuel
oh
there we go
[Music]
watson drives a lovely car around
collecting props
oh yeah i saw her driving a little bit
probably also difficult like the horse
um
okay okay
ah wait i should save
i should save the scraps to make the
second workbench i need 500.
i shouldn't research anything right now
okay
200 scraps okay 300 left that's
manageable that's doable
and i just need one more car cart
one more piece of car
actually that should go downstairs
okay
now let's focus on the hot air balloon
i always
what you doing
how you doing
how are you doing
oh wait i need that to fix it
she answered
no how you
get the fuel
um
i have a fuel i have 134 fuel that will
be enough though
pretty sure that's enough
um
i could bring my night vision goggles in
case we fly in the dark
yeah
oh there's a bit more ammo here
and i could recycle that
i was keeping these in case you know for
the last day
triggered by movement placement you're
doing a lot of handmade shells
i wonder if i should just recycle them
or if i should use them for the last day
you know
wondering if
if that could be useful to do some
damage
but handmade shells
hmm
let's go fix the hot air balloon will it
like go off immediately when i fix it
i don't want it to like fly away
suddenly i'm coming okay
okay
no i have plenty
always aries
iris i like rarely ever interact with
iris
i feel like if i still lived in japan
you know me kelly and iris we would have
hung out a lot probably even go to
disneyland and so on
go on a lot of yakiniku dates i feel
like
we could have been besties in another
life
or another timeline if i was if i was
wasn't myth
then we would have had three members
living in japan at that time
oh
oh we would have hung out so much
there it is i think that's it
another timeline here
okay how do i fix you little [\h__\h]
spoke
okay it's taking club okay
oh it's fixed
this is a more efficient way of like
fixing these things like a super hammer
okay
this is i guess the start button
where's the uh here this is where i put
the fuel no that's where you put the
loot
also it's uh oh seven
oh seven
oh seven is where the balloon
currently is
look up oh
fuel storage there you go
anything else
i hope it doesn't just suddenly what if
you run out of fuel does it just drop
crash
and we die
oh it can burn now
or does it go down slowly
i'm a bit scared and in real life i've
also never mounted a hot air balloon
before but it sounds like fun
wait i remember playing like as a child
oh in like preschoolers so this was a
fun game like uh a lot of like maybe 10
people would make make a circle and have
this big big piece of fabric and they
would like wow wow what
and then there's some kids underneath
why was that so much fun
why is that so much fun but now that i
think of it when i do the same thing
with my bed sheets my cats really enjoy
being underneath
it's the same thing basically just a
little bit smaller
why is that so much fun
i wonder what's it's just like you're
not really doing anything
huh
like
because of the mystery
i think we also like instead of just
staying in we would just run through
oh i think one one way of playing with
it was like
like 10 people are holding it right
and then
we would
run through the other side ah yeah i
think that was like one thing to get
through while it's like up
like you lift it once
and two people switch places and run
through to the other side and hold it
and then you know that's the interaction
you run through fast and switch sides
that's how you interact with the kids
oh yeah wait that's so nostalgic
oh
playing kids as a playing kit as a game
playing games as a kid is just so
innocent and easy everything's fun
oh man
words right words am i right okay until
until she's here maybe i'll check the
convenience store is she far
i wonder if she's far away
i wish i could see her on the map but i
guess that would kill the pvp
in the comedian store
[Laughter]
try piloting first
but then how no i'm scared i want iris
to be inside i feel like
like it would be difficult to control it
so better to have her inside as well
uh i hope she brought her
for viewing goggles
when you call them again
binoculars
did you bring your binoculars
i'm doing sightseeing
oh she forgot
i think
i think i have a second pair and i live
close by so
so let me get them
actually let me
show you my house first then
it's uh
p-8
house
hers is probably so much cooler we can
fly to her house is her house on the
other side of the map you guys i think
someone says she's like really far
and we can fly over to her house and she
shows me her house
i think i had a second
whole live creams
so these welcome to my crib i i used to
watch that sometimes
um
it seems so surreal to watch such homes
that are so
unrealistically luxurious
the wind will take you wherever it wants
wait i can't really control it wow
it will just go to random place
oh [\h__\h] really
i know i'll offer her horse-sitting
service
and in really really tiny tiny tiny tiny
tiny written letters
there will be a note saying your horse
might
disappear
by the random will
of the game
uh we do not
take responsibility for that
we really don't
take any responsibility at all
whatsoever
really though it wasn't my fault i did
everything i could
[Music]
[Laughter]
he's roasting me in japanese she said oh
i feel like she would live in a more
luxurious place
this is a beautiful house no i was
talking about i was talking about
i thought
[Music]
oh please no really that sounds like an
amazing song it will hit the top charts
oh wow really i'm honored
i'm honored i am very honored
what the [\h__\h]
i should be shooting you one thank you
for my house
hi i know it's a beautiful house it's
bigger than my house it's really
beautiful
don't you think horsey yeah where on
your where on the map is your house
my house is on like in between f4 and f5
like right around the line of f45
perfect you know we can fly with the hot
balloon to your house
sure do you know how to like move this
i have a horse horse-sitting service
place
horse sitting service yes is that not
like a i will
i will no it's not a i will steal your
horse no no service i already had one
customer aka inino my inanes and i've
protected her horse successfully oh
there's a charge however i see your
horse is already eating so you're
automatically signing the contract by
having your horse eat it
thank you
how much is how much is the fee um so uh
per rl day real life day
it's um
30 scraps
actually for gen mates it's fruity
scraps are non-gen mates is some 45
scraps and 50 pieces of meat per rl day
because your horse uh looks very hungry
it already is eating a lot though so um
you're going to replace that meat for me
just kidding
we um
we'll see we'll see what it comes out
too
i'm considered kind of a i'm considered
kind of a gen mate right
right
right you release the same branch i get
a discount no no that's all your
discount not right nine branch members
are 55 scraps per day you're 45 scraps
per day oh
oh so it's still a discount
i see it
i see yeah so let me show you my house
and as you said it's not very easy okay
it's not very lip balm as you said
but i would probably it's beautiful in a
short amount of time this is beautiful
it's much
yes two days and this much and there's
so much progress
the president of kfp
no i
am i am not a little sheeta no i am i am
a little uh
i am a little angel yes that's what i am
i forgot that uh
well
but yeah so i'm really proud of this
actually
i've accumulated a few things all alone
i'm working hard on my tech tree you
know
oh you even got it i can imagine you've
been playing did you did you get a
mixing table
i have though yeah
oh yeah you should make one it's good to
get scrap
mixing table you can get scraps out of
it what
like you can no no you can grow berries
and then you can mix the berries to make
scrap tea
and then if you drink scrap tea you can
get more scrap when you
when you like hit barrels and stuff
thank you iris so cool for that
information
that's sick
yes
okay well forgive me for the house
comments
[Laughter]
oh
only
only if i get something in exchange
also you're using my hair um my horse is
then in that case in that case as a
proof of friendship
um
here's some corn
you do see that i have a corn field here
right
yeah but i thought maybe you wanted more
corn
are you kidding me that's five pieces of
foreign i mean
i could cook it for you if you want it
cooked but actually no i don't think you
can cook corn oh but but you know i
thought corn is your favorite food
because you have a whole field of it
i am very disappointed in you but follow
me
yes
i hope that we make it safely to
our destination
wouldn't it be such a of course such a
such a waste if we wouldn't make it
safely
oh what would make you assume that we
wouldn't make it there safely
well it's my first time controlling an
air balloon there could be some
accidents
uh-uh
that's true i fell off an airborne one
oh a real one in real life or
oh yeah and then real life is long
scratch though it was totally fine that
was good
okay so here is the air balloon i
already fixed it for you princess iris
yeah
thank you turn it on but seriously no
idea how to control it
yeah i don't know how to control it too
last time i tried
doing this like it just spin around it's
just span round around and i didn't know
how to move it oh
well
i mean i've seen it in like i don't know
children's shows or so that if you drop
something
some weight
then
oh yeah and then you can go back down
but i think you can just turn off the
button to just turn it off to go back
down but
it's currently going but at the same
time
yeah it's going
nor
wait i think i think this is the
wait wait let me let me put them into
the actually before they fall down let
me put them in here
into the storage oh there's a satchel
yeah
holy [\h__\h] it's going so fast actually
it is
but i think it's spinning round and
round
is it
oh yeah it's going in circles oh yep
it's going in circles
the flag shows the directions beautiful
oh that flag oh it is spinning oh it's
going to move the flag
and it went down
oh wait did you run out of fuel no no we
have fuel in there oh why did it go down
why did it go down you need did i
actually press down turn on the right
height the wind goes in a different
direction depending on height oh
you'll keep on turning it oh is that
what it is oh yeah
apparently okay
um i want to go lead west
west
never eat spoiled
watermelon that's going east
ah
[Music]
oh now it's going
south how do you
okay okay i guess
and now okay so and then
okay now it's going west sort of oh
oh i wait stop no don't don't oh
interesting oh
[Music]
we're controlling it this feels a lit
this is making me this is making me sick
to my stomach
please enjoy the ride i wish
[\h__\h] that's the wrong direction oh that
gravity
kind of reminds me of how like when you
go on roller coasters
and when you go down
that that feeling
i hate that so much do you like roller
coasters
yep
i can only handle disneyland ones
anything further than anything harder
than that i can't
i can't enjoy
yeah actually i was i was just saying
like
if you were
um like i don't know either if you
joined earlier or like you were part of
myth or so
then we would have been in japan at the
same time
and
i
i feel like you know me and callie we
would have gone to disneyland and all
kinds of places
yeah
oh my god we should totally go and you
guys come to japan all week
okay
wait wait wait wait oh okay
we almost crashed on someone's house
no only smoking we're slowly getting
there though wow it's hard and that's
going the wrong way again
and then we need to try to just go ahead
and
get it
uh
we should totally go when you guys come
to japan
even yeah although disneyland is so
freaking crowded man
yeah
it is
but we can stand in line together and
eat churros
yes you good
i've had like churros once in my
lifetime
there you go that is a sin
and chocolate flavored popcorn
oh i didn't i didn't already try like
different kinds of uh popcorn before
what is that sound
are you shooting people i think
someone's trying to snipe us what
for a second i thought that was just the
sound of you turning off the hot air
balloon that's why i was trying to
ignore it but
i think it is someone trying to shoot
well good luck with that
[\h__\h] we're going the wrong way again i
wouldn't be surprised if it's girl
oh
yeah
yeah yeah could very much be
are we close to her base i don't know
where it is there's a sniper rifle oh um
her base is somewhere like around like f
f 11 or f 12. it's it's much lower i
think or maybe more
i heard it too
just not the hot balloon hot air balloon
turning off is there really someone
shooting at us because that's pretty
accurate
i think
i think it's
it might be someone shooting yeah having
a little bit of a giggle a chuckle
can you can you check the fuel
the fuel
we have 77. oh okay that's like halfway
through
yeah last time i checked it was like
around 119 yes i think we still have
some more
come on it was going the right direction
for a moment oh oh okay it looks really
hard to control
yeah but i think all right now it's
going pretty well we're getting closer
oh yeah oh yeah i see i see our
destination wait it's oh there we go oh
there was a wait there was a lag like
[Music]
[Laughter]
this
i should become like a taxi a flying
taxi i'll practice this you're my first
customer
i'm a customer i thought i thought this
was free
that's a practice run free practice run
oh
i'll forgive
i want to see that
oh so luxurious house of irish
[Laughter]
you better impress me oh
it's it's a it's a very um
quirky
you know it's full of originality oh
it's a whole originality house um
yeah it's
it's got
it doesn't have a horse anymore because
the horse is at you
well
but it has everything else
yeah it's big what did you say f f6 or
what
it's f4 around f4 f5 so we can i think
f5 f5 might be a little bit more
accurate
come
[Music]
we've made progress at least yes
so i heard your goal for today is
getting a what was a bazooka
a grenade launcher well yeah pretty much
a bazooka oh there's a horse
wait it's too hot here
is it the fire of the hot air balloon
you gotta take off some clothes senpai
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
ah it's okay oh
okay i took up some clothes
you don't you don't need to take them
let me take off that jacket
i'm pretty cool
yeah
she caught the jacket
no i'm good now
game is not telling me to take off any
more clothes
that's okay okay oh really maybe
i don't know you look like you're
sweating a bit
how do you know
i can see the sweat droplets
oh no
not again
not again your ear
my ear
oh
yes
your ear looks
right we're going back again no the game
graphics looks realistic the ear looks
really
fresh not that way we're so close
oh
just go up now go up go keep getting
there
we're getting much closer yeah oh yeah
oh no that's not my house i see my house
sorta is that my house i think that's my
house
[Music]
no
there's a lot of people living around
here yeah who lives here
in in this area i don't know
these houses popped out in nowhere
apparently bailiff's pretty close
uh she told me that this might be close
oh
well i tried to land on your roof but i
don't know whose houses these are
you want to land on our my roof yeah but
i don't even know which one
it will hopefully stand out to me uh
because of its luxuriousness and it's
bonus right
um it's it's the biggest one in the area
oh
do you see it it's right next to the the
red tower
[Music]
oh
right now i'm not sure what i'm supposed
to be seeing
also i'm just circling that area
around just like right right right north
right north
right above us right north
and then you see there's red tower and
right below the red tower there's the
luxurious
iris mansion you don't mean the
lighthouse right it's our destination
today
no not not the lighthouse no
no no no no um we're going maybe a
little bit to the too much
yeah you could call the lighthouse my
second home
it's like my um
yeah it's it's like my uh what you gonna
call it my vacation house so we just
gotta laugh
okay
[Music]
it's close enough it's really close it
is oh wait it is
[Music]
let's go
soft landing
[Music]
let me mark where it is
here f4
f4 okay
i always in there right here
that's not your house that couldn't be
it
what do you think
um where are those walls what are those
damn girl you live like this this
this girl
this is just this is still in
construction it's still in construction
where it's gonna look better
[Applause]
no no it's it's it's still it's still in
progress there's nothing up here the my
real house is the there's the rock in
the wood part
okay so so first there's
my main my main room oh
it's actually stone in here
girl
[Music]
she didn't think
about that did she
she did not consider that
did she
girl
i take your horse now
[Laughter]
yes
would it also have shocked me if i
wasn't armed but
you know
uh horse is still doing well but i
wonder for how long it's gonna be doing
well
she almost died too oh because like she
was in the
in the like area of fire well
what are we gonna do about i guess ah
i have idea
i ride horse back to you
but
cost
100 scraps for this service
yeah
it's
return service special offer
100 is probably not much for her right
and it will help me getting back to her
place fast to pick up my body anyway
[Music]
yes
yay
good
decision
me lady
we will be on our way
immediately
honestly
that was funny
[Music]
i can't
what the deal
she rock
obviously we expect all my belongings to
be included in
the payment
you wouldn't
rob your
horse sitter's body would you
no
okay i hope i don't [\h__\h] this up and
accidentally kill her horse um
how how could that ever happen
it wouldn't happen
we'll be there by dawn or so
why is it not oh there we go run run run
run horsey run
there's a torch
yeah she wouldn't take my body when she
doesn't get her horse back yet right
don't go too fast i don't want to fall
off a cliff
good
i need to
place like sleeping bags like all over
the world because
apparently
the activated strength
so far she hasn't left a very good
impression she comes to my house and
insults it
and then i walk into her house and it
kills me
not going very well this date and it's
not necessarily my fault
but yeah i was saying uh so if i
understand correctly if you place your
sleeping bags all over the world you can
choose whichever you want when you die
to respond there
come on
ah where the [\h__\h] am i
[\h__\h]
forest yeah okay
cool oh god where am i
delivery at dawn i should charge an
extra fee for a night shift
because that's you know in austria by
law
you get extra payments if you do night
shifts
just saying just saying you know
it's too cold here oh no
not the best uh circumstances
i'm scared i'm so scared
[Music]
it won't kill the horse right it won't
kill the horse
will it
no no no
no no no no no no no
oh
don't tell her
[Laughter]
of course it's fine okay let me bring a
weapon in uh and um i'll wear this and
this
oh wait doesn't that that doesn't work
okay uh i'll bring a weapon i'll bring
my chainsaw
no
uh
bring ah
bring this
i don't know how to use these guns rifle
with the right ammo crystal rifle
does that work
together [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] her horse
will it run away
please don't run away
well i mean
it was night time so there's a it's
dangerous you know they'll see where i'm
going and um you know
okay go go go go go go go go go go go
body is here i was halfway through
heel oh [\h__\h]
zero that's danielle for a few
ah
does she know
late
delivery so she doesn't know okay
okay
i see i see where i died i know here's
that and somewhere at four
four
f4 or so that's where iris is
i hope the helicopter doesn't come
if it comes too close i'm gonna take out
my weapons out of my hot bar
okay it's going a different direction is
good
oh [\h__\h] man
little delay please understand
no no particular reason
for this delay uh just just took a
little lunch break hi chicken
didn't someone say free pieces of armor
is fine
also the helicopter is so far i don't
have to take it off off now
[Music]
okay
oh man
what a day well you know what at least
i
i would say
i got
um
good interactions out of doing this
early stream
no japanese members interactions but
this is fine
you know maybe iris should loot my body
so that i can um
so i don't lose
it
maybe she should because now it's like
getting choked
please loot my body uh
and keep the stuff save a little
delay
here caused by traffic
there's a there's a lot of traffic out
here oh man
[Music]
so unfortunate
boop
move out of the way i have a delivery to
make
ah
or or like um
maintenance
road maintenance
you know
yeah yeah okay we have oh here he is
[\h__\h] you
if i lose my business because of you
i'm gonna be so mad
where is uh
where's horse
oh god oh god oh there's one
[Music]
hallelujah
chocolate
okay oh that's uh that's a good good
friend
uh where is the body i guess i didn't
really carry any
no did i yeah i didn't carry anything of
importance or whatever
need a better horse a mountain horse
like you know like a mountain bike
okay
[Music]
we're back in business baby
did iris read my chat
you're no longer chapstick
does that mean she took my stuff
it's still within 24 hours delivery look
at those trees
there
what now what the [\h__\h] was that what the
[\h__\h] was that what the [\h__\h] was that
what the [\h__\h] was that what the [\h__\h] was
that what the [\h__\h] was that
oh god
it's a horror game
could it have been like a cactus
oh is that my that's my balloon
i think
height bug
ah babe was chapstick oh okay
okay let's uh find this luxurious house
oh now you can't jump over a big stone
huh
i'm
pretty much there
i hope the horse is
not hungry because i ate the last piece
of meat
isn't it this
oh
i hear
iris
horse delivery
service
thank you it was um
totally uh
troublesome uh everything went super
smooth and fine there was no danger
whatsoever of losing your horse
okay wait a sec
i'm almost ready oh wait i'm scared
i'm dehydrated can i drink your water
go ahead
no no no no help yourself
okay the traffic these days
unbelievable
come on in you'll be you'll be fine this
time okay do you want to bring your food
source i think it might be hungry i
don't know
oh no it's fine it's fine right now okay
come on in your stuff is right in here
oh wonder wonderful wonderful
thank you
wonderful i hope there is nothing
missing i will check your vote um why is
there
it should be it should be pretty much
why is there cooked human meat in there
did you cook a part of my body
no no no it's me i thought you wanted
some hope
so
i thought maybe you would like to
like to have a bite of hope all right
where where are the uh here's scraps oh
whoa
that's a lot of
thank you for the 100 scraps thank you
you said it was a hundred
yeah thank you
oh
thank you so much
[Music]
you shouldn't be afraid of just me
though because um yeah yeah you know
yes
why are you hiding something i'm not
here i'm not though
huh
it's not me who's hiding them
there's you know some npcs in this
server that tend to
be around
um
to haunt us us regular players
every once in a while
um okay
and they are watching
from
many different angles
that you do not expect
um
[Music]
thank you so much um so it was a fun
time
i'm i have no weapon in my hand so um
there is
there is no really you don't have i'm
sure you have you have a you had a spa
so i think you do have a weapon that is
just to protect myself from any dangers
on delivery um i'm off shift now and i'm
on my way to report
no no no no that's not fair that's not
fair that's not fair i'm not carrying
any weapons
[Applause]
a present
sounds like [\h__\h]
she's gonna make me lose all my [\h__\h]
weapons she for real
[Music]
is anybody watching her stream judging
by her reaction was that really by
accident or was that intentional
it was an accident
there's too many accidents recently
don't you think
where's my club
100 accident maybe it's about time that
i have an accident
that's blind i don't see any cold i'm
just in leather
i brought all my clothes to them
to fix the air balloon i can't make a
a sleeping bag
this is the last time i'm walking over
there and this time it's with a
without a horse it's gonna take so maybe
i could borrow no
oh
let's accidentally destroy something of
hers yeah
wait food though ah
dehydration too let me at least drink
something
ah lena
in the base
any taxi service you could call no cause
i'm the taxi
mr taxi taxi taxi
i'm not inaudible risk your life for
this don't worry
oh no but i think will i be running
uh yeah i'll be coming by the
convenience store i can get some food
there
she wants my skull
huh
as long as she doesn't take my
belongings but what was that with the
600 scraps guys
what was that about
is that by accident
did she really think i'm charging 600
scraps
but maybe she'll notice now when she
goes through my for my drops again
i was thinking i was also kind of
thinking maybe the reason
she um
killed me
was because she was testing me
if i would give her back
scrubs scraps
um if i would like point it out
and if i wouldn't
she would uh kill me
which she did but maybe i'm overthinking
it
maybe maybe either she
matching purposefully
when i came
with her horse
i brought 500 scraps
um just because
because no it was a payment from another
customer
and um
she added 100 scraps to that
yeah yeah yeah yeah
so the 600 scraps that's mine
it's too late
she still owes me 100 plus extra charge
per second death
and unless actually she killed me twice
she took my life one too many times
there's not much food
it's quite the workout though
chad are you snitching
bad chad bad chest
she's oh she's already thinking of
paying me extra charges for my deaths
i thought she was just like like really
trying to get uh
the element of pvp
and to start some
some fights
for fun
now while i'm while i'm out here
i hear something while i'm out here i
might wanna might as well wanna
you know
get some
pick up some stuff that won't be useful
yeah i just can't read her but if you
guys say it's an accident okay if it was
a declaration of war then okay okay
i give you war
that's what you want
you guys say that's not what she wants
oh this one needs more different parts
oh
yes she should be the one going to me
but okay i'll pick up my hot air balloon
and fly back
but she she said she'll keep my
belongings safe which sounded like she
wants me to
come pick it up
iris is coming to
do something with gouda
oh [\h__\h] it's [\h__\h] hot in here
oh my god oh i'm fine again
put it in a box yeah but it's inside or
outside because i don't know if i can
enter her house if she's not there
damn i've never been in this biome
before
today's the first time i'm seeing this
biome
this whole
thing is taking more time i don't think
we'll be fixing the car
anymore today
i'll go and pick up my stuff and then ah
suddenly i changed
it
did i just change or have i always been
looking like this today
magic
i did it again
i did it once again
what's going on
uh someone else is there for the crate
ah the dome has a crate oh
[Music]
it feels like kuda is online 24 7. right
now like these past days
put a code on the box okay
is it outside though
and also what is the code
would i know
what is the code
sent by the skype
iris iris virus
one one six six
does that have a meaning is that um
[Music]
how do i
i swear to god i swear to god
i swear i swear to god
if i don't make it home safely there's
only 116 scraps in there there's no
extra
where's my extra
whatever
do
[Music]
and back we go wait i wanted to get my
my helicopter um
[Music]
i think it was here right
let me fly back
that iris is unbelievable isn't she
really men ugh
okay
so
[Laughter]
that's what you get
oh it should be somewhere here
[Music]
and i feel well i mean
well at least at least part of the trip
should be possible
wait where is it
shouldn't have been somewhere around
there i i think i saw it once when i was
uh returning with the horse
[Music]
ah
directly south what do you mean that
would work directly south from that spot
it's pretty big i should be able to spot
it relatively easily
[Music]
i feel like it landed
like on a hill
it's closer to the desert
i was pretty sh ah maybe a bit
was
i think here no not f5 at four
south of ireland
i i think it was on the left side of the
square um
green
f4
so
oh yes
huh
okay
it's fine it's fine i'm just gonna walk
back i'm getting so much cardio today
oh wait what
no whatever
i shouldn't get too dressed because it's
gonna be too hot again anyway
well well well well
man this is taking longer than expected
oh oh some of the horse was riding there
maybe that's iris with the horse that i
delivered her
oh there's another one wait maybe that
yeah
maybe this one has fuel
that's not the one we didn't land in
like
the desert that's just the other one
that i saw i guess
uh
no fuel
okay
long long
long long long way home
on country road
take me home
to the place where i belong
i don't want to go by the dome
a lot of scary people there oh
i thought it was a horse but now that's
a deer
london mama
is that a horse that's not something
that's someone's horse because there's a
saddle on it
whose horse are you
i wish i had a horse
no man's radiation ah
did i
no i don't have a suit right now
i see and i couldn't really go there
anyway right now
it's still there
i wonder who's gonna get it
i could have a horse if i took it
i like that logic no i don't know how
you're thinking
you know it's lost isn't it that looked
lost that looked like a forgotten lost
horse to me
it desperately needs food and a horse
sitting service a reliable horse sitting
service
it comes with
return delivery
even during the night
sounds very compelling doesn't it
where's the spot of saddles
oh
but it's probably someone's because i
did see someone riding by and they were
all going for the
dome crate so
my butt really hurts i've been sitting
on my butt for way too long
i should be sitting on my legs hey on my
yeah on my legs
ah anyway
at least we got 100 scraps out of it
right
100 scraps and five corn
but in the honestly in the time that i
was running back and forth i could have
made more than 100 scraps
for real go
i've spent like half an hour
if not more
running back and forth oh
dead
whatever
it's a bad customer i will just never
never
have her as a customer again
and if she ever needs a taxi again
or horse dating service you can ask
someone else
give her a bad review on uber you can
the uber drivers can raise the
passengers too you know
blacklisted
yeah i lost the balloon too
that's okay i didn't quite expect to
bring the balloon back anyway
not necessarily that's okay
it's fine
[Music]
oh
oh i'm at the supermarket
no it's oh my ceiling lamp
nice
ah [\h__\h] i have too much um
stuff with me
actually i brought the night vision
goggles because i was thinking if we fly
in the nighttime i could still look at
stuff but i was so busy anyway
taking care of
oops
flying the thing
was fun though
it's actually pretty fast once you
figure out how to fly it properly
once you have
the hang of it
it's actually quite a good um
method of
transportation
you can get to places easily you can't
really
[Music]
be like shot down easily either
oh wait that's i have two of those
here we go now we have more space don't
need that
ah oh yeah i don't need that
i'm gonna recycle one of those
join gouda and ban kill iris are they
trying to kill iris
oh coyote is there
didn't i have an axe
maybe not
i feel like i had an axe
i'm not gonna go there now i wanted to
end the stream and read super chats man
i have enough for today
do you think coyote will be friendly
towards you oh mixing table
um
yeah
i don't have to talk switch to friends
she's trying to be friendly with the
others
see she's she just wants to be friendly
coyote elf killed iris
very good
revenge so you know she must have heard
of what happened that iris killed me
twice she must have heard that and be
like
no no killing my friend
she's very loyal to me see
[Music]
why i hear something
you can you can figure out what it was
by the footsteps it sounded
like a deer i
think i hope it wasn't the wolf
it's gone now
it's gone
oh
ah another one of those
[Music]
i wanted to keep um certain ones for
research didn't i
let's
recycle though this is this is recycled
ah this one
i was thinking of keeping it for
something
i don't remember what
this one's splitter i don't need that
lampna
[Music]
spare gun oh
yeah okay you know what i'll keep it
i'll build myself a spare gun
sounds
although
is the spare gun good you guys used it
ever
because you have to build all the spares
too
spare gun
spare
spell gun
spit spear spears beer gun
wait if i get a few more
i might be able to get 500.
to get uh you know i wanted to do the
next
uh workbench level five
uh
close
very close wait um this one too
[Music]
spear got like pretty space ah
so this man i never used this [\h__\h]
oh wait i should eat this
eat this
um give me scraps you know what i don't
nor do i uh
nah i don't need it
give me scraps please
ah wait these ones come out as scraps
you haven't researched this one did i
did i research that one
why not research it
[Music]
did i research it yeah i did
okay
no
no whatever
you need to work bench ah just come on
scrubs
all right maybe there's something on the
roof
i need a few more
a few more
[Music]
okay
oh did that already re spun
no i just i guess i didn't take it
i have road signs more times
almost 300 i had like 200 right
all right
he snap
my goal today is to go to sleep uh
at like
[Music]
9 a.m 9 or 10 a.m
because
i have to wake up at 4.
i i hope i can make it
at p.m p.m nine p.m go to sleep at nine
p.m
chunks of cars
true
[Music]
this one doesn't though
did you have something oh yeah
oh more of those
okay now now i think i completely looted
it looted it
oh we made it
[Music]
i'll keep this for now in case i didn't
research it
nice
okay now we go back and we finish this
[\h__\h] up
i'm
gonna uh
get the level five workbench hopefully
and
yeah and i'll say
goodbye goodbye i think i will read some
super chats though i promised
i wanna
keep my promises
super chat
research c4 but no that needed so many
scraps
and
[Music]
i think it's
more important
to get the workbench
i feel dehydrated from this energy drink
more water
ah tambourine
is your tambourine in the loot crate
[Music]
did i put my scraps in here um
i think maybe i put them upstairs
[Music]
oh i should put down them
the mixing table
then iris taught me one useful thing
that a
mixing table i can drink a scrap tea
scrap tea that sounds
interesting let me look at that oh
basically you know pure oh and
basic scrap tea oh wait this is easy to
get especially now that i planted some
berries but i need
white and yellow ones
specifically pure scrappy at advanced
ah
[Music]
okay i will be looking into that
interesting
she taught me to check for traps
yeah then she told me that you know that
was really sus like that those dangerous
npcs who might want to kill you and then
immediately after i die oh how how is
that
weird what a weird coincidence
weird coincidence
just still going to think
okay uh
wait i probably need wood let me see
what i need uh the
work bench
level two metal fragments five hundred
okay okay okay okay okay
huh
ah i need to make it on the workbench
okay
this is so weird
it's kind of annoying some things you
can craft
without it some things you can i feel
like as long as there's a workbench in
your
in your
house or so
you should be allowed to craft it while
you're standing anywhere inside your
house that would be
nice oh i want to build those
i can
i'll do it another time
all my scraps are gone all those
beautiful scrubs
i could have had so many more if i
didn't die a second time
could have walked away with 600 scraps
it's it's just you know when you once
had something and then it gets taken
away from you
it just hurts so much more
[Music]
man it's getting uh really crowded in
here
so much stuff
i guess i'll put it here
let's look at the tech tree
oh
what do we have
what is that
salvaged eyes pig
what gathering eyes of it
homemade landmine grenade
pistols flashbang
flame from
thompson custom essentially
oh there's the ammo
solenoid cried
1600 oh
hold those
sights rocket launcher
high velocity rocket
torpedo
in a submarine you can use that you can
make a submarine or like steal a
submarine
indian i hope it's yellow yellow
yellowstone elevator
oh wow
oh there's some intricate interesting
stuff in here
oh
ah
ah here's the thing this one i need for
example for the car
220 that's not too bad
here we have some oh this is the armor
that iris was wearing
some
syringe ah here are the night vision
goggles that i recycled
oh okay interesting oh and there were
strengthened glass windows not a hotel
okay
last thing let me check my my crops how
they're doing
u-boat time not yet okay that's a long
way to go
although
how do you i guess
do you have to like
how do you get your hands on a submarine
do you go into your diving gear and you
just look for it under the water but
that feels like
is it done
right
oh these are done
it feels like very dangerous conquest
you can buy one
you can buy a submarine
right
[Music]
dying
uh
why are you dying
water 25 okay okay
i will
or can it only be harvested once
right
whoa
nice
so much fun
do i have to
oh
harvest once
and then clear it
[Music]
so then we can plant the white
i think i have some
wait what is that
yellow berries
okay there's some corn seeds again
corn someone's corn
let me let me eat some of those
then we can plant them again
i need white ones too i wonder if i have
some seeds
hi
hi hi hi hi
yeah after you eat them you get the corn
out of their feet
[Music]
and some more in here i think ah there
you go
some a few a couple
maybe i'll plant some blue ones too
potatoes can you
can you
plant potatoes
are there potato
[Music]
i'm not gonna say potato seeds
i'm gonna say it
can you put potatoes
how do you plant potatoes
oh
where are the potatoes don't where are
they
and then they if you eat them
you don't and you don't get seeds from
them how do you get more
[Music]
okay that's done
i'm done for the day
yeah
okay everybody thank you for watching so
far i hope that was enjoyable for you
guys we had some
interesting interactions
there definitely
um
i made some memories that i will never
forget
whether that's a good thing or a bad
thing
well well well well for the person
involved it might be a bad thing
yeah
revenge on the brain
but i i had a good time
nonetheless so we're gonna read simple
chats now
before i
am hearing
go mad
from the energy drinks
but i've calmed down i think let's move
to the office
[Music]
and
insert chat
here we are once
[Music]
again now it's not double right
fun
danny has a plan to kill iris what
aren't they like shouldn't
kind of loud oh sorry
let me about rest in toys what what i
closed the door i think i think i closed
the door i think i remember
i'm not sure this is always like every
time i close the game i'm like did i
close the door
no it's
unsure it makes me anxious and i want to
lock back in but loading up the game
takes so much time
yes annoying you don't want to go back
into the game
hmm
hey you're racing a nutshell not a hotel
well
none of my business
uh we
i think we need to continue
at the second tunic finale stream
correct me if i'm wrong but i think i'm
correct
thank you for the stream thank you for
watching
close your door i think it's closed
i think
you will want to start that holo 30
faction i was going to be pulling for
you from now on
oh that's just normal everyday life for
me it's okay
i'm used to it
is this the right one
a real phenomenal that's it that's it
but
i know ami doesn't oopsie doesn't like
pvp but i feel like we are on the same
wavelength
so
an alliance with alma is also very much
possible
the two
girls who just want to stay out of
trouble
and for that have to protect themselves
[Music]
pbe raids together well i am
just just wait let it happen um
i'll play it again probably next week
we'll see what we're gonna do for that
[Music]
thank you for coming by again
it's nice seeing you again thank you
soon for the support
hope you're doing well
um
get you back on your side is this why do
you even like like good at the game like
i don't see her playing rust that much
maybe it's just currently just focusing
on other games
orphan of course
the water kills everyone outside
maybe i should do that too subaru's
house is already decayed oh no so she's
probably just gonna wait until next
season huh
oh what is this
oh
ah you don't hear mine
guess what that means
only kiara only kiara only
that's what that means
that's right that's the right spirit can
you be chicken nugget thanks for the
pinky
going to popcorn
if yes and i'll see you
there it's less
way way less than 24 hours oh god i'm
nervous i still need to practice
something
also do you guys wanna help me with some
homework
you want to help me
[Music]
can you help me come up with some
pickup lines
that will be upstairs
um in english is fine i'll translate
them to korean for no particular reason
um maybe bird related
like something like you really ruffle my
feathers i don't know but that probably
maybe doesn't even make sense in korean
though
yeah i'm probably going to use one of
the crony ones
asking the wrong people really i feel
like travaji would be able to come up
with some bird related pickup lines
yeah pick up one could be hard to
translate
true if it's a pun
then
probably not possible
yeah
translate it to korean and i will
translate it to korean through papago
i just i just want some good
uh pick-up lines
chicken breast as the punch line oh that
that could work
like i've got some chicken
breasts
in the fridge
at home do you wanna
eat some fried chicken
do you want to eat some fried chicken
with me i've got some chicken breast at
home
how about that
if i said that confidently in corey and
i think it won't get some loves
because they also like fried chicken do
you wanna eat some fried chicken with me
i got some fresh
chicken breast at home
how about that
i have some nice chicken breasts when i
tried it at my place
but i i
uh
i got some fresh chicken breasts
wanna try at my place
okay
it sounds like an invitation for dinner
well
it is but there's an implication you
know
okay another one
oh do you like your chicken spicy
because i know how to make it flaming
hot
[Music]
does korean use the same word for boobs
and chicken breasts like english i would
think so
it's always you know that body part so
i hope you like
spicy food because
this
fried
chicken
whatever
is
hot as [\h__\h] but is that gonna work and
when it's translated
it's like hot and spicy it's the same
word in english but i don't think it is
in
korean
help
[Music]
maybe it doesn't doesn't only have to be
related to chicken but
it could be good or like related to
birds
um
you make me want to spread my wings oh
that's romantic though wait
a minute never mind maybe not
i felt like that sounded philosophical
you know you give me freedom
you make me wanna
outlive my creativeness and fly away
[Music]
bird related pickup
what
bird pickup lines
huge collection with the first best bird
pickup
50 plus best bird pickup lines for your
crushed what
no [\h__\h] way
why is there so many
parrot owl duck penguin birds pick-up
lines
what
why is that a thing
why
why is it
where is that what
oh dear this is disturbing though
after checking the thermometer i
confirmed that you are hot one hot bird
are you flappy bird because i could tap
you all night
are you just happy to see me or is that
oh dear
even the early bird what
no
some stupid ad block thing even the
early bird catches a warm girl you can
get a bite anytime you pop in my life
like what what
hey girl do you like bird watching
because i like chicken you out ah
checking you out
wanna fly the coop come back to my nest
on
now
i stayed awake all
night thinking about you
some of these are really
disturbing
my heart keeps coming back to you you
must have put
a raptor band around it
what does that mean
penguins are the only animals that stay
with the same partner oh
that's that's a good one that could be
translated well penguins are the only
animals that stay with the same partner
their entire lives would you like to be
my penguin it's not too looty either
please be my penguin i want to stay with
you forever like penguins do when they
find me now the first one was better
rewarded
oh
penguins are the only
animals that stay
it's alive
stay with the same partner their entire
lives
would you like to
be my penguin
there are other animals and birds oh
man penguins stay
with the same partner their entire lives
would be like to be my penguins
now it's not as impressive anymore
[Music]
oh since you are one of a kind i'm
putting you in the list of endangered
species
that is so weird
at least not
like exaggerately uh
glued
you must be puffin as you've been
running from my mind online you must be
from tennessee because your car has a
tendency license plate
what isn't that
just a logical conclusion
how is that a pickup line
what
where's the joke
it's an anti-joke
the joke about another pickup line
did you put
wings on my heart because whenever i see
you i feel it takes flight
oh that's cute
that's cute that's pretty cute did you
come up with that yourself
ah you're the only 10 i see it
bird pick-up lines
there's more
oh god
why why why the why
you do do birds use google and look up
pick up lines to pick up other birds
yeah this side has the same ones
yeah that's the same one this lame
does
well
yeah maybe the only people who use this
is bird v tubers
35 plus best bird pickup lines
show me the sight isn't loading
wow
50 parrot owl duck penguin birds pick-up
lens
oh god this one comes with like
really stupid graphics
but indiana is also all the same
[Music]
this is pretty much
the same lens as the other websites
what
some of them aren't even bird related
and really boring really [\h__\h]
you're so unknown with her chicken flap
it's confirmed so i can tell him i told
you
what what
why would you not be no every chicken
all of you are noteworthy i'm writing
all of you down
i've noted all of my chickens down
you were all in my folder
okay i'll i'll look more into this
later but if you guys have some good
pickup lines tell me
um
[Music]
are these flush chats
reminded me of a shitty budget airline
who went
ah
over my carry-on luggage
after they tore my ticket stub
i had no choice but to throw into the
bin many of my belongings
oh
i managed to clear till just over by a
few friends and they still wanted me to
reduce i ended up with all my i read
this already ah that's really stupid
oh man
i heard stork's nest for life could you
help me build one
yeah
[Music]
cute if you guys have read them to me on
twitter later
on
my friends
i think oh this was right when i killed
the last boss
thanks for the pinky witness thank you
for witnessing it live
staying until the important moment
hope you hope it was worth it pirahmana
also thanks for pinky comments on claire
and tunic for a first impression of oh
cute foxtail and really turns out to be
a challenging but fair game and it's
still relaxing and cute and still
supremely rewarding when you beat that
boss
a wonderful journey
yeah yeah yeah iron green
it's about
it sounds rewarding
[Music]
it sounds also very shocking when you
get the first ending
it's like hey yo what you're telling me
this is this is a bad ending really
and then it really motivates you to
get the the real ending too
normally when there's games with several
endings i'm not really that motivated to
do them the other ones
i guess it depends on the game too but
normally i don't really care that much
also i'm not much of a completionist but
yeah it was kind of a first in tunic
typical ending for soul slash really
oh
i was crazy motivated yeah
[Laughter]
and you gotta make the medals yourself
very common trope to have a repeat the
cycle ending oh i didn't know
yeah
now i know what to expect if i ever play
dark souls
let's go cover thank you
lord emma thank you for the pinky the
gamer over here let's freaking go
[Music]
ah well
i don't know i feel like the boss fight
i i'm i'm not so proud of it the first
few bosses in the game i
was doing so well but then it spiked so
hard
at least i did it
at least i and i got thrilled
all of it
i did watch um fubuki zappa's fight and
she at the time when she killed the boss
she had
uh
kind of
less
upgrades than me
quite a few less upgrades
but she also used like
i think more
items she even managed to like switch
items in the middle of the battle
yeah and then she was like oh thank you
for waiting
yeah i already
forgot what exactly her strategy was i
think nothing in particular like but she
also had
quite a couple of ghosts it definitely
took her
over an hour
not two
yeah she she had a lot of streams like
that were like two hours or so
so she she had many breaks in between
she didn't find
uh
many
upgrades but she did do the full true
ending as well
those bosses were hard they were
and it's always you know it looks easy
when you watch it you're like oh you
should have done this and that why did
you do this and then but
when you play it yourself
it's so hard you're under so much
pressure especially when you're
streaming man
[Music]
i don't know how much i really deserve
that title um but
[Music]
maybe it's not so much about skill if
we're judged by how many games i've
finished then i'm definitely the gamer
of ian
and how long i've been playing those
games
thank you for the rest of the time
the game finisher of ian yeah
that's okay wow i knew you could do it
that was an awesome fight thank you
who was it was it
though thank you
very much riveting
definitely
amount of game your time game time
you're comparable with gamers
boss no skill involved i don't regret it
did you just
like spam
whatever
tanked it
had empty spam attack
i also
got it
mindless smashing
then you were [\h__\h] lucky to be able
to do it just with mindless smashing
one
hey now anyway you gotta kiss mwah thank
you thank you so much
fellow thank you soon for the pinky oh
it's quality you are cute fox cat
phoenix warrior can do it
even though there were challenges at
times you braved them all in the end it
was so much fun to watch you kick butts
like the warrior you are thank you for
accompanying me on this journey
it was really fun
i think
that was one of the best playthroughs we
had on my channel
really good couple of streams
10 out of the 10 can recommend
thanks for watching
general run donkey shirt evan's out
there in the lunchbox thank
that was so satisfying congrats on the
hard fought queen kiara that was really
a fun playthrough it was so great to see
how enthusiastic you were about the game
thank you
it felt great too
so i'm glad it came across that way
although i did go a little bit crazy
around the
end thank you so much
congratulations kiana you beat her so
happy you played and truly enjoyed
tuning it's one of my favorite games it
was awesome to see you figure things out
and legit get good at the game it was
such an impressive playthrough
thank you
thank you thank you glad you enjoyed it
also i'm glad i could play one of your
favorite games that's always nice
thank you for the pinky
congratulations you really proved why
you are the gamer opinion oh but i gotta
too much too much praise
thank you so much tiny delta thanks to
the pinky there are cheese only hardcore
gaming that's my kiwawa i'll be honest i
was a bit frustrated when you're going
for street cheese straps instead of
giving it a few more tries because you
had the skills for it all along
but it was a great fight from you
yo but even those cheese strats need
like technique and skill
so
even if i would have went for those i
feel like it deserved respect as well
but you know
no i'm not going to continue albany yeah
it's been too long and uh
i don't feel like it
it's just too intimidating
um
oh i don't necessarily mean
um cheese straps like throwing
a decoy in there and then going down the
stairs that's not what i mean
i mean like you know
the videos that we were looking at
during the stream
you an extension lily establishing
bottom fragrance unknown thanks to the
pinky
no number one max kim no
it's got you too
oh no
i think for this one there's not even a
stream a lot of the other conventions
that we participated in there was at
least a stream but i don't think at
least i didn't hear of it
i don't think popcorn has a live stream
oh
that's too bad but
if uh korean bros keep on supporting me
and keep on um
like recommending me to conventions as a
guest
then there can definitely be another
time
another chance
yeah
well i've still getting stronger in
korea so
yoroshiku
yoshiku
don't know how to say it
in korean
i knew you could do it i'm just really
proud of you kiara always proud of you
my oc you're amazing you really are the
absolute best ah come on
no
you were praising me too much
nah
[Music]
when i just read your super chat
it sounds like i'm like such a pro gamer
no no no no but thank you
[Music]
oh
oh no no
thank you for the pinky i went to bed at
1am while watching you streaming i woke
up in the morning you're still playing
tunic what happened
what do you mean what happened
i just i was just trying to finish the
game and then to be like that sometimes
but
that stream was pretty long
hope you got some good sleep
yeah honestly pretty good once you got
back into the controls
yeah it took me a while
but yeah
thank you thank you that's so sorry this
thanks for the pinky as well dr kevin
casey but don't forget he did conquer it
you can conquer his your conquer yours
too did he conquer he he conquered the
toilets he didn't conquer his
like
condition or so but that's probably
impossible
i don't know is that possible
dr kevin casey dr captain casey dr kevin
casey
who is a very interesting character in
scrubs
thank you thank you thank you i'm glad
to have another scrubs fan and mogu's
but how can you not be a scrubs fan hmm
yeah the toilet was says everest
yeah yeah yeah i know i know
my everest was the game's
mountain
first and thanks for the pinkie and
thanks for being so furious tonique i
love playing the game myself but stop
because the combat was too frustrating
oh
kendra's so good at finding secrets so
this has been a great play for you to
watch
we only all well maybe you could have
like
um
like turn the difficulty down a little
bit more
give it a chance practice
practice
if i can manage to play the game and
finish it
then you can too
definitely
dr clarkson todd are my favorite
characters
um mine
you know after watching it
watching scrubs a few times and like
growing up while watching it
more and more you realize
how stupid jd can be like how
how he has like a hint of a bad
personality sometimes
the way he
they make it really clear in the show
too though but i don't think i was able
to see through that when i was younger
but the way he treats like
people and
his girlfriends and all that
is is weird
yeah he definitely is not a perfect
protagonist and that's that's good i
guess because normally protagonists are
like
often just too perfect
all of them have selfish genders and
tendencies i wonder if that's like you
know with um um
what was the shows
uh what was it
s seinfeld yeah
i was so shocked when i watched it until
the end and then
i was like what is going on in the end
and then the conclusion was
they're bad people
all of them are bad people
and maybe
maybe
maybe scrubs was a little bit inspired
by
given their given giving their own
protagonists and
other characters quite a lot of flaws as
well
gives them way more depth
and relatability
but it's not so much that you would hate
them
outright hate them
yeah
i feel like seinfeld and it was
weird it came so out of nowhere to me
like all that ending stuff
i was like this is a different show what
the [\h__\h] is going on
i was so confused
thank you for the red subject thank you
so much boss you did it so proud of you
thank you
i'm proud to i'm so glad i did it oh it
was such a pain though
it was painful and fun
worth it
thank you rygana
big choo choo
spicy chicken papa thank you
so much
for watching
for the red super chat
well it's been a while since the last
stream that was this long but it reminds
me of why you are my aussie this was
quite frankly a journey of the stream
where we saw pretty much all the faces
of takanashikuwa's ups and downs even
asmr surely you are the gay marvian
well thank you very much for that sweet
comment
thank you
not that you really needed a reminder
right
100 inputs is crazy but the whole riddle
leading to the the puzzle
is quite something
damn
it must be difficult to create something
like that
ah thank you fried scrub
i appreciate it thank you for your love
and support
and your generous donation
[Music]
what an epic conclusion to the series
the last boss one was an absolute
nailbiter
real gamer moment
no cheese or copied strats just
inspiration
pure skill not to mention you're
cracking almost all puzzles at this late
hour
[Laughter]
yeah but i already kind of forgot the
last plus one but it must have been for
me like very very
scary i didn't want to like [\h__\h] up
because i was using
items and stuff but i think in the last
run i didn't even really
use my i think i didn't end up using the
dynamite did i
um
but did i did i use the dynamite in the
final run
i don't think i did
i just ended up hoarding it all
ah we all knew that was gonna happen
but yeah those are manga berries
oh man
merry pip and stockish and miniature
pinch of jam is the last super chat with
a red one thank you it was great time to
be able to enjoy my favorite games tunic
with other chickens oh
really you're you you were a fan of
tunic already
thank you attention and always we hope
you take care of your health also i hope
all the chickens take care of own health
i hope so too
very important
everybody
take care of your health miniature
pincher john you too though
yeah
be careful
gosh i'm so tired holy [\h__\h]
it's it's hitting me now
the
the low after drinking a
energy drink
but i finished reading the finale super
chats which were quite a lot
thank you guys and minister pincha john
here is it
[Music]
i am
tired and dehydrated well
fall asleep quickly now it's just 5
uh p.m now i need to practice and then
eat
and then prepare some
stuff like uh for the panel
yeah
oh but i'm looking forward to it and
then also the meet and greet um i'm a
bit nervous about the meet and greet
because
i wonder if everybody's gonna be able to
speak english
i think there will be a translator
though in case somebody
is not able to speak english properly
an emergency translator might be there
the rest of it no if i rest i'll fall
asleep too early
a little bit too early but now i'll i'll
just
[Music]
ah at least i can sleep early probably i
didn't find my melatonin last night so i
couldn't use it but i still slept
somewhat early
early it's still past midnight but
earlier than the night before
japanese is latin for all otaku that's
some nice way to compare and describe it
[Laughter]
yeah maybe they can speak japanese
[Music]
yeah i'll i'll put up a sign that says
english or japanese please
or german
well
that was fun i think
that was a fun rest day
some tattoos some violence some anger
some fun
yeah they should know i'm not fluent um
your fans will prepare for talking i
hope so i hope so i always tell people
to prepare and then they come in
unprepared most of the time but that's
english-speaking fans so
i think the korean fans they they know
you know we might have some
communication problems so prepare well
wow
um
okay now everybody
we forgot
once you're nervous yeah yeah i am
it's okay if you forget it but some
really don't even think about that no
you're winging it oh
i'll be preparing and practicing
and yeah
i'm tired sorry no
it hits me hard and german will say
affidavit
good luck at the panel thank you
i think it's kind of longer than the
other ones a little bit so um i hope it
won't be too awkward
i hope we're gonna fill the time
bye bye
thank you soon oh
some birds use sticks to make their pet
is pretty but i have to tell you you
don't need a single one
[Music]
that's cute birds do that
birds do that
that is so cute they use a stick to like
fluff themselves off oh that is so cute
i have to look that up
oh
that is so cute
girls use sticks to fight other birds
wow
violent as always
okay again bye bye
[Music]
i'll see you um
you know
actually it's who
i don't um
if i'm gonna sleep early now
i think i'll probably still
take a nap after
the panel
[Music]
i hope i'll do my best to not delay
age of empires
but you know
i have to
adjust it to myself depending on how i
feel so keep that in mind
okay
see
[Music]
thank you
thank you that's so sweet
i wish that for myself as well
thank you
[Music]
you