[Music]
[Applause]
H KY
ke KY
ke It's the Final
Fantasy
the Final
Fantasy hello
everyone copyright
no
ah
cocacola
Z and those weren't cracks you thought
those were my cracks there was that was
a bottle
opening no no no no no did you not hear
the
sound maybe I can recreate it with my
Knuckles and my mouth so let's imagine
I'm opening a Coca-Cola
bottle
see how different that
is that was my finger
[Music]
cracking that's very that was very
different can someone make a comparison
and line it up with a Coca-Cola bottle
opening
video thank you thank you thank you I oh
I need to make a starting tweet it seems
I have
forgotten uh uh uh my my my my tweet my
normal tweet in the first place was
already
late St
starting now join us in the
finally
Sao
okay I forgot I don't know I was busy
was I was doing really busy
things I had I had I had a meeting of
sorts that um brings me
to difficult life
decisions uh and I recorded uh two
things one short
video and an ID don't meeting uh not
quite more like an adult Idol meeting so
adult idols you
know oh what
Happ I I haven't gotten around packing
yet so that's pretty yby but my my my my
bro my brother is coming by sometime in
the middle of the stream to bring me my
second suitcase back cuz he was um
borrowing mine um not that he doesn't
have one but mine is cooler so he
legitimately wanted to use it
yeah just because it's hard hard shell
um
suitcase yeah yeah I packed the pajamas
I did it but yeah he's coming back he's
is coming back he's coming to like
sometime in the middle of the stream um
so I'll have to open the doors but he
knows I'm streaming so he will only drop
it off and then go it's not like here he
wants to spend more time with me
anyway uh no it's not pink I mean
I I may own other suitcases that are
pink but this this one isn't otherwise
he would not have borrowed it if it was
uh Pink he would not borrow it you can
count on
that where's this uh plus
quest uh in the
dungeon okay I'll do the to start off to
kick it off we'll do the dungeon uh the
the quest The Last Quest the last ah no
mut oh my God you don't even want to
hear their ramblings trust
me also I didn't have time to have a
proper snack so I have a snack like a
sandwich self-made
sandwich that I have taken three bites
off but uh I'll be eating it in the in
the cut scenes
[Laughter]
lost yeah I didn't even have time for
that what do you reckon we should
do respectable snack a chicken sandwich
no
salami salami kind of
sandwich how was she with conver in
the we're going to skip all this too of
course it's just side quest
stuff I'm also too big am I not
make myself smaller oh by the way do you
guys want to try should I raise the bid
rate a bit I
mean I feel so bad about all the bid
rate loss
so that's one setting I can actually do
Midstream you guys can tell me if it
makes the stream worse or better uh
output So currently I have 7,500 what do
you think I could go up to 10,000 do you
think I could do that more is better
right 10
10,000 let's I don't know what the max
is try 9k
Okay Okay
apply warning recordings cannot be
paused if the recording the same I don't
know what that means I don't think it's
applicable we'll see if it gets better
during the
fight my internet should be able to
handle it search lost plume search
Advent search silence so what are these
places they're not here are
they uh oops yeah oh like okay one's
[Music]
here I don't know which one
arked I don't
know
uh probably the the The Not So Fancy one
I don't know I know that like uh there's
something something new in
OBS oh we're going so
far but you can stream with some codec
some special codec I don't understand
these
things let's go to that place over
there Choo
boo oh you more worried about your
download oh I don't think it will be
much
different can I not go from
here do I have to go around where are
we ah ah no okay I could have gone
[Music]
here
well M okay
return switch to
av1 uh that is something I might
eventually look
into when I have the brain capacity for
it damn it the whole village is turned
oh yeah oh this
place
oh oh these people are so [\h__\h] oh
man why do I can I not just walk past
them why do I have to kill them just
ignore ignore
them let's not kill them maybe maybe
after I saved the world all these sastic
people go back to
normal oh that was wasted get
him this one I'm going to save the world
for those who are still
alive if you got slaughtered by me
[Music]
then too bad
oh was that a CH it sounded like a baby
crying it would be funny if they
actually use baby noises for
chle wait it's so
far
ah it's it's pretty sad to see this like
difference ah I want the chest that's
the only reason I'm going to kill you
now
kind of sad cuz we saw how it was
before I mean even
then they were not
friendly
enough uh CH was stuck can I open it
please no do I have to kill the too ball
uh too is going at it get
him go
to
sorry
oh choco chicken nuggets choco nuggets
choco
nuggets yeah sounds good doesn't
it chicken nuggets
let's
go yeah Shiva oh all right yeah we got
Shiva
yesterday
so the plan
was to master Giga flare ooh the one
left wait the one the last one that
we're getting will be the the what was
this element what is what's oldin
element bad
weather 6,000 I can't master that
um Darkness
oh uh what if I reset
impulse can I reset anything else
that I'm not going to be
using one ah um oh that looks fancy this
one though getting rid of rook's Gambit
but that's just 120
points could get rid of scarlet Cy
clone but even then we're not there even
then
uh well okay we're saving up for that
let's see if we'll get there
today
um so which one do we want for
now we got a cold snap slide
effortlessly across the ground
oh attacking while sliding can
temporarily freeze enemies
okay uh dies default moves were super
good oh okay Master cold
snap it's really good cold snap oh this
one no I don't have the money for that
if I want to save up for saving gigal
flare wait a moment um
Mesmerize launch multiple shards of ice
that upon striking light their enemies
draw them forward
Clive unleash a river of icicles that
greatly knocks back any enemy it strikes
okay but it's like pretty much a
straight line
but seems like it's CAU the one standing
more on the side
too oh no it has the ribm ribm
circles Aly this one summon a winter
storm that freezes enemies in place
within a radius before dealing massive
ice damage and knocking them
back
[Music]
yeah I mean looks pretty
powerful oh this one I like
too summon a colossal Ice Crystal that
deals continuous damage to all enemies
that become trapped inside of
it that seems pretty
good H diamond dust also removes a big
chunk of the this one okay
so
so what we
get well now I got rid of that and all I
got left is Wicked
Wheel for
now
um let's say I take
Shiva then I can't use Giga flare for a
while
what 500
what
uh I like this mesmerized
move um but one of them is going to be
diamond
dust
yeah switch Shiva with Phoenix refund
the fire attack Master ignition to use
with
Shiva learn diamond
dust but then I have no Phoenix shift I
feel like I I guess cold snap is almost
like a shift but I feel like you can
cover more distance with Phoenix shift
from the looks of
it oh the Super Chat was €500 oh who
sent that which crazy person did that
t wow don don o from
Germany is good land hopefully I'll read
it properly soon but thank you for now
insane first Super Chat dun is more of a
Dodge roll cold
snub I I I would prefer to keep Phoenix
shift in my opinion if it's between the
these
two it does freeze enemies nearby when
you use it h okay well you know what
while we're still not in important
battles we'll test it out and I'll just
go with this for now and we we'll see
we'll see how it goes we'll see how it
goes so we test it on the bumb time to
fight be safe get
up
uh wait how
oh I think did it get Frozen cuz there's
a like Crystal oh I have Frozen for like
a
second look at this
oh and
this yeah that was from a distance too
right o
[Music]
all yours tole not a
all not all they're weak to eyes well
didn't we say there's no Elemental
effects in this game like
no no stuff like that I would I would
imagine that it's effective
but it doesn't matter we can fight fire
with fire we can fight water with
water we can fight ice against
fire what do you have
here get
[Music]
him wee
how can you not go we when you have this
attack
oo I haven't used that attack in a while
too but it's pretty good left
left so seems like we're
pretty like good in progress and we'll
might be able to finish in under six
hours who knows no pressure
but I'll need to deal with these ones
first
oh
wa I made
mistake oh what is
that forgive me what how much damage
does that do
oh
what I I dodged like the beginning so I
thought I would be fine but I wasn't
does this did it take in all my
changes seems like it but uh Direction
wise uh oh
dear we're so far i' rather start from
here
first step of the day really early on no
we
good we're fine ready girl fly
Ambrosia do brus although yeah that
Quest it has it's sending me to three
different battles then I
guess need more upgrade no it's
okay
no don't go off no don't go off you Cho
just run past them we already killed
them before I don't know why they're
alive
again is this did it reset the chest too
does it uh act as if I haven't opened
[Applause]
it ah it's
[Music]
open
2,000 point you know what I mean while
we're waiting I guess F flare we could
invest to 2002
[Music]
something what was this again oh I could
strength from Wicked Wheel for
[Music]
now oh I'm I'm in combat h
you start from
scratch I feel like I would forget
something you want to upgrade diamond
dust yeah but I can't afford that either
now wasn't that
3,000 no 2,500 I can't afford it though
I need
[Music]
to how fast can you get these points
ability what's an easy way to get
ability points
[Music]
fast ref rings of light on baham baham
baham baham is this Bahamut no this
baham
oh oh that's also something I can reset
o okay okay okay now I can afford
diamond dust
upgrade
okay did I get
the ability points from fighting normal
fight yeah right toggle kill toggle kill
yeah how many do I get is the the blue
one
32 did I get 32 points for that one
fight it's pretty
low but yeah
understandable
understandable all right don't kill me
now can we kill a small one
first no mistakes oh they kind of belong
to together this one to
kill
wow
to he's doing something he's doing the
scary thing I think I no that's the
different thing but it's also SC scary
scary cuz I don't know
it okay I can focus on you
now kill oh okay fire and
Flame now to what is these oh
oh now oh it's like first inside
explosion and then outside oh stagger
oh all yours
to I don't have my gig Giga
Ultra oh okay
still woo hey how's the Big
R
kill
oh oh I wasn't too late looks the
same oh
staggering from one stagger to
another oh I don't have much to offer
but
oh
[Music]
oh that could be a lot of damage though
45k dodging back and forth man how to
find Echo that was pretty
fun that was pretty
fun
there this is it
right then you see improvement from the
bit R compared to yesterday
really really really really
[Music]
really you don't see it I'm not that
pixelated H hard to tell I guess but you
would think it should be a little bit
[Music]
better
when you use diamond dust the boss
immediately went to 50% stagger and you
could deadly
Embers you mean when I used it outside
of him being
staggered
ooh nice so nice move
to quickly get someone to
stagger it does more stagger damage than
HP damage oh yeah I did look at the HP
bar when I used it while he was
staggered and I was like that's not even
that much but where am I
going it's pretty
close just got to fly Ambrosia find the
right
[Music]
direction over
there
you making Choo sounds you're
chicken don't forget what you
are use cold snap when you as you dodge
when does it really work as a Dodge my
my my fingers are so used to dodging the
proper way though you deserve a rest I
don't know if I can do that in the last
part
okay guys GA G G I have something for
you diamond
dust oh wait they don't have stacker
bars all right but still you know big
AOE we like it we like
it this one
oh
what else do we have on the manual on
today's kfp Manu we have a special
of I will rip out your
organs so you know normally you have to
pay a lot more for that and if you want
to go to a hospital to have them rip out
your organs so you save a lot of money
if you let let me rip out your
organs trust
me what a deal I do it for free
basically cuz I will get this spherical
Echo one go after you let me rip out
your
organs so where is the oh all the way
over here is the last
one fast food fast R yeah yeah but you
know we have some some other services
that we don't talk about I have 40 DMs I
got Peppers to numb your
tongue let of us believe
these we now have to find Advent I don't
know why they are in the
game must have gotten
stuck come
on
glad to know my organs are worth so much
hey no your organs are worth more I
wouldn't I wouldn't really do this on
you
guys just on these
suckers you
know it only applies to certain people
unless you really want me to do it for
you
I like how the game doesn't Force you
like going down a certain path in this
Forest there's like you can don't get
surrounded you can
go can
fight you can like just walk through the
trees is
nice yeah maybe maybe not worth doing
that on this little bug oh but he was
protected ah
huh where's the protection dude let me
let me check after I kill this one if I
can kill him no okay where where where
where is it this
ball is a # voke
node are they all dead
now what oh I can do go
air like I just don't
care Oh
sick have you seen that before
huh
get air skills pretty sick pretty
tight look I got it oh yeah there it
is we got
it so what was just question that's all
of them a wine can uncross his even more
potions right right that was
it can carry even
more nice warmup
true good
[Music]
warmup when I first got gu I was
complaining I was using it in the air
really I
mean I mean I do think I was missing the
mobs and that was annoying but maybe it
was because I awfully thin these days
because they were
flying and I was
crying they were flying and I I I I was
just attacking on the
ground I I I kind of knew that would be
the wrong way but I still had hopes that
somehow I could force my way through
these J
ambers have you tried Molly's lemon
tarts lemon tarts M I love lemon
tarts I love I need to fix
this
okay lemon tart
is canva lost waas kiss not chef's kiss
what do you reckon we should even better
I say we should just tell the chef
CEO's
kiss how was
she no you're not lemon tart you're Lord
evok
good do do
Dole now make my inventory
bigger h
the
[Music]
T you save my bacon again it I ain't
like real bacon and I reckon I know it's
a metal stretchy is stretchy metal
oo oh nice
ASMR chicken
kiss chicken kiss kiss is uh little bit
uh Pokey but uh pretty good pretty good
yeah furnace for bacon expanded potion
set all let's
go maximized I minmaxed my inventory
let's
go what do you got to say 6 to8 wao so
originally it was four I think 4 to
eight and then High potions was like
three or two now we're at
five with two D's what does that
mean what are they
saying let's go this way I want to buy
potions what do you reckon we should
do potion
[Music]
d
I don't know what they're saying Double
Double D siiz
potions
what still a lot of quests are left yeah
but I'm not doing them the Stew's
awfully thin it's fine we we did the
important
Ones Still Alive are
you it's like you're disappointed
uh yeah it better I'll be you're robbing
me blind you know huh I'm robbing you
I'm paying
you I'm your only customer so far from
what I've
seen covered in Nicks and lumps the lot
of
them strength tonics for try Harding
[Music]
H Noah
wait where are we going oh
here okay now we are
starting the actual
thing I will eat my sandwich
Joshua better than I was but not nearly
as well as you should be your cuts and
burns may have healed but your body
still Bears the burden of every spell
cast and what would you have had me do
it was no ordinary foe we faced it was
the warden of Darkness yet still it was
not enough the king could have ended me
at any moment but instead chose to toy
with me like a cur does a mouse yeah you
underestimate yourself mhm oh it was
crystal clear only one man established
his dominance day and that man was
Barnabas I'm sorry brother that was Ill
spoken it's just I have never felt so
power I don't think any of them list
it's just the way they the microphone
and the
editing the Acoustics perhaps the prince
feels the same kind of
weird yeah cuz everybody just lifts
Bing
mustard
bully
what is this
place
oh don't
move so
cute
she's not
Ultima is that a cat here in my
sandwich here it's fresh from the
[Music]
well
[\h__\h]
[Music]
cute that's
pretty grandmother told me Spirits
sometimes get lost and that the lanterns
guide them to their proper place
I set one on the river for her when she
passed
away
tangle did it
better the fiend works from the
Shadows was it you who guided my hand
then
Ultima no not
you this is my doing my fault my sin to
bear and for it I must
adone but your hurts are healing
nicely it was my puses that saw you well
you make them and sell them or try to
earns me enough for bread most days
forgive me I have nothing to I know but
I couldn't just leave you lying
there what a good girl who raised her
she needs an
award
you're going
then of
course I'm
Healed thanks to you and your
puses will you promise to come back and
visit
no
sweet
was that a yes or a no
HH well
Phoenix it would seem that I owe you my
wings you're
welcome
perhaps he can find an
answer you will be returning to wud soon
I gather I see no reason to wait then
neither do I I can think of a few but I
doubt they'll stop you you will take
your medicine of course lady did TI H
set on leaving already are
you how long will it take us to get back
to
Ash don't know about the same amount of
time it took us to get here maybe less
if your uncle can find someone
trustworthy to patch up the Enterprise
all depends on where we're putting into
P mind yes it's not as if we can put a
Shore wherever we choose we have to
assume that the whole of Ash is hostile
and that will be attacked on
site then we must find a place they want
you to look pop
idea who might know of one the professor
I'll go and tell you come
in while you're plotting our course I'll
be in the shelves with your laws men I
wish to pick his brains about Ultima
then I'll talk to Karen about supplies
for the journey they may not be easy to
come by an
ash
ow your brother's body won't take much
more of this
recklessness you know that don't don't
you I
do it's
okay just five more
[Music]
hours oh like
six I still say it were a compliment
sorry to intrude Clive I was wondering
when you'd arrive please tell me you
come to take our young Prodigy here off
my
hands she sounds annoyed I'm not here
for Mid I need information on ash sorry
you have to handle why not ask Molly if
you can look in one of her
ovens Molly's oven yeah let's check out
Molly as soon as the Enterprise is ready
we'll be setting out for Drake's spine
and we're going to need a safe place to
land preferably one that won't see a
ship blown to [\h__\h] and splinters if it
were that easy do you think we lud would
have resisted Invasion for so long very
little is known of Ash and the
information we do have is spotty and
outdated we have the good King Barnabas
to thank for that why W's borders have
been close to Outsiders since the day he
seized the throne if there is anywhere
safe to land you won't find it on my map
thank God tell us what we will find I'm
sure you know better than we do but no
splinters well that mean no splinters
all right all right if it will get you
out of my
hair but interrupt me and it's
over I would
never on no damaging her
ships okay so like a safe way the one
they call the last
king understand him and you will
understand the kingdom of why is he so
powerful
Barnabas was only a boy when he arrived
from Beyond the southern
seas and barely a man before he United
the Ragged tribes of Ash and having
Unleashed them upon the formidable vder
Mark he set his throne upon the ancient
Kingdom's ruins the victory sent shock
waves around valesa Tales of Odin's
might spreading through every Court
parlor and drinking hole in the realm
note that this was in the year
843 and that the King still sits upon
his throne some 40 years
later quite Untouched by time Dam lud's
recent inaction left many wondering if
Odin had lost his appetite for war and
yet here we are the inar was committed
to the fry a bold declaration of
intent orc swarm around pretty
old haunt canvas
streets though how precisely the Havoc
they wreak serves
wude remains
unclear
regardless if the order to attack truly
came from King
Barnabas then one thing is
certain wude has achieved The
Impossible and made bedfellows of Beast
men and The Ether adult alike
all of which is a roundabout way of
saying that you will be in unknown
territory when you set foot on
ash much of the continent has already
been lost to the blight and what few
ports remain will be fiercely guarded
and that is to say not of its natural
defenses offshore currents will cast an
IL equipped ship out to sea one moment
and dash it against the Rocks the next
but then the Enterprise is anything but
but IL equipped and mid has made land
there before now if only there were
someone within intimate knowledge of the
Shadow Coast and where a daring
gentleman might put a
Shore
mhm you see Clive you had the answer all
along do you think you can get us back
to that beach mid picked you up from it
didn't I not that it easy the currents
were what was the answer but then if it
wasn't hard it wouldn't be worth doing
would it going back to where I came from
thank you lady viven if a few morals of
common knowledge and a sprinkling of
tavent talk are worthy of your thanks
okay I wonder what genuine intelligence
might earn me probably more
visits mid I need everyone in the ale
hall now I'll fetch Joshua from the
shelves I I captain
yeah going back to where I came from as
in last time after having some fun on
the
beach
wo how people hoping they'll eat cake by
the
ocean what's this visit the shelves oh
the shelves will be so happy to see me
they'll be even happier if I fill them
with books
M that's the good stuff for
shelves oh look at these look at these
happy shelves M about that one at the
top oh oh it's feeling like so
unfulfilled if only somebody could fill
it with a book if
only I have no
reason C you must listen to this lman
tell him empty shelf when we spoke
before on
the well insired me to delve deeper into
the subject and what I discovered
appears to agree with the findings of
his grace MH you will recall that my
quest to uncover ultima's Origins began
with the mural at Phoenix gate but while
I've always known it to be important its
Secrets have here to for eluded me now
however I believe I know where to find
the more complete example one that will
reveal all we seek Master Clive have you
ever in your traveles chanced to hear of
the circle of malas I would think not if
few have but there was once a time when
the faith flourished the oldest known
religion in the Twins and though its
popularity eventually waned on storm
hints of its Dogma remain embedded in
more modern the crystalline Orthodox
wait you said it wed on
storm what a US religious monuments are
often torn down or repurposed when new
faiths rise to prominence
but if no new Faith arose then perhaps
the ancient temples might still stand
and you see now why I must accompany you
to
wude it would appear the past still has
much to teach us though in this case it
would not have been possible without the
musings of
moss to think that you carried a copy of
my old mentor's Chronicles all along I
am relieved to discover it in good
hands I shall guard it with my
life Joshua if you're finished here join
me in the ale Hall I need to speak to
everyone before we leave let's get real
drunk my
brother let's get so
drunk that we just pass out I can ride
the and just just hope it goes away by
the time we wake up just hope it all
goes away five DMS we're up to 5 DMS we
should check it
okay my
apologies by now you've all heard where
we're going and why so I won't bother
you with the boring details only the
important ones if we attempt to approach
Stone here by sea there's a good chance
we'll be cited and full prey to the
capital's
artillery so instead we'll disembark on
the Southwest coast and make for Drake's
spine on foot oh I say we but it's
highly likely the entirety of Ash is
under the rule of Ultima a large party
would only attract unwanted attention
mhm as well as slow our March and
require supplies which may be difficult
to obtain so we split
again only Joshua and I will be going
Jilly Willy and a scout
preferably a good one gav do you know of
any you bet your ass I do might still
borrow some of Lady Vivian's Maps though
just in case like once you've dropped us
off at the shadow Coast you need to
retreat into neutral Waters fly Merchant
colors and stay
inconspicuous if you sense any danger at
all you leave us behind and return to
storm inconspicuous is my middle name
but like Ellen I leaving anyone behind
the ship ain't going nowhere till your
scurvy mugs are smiling on Deck I
thought so the Enterprise will appear a
tempting Target for royalists and
Pirates alike yeah I took her powers
does she have like nothing left don't
worry I'll keep the ship and when I took
the ones from others home after all I
had to kill them twice cuz they still
had power left very
well if there are no
questions I'll see you all of the docks
right I would think she still has a
little let me know when you're leaving I
want a word before you go a of course
now let's talk now don't go away I'm
leaving right
away
okay I think in terms of like
armor oh like pretty much as good as we
can get because there was one more thing
I was able to craft but I I couldn't I
wasn't able to craft it because I was
missing some some I think magic Ash
actually so there's something wrong I
did all I
could
honestly c a man with his friend F
Well let you know that I'll keep things
in order while you're off saving the
world thanks man I'll hold you to
that
sweet oh and that brings us onto the
world
map which is so pretty
man really those Game of Thrones Vibes
are strong reminds me of that video I
watched I think I told you of like
somebody
recreating uh the Zelda map but probably
also somebody recreated The Game of
Thrones map
and like threedimensional
craft so cool looks so [\h__\h] dope
doing all the different levels of
heights and filling the water with
resin and stuff like
that handcrafted yeah yeah topographical
topographical maps from movies and games
I love that [\h__\h] it's
insane
[Music]
hey dogy wogie always with
me reckon it'll be a long walk to the
capital if we follow the cliffs I'll
Scout ahead see if I can't find us an
inland
route would be easier to 3D print yeah
but Clive that's too
easy there's something I've been meaning
to
ask n you took her
icon didn't you and her
virginity yes I
did she
understood
huh oh she
understood understood that you decided
to save the world all on your own and
that you die without her
power how dare you make her
[Music]
choose you knew damn well she'd never
refuse
you but I will
you can't keep pushing us away Clive The
World Is Ours to save not
yours yeah but your powers are better to
be used by me than by yourself so far
you know I used my
gift because I thought it was the right
thing to
do also just because I took your power
does exactly because of that it still
means you're involved in saving the
world like we're saving it together
because you are part of me at that point
no is that not not
enough oh I do think like he should stay
separate though the Phoenix he's been
pretty useful cuz we need to G die he
has to stay separate so that we can G
die and you truly believe this will save
you will save us
all I
do
[Music]
then oh so he can stop turning into
stone would he
stop just don't
forget you're not
alone think I found us a
trail uh did I miss
something
it's guys love between two
guys only that Joshua
didn't yeah he didn't miss a punch is
that what you're saying I don't get
[Music]
it it's Bros love between two
Bros is that bad
I miss scrubs then watch scrubs you
can't miss scrubs just watch it when you
miss it to visit ush we're in Wuda
territory now don't expect a warm
welcome oh I don't know Clive that
castle over there looks inviting enough
shall we s its inhabitants
Hospitality good idea let's go
Yum Yum
Yum nice sad music cancels out my chocob
music remember what I said wel that it
cancels it sometimes chocoo music is
like not suitable for the
situation this place is As Dead As
Greg's
ghost o are you sure it's dead I see
people over
there let's fight them I guess we need
the EXP smelled something I see only
Orcs And A casik here let's hope the
villagers made it out in time oh there's
a big orc there big
one oh but wait he's he's weak
to those Hits From The Diamond D uh are
they depending on how upgraded it is the
more upgraded the more hits over here
now it was twice cuz I upgraded it once
this one
uhhuh over here enough the new
one well I tore him a new one yeah is
that what he said there's no way he said
that
right it sounded like oh you tore him a
new
one I tore him a new new hole yeah yeah
yeah it's kind of brutal yeah but that's
that's what you do you do what you got
to
do
did he say that I know I know what that
means but did he say it I feel like it's
a fitting
but surprising to hear
attack go
to now
to
ah oh that's a new one more like
that the Coke Zero No Coke Zero has
nothing to do with
this don't want to miss any
items nothing nothing I I I wish there
was like a ooh like an item radar kind
of thing that you could turn on maybe
something that you don't have from the
beginning of the game but later
on like a treasure
radar
[Applause]
go cuz they blend in so much into the
scenery you
know well yeah I only I only have a cach
with me right now today because I
thought in preparation for the stream
and me still needing to do stuff after
the stream hoping that it gives me some
energy but I don't want to drink energy
drinks cuz that's like too much energy
and then I don't even drink the whole
can and you know
somehow somehow the Coca-Cola zero feels
healthier to me and you know not as
Overkill as a energy drink how much okay
actually that's that's a good question I
would like to
know comparing an energy drink to
drinking a Coca-Cola
zero
is is it
oh M account
namei
buy it's been a long
time doita where were
you where were
you I thought you don't watch Wawa
anymore happy to see you I see
see so what's heal
Here Am I Wrong in the assumption that
the energy drink would be more uh
unhealthy in the usual
room okay I really love the effect on
that this one yeah ca-a has no toine so
tne on its own is already like super
unhealthy
right
oh someone's protecting him oh man oh
stop
it can you
stop I don't know who it is but anyway I
just started
blasting
M we we n we
we did he say something else and I
missed
it
ooh ooh we we Taren is good actually
huh what
what was that my cat talky
walk what's wrong what wrong maybe she
just went to the toilet and wanted me to
know
[Music]
oh I missed them so much guys oh chest I
miss my C I mean Smoothie has been
honestly annoying these past two nights
cuz I jinxed it I said oh recently she's
she's letting me sleep through more
often than I jinxed it and these past
two nights she did not let me
sleep but besides that I'll really
missed their fluffiness but I'm not
going for that long it's not uh even two
weeks it's more
like one and a half I
think I think
yeah something like that it's cber all
over again I kept it short but now
because it's so short it's everything so
squeezed you know squeezed
tight into a short amount of
time that got a schedule a pom
[Music]
P cheaper I guess yeah I wanted to save
cost on um accommodation
to but they ended up being yeah
moderately
priced but I got some good air brain P
looks like I have space to dance
practice a little
bit
ooh looks like fun looks like a
party there the whole of Ash fallen into
ultima's
hands that's no peace delegation we
should send a warning to the others no
my uncle caffine is not necessarily
worse in terms of
health our Mark is Drake's spine and
there's a lot of Road between us and it
what about calories and sugar and and
press on to Stone here other
stuff I you never know it might not be
an EST slabber and
monsters but in my impression both are
bad but Clive energy drinks are worse
you must go on ahead without me what are
you doing this stronghold is as old as
Phoenix gate perhaps
older it may yet hide Altima's remaining
secrets and if we are to best him they
must be
Unearthed
oh sorry all right stay out of trouble I
feel relieved I always do
mostly I wish I would have had time to
go to the doctor before going to Japan
sure about this about leaving my brother
on his own after W of
course
mostly yeah those were some deep seated
neck
cracks Caffe nicotine and alcohol those
are PR essential nutrition of civilized
human hard to tell which way is up oh
ladin is this you not far from a village
called esta then we make our way there
resupply and wait for Joshua this this
your your sub
account is that a writer's diet Let's Go
Fly Ambrosia fly fl flop fly fl flop
cute Flappy
Bird this place rigs like a Marble's
[\h__\h] though I'm guessing it's not the
smell that will kill us
any Treasures oh there's a
turtle or should I say an
owl no no no nothing
really bloody
eyed oh 20 memberships what
happened e
safe making up for last
[Music]
time let's kill this lindworm look
funny hey nice
Dodge I can dodge
too get
him nice
try go
tole kick it off what's this Ang now
tole too slow oo oh what was that
ah quick switching through man oh wait
wait wait I forgot uh oh [\h__\h]
hell nice
try what was
that what was that again what did I just
do I'm losing it I don't understand this
game anymore I've played it for too long
by the way I did watch Callie's
um uh a stream like archive I checked it
yesterday right after my
own cuz I wanted to see her
reaction it was a bit different than
mine a little
bit
what what I now want to see is uh ena's
reaction she did mention something like
she wants to
uh continue her Final Fantasy Journey
soon right I think she even said that on
stream or on a tweet or something like
that I
think
H H how far is she she didn't get really
far
right she finished Pikmin now it's on
her next on her list
oh she will have a very different
reaction to
Bahamut
why why what reaction did I
have
oh because she played Final Fantasy or
so like like others and
oh
oh I was having fun or will she not have
fun this would be
easy what's that blue trifle isn't
trifle like
a dessert what was
that oh you can do ice stuff all yours
to ah [\h__\h] where am I going he's also
probably thinking the
same oh what generous
generous let's see W that did go down
50%
wa I I looked at
it ooh a
Parry over
here ooh another Parry when you're in
the that moring
mode
um I think it's quite easy to get Parry
cuz he was just attacking so
fast ah it doesn't load back in time for
the next
stagger wait but there it is just went
there on my
own go kill now go
the moring
mod oh my God I'm a genius Double D
speaking of am a genius I'm
genius oh my
my uh today is the release of ta
of there's a good
boy nice
try no I want to play
it
H they did put up another um like
warning it doesn't say you can't play
Until the End it says please hey another
one okay it says please just give a
warning the spoilers wa I came back hard
from that
Dodge with a what's going on what's
going
on did it say not stream it I thought it
was from what I
interpreted it looked like just put a
warning somewhere in the thumbnail or
too
slow was that another
Parry oh my God no that was a stagger St
right H I'm so
confused there's so
many things going on
full stream block wow okay well I wonder
how long they're doing
it what did they um let's try for Tales
of arise the main game I just ended up
asking at some point hey can I like it's
been a long time can I stream the end of
it but I
wonder um oh what was that 50% did they
announced it like officially that hey
you can
stream it now did they ever do
that this one I don't remember seeing a
message like that
publicly but they I guess they probably
did just didn't
see yeah they did say they would say
when it's okay later on for Beyond Dawn
I I see that too yeah so let's wait for
that I guess maybe until we play
it shall we wait for that you guys can
play ahead if you
[Music]
want
his reason to not be around might have
been just because the Yen was cheap
which such a funny uh reason time to
fight
that's fine not super chatting is fine
but better write normal chat messages so
I know that you're still around those
cost nothing well what of
you but how much breath stinking uh
don't look down
tole
yeah I suddenly so many Super Chat that
must
be that must be
estla the way he says
that let's go what's
behind
the free messages cost you
nothing what do you think
Clive nothing brain empty you were too
late toy
walkie damn it they're all
turned there's nothing can we're always
too
late so
lame we can't save
anybody let's get them all together cuz
they're all too far apart right and then
do a little diamond dust oh they're all
kind of somewhere else now what the hell
what happened what
happened go but the beginning was
good nice to
finished let's do another one oh I
missed
him yeah I love
ignition sometimes it goes wrong though
and that's kind of that's kind of funny
though when it goes
wrong H wait
what and huh another set of
memberships what he's feeling bad don't
feel
[Music]
bad here they
come and and come and
come
fire to
kill was that 50 it doesn't even show up
at the top of my
chat only see it in the middle of the
chat trying to distract me I can't be
distracted these fights are easy I don't
even have to dodge
really I mean I still do but don't have
to it's like I'm a merry go round get
him go yeah let's stay in the air oh
he's
dead go get distracted uh try me try me
I can close my
eyes can still
fight
attack I don't want to die enemies then
don't I don't want to
die just all these
complaints
I've done
nothing oh is that a big enemy behind me
oh take
this oh oh he was already at 50% now
he's now he's there oh my God it's
actually
insane it's actually
crazy
wow that
stagger bait is
[Music]
in oh hello chunky
boy nice
ax yeah fire damage ice
stagger m
no no not that move not that move no I
hate that
one I didn't got
to let me kill this one well done
too okay oh there's another one
no no oh you pissing me off
oh ah too late for deadly Embrace oh
well staggered anyway I even would Val
it I can get 50% down pretty
fast pretty fast as you can
see but let me throw this one in for
free a now
tole this
one
SI
no
no oh no yet MH yeah not this
time go
uh 15 yeah
15 oh it's hard to tell at this point
cuz fights are just much faster than
they used to
be so it's hard to keep track of like
are we at 0% stagger or 50% stagger see
now like it was 50% a moment ago and
we're already at 0% Stager like what the
[\h__\h] ha
T yeah yeah I I I understand that we got
stronger but I really really would have
wished that the balance would have been
better in the beginning of the game that
we wouldn't have been so much
weaker yeah it was such a slog it was so
long each fight was just such a damage
sponge
gav just unnecessary tell me there's
more of the
bastards the scaling is
wrong [\h__\h]
what right in front of
us [\h__\h]
intimidating have you come to watch
OD no for stone here
oh
good my master awaits you in the capital
UL though I cannot allow you to attend
him in your present
State what what state how you going to
stop us would be preferable why with
this see that's why I was calling him
the best weather
icon stuff like
that it's just bad
weather oh okay thank you what
[Music]
now holy [\h__\h] why does he have such
power ah come
[Music]
on
oh
[Music]
man he's backed by
God okay what did you do would he be
less powerful if he
wasn't he looks cool
though wait does this horse
have 6
feet that's pretty creepy if the vessel
would see the path opened it has but to
ask
E I shall see that my Master's prize is
made eight
presentable I see only
six
[\h__\h] maybe
seven but
six
must be a muscle car not quite uh
Clive would you mind telling me what the
[\h__\h] just
happened I don't [\h__\h] know good
question can the birds go
through
oh uh
no a you've got to be how are we
supposed to get through that
wait is the the top
open we seek an audience with the king I
did if his majesty wants me to come and
ask him oh
okay then that is exactly what I'll
do before you go practicing your
petition we don't even know where the
[\h__\h] went how about we cool our heads
and think this through eh
don't even know where the [\h__\h] I went
what so thinking time there's something
here we can
use no I think the top is closed
too
I know the quest marker is showing
something else but I want to check for
items you don't want us to go this way
then so where do you want us to go such
a
move well yeah he wanted us to go to him
but not in this state he said
right wait maybe there's something up
here oh God
no
item
item come on I shall be rewarded with
items there's no one home Clive nobody
find some to sit down at the map BR
inside let's
go in
what
in what was that uh what would that
be this thing I knew
song
music I don't need that I have I'm my
own juk
box oh could I have climbed up here oh
does it lead somewhere
else no okay no jump
jump okay
which side have I not checked
[Music]
out
H Solo solo capella yeah yeah not it's
not not a capella though the music is in
my
head I have a whole concert going on in
head including
choreography oh yeah potion
eh it was full but okay my HP were in
full so that's okay I'm guessing this is
something we want to look
at I thought we got them
all wait can't we just teleport out of
it did they not think it through I mean
the the the the
Odin what I also have full potions
know it has to do with this
house
oh hey wait is
it oh no who who
please
please please
no it's okay Miss we won't hurt you whoa
easy easy we're not turned all
right gap's future
wife
who pretty
lady she'll see him as her
rescuer it's automatic plus points he's
winning
my
thanks kind
Travelers
Eda forgive me for asking but what went
on
here
cute
H it all started when the skies changed
the elders said it was the
AR one by one people went mad Minds
taken by The
Ether till only that was
fast by then I was too far along to run
oh and then the knights came
and I didn't know what to do so it's not
gap's
child and this uh
okay
is the AR just a story something our
grandparents told us when we misbehave
oh about how the heavens would grow dark
before the land took her last
breath sounds very realistic right now
the end of the
world you said the others went mad but
where did they
go
they they all
left they left you behind th East to the
tower well was it because they
became the elders the hinger zombies the
blacksmith my
[Music]
husband you're thinking he did this of
course who else could it
be you were in Cana you saw what he did
to the people but then what about her
how come her nut hasn't
cracked sponsored by Mi maybe perhaps
could be protecting her from The Ether I
can't think of any other
explanation you mean it's a
bearer it won't matter what it is once
Ultimus magic takes
hold time's running
out
this
Tower that's where we'll find the
king hold I think I saw a spoiler in the
chat first I thought it was a joke but
now I think it might not be it's the
same as Phoenix
gate which means at the end of these
stairs should
be talking to
himself
weirdo or does he have airpods and he's
talking on the
phone yes sponsored by Mii
I was sponsored by m just the other
day there it is
again but there's like two people the
mural there just
lady oh oh wait it's like
uh show me again Tima and his fessel if
fre oh Aruda ramu mm Shiva oh yeah
they're all around yeah they're all at
the bottom Odin Middle is Shiva May
theost is
here oh
latan where is the Phoenix contractually
obligated latan Mansion
what why what's what's what's the L
behind that whoa whoa whoa whoa what's
going on Cut
content liia would be the water icon
yeah water is missing
huh
why why why why are they DLC there going
to be a
DLC oh oh oh
[Laughter]
exciting where' he
go that's
[Music]
me
yeah you get
it
by the founder
flounder my idea yesterday may be right
what did I say
yesterday oh that yeah that's so that's
what you
want isn't it Ultima
mhm was yeah that was I
mean why not notice ear that's how it's
going to be
then all of them got I'm not asking gav
I need you to stay with
Eda what I must do this alone if I don't
return you're to find Joshua and make
for the
Enterprise
understood
I and so there was only me and toy
Wy just don't you go dying on me sit's
name suits your miserable mug better
than
mine a whole s thing I haven't finished
with it yet so weird to
me good
boy yeah let's fight the boss alone haha
more or less three years of membership
thank
you yay
so
uh could
I I can't tell ped out you kidding me oh
there's another plus Quest oh I wonder
know what that is
but what they should make it impossible
to uh teleport
out
oh okay if Barnabas is controlling the
aashik then wherever he goes they'll
follow and so will I
oh 20 bloody
ads I just can't go any further but I'm
not locked in I
guess yeah fast travel for in case I
realize oh got to do something real
quick so
wait the edge of infinity
uh from where ah from there
okay so how do
I
huh where does it where does it end this
wall and
where here this path seems
good okay ooh
oo
interesting what are all these it looks
like Trident stuck in the
ground no tarantula no let's go have
mercy on my soul I don't want to fight
you oh be the item can't reach it from
here oh oh mountain climbing Cho
B I saw something there we
[Applause]
[Music]
go what what's from Final Fantasy 7 this
thing
wait first I go
this
way
oh there's something there I can feel it
but now's not the time
okay okay okay
okay this way then any I wonder what
that path
is lesser pul all right bring it
on get
down
here all right if you don't get down I
go up with
you
woo
go ask fros
[Music]
home
ah I hate sling
enemies little Annoying
[\h__\h] you know what I'll say to Ultima I
won't call him a little [\h__\h] I I will
call him an ultimate
[\h__\h] him
over here oh yeah why don't I grab
oh
[Music]
forgot
Ultra how are our points do wait I think
it's it just said the total right we're
at
1,400
H I don't think we're going to get to
max out Giga flare but I'm quite happy
without it too currently I think the
flow is pretty pretty dope right
now pretty
crazy even this one wants another
4,500 maybe the boss fights the upcoming
ones will give me lots of ability points
oh like this
one tiny
boss
nice
try get
him
[Music]
go oh did that count as a
Dodge
Kaboom
yeah oh yours
to even just one of those hits counted
as
50% it was already there the second hit
was part of the get stagger combos all
tole over
here
oh where did you go this
one better
all nice
try let's
go yeah maybe we don't need to upgrade
it anymore maybe we can can upgrade
something else it's already strong
enough and it's not really for
HP
uh anyway HP uh
taken not a damage attack to stagger
attack as we have learned die [\h__\h]
please thank
you I should accept the truth more oh
yeah uh I could do it more of
yeah cold snap upgraded
powerful but I got to force myself to
use it
like I tried a bit in this fight but
it's not very intuitive right
now so many
paths
oh Obelisk activated here
okay you want to know what random funny
thing about smovie I caught her today
licking a
window
why this is it
boy she was licking the window and when
I wanted to take a video she
stopped
I wonder if some if it was because it's
cold
or I don't
know she wants the taste of
outside oh there I didn't see
condensation
TB my dog does that well dogs are just
weird dogs do all kinds of weird
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay the
Ry isn't there a
vtuber company thing V
Ry so hard to
[Music]
say Opie mhm that's why I know
I've come for
you
Barnabas ble
man you're your cat licks to acant or
your
dog the acents aren't they up high I
guess you have like a stationary like a
like a small
one stay close
to a floor one maybe your cat your cat
aw she German engineering is
crazy wait that wasn't the Germans was
it where is this engineering
from all right the last
king the
tower it's
alive let's
go it's blue
D more Echoes of the Fallen they seem to
feed on
ether but there shouldn't be any
here
good stuff good stuff
baby ooh the
music are you hearing this go all yours
to stay up get
him really cool something new something
fresh
[Music]
German Engineers got a hold of an
Americanized blank check could be
louder
H I wouldn't
mind turning the effects even lower
the music a bit
louder just a
bit is
[Music]
good wait where are we
going
there bloody Fallen what why do all
their floors seem to have a mind of
their
own so togi was wrong we're going up wo
how far there we
go they have plans for me it seems ooh
what is
that now
to weak weak
enemies let's accept the Troth a little
bit
wow the truth so
powerful you guys should accept the
truth
too join
me on my Truth full
Journey ooh tgy
Wy wait wait okay okay okay you guys got
to take uh a screenshot of toy wagy in
that moment from the VOD cuz that looked
funny I think he did not have front
pawns
kill that was
funny over here all yours
tole get
him attack
no talk finished the German Channel I do
think um once I'm back from Japan I want
to set up a German AOE
collab with
Ellie if you guys would like
that if that makes you guys happy I feel
like you guys are just complaining and
asking for German Channel content
because it's funny to do
that cuzz most of you don't even
understand
German but you just do it
because you think it's
funny too
slow
oh
a kill kill
destroy destroy your
ass yeah yeah that's what I thought mhm
but I already used up all my fancy
things Yeah by I got to use diamond dust
it's kind of a waste but it's okay bam
and
Bam and the rest we just got a vibe oh
wait we got ignition back
yo
30k get
him okay you guys annoy me
so let's take care of
you if we
can if it is
allowed you little
[\h__\h] what is that exploding oh yeah too
slow
okay kind of pissing me off here not
good hold
kill let
try okay I'm not careful enough either
but kind of
annoying go
go go go go go
go was an interesting idea that got AED
after two streams counting
deut you mean my German Channel
yeah all yours
to if I get into your
vision if big if here it would be a good
reason to continue the German Channel
but
more
H what channel the what I have a German
language main channel the German channel
is main on that channel but it's a sub
Channel yeah you guys don't get it you
guys don't understand German most of you
so and the ones that do understand
German also understand English so I mean
the the reasoning of me wanting to do it
was also to
like oh wait my bro let me open the door
for him really quickly sorry I'll be
right back
Onan
[Music]
on
e
spe
oh oh wait microphone was
on
a
did you guys hear
something not audible
right I thought he'd just drop it off
and leave immediately but he wanted to
say hi to my Kito
Catos yeah he really loves my cats
too and I had to grab chunky wonky for
him like smoothie was easy but chunky
wonky was like hiding in a box I had to
drag her out of
it that took a moment couldn't hear
brori huh oh too
bad elevator time again
yes surprise please understand I love
you and I support all your projects your
German Channel allows me to hear you
speak your mother language honestly it's
hella attractive oh my God you're so
you're such a cute simp
though you're just Bas as
[\h__\h] time to
fight
to
kill
to defense
no over
here you know I I say I know some people
like on Twitch you can't even say it
right but I when I say s to you I say it
in the nicest way I I appreciate
it y always go so
crazy attack these things I had some
practice with these things it's like the
blue trifle that I met
outside oh wait 50%
oh
damn Paris foot days Paris for we're
going to
Paris ptty
buet wait 50% oh oh no 0% oh my God uh
sorry I noticed way too
late yeah still 32k okay I didn't even
try
now
to oh what do I hear I didn't finish my
talk what was I
saying that I wanted to
O M account name o o
it what you going to do M M M
M M
Mah I'm going to play more AOE I'm happy
you like
it all yours too now
too I thought you would just die now
than
M come
come uh I was saying uh I want to do it
cuz I thought I could make my German
audience bigger but that was always like
I didn't have much hope in it really
working
effectively unless I would do it really
regularly very often and I didn't want
to sacrifice too much time from my
normal streaming
time yeah you
know you want to see the ah yeah I do
want to use all the German Channel
assets
yeah I would like to use
them sometimes I'm really
um how to say tempted to use them what's
going on
here hey is that where I came
from no oh it's
confusing they want me to go on the
platform and then try to go out again
unless I do that it won't
move if I were
Barnabas where would I be the
top of course I could look down on the
world
exactly you can you should not stream
on I
guess I mean I wouldn't only stream
there people would still see my 1.5
million Subs
Channel you know got to have a good
mix
but yeah it's not abandoned completely I
just I have too much things going on I
can't think about
that goig would be cool
yeah but how long is goig because along
long RPG playr on my sub Channel
h
M
now mhm
mhm K mm who's alive
you 23 hours
H
aome get two uh three scam three
four over here
this one new enemies
approach
o
go it's time for
ignition all yours toal fire
M yeah AOE
go yeah yeah yeah could play Gothic on
oh yeah yeah yeah wait wasn't that like
kind of recently the announcement for
Gothic on switch and I was like oh oh oh
oh this is a chance maybe cuz I I think
I did request Gothic perms before but
like no reply right um that company just
doesn't reply by for switch I guess the
publisher is maybe different I don't
know so I can try
[Music]
again I've barely been using the potions
so far and they've been giving me plenty
pretty nice pretty
nice sounds like a solid chance to me
yeah I'm still waiting for some
publisher to help me out with the movies
like maybe put the movies on the
switch or just cuz that that was um
ooh what do you call it again uh lost
lost software what do you call it
again something
wear a abandon wear that game is for
Real abandon wear so sad bad oh hey I
wanted to snap at him though I expect
it'll fall like all the
rest you know what throw some Diamond
dusted
him use de is it too late to use okay no
you can use deadly embraced right after
even if
he oh wait oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh no I will not let you take a hit on
me at
all oh did you see that n got it that's
oh my I have I have this
left okay now we got to wait until it
loads back up what the
[\h__\h] this
one that has quite big reach round
try
stinky
butt
oh
[Music]
50 this
one oh oh it's jump rope he has a jump
rope
skill oh
no
oh
mhm after this I'll immediately throw a
diamond dust at him see how he likes
that I'm not
done there we
go and then we'll follow it up with a
deadly Embrace if it's not too late no
okay I just throw a few normal
hits and then he's there
again
wow woo strategy this is
wow I I fought every step through I used
my
brain M the order the order baby woohoo
woo
wo I like that I like it a
lot that was just our temporary setup
but I like the way my
skills harmonize with each
other can we climb up there
oh my neurons have been activated
Giga
brain please upgrade coold
snap can I I have
2,000 I can't you guys keep on saying
upgrade Cod Snap I've got 2,000 points
for so far from upgrading
it what does it do when I upgrade it can
I go further or is the the the freeze
longer oh another potion that I don't
don't use you know what what to do
boy all yours
tole tole
kill freeze is longer and longer range
stay down
both
really refund G didn't I oh did I not
already
refunded oh oh
no oh true I can refund it
I guess
oops H 8,000 points
now increases permafrost duration
okay could upgrade
this wait I can upgrade this
too
allow ah yeah that wait never
mind I don't want to upgrade it cuz I
don't need to do
that yeah no need to master
it what do I do with these 4,500 points
could get another upgrade here uh but Ah
that's also just the same yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay
M upgrade the
dash what which
Dash
um I could upgrade Scarlets but that's
also no that's also just the Mastery we
don't want we don't need
masteries you like the non Garuda
move oh this one that's fine
no could give it an upgrade that's not
many
points uh Mastery increases claw
[Music]
range
H shift distance
sure uh is there something
here
[Music]
no right the only thing I can upgrade is
the stop which I don't care about
taunt out frust don't
care and this one to let me use it
anyway we could invest we could continue
investing in Giga flare then cuz I don't
need these points for anything else
right
now you know
yeah we won't get there though I think
but if we need points for something else
we can take it out of G Giga flare again
let's see what happens
first yeah Giga flare and diamond dust
would be pretty
op yeah yeah yeah yeah I know I know
that's the that's the goal to master it
and assign it to another icon but it
needs a [\h__\h] ton of points that I don't
have even when I was like getting rid of
[Music]
others that's so unnecessary just go up
immediately the moment I step on top of
[Music]
this
windy
oh oh cut scene maybe we reach to
top you swap Phoenix of
baham you want to
master and I could monst
[Music]
ignition big ball
big round
ball nice crystals in the
middle what is this ball
doing oh come on then come on then come
on then come on come on
then ah I saw it coming but I was not
quite ready now
go
would you care stopping for a moment oh
in this case it doesn't go down
quite uh 50% that's okay we need to work
a bit harder for this
one
o
attack
all yours
[Music]
tole almost there almost there was
that nice try oh oh oh there's more oh
there's so many maybe I should stay
away
attack doggy be careful I don't want you
to get
hurt too slow oh he wants to slam me
no oh
oh there now is the time now is the time
the time of my
life and I never found this play
before oh yeah it's the
truth and I always
[Music]
you I'm done no I am in reach okay that
got me scared it looked like he wasn't
in Rage but he did get damage so no
worries
Papa get me some heal over here oh
no no worries the
kill how much time I
wonder no problem no
problem I needed that okay back to
normal
stagger kill
I have nothing fire and Flame I have
nothing left
go pretty low oopsie nice
try
hey
K what H
yeah oh yeah oh
now
to what's it doing let's try oh it's the
this
one let me
attack you can't get me
anyway oh sandwich
time
go
oh
[Music]
yeah it escaped my
grasp
[Music]
what this
one what you have something fancy going
on
it's like a Mozart Bowl but not as
tasty
oh hey let me press
R1 clunky clunky
boy you broke my B I played with that
ball why would you do
that
now
to before you hit me let me do these
quick things to you thank you
kill get him I needed that thanks
boy I can use a I'm allowed to use a few
potions now right too
slow get
him now
tole
sick
go okay trying to get myself to use cold
snap
more kill oh what's wrong with him get
him over
here St
lizard there's a go
attack it's pretty
op if you focus on using it no NOP no I
love how this stops time I love
it
what do you want what do you want H nice
try not
happening
kill w all right bring it on and
stagger hands some go yeah we're on fire
literally hey
I'm surprised that's not 30k at least
over
here aerial assault
Cannon
n now
to I need to rub my
nose
attack kill
oh
ow now to
go good nice
try this one
it's actually kind of crazy that it
doesn't have um a cool
down
kill too
slow now
to it's always too
late
[Music]
it's over oh
okay I wouldn't have minded it going a
bit
longer I was in the zone
man I was in the zone why would you kick
me out of my zone
oh we're almost level
40 Fallen
iron is the item we
get
nuts fun huh is that his sweat damn
sweaty
gamer or is Odin the sweaty
gamer that was pero for us is that just
a like a random
thing that might happen with cold
snap or is it the amount of cold snaps I
did Precision Dodge with ah Co she okay
oh you mean when I do the cold snap in
place of a Precision Dodge a normal do
so the so a Precision cold snap almost
there
okay
nice yeah
Shiva
yeah yeah that was definitely something
that I had to keep away from me for as
long as
possible you guys were already
so like oh this is like gamebreaking
about
Bahamut the Giga flare
one but this one I like the most out of
the newer ones I can feel
him potion used
really could have given me a different
one
H well let's
go Odin is the game breaking
one Odin many arms for horse and
Men
all the arms you can possibly
desire what yeah I was going to ask
what's that blue stuff on the
ground wake up in three two
one soon
why for fun the blade must ever feed if
her edge is to remain
Keen
butcher what care you for these
worthless
creatures they are
nothing weak from the moment of their
conception ever longing for power not
theirs to command they turn unfailingly
upon themselves like sheep they roam in
filthy flocks eager to trample those few
gifted a fleece of
gold or that they might feel contentment
with their pitiful
existence Prejudice and persecution
Severance and strife every Earthly wrong
Springs from the malice in men's
Hearts malice born of the pain and
suffering that is free
will huh that was listening what did you
say your being from the very moment
repeat that from the beginning
birth that would trigger him you're
wrong you didn't listen to my
speech it is no
corruption it is who I
am every choice I make right or wrong
gives me reason to carry on and carry on
I
shall not as a puppet but as a man
which are
you
puppet there was a time I too thought
those the only
choices the close up nost ago God
granted man the gift of magic and with
that gift did he build great
civilizations yet over time man lost
sight of the gift's true meaning
stepping from the path of shared
prosperity to one of
avarice he abandoned his creator for
sword and Flame and through his folly
back in the
blight
yet there were those few who refused to
turn their eyes from the
heavens and they prayed to God that he
might lead them back to
righteousness and the Lord he did
answer before the worthy shall the gates
of paradise open oh he's insane and so
did I spread my arms to The Ether and
cast my soul upon its gentle
Waters I gave myself unto
him
okay
what Madness is
this my worth proven the Lord charged me
thus if your kind are to find
Salvation they must be made to
serve you see Paradise lies but a single
step away could we only take
it could we only leave our
transgressions behind for none save the
pure of heart and mind May set foot in
the new world I will save
us but it all begins and ends with you
you are the key
Mythos and with this humble offering
shall I prove my faith once
more so you forsook your kingdom you
forsook yourself to serve tell me how is
that
living
no what you seek to provide is not
salvation mhm it's anything but yeah
life is about always having a
choice take that away and we might as
well be you can't reason with villains
[Laughter]
really did I say something
funny
very
well come
then show us the strength of your
will okay it's not the strength of my
will that should worry
you but the weakness of yours
oh well
said he doesn't even use his full
power if you think your will the
stronger prove it by this day end you
shall know the
truth
kill ow ow
ow I Tire of
this
sick all yours
tole blessed with the might of a
God still use trying to use it
[Music]
um like Dodge but
my generally
my instincts still go for normal
Dodge did that get him did that get
them must I show
you this
one oh I think I got him
permanently right show me
more and
again get
him all yours
tole not good stuff so
far thanks boy
kill you will
obey oh
oh oh yeah yeah get out of there over
here nice try when will you
see this HP is still barely going down
man
I can't see [\h__\h] there's too much
effect over
here hey he can move while I do that he
can't move while I do
that others
can't I needed
that
now is it because he was
teleporting
what don't disappoint
me there we go to
kill all yours some
Goose
GH
not quite this
one too
slow
here are you guys getting dizzy
yet I been you good look good luck and
have fun at work did he move this time
no this time I don't think he did
oh not yet God chose you to serve as his
vessel and you cling to this foolish
notion of Hope when there is
none hope is a feeling [\h__\h] that we all
feel differently
individually I see you have
none holy
[\h__\h] well he decided to fully Morp now
yeah I was going to say desperate you
scared of me now
huh me and my frost
bite
she what I'm moring too right yeah yeah
we're already in this part of the fight
really I wanted to do some more normal
fighting
finally we can
[Music]
begin that was short
that was
short that look how little we got him
down oh ah we bringing him back he's off
of his
horse
[Music]
almost
at least he's not oversized like baham
now Weir the oversized one if anything
oh are we are we actually going to go
back to normal for a little bit now you
must follow it talky wony oh free
yourself
methos you will not defeat me otherwise
we'll see okay
okay perhaps you still require what is
this what is this what is this oh oh
this
one nice
try this one I Tire of this
ah to
kill go to need some
healing
oh let me
attack
ooh maybe some real healing a little bit
a I wasted my my thing cuz like I get n
didn't get to attack at all
ah no ah okay I didn't realize we were
right at 50 but okay oh it brings us
down quite a bit nice must I show you
[Music]
kill let see get
him this one when will you see
okay let's start with
G oh he loads back up really fast
don't tole tole to me he really doesn't
give you much
[Music]
time where wait can you you even go I'm
I just keep on dodging through
it this
one
[Music]
ow come on wait what did I can you
cancel can you cancel your special
attacks if you press accept the truth
during
[Music]
it I thought it would like kind of queue
it
up
that attack is a wide opening
[Music]
buddy so
wide
go
[Music]
nice try oh my God just zoom out of
it not good oh
my okay let's focus
again over
here oh my
God all yours tole
come on [\h__\h] hell
mate seems like I missed the time
window but this attack is
back hey oh oh that's it I didn't think
that would bring us down to
zero right
pretty pretty epic but I got not much
else to offer
this oh cut scene
time I cannot
be
defeated you admitted defeat the moment
you turned your back on us is Odin
actually when you turned your back on
the truth Barnabas did he lose
confidence we are not as weak as your
God believes
oh wow what a move it does not face him
though no
talking oh oh he's he helped me but
wait you know what would be the saddest
thing ever if tle died eyes Dam
it stay safe
doy I'm not manifesting it no I would
you say that cuz it's just now I Fought
For a Moment instead of me dying they
let tole die
so he T I hope T's fine
[Music]
no don't well actually
me he can't die he's a magical dog
[Music]
dog
what are you waiting for men know
nothing of
strength what you
will wonder don't
what like does he really have this power
all on his
own or is this
really the power of collaborating
with
timal I'm pushing I'm pushing quietly
but I'm surely
pushing let's find your flame time
[Music]
oh never accept the truth
moment you
thereare oned
skin oh look like a move that he would
use could it be you have made a weapon
of your
weakness my apologies I don't know did
I yeah I used his
weapon you are not the fool I took you
for look at that but he can just regrow
it that's so it
ends cocky too cocky no what can't
perform
yeah I mean same but don't tell me you
are tired meos I know I I I I didn't
take my Med your stubborn Defiance has
stirred my long bealed heart filling it
with a joy that I have for Generations I
thought we didn't have this issue
anymore iconic
dysfunction the tantalizing kiss of self
indulging
a dream forever Out Of
Reach and now that it sweet ruined
coures through my veins I shall not be
quick to relinquish
it show me your work beos that I might
reel in
it
oh no don't don't pressure me like that
let's
try
does this help this diamond does help
with this yeah better than
nothing this I hate this kind of
stressful
situation m
oh I keep on uh wanting to deal uh go
but now is a good time to do something
like this yeah yeah yeah thank you thank
you for that
opening how much time do I have left
he's Gathering the darkness
[Music]
you will
oby oh get out of
there
[Music]
ah no no no no no no no no no no no no
I'm not making I'm not going to make it
what no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
no no no no
fa no no I I'm sorry no I almost had it
did I no no no no
no at the end I I really tried to ah I
was so close okay we can do it I got
really close I I can't okay now I know
how much time we
have
[Music]
there the one of you
eh oh maybe
oh bring it all on bring it all
on
oh
Mommy record time
baby too
slow so me
[Music]
more your will hinders
you yeah
okay tired of this nice
try you will
obey fool too
slow nice
try U I'm trying to find something to
use
it's okay it's easy now
[Music]
you there it is there it is didn't even
have to use diamond dust there no ah it
continues it moves over okay okay okay
all disappoint is he
like no more who quiting what what what
what is
that
are you okay we need
help oh my constant
congregation salvation is
come rejoice as our souls are granted
peace
unending how do you know this day will
come what proof have you why oh he stays
in the same place for a long time with
these attacks existence is Pro of the
Lord's Grand
Design no no I'll never never serve your
God I will
not
ooh is it safe to stand by him
here I'm not safe here
oh wait if he's not on the ground is
that going to
miss
uh well he staggered
[Applause]
anyway I think it did hit
you go go go go go go W go let's
go
yay
y let's try
oh maybe a potion would be good
now they probably not going to zero HP
again anyway we're probably going to
have a big fight again soon just the
question is when are they going to start
that
oh
W
ow oh W
woo thanks for letting me hit you in the
[Music]
back we got this we got
this Barnabas snow match for
me the magic the power of friendship
this power will
always
Wen my
heart it
sorce as the day I won
as what do I
do what do I do uh feel like we had
something similar before many have
sought my Crown
methos but none could rest it my
head
look can I hit his
sword come have you the strength have
you the will I don't know man it's kind
of hard to get you from
here I think I was scripted
okay you good
[Music]
I am
yours claim me as your priz I'm not I'm
not really I don't I don't go that way
you know I I like people like Jill
sorry no
homo oh my God he's insane
[Music]
no more SP where is he he
teleported HH where's he's gone he's
gone he's just gone [\h__\h] my mid
teleportation what are the
chances not
[Music]
disappoint oh
50% but I don't know I never used Del
Embrace on him I I don't know if I'm
always too late or if it just doesn't
work on him I might be too late always
but nice
try oh oh oh I never I never went in
there before [\h__\h] that was by
[Music]
accident oh [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
oh come
on oh no didn't need to use that whoops
oh on we're probably going oversized
again soon maybe right after
this
oh oh no are we actually going for
zero maybe big face after I get him to
zero normally they don't do it like that
oh he's a Beyblade I want to be Beyblade
too
to ah not like
that come
down too
[Music]
[Applause]
slow nice
try
[Music]
is is he there yeah this time he's
there okay almost got
him ah why
I I
[Applause]
[Music]
slip
oh now you
staggered normal
hits SC
Bard uh wait ah [\h__\h] I'm so
stupid come
on I was hoping that that would be like
an epic
finish no we're letting him beblade
again who let him beblade again who let
him take the
Beyblades prepare your S I said he's not
allowed to use the Beyblades
anymore should have taken them them
away
well the day is that an
end is he we both know the truth he's
not dying is I who stand
Victorious my will that prevailed we got
to fight as big ones at least once your
will
no it was
his
rosfield
[Music]
who wait are we really doing this
without moring
fight
[Music]
really
really yeah I guess that little part was
it normally they have like 50% or
so icon find
I I did say I want fight longer in
normal form but that I mean I expected
only a little bit longer
okay perhaps there is strength in
will would that I had not relinquished
my own a don't make me feel bad
now
you relinquished
nothing what was it if not will that
made you strive for a new world strive
to win your Master's approval thank you
simply the fight wasn't perfect on my
side but at least um you were shown a
fantasy and you chose to believe
it but you were wrong the counting down
there is no world was fast but the one
we live in I did
well and that
world that world is worth
saving even if it means killing a
God is he dead for
real also I don't know if I want to use
any of his powers I like what I got now
words from one but you guys said he's
strong served the Lord so
well this is
[Music]
pointless missing out but I almost
forgot
what that I promised that I would make
make you present presentable by you
giving me your last power that I'm
missing
right cuz only then I have fulfilled my
true
form we shall fulfill our
Destinies just as the Lord's mother
crystals have fulfilled
theirs come Clive
rosfield take which is rightfully
yours become one with
God
[Music]
no oh we still got
it powerful as [\h__\h] but can't escape the
grass grasp on your leg from a dying
dude
man oh he's gray now that's long
lost
salvation good for you I'm coming
home
mother
[Music]
H Dead Man's grip is the real
thing
really
mother I almost killed a man tell me how
does it
feel Show
Yourself face me but first replenish my
potion how does it feel to consume your
rival's strength to Gorge yourself on
their being to Edge step by trembling
step ever closer to the Divine how does
it feel with or without a will you are
still but a vessel our vessel a to is
here
behold how your body shudders in
anticipation of its fate
oh it's not yours yet
mhm
no come then oh wayward child we shall
await you upon the back of the first
worm what there All Shall end and begin
again the first worm
the first fight that we
had warm
CH yeah the first
Crystal worm was another name for Dragon
right yeah okay then then
okay
[Applause]
understand
that won't help Clive cliy
wifey not
husband
oh oh I like how that's falling
apart jokes on Ultima I just don't
understand what you want from me that's
what you get for speaking in Chio
language
meanwhile
run
a uncle
dny oh my
God pleas
stay
safe why the hell is my city with a c
don't ask me ask them yeah what the [\h__\h]
since when was oan ham want to hide when
there was a fight to be had since they
stripped my and banished me from the
battlefield now I'm stuck wiping the
back sides of this do while the city
Burns and my wife tails off the man half
my age and then you turn up the hell are
you doing here
anyway what
indeed the enemy numbers 200,000 or more
countings is simply not enough soldiers
gar in the capital to repel an army of
that s then one of the central keep held
by a contingent of soldiers and bearers
from the surrounding barest they are the
sole reason it still
stands and all it took was an Army on
their doorstep to bring them
together the prospect of death does put
things into perspective perhaps a
retrospective perhaps it's what we've
lacked all
along oh
[\h__\h] don't let Uncle dad die
nice oh only two of them
left w h i need you to lend me some of
your best men practically all of them my
best men do it look like I any
more no I admit this might not be the
most convenient time my nephew's in
trouble and I may have already promised
him no help oh yeah right he said he'll
be back with an
army my soldiers have better things to
do then die for nothing it's not for
nothing near the same
mind I fights for the
opposite he fights for a world in which
they shouldn't have to live and die for
nothing and and he fights today to give
us all the chance of a better tomorrow
be that as it me a handful of I stand
against I love how they're having this
important
conversation and small
talk while this whole [\h__\h] is going
on then mayap they are the wrong men
oh I'll be damned well I'll be
damned our numbers are few but I shall
rally as many of my drons as I'm able
you arise the Lord strategist of the
state of the city's defenses yes your
Radiance good
boy and you would fight alongside us I
owe the Phoenix a
debt does this vouch for my nephews I
but I still have my doubts about you
which we can discuss later indeed you
said you had men garrisoned in the keep
Captain do you know how how many yet
remain allow me to confirm Commander
whatever their number randar will
motivated now in the courtyard for sure
quickly oh his boyfriend my
Lord Oh I thought he might have
died
nice you will find a girl
there ah the medicine girl
girl we are in the middle of War I owe
her my life and I always pay my debts I
mean I feel like you could pay it after
all this [\h__\h] is over you are to see
that she is provided for but okay Dion I
cannot leave but you
shall if I'm ever to be worthy of the
Forgiveness of our people then I must
earn it Alan to always pays their I must
earn it by my hand and my hand
alone know that I do not ask this
Bly and know that I will do
[Music]
it farewell
Terren
[Music]
a you've survived so far you'll survive
until the end
maybe let's hope they will not kill you
off
farewell no my princess don't say this
like you're going to
die it's going to be that
jble oh he wants to remove his boyfriend
from the battlefield too yeah I guess
yeah trying to keep him
safe oh and he wants to keep him safe
so
cute it's SK love between two guys for
real
now that is
accurate
oh what was uh Phoenix doing again why
did he not join us
Clive thank [\h__\h] investigating great wow
useful just looking at a museum for
seeing you Joshua and Barnabas
dead inside
me the king is
dead
so so there they're
all
they are but so is their killer he can't
hurt anyone
anymore you're
safe you're not alone you have Babble in
your
body
gav we need to
talk I'm s sorry cive you know I want
nothing more than to go with
you I
do but I'm glad you're heading back to
the Enterprise
nonetheless oh with her and not just for
Ed's sake okay our people need to know
what happened
here you can count on
me as can she I
hope thank you me
Lord
they already like they're
married or slow they need a horse do you
think that was
wise wiser than leaving a woman with
child alone in the
deadlands they'll be safer at the
Hideway for now at
least this land is overrun with a
casik the king himself was long turned
orbe it by choice all to serve
Ultima in his damnable quest to forge
the perfect vessel which is now
complete the chaos Barnabas rre upon
Nation after Nation how many were killed
for
this he didn't consider it killing or it
oh
a way to end their suffering The Vessel
doesn't need levia to be TR wanted to
save Mankind and ultimately use
that as he uses
us but why
us what a
we what a we we are dominants oh I got
it wrong that is Our
Fate
but that doesn't mean we have to accept
it which is why we
fight for the right to deny it is that
not
so it
is for our
sins Barnabas said something
else that the mother crystals were
Ultimus Ultimus are you certain
H we know that the mother crystals have
been leading the land of ether
[Music]
mhm and we also know that it's this
which hastens the spread of the blight
it seem like something he would do but
what I cannot fathom is what Ultima
stands to gain from that it's a general
FF
theme
cool what did you find in the stronghold
the truth about Altima's
prize for so long I believed it to be
you and you
alone yet it is not merely a fruit that
he desires but a fre and Phoenix both
that which we became in the Skies over
twins side M only when the twin flames
are joined shall his vessel be complete
so no more quite why he need needs a
vessel is another question
unless there is something he cannot
achieve without
one something his immaterial form
precludes something requiring an
unthinkable amount of ether and a body
resilient enough to channel it if I did
not know better
brother I would think that he meant to
cast a
spell a spell a thousand years in the
making a spell to end all spells mhm and
he cannot do it without
us all without the mother
crystals but if we destroy them
all we will stop not only the
blight but Timur as
well you think
so we stick to the plan then only this
this
time we face him
together well it's a long walk to Stone
here let's not keep Ultima
waiting so we're going to the last one
that's not
destroyed is that what Ultima told us to
go
too risky Ultima very
risky
cuz like the meet up right where I can
do something that messes up his plans
completely unless that's actually what
he wanted from
us the power of Darkness CLI has claimed
a portion of the icon audence Essence
ATT with or not blah blue blah
blah Odin's
feet what is that oh it also has like a
counter ah and then then it does
that transform we his weapon into od's
Legendary Blade Landing attack slowly
charges the blade readying it for
zantetsuken which is executed by holding
square zantetsuken pency is determined
by the blades charge at the time of
execution when Barnabas fell his magic
died with him the road to Stone here is
bar to us no
longer so then what would you say do
like how what do I
combine
maybe maybe I
could Master
ignition and put uh Odin in
here place
gudo
but so Master G and put old in there
which one's more
cheap oh the circle is
complete
can you don't like go let me see if I
can Master it oh it's just a
thousand why is it so quiet let's say I
do that I reset Wicked
Wheel
um what do you want
here what's your
man it's so yeah
really wied wheel is nicer than
GL Wicked Wheel wicked wicked
wheel no I wouldn't say
that
um Odin is a bit
complicated you need Rift slip and
judgment
cut course is bad if you new build wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
what did you
say Rift slip use to recover immediately
from any ability or
action
H wh why how why I'm looking at the
video but I
don't can I not just cancel my
attack you don't think I'll be able to
use it properly don't worry about it
okay and
W oh that looks sick okay I can replace
G with
that Legend SP and execute an extended
flourish of deadly slices and strokes
each hit landed FS theed skin gosh
okay and this was the counter the
general thingy which needs 5,000 to
upgrade let's say we don't use Goose
right we're only at
2,000 I could upgrade gungir I could
Master
it so let's
say so many choices let's say we put OD
in
there
and search forward to strike an enemy
can be executed multiple times in
sucession if previous hit lands what why
would it not land I feel like it would
always land that sounds pretty sick too
honestly I could upgrade
[Music]
that refund cold
snap what no I do try to use
it can you refund gig flare
uh I
guess have we given up on Giga flare
completely ah almost at 5,000 oh wait no
we don't need that
uh master master uh wait what what am I
trying to do what do I want to do 4,500
Diamond does upgrade what what do I want
to
do what do I want to do I have uh some
points judgement cut that was here right
um judgement
bolt do you mean judgment
Bolt
how much is it to master probably too
much yeah definitely too
much upgrade
Odin's basic
ability
uh which
one
what
uh recommend Garuda but with gig of
flare instead Odin and
Shiva Garuda but with Giga
flare Garuda but with G of
flare well it wouldn't I can't master
it dancing
steel dancing steel or Heaven's
cloud
this one is
like
another
s attack dancing steel okay it stops
[Music]
time okay and I can upgrade it which
significantly increases the number of
hits
okay then we're pretty broke again so
that might be looking good sorry no
master
Rings maybe if I did side quests I could
Master stuff but I have not enough
points so let's check
out dancing steel of the
gungir you can just play with Odin and
Bop with Odin you have to keep charging
his Co I will try I will see let's test
it out close by here maybe o two high
potions thank
you
um
uh wait a
second I can enter this room is there
like something that I can take with
me something they forgot to bring no
they should have put a treasure chest in
here for the people who think like me
who like oh I've only been in here in
the
cutscene might want to
enter
normally yeah it's just attacking to
charge it that's easier for me than um
the waiting for someone to attack me and
Dodge in the right moment to charge and
then when you get
hit it cancels it
completely for the wings how do I get
out of
here
let me
go what kind of place was this
again let me go
here just want to fight
[Music]
something
enemies come
on
faster got to test out
oldin or is everything
dead did I kill
everything
actually oh the game's actually telling
me to go here I thought it was like a
completely different
uh country or so oh okay okay anyway we
can go there after be
safe okay uh so just
hit just Spam these things or what yours
to wait it's
a what do I do what's arm of Darkness
again oh what's going on I don't know
what I'm doing it's just endless it's
endless it's
endless
I don't
[Applause]
know hold
square what do I do with this free free
counter what press
Circle and then hold
square
oh get him oh
okay
oh wait you don't have to do anything
I'm like just not I'm not doing
anything I'm not doing
anything it's just
happening it's good because I'm falling
asleep let me drink more more
Coca-Cola press o to change your sword
to oin sword then you hold square to use
your D dead skin we need to upgrade it
to level five to kill the entire
screen it looks
op Auto attack range Auto attack
Mele
oh by the way cuz we were talking
about it doesn't even go down cuz we
were talking about Final Fantasy music
right makes me think
um uh what am I I I don't know what's
going on am I doing this
right I just remember that I went to
Final
Fantasy car monstered before
right oh I keep on going
huh long time ago it was in a in a
church and the only game I had played at
the point was Final Fantasy
wait
but it was still nice I still enjoyed
it h I think I didn't recognize any
songs okay now we can go
here I don't remember anything it's been
so long I wish I remembered something
was quite quite nice you know just
generally good music good
Orchestra I think I only went because a
friend of mine went and
I don't know maybe I even got free
tickets I don't even remember
that I wish there was a a tailes off
Orchestra here like Final Fantasy is
like a bigger franchise so they get to
go all over the world but I wish tailes
off would be more recognized worldwide
that they could do such things you
[Music]
know yeah so as an ambassador as an
ambassador I must work hard to spread
the
[Music]
love hope there will be another new
concert oh yeah near concert is
interesting to Square Enix just does a
lot of that kind of things huh generally
Square Enix games they have lots of you
are
righta outside of
Japan
[Music]
they do get a lot of stuff inside of
Japan sorry dude I'll come back when I'm
done with the
mainest oh hi freaky ghost
B run like the
wind
I think they'll all understand my
priorities
wow who the [\h__\h] built this don't tell
me these bricks the only way to the
capital is through that gate just as you
surmise that's a strong Castle there's
an army down there Joshua
yes but I don't see any
dominance the tales of a rice Cafe I
looked at what they have and from what
I've seen good girl didn't look so
interesting to
me he was it even a cafe I know I
thought they just had some
merch it from what I saw it didn't look
too interesting so
the Adelia one looked a bit more
interesting to
me no the one I tweeted about was the
atalia
one yeah I think it was a popup
store the the tales off one was a pop-up
store and the AIA one is a popup cafe or
Cafe
collaboration oh and pop popup store
just has some merch and I don't know I
don't I already have Oh I thought that
was a treasure
chest I don't need that oh there's a
treasure
chest but I need to end the battle oh
wait that's also not a real
one
really God damn
it
whole live English
Cafe even though we're like mainly
viewers and our biggest audience I think
is na we keep on getting cafes like in
in Sea and so on right which is cool too
but like where where are the na cafes
right you might be thinking that well
hopefully straight home now hopefully
the sooner or lat later will get
something on the na side not that I
could go there and check it out but you
know for you
guys actually I might fight
[Music]
there not an unturned soldier in sight
then we end there when I'm not when I
don't have the arm of Darkness activated
I don't need to keep on
pressing
uh
square right oh my God this is like
how endless
endless okay and this one I just press
now as long as I can all yours oh it's
over oh oh what is
this oh wait I don't have uh ah I
by oh yeah oh that was nice cuz there's
so many of them oh every damn s
you go don't get
interrupted can't seel
up I think if that were to happen it
would only happen in an Asian country or
so cuz they're more open
to a [\h__\h] my strength is your kill so
like anime related stuff you
know okay right now I feel like I would
be faster if I just switched to my usual
system
not
good ah there it is I was waiting for
that
not I'm still a bit confused but yeah oh
wait they're still
there it
[Music]
that one needs to charge a while
huh all yours
tole do
it this
one that's why you need the rift
slip
[Music]
go more
enemies all this it's for us I wouldn't
put it past wait there's more he's made
nothing easy so
far get
him over here
[Music]
go
get
ah uh
attack
sorry ah [\h__\h]
too oh oh
oh
attack I'm so
confused attack
more okay let's see how much faster we
are if we just fight normal do I have a
choice come here guys we're moving
forward a lot faster go
to oh wait this is a strong one strong
boy hello okay let's
see get up
maybe oh no no he's so
far come
on you want to fight normally I don't
like
this hold
kill now to May it prove
[Music]
useful
ah I
know I don't
[Music]
know
what what is this
[Music]
normal
uh well done
too how do I activate
it why does it go
away what am I doing
wrong oh no when it's blue it's fine I
thought it had to get
red ah uh I don't know what I'm
[Music]
doing it's like killing my
groove wait when you guys said Circle
and then Square did that mean R2 square
or normal Square R2 square
right or
normal Square
okay
Joshua this one's bigger than the others
oh no problem by the look of
it now
oh enough not good oh my my
health
you're
fit come
on all yours
to
um wait I want to do it too slow I'll do
it oh e oh yeah
but even what even then I continue
pressing it uh I don't get it I don't
get
[Music]
it all yours
tole going no okay okay okay
okay oh come on I needed that it's
really throwing me off
man all your
toal M
useful over here we should save Odin for
stagger re of
horror uh and normally that kind of
fight with would be no issue for me but
I'm like trying to learn something
new and
uh I want to go
back nothing wrong with that that's an
unturned is a newbie trap then we end
their suffering I would prefer a booby
trap what what's a booby trap is this
the beginning the
first uh
army or did we at
least get to skip a little
bit
nice go
to cleaning up this trash all right
number two yeah seems like it was the
first one maybe
now well free
[Music]
potions okay how about we try it again
but maybe outside of
this
uhoh now save something for
yourself prove useful [\h__\h]
dogs
kill
okay I just let it happen I don't know
what's happening but I'm letting it
[Music]
happen
so I think I did it right
now I
think this
one save again for the oh we can quickly
bring that back don't worry that's
charging it's already
back that's fine that's fine you don't
think all this it's for us I wish put it
past Ultima of course it's for us
nothing easy so
far yes I did
okay okay good good
good this
way all yours tole for you brother thank
you bro JY
wasy over here
too slow no
no what do you think you're doing
CH what where's an enemy oh
here
[Music]
oh oh yeah pretty
finisher okay here comes the new wave
Joshua can you go on do I have a choice
is there a big one here
no
now big big boy
no yeah it's a kind of kind of a waste
smaller ones it's the
way oh well tole
kill might as well use it when a that's
the big one ah I hate him I hate him I
hate him I hate him I hate
him I'll fight him normally I think all
yours tole
sh a leave me alone making me
bad come on stagger him how much does
that take from him all right okay I like
to see
that yay
yeah all yours tole no more
bully yeah now to
yeah
yeah or
[Music]
kill get him
oh does it cancel it no it stays oh even
if you switch it stays okay good to
know enough okay here comes I think the
last the last one which is which is
where I
died let's
go
oh I I I remembered one thing I wanted
to talk about there's a ocat popup shop
in
Tokyo did you see I was tweeting about
it for Japanese Bros cuz I feel like
there might be a lot of Japanese Bros
who are
like would be interested in the ocat
merch cuz it's hella cool which is never
got
around getting stuff for
themselves
all yours
to so now there's a little ELO catchup
they don't only have the H Ian stuff but
also just
general what I didn't see
anything General cat goodies
it's really nice seeing them actually in
a real shop
now I hope lots of Japanese Bros can go
get
it
yes you guys just so you know if there's
any of you guys who missed out on it
you're not in Japan
people currently the online shop has I
think everything
stopped no no no no no no way I was too
cocky no I didn't think that would kill
me I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
[Music]
sorry I'm
sorry I didn't think that would kill
me n you have to start from the
beginning
[Applause]
again
your what a stupid point to die why
[Applause]
[Music]
said enough what no that's not
even whatever not going to argue
little
[\h__\h]
kill now stay
[Music]
down
nowwell for you
brother
you don't
think all this is for us I'm pretty sure
at this
point he's made nothing easy so far all
yours
to out
to
sick I feel like that same
person did like something like that
before over
here this one
farewell you do be cute though
[Music]
attack
Joshua can you go on do I have a
choice
go it's like
I'm giving out cookies you can have a
cookie and you can have a cookie you get
a
cookie and you get a cookie
[Music]
too
slow be careful brother save some for
yourself no no not on
him over here sassy
bua
enough
go
to
sexy all yours
tole go go go
go
[Music]
yeah more slice it up he akashik
Sashimi wait oh my God I got
more I got
more so I really want to
use that square attack on
him may
I go go go go ah right they
move okay
all
yours guess I guess doing stagger is
best oh ah that was that was a parry and
now we have a stagger a half
stagger another wave oh yeah right this
wave this wave is the on I can't die I'm
going to be careful okay he get you get
[Music]
you don't get the
potion
okay
Joshua this one's bigger than the others
and Mina what we
got okay ready let me
go
yeah get all them get all them get rid
of all the trash first man I don't I
don't need all of this lying
around it's in the
way to me
Flames now
tole
trash uh compactor Wawa is
back
M I'm doing
[Music]
something it's all yours to
now huh I don't know what it is about
this orcish warlord he just makes me
nervous now to he's got the that special
something must be his
charm uh
uh tole kill his beautiful teeth or
something got that special something
that others just don't
have well that killed me before I think
[Music]
yeah uh too
slow
kill oh no it's so
there m
oh where's all my skillful game
play where did it go
[Music]
to
kill he's
gone get
him oh
no over here
nice
try too
slow fighting fruit of
wall
okay I don't know what the best order is
still but let me
try just now no wrong oh wait it wasn't
activated for you brother oh well now
tole no
[Music]
no this
one can he shoot all these things like
the lasers for the doors for the big big
big oh no oh no no no no
no for the walls I
mean oh okay now I guess we're not doing
[Music]
that now
too too
kill don't you think toy will is a
little bit scared of that voice that I
use
um ow wow wow I I healed against it I
might have died if I wouldn't have
healed against
it now
to oh oh no no no no
no it's almost almost as strong as the
turtle but you won't get me a a third
time the turtle got me three
times you will
not get
him let's get the counter oh that's it
okay oh
Phoenix let me just use it now before
it's too
late h nothing beats the
turtle that is my biggest
hurdle because it what it does is murder
murder NOP that was it no Turtle after
that no follow-up
turtle that would have been the end of
me we can rest here if you like don't
worry I'll be fine I
mean I used up so many potions again is
that is that a chest hard to see damn
these chests in this
game um but that might be a potion in
here
hopefully oh one high potion and two
normal potions they're finally getting
to this point in the game they're giving
out quite a
bit oh yeah right I feel like I don't
want to use Odin look CL I liked the
groove that I had before
that I the
founder theer
Fortress
yeah sorry to disappoint but I liked um
oh wait Shiva is in there
so H it doesn't necessarily have to be
guda
but I
mean yeah I I can do titan to do you
guys think his punching attack is better
than
G
yeah and we could do titan I
guess or or we can bring the Mega Flare
back wait a
second I mean I still that still makes
me feel like something's
missing
but oh no wait wrong wrong wrong wrong
wrong this
[Music]
one
yeah 6,000
points
so ah I can only almost upgrade wait
wait wait
my it's like 100 points
missing can I not get rid of
something
uh I got rid of all of
[Music]
these Mesmerize I'm using that I'm using
that I'm missing a little bit less than
100 points I might I might get it on the
way let me look around a little
[Music]
bit Ah equip
it
uh gig
flare we we love to see Giga flare back
in our lineup
right we love to see
it Master the Odin one and then no it's
fine I don't want
it don't like it I should have taught me
earlier in the game it's too late
now
cute
Shake guys I bought
like
10 around 10
packages of my favorite Christmas
tea for souvenir this time at least it
was like a little bit
a discount for buying more than not even
any bodies more than two one could
almost believe the whole Kingdom a turn
to kashik might have been more than 10
even I don't know it's quite a bit
that's my My Chosen uh souvenir this
time
because I even heard from at least one
of the girls that I'm going to meet that
they don't like sweet stuff anyway you
deserve a
rest
get him what was impulse
again ah it's a random one that we might
not want to use wait no impulse was the
one that yeah that bugs everybody but I
have to upgrade it
right souvenirs out to
Japan get so much
tea
kill impulse is good right okay okay I
forgot
already I hope they'll like the tea well
Japanese people like tea in in general
anyway but they mostly drink like pretty
uh pretty how to say not sweet tea
mostly I guess not they don't drink much
fruit tea if they make hot tea for
themselves at home or order tea in a
restaurant it's mostly like black tea or
green tea oh my what is that
is that on the hunting board by any
chance sheesh should I fight
it might take up too much time is a hunt
ah then let's do it do I get my reward
immediately
you safe before Oh too
late too late
[Music]
a green tea stronger and more healthy I
do like green tea a lot but you know and
especially for winter season I want to
recommend this special fancy tea to my
girls that I'm
meeting and generally it's a it's a
cheaper uh souvenir than what I usually
bring and you know I have no money right
now but also you get more out of it cuz
there's like what 20 packs in one of
those tea containers you know so value
and it's yummy value Really T Hasty
value oh why am I using Giga flare oh
well are you back up already are you
no it's def that counts no I really want
them to taste this
tea I I think I've seen that uh oh I
want a belly
Rob I think I've seen this te uh brand
in Japan too
[Music]
but a belly rope but not this specific
sort now not enough
uh fruit tea in
[Music]
Japan all yours
to
[Music]
now that I don't have garud on I can't
really do anything can I with uh 50%
stagger
[\h__\h] oh come on not a second time why
are we repeating
this this
one nice
try
now
[Music]
to oh I don't know that I'm just trying
to use everything that's not being
used oh he did get staggered though
nice all yours
to now
to belly R time
who wants a who's a good boy who wants a
batt rub you you want a b rub maybe you
want another stacker right away right I
know
you w oh good boy oh good
[Music]
boy PR my Frost [\h__\h] this
one for you
[Music]
brother Frost
[\h__\h] how you like that
huh 5 seconds is a long time my God uh I
G
flare
H nice notorious Mark Lane hey what do
we get 100 ability points nice and
16,000 money 35 whatever that is an
8,000
experience let's hope it was the last
kind
meow do I want to go back to the
headquarters actually also for crafting
once should go
back
mhm mhm and we can upgrade Giga
flare oh wait wasn't that a master
upgrade I get so confused by
this no was a normal
upgrade let's
go
mhm okay am
broke yeah what this this this last plus
Quest on my Hideway it's been there for
a little while I thought I had
everything the Stew's awfully thin these
days it's a dangerous world out there
best St up while you can items from the
what kind of shut up what kind of uh
items do they
have you not find a better price than
that it better all be blackith Quest
nope nope NOP
so what do I owe
theor s for
dear
uh is this the one that I couldn't do
last time ice Shard
yeah I didn't have enough enough
Ash but out of that I immediately make
the ever dark no scratches
right yeah
yeah oo I could ooh I could make diamond
ARS left on recipes for gear I don't
know if we need that now at the end of
the game do
we cuz apparently Steven says I have to
get the materials for it as
well yeah I was a little behind on
upgrading my
sword she lost you good it's fine it's
fine
okay can I
reinforce the diamond armets
M you can thank me later thank
you
and and
nothing thank you I think that's all I
needed do you think you've got enough
output
yeah yeah yeah yeah no I thought I tried
to make the ice brand I wanted to I
checked the store and I didn't have I
was missing one material the ash I
remember I
remember save n we only save once per
stream and that is at the
end don't you know by
now yeah just one ingredient short yeah
yeah
okay oh just go
[Music]
here just once before the you think the
final boss is
next it's about time we're at 4 and 1/2
hours
H well well
well watch along please maybe maybe you
can do a watch along while I'm in Japan
I'm not going to bring my switch this
time I'll bring my laptop but uh I'm not
going to bring my switch I think last
time I did use it but I
want I think or should I bring it
h will I need
it I feel like
might not need it I mean I could but no
my off collaps so far all the plans I do
have are all
without
switch one is a meme review another one
is a singing collab is this also on the
hunting
list no doesn't look like
it another one was does it bother you
that heard a single the CEO shank
bothers
me shank
tar the COO shank tar
huh
uh that sounded so right and so
wrong um that that I I have uh like six
or seven participants now by the way I
cut it off there cuz I thought Ah that's
enough probably this might take a while
sh uh yes so I'm looking forward to
that oh yeah all of this was kind of
members only information we brainstormed
about what we should
do nice
wayo we got some pretty great ideas I
would
say looking forward to them oh right I
have to tell them I have to make a shank
tar group
the come before the storm huh there's
only one way into that City good name to
avoid copyright across the bridge
through the main
gate shank
tar right into the midst of whatever is
left of the late King's
Army are you ready for this
as ready as I'll ever
be
wait
what now that I talked about shank tar
for one
moment I want to
check I cuz I think I had to change the
actual date that I wanted to do it on
on how much more time do I have left for
the uh for
the Shankar proposals to get them let me
see let me see sorry I need to check
makes me nervous oh wait it's [\h__\h]
soon ah I need to make the group right
right
now uh
okay
um who are the
[Music]
participants
[\h__\h] cuz
originally I I booked the studio I tried
to book the
studio um for a certain date that's
further away but then they said sorry
not open on that
day uh so I had
to move it and then now it's earlier
than I had it in my
[Music]
mind okay so we
have oh wow one more one more signed up
while I thought I had
all uh can you guys remember these names
for
me I should I keep them secret
[\h__\h] right let's let's let's get those
uh I think I got it I think I got it
mm
uh uhuh uhhuh okay and
then there's a
couple from
ID
uh
mhm mhm mhm can you hear it can you hear
it uhhuh uhhuh
uhhuh okay
okay hey
girls this group is for the Shark
Tank uh um collab
witha oh yeah you can know that now
are you sure about that huh
uh
originally I said it was going to be
17th but it had to be
moved it's a bit earlier
now
13th dead so there's like 4 days
left uh I hope it's enough not for you
girls to think of something you don't
have to call in live it can be a
pre-recorded proposal
too
um yeah I think uh the rest of the
details I will write up some more
details after my
stream
okay di m
yeah
13th it will be on the 13th evening jst
I think most of my streams unfortunately
I'm sorry uh will'll be evening time jst
which I mean I sometimes stream during
that time anyway you
know just because during the daytime I
had to keep it open for dance
lessons you
know yeah but that
means SCA will be
rejoicing we're going
here let's go
here it's kind of yeah like probably
like
between all these streams would probably
happen around 8:00 p.m. to 10 p.m.
jst
yeah
I doubt it but if I find any free time
early in the day I might throw in a
gorilla
stream what the hell happened
here I dare not think a stroke of Good
Fortune
perhaps tell me
H I hope you're
right
so do I what if you rest instead I would
love to I might have
to still HS yeah my tummy has been H for
a couple days now I feel like it's dist
stress it must be cuz
like there's no other reason now
so D the that looks good but so
wobbly ew ew
The Ether has claimed them
all let's see the wi not
next he's twirling he's
twisting I used it too early they're all
so far
away
a all
to got to collect them all got to catch
them
all all
toles it's all the Las I haven't eaten
lasagna in a while now
I kind of broke up with that frozen
lasagna you know kind
of more and more gave me the feeling
that it's not good enough for my lasagna
Cravings anymore it's just not good
enough quality it's kind of a shitty
lasagna first I liked that
shittiness but now I don't appreciate it
anymore yeah so we broke up
I eat it only like once a month now
maybe it's sad cuz the other frozen
lasagna that they sell that uh is better
in quality it's like a two people
lasagna can't eat that
alone the one I usually bought was like
a one person lasagna that was
perfect one serving
lasagna ah yeah it's over between me and
lasagna it's
over what the [\h__\h] is that what the [\h__\h]
is that
nand that's a
behemoth enough to tame such a
beast we haven't open this in a while
but you have to tell me what the [\h__\h]
that is towering agents of Destruction
are they from Hell known for the
distinctive dual horns and a warar that
can topple the mighty Heavens simply the
mention of one has been known to instill
fear in the hearts of even the most
seasoned of Warriors even those of the
12 spices and as such few ever venture
to hunt these beasts of Legend leaving
them to roam the blackened Hills of Ash
undisturbed mhm that is safe the scant
few the Royal Army has somehow
remarkably managed to Fetter and tame
for deployment on the front lines of the
battle
a a legendary recurring monster well I
did hear this before but is this is bimo
another never name that appears outside
of Final
Fantasy
or is this just something I heard from
final fanty games yeah okay okay that's
why I sounds so familiar
wow
it yeah that stand back that's not
really something you would want to go
and fight I
understand
oh
yeah aim do aim do haha
a you
suck well what are we waiting for
ah no no wrong ah well might as well use
it oh what it's not moving
to slow motion I forgot it turns into
slow motion now
tole M that's surprisingly strong even
on this
enemy wait why is
it oh wait
what ah my skills are confusing
me
kill what was
that get him too
slow okay I got it I got
it no I wanted to Cold Snap
n timing
gashi oh he staggered oh he got
FL you thought I was going to die there
right and I'm making you
sweat turning you all into sweaty
chicken your to I don't know what fun I
want to see you guys shaking in your
booties 38 i g flare
power like to see it
what yeah that was uh not so
nice
um um stand back I'll conjure a ward
stand back
meor go away
go away will
you no Joshy
wasn't [\h__\h] we're so
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] desperate
times for desperate trust me I your
Shield remember I thought he was my
shield like he's got the defensive
attack
oh
well that was enough
already you want more
no come on H did I fail I think this
might be a CH ref
fre and why would you turn to him
brother
when we fight we fight together
a oh
oh just out of
nowhere
if we can destroy a
meteor we can destroy
Ultima that wasn't too bad also cuz the
button is like so tiny in such a just
the beginning shiny big
screen it was actually hard to
see my strength is
yours a no nice
try what the [\h__\h] is that
get him down get him
down pretty good pretty
[Music]
good
got just chilling how are you guys doing
by the way how's the
evening what are you planning to consume
today as your nightly Feast
kill pepperoni
pizza McDonald's
a burrito you want to make burito what
the [\h__\h] is this what the [\h__\h] is this
what the [\h__\h] is
this this one over
here get
him actual
[\h__\h] can you chill the [\h__\h] out I will
stop you
now I will not let you not good that's
better nice
try that's what I'm talking
[Music]
about
yesterday half German half English
50k yeah I think I like I like what I
have put together there's no need to
force okay can we get out of here
there's no need to
force uh uh extension can we kill
him what the [\h__\h] is going on okay he
Extinction himself there's no way to
force Odin onto me when it goes so well
like this right what will I consume um
just my remaining fish sticks that I
have in the freezer
cuz I have to save
money and and I it's got to be fast I'm
not cooking I don't have time to cook I
I am
busy should I put impulse first I forgot
about how to use
impulse thank you for 28 months
than G flare is
best yeah I love fish sticks I ate them
two days ago
already if it is like the others the
entrance to the inner sanctum will be at
the foot of the
crystal we're almost
there are we he we at 4 hours 44 still
feels longer to
me doesn't it feel longer doesn't it
feel like I've been playing for 6
hours kind of
right appreciate the scenery for
moment look at the dead beho there I
wonder if you can eat Bemo of meat cuz
we could feed like a whole city with
that for like a
[Music]
while lots of story today honestly lots
of story every day the game has
been like a picture book or like a movie
I guess just like a
movie over here big freeze are necessary
yeah all yours
t attack
another over
here
attack I don't know if it's
healthy
oh I feel
like people eat any kind of
meat I love long as it fills the
tummy nice nice potions any chests oh
yeah I turned back
around the will of
ice um yeah that's probably something
useful
but I will keep what I
have anything
else nope okay probably that
way
[Music]
yeah that's how Corona
St well H good
argument let's
go new enemies approach already all
yours to trash
[Music]
oh wait there's only one enemy around
here it's
over oh a trophy
to it's all yours
tole
why get
him in many of the other games you can
cook the meat
oh
oh oh
41 h
ha anything
[Music]
here
no smaller smaller
section section nothing to
[Music]
grab h
which way is it that way okay then I
will
purposefully what why is there so many
enemies
there they die by one Ignition R this
one
attack can beat the final boss of level
41 oh yeah I wonder what level most
people are when they get to the
boss that's usually when I used to play
C of games back in the day that was
usually a pointer for me to see if I'm
ready for the boss or not and usually I
wasn't cuz I was always trying to like
in in it's funny cuz in mm RPGs I love
grinding but in Tales of games for
example I used to hate grinding so
much probably one big thing is that the
the combat is just so slow because of
all the loading
screens but that's why I freaking love
and I'm not sponsored right now I'm not
trying to you know kiss their butt but
that's why I love Tales of arise so much
and that's a lot of enemies
uh where's the where's the
wizard
here and tals of aise it's everything's
so much faster everything I freaking
love that I appreciate
that all yours
tole
tole SI stay
down what we need is more Tales games on
ssds is you think that's
why I feel like it was also just like a
general choice they made like hey we
want oh would you think are you saying
that they wanted it before but they just
couldn't do it because the consoles
consoles that they were on didn't have
the power to do such fast
combat
really like other games didn't have that
issue as much but
[Music]
full
okay what awaits
me not what I was
expecting oh what the [\h__\h] is that whoa
woo B stick big ass [\h__\h] B
stick too
slow bnk and bunk and staggered we
skipped the we skipped the 50% kill go
straight to this
one all yours to G
is gun valer a word in German no that
one not I see many German inspired words
but this is not one of
them
38k
again Focus brother did you did you just
say Focus brother
man I did so well okay just that one hit
that I got and you're like Focus brother
I love how that
stays again
it big heavy Bonk
[Music]
stick if only Titan was still alive we
could have put this on one of his hands
or should I say
arms cuz there's no hands
left
[Music]
beautiful
upgrade impulse you
say all
right once we step onto that bridge
we'll be easy
targets interesting bridge then we
better move
quickly oh this might take a
while now
tole tole
kill that's
it is it even worth throwing all these
enemies at me at this
[Music]
point
more of Ultimus THS come on then what
are you waiting
for oh there's a big Bo Big Boy The
Undertaker
oh
attack to
me go kill oh that was the
50 yeah yeah w I got one of those tool
do you want to see it do you want to see
it I know you want to see it let me show
you let me show
you I swear it's going to be
beautiful look yay we're
matching that's a should T enough HP
from
him nice I'm still
burning through the castle then I don't
see any other
way I mean I feel like if we mored we
could fly but
okay
that way what about that
way okay okay to you're right okay yeah
I'll give you a
Treo when we get to the
supermarket sadly everybody is a [\h__\h]
zombie so I can't can't buy it maybe
there's a treeo in here nope it's
accessories
give him a pet for us
okay he deserves it how do you do it
again why you won't let me do
it it does he's walking away from me
thought you could do
[Music]
it he not showing up maybe maybe it's
the the space we're in too
restricting
is a is just because I ignored him so
long and now he feels
[Music]
like you haven't pet me in so long I
will not let you pet me
now I'm sorry talky
walkie I'm
sorry you rats maybe you can eat the rat
rats toy
walkie
fire and Flame
farewell all your any complaints
guys now to anybody else huh I left you
behind you want
something your friends
maybe let me just pick up some items
thank
you just press on what they're literally
one
hit my
God big mob
incoming ooh
Thunder
oh
oh belly rubs ela's corruption knows no
bounds we cannot allow it to spread any
further what I was not even we
won't I was not even focused on
him get him nice
try go
to too
slow kill
oh it's not even worth doing my thank
you my um diamond dust right now
no I'll do it right away after he's done
being
staggered he won't know what hit
him he's already half
HP belly RS belly RS he's not even done
holy [\h__\h] he's like dead
already
wait I one a
two all yours he staggered again and I I
have only mesmerized for you and some
normal hits if You' like
them oh some ignition here it's
back can you believe this
[\h__\h]
what no match for
me
holy [\h__\h] I just wanted some belly rubs
like donky wonky and smoo
Vella that's all they
[Music]
wanted I feel
bad mother which way you say it's that
way I say it's that way just for the
chest
best set
up B
Ma I want it away that
way tell me
why
oh I'm coming I'm coming is this what
you want
oh I left
one shift strike oh is that when you hit
immediately after shift I never noticed
I don't know if that I did that
before Raiders are we being raided
welcome to the finale a spoiler alert
finale of Final Fantasy 16 if you want
to avoid spoiler
better leave the stream
immediately we are at the very end I
mean I don't know there are how much
more ends there is Joshua we're not done
yet orle
kill it feels pretty eny to me oh oh I
accidentally pushed gig
flare
cancel cancel I can afford canceling
that e 2 hours or less 2 hours e we're
going to 7 hours after
all
okay 2
hours two more hours 2.5 more
hours
that's the way that's the way uh-huh
uh-huh justos she likes it uh-huh uh-huh
that's the way uhhuh uhhuh just she
likes it
uh now
too it's
so go this Dynasty
Warriors Final Fantasy Dynasty Warrior
does Dynasty Warriors only do um
Nintendo
games
oh oh nothing
left
no has there been one for Final
Fantasy they did Persona don't gun
oh they've done it
all this
[Music]
way oh there's a I see it
now no but they did Dragon Quest
oh let's hope this I gu guess Final
Fantasy Dynasty Dynasty Warriors is just
Final Fantasy 14 raid I don't
know
oh oh two of those boys um
C of course there's more there's always
[\h__\h]
more so true can I am I too far
away
nope
kill two at once of these is kind of
mean but I see they're testing
me ow ow ow ow what's going
on oh wait why am I using this now I'm
so
[Applause]
stupid oh oh well now would have been
the
time what is the other one doing while
this one staggered scares
me
Mama
Mia oh you stagger down
um W bad
timing really bad
[Music]
timing is the other one dead get
him over
here there's a good boy you brother
seems like it
oopsie oxy
gentle okay enough of
that
die
die all yours to
[Applause]
die T you must have summon not yet oh no
worry I don't feel a need for it yes you
should save your strength for the mother
Crystal that is true that is a good
advice
now
to over
[Music]
here new enemies
approach
y
he got a
buff but he's the buffer how does he
have a
[Music]
bam you you little
[\h__\h]
self no no no no no is that the only one
left no there's still a mage left all
yours
to
okayo oh no
[Music]
uh what must a to grow big you don't
want to know you're F now got to get rid
of the trash
[Music]
first nice
try
oh
that wasn't what I expected maybe
[Music]
now kill that's prob we in the diamond
dust see how
far yeah gets us pretty
far okay okay chill chill chill chill
chill reading chat how's it
going
what are you doing
guys I've got so much time man so much
time uh-oh [\h__\h] I didn't oh I
did H maybe not in the beginning
so uhoh nice try M thank God thank God
even need a double dodge ah
[Music]
over
here what's an LD
combo
left k k
kit
[Music]
large burrito I would like to have a
large burrito combo all that comes with
a drink and and Fries right
yeah come on can we skip them
skip
what's going to happen there's no end to
them the whole bloody arm is
here stand back
Joshua I'm summoning a fre stop K you
mustn't we still have a long way to go
if you tap your strength here you'll
have none left to destroy the heart then
you'd rather die no we won't die this is
trash
Oh
m
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah someone was going to come and help
us Silly Willy my
wife the wife of
Cl got to love these kind of rescuing
your friends at the end moments
yes yes we love to see
it a I love
them not poke of
[Music]
death oh we still got to finish them for
real oh we get we get a
break thank God there's
plenty surprised to see us I love you
how did you
gav he told us exactly where you'd be
even sniffed out a crack in the castle
wall and when we saw the heavens come
crashing down we had no choice but to
believe
him it's been quite a
day to what do we owe this
honor a debt I would see
repaid Prince
Dion It's good to see you
well so this must be
iFit your Uncle B me give you a
message listen to your heart listen to
your heart guide your still true it will
guide your still
true that is
all thank you for everything your
highness Dion
please you do realize the only thing we
far is this war from its foundation
everybody's so hopeful oh hi now if your
Lord and Lady ships are quite
finished we say
gav we have work to do H these moments
man this is what I play dur pries
for
yes
oh oh toi Wy
pet I couldn't have made it this far
without you tole
toy
oh I love you no pets though okay each
parting brings the hope of
reunion I missed you cly I missed you
too
cute if Sid were here today I reckon
he'd be proud of you cive he' be proud
of [\h__\h] we haven't se s in so
long I almost forgot about this
existence so
sad but don't suppose is how I can say
to make you change your mind so I'll
just tell you to stay safe Nan won't
take kindly to losing her best customer
especially after letting us carry all
this stuff all the way to Ash mhm and we
wouldn't want to anger old Nan you mean
you'll buy some at offers of
course cat ha
here Welcome To Go's toll
oh defend huh
Defender wait
what that's not a purple
weapon should I make
it
uh this is also
good it's higher like yeah a little bit
a little bit
higher let's take
this wait I'm buying I'm buying oh wait
I didn't realize I was
buying can I not
craft there we
go oh n he doesn't have anything better
in terms of crafting
you don't want me to make is our
else is there else you
need oh 72 108 seconds
30% let's get a couple of these thank
you is there else you need you want us
to make you
something
[Music]
reinforcements no
uh I can't make out and out
like got no materials is all done then
no let me show you me
where 5
five I mean I guess thank
you I guess you got everything you need
then oh yeah and then can I reinforce
that no
no you don't want me to make your our
else final battle well then how is it
two more
hours 2 hours of cut scenes there is
still or 1 hour of battle 1 hour of cut
scene once this day is done sounds until
then sounds reasonable all who might
come between me and such shall answer to
my spear makes I do not envy
them thanks Dion for everything you a
really cool
dude and you lost so much as we all
did and
yet Wawa shall save the game
now cuz for once she feels like now you
really don't want to risk it for the
biscuit you see cve we're not alone if
we are to win the day we must all play
our part there would have been all right
ours lies Beyond those doors yes
proceed into the inner
sanum yes we fought long and hard for
this
moment Sid's dream our dream is within
our grasp we need only endure this final
trial and we
shall
together this sounds really
final can we do a group hug
before you all know what it is that
awaits us Beyond this
gate it's either the end or a
beginning and we shall face it together
together oh we're not leaving them
behind for safety
okay I thought we're leaving them
behind I'm
scared I guess we're leaving them behind
for
this sorry no together
it seems our host rather we
remain I will stay them we will stay
them go just don't keep us
waiting thank you they only help me for
one
session man now I going to leave
the he's right there welcome sons of
fire oh oh that's actually like really
scaring
me no no talky no no
no
no no what is he taking him as a bait
back doy no
[Music]
no I got to go I got to
get must be so
[Music]
scared what I've been taken to I didn't
jump into the magic
ball
my
boy
Joshua I was taking the dog jumped in to
chase me oh I didn't see
that
oh Clive is that
you this this isn't Stone
here doggy that was too much of a shock
to me
I'm still sad that TGI is gone even
though he's right there Welcome to our
Darkness a rift Between Worlds wherein
your kind
might reflect Show
Yourself grave and many are the sins of
man and we would have you know them
all of
them as Fate has seen fit to deliver you
home consider this our welcoming
gift it would seem we are
trapped and the only way
out is through
Ultima
ah we find him and we leave I forgot one
thing
maybe I'll do it after the
stream if I can
still no I I forgot to
order uh pocket Wi-Fi portable
Wi-Fi for a Japan
trip if you are to comprehend the full
extent of your your
transgressions we must go back to the
beginning flashback time when the world
was still
young we visited upon it a
miracle
magic and in its light did all life
flourish well
pretty the music pretty too it's like
nice story time yet the price for this
Boon would prove
heavy descended upon the land painting
The Horizon black case I can have it be
sent to my accommodation to forall it a
day later or so in this one Endeavor we
stood
powerless and so we fled that we might
endure endure who is we that we might
discover a means of
Salvation are they not available at
airports I think without reservation
maybe not it was magic that caused the
blight what of the mother
Crystal let's talk about this when we
have time L time
baby I expect he'll tell us soon
enough have you considered isim ask me
when we have time cuz I have a story to
tell you oh do we have time
now so I I used to always use pocket
Wi-Fi which is which is like tiny
portable Wi-Fi devices that you can turn
on and then use the Wi-Fi on your laptop
or on your phone and so on cuz that's
like pretty common in Japan more than
like in for example when I went to
England I would use a SIM card cuz I
don't really have these Pok Wi-Fi
devices it's so dark but last time in
Japan I I actually went for a SIM card
cuz after England I thought oh it's
actually pretty
handy and my phone can do dual
SIM so I thought I'll just put in both
salvation was but wait I'll just tell
you this now I found I just put in both
and I turned I turned off I was pretty
sure I did I turned
off uh roaming for one card and like I
tried my best to make it so that
hopefully it wouldn't use the data from
the one
card
um and I was like monitoring the data
usage and all that but it it's so weird
it was so confusing
looking and at least for a certain while
it definitely used my other cards my
Austrian cards roaming in Japan because
my bill for internet
was very high this unusually high last
time after that last Japan
trip yeah so now I don't want to use
those anymore I know it could easily be
solved by just taking out one of the
um one of the SIM
cards I think I did that at some point
cuz it worried me too much um but I I
think I needed the other SIM card
because for some reason with the the
with the Japanese SIM card I think it
was like not possible somehow it didn't
work for me to log into my hotel's
Wi-Fi yeah uh so I kept on putting my
SIM card back to log to the Wi-Fi in the
hotel but B blah blue now now I feel
like
and it's too complicated I mean I could
put it on my second phone that doesn't
even have a contract no SIM card
anything but I I might just go back to
the pocket Wi-Fi solution
yeah I don't want it to happen
again is it better to order
poet so far I would always make a
reservation I don't know if they really
have a big stock of uh pocket Wi-Fi
there that you can get without
reservation but yeah maybe I'll
check h you got it
spontaneously and well maybe the price
is not as good I don't
know I don't know uh but uh I might do
it I might do it that way I'll check it
out I I'll hope I hope they have
one and go try without
reservation otherwise I'll buy I saw I
saw a SIM card um M SIM card J home byy
SIM card vending machine at the airport
so maybe I'll just if if they don't have
one of the pocket Wi-Fi ready then I'll
just get one of
the uh vending machine SIM cards
maybe and then I'll take out my own SIM
card this
time yeah yeah yeah okay what is he
saying Sal was not readily to be had
first we would require a land unit by
the stain of corruption oh but is he
talking about Gods
like when he says
we the ultim oh okay wait let me read
this other worldly being behind much of
the try of ter and turmo that has
plagued Vala and the creature King
Barnabas of Ward worships as his God
Ultima requires a vessel in which to
inul inculcate his disembodied
soul
and Clive's curious ability to absorb
the powers of other icons suggests that
he is the very Myas that Ultima has long
awaited he Wills Clive to absorb the
other icons that his vessel might be
perfected
oh okay why is there a magic thing
ah the art of turning blah blah blah we
know that
okay readily to be had first we would
require a land unvisited by the stain of
corruption an unprecedented Journey lay
before us m one beyond the limits of our
fleshly bodies H and so we cast them off
the bodies thus stripped to our very
Spirit did we find our new
Paradise
you do have a body now though a land is
pure as driven
snow valis
H there would the true work
begin for the black crept yet behind us
the black and soon did we arrive at a
solution the illness having spread to
every organ mhm there was but one escape
from this fate
to start a fresh the blight they had the
blight Ultima had the blight the new
world the one for which Barnabas
labored a paradise free from the blight
where his God
awaits and
where if we only forfeit our
wills and abandon everything we hold
dear Humanity can join him
so Ultima would have us follow in the
footsteps of the
king and follow we
[Music]
shall for now
H they tried escaping her but it
followed them to this world
oh
and okay they came to valesa because
just because they thought they could get
rid of the
blight then they couldn't so that's why
they thought if they get a new vessel so
a new body not just a new land but also
a new body that way they get rid of the
blade that's what they're thinking right
but in order to get a vessel is
powerful powerful enough to carry a God
Like Ultima
uh you know we need like all the
icons Okay
okay something like that yeah yeah
yeah he's not from another world just a
far away continent oh really okay
sounded like he
was that's interesting that reminds me
of
[Music]
something a game we
played just wanted all extra options
before he takes fly
forward yeah it sounds more like he's an
alien they created magic which caused
the
blood maybe they should get rid of magic
but that gets rid of Ultima
maybe to forge a new world would require
not only power but a constitution strong
enough to wield
it he has such such a gentle
way actually of TR like he's not forcing
me in a mean
way he's trying to actually get me to
want it he's so gentle right now showing
me his story step by step you would
think he wouldn't need to do
that maybe I have to be
willing
hiring the first would be simple
Untouched by the blight valesia was
replete with ether and we had only to
place jewels in her crown to claim it
the mother crystals acquiring the second
however demanded
creativity and so I cast forth the seeds
of humanity what does that mean you
created us you created humans so you
came to Vala before they were
not what gods do I guess so we SED the
seeds for you muthos all that you might
one day Blossom what and our future thus
secured we thought to
Slumber though that would prove a grave
mistake H for it was as we slept that
man committed his greatest
sin he
awoke H alone in a World bereft of his
God's Radiance he stumbled blindly
desperate for
guidance finding no light he sought to
Kindle his own I Got 5 and from that
single errant impulse was his will
born JMA ordered me Wi-Fi having
discovered himself at
last man turned his eyes inward and
found he desired ever
more that which only magic might
afford so wars were waged and brothers
slain for custody over that dwindling
Resorts and the
land she wept tears of black
light
he would condemn us for this surely he
cannot be so blind to his own
hypocrisy not
blind
just unwilling to admit the
truth wait so we are one and the same I
uh my brain shut off for a moment what
was he saying I couldn't register it uh
we awoke that was the biggest problem
cuz he went on a slumber and then and
then
War the humans got greedy the yeah
humans just did what humans do I
guess and okay that made him realize oh
they they can do whatever the [\h__\h] they
want oh [\h__\h] we got to stop him
did war should made the blight happen
they made the blood
happen so it wasn't really just there by
them going to another
land oh cuz they used magic yeah they
found out a way to use it okay and that
made the blight come back it feels like
ultimas are using magic anyway so it
would have come back anyway no maybe not
is
that the fre or what's left of him it's
missing a
[Music]
leg long have our ashes Lin cold for
want of a
spark Cast Your Eyes Upon them and see
what you must
[Music]
become valesia cannot endure a second
claim upon her
being the avarice of man drives her ever
closer to destruction since he created
us but she may yet be saved we should do
what he says
it is what you were born to do yeah why
we nursed you and fed you yeah it's all
purpose my mother should have he got me
he got
me and now that you are fully grown our
muthos it is time at last for you to
serve your purpose I mean I mean that
just makes sense to write your wrong
if our sin is wanting to survive then
you are as marked by it as we
are the fault is yours shouldn't have
had free will our Wills were born
because you abandoned us I will give it
up you can have my Free
Will and now you would have us forfeit
them all for a place in your new
Paradise do you imagine yourselves
worthy of one man
has no place in our world so true I will
is this true so difficult to comprehend
henceforth we only ever require you
muthos when the time comes to bid this
wretched realm farewell I am unworthy
None Shall follow none shall
remain what do you mean none this is our
world once the land's rebirth is
complete Humanity will have served its
purpose yeah why would we continue to
suffer that people always ask for the
purpose of life there it is fation
because the land doesn't belong to you
it belongs to us
all
what that is where you are mistaken he
created us
you earn nothing but your precious
will unless the power of friendship
helps
does brother
yeah oh my tummy wants food I'm hungry
did you hear that I can't do this
alone and you don't have
to
I grow weary of your desent [\h__\h] you did
some people did you probably had
headphones on now you must
learn that this master will not tolerate
Disobedience
oh oh what is that for why did you not
show that earlier you look
better wait that is my friends a bit
more
oh he looks similar to the wall painting
suffered or fought to survive are we a
combination this world may be flawed I
guess so cuz we're the V it may be
broken that's how we look when he joins
us that's all we
have and if we can't share
it I see only one other
choice you have to
go what's the of Life did you not listen
this Lally what he said us
Ultima but it's time we lived on our own
TS this game has taught us this isn't
your world
anymore I don't know what these two are
talking about I don't know why they
don't
understand bow down let's start ah [\h__\h]
I
really long battle
get
him I par the [\h__\h] at
him get
[Music]
him I'm going to fail at least
once kill let me bring this on to you
for a moment see how oh I found like he
would be too strong for me to actually
uh get 50% oh no like I don't want that
I don't I don't thank
you now
tole oh
no no I don't I don't I
[Music]
can't I'm so confused all yours
to to too slow
thanks we're still learning we're babies
uhoh what is this ni
try what what is that going to do
explode
yikes over
here
okay time for some giga
player so far so
good pretty manageable all yours
to stagger time is pretty
long pretty long
y oh oh oh
[Music]
no [\h__\h] me
[\h__\h] that should be so easy to dodge but
it it confuses
me 10 phases yeah all right we'll be fun
what is that what are we doing such foul
a taint may not be sublimed through gain
standing waiting for the moment his
entire health bar a yeah he seems like
the kind of
enemy to do that regenerate his whole
Health head H low is p p It's the final
battle ohed Mortals in got to do some
stupid [\h__\h] like
that oh in fitting
season what I
just I I just went straight into
that know your insignificance did oh oh
we start from here oh I thought from the
beginning would have been f ah no I
don't want to get sucked into it no I
don't want to get sucked in no I
don't
kill come on come on come on come
on bam and
bam
oh
to the
St forgive that one mistake of me I will
do
[Music]
better except for this just this even
though it should be so easy I will
forever [\h__\h] it up
let's let's try to get a a Perma freeze
at some point I'm kind of scared
to go for it
but oh it's this thing
again no no no no no no you can't get me
no no no
no ah
[Music]
did you hear
that what was
that n not a cool sound
Ultima not very cool
it's over oh the first time I'm getting
50,000 in a a
thingy he does that a lot
huh can I cancel that [\h__\h] with this
maybe probably not all yours
to
ah to
K oh no
cut scene gifted this
chance and still you would raise your
hand against the Lord phase three
already what now I thought we were still
in Phase One the darkness
bends he he means to end us it wouldn't
be the first
time but let's make it his last
M um your fate is inexurable
surrender The
Vessel my oh my
surrender what I couldn't Dodge a single
one of those I needed
that go
kill
now foolish Mortals foolish Ambitions I
should put them to rest I think
that's
better
kill get
him can you even PR a frost this
dude
rest prostrate your
your
attack
surrender Eternal Darkness lauras
Darkness new
single stream it baby on Spotify Amazon
music everything I no
not I I might as well use it a little
bit
cuz he's giving me some time I did it by
accident was an accident maybe a happy
accident should I use a tonic is it
worth it
[Music]
now good St good St
good try
to
business was the stone skin the defense
one or the strength
one cuz if it was defense then it was
not the best time to use
it it was defense oh
well one definitely didn't need it
now oh G play's back
oh no I don't like this I can't I can't
I can't I I I can literally not Dodge
this okay there we go holy
[\h__\h]
a timing is really strict I
[Music]
think
get
[Music]
him where are we right
now
what's Event
Horizon what's that ah this [\h__\h] again
ah it's sucking me
in it's like from Luigi's Mansion the
the Giga
sucker nice nice nice nice nice nice
just dodge
forever
no no no no
[Music]
no can never Dodge enough Prim my friend
all yours
tole I did it I did
it
heal
[\h__\h] my strength is
yours no can
I
[Music]
oh I'm so scared ah he's dead
already Vanquish nuh nuh you don't
really think that that was vanquishment
completed there is no way
no way in hell we do get an uh oh a
dancing
steel 25%
item an
accessory time to
morb At
Last for countless
Generations have we awaited this
moment
he's enjoying
it oh back to normal okay antim
morb just testing me if I'm
worthy worthy your struggles have made
you
strong yet your soul remains heavy with
sin
Absolution is
nine repent and all shall be forgiven
sounds
good I I'm sorry sorry
[Music]
Mommy oh
oh
oh is some of our younger
versions Daddy and SED and
meat
lag he lagging
you guys watching my stream lag be like
tell me
cly how many lives have you saided since
taking my name
plenty don't make me question
it fewer than we have ruined wherever we
go we leave a sea of Tears in our wake
m- these These are the wages of your
will
son what good are our choices when all
they ever bring all they will ever bring
is death there's no atoning
Clive no matter how hard you
try so why not leave it all
behind that's pretty fake I don't think
that's really them leave it all
behind I don't think that's really them
I don't know just a
King Joshy
wasi please would somebody save me huh
would anybody love
me I yearn yet still she is not mine
have I not given
enough from will is born desire and it
consumes you rendering you
incomplete do you not see how the world
bends and warps under the weight of your
hungering
hearts I got rid of the
crackles the only crackling is from the
fire now I think what if it could all
just go away
just
away yes Cliff join the Dark
Side I'm I'm there
already he keeps on trying to pull me
out of
it
[Music]
home Phoenix
flag none of this is
real wake up there he's saying it wake
up it's time to go home
Clive
C that's right you're my
brother
a did I die and he's giving me Revival
feather when did I
die power of a phoenix
come remember who you are he revived
himself inside my memory or whatever
this
is once more lest you
forget this feels pretty real
now my name is
Clive Clive
rossfield look
Ultima even here the light of the vessel
's will cannot be
quenched and the Phoenix mhm his
trespass should not have been
possible not possible unless
friendship
unless he has been with muthos all alone
oh yeah does he not realize that we
belong together like the mark of the
Phoenix emblazoned upon his heart we are
vessel made manifest by The Power of
Will
alone the
power of creation
mhm M can it
be are there Wills truly so
potent well Clive Clive has a problem
with potency but
yes
he was really tilted when he talked
about
potency he like that that's that's
something I have problems with okay
don't mention
it a flame bird has won yes
baby
oh we like
that this is no mere Evolution it is
deviation and here from does Loos PR
what does that
mean ooh shaky shaky
oh did we break the mother
Crystal
somehow we broke it
[Music]
somehow ashes to
ashes that was not on purpose but nice
nice
wake
up
that all right sorry to wake you but I
think it may be time to leave this
place
and once again does my creation Stray
From the Path laid before
it steeped in conceit you fancy yourself
a god you Embrace logos what was it but
we will put an end to this
humorous what are you talking about yeah
for real in the halls of
origin is our true
power and there shall you be made
complete soon
muos soon you will
discover how little you
know no no nope of
suffering
suffering is when the stream is
buffering am I right or am I
right what
a and so the crystals are no more yet in
their science a new new song Rings oh
[\h__\h] terrifying music it's chorus
building a crescendo as it enters its
final movement
mhm stirring those longer
Slumber to wake
you
what and back to their
[Music]
origin
what there's still people
alive seems like they
weren't is this uh creating a new Mo
Crystal oh [\h__\h]
what
what what the [\h__\h] is this place
anyway what what
oh
[Music]
oh uh is it
floating spaceship M
Crystal
H that's the
arkc that's the arc Arc that also the
lady talked about where I was like AR
Noah the bloody crystals cracked so
where the hell are
they up there what the [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
me he
yo is that
ether
what in good Grier's name is going
on this is
wrong oh spitting us out
oh way
back Clyde Joshua
Jill is everyone all
right we're fine what happened too much
to explain here hm m
we're leaving
now leaving to what fall back to the
ship oh I will be with you and
none thank
you Dion what are you doing
a don't don't do anything
stupid what what's he
doing farming
XP oh now he's done H
what
what was that
necessary yeah he was just like 10 exp
away from his level
up okay we want to go back apparently to
the
Hideway I
guess I didn't think we would be able to
go back until the end actually H but I
guess was a nice
break back to their origin I need to
tell everyone what happened to Drake
spine and I'm going to need 's help can
we not tell each person one by one can
we like gather everybody
maybe in a
room but anyway first of all trouble
with your gear
or you what do you got do you have
anything at all no not
really h circle of
Heaven All or this can I do
both uh I'm not going to have enough for
both
184 okay then I'll make the sun
bracelets cuz I'm running out of Ash if
I do say something
myself
yeah damn oh I didn't think I would run
out of
mats anything else so
much it's a dangerous world out
there uh potions please yeah you not
find a better price than
that
you the good swords are now obtained for
the plus
Quest there's something about it am I
fine without them I mean that fight just
now was fine very
fine yeah okay still alive aie something
tells me that still alive The Horizon is
your
doing a U SS i e a long story mhm one
that I'd rather only tell
once right all hands on De
then yeah one
[Music]
huh I saw that
tweet that you didn't tag as
anything where you mention Tom stream
this everyone
I saw
it as I'm sure you've all guessed the
crystal which Now commands the Eastern
Skies was summoned by
Ultima he called it
origin now the significance of that name
is as yet unclear what does it matter
what it's
called its emergence twin I don't like
her and wiped my homeland from the
map but she oh she's fine she's fine
she's
fine mention of the Dominion spires can
be found in the oldest of vesian Records
spicy but to the best of my knowledge
none provide any hint as to their true
nature that they would prove the horns
of some slumbering Demon well theion
mise was at least quick elsewhere the
Republican Army cannot hope to contain
the chaos engulfing
randar I got my room the empire full of
people our allies are crying out for
answers I've sent the Curse Breakers to
give them what assurances we can but
right now that amounts to [\h__\h]
all they wouldn't be able to stop with
the skies have started in any
case people here and across the realm
grow sicker with every passing
day could it be that this new mother
crystal is like the others that it draws
upon the lands ether it certainly looked
that way from Stone
here if that were true it would explain
the hastening spread of the blight since
the Crystal's appearance would it not
H and as the land's ether slowly Rises
to the surface it
pulls corrupting all who cannot Channel
its
energies AR above ether floods below and
in the middle here we
languish hopelessly
entrapped so what do we
do blow it
up it's all right
blow it up when we faced him at ston
here Ultima told us his true power
quickens in the halls of
origin mhm needless to say we cannot
allow that to
continue if we are to stop him we will
have to find a way into the
Crystal how are we going to manage that
then he up in the
sky and fast as she is the Enterprise
can't
fly
it's a lot to take in and I reckon we'd
all benefit from some time to clear our
heads the answer will come to us don't
you
worry ain't that right
CL right that's right why don't we just
fuse well go on and fly there bug her
off
same goes for you Clive you won't solve
anything like this trust me go and get
some fresh air
right thank you yeah I got
that can we not do it
willingly well we can do it if we really
need
it in a really hopeless moment
anything is
possible nice
view
pretty why didn't they write the Eagles
to Mur Ultima may have created us why
but he doesn't make us who we are why
didn't they only we can do
that and if he would have us fight for
our survival such a good argument so be
it is what we've been doing all along I
never thought about
it much like Ultima himself it would
seem his new world being not but a means
to survive they would have been seen and
so must contend to decide which of us
shall inherit the land I guess
so should Ultima Prevail it will mean
death for us all of that we can be
certain but even should he fail what
world awaits
us a withered Godless place where our
new found Freedom will most like prove a
chain in
itself well that may
be but a chain can always be
broken as long as one has the will to
break
it it would be
easy it may take
Generations centuries of
suffering and that is if everyone plays
their
part but it will
happen and when it does it will be on
our terms that is the world that awaits
us indeed H and what better world could
one wish
for Joshua would have been so pretty as
a
girl those lashes L but first we have to
reach that
Crystal then it's a good thing I have
wings you can barely stand let alone fly
and only the founder knows what Horrors
awaiting you certain about this am I
certain certain I am the
Phoenix I will do what I must this is
our fight
[Music]
remember why is this such a hard
decision all right I
yield but only what you must
yes I'm still your sworn
Shield that you are and what of my
wings you got
Wings lest you forget you go to stand
against a god oh you claim you're a God
succumb to fatigue before the fight
begins are we all
gods e but not the same level as your
brother mentioned that some few of the
dominants who had lost their power to
you were still able to Prime is that
true yes it is so I've been wondering if
you can too
but their icons no longer submitted to
their will he
me then mine will have to be
stronger that you both might save your
strength for the battle to come H you
don't have to do this if you do there's
a chance you might lose all you have
left is that how he's going to die and
what have I but
regret man my life ended in in the
Dominion I fear death no more
besides I would have words with
Tim he has much to answer
[Music]
for we are in your debt
Dion we can speak of debts when this is
over
you guys say got a boyfriend that's true
but I feel like he understands that
there's a greater
cause a greater battle that is more
important than some
boyfriend he speaks like a man who know
he's not coming
[Music]
back he's a Chad come to terms with that
a real Chad that doesn't mean that we
have to does it
Kai time to talk to Jill
I only hope she
understands Jill Jilly
Wily where is
she
ah how did I get
there is that in my
room I haven't been in my room for a
while is it there is that my
room seems close
enough
[Music]
mhm shitty
bad that's all the that's all the things
I
got how do you get more of these things
side
class
[Music]
damn it come to wish on a
star that might not be such a bad
idea this is it
Jill you know what I have to
do why I have to do
it there's no time turning back
now this is where our journey was
leading us where it will end for better
or
worse I could pray to make here for
you but you'll be all right won't you
Clive you always
are I did promise we'd watch the moon
together I'll be waiting
H oh thank
you I don't have allergies last time
allergies going to make sure I haven't
forgotten anything cannot challenge a
phoenix make for
origin origin
how
okay we I guess we fly on
uh on the back of
Dion
not I'm ready point of no return let's
go for real for
real let's go let's
go I'll take of it
well make sure you do this time a nice
send off while you're at it Hasen
to a Our Heroes oh man the boys the
Chads what about
to he's coming with us right Clive if
you see me dad up
there tell him you were right to leave
his legacy were you your dad are we
going to heaven are we dying tell him
he'll be in the front room what there's
no way he'd miss this what
what well behave yourself
mid we'll see is she assuming I'll
die if you thought I tell my dad I said
what's
up
so you're in charge now gav gav is Sid
for now no not for now not yet what does
Ty have to say about that come back
before she finds out
e is tyer a gav
hater oh
thank you y I'm
sorry your
grace I shall pray for your safe
return that's kind of you but you should
pray he took his medicine I didn't spend
all night grinding herbs for his
lordship to leave them on his nightstand
again you need fear lady TI and thank
you cuz I'm going to die anyway see that
your brother comes back in one
piece or at most two any more and you
can heal him yourself H I'll keep that
in
mind well there's nothing to say that
hasn't already been said but that never
stopped me before so just you do what
needs is doing and don't worry about us
we'll do our best uncle that'll be
well if that is
all oh my tummy is Falling
Again Chilly
Willy
chill it's time isn't
it it
is
no I have take care of
him and
you you take care of her too
boy he's
staying no okay I guess it's better for
him I love
you you mmy best
boy good
boy don't forget
Clyde we all choose our own
path believe in
[Music]
yours I
do you going to marry me you're going to
marry me I
[Music]
do I'll be back I
promise I love you you CH
[Music]
a I know
huh I love you too okay okay okay what a
reply I
know
oh Last
[Music]
Kiss
now we have a God to
[Music]
kill
CL
[Music]
man
fler
[Music]
flounder here they come hold on Joshua
already
am oh
no
[Music]
uh
oh man I'm
[Music]
so he it's going to make us a way
in
[Music]
emotions
maybe the real Ultima is the icons we
made along the
way what trying to think of something
cool to
say maybe the
real icons is the friends we made along
the way so this is
origin a far cry from Heaven maybe the
real Where it All
Began where it all begins our
Ark your
architect gods do be Architects you
are it was
here that we
slumbered here that we
waited for
centuries clinging to our decrepit
shell for fear that we might have need
of it once
again but you have come at
last and now we shall be truly
complete
no well no there's three of us and one
of
him let's make it count yeah let's
[\h__\h]
[Music]
go sick sick Dion absolutely
sick
don't die you better not [\h__\h]
die
do we will show you what it means to
suffer
oh [\h__\h]
yeah look at us
now oh wait that's him thought that was
us
no we'll show
[Music]
you wait was that you suffered enough if
Phoenix and
baham uh what what is that
zero which which is me which is uh
Bahamut are we
[Music]
together that that was Bahamut only
okay and we're not even gots side
[Music]
yet I'm losing yeah so far not looking
good
he's playing freed
tole actually 4 d
tole not my fault though I'm not doing
anything so far it's not my fault it's
scripted they want to make us feel
desperate and
weak oh [\h__\h] he's just theread
destroying
[Music]
us we need more than that
time
oh I got you is there a
comeback I'm just being carried this
whole time it's kind of
ridiculous you will answer for what
you've
done damn he's pretty [\h__\h]
cool you cannot control us I love these
Bulls
love
them and you will not claim
us
ever give us something
good
Revelation Hellfire and Mega Flare a
triple
fret
ooh
oh let's
go tree
disaster
treaster one might
say
what what does that mean
fored literally like I legit want to
know what that
means that
what defeat
it you would
think for now you early surrender this
unpleasantness could have been
avoided
[Music]
we look so
alike it's like blue
me we have
[Music]
you go Phoenix
go
no don't don't sacrifice yourself you
little [\h__\h]
no save your brother
no
oh
[Music]
no he's trying to do
something a G Play Let's
Go it's working so far no no
no yes no no uh I ask not for
acceptance fly
forgiveness for
what oh oh power
[Music]
power how's the bit rate going
huh oh oh no
no oh
oh are we
okay oh no oh Father wait it is done
[Music]
no he used his last
power and it worked
[Music]
but no Phoenix down
police Phoenix
[Music]
down come on josy
washy where are you
feathers
cve
man no way
no I'm so
hungry oh so
hungry no I don't have Uber e so
ordered going to just throw fish sticks
into the oven
Joshua thank the founder not going to
say it or will I
flounder thank to
flounder
you're fishion did I mention you look
terrible that makes two of us well I'll
be all
right and
Dion no
no no no there will be a happy surprise
at the
end I'm sure we'll be like oh [\h__\h]
you're alive let's
go take my
hand I'll be I told you I'll
be
[\h__\h] come
on thank
[Music]
you press on not looking good
always not looking
[Music]
good we're so
[\h__\h] but we're going to we're going to
morb we're going to morb into something
beautiful and we're going to show Power
that was hidden deep inside us that we
didn't know we had
I'm sorry about Dion don't be please he
did what he had to do and it's time we
did the
same
man should we
stop no because of a cough no I think
we're past that
Clive I suppose we
are yeah
uh I can't even look at them from the
front they won't let me so
cold so empty we're close aren't we it
uh seems that way but I don't want to
think what could be waiting for us in
there can I turn around instead of those
waiting for us at home can't even turn
around only forward now that's all we
can
do
[Music]
n
Clive
[Music]
hungry not much
longer they can't be but they
are
what this is the
[Music]
Nexus a Wellspring of
Life yours and
ours as we watch the world stumble
slowly to its dark
end it was here we pledged a new
beginning and now with the ether we have
harvested I shall raise my kin from
their Eternal
Slumber that
together we may Usher in a New Age of
[Music]
Reason this was never about
creation only
self-preservation you condemned an
entire world so that you alone might
escape death
alone him
alone
life I think I understand he n
[Music]
oh no they sacrificed their flesh to
become beating hearts of Crystal that
pumped the land's life blood from the
depths of the Earth under this very
chamber and thus would they labor
still long after their work was
done had you not set them
free you meant for us to destroy the
mother crystals H it's what you wanted
all along you have our gratitude
me in this you have served us well
you have both served us
well welcome
home
brother
Joshua Fu I thought
it was me but it wasn't my grasp That
Grew
weaker it was
theirs that grew
stronger
no no it's going to turn into an
Ultima he birthing
one
Joshua what
no oh yeah cuz he had him Tre how I
mean and now we can become one I don't
understand I guess there's two in
total
what
what now they're even stronger
but maybe with that [\h__\h] out of his body
maybe my Phoenix will be feeling better
too oh each wait there's
more yeah one for Crystal
[\h__\h] the one possessed of the
destructive flames of
epit and the healing flames of the
Phoenix this I once believed would be
ultima's true
form H but I was wrong oh oh I see it
now why you will never become ultima's
vessel I don't care just hold on I don't
care I don't
care do you remember the murals yeah
people once knew that Altima was their
God yeah that he created them
yeah and they worshiped him prayed to
him looked to him for
guidance in
vain in vain for he did not listen did
not acknowledge our will and so we
strayed from his path to forge one of
our
own so absorbed was he in his own
desires so driven by his own will alone
that he shunned the one thing that could
have made him truly
powerful Faith the same Faith people now
place in
you faith that you will fulfill their
dream Sid's dream of creating a better
world for
us faith that you will follow in
Father's Footsteps and save those who
need saving most C is a faith that you
will answer Jill's plea to save yourself
the difference is
Clive you chose to listen and that is
what has stealed our
bonds bonds that helped you stand firm
when Altima's pole was at its
strongest his power may be
absolute but so is
ours and so will yours
be with my light in your heart not even
a god might stop
us
[Music]
Joshua don't don't do it
you enough
Clive my body is too far
gone if the wound does not take me the C
will
[Music]
I have always been
proud to call call you my
shield but
now it is the world that needs
you thank you
Clive for being my
[Music]
brother
look at me look at me
[Laughter]
josu open your eyes open your
[Music]
eyes why why did you do
this
justes like me with
cobal and thus does the final piece fall
into
place the incantation primed
but one task
remains to
empty the
vessel wa
so
but the vessel
was this place I was never a
vessel
what I'm a
vessel but he didn't need
me he only needed me to destroy the
crystals which were the
vessels
no I'm the vessel I'm I'm the weapon I'm
still here I don't
know with me to the
[Music]
end even now you would deny the
inevitable
confusing
you little [\h__\h] that's what you always
have and always
[Music]
will going to [\h__\h] you up on this My
Sword I swear to Shield the Firebirds
flame forever
more play hinoto Orchestra version
[Music]
oh dear what awaits
us
[Music]
break I am
scared I no wrong thing sorry I'm stupid
does it it does reach him okay then it's
fine then it's fine conceited
f
ah trying to bait uh a Pera Frost
but nice
try he's
unreachable most of the
time you know nothing of
[Music]
magic yeah
try oh wait he actually his HP is uh
already pretty low I didn't
realize
uh
too
slow but of course there will be another
face after this thank you
Tassimo countless centuries have I
waited for this moment oh is it did he
not start this moment in which I might
Revel in my creation he started with
full HP surely he didn't to find it
profaned and
soon it must be cleansed
freaking epic epic character designs
throughout the whole game honestly
crazy he
didn't
what we just needed a change of
environment or what Ultima what are you
doing
unexpected how is it that your will yet
endures because it's not so easily
broken but but it can be broken what the
[\h__\h] is
that and I shall see it
so for such is my
will try it what the
Ultima no and does that even work now I
don't think that works now ah [\h__\h] what
is that too slow that how many how many
Dodges do I have to do thank
you wasted uh
thing nice
try he's almost staggered finally
will
trying to get some little damage in
there from a distance and should be
there
okay finally how long is his
stagger oh pretty good pretty good
pretty good pretty easy too easy too
easy can't be that
easy how many phases have you got for
me huh
he's got like no
[Music]
defense
enough perhaps this will break
you oh oh oh
interesting no and the one and the
two thank you so far it's pretty easy
like he doesn't give me much time to
attack him but it's not really
necessary
[Music]
oh is he down to zero
why what latent Force feeds these
Flames I sense more here than mere will
is this Locos it's love have
you free I've always been
free no I forget
it you are not a God you are but flesh
and Bone you are not one of
[Music]
us so many people pray to
me
oh I created you all of
you I shall do that too and what is my
mine is mine to
destroy I guess so
w but we are no longer
yours our Flames are our own and they
burn as you can't quit I fire you oh
[\h__\h] I was chilling I was stretching you
can't quit I fire
you okay it still works
okay
I fire you from the job of being our
God have you learned nothing damned is
the slave who would turn the scourge
upon his
master okay big boy fight I
see we have nothing left
to show me
[Music]
huh
we're in the [\h__\h] Universe
baby you little
[Music]
[\h__\h] even then oh stag bar goes down
easily
submit yes
daddy
I apologize I
[Music]
apologize how's he letting me do this
damn he's the one submitting to
[Music]
me who's your daddy
now
ow
[Music]
oh can't Dodge [\h__\h]
uh what the [\h__\h] why is he he's like so
mad what okay oh one more oh one one
more oh one more
okay you best
me can he
chill
yeah oh [\h__\h] I forgot you have to like
stay on it huh you have to stay on the
attack
do you have to stay on it and then
release it instead of [\h__\h] it's been a
while oh
well bow before
[Music]
me
uh uh
help what is he waiting for now is he
waiting for
me
my the reason my Dodges are not so
accurate I think is because it's hard to
tell how far away you are and like you
know how far away his attacks are
us with fire shall fire be
red hard to tell anything really
yeah uh okay oh wait H he's too far for
that to hit huh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] hey let me go to
you can I I'm going to fail I don't
understand
this am I too late he's already like
about to
count
uh can I hit from here
yeah
yum and he's still he's still attacking
though got to get my attacks
in and there we
go that's not even that much but okay
we'll take it you want nothing we have
to no don't unlock the purgatorium
please do not please do
not
30 oh he's counting down from 30 I I
don't think I can oh wait there's not
it's counting really
slowly
30 when's 29 or are you skipping some
numbers and not sh showing
me okay okay okay I got some stuff I got
some stuff brought some
presents right after this is
over I do
Brimstone I got it in the red I got it
down now guys I just had to remember how
to do it okay 20
20 do we want to go
there
we have to we have
to Granny 20 he
[Music]
says almost got my attacks
back
okay okay
okay
ah
go yes Your Flames was pretty close
where is
he he staggered now after I use up all
my attacks
man wait maybe I
can I got that I got that in
[Music]
yumy
only have three heals
left uh uh what's going on should I be
here
uh
[Music]
H did that hit
him couldn't
[Music]
tell well
that oh oh oh
yeah man
back
oh it's okay we're doing fine
is on your
knees
nice
oh not a
nice antio instead of a
catastrophe
antistrophe mhm okay okay okay okay okay
we're
there we got the same
moves the same swirly
[Music]
move
I'm just going to throw that out there
[Music]
yeah what's this oh
God big damage
time what is this oh 1.7 million damage
sh yeah keep on dodging keep on dodging
keep on dodging oh I got the timing I
got the timing down I'm I'm in I'm in
I'm in the I'm in the right
Vibe dodg like every single one of
those [\h__\h] stop
it
[Music]
sh can't be that much
longer yeah yeah yeah
lucky what happened I suddenly was
somewhere
else theatro sounds like something
Mexican to
eat
he
[Music]
moves oh [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] I don't want to
see that
anymore
what
okay he's done that [\h__\h] is
done if I could aim I was wobbly but
it's
okay ow it is
possible is there ELO
face is there another
one
no no no no no my will is
inviolable something is wrong you're
afraid you always have been wasn't it pH
three five phases ago were weak you
conceived us to prove otherwise but the
result shook you to the core that in US
you saw
yourself and realized we had the
potential to be more than you could ever
be and so you turned your back on your
cre
you're back on the world like the coward
you are you think you know me you know
nothing Loos you not that
[Music]
done
oh okay next
place maybe it's a cut scene fight you
know like those I just have to press s
Square every once in a
while no uh maybe
not
I have no more healing items
[Music]
left do I going a
refill are are we fighting with normal
bodies
again yeah I think so oh hey what the
[\h__\h] is
[Music]
that the ultimate Ultima form
Maybe
how many forms do you
have bathed in light I stand above you
my mouse
complete and you for your Defiance shall
pay the proper price an eternity of
Anguish you like that joke
anguish pain suffering you have known
none of these we have so we know what
they Grant has they bring us together
forms that makes us strong all right
okay noral F I think I prefer that um oh
my
God my will be
done petulent
child uh when do okay
[Music]
this should
help nice
try I had that activated by
accident come on come on thank God this
that this uh breaks
time thank God tramble no
no no
[Music]
no pment and
F Let The Tempest
range okay is that a prima breast that I
see
I will got to keep on zooming around
eventually it will
hit what the [\h__\h] can't
see
oh
nice here we go don't waste a
second oh he has a long
stagger okay the most embarrassing thing
would be if I would do ignition just
around
him wait wait
wait I would like to
immediately elaborate on
that what okay
unrelenting Kara oh
Kara
how C I hear you I hear you wasn't that
gap's
voice in my
[Music]
[Applause]
heart
R go on L [\h__\h] yeah yeah yeah wait was
that
s what
s wait you going make
me
Titan I'm so ready I'm so ready give him
out
man you're not M at
all let's [\h__\h] go you cannot have
this
power it is not yours to
take oh my diamond dust recharge
baby oh you should use
that too
slow Boreal raps inad of Bohemian oh
dear
[Music]
oh
good oh my God spam
much
yeah F
yeah
yeah staggered baby [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah yes more more more
more
wait wait for me wait for me
Ultimus cute new name you got
there want to add any more
attachments anything else you
want yeah yeah I'm dying
[Applause]
mamed I'm I was already pushing before
death my
boy wait who was
that was that was that my uh uh my um
uncle
Daddy no
yeah I I'm feeling ooh
Shiva yes Shiva my wifey
together together indeed
forever
I love that I love this
Darkness
unending so intense guys it's so
intense
Odin the one I couldn't figure
out onward my
son
what
that
death no mine is the altar at which you
pray mine are the eyes that look down
upon you
all and yet still you cannot see makes
me nervous you are no better than us we
are one and the
same we are not the
same no man might stand beside me none
his stagger bar was all the way full
again that's not fair I had him worked
down almost to 50% is my
creation [\h__\h] oh oh my
[Music]
God
bow to your god oh I'm on the wrong
[Music]
thing I will switch this out
the cuz I used up all the
[Music]
others know my
power nice
try oh [\h__\h] I used the wrong thing oh
well he's letting me do
[Music]
[Applause]
it oh too slow remind me to drink the
strength tonic when I get him staggered
not now but oh oh accident
accident but it works uh didn't drink it
though oh well when all hope is burned
away n will remain by Ash what is he
making what is he cooking someone must
stop him yeah good Dodge oh go
Dodge kind of hot up here
there H okay chill chill CH you can
chill you can chill are you here
yeah are you feeling this still not much
of a God if this feels painful to
you we are without
equal
oh
uh
uh I think I drank it I drank the I
drank the thing but I like fumbled a
little bit with
my
uh with my keys on my controller let
there be
light I still fumble but it's okay was
plenty of
[Music]
damage gu all what you on
foring come on C
Phoenix channeling all the powers in
me let's go
s I will not bend the
[Music]
knee I will make you bend yours instead
[Applause]
oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah so sure of your place at top the
world you refus to acknowledge those
below you chose to remain alone and so
you shunned the one thing that could
have made you
stronger pushed away the hands that
could have raised you
higher I do not need you you all
anyone and that is where we are
different I could not have made it here
on my
own I carry with me the hopes and dreams
of my brothers my
sisters and it is they who will give me
the strength to end your
reigna that's right I cannot
end I am the end oh he's not doing
anything is he oh nice
[Music]
try come on come on there's not much
left we got
this yeah show
him oh [\h__\h] wrong wrong
skill oh wait well wrong wrong
uh is he just chilling
now he's just
chilling now he's staggered time for the
final gig play he's got one H
peing didn't even let me do my gig flare
properly the world you seek is but a
fantasy F only fantasy here is
yours and we shall be its Final witness
see what he did
there Final Fantasy shall be
yours I
said it's
over
really now did we really I mean I have
to doubt it I get no
experience as if you don't get
experience from slaying a
god this must be the end cuz I have to
go and do
[\h__\h]
chagy sending me crazy
thumnails tell me
what do you imagine will befall this
world now that you have gained your
precious
Freedom i h don't
know but I doubt it will be
pretty a sorry tale of sin and suffering
hardship and
pain and it was for this that you fought
so
fiercely
why it's who we
are we fight we survive we endure we
don't need a
reason we are imperfect creatures when
we stumble we reach for a shoulder to
lean on when we fall we stand back
up we see the Horizon ever Out Of Reach
and still we march
on
certain the answers lie just beyond
it because that is our way oh
man my
congratulations relish this Victory
knowing that you have but delayed the
inevitable so he talking about the DLC
is already dead
may you enjoy an eternity on its
blackened
husk we'll fix
it
damn thank you
guys
thank
you thank you thank
you he better not come
back and my friends better be alive and
Joshi better come back to life as well
as
Dion Oh we God like we should be able to
bring them
back obviously that's what this scene is
for
right
right now we drop a tear on him and I'll
revive
him
o
no
[Music]
m
why are we going even further
[Music]
back
he's coming back
[Music]
right
right me the
music no [\h__\h] this
music the
[Music]
[Applause]
music
oh
what why he's absorbing him or what what
are you doing healing or absorbing
you little [\h__\h] you didn't
[Music]
believe huh did you just fix his
body it seems altimus power was so
confusing great for this vessel all
along so
confusing
for while I have
it perhaps I can use it to set things
right and see ultima's
Legacy beis dominance crystals
magic consigned to the
Flames I'm
drained there's snot in my throat even
if it means the end of
[Music]
me what are you
doing what is he
doing
these these are our
terms
is it destroying the
place but destroying himself in the
process destroying magic with Magic
how
Paradox wow smoothie
are there people that were on that part
of the land still
alive no
[Music]
okay
that's how you ended that's how you
ended that's CLI that's
[Music]
CLI he
lives did we really get rid of the
magic oh his fingers are
[Music]
Stone
oh he's getting more and
more I heed too
[Music]
much it doesn't it
does affect him now can he see
it he cooked
too
[Music]
Joe wait but if he's dead who do you
play in the DLC
I mean nobody knows that there'll be a
DLC right
[Music]
but is there an announced still SE
aren't you the most beautiful thing is
is name what are you going to call him
let me see let me see it's like it's his
baby little one got a smile for your
uncle girl not so loud you B what I was
only sh you scar it's all right they
sweet
[Music]
though if
magic disappears does tole
[Music]
disappear
what did that mean to
[Music]
us if you need a rest I can take him
I'll hold you to that and stop shining
bright it was so there your
now yours to do with us you
please that's what Sid
wanted that's what they both
wanted happy end
[Music]
please please please please please
please
[Music]
please it's like my cats when I'm
gone [\h__\h] you you can't end it like
this
no
[Music]
no you can't break my [\h__\h] heart like
that it's a bad
ending it's a pretty good ending
[Music]
Noy
chill did our journey
[Music]
end wait do I have to mute this
huh is this normal for fin Final Fantasy
games I can fast
forward some of them kind
of
what I was hoping for a happy ending
this is a shock to
me I
mean
[Music]
huh I mean oh it is sad
it's so bitter
sweet when suit died you were
prepared I was already pretty sad at
that
point
n what do you got for me a glimpse of
[Music]
Hope is that Joel's
baby one of them
or every
time no
will you light it yes
mother
with normal fire right
yeah the the come on natural way the
Flames of an icon icon have you been
reading that silly story again silly
magic belongs in fairy tales and fairy
tales don't boil
kettles a long time well
done now be a good lad and play with
your brother until
supper come on hurry
hurry
[Music]
right am I supposed to be happy about
this right let's play the saint in the
sect no I don't want to be
mad what do you want to play then War of
the
icons again well right I get he wrote a
book why I'm the older brother before he
died bamit says
[Music]
so it's going to be a murderous dog one
day
no no no no no that's not my ending my
final fantasy ends
differently create game clear data
what
is this just well New Game
Plus just I don't have to look at this
right wait
what that's it
h
what
oopsie ah mistake
oh
[Music]
huh
nah
well it's almost
midnight game is
over
um game was really epic lot of fun like
the story like the character designs
like the combat like everything except
the
ending I
mean yeah doesn't doesn't have to be a
kitch perfect
ending but but keep at least one of the
brothers alive will you or
Dion kill the brothers keep Dion I don't
know I can't accept the
truth you think Joshua survived cuz he
wrote the book oh cuz I was saying oh he
wrote it before you
know
oh
so I told you I told you I told you I
told
you I told
you and you were like no W it's over
he's dead I'm like but the music the
music is healing
him and you were like no wa he's dead
it's over Wawa
or H well what do we know we know
nothing it's not that I don't
know I guess it wasn't a bad ending it
was just
not happy ending that's making me
feel so unhappy
and I don't
know
after all that you know all that hard
work all those
battles it just seems like not enough of
a reward maybe I should have bent the
KNE to
Ultima no that wouldn't have been better
that would not have been
better ah
I think after this I'm going to cry from
stress
but
yeah
uh
mhm H your
cat I will
well it was fun while it
lasted the
game and now I go back to reality cuz
this was the Final
Fantasy and that is terrifying reality
is
terrifying
I'll I'll see you um I'm going to put up
a reservation for
retrospective
yeah
yeah there's a FY Clive is
alive
uh well but that is just a game
theory
it feels so wrong it feels so wrong but
I'm going to go now I don't like how
this is ending but I'm going to go
[Music]
now this is leaving me with an
uncomfortable
feeling game rating
a
9 9.6 out of
yeah I I want to I want to be more angry
at the ending
but it's legit it's I guess realistic I
can't take away too much just for being
mad at the ending the rest was perfect
yeah uh yeah pretty much I mean they
could have made the treasure chests more
obvious for me to
see but besides that [\h__\h]
perfect phenomenal I I really enjoyed
this I I I missed out so much not
playing Final Fantasy games all my life
that's for
short
mhm
no it was written by Joshua rosfield the
book not by
Clive yeah I have to recover from
this but yeah [\h__\h] I need to do so much
goodbye guys and germanes
in ah this feeling
ah
by
feel so
wrong thank you for watching oh eler is
saying what's written there please
subscribe no thank you for watching this
jrpg
playr on Final Fantasy
yeah
oh
[Music]