[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
so
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm hello everyone
nice to meet you hello to the new ones
hello to the old ones hello to the usual
ones
welcome with me i have
gouda hi
[Music]
i think the best way to start a good
morning is to scream
on uh out at the top of my lungs right
it's like a like a bird exactly
but basically i found this game uh
supermarket shriek i found it a little
while ago
and i was like this looks like fun
and yeah i know there's no game audio
right actually no
there should be it's just quiet probably
oh i thought
i turned it louder um but yeah i was
like ah
this game looks like chaos and fun
exactly ah basically the whole game will
be us
screaming um
aren't you excited i'm super excited
the game is normally like you can use a
voice activation
but we're using remote play and it
doesn't really
work well uh so we are gonna use the
keys
but we are still going to scream every
time we use the keys even though we
don't have to
right yes yes ma'am
good one question are you are you like
uh uh no no no problem okay oh wait are
we are we starting or is that
that's still the the starting stream
okay okay okay
gonna have you have you warmed up your
voice yet for a screenshot
at all not really hurt me now because
otherwise
your voice is gonna go like dead no no
it's okay
it's okay i got the fix on i went and
today i got a humidifier
so now i can scream forever cause that's
how that works right
i have a humidifier too a pretty big one
but i don't
know if i ever notice a big difference
really yeah it just makes the air really
thick
like like i want to eat it it's like
thick air now instead of hidden
air really you notice such a big change
yeah like it feels the hair feels
heavier
there's moisture oh wow wow then you're
actually
yours is actually working well yes i
barely noticed any difference but
um damn it give me your humidifier give
it to me
i want it okay hey do you have it on
full blast i blessed this
yeah although like i don't know it
doesn't really change much
i'm gonna have it on full blast it's so
noisy but oh well yeah
oh my my key to
a nice smooth fruit is
uh drinking tea all the time however uh
soda senpai told me that tea is bad for
my voice which i guess is because of the
caffeine
right yeah yeah but i put like a [\h__\h]
ton of honey in it
which is there you go yeah that's
basically
yeah i only drink the tea because of the
honey
yeah because yeah it makes me smooth
smooth and and sticky and stinky oh
silky yes silky totally yeah they say
you could avoid caffeine
chocolate mint spicy food alcohol uh
and acidicy food and dairy if you want
uh
no no troubles with your throat but
that's like wait
you mentioned chocolate too right now
chocolate yeah
chocolate i think so i'm pretty sure oh
are you that i eat a lot of chocolate
that's i think that's what they are
those are the things you should stay
away from
for your voice oh easily irritate your
stomach i'm not staying away from
chocolate no way
all right i need chocolate and also some
coffee
also uh solas empire told me and this is
uh
i will i will i will um give this advice
to you as well go down
she told me that pineapple juice is
really good for
your fruit yeah pineapple juice it uh
lubricates and green apples as well if
you have a dry mouth
green you are top informed about
uh making your throat smooth as hell
nice
nice okay well nothing new to you then
okay so i i guess above
our voices are uh lubricated as you just
said that wasn't me
i mean you mentioned that word you used
that no i didn't you did it
you did you told you said you said it
first no
you
i mean i'm usually the one who says
weird words
but this time it was you it was you
no no no so to further uh lubricate our
voices i think we should
start in the driving school right okay
and yeah i need to drive easy totally
i'm gonna control the the man
and i'm gonna be the goat i'm the
cowgirl
wait i think i still have to turn on the
to turn up the
game audio one second guys uh
where is it where is it oh where did it
go
oh yeah
actually let me let me change it here uh
uh on that that was that was not it
oopsie
all right so we have to go back one more
time
do the settings here and turn off that
master volume yeah is it better you guys
know
oh that's nice and loud i might use
sorry glitter you have to adjust on your
side
okay because i'm the one streaming
okay all right let's party
let's scream
[Music]
shut up instructor man we already know
how to play this game yes
no let me go
[Music]
thank you thank you
nice nice
you can't hear
oh me the game audio is a bit too loud
god damn it uh
[Music]
wait let me see if i can adjust it again
on my side at least
without going outside of the game we
turn it up a bit too much
oh there we go
it should be a bit better now this one
for my side stop on the target at the
end of the track
okay don't listen to him don't listen to
me remember
[Music]
we gotta do it again we gotta keep it up
[Applause]
we had a lot of problems with this one
um
one second i still want to adjust the
audio a little bit there we go
we had a lot of problems with this one
didn't we yeah it took us a while we can
do that about it
we can do it we can do it we have
practice now
we're professional streamers you know
how to drive
no no i actually don't oh wait okay
i feel like i asked you this before in
the mario kart stream you don't have
elections do you
no i am not licensed wrong direction
good night
they
[Music]
okay
me
okay at the same time in three
two one
um okay three
okay wait we gotta keep going okay
oh
you have to stop screaming no i have to
keep screaming you gotta
take your hand off the off the gas pedal
yeah
well but but but but but you have to
when we go around the corner that's when
that's when i have to be mainly
screaming and you have to stop for
a little bit oh really yeah
because it goes if you turn your head
around it goes
i think i don't know oh [\h__\h] i
controlled the wrong piece
well oh no maybe they do
i don't know i don't know i suspected it
i know
you you
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay okay i i'll adjust
i'll adjust
[Music]
it go down we can do it we can do it
okay um together on three to one tonight
i will stop screaming
when we go around the corner but you you
don't stop you never stop
yes ma'am yes let's do that yes three
[Music]
that was really good
okay hey that was good we were drifting
and everything yeah
okay yeah same technology same technique
yeah
yeah you again
one second okay and now we go straight
in three two
one
[Music]
i think that yeah the last curve has to
be a bit more
sharp oh yeah okay okay i see i see that
was amazing
yes okay okay three
two one
[Music]
oh my god three
two
[Music]
wait now i have to focus okay okay and
now
now um now i continue screaming
you stop screaming when we go around the
corner and then you continue again
i think that's how we do it okay three
two one
[Music]
and then one more round
go
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
oh my god there's some luck there's some
lag going on right now
sorry connection is really bad let's
let's wait a little bit
it's going to probably come back remote
play mine is doing a good idea
youtube youtube it's youtube
no i think it's the game
yeah audio is getting really weird
oh no well i i
i think if we wait a little bit it will
go back to normal
okay come on come on internet connection
fight
[Music]
if you look at the right corner of the
right bottom corner of the screen
and gouda moves her head to the left uh
yeah then you see we're having a really
bad connection right now
[Music]
but maybe maybe we go
uh out can can you escape the
the game one one one moment like the
i do that uh escape
escape and go out of the course
can we exit monster when was the accent
again
that sounds funky funky sounds gonna do
a brb screen and we can figure this out
now it's back to normal i think okay uh
but continue okay let's try to continue
oh there we go okay
[Music]
okay how we how do we continue good
hi guys right
okay are you and me okay
okay okay
well we have practice with dressing now
don't we
yeah we can do this oh easy
don't listen to him we're professionals
uh when we go around the first corner
i stop screaming i guess and the second
corner is you stop screaming okay oh yes
okay
brains activate it
both quarters we have to
i think we have to try to start out a
little bit more
um straight we have to count the oh yeah
i'll just say do we have to count the
delay like
half second delay a little bit yeah
okay okay three but who is calling the
delay
i can count the delay okay you lead i
follow okay three
two one
that was fine the way it is they want us
to do a
big drift then i guess okay we can try
okay
three two one
[Music]
i think i should i have to start
screaming
again a bit earlier possibly
or no no actually no no no we'll figure
it out
after 10 tries oh the ghost is so
cute it just like scratched its neck or
something cute
it's a cow goat yeah okay
[Music]
okay three two one
no no shortcuts and driving school kiara
we gotta do
exactly by the course okay but i ain't
got no time i gotta go fast
three two one
better
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
now we can try baby license to drive
let's hit the road
oh was that was that the whole oh that
was everything okay
so we can go yeah the bike helmet is
that but i was already
wearing one no is it for the ghost yeah
you wear
one yeah let's go the gold needs one too
can we give the gold a helmet maybe
and go next and then one right
oh i'll let you do it
no no
[Music]
don't don't hit your headphones okay
i'll try out you i got a hat though
okay are you ready for story mode
[Music]
let's see let's see what this game has
to offer
we're gonna i almost we're gonna give
some trouble to the supermarkets around
town
yeah what the hell hello
your uber's here you just you just
purchased me basically
um scream like a man
[Music]
[Applause]
video
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
that kills us
three two one
ah
oh
like a like a what like like a record
baby
right around right around
wait okay okay okay okay
[Applause]
amazing we took one minute to go for the
supermarket i mean that's quite
fast
it was so loud oh my god very loud we're
having a party wait can we still adjust
it
yeah it sounds perfect okay that's a bit
better oh my ears
[Music]
your dead friends wow that's really dark
oh wait oh wait that's that's it
[Music]
is that pigeon poop at the pigeon
oh nice important question did yeah did
a pigeon
ever [\h__\h] on you yes
well no not a pigeon but a seagull i've
had multiple birds poop on me
yes she's a lot of time i will tell them
i know
her behavior but i actually i know it
happened to me once
well did you know some people say that
when a very poop is on here it's good
luck
because it's such an odd chance oh wow
i'm so happy to be pooped on
should i take my breath if you want to
only if you promise that it'll give me
good luck uh
yeah but the poop might be a bit uh hot
because
it's phoenix poop so it's gotta be a bit
on fire
wait hold on artists no yeah
okay what do we have here some fishies
oh no this looks difficult oh no
okay okay okay we go straight tonight i
think that the rails lead us anyway i
tested this out it wasn't that hard okay
okay okay that's pretty easy
i wanted to go swimming it's nice to go
swimming
it is nice oh
[Music]
today today i went i went to a pet store
right okay
if you went to a pet store are you
trying to get a pet i
am i really want a little i'm a
companion
well i look a tarantula
are you kidding me i thought you want to
say a cat or something or a doggo
no he wanted tarantula are you kidding
me he was so
cute and fuzzy
uh i guess it's close enough to the cane
close enough
right it's kind of like a kitty it still
has more legs and
well no tail but still wow are you for
real
[Music]
did you like is there like any any
special
like thing requirements to get a
tarantula
i don't know it's just cute oh oh
oh oh okay no problem
you're not made into sliced uh sashimi
yet
just yet oh no smack says
have you ever seen a bearded dragon uh
yeah
they're so great like a lizard right
yeah they're
lizard they're really cute those are
cute i understand if you would get a
bearded dragon
okay okay we just gotta go straight it
can't be that hard ah
we can't mess what's up we can't wait
[Music]
[Applause]
that's oh it's probably they probably
did it did they seem like never mind
let's go
next super mangas why let's go
you you don't you don't like do you not
like oh wait did we
try i think we restarted oopsie
uh we go out okay let's go outside it
seems impossible nice
sorry we don't want to buy anything
afterwards now we just want to
smash up the store but yeah and a drink
trip shop is not good
you for real there's a drift shop what
what can we do
what's what what can what can we buy
interesting art
clothing oh oh it's a fruit shop not a
drink job
oh nice all these barbies
oh and i'm so distracted by the maps
there's a jump there's a jump we need to
go off the jump when i was a child
oh i wanted to get all kinds of cute
barbies
yeah i didn't get money like
[Music]
okay no anyway so
what did you play with barbies when you
were smaller
i mean it smelled like strawberries and
i like to lick it
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
again
oh my god did we almost die oh my god
okay that's part of it okay that's part
of it okay wait what are you gonna say
about barbie
and i i was just saying that i i i
didn't oh my god i didn't get many
um barbie toys even though i wanted the
newest barbies but i
we couldn't where are we we're wrong
after all we gotta go this way
we couldn't afford too many new barbies
at least i i i could buy some in the
first shop right now i bought some
some barbies what did you buy right now
did you buy something
i want to play no i want that teddy bear
or maybe
maybe that chair because i could use a
new chair for my butt because this chair
is bad that i have
don't you have a gamer girl chair no
i have like a what is it like a fifty
dollar wonder
oh it makes my butt hurt get yourself
you got a chair
i need a better chair
wait i think that's a close karaoke shop
we can't go in there unfortunately no
talking today i'm just screaming is this
the next job
getting some beans wow yummy that's the
law of beans
wait
the extra time thingies
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's just beans okay
it's b sauce
[Applause]
is that me okay
everyone this is not blood this is bean
sauce okay
it's beans it's bringing tomatoes
oh wait wait wait wait
it was probably better to leave one time
and then restart all over and nothing
happened and we're gonna
we're gonna focus we can do it
okay okay we can do it i believe in us i
believe in us
we have we know the drift ah
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
like half of the store but okay
i think oh i think i think the more
beans you get the higher you score
do you do you want to retry it or
if you want to retire we can retry or we
can see what else they have
okay let's go to the next supermarket is
it
[Music]
look at it it's like oh my god
give me your dad's moves
[Music]
wow
oh
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
ah
give me those lemons oh you want some
lemons yeah
what what happened there i want some of
that ones too why won't you sent me any
lemons
it's funny it's well it's not your
birthday yet ah oh that was a birthday
present okay
nice birthday present nice i i'm looking
forward to my lemons oh my gosh
actually when i went shopping today i
found even bigger lemons
real ones or fake ones i also think
the big huge the size of oranges and
grapefruits
give her some
[Music]
uh fancy expensive salt amelia salsa
food
sorry sorry sorry i lost my
concentration ah
[Music]
wait is it you or me ah
yes
[Music]
there we go there we go
oh my god that was difficult we are
still we're going we're going so
fast gotta go back
oh
it's like the thing when you're going to
the park and it counts you and it smacks
your butt on the way by
no no no
i see that i see i
almost made it we just gotta spin the
buzzer out
don't talk to them to the clerk don't
talk to him don't talk to him he wants
to box
us he has boxing gloves on
barry the boxer wait we can do this
oh my god we are um
i think pretty bad at this game
[Applause]
one star is better than no stars you
know we're just a little bit bad with
directions that's
uh no problem with that next no you love
some right
next door oh oh okay this is where it
gets bad
so about that one star thing maybe we
can
uh try to go to the easier the earlier
stages to get more stars so
yeah now that we're warmed up
let's get three more stars uh is that
the first store
no this one is right here
oh yeah
[Music]
okay what did you forget in the
supermarket i forgot to bring some
tomatoes
i forgot the lemons
it's starting out great
nice get some of those for this nice
[Music]
nice nice
wow
[Music]
ah
oh
okay okay nice nice up until here nice
ah
okay all right okay
[Music]
how do you say grill goat in in japanese
yucky yucky yummy yucky
yogi yeah cause yagi is gold and yaki is
uh
grilled okay we're messing up this
we should we should we should restart it
let's go outside again
let's go we'll be back
we have to restart okay um
okay focusing again focus yeah
[Music]
wow
were oh
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
48 seconds four seconds okay okay we can
we can do four seconds better we can do
it
yeah we do we just gotta really
concentrate all right
rain brain turned on
okay three two one go
wow
[Music]
yes
ah
okay i see he went straight for the fire
after we passed the mark i was tired
he's balancing
[Applause]
wait i got an achievement the definition
of insanity oh my god
it is indeed the definition of insanity
oh my god
[Music]
[Laughter]
no it's too late to go outside anymore
come in
[Music]
oh
okay
[Applause]
[Laughter]
believe in me who believes in you
i believe in you who believes in me who
and then believes in you
yes nice inception
okay
oh really
[Music]
[Applause]
sorry sorry
[Music]
yes
okay i think 21 seconds is impossible
for us
so let's get try to get two stars in the
other
in the fish market that sounds good
let's go
give me some of your special juice
sorry go that sorry i'm so sorry i'm so
sorry i i was no i was
no i was i i was
did you say that again could you repeat
that loud and clear for me i
i don't i don't i don't know what i was
trying to say
can we can we redo this and leave the
supermarket one time
i'm so sorry we can redo this nothing
happened i didn't say anything
nothing happened oh yes another stream
of
yara didn't say anything weird i promise
[Music]
okay
it's okay
[Applause]
who the hell are those people that's the
leaderboard
oh good job those were high scores 15
seconds
damn yeah that's impressive all right
let's try to get the two stars in the
in in in
[Music]
[Applause]
it looks like callie's gift from
christmas
that's right wait can we enter that new
store i thought we need nine stars
i guess we can go ah
pedo that looks like little
hey do you guys have lidl in in atlantis
no i've never seen little oh wait we
have to buy stuff wait wait wait
oh we need washi oh my god for real
oh wait okay where is washi
the soap excuse me ma'am
[Music]
where is it where is it i mean there it
is
nice nice whoops
okay okay let's let's buy those
groceries let's buy them groceries oh
damn it
oh no we need everything again
let's just buy everything
50 off that's a
[Music]
the washi the washi the washi you wanna
[Laughter]
wow
[Music]
wrong side i guess okay okay
the other one is all all over there do
we have then
we go off the on the way out and then we
go okay
uh
[Music]
do we really want to go there do we
really want to go there
[Music]
oh
i'm not there i know we need beans no we
need beans yeah the beans are in here
they're behind the moving platform
behind the moving platform oh yeah which
i'll go
[Music]
nice
[Applause]
[Music]
your child out out to the first sky yeah
for the first event yeah can you say
hajime
how's it going old school
parents would be proud of us
hi mom it just only took us two minutes
two and a half minutes
they let us continue even but i think
very nice
uh wait let's check out what the last
store is and then after the last store
we can finish it up i think we have made
enough purchases
yeah warehouse
offline warehouse what do they have
there
oh my god there's a comic sense store
over there
you don't comment sans the the
family oh the [\h__\h] caught the sun's the
fun
okay skidmark it was not the offline
warehouse oh
yeah okay don't we i don't think we can
but okay
[Music]
that's a little longer
is that the police oh oh is it me is it
me okay
[Music]
oh
yeah we're going oh my god where are we
[Music]
is
the road you know catch the police
[Music]
okay
nice
[Music]
me yeah okay nice
[Applause]
nice
we're right
[Music]
oh
okay for next time we we know how to do
it now oh [\h__\h]
okay yeah we can
[Music]
[Applause]
excuse me barry
do it
[Music]
excuse my language
through first then we could have been oh
wait wait wait wait
i think battery looks like bigger
batteries i need some new batteries
please please
please [\h__\h] here already
it's okay we can catch up with him we
just need
[Music]
uh
[Applause]
driving in the 90s
[Music]
bye
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
you scaring oh we did this to ourselves
let's redo let's redo it
retreat
[Laughter]
[Music]
how about we do a round where we are
completely quiet and don't say a word
that sounds like a good idea okay let's
do a quiet one we use our telepathy okay
[Music]
resting our
[\h__\h] up mate sorry
oh sorry
[Music]
oh sorry okay
ugh
why is he so fast
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
sorry yeah
[Music]
very nice
very
let's nice here for a moment
okay we're relaxed isn't it nice
these bikes are 50 percent off
that's a pretty big deal that's more
than a quarter
this is the one i feel it's the one
[Music]
sorry
[Applause]
we
the only curves you got gooda hey
wait
[Applause]
yeah oh okay it doesn't even let us lose
oh
okay wait did we just have to can we
catch him in the in the checkpoint
i guess we just have to get him in the
checkpoint oh really
we won
[Applause]
[Music]
our vocal cords can recover now same
um that that was nice and fun
that was fun so it's very chaotic
we did a lot of shopping we did we got
some groceries we got washi
and uh beans i think we are now forever
banned in those super
supermarkets restraining
thank you for teaching me how to drift
thank you
i appreciate it now i think it's time to
drink some honey straight out of the
straight out of the jar yeah you got to
get the honey bottles with the nozzles
on it like a baby bottle and then you
can just suck on it
i'm not going to comment that because i
think it will only
go really really really fast
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
goodbye to my viewers in german as per
usual
oh yeah okay do you remember in my
migrating
auf wiedersehen yeah
okay did i give them a nice auf
wiederseh in three
two one i'll see this sound
everyone thanks for watching this
chaotic screaming stream
we will be quiet now we will be quick
bye bye guys i hope you enjoyed it see
you
see you uh oh wait tomorrow on holo talk
oh yeah oh yeah yeah tomorrow
everyone around the same time but
two hours earlier than in this stream
yeah where is the guest tomorrow's guest
yeah see you guys
[Music]
you