[Music]
Thank you very much.
Well, the music garden has started tonight. I
haven't finished it yet, but it's
getting hot, so I've
been thinking about going there a little bit.  I
got my hair cut, right? Come
to think of it, I haven't had my hair cut quite a while ago. It's my birthday. It's my birthday,
so I'm happy. I
haven't brushed my teeth, but I got my hair cut.
First of all, let's introduce today's guests.
[Music]
[Applause]
Tonight we will be bringing you another gorgeous guest,
Music Garden. Tonight, it seems that
overseas groups that are a hot topic will also be connected via broadcast. You
can't miss it until the end. Yes, this is already
expensive.  Thank you Luke for being a regular. I
think today is just the first time,
but thank you very much.
Thank you
very much. I've appeared 61 times, so from now on, I'll ask you to do it 62 times, 63 times, and every time. Yes, that's it.
Thank you very much for your support.
Now let's start the Music Garden.
[Music]
[Applause] The
first guest will be High Price Louis. Thank you
very much. It's my
birthday, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.  I
heard that the information I received recently causes me to wake up from nightmares.I've
been watching a lot of shows, and for example, I've had nightmares like, for example, there's no
one left at the M-ga recording, or when the
curtain goes up on a concert, and no one is there.
look and wake up  When you
cry,
when you cry, when you call your manager, that's what it's
like. Manager, isn't that a big deal? You call me after you wake up, and she says
ok,
yoshi. She sleeps like a mother. Do you have nightmares lately?  I don't see it, I don't see it, I don't see it. Do you
dream?
Famous: I do
n't remember, Shirakami-kun.
Dreaming.
Of course I dream.
[Music] The most
famous thing I saw recently was that I was in the mountains,
picking mushrooms that I don't understand.  I
don't know. I
think I'll go have a dream interpretation. I'll go back later and make adjustments.
Okay, that's it. Rui Takamine
will perform his very popular cover song, Loveka. Please stand by.
Thank you.
[Applause] You
don't remember your dreams. You
weren't in a deep sleep. That's a good thing
.
Well, it's popular among young people. It
's on Wikipedia.
How many times has this happened? I'll
check with the manager later.
Okay, let's check. Okay, I'm
ready, so let's go. Okay, let's
go. Rui Takamine's love song.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music]  Will my
unexplored
feelings change? Will they change?
[Music] If it's
too sweet, I
won't let you lie, and the love that's elaborated on. Or should I start writing it down?
The art that was waiting within reach
[Music]
Surrounded by a frighteningly evolutionary level, la la
la la la la la, my wishes are launched and delivered in a whisper,
yet the light is
already about half of it My
uncivilized
feelings change
[Music]
Or
[Music] La
la la la la la man capi? A
love affair made up of lies, no, no,
no  Or, why don't you write it down? It'll
be painful to wait at a distance that you can't reach. Is it a
bug, a bug, a bug? It's
fallen.
If we meet at a distance that can reach you and it's surprising
[Music]  La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
[music]  Apparently they didn't have enough
microphones, so I didn't have mine. I
looked around and saw that everyone was full of animals, which
was nice.
There were people with dogs and sushi ram con con con leg, which seems like an ingredient.
Yo, would you like to
eat lamb
? It's delicious, isn't it
? You'll be able to perform the song, right? Yes, I
was a little concerned about how delicious it looked,
but I hope everyone in front of the screen will be excited as well.
Yes, then please
stand by. [Applause] I think you'll be
able to eat more than you think. The most popular thing to eat there is
the lamb. I
think it's delicious. The ramsam
is delicious.
After this, do you want to go out for a bite to eat?
Yes, then,
let's go and enjoy the week at Inu Takashi Shiram.
[Applause]
[Music]
From tomorrow onwards, we'll pass the tickets, and we'll
make the most of our dream days.
We just have to enjoy our days and
live.
Yeah, let's go. We've just started
thinking longingly about each day. I've gotten used to the practice.
The smile I put on is always
careful. It's very important. I'll look at my plans starting tomorrow night.
So, let's think about it on Friday, let's break down the wall with freedom, pull it
out, and our hearts become
cloudy.If we give up on the hearts that walk by, that's
okay.Let's take it easy, there's still sun and moon
left tomorrow, so let's turn around and cherish the days of Sunday dreams.  Let's
go.
Starting tomorrow, let's
enjoy each day and live.
[Music] There's
nothing I can do anymore. There's so
much to do, I'm toast. I'll sleep four hours a day,
pour in my physical strength every day, and become an adult.
After 35 episodes,
what do we look like? We've become cool adults.
Our hearts are clouded. We love each other.
Take it slow, don't stop. Someday we'll
be free. We'll definitely be together
again tomorrow.  Tickets to Sunday Let's
cherish the days of our dreams
Starting tomorrow, we'll find them again, so
please enjoy the days and live
[Music] Every
day repeats, and this feeling with nowhere to
go goes around and around, spinning
around in a dizzying pace.
Starting tomorrow,
let's cherish the days of our dreams.
Since we want to live and enjoy each day, tomorrow
is another day.
Let's cherish the days of our dreams.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music]  ] I
think I flew too high Even if it starts raining again,
I'll
protect you, so I'll fly ahead. I
don't know if I'll be waiting for you in the future.
As long as I'm with you, I'll
go anywhere. The three of us from SSS
will continue to support you. Thank you very much for your support.  Looks like it's going to
appear.
What does SSS mean? It
comes from the initials, and it
's a sexy, sensitive warrior. Does it
have any sexy episodes? No, that
's right. It's a bit location.
When these three collaborated on Chocolat,
at the chocolate house. Well, these three  I'm really
sorry, but I
can't really say anything here.
[Laughs] I see
. So, that Marin-san,
Marin-san, too.
Oh, hey, that day I was allowed to do something from an erotic book,
but I did something that I can't talk about,
so I won't go into
details on this show.I
brought it with me.
[Music] Do
you want to do it?I'm fine with it.Listen
to the song.  After we hear about it, Pol-
san will also make a decision, so we'll be performing a
sexy song tonight,
right?
It's a song that's perfect for us, who are already really sexy, so we're
going to make you guys fall in love with it.  I think so  So
melodious, so melodious, if I say so myself, sexy so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so 'so sexy, so sexy.
Well
then, let's go to SSS in style
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] My
nerves are already
drowning in eating everything, so I think I'll take my heart and push it in my mouth
[Music]
[Music] I
don't need everything I don't need anything I don't need Calm
ambition Satisfaction is
not there I can see it
It's up to you to do what you want I
won't do anything I'll do it as long as I'm happy than anyone else You
see, there's nothing in this world
[Music]  ] It's
not the time to be small.
[Music] I
wanted it. Does it feel good
?
[Music]
[Applause]
Okay, next we'll split the bill. Thank you.  You
shared a cream puff with me.I
wonder
if it's okay to spoil me.I wonder if that's the key to maintaining a good relationship.But we
meet almost every week.I
don't really say anything about it.
But I thought we got along well after all.Okay, I'll
ask you to stand by for today's amazing cooperativeness and trainability.Thank you very much.
[Music]
[Applause]
I think the female executives in Tokyo are a bit too strong.  hey
Well,
since the relationship between subordinates and subordinates ends, I
wonder who is actually superior.In
terms of power, the demon is the better one, but
Ayame-san is still a little
young, so it's still
cream puffs, cream puffs.  I'm in a good mood,
don't you think? Well
then, let's go. I'm sure there are many people who wanted to listen to this song with these two.
Turing love with a demonic feeling.
Ah
[Music] I
don't understand the weather of love.
[Music]
Time Evidence
[Music] I
want to prove my course today It's an invisible impossibility
What is it? No matter how
many times I turn around or bump into something,
this Mario of the organization is a condition for using it.
[Music] It's
like that.  That's what I thought, but I
can't find the coordinates of the star, and it's
not even listed in the tourist materials, so I'm
looking for this feeling that happens in a three-dimensional world, and I'm shaking
because I don't have a goal
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] The
baby motion is to look at the other person.  It
seems like the lighting is set at an angle that makes my pure chest go higher.If it's like the biggest war right now, then
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] [
Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
Next up are the two analogists, thank you very much. I
think people are paying a lot of attention to what the two analogists will sing today.
Thank you.  Thank you
Masuya
Did you know that today I will be singing Bug?
Yes, when I thought that I wanted to try my best
at singing, I ended up thinking that I really admired Mizuo from the same agency as a senpai,
and even more so, if we could sing together.  I
wanted to sing a cool song with you,
so I invited you with a bug.
Thank you.
[Music] It's a
big difference from before.
Lately, I've been like a comet, a senior, a junior, a senior.
There's a warm episode with my juniors. That's
sudden.
[Music]
In the warm episode,
there's a chorus that captures this bug.
Thank you very much.
[Laughter]
Please, thank you, thank you very much.
[Applause]
Well, it came out again this time. It
seems like it's going to be like a warm episode or a freezing episode. Do
we have any warm episodes?
Ah, the venue and the lights are pretty
warm. It's warm. This is the 61st time. Let's
go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's
take a bug by analogy.
[Music]
[Music]  ]
[Music] No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no [Music] [Applause] [Music] See you all
soon! I'll also be introducing the High Price Louis Birthday Commemoration 2023 goods.  It
goes on sale from 10pm, so be sure to check it out.We
have four types of goods available this time: Canvas Art Random, Magnetic Coaster, and Ice Cubes.Of course,
there is also a bonus for purchasing the full set this time.  The limited edition comes with a
bonus voice that lets you eat omelet rice with me,
and a postcard with my foil-stamped message and autograph.It
's limited in quantity, but I've prepared a lot, so
everyone who likes it, and people who don't like it, too.  I'd be
happy if you could get your hands on it. The
regular version has a handwritten signature that I
want to know. Now, let's take a look at each item one by one.
First, the canvas art. An
illustration of someone loving omelet rice drawn by Mr. Kuchiko.
This is so cute, isn't it?  What's more, it's
stylish, and I think the colors will blend in with your room.Let
's hang it up in your room and
eat together.Click here for more
random
magnets
All the magnets with cute cute illustrations drawn by Mr. Tumi
One of the four types
will be delivered to you at random. When you think of magnets, you definitely
want to put them in your refrigerator. All four types are
cute, so if you like it, please complete the set.
By the way, I
particularly like the drooling one.  Teha-chan-chan
coaster When you put your drink in it, water droplets form on it and you
're worried about it.This coaster is recommended for those times.It's
made of metal and cork material, so it has a solid feel, making it a
coaster that you can enjoy as a decoration even for everyday use.
After all, I
want to put a glass of a cold drink here and make a drink.
So, I
need ice for the gate drink. Lastly, I
will introduce ice cubes.
Wash and repeat my ice cubes with various motifs.  The
good thing about Ice Cube is that it can be used.I
wonder who has the Kasako panel.That's
why it's Great, the
ruler of New Japan Pro-Wrestling.Even
though this world has taken the trouble to directly introduce Gucci, I'm
sure.
Go home and aim for a complete match
Hey, you high-priced bastard from there.
What's more, he's good at pro wrestling. Besides, it's his
birthday.
This is your birthday present.
Hey, hey,
princess. Happy
birthday.
Next up is this week's pick-up artist
section.  This week, a group that is currently attracting a lot of attention from overseas will
be performing live.
OverseasArtists I'm
looking forward to this. I
'm looking forward to this. We're connected, so let's connect right away.
Watch
[Music]
Everyone's cute, there are a lot of them, but
there are some people who were here earlier. I
went early. Hey,
isn't this the usual Louis who was in the studio before the station? It's hard to hear. It's hard to
hear. It seems like the reception is a little
bad.
So, thank you again.  Everyone from Holotori
[Music]
Thank you very much. It seems better
if we don't talk about it for a moment,
so let's introduce Horotori.
What kind of group are you?  I
have summarized it on VTR, so please take a look.
This week's pick-up artist
FOLOTRI JP A
global idol unit that goes beyond iden's national flag
FOLOTRI members are
Peacock Favoria Rayme from ID Takanashi Phoenix from en
[Music]
Side
JP to Takataka email
[  Music]
Ozora
Subaru A group that is currently attracting attention as they speak other languages and are made up of core birds.What we
will have these unique girls perform tonight is to express their brightness.
Nikkori Research Team's Theme and the World in This World There are
many hololive songs by Econina and Shota Horie, who are indispensable in the music scene. A
dream collaboration song between two famous artists who have worked on it.
Holotori is spreading its wings around the world with wonderful songs.
No, it's a bath that is attracting attention right now.  I'm looking forward to Tori's performance.
Yeah, I
guess we can look forward to this.
By the way, do you have any favorites? No, everyone had a fresh look and
was really cute, but
that's not the case.
However,
with Treat Box, that's already the case.I'm
sorry for that, but the
meaning is a little different.Group:
Nowadays, Mr. Hako and everyone else remember it, too.Thank
you.It looks
like you're ready, so let's go.
Let's continue with the 2 theme world songs of the Nikkori Research Team in Shoorotori
[Applause]
[Music]
Today too
Collection
[Music] The
smiles of the world
Anyway,
I don't mean it. Let's
leave for now. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.  Let
's get started First of all, the basic
master Change of clothes I
forgot I
have a mobile battery
Of course it's off and I'm here and it's
not normal I wonder who it is It's impossible for us It's the
best crunchy
[Music]
[Music]  ] My
heart swelled even more when I touched it.
[Applause]
[Music] I've
been looking for a
place where I can say it's special. Why did
you choose me? You made me fly.
Because you're amazing.
[Music]  I
feel like I can't lose No
matter what, your voice has been ringing inside me
[Music] I'm
scared, I'm nothing but I wonder if I can do it
[Music]
But you're singing with a face like, "What's the point?"  Let's
not sing, that's not it, let's jump in and
go to our world.Will we be able to meet the feelings of the world?I
want to sing, I
want to dance, so that I can laugh as much as I want to say.With
you, we can get lost in our nameless world, so we
can change,
as if we wish.  now we  I
want to drink your hopes up, but I'll sing about your future.
[Music] I hope you don't
think about it,
as I embrace you, I'll go to the world I want to see with you.
[Music]
Thank you to all the chickens. I
'll keep an eye on your future activities. That's
right.  Nekore and Music
Garden ended up with only two songs left. It
felt like it was about 8 hours long, but it's only about an hour long. It's
perfect, isn't it?  The latter two
songs were performed by the guys mentioned earlier.  I
made a song called Sekai yo Sekai. I
didn't make the world, but it
's a song based on the world I mentioned earlier. It's a new song written by Teko Nina, who made it,
and another song by Shota Kawahorie. That's
right, thank you.  I'm
surprised to hear that both of these songs have a strong message.Now
then, let's move on to the newly
written section by Deconina.It's all about
idiots.  First
song written by Shota Horie
Cry Two songs in a row
[Applause]
That's enough, it's time to turn around and
put on a cool look. I'm tired of things like that.
Leave me alone. I don't want to know. It's
okay now. Are you getting
jealous?  I
can't be jealous, I can't hear you, they
'll tell you to cover your ears, it's annoying, no one
will look at me, so just leave me alone and I'll
let the idiots who are just annoying crawl at me.  I
'm
actually scared that you're waiting for me again, I'm just a weakling who just barks [Music] Yes, yes, yes, you're always just fishing, etc. I keep my walls up and laugh. I won't come any closer. You're scared. Enough is enough. Are you still angry?  Leave me alone. I
look away as if there's no future in my life.
Even if I stand there, I'll follow you. After all, it's
okay to roll around.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's not
okay. If you don't like it, then...
That's not good,
no one's looking in on me, so I
wish I could just keep quiet about myself and say that I'm okay with all the things I don't like. I
wish I could think that, no,
stop, that's always my
goal. I'll say it again.  Kill what you want
and then forget
about it. I'm so scared of the idiots who are just making annoying rumors. I
'm waiting for something to happen again. I'm
actually scared.
[Music] I'm a weakling who just barks. [Music] I'm
being bullied.  I
'm laughing with my walls up, don't come any closer.
You're just being too
lazy. There's nothing I can do about these words. I can't help myself. I'm
laughing with my walls up again.
Don't come any closer.  That's
scary.
[Music]
Even if someone didn't break it, I
hate it even more. My noisy
imagination
blocks my vision, and I'm
always in the classroom writing down reasons why I'm miserable.  There
was a dark shadow on the other side of the road,
looking at me without saying a word.I
cried because I wanted to be saved by you.I
couldn't stop the voice.A
thousand times over again.
[Music]
In the middle of the night, there was so much hope and despair.  I
was the only one who wanted to forgive the ugly light. I
put on a balloon and
opened my eyes.
[Music] I wonder
if this is the last time. It's not surgery. I
don't want to die.
[Music] I
blacked out the answers I couldn't solve. It's funny anyway.  I could
hear it faintly through the window.It was
just a prayer-like movement.I
don't know the words that can save you, but I
called out to you to say I miss you.
[Music]
[Applause]
Last time and once again, I almost died,
clothed in the night of hope and despair, and
took my breath a thousand times again. I will follow you to you.
When I was able to love the light on the other side of the window, it was hard to describe. I
couldn't let it end.
Yo song.  Let's,
let's both  Let's
be together
[Music] The
living you,
following me,
is on the other side of the window. I'm not a band, I'm dead. I'm also a
talker. Today, I'll smile with my walls up. I won't come any closer. I'll
turn around and try to be cool. It's not
good.  Don't get tired of that kind of thing, just
leave me alone. I don't want to die.
[Music] We've had
fun delivering Music
Garden. It's almost time for the ending.
How
was your day today, Pol?  fun  It
feels like I spent an hour.
No, it doesn't feel like an hour.
[Music] I wasn't
really busy. What do you
mean? I have a lot of alter egos, but I
was able to perform with a lot of different artists.  I was very happy.Thank
you very much.Congratulations on the sale of the
high-priced birthday item today.Thank
you.Today,
after the cat, there will
be NCC distribution for members only, so I
think I'll give it a try.  I
thought I'd share some of the things I mentioned earlier.
Please come and see me. I'd like to
ask all the guests for their thoughts.
Let's start with Inutaka Assislam,
yay,
yay.  Happy Birthday
Yay, thank you very much
.
[Music]
Thank you.
Next up, Ayame-san.
How was it? Hello, Rei-chan.
Happy birthday, thank you.  I'm glad I
could sing with you. Thank you for inviting me.
Yes, thank you very much. Well, time flies, but
tonight's Music Garden
ends here. Thank you very much. Goodbye
[Applause]
[Music]