duh hey guys
hello hold on i'm adjusting my mic
volume there we go
hey hey
um i haven't i haven't unmuted everyone
yet but go hello i'm here
i'm here on this lovely morning how are
you guys
you guys doing good
we're gonna
we're gonna play a little quote-unquote
sociebaca game
ah just waiting for the okay
from the others
and then we go play
doing great doing better now thanks
let's have fun indeed let's have a good
time doing better now me too
now you guys are here welcome welcome
some queer flash three
that's right
[Music]
you guys hear my my little stomping
stompy stompy um
among us feet
a stompy stompy stompy
yes it's me running around you guys
can't see yet though i'm waiting for the
okay
i'm waiting for the a-okay
god to hear your voice yeah
let me see
okay
all right it looks like we we've been
given the okay to go join the rest of
our crew time to um mute uh sometimes
you even notice oh wow
that's the big green button
[Music]
i wasn't sure if i could enter or not
listen
well welcome callie
hi i'm here you're not the only one you
may forgot to start the stream um
[Music]
and starting one minute late doesn't
count
that doesn't count
it never has counted
they started like seven minutes later
we're all here
right indeed yeah
all right then um so i would like to get
some introductions from everyone and
dream up yet
is everyone are you
are you ready roommate
are we all ready yeah
yeah okay i have a stream going okay i
can hear you guys all around me
it's like binary oh my god father's so
[\h__\h]
loudly turn it down besides
self-introduction can you all go girls
give me a reason why you are not suss
today starting from amelia
oh why i'm not fast today
[Music]
um hello everybody i'm amelia watson
hello live english and miss number one
detective and um i'm not wearing pants
ah that's why you know
yeah i mean there's a lot of stuff you
can keep in there
precisely
[Music]
your introduction please
[Laughter]
proximity baby
[Music]
sorry okay i'm not sucked because um i
got a cute pet look at my pet
oh yes you purchased a little hamster
real money you bought it with real
i saw the hamster thing and i was like i
gotta i gotta
yeah
[Music]
um
wow that's kind of kind of weird
what what interesting
all right
okay
uh definitely not sus yeah your turn
next all right um so yeah um death is
real sus but guess what everyone i'm not
death i'm the sheriff around these parts
and because i'm the sheriff the sheriff
is never suss the sheriff obviously
didn't do it um
some people may say i i shot the sheriff
but i did not shoot the deputy meaning
uh i don't know what that means it just
has something to do with the sheriff and
i'm not i'm not suspect so there you go
how can you be there right whatever
you can't even spell sheriff ryan okay
now that was because now that was
because there wasn't enough room for for
me to spell it correctly
all right
[Laughter]
listen i am definitely
i'm the sheriff obviously
well that is very necessary yeah
yes yes it is there because there's only
one all right who's next who's next
we're going to get kicked who's next
no my name is fauna and i am simply a
potted plant therefore i cannot kill
your plant oh
poisonous powder plants poison no no no
no no
non poisonous foreign
no no no plant has never killed anyone
little shop of horrors does it ever i
remember that musical
um
suspects all right alien planet your
introduction please and why are you nuts
hi my name
is up everybody
oh i'm not sus because
um
[Music]
likely story
i don't believe in such you're sounding
like a sexy boxer
[Music]
hi miss it's iris live english project
hub video
singer
uh
i am very excited i
am 100 say so i would never lie which is
why i would never recess
that explains everything i would never i
would never do anything irish don't
trust me
iris yes no trash
iris that's not what happened to my fox
yesterday
[Music]
but i don't have to say uh iris uh it's
a very very um
good self-introduction while a lot of
people mostly just say hey my name is
this
is
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yes
hello my name is cronie oro
from
the council
and
i am blue
yeah
your senpai has stolen your color
right i'm a more royal color royal girl
okay
okay don't look at the color objectively
look at the color that's inside all of
us
red and flesh stuff
yeah
i mean she's right blood she's right
baby
all right then um uh wait did crony say
why she's nuts us oh right i'm not sus
because look at this i'm wearing a mask
i'm doing my uh part
in this situation don't get close to me
well i tried to social distance but i'm
not size because i'm doing my part in
the society and are you funny i'm in
holding
and that's how the cookie crumbles
ladies and gentlemen
that's how the cookie crumbles
rut row raggy
that's fine we got a new one
lol
all right uh could not
oh just kidding
here let me do it again
well that's not fantastic
this is uh what happens when you tempt
fate
ah just kidding
because it was a mistyped
it was a missed type we're fine
no curses
go back to game
stream there you go there we go
[Music]
just missing
new missiles
[Music]
i am the guardian of civilization and i
am an apex predator of the sky and i
could kill you if i wanted to
stop right outside
that's not how you defend yourself that
is that that is the most nonsense
introduction ever yes
but i don't want to so i won't
okay
but i believe
because you are so peaceful
those berry bushes sweet
i take it back i take it back um
i i might not right no taxi back seat
[Music]
hello
i am nina my ian is from hall of english
um
the uh
priestess of the ancient ones
i think
i think yeah sometimes i forget but um
oh i am not sauced because i'm already
dead look at the the halo above my head
[Music]
that chorus of o's was wonderful
that makes a lot of sense all right then
thank you ina
next up sana is not streaming but she's
here so please let us know who
[Music]
english council
uh it's been a while hello guys
hey
i'm going to take it off and take all of
you down with me oh oh
oh
that's really reassuring take you back
into back into the space where you
belong yeah i think you're a part of
really you should be fine you should be
fine if you get kicked out it's like i
haven't
well
i'm very happy to have you here sana
thank you for participating we're really
glad to have you as part of this even if
you're not streaming thank you thank you
hey
course of yays
back soon so we can all look forward to
her stream
yeah um
[Music]
and uh i am the one organizing this
and i'm really happy that we could all
get together 11 people is a lot but
we're going to have a lot of fun today
so let's get right into it are you girls
ready to
be uh
[Music]
all right let's go the crewmate
cooking
what's cooking good looking the sheriff
in the kitchen
no during the practice round i was able
to cook why can't i cook are there no
cooking jobs all right well that's fine
let's see what else there is around here
i guess oh the plank i don't want to
walk the plank
well you hate to see that i love the
cook oh cool armory
okay put away the pistols
so guys i was in the army ah
that's son of a
high risk let me finish my job
let me finish my job please
there we go
i'll complete my tasks i just wanted to
cook a nice tasty lunch i'm gonna go
haunt her the whole time
i'm gonna go haunt her the whole time
where is she
where is she this place is huge by the
way there's like a new map
this is whacky
hey
run
you guys are safe right now run it's
cyrus it's cyrus it's a cooldown on it
it's iris
so they're they're safe what can i do
there's three
who is oh my god hold on hold on hold on
hold on who is someone's really loud
[Applause]
i think that this might be quick
it looks like iris or bay
both of them
girl
this is a cell phone
no it's iris
it is iris
[Music]
but
maybe i don't know maybe reinstall among
us or something like that because you
had that before that's weird yeah can i
vote
i don't think i can vote yeah
i mean they're right
i was by myself it was the room with the
folder on the table oh records okay i
resorted to spawn
uh where did i spot let me look at the
map real quick uh being a detective
i i do not have not really played this
map um i think somewhere like in the
main hall
okay well me santa cronie all spawned in
the cargo bay and we were all by
ourselves trying to make friends
yeah they were already fauna and cali
were already dead so whoever spawned
with them there were two killers with
them and
[Music]
at making friends
i appreciate it
all right thanks for throwing me a bone
moment
thanks for telling me a bone
there she goes
oh my gosh
there's a ghost in the kitchen hey iris
hello my old friend
we're all haunting watson now watson no
there are no burgers to be made here
are you guys here yeah hi
they made the wrong decision hi
oh what a shame
what a shame they that they killed you
when you're so when you're so innocent
you're interesting yeah
wow oh my god
oh my god how did she do that to me i
thought we could do a double kill
oh
she threw you out huh
we both blamed the guru i think it would
have worked it was just like i have to
make some volume adjustments on me there
we go this is why the relationship does
not work okay watson no you can't we're
here
wait i don't think she can hear us if we
scream
[Music]
they have to do those i'm gonna do other
tasks make myself useful
[Music]
i'm dead already oh boy
yeah like you'd be any help iris
you don't want him to win this is
reminding me of henry stickman
[Music]
oh boy
[Laughter]
seems tough huh the drama
got a lot of issues going on let me
check the map that's the thing that we
can do yeah
let's see all right so there's some
stuff close by
down here
i'll get the hang of this game
i can go through walls that's right
we can open it down here together all
right shower time is this a theater is
this a fighter right now yeah
develop as it goes you can develop some
photos take a little shower
see there's me completing tasks
from the other don't say those words
into my ear crony i swear to [\h__\h] uh f
word
i swear to god crony a message okay i
see yucky i
don't say those yucky words in my ears
i don't want to hear them crony
i don't want to hear them
you know
fix the lights oh they have to fix some
[\h__\h]
let me look at my map again
yeah they're in trouble
oh meeting room i can do something there
all right it's useful
about the code somewhere else
all right all right gotcha
it's gotta be somewhere else
let's see
oh
go to the lounge for now
hey why'd i lose all my hats and [\h__\h] oh
probably because i'm dead
oh i hear them
what is what is crony and what are
cronie and gura doing in the bathroom
together that's kind of weird
that makes me feel uncomfortable
wouldn't it be cool if like the ghosts
could connect at a very certain point
haunting your goal
[Music]
finish your tasks to win
oh sheriff i need to quit playing around
yeah yeah yeah howdy howdy duty
oh son is dead
yes i am maybe maybe you know you can't
do [\h__\h] from doing the test you can't do
[\h__\h] to me now iris you can't do
anything to me you can't do anything
we're both ghosts
and i have iron focus
because iris
we have a bit of a a relationship um she
took my life and i didn't think that was
really cool cash money um especially
like gucci
i wasn't really cool with that no no
we're gucci we're good she's right there
that's a word for it
and here we go there's sana
i have found this um but i have
absolutely no clues because i was
running around a while here and i
haven't i met no one i'm on the cruise
side i guess i'm not i'm not right you
were seen i'm not asana i'm not amazing
i'm abandoning
guys
[Music]
but i think that's something that an
imposter can do like show
uh shall we do the way that
they can fake that acting like you're
part of the crew anyway uh
i think crony can vouch for me that i'm
not obsessed right crony what do you
think i mustn't look at me well i i know
that once and and so it's so funny it's
definitely safe because the killings
took place when uh all of us were still
around it's bae people who are
considered suspicious to me would be
bae or chiara
it is literally bae yeah girl grace
definitely
[Music]
then we'll just check um we should end
the game earlier i'm gonna check uh bay
first and see if the uh
i think that's us i don't know who to
vote for
i don't know
the whole way like how amelia is trying
to control this whole room makes itself
to me
no no no watson's definitely in the
clear because i was with i can't type
that song
i can't do my book now
that's
i feel like if it wasn't based you'd i
was cleaning my guts out of the toilet i
couldn't sleep
i thought it was a kid with a glomping
i can't with that [\h__\h]
oh this is weird
[Laughter]
oh this is not great
this is not good
let's see all right can't get distracted
from my tasks
so let's follow the arrows and go do the
tasks
you can't do anything with this
i know oh i see not a huddle
all right
we just gotta wait it out
can i get a signal
where's the wi-fi
i'll wait all day
okay next hey kiara
good luck to you i'm gonna finish my
tasks now
all right how does this do hickey work
there we go oh that's an easy one
[Music]
oh that was a good high note that you
hit right there
i still don't really know what the code
oh duh you silly i can't believe you
didn't see this before
oh my tummy is rambling
all right uh security rewind tapes
there's security all the way down
alrighty aha
oh boy
i finished them now i'm just gonna go f
with people
dummies
oh finished all my tasks uh
oh
good good sheriff yep now we're just
waiting on everyone else gonna play some
pool stand on can i haunt some people in
the toilets
task master sheriff always completes her
tasks
everyone knows that hey girls
special phones
um
[Music]
that'll be okay i think it's just it's
just bad now with iris out of the mix it
makes things a lot easier
hey crony
uh oh gotta fix the lights i don't think
i can do that though
yeah i can't as a ghostly ghost
let me go find bae
i want to watch her antics
oh
[Music]
we all watch that happen in real time
yeah well no i saw
you i watched it all happen we can hear
you now
where have you been just now but no just
now oh my gosh
where was that
voter down butter down let's make this
quick though so that ina can come back
no no no no no no no no no no no no i
mean i was
bae in the surveillance camera and
she wasn't really doing her tasks she
was just walking my tummy is really
rumbling
i mean were you doing tasks
yes
what were you doing what was the last
task you did i have a good one
overrated so
i haven't really i prefer
you i wouldn't be able to it was
emptying the trash in main hall
i don't like
[Music]
um
i think it's between
storage and like developing room in the
question question question room
i had just seen kiara like right next to
me
uh we were together by the doors
i mean i was around as an electric
somebody an imposter
the one who reported the body too right
that's an impossible this is my second
body i'm recording yes
triple production all right all right
[Applause]
winner winner chicken dinners why am i
so sucks
[Music]
well done ladies um well done
oh hi oh my god i haven't heard you guys
in a long time yeah
doing tests yeah i'm sure they heard us
loud and clear though yeah oh yeah
definitely
um
it it
it looked like iris on my screen though
she as i don't know if it's king or
something
i thought we could do a double kill i
thought i thought we could do a double
kill no but on on
because it was iris and bay in the room
and it looks like irish
[Music]
connection eric and i'm gonna try to
open one new lobby okay
okay
hey
all right
with me
we leave we leave the room right
yeah
bye-bye
[Music]
now it's just you and me chet
hey what's up
hi
ah just kidding new code
no i i enjoy i enjoy our
chats but we gotta we gotta get back to
work being the sheriff you know sheriff
has duties
yeah we're in boys no no i was able to
get in in one try
same room
hey hey hey ladies ladies
ladies
yeah me too
i'm also the sheriff ladies
sheriff sheriff why do you keep on
sussing your senpai huh
why would you put the blame on me what
i bring the previous round right i think
it's because you're you
are so uh
experienced
first
and i always think whoever says it first
is suspicious uh
i feel like imposters are usually very
quiet like they try not to talk because
they don't wanna unless they're very
experienced in that sense yeah yeah yeah
yeah
people are usually bust into the room be
like all right so who did it
hi
everyone's just like uh you
you
you did it
oh i think that's you
oh no wait i think it's
[Music]
all right which one of you suckers is
the imposter um it's probably you callie
it's probably you
oh so it's cali
yeah it's me
is kelly looking yeah
[Music]
you come around corner crow
i do now
okay
no this is a cool kid's corner go away
[Laughter]
sorry about the fox by the way yesterday
yeah it's okay i mean apologize to the
waiting for it
you can't
i saw it i saw the blueberries
you won't get revenge or anything right
yeah it was kind of heartless she pushed
the fox down the hole
no no no it was it was an adoption and
you know it doesn't matter anymore right
really i'm gonna
because inaudible
[Music]
that's like a weird thing uh
drop out on
that's like um
that's just kind of weird
uh
what were they talking about
eating um
their own
their own children
did you guys like my little wink dance
yeah i came up with that myself
oh we're gonna go chat and discord while
we wait for ena
ladies oh hold on i have to
no problem
this is the curse the en curse is
kicking in and leaving it's ian's it's
ian's log because there's 11 of us
i'm making a lobby
oh yeah okay yeah yeah
you might get the same error or dodo
cause i got the same error uh when i
tried to creating the lobby before the
stream many times
just try again again again i'm here
i'm alone just kidding angels went to
the wrong way in this game
the better connection you have
oh wait my ping is fifth oh
the angel side of me is nerfing me in
this game
yes
oh hit the screen when typing code
that's right
yes
yeah you might want to do that is there
a new club here
all right we're having trouble making
the room too so it's just like ah the
servers
yeah um maybe maybe we can try i i don't
really think it's closer but let's try
maybe an asian server
okay we can we can try
do you want to try you know or should
maybe someone else you guys can try
someone else can try making it okay i'll
make one i ate in asia everyone change
up to asia
oh yeah bottom right okay
bottom right corner yes
oh wait are should we not saying this on
stream
i'm not saying it okay
okay
oh d
e and at the end is always an f
okay oh no one yeah
yes yeah yeah boys i'm not even in there
yet
did you get the first try yeah yeah i
guess it was just sorry though
and the black screen again just going
without me it's fine
no
i don't wanna yeah i don't wanna
yeah yeah
[Music]
it
this is a full en collab and it would
not be full without you
[Music]
yes
hey
holy [\h__\h]
oh my god it's [\h__\h] loud
[Music]
here is a little loud for me
person who's organizing this
ah it's a chef
hey guys
just trying to do my tasks
where should i go next ah
hey watson
why are you so scared watson why are you
so scared of me i'm not doing anything
ina was with me she can vouch i didn't
do that
oh my god she's so scary
she's so scary
what can i do here
is this where i can do a task
hold on a sec can i do
can can i make lunch
[Music]
the only thing i can say about that is
that i heard kelly's voice close by for
a moment but
that was like
i didn't even see her close by i only
found the body like a a few moments
later wait wait wait wait did you find
the body wow
bottom right it's uh
cause cali was i was going down to their
bottom oh i was bottom left
i was thinking i was trying to fold the
entire time i was down there i was i was
in the down i wasn't i was in the bottom
area but i wasn't i wasn't doing
anything i was like looking for a task
to do well why were you not doing tasks
i don't think you're done with tasks
which is i don't know how to play the
game i doubt it i don't know how to play
the game
it's a really big map
i saw her coming up towards me and i was
in the armory which is on the bottom
left side cali passed by me that's very
funny hahaha time to kill hahaha
me e94 and cali spawn together but kelly
went off pretty
um yeah
somebody laughed
how was that hell stick around with
anybody around but callie just went zoom
how is that a tell
well
i was looking oh my god i don't know how
to play the [\h__\h] game
[Laughter]
if you really don't know how to play the
game i will give you a tip now a serious
tip press tab to open the map so you can
run around while seeing the tasks and
that is a very easy task
[Music]
yeah i'm not sure
i'm not voting
[Music]
this collaboration again
well that's enough that's enough to
throw me out
oh just kidding what is that noise in
the background
for now
um
i have never been to the brink
maybe that's like not the thing to say
the [\h__\h]
here all right if it really if i really
can see show me the tasks
i'm pressing tab nothing what
okay
nope
[Music]
oh
can i
[Music]
here
code
oh okay
[Music]
i helped
i was useful
why are you so scared of me i'm not
doing [\h__\h]
why is everyone afraid of me
i don't do anything
oh these are like the little computer
thingies
howdy partner howdy ma'am
what
howdy ma'am
i'm a sheriff man
you don't understand how this works
oh
which one of you just closed the toilet
door
what the [\h__\h] was that
the cockpit
i was about to go uh to the very very
bottom
[Music]
uh
who used the toilet
i was not anywhere near that area toilet
because i this bathroom i didn't know i
was overwhelmed
slide the toilet but it was locked for
me
uh because when i found iris's body
right as i hit report the door the
bathroom door closed
you can
i can vouch for sana at least
hmm i was trying i don't know i'm just
lost every question i was trying to put
the egg on the uh the frying pan um
are you sure you weren't talking to the
ghosts
no i wasn't looking at chat i was just
talking to them so they didn't have to
listen to nothing
where were you last
moment at the last moment where were you
i was also in i was in the area below in
the bathroom i was doing the task where
you pick everything up off the floor and
guru i did see me there but i didn't go
up i came from the other side
someone's in the bathroom
who's in the bathroom who hasn't just
out yourself put out a statement
where were you
i don't know where it was
yes here's a better proposition
whoever's in the bathroom wait
when we spawn back in while i see you
come out no
ah
we spawn somewhere else
all right in the very beginning i
spawned with uh inner and fawful i can
vouch for
i just remembered
yeah just because you spawned with them
you can't vouch for them i mean i was
running around with sana at one point
lost
okay okay i don't know well found
ourselves for
are you guys really just not talking i'm
talking i'm talking a little bit
i talk to myself just as i idly do stuff
all right
i want to be useful i want to play the
game right
um
there's just a lot
that like i don't really know
like how to do
very dirty
huh
that was spooky hey mume hi party
what was that scream he like blasted out
my eardrums
oh my god you're blasting out my
eardrums
all right let me see
what else can i do around here
what else can i do
hello
there she goes hey ina
uh no
that's a one-way it's a one-way street
down there
mume is so afraid of me
these the forbidden bathrooms
all right let me see
i'm gonna be useful i'm gonna be useful
once i figure out the game
i just gotta figure it out i just gotta
figure out the game
here do we do we look at this thing oh
my gosh i cannot go on my task
[Laughter]
i saw something suss um i was uh in the
top right area that's like uh before the
wreck
right yeah around the records area yeah
and um when i was about to enter the
rikers area i saw cali so i wanted to
say hi so i followed her
and
next moment she completely disappeared i
went i went into all other like like uh
ways to look for her but she disappeared
and there was a vent right which are you
saying i vented what
you can vouch for me i went down to the
bottom and tried to go through the vent
and i couldn't
rather there no no there was a vet no no
no no no
no there was a vehicle
stop stop stop let me talk let me talk
let me talk let me talk let me talk let
me speak let me speak
okay
what i mean is there was a vent down
there and i couldn't get through it
because i'm not the [\h__\h] imposter
that's what i meant
no i went down to the bottom i was
trying to go to the right
i was trying to go to the right and i
couldn't but that's the second one
that's the second time that she says the
second time guys i'm just saying
kiara has
[Laughter]
[Music]
why else would you call this [\h__\h]
suspicious emergency meeting kiara
that's what's suspicious to me
imposter tactics
[Music]
you're doing a good job though
doing a good job i'm
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm just trying to do my job man look
i just want to be a good sheriff
let me look at this map
why are you so afraid of me i'm just
trying to look at where the tasks are
jeez
all right hold on not in here not in
here
nice and clean
yep
oh my god
please
is this just like how it's supposed to
be
all right
i'll get the hang of it i'll get the
hang of it
i will get the hang of it
yup i'm i'm slowly getting the hang of
how this game goes
holy [\h__\h]
there we go
and that one was me boys
found her in the kitchen
was walking around doing my normal share
of things which i normally what the [\h__\h]
i'm trying to get back with me
what everything you say no
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] i meant i reported the body
listen
i reported the body
i found it in the kitchen thank you
you're just you're just being like i
don't know clumsy i just found the body
in the kitchen
i was just wearing my share of rounds
and i found it in the kitchen
mermaid and sana this whole time so i we
i think we can vouch for each other oh
at the end right before the body was
reported we saw ina and gura together
um
yeah carol's with us too actually
yeah yeah
you're fine they're all fine hmm which
kind of leaves them
me
are you kidding me
well
trying to save her reputation by
reporting the body she killed trump why
would i report the one i killed
literally kill someone and then report
them immediately can i press can i press
the button
why i don't know why would you ever do
that
um but we also gotta remember we haven't
killed often imposter yet because all of
these have been
all right well i don't like you pointing
the finger at me bae and i think that's
suspicious so i'm gonna point it right
back at you
very quick to shove it off on your boy
i'm just trying to be a good [\h__\h]
sheriff
[Music]
are you kidding me
kelly it's it's nothing personal it's
just i'm loving this
this is beautiful
[Music]
i don't
wow literally
no one no one's standing up for me when
i when i like literally why would i
could have killed you if you guys were
alone but i did [\h__\h] nothing is there
anyone
who would vouch for cali is there anyone
listen uh
i haven't
okay so why are you blaming me bae she
was standing why are you pointing the
finger at me
i don't think i can when you haven't
seen me
that's the reason why i can vote
why can't you vote
because i'm so unsure
all right you guys gonna regret this
peace
[Laughter]
you're gonna regret this
[Music]
but at this point everyone had something
there is the sheriff well to be honest
guys i'm kind of glad that i didn't win
that one because
you really can only use the i don't know
how to play the game thing once now
there is truth to it i don't know how to
play this game for example i don't know
how to sabotage [\h__\h]
at all
i also don't know like how like when you
do your tasks i don't understand like
when you go to the place where there is
a task if the others can see if there's
really a task there or not so i need to
ask them later because that's a big game
changer so
sabotage
i can hear you now
sometimes you cut in and out
[Music]
yeah i just kind of need to figure out
how to play the game but
i mean we got some dead bodies so
probably could have gotten more but i
was very concerned with keeping up my
image
next time i should probably get a little
more go a little more crazy nutso kill a
couple more people and just like let
myself be a sacrifice for ina who turned
her back on me
ina
why did you why
i thought we could do this [\h__\h] together
i thought we could i know you can't say
anything now because others are around
you but you know i'm disappointed in you
very disappointed right now
[Music]
extremely disappointed
we've been here everyone's gathered all
right let me figure out let me just
figure out how to play the game i can
still sabotage so let me learn how to
sabotage things
how do you do it
when i press tab nothing happens so
and i didn't want to mention anything
about it because that could mean
oh is it because you're
the imposter or something like that so
who's not here
electrical
well good luck you know i guess
by the way i'm gonna save a few kills i
can't do anything click one of the icons
that's pretty helpful thank you
oh my gosh
i might regret this oh look at this i
might regret
[Music]
yeah there's a lot of weapons here
hammer
hammer time
okay
all right i'm going on the internet
how's the sheraton how is imposter i'm
trying to figure out how to sabotage
things silence
[Laughter]
how to sabotage because i'm getting
different answers from everyone and i
just i want an answer yeah just just
press this press the button at the
bottom of the screen that looks like
down below click on the area on the map
you want to sabotage the icons with the
cross and then our door sabotages okay
yep and then there's also that easy
yeah yeah you just press you just click
the icons so you don't even need to go
anywhere
no no you just click on the icons yeah
so you can you can basically uh playing
around with all the doors in the game
wow
thanks for the hell by the way it's a
remote control appreciate it yep no
problem what the heck no problems for
the sheriff than pastor sheriff thanks
oh well
yeah i would feel bad winning that one
using that i don't know how to play the
game card so i'm kind of glad i got
thrown out
[Laughter]
[Music]
all those times that i tricked you into
thinking that i was normal this is what
you get didn't stand up for me oh no
it wasn't me
now it all comes down
why was it me and why was it eating look
at this
kept saying that she was lost and i
thought that it was
suspicious
now now inna is also using the i don't
know how to play cards
[Music]
what was the last task that you did the
last one i did was the one where i had
it
[Music]
she's good
nina's good at this game
everyone votes for each other once my
husband really quiet hasn't she has
amazing
that's what you get for not standing up
for me
[Music]
what a shame what a shame
oh boy
and i say
i died howdy partner howdy
howdy howdy not forgot your goat
um
everyone
[Music]
oh right
that's right
that's right everyone got my goat
be careful babe hey
[Music]
wow is
pretty sure oh my god nina's such a pro
holy [\h__\h] oh my god
she's such a pro
she's such a [\h__\h] pro
she's such a frog
[Music]
that was not that was not your boy's
victory that was definitely ina right
there
no i felt really bad using that i don't
know how to play the game card so i'm
kind of glad i got killed but ina
deserved you know deserve that [\h__\h]
can i ask you i don't know how to play
the game
yeah i know right
can i yo can i ask a question the card's
not gonna work anymore yes please ask a
question
hey yeah so i have a question so when
you're imposter and you're like going
pretending to do tasks etc can others
tell if there isn't really a task there
to
no do okay you know what
but like if you're doing certain like if
you're acting to do tasks that should be
probably longer because there's really
long tasks that kind of can't stand out
though oh i see you were done
hey
[Music]
okay
that happens to the happiest to the best
of us
hey guys don't do that it there's never
a universe uh that exists
um where that happens where we say yeah
let's let's do that let's roll with this
mostly because
we want to play with the others
and there's only 11 of us so yeah
i'm set on mouse only
need to go with mouse plus keyboard if
you want to press tab okay
let me see what i can do okay i don't
know i don't know this game
thanks guys give us a statement of how
you were able to hide your imposter-ness
for so long
god she was very good i blended in with
the crowd you know even if i could make
the kill i i i waited for my chance i
was patient she's extremely believable
it was stuck around because it was my
first round
[Music]
yeah i got watson callie the performance
was so genuine yeah
oh yeah a little bit i was asking enough
i asked you not to kill me and you said
okay
that was those were my last words
was laughing in my ears the whole time
and i literally could not hold it
all right let's do this
oh i wish i was
making a tasty sandwich in the kitchen
oh there's no
task here all right so i was in the
kitchen i went to the right it's like
you need to remember every single thing
that you do in this game
all right let's go to the deck
because there are tasks to do there
oh i can do this
this is a nice easy one
god this game is scary
all right cool
oh there's another one up here
that was so fast
[Music]
wow
okay can you explain what girl did you
know what did she do excuse me hello can
i have the floor please
explain yourself
electrically
after excuse me taking off kiara's head
i have i have the megaphone i have the
megaphone yeah stop report cause you
panicked uh excuse me i have a question
was the shark near the washroom no
questions at the time okay i saw i was
then you were saying
and i just
go left and then i saw the guru was also
in the room that kiara went that was
quick right
you were by yourself in electrical
because i was coming up
[Music]
did i stop by the washroom i spawned and
i spawned in the place with the folder
on the table and i went right down to
electrical i don't remember how what
happened never stopped by the washroom
that's pretty much it
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm pretty convinced can i can i have a
moment to stink cause you didn't shower
can i can i have a moment please i have
no enemies here if i'm gonna scare you
flip-flopped her story she's gone from
meek and shy to very suddenly very
demanding of the room's attention
which could mean she
i have nothing to say about any of this
i was just in the kitchen
but then we can't get all our tasks done
we gotta do them tasks
you sillies we gotta do the test
we gotta do the tasks
i wanna do some tasks all right now make
sure no one weird is around me
quick
all right engine room just did some
electric stuff now we're leaving the
engine room
uh
going to the right and up
where is it is it in here hey guys
let's see
where's the other hello sheriff hello
are you gonna kill me can i ask you
honestly no i'm not gonna kill you are
you gonna kill me
because i cuz i just didn't because i
just didn't vote you out because i
believed you
so yeah well i believed you last time
yeah thanks
appreciate that i would also like a
buddy
[Music]
hey you know we have a good relationship
yeah no no no no no no no no
i'm gonna watch you no no no no no no no
well then i'm gonna have you
okay i'm just doing i'm just doing my
time
around i'm just doing my tasks i really
need to do tasks but i cannot be near
enough hey there's three of us in here
so if none of us were the imposter we
should all be cool together yeah
yeah unless she's on cooldown
guerra i can't be alone with you i'm
sorry it's just
it's nothing against you my dude
all right task complete i feel good
about that
i was just doing records now i'm taking
a little bathroom break oh that was
spooky the door just closed is it
because someone's in there
oh okay that was weird it was like a
ghost was in there now i saw the trash
can had a task that i could do
so
please i'm gonna do the trash can
here okay you guys protect me while i do
the trash can how do i do this i got
your back i got your bags i've got your
bag okay how do i create amina
how do i do the trash okay there it is
hold on i just gotta shake it there we
go what's up hey guys i just took out
the trash
i'm doing a lot of tasks guys i feel
really good about myself right now
i'm like really proud of myself right
now for all the tasks that i'm doing
i feel like a badass
the sheriff's getting tasks done
all right so what did i do i got the
records i did some electric uh oh
[Music]
okay
that's complete
all right next uh let's see
this electric right here
if someone knows how to play the game
well they might come and kill me
[Music]
all right there's that
uh there's some bad emergency tasks i
think they got it though
and if not i can go help him in a minute
there's plenty of time
all right they're going to help
[Music]
you fixing this thing you got it okay
cool
no you didn't
[Music]
that's kind of spooky i don't really
like that
i don't like that bae it kind of spooked
me a little bit the way that you that
you kind of came after me there
seven five one two one
here i just fixed it we're good
i don't really feel good about that
that made me feel icky
there's a lot of gold in here
is there anything i can do in this room
no it doesn't look like it all right tab
where are we next let's go to the
viewing deck that's the one with the
cell phone right
just being a good little chair
that was [\h__\h] scary
i can't move why can't i move huh
oh duh
god that scared the [\h__\h] out of me
okay we've got the armory was that where
i think a task was here
no it's the viewing deck sorry
i'm still getting used to this new map
so kitchen
it's it's gura it's gurah
yeah i kept telling her not to follow me
and she just said you're crazy
no i was trying to i was trying to keep
an eye on you just in case you know i go
for that kill you know yeah she was
saying she's trying to write nina
okay how is it okay that ena keeps watch
of you for protection but it's not okay
if i do that i don't know likely it
should be when in the very first round
when i reported when i reported ina
absolutely flipped her story and went
from the super meek i don't know where
i'm going to suddenly
super loud and embracing as if she's
trying to protect yourself oh to be
honest i don't trust either of you so
yeah okay that's fair
oh really
both y'all were a little suspicious
okay okay
is that you're suspicious of both of us
and not one versus the other that's not
enough she went to go do a task and she
ignored me and i yelled and i had to
talk just now
she didn't but she might have been
cool down
i think two imposters
probably
was because i kept bumping into her
every time
uh it was just three of us in total so
if one person uh left it would just be
two of us
and i kept having that situation
because you were being left alone with
ina yeah
and i wanted somebody to be no
my watch
um
okay so wait are we still gonna be
going together then are we skipping are
we skipping anything i don't have a
reason to people i don't know to put my
vote on gura i don't really have a
reason uh i'm just gonna i don't know
both ina and cronie were like
so please be mindful of inna
i'm just going to keep doing my tasks
this is close to the viewing deck right
oh i can do this here
all right no one's going to hurt me
right download
come on hurry hurry hurry
come on
yes
okay
here it is
come on
no one really thinks to come down here
yeah
but it's the perfect place to get killed
please don't hurt me please
holy [\h__\h]
i got a toss okay
okay please
okay
i think sana's okay
okay all right
good it's not you okay
okay we can vouch for each other that
was good that turned into a wholesome
interaction
watson why are you following me
oh [\h__\h]
oh i'm stuck
no she's right here
sorry
okay
all right i just have to divert
electrical power
okay i have like
i have two more tasks i have to do if
you'll excuse me i probably shouldn't
have said that around someone who could
be
oh god it's a standoff
i'm really feeling like maybe i should
have
come on it's not that hard
it's not that hard come on
why
come on
you've got to be kidding me
yeah that should have definitely killed
your boy but we're okay
please
thank you
okay now what can we do in here
cargo bay
is there any task all right tab see the
tasks okay up here
in the toilet
oh boy bay is dead
[Music]
oh no i can't
i cannot self report i cannot find the
report
bottom right i just want to say
something i just said guerras and the
clear have been uh following her around
and oh really yeah
[Music]
yeah and i saw her doing the carding and
okay
yeah it seems like she's in the clear so
you guys trust me now that it's enough
so i'm pretty sure she's in the clear
too yeah sana is also in the clear we
saw each other and didn't kill each
other so i think son is okay as well
you really could have killed me i think
that it's ina though
i mean i've ran into so many people i
haven't excuse me
is your name no it's not let me answer
the question thank you the microphone is
in my hand uh because at the very
beginning of the match i was singing the
berries and cream song and i went into
electrical and right down there in a
beheaded that person
the story's changed get out okay
story
nice job detective you can't read your
own handwriting it didn't change i don't
know
i don't know what to do
[Music]
yeah yeah iris isn't very clear
if it turns out that it's not enough
i don't know i still
i mean did you guys see cronie following
gura
i don't know yeah i haven't saw them
once a while but last time i saw crony
she wasn't with like nearby guru though
um oh so that was when the livestream
turned out
and
the meeting was nearby
all right well i don't know what to do
so i'm gonna skip freaking out
i have no reason to make enemies you
found the body yeah
where did you find it yeah where the
mannequins are
oh
watson why were you there why would you
lie
[Music]
you didn't accuse her of killing you
just said she was more suspicious but
now i actually literally see her
is my mic cutting out
uh i don't know guys i just want to do
my tasks
i'm just trying to be a good sharer
i'm just trying to be a good little
sheriff all right let's go to the lounge
we were so close before that body that
freaking body got reported and i'm
trying to um do my freaking tasks please
no more cards please don't make me swipe
the [\h__\h] card again i'm begging you i
don't want to swipe the card again
please no
you don't want to or you can't i don't
want to
watson why are you being so aggressive
let me see how do i get to the lounge
jesus christ watson
yeah i know
i know you're playing with me detective
all right i was unclogging the toilet
that's what i was doing
can i close this door to make sure no
one follows me
come on
yakiyaki
all right how many more tasks do i have
one more
i'm the task master i'm the sheriff
here let's see aha electrical all right
this is it for the red lights for the
wind
for
[Music]
i was watching the security cameras and
ina and iris iris leading ina behind
went into the room to the left of the
engine room and then only ina came out
and then crony came in and i said hi
cronie and then nina came in and i said
oh crony i'm gonna go see that body that
ena just left in there and lo and behold
there was the body of iris oh well
that's a very convincing you know what
it would say you and your defense do you
have any defense
no she doesn't lift the tackle
wow girl i'm sorry i doubted you holy
[\h__\h] that's fine i feel bad i mean i
never i never voted against you but i'm
sorry i died
i'll be honest i thought i was going to
um
not last the very first trial but i
turned it around and i think that was
good enough for this round
i lasted this long
the other imposter huh you gonna tell us
why is it amelia watson no it's not
farewell
i haven't killed anybody
[Music]
watch somebody stay with me next round
you'll see
[Laughter]
well i don't think it's gura anymore
because
eno wouldn't have voted against her own
team unless she's angry
like that
all right
i'm gonna finish this once and for all
howdy sheriff hello i'm gonna finish
this guru if you're not the imposter let
me finish this final task
she
disappeared
please don't let it be gura i'm gonna be
so sad if gur is the imposter
i'm literally gonna be so sad if it's
her if i was the imposter i would kill
you right now but you're lucky i'm
uncool then okay
oh what
she's on cooldown
is watson just messing with
god damn it watson
i love that watson just is saying
suspicious things
just outright
you gotta love that about watson
she just says [\h__\h]
all right here we go
done
oh again
all right
are all my tasks not my desks are done
i'm done who isn't done with their tasks
who is not done with their tasks i
finished all my tasks
who still got tasks to do
maybe i should follow people to make
sure they're doing their tasks who ain't
doing their tasks
are you doing your tasks
i finished all might
look at that though the bar isn't even
full
all right watson
where are they going
there's sauna
watson and gura are acting real strange
they're like having a little dance
together oh
i think it's one of them
[Music]
it can't be sana
it can't be her
yeah the taskmaster comes out on top oh
yeah ladies task master comes out i mean
all of you guys also doing your tasks
but good job everyone
nice
so who was it
i knew you knew me
yeah the task master
good job guys we got there's a time
limit
task
[Applause]
really seemed very innocent so it would
have been difficult to find out it's
women unless we would have done all the
she was kind of quiet though good ways
just keep quiet
i was really suffering with good adele
because
watching the whole thing unfold from the
first moment
[Laughter]
[Music]
i was
[Laughter]
right
yeah we can't even if venus is crew i'm
just like maybe we should just vote
oh
[Music]
does everyone have imposters here dead
uh check yeah because it didn't work
last round i think well
yeah
i'm i'm more curious about the private
talking vents is that working because
i've never like i mean i
all right
we're all ready to meet
[Music]
is this rapper music is that what you
just said
[Music]
we're done we're done
he's back
[Music]
no no no no no
that was fun
it's definitely me all right cool cool
cool cool
time to do some tasks i'm ready to do my
tasks oh there's no food i want to do
the food one time there's i thought
there was the first time we played and
now it's not there anymore
i'm not gonna be the first to die this
time i refuse
i was last time there should be an
electrical task right
here i know i can look and see where the
tasks are but i might as well go unclog
the toilets
we're really good at doing unclogging
toilets
no it's not this way damn it oh let's
see
go up here where's the where are the
toilets up here
it's this oh it's the trash
come on
nice
all right
we got another one down here
this is an electrical
please don't kill me oh that one's fine
okay
let's see next
records all right i'm gonna go through
the toilets again
and then
hey cronie hey guys
i just unclogged not unclogged i did
some trash
let's see
we're gonna go down
ah
here
[Music]
all right
over here how do we get over there
not that the showers
[Music]
let's see this way
i got the one to the right guys leave it
to me i'm the task master
i'm the task master
there we go
that one's fixed now let's see
electrical
i got really lucky last time and that i
didn't run into any trouble along the
way
but here
i don't know i can see myself hi you're
not the imposter right
gur
you're not the impostor right
no please don't kill me
no wait you're the imposter no
hey watson
please don't kill me
oh that's a scary room to get killed in
here let's see can i go up and around
through records i like the records one
all right here's another electric
there too
like a little swishy switch
and now the lights are back on
it's like magic
all right let's see how do we get up
there i wonder map
gotta cross a little bridge thingy
all right let's use this
all right we can
trash
and
another electric
i probably should be more cautious about
who's around me but
i can't help myself
i'm addicted to my tasks
oh you scared the [\h__\h] out of me
howdy howdy even halloween yet no it's
not
i just did a bunch of tasks though ah
all right let's see
i love how kiara says that and as soon
as you say that there's a report
holy [\h__\h] painfully oh
totally i can't vouch for kelly because
she's been doing tasks alone and i keep
on running into her and i can watch for
a good
a detective a beacon of the law i clear
cali and gouda uh from being uh
imposters as i was with them and bae
yeah or actually don't clear cali
i did see watson at the end i was trying
to open the door i couldn't open it
no the card key the card open
real quick point some fingers
yeah
[Music]
someone saw me
detective
[Music]
she's talking to you right now huh she's
a ghost and you killed him
on this extra oh no
[Music]
hello
yeah but why would watson uh out her own
teammate or skip yeah i think i'm going
to skip but i'll maybe just like mine
yeah
i'm gonna be really cautious of those
those two now
and also iris iris was really kind of
getting at watson so i'm gonna be
cautious of them
i'm going to be very cautious of them
gura you're not the impostor right
let's go to
why i didn't do my reading room
all right girl is safe
let's see we just got to go off to the
left definitely not girl
no one can stop this sheriff
i hate this
this sheriff cannot be stopped
there was nothing to do there great
awesome all right armory
come on
no i'm gonna do my armory task
[Music]
oh boy i found rey in the shower
that's a nasty place for a rat to die
i don't think it's gura we were alone
and she could have killed me but she
just went off and did her test so i gave
you a kindly howdy and i went on my way
through i saw kiara and we were on the
left side of the map so this kill
couldn't have been kiara but i think it
was the other imposter who might i
didn't even see you the other you passed
it because
where did the money i don't know i was
trying to get to the whatever it was
sabotage i forgot what was crash course
or whatever
i was in records but i didn't see
anything you were in records mm-hmm i
think i was in records
that was so loud
i don't know if those records it might
have been the room next to it i was
trying to go towards the other side um
does it have the
table at the folder on it that's the
record room
yeah like i walked in from wait i'm not
so sure anymore
that's not a good answer i know you were
talking i really don't know
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
it might not be records if you didn't
see me but i'm pretty i thought it was
records it's like
describe it
i don't remember it
it was but i'm pretty sure it was
records uh i've been there so
iris no it's not so i take my vote back
i don't even know where where are the
showers i don't even know where the
showers are pretty close to the shower
it's just pretty close watson who are
you voting for
with the huh i don't even know where the
showers are waiting i don't know
we haven't heard a lot from mume or ina
yeah
isn't it close oh i was all the way okay
i spawned in kitchen with mumi and then
i went to do my task in the uh the
bottom left thing though it's called uh
so our our suspects are iris and kiara
got it
i don't know usually you should
be like deducting
like the most productive
vouch for me right
i mean you didn't kill me you said yeah
we were up there at the top uh room
where it's really easy to kill people
blonde didn't and the shamers got caught
i wasn't very convinced by iris i was
not convinced
what's your problem enough i don't know
now everyone's suspicious it's every man
for himself on this here ship today
now when was a gym
i got very lucky
now then let's see engine room so now we
belong
let's see
yeah now gur is totally fine
but
communications
we have to go
here is this where it is
everything is broken now though
hold on
all right down here is it armory
no it's electrical huh
all the lights are down
i fixed the lights i already fixed the
light you fixed them
did you though
cause the lights are still off aren't
they
or did she get it
i don't like that why are you two
following me
no no no no i have some stuff to do
yeah they're both super sus
let me get away from them first then
we'll get back to tasks
all right now
hey watson you're not going to kill me
right
i don't know
watson's just [\h__\h] with me she does
[\h__\h] like that
i needed to go over there watson
damn it
well there's got to be another way
right
i have to go all the way around
oh boy
thank you ina why are you thanking enos
why were you thanking ina
nothing nothing no no no no um why were
you thanking ina iris
all right we got we know who else we got
now we know who it is all right
interesting let's uh i guess we'll vote
for irish first uh yeah
that sounds about right
what no hold on hold on
you need to hear me out right now okay
so i was doing my favorite task the
potty task right elbow deep in the
toilet
and
uh kiara came in and ena came in
tiara is now dead i was the one that
found the iris's body because i left
because kiara and ian and i said haha i
did the sucky toilet okay guys bye bye
ah and then i stumbled onto iris's body
and now is dead i was with um i was with
ina and iris and kiara and i left and i
saw callie and then now kiara's dead so
that will tell you
um
yeah i think that's uh
i think it's either who are we voting
for uh iris or inaudib
i'm voting enough just because it was
it was literally me
i don't know i'm trying to think
it was me tiara and ena and literally
seconds afterwards unless somebody came
in between them
yeah
i think it's irish i haven't oh i
haven't voted wait uh i mean i just
voted for ina though guys so if you want
to if you want to make sure
yeah it's definitely both of them but we
gotta be strategic about who we vote off
because if it's one for each of us and
then um
we could call a report and then vote
somebody yeah yeah true we have to get
birthday meetings
oh boy
[Music]
there she go meep was ejected
that sucks all right emergency meeting
i'm in the main hall so where's the
button
she's probably gonna go crazy now
because you know we've figured it out so
we need to be careful
[Music]
yeah let's call him i thought main hall
would mean the button would be here but
clearly it isn't so
all right well i need to stop bad [\h__\h]
from happening so
[Music]
left side not at guys
someone call a meeting
i'll hold it off
somebody call a meeting hurry i'm gonna
get killed she's gonna kill me
guys somebody call a meeting
[Music]
can you not call a meeting
come on
all right someone got it
nice
now let me figure out where the meeting
thing is
[Applause]
sorry we had to die
oh no rest in peace watching
any last words
um you got some say for yourself last
words that was that was fine
sorry i'm sorry ina i i totally forgot
about proximity chat that was pretty
funny though i gotta say
irish my like throw wrists
oh man what a game good good virus good
virus see you in another life for us see
you in another life yeah enjoy the
vacuum of space really we're not here
it's nice
it's yeah no i have wings i can fly i'll
be fine dang it
f should probably be okay
yeah well the shimmer pad never mind
that's dark um oh god
yeah well you know what um
regardless of where you fly after this i
hope you learned your lesson
to not to not kill people that's my job
i feel bad i feel bad yeah i feel guilty
um i will i learned my lesson i'll be
i'll be so
such a good i'll be a good girl you
could be a good citizen all right i'll
be a good girl yes all right let you off
with a warning letting you off
i'd be very grateful if we can i can
stay on the ship a little longer silence
sure but we're gonna have to tie it
together we're gonna have to put a leash
on you or some kind of yeah yeah you can
put a leisure on me anytime anytime um
i'll be obedient very obedient
so i'm gonna i need you to put your
hands up
that's well
what please raise your hands
there she goes again
oh we did it
yeah
hell victory
oh victory
that felt good
over here oh my god
all right let's mute spread acrylic and
go through i couldn't
but okay
okay
what okay
i muted there
and now discord on deafen hey ladies
hold on you guys can't hear them yet
hello hello hello hey ladies hello
that was fun
oh i mean you can still stay in there
hello
oh everyone here except callie i'm here
i'm here
hello sally and muto
sorry
it kind of gets questionable when you
get it three times people don't even
trust you off the bat
it's harder as the game's going along
yeah
three times yeah three times in a row
what are the possibilities yeah
[Music]
it keeps giving impostor to like the
same people yeah i was really surprised
that like you would assume that you
would assume that the reaper would be
like the number one killer of everyone
but i'm actually just a task master like
that
i do like the tasks
when i saw you callie you were so scared
of death i know right because i'm
killing you i don't like yeah exactly
we'll see that's the thing is death
can't die so the prospect of death dying
becomes a thing it's quite frightening
um i think we got a lot of really golden
moments out of this stream i'm looking
forward to all the clips to see the
other point of views what happens
[Music]
yeah yeah
it's really fun to hear ghosts
[Music]
yeah iris you almost blew our cover at
the last time i'm sorry i'm so sorry i i
thought you couldn't hear me right now
yeah i was like i was like okay if we
get a double kill like like this is good
but i couldn't say anything so i was
just trailing you around
yeah
yeah if you were on cooldown or not so
no
that's why i like i i thought we were
going to do a double kill too that's how
i was like around and then i killed
someone and then i see you went
somewhere else it's like oh no no the
double kill and then i think yeah
because all right
right so yeah
[Laughter]
but you know at the same time like you
know the senpai's i i can't i can't go
and kill my senpais right away
[Music]
i like that i like that way of life good
good one
wow okay girls i'm gonna go through
everyone from top to bottom again to
give a goodbye one by one and maybe tell
me your favorite moment from today or
your favorite kill or whatever so let's
start with amelia watson
oh uh wait what are we doing oh goodbye
and your favorite moments as your
favorite kill from today okay uh thank
you guys for watching and thank you
kiara for uh setting it up again and
organizing everything and my favorite
moment
uh i really liked messing with cali that
was fun that was pretty funny
no she would just outright say things
like like i'd be like are you gonna kill
me she'd be like yeah you're lucky my
cool down is off and like run away even
though she's
for me okay well thank you amelia next
up bails
um
thanks for coming guys i hope everyone
had fun thank you kiara for organizing
again so powerful
um my favorite moment i wasn't actually
in game um it was when i went to the
idol meeting and i
[Music]
yeah it was it was like bathroom music
all kinds of music
yeah without character management it's
just chaotic
it's even more chaotic when chaos is not
there and that's that's the sad thing
you're gonna have to talk iris very soon
just wait how what
what
oh i'm not wait i i don't need to wait
right yeah i mean you can
oh and yeah
right here for everybody really good
and a room
all right ladies now let's now let's
dial it back just a little bit
me oh let's see my favorite moment has
to be um when i was trying to hold up
the the cell phone to get the cell
service on the deck where anyone could
have killed me and i saw sana come up
behind me and i was like holy [\h__\h] this
is where i die and she was like okay
callie and she just walked away and
she's like no i have to do my task here
and i was like okay so we just switched
spaces and we like watched out for each
other it was kind of cool it's like a
bonding moment i was like oh okay
cool i feel safe here
yeah oh really
that was so cute yeah santa being santa
all day today
i'm just excited to explore yeah yeah
yeah it was really fun okay well thank
you next up fauna
hello thank you everyone for watching
and thank you kiara for organizing
everything it was a lot of work and i
really appreciate it
uh my favorite moment was not being the
imposter
oh
yeah i don't know i i think i prefer
indian pasta too yeah me too
be honest
um being impostor is just so much
pressure
and especially what the wants to meet
you can't really say anything because
[Laughter]
i wanted to get into that situation
unfortunately it didn't happen today so
yeah well thank you fun i'm glad you
enjoyed it next up
gouda how salty are you
i'm fine i'm fine i'm saying i was
talking to my chat though about like how
i don't usually i don't know have
conversations i don't talk like this
usually like accusatory whether it's in
a game or not it's quite like it feels
very draining uh mentally i guess i feel
yeah i always
like yelling at my friends
i'm not talking at all i had a lot of
fun um my favorite moments were
uh and i i'm asking clippers please uh
the various perfectly cut screams with
the proximity chat
specifically
that one round where everybody was
terrified of me and every time somebody
would walk by me it would just be blood
curdling screams
i would like to see a perfectly cut
screams uh compilation of some sort if
there are enough
you had a good one too
for putting this together thank you
it was it was my honor my pleasure it
was my pleasure i was very terrified
but i thought it was girl
[Music]
okay yeah thank you so much for
organizing this wonderful collab camera
i love among us to bits me too i'm so
glad i was able to do this and i i i
would go for among us like off stream
anytime if we had enough people oh my
god i like it yeah but
yeah it was a lot of fun and being
impostor was great pressure but great
and my favorite moments have to be yeah
killing a lot of people that was fun um
well personally for a moment that really
didn't have much to do with me um i
really liked how cali you know when she
found fauna's body was like it was me
boy
[Laughter]
oh god i need to be careful with how i
say words sometimes
yeah that was my personal favorite
genuine very fun game thank you so much
yeah she was obsessed all the time all
the time
yeah sounds like you're gonna love good
kills when you're uh oh
when you're imposter though
i was playing safe i was like okay if i
get all the ad girls and maybe the other
imposter can go on a killing spree oh
yeah that's right yeah all right when i
was imposter too i was like oh you know
probably i'm probably going to have to
be aggressive so that's right yeah i'm
killing and killing you
yeah
but i was trying to clear my name and
that was how i got out trying too hard
to clear my name but i'm just too
suspicious
yeah amelia just laughing a ghost in my
ear
okay crony next doll
oh
sorry um
what was i was i gonna say oh yeah thank
you
no no no thank you so much for arranging
this
oh
that's fine we don't need no problem
once again
yeah free bgm yeah so
thank you so much to kiara uh for
arranging this i really love this game
and
it's been fun i think my favorite moment
was
uh
well every moment was pretty funny but
whatever the
the proximity chat exploded whenever a
meeting happened
and
the first time when the meeting happened
everybody was screaming and i didn't
even know what was going on but that was
funny so
thank you for that
i love you have fun thank you cronie
yeah next time
hello
thank you kiara for
organizing everything everyone says that
while you're waiting
though
yeah
[Music]
i i'm blushing thank you please continue
uh i think one of my favorite parts that
i experienced was i spawned where ena
were with ina
and i turned and i said wouldn't it be
something if you're the imposter three
times in a row she's like yeah that
really would be she just walked away
i was like floating i was like yeah it
would be really funny wouldn't it be
yeah
just absolutely drenched in sweat
oh my god
you know there's so much blood on her
hands today
yeah i don't know i killed how many in
the last two games um in the last game i
really like that you know until they're
very good at innocence
well then
you know your goodbye and your your
favorite moments who who was your
favorite kill maybe
oh who felt the best putting a knife
through their stomach
well
um it's gonna be half
there's there's been a lot of good kills
but i think it's gonna have to go with
the uh cronie in the it wasn't the first
game or something where she was like
please don't kill me and i was like okay
incredible
score you just said
oh yeah
yeah i want to see the kronester i want
to see evil chronister
yeah
it would be very scary and intimidating
though because callie was every time
when i was sussing callie like she was
like so intimidating to me i was so
scared when she was yelling at me oh i'm
sorry it was right it's you huh
no it's you know you re race
your your okay and your favorite moment
please
okay thank you very much for organizing
the collab cara um i'm really happy to
play a game with you guys again it's
been a while me too
it is
[Music]
my favorite moment as uh
pretty much every time i heard cali
scream and now my favorite moment is
spending time with all of you guys
i wish i could hug you
[Music]
[Laughter]
you should next time next time you
should uh leave me leave me alive
because i
believe everything you guys say
she's so innocent
[Music]
all right well um
for me my favorite moment one i had so
many but i guess the one that stayed in
my head now is um i think it was in this
in the
round before the last round where uh
everyone was sussing
gouda and she was just trying to speak
but then like i was really
mad and then ahmed was like well i'm
gonna follow you to see if you're really
innocent and i was like chilling with
ina as ghosts and we were just talking
about the better curling
we're standing there together as ghosts
and then ahmed and guna ran into the
room having a huge fight like discussion
like
[Laughter]
watching a kindergarten fight fights
regarding playing that was good that was
good they were running in circles
yelling at each other it was so funny
oh man um but yeah uh um it was it was a
i'm really glad this all worked out fine
in the end uh you know i had some
troubles in the beginning but i'm so
relieved
i'm sorry about no no no no no no
okay
you came in
i'm just happiest that everyone had fun
and and no hollow ian scuff was that
present today yeah
[Music]
i'm sure there's some some among us who
are a little bit tired of this among us
game but uh i think with proximity voice
chat mod it made it a whole lot more
interesting and kind of refreshing so
yeah i agree with that it was a blast
definitely i'll tell you
this some time again in the future i'm
down
if you don't mind hell yeah let's do it
with everybody yeah i'm having fun with
it now christmas among us yeah
yeah
games we can try to yeah
oh
one more thing i kind of want to do is
like because i organized the ian id
mario kart tournament now that we are 11
he ends we could do a full en mario kart
tournament as well nice idea
eleven people like not twelve by eleven
is it just one of the one of the people
are gonna be bought is that what it is
yeah one of them could be a bot i think
or you can just leave that one out i
think this is
is it time for another training arc yes
let's do it
do it
well it is a past five a.m for me so i
hope we can end it down we all got our
nice cleaning yeah yeah yeah definitely
now
sorry
announcements
do you wanna announce something oh yeah
yeah yeah oh um i have an announcement
for next weekend that we will be having
another
um club
no collab
yesterday
yeah big halloween collab
details are secret for now but uh yeah
now you guys mark it down
[Music]
pun i'm just really saying it's
genuinely going to be amazing yes
amazing amazing
yeah this looks great could we sign up
with
otsu
[Music]
oh
three
two
one
[Applause]
[Music]
they're gone now
i say i say goodbye to everyone i just
want to give a personal thank you so
much to you guys as well for being here
uh thank you so much for cheering me on
i saw a lot of people in chat saying 100
win 100 win but that is that is because
ina really definitely hard carried um i
just want to say this game uh is not a
game that i thought that i would have a
lot of fun with a game that i thought i
was very jo-zu at in the beginning um
but slowly i kind of got to learn it
more and got really comfortable playing
with the others um
and it ended up being a blast i was
pretty nervous about it because you know
past among us games have been
interesting uh with your boy but i
really had a blast and felt like i
helped out especially in the last two
matches there so thank you guys for
cheering for me and thank you for the
big ups and yeah that was cool
yeah
i'm gonna get some more tips for being
impostor someday though because i want
to do that right as well
anyway guys hope you guys take care of
yourselves i've got a phasmaphobia
collab uh tomorrow
let's see let me figure out the time i
know that i put it up i just want to be
able to tell you guys
so that you know those of you who are
here you can mark it on your calendar if
you'd like phasmaphobia with kiara fauna
and bay and it's going to be 8 jst in
the morning so i got to wake up earlier
than usual but that's fine um 4 p.m pdt
and uh with british summer time it's at
midnight exactly which makes for a lot
of spooky fun i think um so i hope you
guys have some time you'll come check it
out and have some fun with us with that
being said guys i'm your mori hope
you'll remember me this has been a blast
you guys take care of yourselves okay
peace
goodbye
you