[Applause]
[Music]
e
let
[Music]
[Applause]
hello hello hello
[Music]
hello Mer Merry among us Merry Among
Us don't want get Among
Us welcome everybody to the uh Christmas
or Holan holiday Among Us stream we have
gathered here today with so many lovely
cute girls and we're going to have fun
choking and stabbing each other right
the perfect
Christmas let's go awesome well we're
going to um do it without proximity chat
by the way guys
uh because you know we have some first
timers here I think it's Advent girls's
first time Among Us
s first timers that's going to be
fun we're not yeah we find out how they
act when when they're impostor we can't
tell yet like for others maybe we
already know a tell but for these
newbies we don't know what is there tell
maybe that's maybe you could tell us
would you be so kind when your
introduction to tell me what your T
is please nah you got to find go that
information's classified going to need a
little cash money up front first I'll
try well okay then let's start with
introductions let's start with the only
one who's a real astronaut Here
Am uh hello Amilia Watson number one
astronaut
detective yeah I like Among Us so I'm
excited to play Let's Go let's
go maybe there's some new viewers at
this point who don't understand why is
am able to wear her own clothes in the
game and why am I wearing P's clothes
and is wearing man's clothes am do you
want to explain uh yes we have uh we had
a collab with Among Us where you could
get a few uh Hol live outfits and items
in the Among Us shop but I don't think
it's available anymore it was kind of a
little time thing a
time too bad if you missed out me and W
are P right
now I thought this was a keyboard slam
you guys are actually you guys are in a
room okay oh yeah okay I thought you
just slammed the
keyboard slam I know that's what code
looking like a slam Oh no you're giving
them hints you're giving the HS on what
the code is know and slam welcome to the
slam jam please join there we go get
some fertilizer on that who is CM
spam all
[Laughter]
right oh you have spam color
too yeah a Spam color that was amazing
nice box oh while we're at at's uh you
know bullying her for her name Callie
please introduce yourself so we know
that's really new oh yeah if you insist
me a s it's me Mory Kip H live english's
hardworking
Shinigami uh I'm in a place with very
terrible internet so I can't stream my
POV but I'm very excited to be here with
all of these lovely ladies as the
sheriff completing my tasks and making
sure that we win the day let's go yes he
wouldn't kill and she is now known Asal
my
jobal but yeah I'm so happy you're
joining even though you can't like
stream properly thank you so much dead
beats they train well I wanted to show
off my new skills that the dead beats
have fairly
recently got to watch out she's good at
the game oh oh no only thanks to the
dead Beast you just ask us how you kill
people in this
game okay I guess I didn't help at all
that you played it recently it was
unhelpful well okay moving on to fauna
where is she where is she I can't find
her she's hiding in the corner in you
can't vote me as the Imposter if I'm
hiding
right there from H live English promise
hello hello I'm here does it feel does
it feel like normal now like it still
feels weird to me to hear that
introduction
promise yeah I think so fresh still it
is it is still pretty fresh fresh it I
think yeah the boat not boats I feel
like everyone's been traumatized by
boats what's this trend in the whole lot
English of watching school days what's
no it was something we wanted to do
since last year we finally got it
everyone about the
tree yes the
tree why you like it there's a staircase
did you know there's a staircase in
there I know I know now
therea
I have no idea what these girl are
talking about good I'm so confused you
don't need it too cursed yeah it's nice
that everybody is having fun school days
and all that fun a jolly season it is
great piece of Cinema yeah yeah all
right Iris our number one Christmas
lover hello yes number one Christmas
lover here hiis it's Iris from H live
English promise you're number one
Christmas lover all right
closing yeah uh I love this game but I I
I really suck at being imposter but yeah
so so yosu yeah but I'll do my best this
game is f you're really bad at it I
don't remember I I was horrible at
imposter last time I played this I
screwed up so bad finger she imposter
maybe you just need a better mate to
work with cuz you're dumb D youm shut
up shut up were you the one who
plastered this on face bit of a poopy
head it's your poop what you're talking
about the lobby will fall apart it's no
problem but let's take our time okay
yeah by the way have you guys speaking
of Iris have you guys all seen the
yesterday and today's episodes of the
Holo Ian Advent calendar I was very
involved in I was very involved in them
yes just happened and they were both in
3D
space yep so Iris why did you do it um
oh it's cuz you know we needed some
light to bring up the Christmas spirit
you know mhm what better light than
actual fire right yeah that makes sense
and you know it was my whole plan so
that I I could become the Christmas tree
in order to become the Christmas tree
you needed to burn the actual Christmas
tree first true true you took a
Christmas
trees
it is the master plan it's pretty lit
yes very
lit it was
fire indeed fire fire light the fire
fire fire light the fire fire light the
fire fire
fire y uh everybody's uh joining in
again in the lobby I think I'm coming I
got my name I freed C spam he doesn't
exist
anymore iam no more com spam I'm sad is
it gonna hide the code if I have
streamer mode on I'm s yes it's hidden
for it does hidden people self-
introduction please hi uh bom you I'm
close you sparkling Gem of Hall English
Advent and today I'm a space Rock but
that doesn't mean you're allowed to
Stellar Stellar me out of the ship so I
am not sa I am
nice wow okay that was pretty good me
Ni No noon work here doesn't work
here man so you have to prove yourself
prove the truth you can't fool us people
you're sus D already you already sus
already why are
you I think I think it's her yeah I
think it's
guess it's
definitely okay let's move on
too
police I'm Nota i h I'm not h
i
together
okay sometimes I become a dragon
sometimes you know but as long as you
know I'm not Chihuahua I'm not Hua
I'm there go and together we make the
best crewmate you know dogs create not
kind of unfair it's kind of unfair yeah
impostor it's two there's two of you
guys
already cover your own mistakes I think
we should vote them out right away every
time I
that's well do that but indeed as a crew
mate they might be very helpful cuz it's
two brains for one I guess how do you
who's on the keyboard who's
controlling contr I'm the legs you're
the brains I'm also the the pointer
finger yeah nice looking forward
to be nice see one one day they will
play separately but today is not
today isn't this game a mobile maybe
somebody could play on mobile I
was white
work connects right isn't there doesn't
work on this side I think
[Music]
so well okay and then now we
St an
imposter English ad devilish diva
C I'm an impostor today because I'm
pretending to be M and I
guess oh my gosh fake it till you make
it fake it till you make
it we're we're a nice couple in there so
aren't
we guys are married I should be running
away from
you I don't want your
child even if honeyworks made a song
about our child I don't done
it okay and
then
please this
Ison from live English Pro what H life
English
promise um please don't arrest me I'm
going to be a very good egg for today uh
cuz even if I want to be an impostor I
never get it I
ever you can trust me I believe her I
trust her 100% yes I trust her 100% I
trust everyone 100% what are the chances
everyone only says the truth today I
look so kind SCI none none of us will
get imposter probably yeah probably none
of
usit how many how many imposters are we
doing for this I said it to two is two
wait
for Deputy yeah I I don't know I feel
like three
might is good two is good
okay and I I have in case you're
interested uh two long tasks and five
short tasks uh as well as two common
tasks I don't remember what common tasks
were that's
suspicious why you don't you don't
remember are
you oh yeah cuz imposters don't do
tasks well it's been too long rolls or
something right like you can do stuff
now or
something like rolls rolls or something
oh yeah wasn't there something besides
crew mate now like um uh like besides
someone that helps the Imposter like the
Spy or something like that's not the
Imposter but can help
impost yeah keep them on that's fun I
don't know how does that work though I
don't really know the r I've never
played beginning so wait yeah there's
four roles there I don't know you girls
can probably see them in the settings uh
on the on the computer here there's a
scientist who can access a portable
vitals panel so they can check at any
point of time if there's somebody dead
so they always see the status of the
crew and then there's an engineer who
can use the vents even though they're
not an impostor but then you might be
sused and you have to be like I'm not
the Imposter I just vent that's pretty
cool
really and then the guardian angel uh is
the ghost of the very first one of us
that dies oh is that how it works the
first person that dies yeah something
like that the garden G Angels the ghost
of the first Dead crew mate they can
temporarily shield and protect other
living crew mates so I guess if you're
the first one that dies you become the
guardian angel and then you can protect
somebody else so that they don't die
yeah if you do it properly and well
timed you'll be able to prevent
imposters from killing their victims
sounds amazing me throwing so that I I
can become the guardian
angel a good the guard wow the guardan
and there's a shape shifter who can who
can change the appearance and disguise
themselves as other crew mates why would
you do that though that just confuses
everyone it's just makes the Imposter
easier to the impostor or yeah they're
not even the impost make the Imposter
harder to find too because then you know
the Imposter can say I'm the engineer
and oh no I'm the shap you know like
please I promise I'm not a
murderer it's only impostor but why
would would would a crewmate do this I
don't know why would a crewmate turn
that one off but I like the other ones
yeah should I should I keep them or
should I I think shter is
impos it oh okay yeah it just doesn't
say so so wait does only one impostor is
only one imposter The Shape Shifter is
that how it works or do all of them get
how many there will be
I I can say we want two or I can say we
I want one or zero I can set it in the
settings but if I do one then only one
of the uh imposters will be Shape
Shifter but only 50% chance the one will
be oh I can I can make it higher too
that we have one for
sure default is good right
balance okay okay default then let's
keep the rolls then let's go going
straight to the you
introduce yourself before
we before before we go um can we have
the visual tasks off because if we have
it on it might be too easy visual tasks
off oh yeah true true you can tell right
away actually yes very good okay and
before start I'm Tak I organized this
thing the logos at the f nails are
commissioned by me
so don't kill me because I I paid for
this okay don't we M right we M
right byebye byee
byebye oh thank God thank god oh this
this is a new this is a new
map oh it's like a
camp uh where do I have to
go uh this
way oh oh it's like a beach that's
pretty
cool okay um I'm so glad I'm I'm not
imposter first
round oh wait wrong way wrong way how do
I how do I get
in what the hell why do I have meat what
the what is this why do I have meat on
me huh did I become did I become raw
meat what what's that what the hell was
that
[Music]
um it's like a
vacation what sort of task is
that oh oh trash trash trash
yeah this reminds me of those Warrior
Games still haven't meet met anyone I
saw that was cie right that saw me being
a chunk of meat I don't know what the
hell that was
but oh no
[Music]
Amy
no I'll miss you byee really you guys
killed the only real astronaut you know
what that means we don't have a chance
of getting back to our own
Planet unbelievable so who saw Watson I
didn't see her at all I didn't see her I
didn't see her at all I mean oh no I
didn't see her who who reported just now
me I did oh where did you did tell us
about it where was the body so I was
going around
Communications um trying to figure out
the mushrooms and what not and I went
down uh the the little zipline and then
in the storage room Amy was
dead storage room oh the one that I was
able
to we saw around the
Busom
saw wait so F was also in the storage
area no no we were at the mushrooms and
we were having problems with that and
crony Senai was around and then crony
Senpai went down but Senai was there too
yeah yeah mococo was chasing me
around confused I don't know what's
going on I have mushroom problems yeah I
had like a meat problem I don't know
like it I suddenly turned into like a a
lighter pink and there was like a chunk
of meat chasing me
I puff and then they change into people
or something like that what does that do
is that just an effect to freak you out
or does it do something I don't know I
don't know I think it I think the the
the mushroom like if you touch it or
something um it hides the the people so
you can just like kill them and run away
and they would be able to kill SW my
skin or something like
that why do you know that hot yeah yeah
my skin got swapped as well yeah it
swapped the skin a wizard and then I had
a little worm next to me for a moment
and then poof it was gone and the light
was back
on it was weird I I don't know what what
goes on in this map I I don't know I
feel like I trusted crony Senpai and now
I feel like I don't trust crony
Senpai I will say I passed by and I was
actually running away from crony cuz I
felt like she was chasing
me where were you you you followed
me
really you have
there bye everybody okay
goodbye I don't know the fact that she
had like her own like um name plate and
everything oh oops oops
oops
okay it should be muted now
right yeah yeah okay muted
um uh
where do I go where do I go since she
had her name plate and all fancy and I
feel like it wouldn't be surprising if
she did
self-report oh I'm going through the
mushroom area
again okay okay I go this
way this
way find the stuff I don't know what
what the hell was that is that an egg oh
go to the library okay and nissa's over
there
how do
I oh do I have to oh damn it oh whose
dead body is that
oh oh
what wait I just saw Nissa like 5
seconds ago though so no is in the South
part of the map with the lab in the
hallway I don't know this
map um wait how do I look at oh I saw
narissa around like next to the
greenhouse when I was passing by I was
moving to the laboratory yeah it's she's
above the green house I saw her walking
around I didn't see anyone near her I
didn't see anyone else I always saw
narissa when we went up to
Communications and that was the last
time I saw
her we didn't see anyone except for site
and I think she's good scared us I ran
away instantly cuz I will be honest I
don't trust anyone who voted for crony
in the last round what seems like the
imposters were trying to get her out
because knew she was I voted her because
car is
dead there a
double what did K by tell us before huh
huh that's something important when
we're going to start yeah I'm about to
kill her who did
it there's only there's only three left
Among Us really there's oh that's true
wait two imposters crony could have been
an imposter though honestly like I don't
know I don't I wouldn't put it behind it
doesn't say who it doesn't say oh I
wouldn't put it behind her if she's
self-reported because look at her look
at her um her icon like it's all why are
you so suspicious of her for no reason I
don't know I feel you wouldn't be this
suspicious unless you were the impostor
not I swear to God I'm not I I know I I
said out right that I saw like narissa
passed by just 5 seconds ago before her
death if it was actually me I would say
saw narissa I didn't see you though uh
no I was pass I passed by her when she
was going greenhouse and I I'm currently
at the meeting room I went the opposite
direction that's why she was like stuck
on that that bi and Irish Senai are
suspicious I think so too I swear I'm
not I was walking around I was in the LA
the LA wait where's my the lab and then
Thea was on like the 10 seconds I'm vo
bio
I I don't have
enough
going I swear it's not me it is not me
uh oh I am in
a we get
him
aw I thought we won you guys I told you
I wasn't
me me you didn't even notice I was dead
guys literally I was pass me and biu
killed me
immediately oh it's a
self good team you two that was pretty
funo Tombstone let's go I was surprised
well you know what we learned from that
because call was pretty quiet sus out
the quiet quiet The Quiet Ones true the
quiet fooled me cie fooled me
too
strategy I was just confused cuz like my
voting was super rushed I was like wa wa
wait why am I suspicious all of
a Lally Spiderman everybody pointing at
each other no one in there it was peer
pressure peer you don't have to B
don't have to
vote need Iris out that was so weird I
thought it needed to be like majority
vote to even get anyone I thought two I
didn't think two votes was enough to
kill
me was only a little bit of us left so
two was enough people already
[Music]
died was strong at this H we're good
pretty good doing our tasks wen't you
the ones
who
[Laughter]
I guess we're S no matter what can't be
helped well that was a good first round
let's let's try to be you know we turn
extended voting time yeah voting
time yeah uh it's currently 90 seconds
should we do 12 at least a little yeah
at least 120 oh 120 is the max
okay good says apparently we can vote or
skip the vote if you're not confident
like who it is
you pretty
confident you were confident but you got
it wrong cty there pretty confident
voting out all yeah
I well now you now you know then you
maybe cannot trust your
confidence yeah true
enough all right then let's start
another
round
[Music]
even though this is really fun here
thank you C for finding
this see you on the other side bye see
you guys
bye okay oh shoot I already have to
sabotage
I don't know how to I don't forgot how
to
sabotage I forgot there's too many
people
here there's too many people here let's
go in here do whatever this probably is
a task right so C go that way kind of
want to try where are the are there no
vents here is just me or there no
vents is that a vent
oh it's a
vent it's a
vent I swear I don't know how this works
is there anyone around anyone around
alone oh no
that's how do I how do I go up
this I need it I need to I need I need
to kill someone
anyone at the
top I'm looking at
security I forgot where did I where did
I kill I just realized I'm almost dead
first
again I feel bad now where did I kill
her I killed her at was it
Communications I killed her at
communications okay
um what the hell the hell is that on
me oh this is a mining pit
okay probably kill one more I saw I
think I saw fauna this
way I
[Music]
no not again come on yeah come
on again
really
what right I'll break it down for you
oh I did all my tasks you guys could see
me I think some of you saw me watering
things in the the mushroom place I moved
some storage around roasted some
marshmallows went up to do my tasks in
the communication room and what do I
find Watson dead middle of the floor I
didn't see anyone leave though was
anyone near Communications recently
where communication top right you take a
little like a what is it a wire zipline
zipline
oh a little bit but we didn't see muchad
the zip line yeah I was just jungle
area yeah I know was there's like oh oh
okay these white white things are oh
okay yeah the line you can go up and
down but yeah I wasn't there yet um in
the bottom right um there was a lot of
shape shifting I don't know who is who
yeah there what happened with that the
mushroom is that the mushroom stuff
working everybody everybody got a skin
shift right
yeah we don't know who is who and then
we can't prove like oh that person was
there or whatever but we all look
different like not like each other right
so it's not shape shifting yeah no it's
just the mushroom
power is that somebody doing it or is
that oh by the way
yeah I haven't used it when pass by a
mushroom it does it
okay I can vent but I'm not the The
Imposter just saying I didn't use it yet
though I wonder recently was anyone
around upper engine Lookout or mining
pit because the impostor may have tried
to escape by going down the ladders I
will check it out I was was walking that
way but I didn't see
anyone okay I've been down over in the
left area for the whole time doing my
tasks so I haven't even G over there
seen I haven't been up there yet I have
Tas and communication like I was going
to go up I'm currently passing I was
passing by the greenhouse I was going to
go up but and then someone found the
body see anybody run past no I didn't
hard to tell still least
to yeah but people was kind of quiet a
just saying actually bi boo passed by me
and didn't kill me
so me this is the first time I'm doing
task I can tell you I've been doing
water with narissa and then I did the
marshmallow thing
and game I shot
asteroids and I haven't been up there
yet so I I do have t up
there okay we'll see we'll see evidence
inconclusive but keep your eyes open
yeah maybe don't don't go alone don't go
around alone guys go with a
buddy we don't need a
[Music]
buddy I'm surprised F didn't kill anyone
yet I'm genuinely
surprised uh wait do I I have like let's
go this
way
[Music]
storage there's only one death I guess
there's still new that's why I am I kind
of want to try double killing like with
foko but it's they're they're new so I
don't know if they would get the hint
and it might screw up and I might just
just just make me extremely suspicious
actually it will just out me if if it
fail fails it was just out me if it
fails oh trash can Nobody's around
huh I'm muted right okay no I'm muted
I'm muted I'm muted I'm muted I get
paranoid because of that one time I made
a mistake and didn't
mute this is an interesting Island
though the
hell I can pet them
okay let's see where is
everyone where is this I I can't tell
where where this vent
is I'm scared I'm going too
high
what oh
no I she was innocent was
only a
little she was I passed her going down
the ladders from communication to the
lower part she
pass maybe went up the communication
where'd you find her I was going up the
ladder to the communication and I didn't
really see her body but um I saw the the
vent which is the plant kind of opening
up and then closing so they
vent yeah they vented to wherever it is
from Communications oh oh does anyone
know where where the vents from
Communications connect to they can go
anywhere right I think all the vents can
only usually I don't know in Old Maps
usually vents only connect to certain
other
vents I should have checked and then I
could have told you but too bad no
idea I I can kind of say I think crony
is not self-reporting at least because
like I feel like I was I was running
around with her a little bit alone she
saw you yeah and she didn't and then I
saw cie running around I think we were
alone for a little bit but she may have
been on cool down as well but she yeah
she was coming down from that air she
was she was coming down from that area
yeah I told you I crossed paths with her
oh yeah okay but yeah and Cory said
someone
[Music]
vented where were you good question we
were at the the beach we're just kind of
going around but we don't really
understand I don't know what's going on
the map here we just tab it'll show you
where you are oh tab yeah hit tab the
map will pop up there's also the map
icon on the top mhm the map
ion yeah the top right a there's a set I
see a map but I don't understand it it
has a lot of marks on it
yeah a lot of marks that is that is it
exclamation
marks a lot of marks on it does it have
some x's on
it I'm
L the marks I mean I don't see so many
marks on my map yeah what does an
imposter see maybe does a previous
imposter want to tell us what they saw
like Kelly yeah Kelly I saw some x's
with circles on time and I clicked them
sabotage a lot of marks on the
screen I'm
OK do you have any anything to say to
defend yourself we're just doing our
tasks if you were doing task there
wouldn't be so many marks on the screen
would there
be yeah you had a lot of marks
know good do it
I
I hope we don't regret
that okay well that about out of the
game
already oh is there like
no okay guess we'll go I'll go
down I'll go down I'm muted no I'm muted
I'm muted I'm muted that was quick
though oh shoot touched the mushroom
again okay I got to I guess I have to
kill a lot of people now wait wait cuz I
mean is everyone upstairs I haven't
really met many people I don't really
want to go
upstairs yeah no I'm going down no I'm
going down I feel like it's easy to
figure out where someone is you know
what but
no I'm going up I'm going up I'm going
up I'm going
up I feel like people are up up there
oh there's so many of
them why are there so why is everyone
here it's not
possible
okay I feel like everyone's getting done
finishing their task so oh shoot I
touched that again okay I need I need
someone we didn't
go where did n Go I need someone to kill
I need to kill someone fast where'd she
go nope not here I need two people for
this
thing should I go back up oh shoot I
keep touching the mushrooms I don't mean
to everyone
upstairs
who who's dead cie I
saw I just saw her like yeah I saw her
too just saw her too I saw her body
right underneath the the
ladder the the left ladder like close to
the green house you check the map you
can check the map see exactly where the
greenhouse like close to the greenhous
yeah wasn't she just just with me at
around like yeah I saw everyone at
communications and I was getting some
stuff done there and uh and also the
lookout and then I went down and I saw
her dead I guess she moved
fast and then
died is there anyone around
there I'm in the lookout right now I'm
in the mining pit I was around I think
when everyone was
around oh we all went to Communications
H yeah everyone like uh everyone
except uh who was it like R Rissa and
FAA uh I think they were around like
Communications and like Lookout and then
everyone else went to the other coms
yeah
um I am sorry FAA but it seemed you were
being just um you know a little very
cautious I don't know if you were
careful about being stack killed but you
moved away from the the radio like where
everyone was trying to fix it oh that's
well you needed to go do the other thing
right to fix it I was the first one
there in the radio and I tried to put in
the code but I think you have to put in
a second
code yeah also I had two tasks that I
did in
Communications
oh I wented them cuz I was I was in
Lookout I was putting the code in I
think was the first who arrived and then
nothing was happening so I I thought I
would go to the other one and I saw Cali
was like doing the code at that point as
well so she was like she already arrived
and then I left her alone there and I
was about to go up to the other
communication thingy but then uh it was
already fixed so then I went back and I
saw I think I saw crony again or so yeah
but I didn't see fauna and I didn't see
Iris at all I saw you I saw all of you
guys I don't know I don't know I saw all
of you guys of communications I I was I
was with SAA alone for a while and she
didn't kill me I saw narissa go down go
down I didn't I saw you going where are
you right
now um I ended up in the lookout because
I got lost and I was very confused oh so
you went back aren't we
all yeah I'm a little suspicious of
crony cuz she didn't vote for fuam moko
time we're running out of I don't know
if I'm suspicious enough to vote [\h__\h]
yeah I don't know I I I don't know
either I'm going to
skip you're going to
skip
skipping we
we good luck crew
mates the one thing about the voting
system this time is you can tell who
voted who oh shoot not again I feel like
that's just kind of
scary sure something in the
laboratory I think crony is sus about me
a little that movement was kind of
weird
that was close
yeah oh shoot not
again how do I how do I get inside
this this map is so I don't I don't know
what the hell's going on in this
map there we
go oh cron is still there oh you can I
didn't you can do that what you can just
kind of SL slide through there what how
does that
work oh wait but cron is H fa us I don't
think I should kill
her I don't think I should kill
her oh I'm
stuck I need to can't get
out sorry so sorry I can't I can't get
it I know get out of here I I get out of
here oh that's how you do it what the
hell oh there we go there we go okay I'm
not going to kill funo though I need
someone on my
side I want to kill
crony oh wait oops wrong way this
way F has been following me this whole
time she's following me this whole
time I want to go to the kitchen
uh hello hello hello I think Nissa is
trying to kill me ah you are so I can't
believe you I was not I checked
everyone's vitals and I decided to go
back to the meeting
area and I saw her and I got a little
scared so I ran back but then she
chilled so I thought it was cool but
then she hit the emergency meeting
button much to my surprise no the thing
is there's a little bit of a backstory I
was running around and the there's a
back story yeah I'm my task what do you
mean
backstory I was running around I was I
was you know I I I was running around
crony alone she didn't kill me I was
running around fauna alone she didn't
kill me and both of those I kind of
thought were sus and then I found you
and you kind of followed me and now I
think if it's not cron if it's not fall
enough I didn't even follow you what do
you mean I ran into you and then I ran
back to the meeting area you are so
fake I was also around crony and she did
not kill me either yeah even though she
could have and as I was doing tasks I
could have killed crony too and I didn't
which I would have if I had the
opportunity
to would tell me everybody tell me Iris
and tell me fauna what are the remaining
tasks that you have I'm done with tasks
I was hanging out with Iris yeah I saw
yeah B was follow sorry if you felt like
I was chasing you I was kind of scared I
was kind of scared you were like stick
to me like little time yeah I have I
have a task to do at the dock and then I
have one at the cafeteria then do it and
then we win task win let's go guys we
have to also I think people who are done
with the tasks can um follow let just
wait in the meeting area or follow yeah
I mean we have to do the tasks we can't
just wait in the meeting area no no no
like people who are done with the tasks
can I don't know can I add on that I do
think I do think narissa is a little bit
suspicious though Nissa you and me Let's
Stay Together I'm I'm not with
you you or not we're staying together
now I'll actually take along with you
guys if that's okay just to see if one
of you okay safer cron is there wait
then maybe you two are the imposters no
I'm done with my tasks as a thing so I
don't want to kill me it is kind of
scary oh my God I didn't kill you when
you were around yeah what the heck oh
you two didn't kill each other because
you're
both oh my God you can come with me and
IR why you depending it on the blue
women yeah let's just all stay together
and we'll see what the blue women do oh
my God we follow Iris does anyone else
have t left no no I'm all done oh yeah
we should follow Iris we should pressure
follow IR okay yeah yeah you can totally
follow
me okay nice hey who voted for me
me wait am I getting okay okay good you
better you little [\h__\h] love you Ki
please don't kill me
okay okay muted [\h__\h] now everyone's
going to follow me [\h__\h] am I the only
one
with someone didn't do their tasks
though someone didn't do their tasks how
am I going to you know I'm going to wait
for okay the only way I can do this is
um is um how do how do I how do I how do
how do I do
[Music]
that task win who was
it excuse me I was it was task yeah who
was the was the
impos were I wonder who was was it
[Music]
was went and you know outed themselves
doing so good
the doing I'm sorry I was suspicious of
you fa I'm sorry I was suspicious of you
Iris didn't kill
fa why didn't you
I wanted to keep someone on my side
that's why I and because crony was
susing fun in the beginning I was like
maybe I should keep her on my side and
kill crony
instead I was thinking that yeah and
like I I saw that Iris was uh going into
the same room as uh narissa was so I was
kind of waiting outside the room I saw I
saw I was like oh no I think she's sus I
was trying to kill I was trying to kill
you actually um I when you were inside
the lab I was I was following you and I
was going to kill you but then I noticed
you were moving weirdly and you were
like running away and then Marissa came
comes in right away like oh never mind I
can't kill you we're
here gave up went back I think I was
playing a little bit too cautiously but
um but so difficult there's only there's
only me that's why I saw I was I was
worried like yeah it was still pretty
good feel impressive yeah I can't I
can't believe you suspected
me all's well it ends well hopefully
when we're together alone in the males
nothing I won't kill you don't
worry Don't Drown me in the ocean
please
mly oh sorry I was Stucky just I'm here
sorry um I don't want to like you know
make any hard rules because you know you
just kill whoever is conveniently there
but please do not kill Amit right away
next
rounde no no no we need our we need our
space on out to doob yeah kill me first
I love being the
ghost no pressure yeah no
price okay we complete I changed one
thing I changed the votes uh you can't
see Ved that makes it really hard for me
to try to vote
someone oh boy let's go let's
go see you later
bye oh thank God thank God I don't want
to lie
anymore but I can use the vents I can
use the
vents I can use the vents let's go
that's
fun what a task what a task wait so Amit
and whist
okay I can use events that sounds fun it
doesn't seem necessary though unless
you're unless you you're an impostor you
know H come on come on pop
out there we
go just get all the tasks done was it
was it AIT Nissa that were there right
okay they probably moved somewhere else
already
though me how do I use
this like
this ah okay refill the water okay okay
okay oh
no boom boom boom Oh my God this is so
loud okay I got a cafeteria one be who
is the green one with the a
hat 34 ping I feel like that's pretty
high I don't know if that's a good thing
fauna okay fauna has the gr hat on it's
[Music]
confusing she saw that right away H oh
for a moment I thought you were dead
again oh
[Music]
no hope is dead I just saw like less
than 30
seconds I just found it but I was up in
the drop ship if you look at the map and
then I went down and I found her body
there and was up there was up there and
people look like she came from down
below so I'm a little shap shifter
think knew no one would kill you so I
thought it' be safer with you oh I see I
did see fa go up following the bullets
of maybe that was a fake FAA I was just
making sure no funny business was going
on who was I saw Iris alive like less
than 30 seconds before she was found
dead maybe it was a shape shifter I know
who you fell like like 10 seconds before
so I'm I'm surprised didn't see who that
was a really fast I'm surprised I only
passed by in that area was
like and that's it I think in that area
might
be like coming from that direction might
be
B I
saw storage room and then I was using
the
zipline and
like zipline up with
me oh well B would you like to defend
yourself
what I was following Amy because I no
one was going to kill Amy so I thought
Amy was the safest B saw you didn't she
not following her but coming from a
different direction no I was following
this entire time you you the entire time
I was running away from you so I didn't
always see you I was following you the
entire you want to kill why you
this this
is T I've done one task so far it was
asteroids I haven't done the rest
because you only did one so far though
it's been a lot of time you do asids in
the last one to yeah I have what is the
asteroids one
like oh wait I forgot I I Communications
I mean I will do
my forgot I'm
dead last time too I don't want to
die I don't know if have enough by the
way Iris I don't know if you know but
you mut oh it's because she's dead oh
never
mind
but she is gay I just wanted to make
sure she joins the conversation you
know if I die it's or sus one of them
out if
I byebye people this is the last time
I'm I didn't I voted I just
skipped I didn't vote for you it wasn't
me oh thank you oh no
one I think it's I think it's I think
it's
okay I can to mute myself and just stay
in here I'm dead oh am I guardian angel
I can protect I can protect okay okay
I'm going to protect F wait where's be
where's beu I got to be close to where's
beu I can protect okay where there's spe
you protect more protect
Callie feels
like there's two over
here I wonder how the protection
works I think oh yeah my tasks oh yeah I
have to do my tasks too even though I'm
dead H but I want to I want to do my
guardian angel duties I think it's
definitely
be
already wait I just saw I saw
I
saw
what what wait wait wait okay I'm GNA
I'm going to
listen much worse I I know it's not bi
boo okay because I went down because I
saw bio pass us we were both waiting to
get into the kitchen because last round
fuo and I were frying fish together
right so as I was waiting I went to get
bio cuz I was like Advent together
strong and then when I came back it was
right in front of the kitchen it was
right in front of the kitchen is where
is where the death just happened and I
saw someone running up to the Splash
Zone so where was everybody and don't
lie wait God found which which of the
two
bodies I don't I don't know where I
don't know
where then I have something to add I was
just up at the very top of the
communications I was falling be the
whole time there was crony and there was
fauna first there was fauna and
me cool then crony joined left and now
fa is dead okay can you confirm this
crony um after I was uh doing the ladder
task I went down I everything CR says
just sounds so I didn't really you saw K
up there yeah I saw Kiara and up there
and then after I was done with the
ladder I went down the zip line and I
couldn't see anything else aside from
that maybe someone vent I'm not really
sure cuz it's kind of a short maybe
you I mean I
know my Al really quick and I saw bio
and we were alone and she didn't come
after me or anything but I was in the
Splash Zone in the beginning I collected
shells and then I left okay where were
you though at the time of the
murder I went up to just happened I
reported it immediately yeah I I know I
went to spash Zone and I collected the
shells and then I saw bioo and she
didn't hurt me and then I went back to
storage okay and then crony FAA and
kiata were over in Communications yeah
so Watson where were you I was at the
laboratory laborat I I am s of am
because iish was around me fa and Amy
yeah I am too and now so now I'm s it
seems weird trying to vote someone off
no cuz the last the last murder the
everyone who was president we know that
it wasn't fa now and obviously iris is
dead so it's only youo but I know where
was the time of the Mur getting that the
first round I reported the body and both
biu and faer were with me and none of
them said that they bi even said that
she was following me the whole time but
she didn't see me kill anyone it might
beit it might be trust me at the same
time she hasn't been alive she usually
act like
this who are we voting
for selfreported
[Laughter]
it's all
split oh my
God says no I don't know Kiara's really
sus ah okay I'm going to go to the dead
people's
room hello
hello crony got voted at I didn't expect
that I
know
oh she's here ghost is here she's here
yeah oh why why is why is oh can I haunt
her oh I'm haunting her what does that
mean I have no idea where did all the
fies go
her where that's what she
deserves okay but I need to do my tasks
oh it's cuz never okay I know no nothing
nothing when I joined the dead people's
child of a sudden your fugie became
humongous it was only you because I
think everyone else yeah it's cuz we're
in different channels yeah okay I have
to care be careful about that okay uh
I'm I'm a I'm a guardian angel who do
you think is other impostor I should
probably stick to
them
um wait I I think it might be probably
know I think it also might be am I think
am was suspicious let me know if you see
somewhere wait did she not kill you
though I don't know I got killed by F I
don't know I don't know who it is yeah I
feel like she killed you cuz I saw you
alive and then like L like 10 seconds
later reported so I'm like who could
have been there it's definitely it's
definitely me I see I see I think it's
am me I'm following on me right now I
should also do my tasks while doing
that
okay I think it's am I'm going to follow
am CR not know about this dead people
chat that she
could maybe she's not joining cuz she's
ashame
maybe she maybe maybe oh what what is
the code how am I supposed to know the
code for
this uh where like the right where I'm
where um at the is it on the little at
the lookout ID card yeah in your pocket
oh you're right
oh I kind of like just doing the tasks
me
tooing
okay I've finished I've finished I still
have a lot actually oh God I need
to okay I'm haunting Amy
okay do it does haunting just mean you
follow her you you automatically follow
them it's like Auto follow oh okay
okay I need to see who's alive oh I see
you can
haunt other ghosts as well o
oops I can haunt
you okay
let's see this oh oh wait did anyone die
I don't I don't think oh someone did die
okay okay let's go back
then oh
yes uh yeah I didn't I was wondering
too I I think Kiara is safe yeah cuz we
just did the emergency thing together
yeah and then I'm a joined right when we
I really I ran away both of you guys are
I thought both of you guys were the
impostor you were going to kill me
no I why you think I really because the
first death was Iris and me fa and Iris
were the ones that were closest to each
other and mhm yeah well that's and now
I'm scared I know it's not Kiara because
Kiara didn't kill me could be so could
have I did follow her tasks left by
after I so why did why did meeting
because I know it's definitely was one
of them because we're about to finish
our tasks and you don't want us to
finish our tasks I was too quiet and I
was scared of anyone was going to die
and I thought like chat chat chat chat
might as well chat and like Kelly what
were you doing I went down to mushrooms
mhm and what's the last task you did the
Sorting the mushrooms into the jars and
the crystals okay Kelly has been quiet
yeah I mean ask me any questions you
want but if you talk too much you get
sused out too so just just ask me any
questions and I'll tell
you what's the last task you
did um I don't remember I was in
the I can't ask chat too cuz I can't
even look at chat um I know this sounds
suspicious but I don't remember I'm
going to I'm going to vote for a I think
yeah you're the Imposter you're just you
called the meeting because we're so
close to finishing our tasks that you're
scared no [\h__\h] I'm scared of
dying aren't we all I mean I saw cie and
she didn't kill me and I was running
away from you guys cuz I thought you
guys were going to kill me so that's my
defense yeah okay we voting okay oh okay
you guys if you guys vote for me you're
wrong just so you know do your
test I'm gonna vote for Cy what is
this oh
or call you Su cuz I saw you I saw kiar
and bi together and you guys didn't die
so unless you're both the impostor
no we're not uhhuh that's exactly what
an imposter would say betray from last
if there was two imposters alive we
would lose by now so there's only oh
okay that's true so one of the previous
was crony I guess was the one that got
knocked out right so wouldn't that be
yeah
yeah I don't know I don't know I don't
know I say we just Skip and continue
doing our tasks unless you guys are if I
was the Imposter i' I'd try to vote one
of you guys out right now and then I'd
probably
win I can just hear their voice you guys
are wrong regret your decision love you
I'll miss you yeah
right no I I think it was ony oh wasn't
noty it
wasn't I I thought it was Amy I thought
it was am was it Amy
appar I don't think so oh was it was it
beu then but I was following be after I
died is it C it shows you if you haunt
them sh it shows you who it is oh my
God yeah oh no wait oh my God how did
I'm so lost okay anyway I even crony but
oh well
that was wild I was shap
sh turned again that's her T she was
quiet oh you turned to fall I see see we
thought Kelly was quiet too but
you [\h__\h] I'm so sorry how do I ever
redeem myself to you it's too late it's
too
[Music]
late yeah I totally thought it was me
too oh my God I'm not a real am
goling
I tried to protect her and now I'm the
one that killed
her I can't trust call
anymore yeah I can't trust I'm sorry I
can't believe I got imposter twice
believe me I won't get lying why is
everyone so good at lying been watching
professional Japanese Among Us players
recently
I the whole time had practice
that's the warned you guys you didn't
listen to
me damn it and I still didn't get
impostor single time
man we still got more we still got more
time
right yeah yeah there's a little more
time then let's go next
round oh I saw I saw by the way the
ghosts uh were going in their own
channel did you have fun yeah yes
yes that was fun I don't know why cron
cron was probably too guilty to join
join the dead voice chat she felt like
oh wait there's a dead voice I didn't
even know there's a dead voice CH I was
like why isn't she joining like oh
probably cuz she feels guilty oh no I
don't feel guilty at
all you don't feel any
shamey just randomly get voted off too
cuz I don't remember like everybody yeah
I
V was ging it for that yeah Kara Kara
knew yeah cuz I told you yeah yeah I
told you to believe me see oh it was
actually good what I did thank God she
was right you were so right I think an
easy way to tell easy way to tell if if
Callie is imposter she's quiet when
she's imposter all
right so I don't know bye you are the
Imp
wait do your tasks okay I'll do my tasks
let's
go I love the non pressure of not being
impostor okay let's fa oh wait no this
[Applause]
one oh really this is this takes a while
I'm bumping
[Applause]
it okay there we
go can we go this way Calli Kiara am why
are they all here there is there
something do
there oh did I get it okay oh there is
stuff to do
marshmallows hey this is literally just
a
vacation damn that takes
forever that looks delicious
though what does that
mean reactor meltdown do we all die if
we I'm got to go to the
reactor who did I see over there was
that fauna
oh wait no reactor's done
okay let's do
this okay someone's over
there what do I have to do over
here ra is the temperature be is also
there doing her stuff okay yeah she's
probably not
SS at green
[Music]
house there we go I love how all of
these are just so simple sometimes you
get those tasks you have no idea what
you're supposed to do
though but what is it telling why is it
telling me to go up I think I'm done
with my
tasks calm sabotaged oh okay I guess
I'll I'll fix that I don't know what's
the whole point of sabotaging comms
anyways
uhoh I didn't even see I didn't even see
I didn't even really see I didn't wa I
didn't even really see she was just
there did I see no no no no was where
where were you where were you when you
pressed it
wait who pressed it wa I I pressed it I
was oh my God I was so in my tangent oh
my God I went up to the top right to the
communications and I was just Tangen
thing and doing task and suddenly I see
a dead body but on the same spot I think
I saw at least one more person maybe
another maybe two people I think soar
iris from and then I just came into the
room outs I didn't see the body I just
the moment I went up the ladder all of a
sudden was
Communications the same time and then I
was trying to go in the way to the
mushroom door but I got rid of the
mushrooms but I
maybe killed by
accident maybe it's just amaz him by
being silly uhhuh wait
what wait I mean you were there right
when I reported right no I I just walked
into the room like after cie she was
already in there like alive and you guys
were all doing the power thing or
whatever and I was also starting to do
the power thing putting in the code but
then you guys finished it and then
somebody reported Callie's body so I
didn't even see it wait so you're saying
besides me there was cie and you like I
I just went inside the communications
the moment you
reported how all in there no one on the
other side of the mushroom wall so I
don't think they could kill her on the
other side of the mushroom wall but I
don't know I just went up the ladder was
how it went and then all of a sudden
report there might there was one other
person in there but it was hard to see
cuz everybody was bunched up I think saw
purple I didn't know zie was was was
Call's dead body no no the purple
we do have something to report
yeah we
heard okay you are the and the
M we were thinking maybe this
being that's good thing that we do that
I heard that I thought you was saying it
to someone else and now I'm can we have
someone who hasn't talked talk
please me me me
yes so um I was at communications I saw
a bunch of people there and I was trying
to like uh do my task and like I was
still on the task when it happened so I
didn't really see anything oh so you
were also in
Communications report okay yeah wait you
were there even now when when I reported
you were still
there um yeah yeah oh so you were one of
the other people I saw then where I
wasn't sure who am I seeing oh [\h__\h] I
voted for f well I remember this I will
remember
this but oh shoot you guys
what
uhoh I don't know if F sounded sus
sounded
sus I feel like it's necessary to get
someone
out the way they were talking I I I I
kind of trust D I trust D um not this
way I'm going to do this
way fire fire light the doubts of
fire ooh that's where
they what what wait wait
what
what there was like a crowd of people
that communic wait did you did you
double
kill did you guys like kill four people
my gosh like how did you yeah wow see
The Quiet Ones it's always the quiet
ones I knew cronia never hasn't said
anything I was ctive last round that's
cuz I asked you to
talk
we're both innocent I'm
sorry I thought I thought it was B too B
sounded sus
but was suing for was susing Amit right
because of her statement but it
was said that on
purpose being silly the two imposters
would of course vote for Fu Moko because
sorry I also voted for I'm sorry oh my
God this is what happens okay next we
got to
[Music]
go don't give it to the blue people
don't give it to the blue people
n another stress free round oh I'm an
engineer I can use vents not that I will
ever use them cuz that would only make
me look
sus what was that who was that oh Kiara
am
okay Kiara am
Cali
[Applause]
okay
nice nice nice okay next I can
go oh oh they they they sabotaged comms
again so far away I guess sabot com is
really strong in this
map it's hilariously far
away side the
chist oh
wait this would
work 471 eight three what I was going to
fix it oh it's Callie Callie
dead did I ran up because of the
communications thing was down and she
was right there in Communications in
front of the the thingy I other I was
the other uh I was with f but I didn't
see her body I was down by the dock I
was in the labs oh me um oh yeah I just
met crony in the labs yeah
Iris and I the other task yeah we were
doing the other task and each other so I
think we're
safe pushing up some lifts what what
narissa F where were you I was down by
the dock I I figured that you probably
all were going there and I wanted to
keep doing my tasks so I just went down
and I was doing a sand castle and then I
was checking since don't the don't the
um don't pass to don't the T they
disappear but if you pass them you can
still do them oh okay yeah I was
checking manually okay I thought that's
what yeah or if you just still like
remember where they were before it went
down
yeah moo
reactor
reactor what were you doing at the
reactor we're doing our task which task
what task was
it use the map I like the map I like
finding the little yellow mark on the
the screen is now you
know
sizing I actually haven't done that yet
the yellow there's a yellow mark one
marshmallow so cute a little Among
Us
uhow the marshmallow
[Music]
yeah so inclusive but what task were you
doing
yeah the marshmallows are nowhere near
the reactor yeah so what were you that
was that was yeah what were you doing
today we doing a bunch of in the reactor
what were you doing what were you doing
in the reactor yeah what were you doing
in the reactor
[Laughter]
kind now I'll give you guys the benefit
of the D thank you please don't kill us
again
[Music]
No Bully no
bullying I don't know fact they didn't
know what they were doing at the reactor
reactor was really Su okay we got to fix
I was so close to fixing comms
too
I'll fix bottom coms everyone else is at
the top coms I'll do
bottom uh 5 3 3 6 one
okay okay do I have anything oh I have
something to do here
nice uh three
two
nice got nothing else to do to up here
oh it's Kiara
okay
it's nice that you can tell where you
are on the map real
time what am I supposed to do here huh
oh get the watering can okay
okay was that who was that just now was
that c I think Call's dead right wait or
is it Nissa wait wait I don't know
forgot who it was
already I'm just an
engineer
uh uh no no no this one no oh
this
this this this oh God that's a lot of
parts
[Laughter]
okay I kind I want a vent but I'm scared
I'm scared I'm going to just be
sus okay you know what I'll vent never
mind I can't
vent why can't I vent why can't I vent
now
huh that's
weird U which is my closest
[Music]
way oh Noy it was Kara it
wasara killed don't believe her do you
see I people kill am I am medic I am
medic I can see people's vitals yeah and
I can see you kill Amy is that how it
works I I am many I can see people's vs
I have three battery charges every round
to see how many people are alive this is
the first time I have medic I saw Ki
kill no people no no it say hard for me
because I had just I had just seen biu
and but I did not see kiata and I was
going going down and she didn't follow
me so she might have realized she was
alone with a but uh bio also when she
killed me self-reported and then
immediately this is literally the first
time I've gotten scientist and I have
this is the first time I played it so
how would I know that I have three
charges of scientist to check vital
where is the body first time in a while
all the body is up the stairs
communication oh okay saw Kiara who
watch
you probably just looked up some guide
about those no I didn't this is the
first time I have whatever scientist
whatever I can check people's well I was
I was so often alone with others and I
didn't kill them so why would I you know
can somebody vouch for me cuz I think I
was alone alone together with a lot of
people come
on I was alone with for a while but I
was not alone with Kiara I only saw
Kiara for like a Split Second I'm sorry
Saw s times alone and I saw crony
several times I think alone and I saw
narissa like maybe one or two times
alone yeah it felt like um either Kiara
or fauna was going to kill me because
like they were just kind of walking
around so I stuck around one of them to
make sure I didn't get killed um it
would kind of check out if Kiara was
the I believe I believe
wow okay you
Sor goodbye forever thanks forever H
what was that I I love you or I'm D
thank you
for
well somebody's not voting someone's not
voting I just accepted that you guys are
voting me me out but I guess you'll
you'll no you're running down the clock
it's so sad I I was always with you
guys you goodbye goodbye goodbye I will
go up like a phoenix and I will rise
like a
phoenix yeah she did burn Like a Phoenix
okay
well I believe be
boo
um as for
okay let's go
Greenhouse I think foko is sus I still I
still kind of think they're
sus what the hell is this am I just
revitalizing the plants
interesting it's nice to know what these
tasks are though they help with my alibi
future games that way I'm not I'm not
going to end up like full that doesn't
know what their tasks are making them
happy
okay
okay crony passed by me and moving in
the most sus way
possible like usual wait this
one oh they did comms
again shoot I can't do
this I can do this though nice
nice mushroom mushroom
nice nice okay let's fix
coms this
way be and Faun are just following each
other why did F just come
down F just totally ignored ignored
comms okay it's definitely F it's
definitely
FAL it's definitely
them oh now it's a different code shoot
63 71
Fu okay I just want to I just want to do
an emergency meeting I can't why is is
nobody doing the one on the
bottom for are not are they they're not
dead
right oh the one on the bottom is done
what
oh definitely not crony or narissa okay
yeah no it's definitely flal okay I'm
just going to I'm going to go emergency
meeting emergency meeting I think it's
full
FAL
how do I do
this hello why the Emer oh no I I cuz I
I I believe it's
F what because like when when we were
going to when comms were down we were
going up I see I see like um many of us
were going up I think it was like mhm I
think I saw fa beu um I also saw I was
also with crony and narissa alone none
of us killed each other um and we were
all going up to comms but then I see F
coming down from comms ignoring the fact
that comms is being sabotaged do the
bottom one first right we just try to do
the toas and but you were at the Top If
you were at the top you would do the top
one right we just counting on we're
focusing on our task yeah you can't see
the task on the map when comms are down
yeah yeah you can but if you
walk last time too I'm like 99% sure
it's that's why I decided I decided
to that's how we play
a me a you did this time what's what's a
task you did what's the task you
did why did you you you come came back
down from comms even though comms is
sabotaged all the way back down to the
greenh house the green house is
greenen is
pretty got
a we're the cutest
puppies far
wow Little Liars look at the Little
Liars oh cute Little Liars
just B bowing and hoping
[Music]
that
goodbye come on F Go cast your
V yeah don't don't um delay your death
it's yeah it's an it's time to
go excuse
me byebye
[Music]
puppies like the green house really good
susing out Iris that was impressive no
it was it was obvious from the Rea too
even the last round when when we almost
voted them out cuz they didn't know what
they were doing at the
reactor was that made me 80% sure and
then I saw them going down from C so oh
yeah yeah
definitely what this we crew will do the
exact me to
yes I'm so sorry it's okay
you were just trying to survive I
understand I think out of this whole
group of people me and Fu are like the
worst Liars so it was
Comin my you B
my we were so bad hard to
Li it
is M makes me
laugh I make M laugh too you see see I I
had the good the good life you know I
did the marshmallows and then she goes
oh we did that last
time God well at least I finally got
imposter do we don't want to do one more
round yeah hi and see for the last
change the yeah hide and seek hide and
seek hide andek hide andek
fun it's like hide and seek like how
you'd really think hideand-seek would I
don't think we have to M for hide and
seek wasn't there an actual setting for
hide and seek yeah there there is there
is computer uh you might have to make a
new room though maybe um if you can't
change it in the settings um on the
computer yeah then you might have to
make a new room is
it yeah no I don't think you can change
it
here okay
then I'll make the new
one
okay okay it's kind of like oh it's
pretty much like playing tag yeah
cute um any preferred
map let's do the original oh yeah yeah
let's
[Music]
do I'll send you the link in the group
uh the in the group mhm mhm okay yeah
this one's chaotic but really funny
thank you never done it before oh it's
fine and it's a short game too so let's
go
perfect man this is scary this one this
is like the only time I actually want to
be imposter hide and seek
imposter kill imp don't have to M for
this say we don't have to mve for this
you said oh no I don't think so right
you just
Goos we could mute if you want give away
a location on accident I guess we can
mute if we're
done uh we don't have to
right wait we can we can hide in vents
oh is there only
one oh is this like
zombies
what the hell was that we can hide in B
really slow tasks the timer goes down
quicker we have 3 minutes to
[Music]
hide minutes 3 minutes to hide she's in
the med
Bay she in the upper engine she's
coming what wait
what oh man oh God she GRE oh no she's
GRE who knows what color
[Music]
my everybody's clumping together there's
tasks tasks where where is she right
now my god oh the
Scream Wait how does this
work
you can hear the music come close to you
when she's close by that's
scary crony where's she looks don't ask
her oh that's fun that's so quick
too another one another
one again again again again
for both the impostor and the the the
the crew
mates can we increase his speed for both
crew mates yeah I want to but also I I
uh I think I have to make a new Lobby
because I don't think I can change the
amount of uh Seekers oh there's only one
there's only one Seeker oh yeah I it's
fine to leave it on one we just need to
speed up so we're all running really
fast extreme
maximum let's go this is how it should
be oh jeez oh
boy yumpy let's
go do I get to that I think so
oh I'm going to be Unleashed for my CH
you
might why are there tasks
okay oh God where do I go do we have to
do task do your task do your task Tas
there task I don't see them I see tasks
but I don't know what I really want to
finish though
sorry it's
[Applause]
good why do I
have I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared
I'm scared I hear I hear the
we got to win we got to win this I can't
find you guys what the heck everyone oh
it's so
[Music]
fast task task task task
task music music is yell I'm not even
near you terrifying oh my God
screaming it's like a horror game all of
a sudden on is
[Applause]
screaming terrifying
[Music]
dream going
louder you're going louder and louder
yeah it's so chaotic
get the moment you hear the guitar riff
you're
[Music]
like I'm almost done almost done almost
done almost spinning 20 seconds more
[Music]
seconds you're going to be even Al the
final round I'm alive okay should I do
Tas
yeah hiding I need you to run around
like chicken what what's there's more
she get one more
minute don't stand still because it's
going to show your location later on it
shows it shows your
location yeah there's a there's a red
dot uh that indicates where the I have
it on that's scary as hell what oh my
God I see dead bodies I see dead bodies
I see dead people
I [\h__\h] does she see me from the map when
she gets closer oh God oh
[Applause]
God
that was so
[Applause]
CL that was impressive
I I don't know how I just didn't really
see her on the screen that often so
thank God everybody
so awesome that was close that was
close the
map yeah the ghost couldn't even keep
track more more one more one
[Music]
more nothing is is it let's go who is
it I she have fun oh run run
run does doing tasks do anything like I
feel like
ear if we finish them all
yeah I was being very proactive with the
task hide it's hiding to hide not
not I can't die oh
[Music]
no okay got to go got to go got to go I
about to the thing I'm
sorry
wait
was
no guys
I I do wonder if doing tasks is even
worth
it I feel like you just kind of stand
there you become
easy oh my God even the ghost are
extremely quick she ran past she ran
[Applause]
past oh she's going on a murder going to
the cafeteria wait can we tell her okay
might be a little
unfair okay okay I felt that was the
wrong direction okay you know what let's
do our
task I don't know I I I die whenever I
use do tasks it's
[Music]
just in 4k she only has only three
left what is the danger meter come on
guys one more one more
minute oh no
she's going at a good Pace very good
Pace
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh that was a really good hiding spot
yeah that was a nice hiding spot
[Music]
what it's so
loud oh no
whoopsy are slippery yes everybody so
fast one is there overtime she oh
there's overtime there's one more minute
it's so fast I
can't you got
[Music]
survive no pressure oh man 35
seconds just go just go just go you have
30 seconds do it 30 seconds
you're
Phoenix the
walls you have 10 seconds 10 seconds
just 10 seconds easy easy easy easy she
won't get you she won't she won't get
you oh
[Music]
no clut
what I thought we had it in the
bag absolute clutch left one literally
one literally like a millisecond like
0.5 seconds good match
though
amazing that was the clutchest ever what
yeah can't escape time at the end of the
day butar was really slippery oh God
yeah really slippery yeah yeah oh my God
that was
exciting
ex I'm I'm pretty exhausted from that
but we can do another one if you want
I'm down for one more okay
oh actually you know wait wait oh no
before Oh I want to I want to speed so
fast yeah it's fast oh good okay okay
never
mind how do you kill the whole time
there's a kill button so don't you worry
okay oh my God no
way oh no she has awakened she has
awakened I'm coming for you nobody's
using my hiding spot
right good idea don't use my Hiding
might go use it was that your no that
wasn't your
shoot I didn't notice she was there
she's on a rampage there were two people
saw one
person
overlapped does the music get louder for
me too I feel like it does I don't know
it gets louder for oh when you're near
someone really even for
imposter get out of there get out of
there you little
[\h__\h] oh my gosh what's going on
[Music]
no
slippery
[\h__\h] I
loveing checking the
corn oh no that's okay dead bod okay
okay I still got time I still got
time oh I saw someone where
[Music]
is that hiding
spot
oh my God that was that was nice no I
haven't found anyone in my PES you
passed by
somebody someone's here no oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] where are
you hello I'm all
alone no hints no help what was that
there was some button popping up there
the use button
yeah I didn't even see you that's lame
what the
heck see you I saw you that's all that
matters
nice quick oh
no oh one more one more one more
[Music]
run no no no one minute there's still
one more
minute they're literally right there run
run run run run
you can throw it through a loop just run
just
[Music]
run that a sick game p p p p
p
wow do
do that was clch again pretty clutch I
would say that was game
Mama Mia that was wow that was fun that
was that was fun that was merry I'm too
excited to say anything so let's start
with the with the goodbyes from anybody
but me
um please do yeah this is really fun I'm
glad we could get together and have like
a little Christmas Among Us
celebration perfect holiday SE holiday
game
righted and some blood when I think of
Christmas I think of Among Us violence
and death ornament yeah that's pretty
festive you know this makes me want to
play this makes me want to play project
winter
yeah fun yeah I know Cy project
and it's winter thank I'm sorry you died
so
often
St detective but that's okay it's still
fun Kelly what about you you had some
good good kills was fun it was nice
getting to dust off the old Scythe for
once and get back in the game for a
little bit that was nice happy
holid yeah I had a great time with
everybody here everybody here is fun to
talk to fun to argue with in a fun way
really
in a fun way in a fun way I guess that's
about it we should argue more often yeah
let's do it let's do it no no I can't
maybe not yeah no we just stay TIY but
within among us we can argue as much as
we want right and then outside of Among
Us you know we're different people among
us changes us but what happens in Among
Us St in among
us us Among Us
[Laughter]
all right and Fa please please tell me
about your experience today science
Rules science science the science of L
science science science Rules end
statement next
great interesting interesting I don't
quite understand but I agree oh I don't
think kiar knows about Bill it's all
right don't worry about
it don't worry about
it tell you later we'll tell you later
oh it's a m okay
a Mrs Mrs Santa Claus yes yeah no this
was fun I'm glad I was able to lie
better this
time yeah you did some good lying yeah
we to learn from
IR that was fun everyone everyone was
great I love how bad F was at
lying you you can tell it's their you
can tell it's their first time you can
tell it's their first time I would be
like that my first time too it was the
same as me when I played for the first
time worry first time was always like
that it's great I love it thank you very
much that was fun they were so lucky cuz
like in that one round they were about
to be voted off yeah the first and I
thought I was going to be alone but then
somehow somehow they survived they
survived
right we couldn't save
you it's okay we couldn't save each
other even if we wanted to yeah well
thank you Iris and then
people what about you I was happy to be
able to kill people I wish I was able to
kill more people but I was satisfied
with the amount of people I was able to
kill this time Dad the spirit thank you
for your service dad's the spirit that's
Christmas Spirits let's go let's
go that was some good it was
solid good job again I'm so sorry P it's
okay
Trail what stays in Among Us stays among
exactly
exctly well we l a lot of things today
we're really good at lying right yeah
that was
it yeah and uh we have fun we we yelled
a bit screamed a bit and we did a lot of
lying yeah most importantly we had
[Music]
fun so true let's play
more when I saw I was imposter with Fu I
knew I knew that you weren't going to be
good at
lying
have to do
face sweet yeah it's all good it's funny
good I had so much fun thank you so much
for putting it together
K I'm sad I had to be the impostor I
don't like it brings me no
joy what you mean no oh but you were so
good though you were good at it round
was over right
away of blue women women are scary blue
women I always say it it's the blue
people the the avatars I always say
it yeah thank you you're welcome I'm
glad you had a good time let's continue
this in the Mal Dives yeah
peacefully the other the blue woman
Quon yeah it was a lot of fun I'm kind
of surprised that I actually got
impostor twice oh was it I never get
imposter yeah I never get these
roles yeah and thank you for organizing
this it was a lot of fun I love among us
this is
fun I guess you know there was all sorts
of drama but like we said earlier what
happens Among Us stays Among
Us wow
beautiful well said Thank You
Quon well yeah that's pretty much it um
but Christmas is not over yet I think
there's still members that have like
special streams upcoming so check them
out everybody and I just want to make
one quick announcement about the whole
Ian Advent calendar some people may
already know but the last day the 25th
day will will be delayed a little bit so
uh a few days uh the it's out of my
hands out of my power now but please
check back on it next week we'll all
tweet about it when it is finally up uh
so stay tuned stay excited and thank you
for spending Christmas with us viewers I
say to you viewers thank you for
spending it with us and thank you to the
girls for spending it also with us thank
you for getting together at this time
Merry
Christmas
[Music]
CH happy H every had a lot of fun that
was really great and I hope everybody
has a nice nice holiday season cookies
yeah y yum yum yum yum I have some
protein milk in my fridge cookies in
very
Christmas maybe Sant Santa will come to
drink your milk oh protect your
milk yeah protect I don't think that's
going to make Iris like Santa
anymore does not a lot oh no that's
scary Santa is iris is literally the
tree now I'm the tree but I'm not yeah
tree is don't let Santa drink the
protein milk we can't let him get any
stronger no no muscles for Santa no
don't give him the power poison the
cookies wait is like in some countries
Santa drinks beer or people give beer to
Santa really maybe something Santa gets
drunk I don't know I think so drunk
Santa visiting kids homes I don't know
that's yeah oh no oh
no it just makes it worse that doesn't
really sound like something I would want
to tell my
children yeah okay with that I think
some people already gone like fle is
gone already so let's go everybody thank
you merry Christmas happy holidays and
to all a good
even Merry Christmas Merry Christmas
Merry
Christmas Christmas you
my
no next
something
fall I've been down
here almost like I'm back
[Music]
home lonely and all begins to
fade I got no power left
today I don't know I don't know if
things would ever change I think I'll
just be stuck here
anyway those nights when your energy is
nowhere to be nowhere to be found do you
see the LI
or feel like a oh it's
bottomless I'm trying to figure out how
to St in this and all of
gravity when day the is grabbing me and
E think nobodys what they're Me Maybe
I'm not alone maybe not
alone
that was fun wasn't
it a lot of
lying if only if only if only I wasn't a
little I should have I should have been
a bit more proactive in killing but I
feel like if I did I would have been
caught I would have been
caught it was fun though it was fun I
think this is the that was the best um
the best impostor I've tried so far yeah
ah that was a lot of fun hideand-seek
was
wild I wanted to kill croni I'm sad I
couldn't kill
cron I'm upset I couldn't uh but
yeah and the self report I'm I'm
actually I'm I'm super proud that my
self-report actually worked like I was
able to self-report without getting
caught that I was self-reporting
it was it was I was I was really proud
of that that was my most proudest moment
I think seai killing Mak
yeah
yeah oh God don't don't don't bring this
back to school days that was fun Merry
Christmas guys
h i i kind of used my Thro a lot today I
don't know I don't know if I will I I
want to do at least like a space
tomorrow or
something I'll try to I'll try to do
like a space tomorrow yeah might not be
long but I'll try to do like a space or
either that or if my throat feels fine
maybe a members but maybe I'll try to do
a space yeah I did I did sing and then
screamed a lot in Among Us I'm just like
but I do want to you know I am spending
Christmas with you guys right now even
though it's Christmas Eve over here it
might not be Christmas over there though
so yeah
but thank you very
much I took like a two and a half hour
bath yesterday I was just in the tub I
was watching all the school days ending
Clips I was watching all the school days
ending Clips I was watching kotona fall
from a fall from a building I was also
watching cotona SL seai on a bridge I
was also watching seai stabbing Moto at
a at a at a lake and then see I was
watching all the endings in the bathtub
last
night it was a very comfy comfy watch
yeah
yeah and then I was yeah and then I was
looking up all the other games and
there's another game that the cross days
and then um Shiny Days and all the I
actually haven't checked out the endings
for those I should I should I
should but yeah that was comfy
I'll see you guys again soon though
thank you very much virus
virus