[Music]
hello kitty
i feel like um the subscriber count is
like going up faster
than like normally
on purpose just so that i don't have to
sing so long you don't want me to sing
longer
wet
[Music]
i always wanted to do a stream like this
and i woke up early today because the
ghostbusters came to my house again
uh again they found nothing i mean i i
know there is something but
then they are just invincible the ghosts
are invincible
so anyway i was awake and then i
realized oh my god i'm so close and i'm
not sure like what i should should i do
a celebration afterwards or so
whatever i came to the conclusion the
best idea is
to do this kind of stream where i sing
until uh
i reach 500k subscribe by the way this
that is not a live count that is just a
screenshot
so let me know if we reach 500 thousand
but this stream will be archived yes uh
uh since it will be uncapped i cannot
sing any random song it has to be on our
list where we have permission
uh i'll sing a few songs and we'll see
how it goes
and this will basically be our 500k
celebration as well
so since it seems like i don't have much
time
should we go right into the first song
[Music]
30 minutes i will definitely read super
chats at the end though yeah
oh my god okay let's go let's go i'll
sing an idol song
let me put it in the list
should i translate that for you how do i
translate that
uh how do you write campus like a school
campus how do you write that
something like that okay that's huge
okay something like that okay here we go
this is scuffed this is very scuffed
doom deny i'm not prepared let's
go
is that okay
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
hey
is
[Music]
um
me
i made the bgm audio louder is it fine
[Music]
now
me
[Music]
yay we got one song down
yay now
let me check
ah okay ah i think it didn't get updated
it's it's fine okay it's still fine
we're not
we're not i don't think it changed
thank you okay next time but it's
totally unplanned i'm going totally
random through my list
of nothingness
i think um what should i sing go to my
collocate list
[Music]
have i sang uh have i sang
have i have i sang bluebird without my
leg before like after i fixed black
i wonder no no i can only sing songs
today that are
on my list with permission because it's
an archived
one no you know you don't think so yeah
you think
not sure well okay you know what i'll
sing another idol
song maybe
[Music]
sorry i'm not so so so so prepared
i want
[Music]
yeah next song
let me write it down stupid ads
i have a ad block but when i turn it on
then youtube doesn't work properly
for god's sake okay next song is uh
yumeyum i love this song
tell me if the audio has to be adjusted
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
a
[Laughter]
[Music]
hello
um
[Music]
da what
i was i only sang one and a half song
not even one and a half songs before we
reached 500k
really though let me check
is it rounded up for you guys or
something
oh dear why is it so much faster when
you do this kind of marathon streams
did you guys make like fake accounts or
something i hope you didn't
this is are these real people
wait let me let me uh
screenshot that and put that on this on
the screen
hey thank you all so much for the super
chat thank you oh my god
well that was fast um i think i'll
continue singing though if you don't
mind that was too fast
at all
[Laughter]
sing kelly song i still can't i still
can't
[Music]
wow thank you so much for subscribing
thank you
can i sing more sing cruel angel faces
oh okay did i ever sing that before
oh yeah did i never sing that before
i feel like it's a song that i would
sing before but
then i've never seen that before
thank you
[Music]
i did oh well i shall sing it again then
okay where is it where is it everywhere
where we were
[Music]
where is it where is it
my voice is still like so rough
from waking up
i wish i could sing tamashii refrain
[Music]
i shall answer to your request my friend
it shall be my next song very epic song
i don't need your ads for god's sake now
okay let me write it in the list well we
already reached it we're saying a few
more songs and then i read super chats
this is how i write it i hope
thank you everyone for the super chat
holy
thank you my voice is still so rough
today
shiny smiley story that would be very
inspiring because i hadn't i didn't sing
it
since my debut stream wait was that
chinese man of story was it a different
song that i sang
oh is that the song i sang during my
demo
was it a different one
thank you guys thank you
until 600k um no i don't think that's
going to happen
yes it was okay well um
do i have the karaoke version on my pc
right now
wait a second let me check that
because that would just close all the
circles
i don't know where it could be shiny
[Music]
ssx god damn it i don't know man
or maybe he ah i found it oh i found it
well okay you know what i will sing that
because during my debut uh stream it was
uh kind of
scuffed anyway because i still had the
bad microphone and
i still had the lag issues which is
i think now kind of fixed okay
then forget that oops
forget that maybe we'll sing it
afterwards
500k shiny
smiling smiling spotlight smite smiling
story
let's go oh but wait oh we'll wait i
think
it should be fine it should be fine
because this one i don't play on this
one i'm not playing on
on youtube i'm playing it on my play
music player
i wonder if the lag will be fine i hope
oh it starts off right there right
okay
[Music]
i know
high
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
hi
thank you so much for subscribing and
supporting me
[Music]
is
my
thank you
[Laughter]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
uh i don't know if i should end the
stream now man
or should i sing more
do you want more it was too short i
thought i
could sing like at least like 10 songs
or something
thank you i hope that one day
one day i want to sing the song on stage
with my senpais one day
[Music]
but no problem let's go
my god this is so exciting
[Music]
wow
let's go
thank you my super chats everyone
one more time one more time
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
foreign
hmm
[Music]
hey
m
[Music]
foreign
is my papa here papa
[Music]
papa
hello hello welcome everyone who's still
coming in we already reached 500k
but we're still singing because we're
celebrating celebration
down come on whoo you know what i want
to sing
that song because i never sang that one
before but it's quite a classic
yes of course you have to show me ads
first of course you do of course of
course yeah
totally normal
[Music]
in like i don't know a year or something
so
[Music]
let's go you guys ready sing with me
me
[Music]
thank you guys for the uh
uh
[Music]
[Applause]
m
[Music]
uh
hi hi hi
hi hi
[Music]
guitar
um
[Music]
be
this song here
yeah yeah oh i wanna sing this song
because um
i wanna sing this one and i wanna sing
this song and i wanna sing this song and
i wanna sing this song
thank you thank you
next song i want to sing because i sang
this one before when i was doing like
whisper asmr but i was only whisper
singing it and that was kind of lame so
we're singing in
the the actual song properly now
secret bass kimi
ga kudeka
well i need some water
by the way by everyone who doesn't know
for everyone who doesn't know let's
let's have a brief intermission of uh
of uh advertisements
[Music]
number one
first original single releasing 26
november this week
on thanksgiving
first of all on youtube and um
later on maybe a week later or something
i don't know
on spotify itunes amazon music
everywhere
as well and number two this will
probably be a bit too big let me fix
that
yep that's too big one second
there you go thanksgiving 2020 special
voice
also on sale uh on thanksgiving because
uh
to celebrate till the release of my song
situation voice a quickly morning at
cafe thank you message from kiana and
bonus takashikiya's first original song
of goku
it is uh quite the week for
takanashikiyara fans
it is quite a week should we get rid of
this one
yep very exciting week and if you didn't
see my schedule i'm also collabing with
bacon i sent by this week
so now that we have uh the
advertisements done also later today i'm
playing fire emblem please come to my
stream
now that we have that cleared out let's
sing the next song
[Music]
okay relax
oh
[Music]
alexander
okay
[Music]
foreign
my
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
oh
thank you for finding me
thank you
[Music]
thank you for all the super chats thank
you for all the memberships thank you
mario and thank you for
hyping up my karaoke stream for
celebrating together with me
thank you so much
but this was not the last song
no no no i'm still going
i'm never gonna give you up don't worry
i'm not gonna sing that
next song
you know by this sound which song it is
do you know by this sound in the
beginning only
no you're wrong i guess you're wrong
okay god wait is it gonna be
that's a dot dot god knows
lots of her first time singing today
okay
[Music]
foreign
god
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
i
is
[Music]
i
yes
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you thank you that was
fun that was fun i didn't even practice
but i'm so glad it went well
thank you that was fun
[Music]
is it okay if i still continue singing
i wanted to sing this one never sang
this one either
before oh yes i have to sing this one
sorry i'm having so much fun 500k
celebration
thank you all for the support thank you
for the super chats thank you thank you
thank you
next song is the first time for me as
well
i actually love guren nagan
so much it's you could say it's one of
my top five favorite animes
oops
so i never sang this one in karaoke
before though so let's see how it goes
yeah cali do it kelly sang this as well
yeah my wife
there we go
[Music]
today
is
[Music]
uh
um
[Music]
the drums are up
what do you mean
[Music]
yes
is
[Music]
oh
thank you
thank you was there something off with
the
audio
i hope not
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you i hope you enjoyed that
also my first time singing that one yeah
it wasn't the original track yeah we use
like karaoke
versions that are like made for
our karaoke sessions i guess it's a
specific channel
music sounded off
nice that crap okay
i wanna sing like maybe three four more
songs
never ending karaoke
[Music]
wait was the one yeah yeah the one i
just had in my head was
um do i have it in my list
yes
okay my second favorite anime do you
guys know which one it is
my first favorite anime is uh
right you guys know that do you know
what my
second favorite is
because this the next song is from that
anime
actually no it's uh i mean i like stands
kid as well
no no you guys don't know what
and you say you know takanasi kiara
but you don't know this what
what well my second favorite anime
is
so i'm singing only my railgun
it's a difficult song so don't judge me
for
messing up ok
that was unexpected well i hope it's um
i hope i'm not gonna mess it up let's go
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
m
but
[Music]
wow thank you what an exhausting song
what an exhausting song
i love railgun so much
thank you thank you thank you thank you
i hope that was not too bad
next song
[Music]
there's so many songs that i want to
sing but that i
that we don't that we're not allowed to
sing and in
archived streams only in on archive
streams
but i think i want to sing one last song
oh one last song one last song
i kind of have uh already an idea
of what i want the last time to be but
i'll check for my list one last time too
oh maybe i should ah
[Music]
yeah no kimi no no nagatari is not
actually not really allowed for our kept
song with archive streams
microphone moved come back come back
don't move stay
okay i'll give you some choices uh eva
why why don't we sing all kiana why
don't we sing all of them
why does there have to be a choice kiara
good question
wait a second i'm going for the list
looking for anything that i didn't think
of that i want to sing
[Music]
all of them actually
i found no never mind that one never no
no
no so i was thinking bluebird
or
bluebird or lion
anything else
but those are songs i sang before right
but lion i never sang alone
unravel i can't sing that song i don't
have any practice
in that song
all the above
i mean sounds good to me
song from cali i can't i can't sing her
songs
so they're so difficult
[Music]
i want to practice them until i can
actually sing them properly or like
wrap them properly i guess you would say
late congratulations it's not that late
it's just it just happened like
i don't know 30 minutes ago or one hour
ago actually now
well we've been saying it for an hour
really that long already i didn't even
notice
what we're seeing for an hour
and pretty much with no talking breaks
in between as well just now
taking a little tiny break
okay i'm gonna end it soon because i
have to take a nap again
i have to take another nap as i do every
day
i don't need
[Music]
it's so hard to choose
actually i wanted to sing one really
calm
song as well but i don't know if you
might get
bored by me singing that particular song
it's it's quite the beautiful song
never really you'll find with a
with a chill song oh god there's so many
songs to choose from
okay let's sing okay three more songs
three more songs
the next song is a chill one next song
is a quiet chill song
where do i have it
wait a second let's go here
this this is the title right
i
i can't i can't find a key
i can't find it now
okay i don't think it's in my list after
all i thought it was in there
for some reason okay i'll sing
no no no no i don't want stupid ads no
shut up shut up shut up
goddammit stupid ads every time they get
me
every goddamn time and then they don't
stop as as fast as i want
oh wait wait this song this song i want
to sing this song
i remembered one song
but this time i'll probably not sing so
well because it's kind of low
for me at least
okay
let's sing let's sing two ikimono
songs in a row thank you all for the
super chats by the way holy
i'm gonna read them all after we're done
singing okay
and you a new ikimono for me is because
i didn't sing it song
sing it yet i can't even speak anymore
oh my god what
sakura it has a lot of deep parts and i
can't really sing deep parts that well
but i'll try
let's go
[Music]
one more time
i wasn't ready
[Music]
foreign
hello
[Music]
oh
him
[Music]
i
uh
[Music]
a
me
[Music]
oh
hello
[Music]
m
is
[Music]
hi
so
[Music]
thank you while i was singing i thought
my super chats were like bugging out
because
i i felt like i saw the same message oh
no it's not just the same length
over and over again in the in a in a red
super chat it was kind of confusing like
hey what's happening with my super chats
thank you so much what the hell
i'm going to read those carefully but
did you notice how
the the really low parts i could barely
sing
my voice was dying there but i wanted to
sing this anyway
i did see it while i was singing i was
like what what is going on
thank you so much
i will sing that i will sing that count
i will i will read that carefully
when we get to the super chat reading
now let me sing two more songs because
we are celebrating here we're
celebrating celebrating that we reached
500k
thank you thank you
well after sakura
comes bluebird is that
is there space between that i don't know
one of my favorite songs to sing for you
guys
actually i also really like
[Music]
it
i like that one as well but uh the
um it's kind of the there's like a lot
of
fast parts that are really hard for me
to sing
all right i need to practice that song
so i can sing it for you guys so we get
all that
we got we're going to practice all the
ikimunogakari songs
so i can sing them all for you
but for now
[Music]
solar
is
[Music]
okay
m
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
you
oh
thank you thank you thank you and we
have come to
the last song are you ready
with no break in between for one last
song everyone
and then we shall then we shall read
the super chats after that
one last song is going to be
as i told you
this one
lion
let's go
[Music]
m
me
[Music]
ah
um
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
is
m
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you that was a cough at the end i
can do that high note better i can do it
better
i can do it better but my my voice is
kind of rough today
thank you that was our cardoke marathon
our spontaneous karaoke marathon to
reach 500k where we reached
500k literally after the first song
[Music]
why am i surprised why am i even
surprised that inna is a link
hope you all had fun thank you so much
for sticking around thank you for
subscribing let's see what the
what the most recent subscriber count is
though let's check it out shall we
refresh
damn like is it a thing that when you do
these marathons
everyone just suddenly feels like they
want to subscribe out of nowhere
cool
[Music]
this is quite quite amazing
let me add the latest status
we are at 505 503
000 current subscribers we started out
with
uh 498.00
wow thank you all so so much for joining
the stream thank you so much i had lots
of fun to be singing with you for you
guys and
hyping hyping hyping hyping my karaoke
songs thank you guys so much thank you
for all the
support you give me thank you for
supporting me not only today but since
my debut
thank you so much half a million this is
half a million
half a million that sounds quite uh
crazy
i would i would have never imagined to
reach
such a number like
in this year or even next year like
i would have never imagined these kind
of numbers before i debuted that
it's quite crazy um but i'm really
really really thankful
for all the support and the love that
you give me guys thank you so much
please support me
and with that said i will move over to
my super chat reading screen
everyone who wants to leave you may
leave but
i do uh i do want to say
my super chat reading streams are super
chat readings are famous
for being quite fun
oh my god thank you thank you all so
much uh
and the thing is like the week the week
stays exciting like that the week
doesn't even stop yet it just started we
reached 500k
but on thursday i'm releasing my first
ever original song
non-stoppable kiara where's my chat
well there it is
there's so much stuff going on i should
maybe turn off my my echo right
i'm scared that recently obs streamlabs
has been acting
weird so i'm kind of scared to turn off
my echo
let me build myself for a second
[Music]
uh and you kind of need to go to an idol
meeting
for one minute is that okay
can i take an idol idol meeting break
for one minute
[Music]
it's
please no please don't send no don't
send flush super chat i'm gonna i'm
gonna skip them by the way i'm not gonna
read those okay but do it do what you
feel like you want to do
do what you think you have to do to be
happy
but i will not read those plush super
chats
no way no way
i told you don't send the flash super
chats
god's sake you're spamming
the next guest for the next guest for my
next holo talk
has been officially decided
oh my god where should i put this
there's no space
i will not tell you you will see next
week
when i post my schedule
until then it shall remain a secret
alrighty everyone are you guys ready for
some super chat reading
you guys do hear some btm right you
should be hearing some pcm
[Music]
wow i'm just i'm surprised there's still
so many people here thank you guys for
hanging out with me okay so yesterday in
my super chat reading i did catch up so
i only have to read the ones from this
stream let's see what you guys have to
say in your lovely lovely lovely super
chats
you all are such sweet sweet cutie pies
scroll scroll square squad squad squad
squad as well
oh god the flash super chats you really
had to do that right you really had to
i lack free version of connect but the
one with with nana was lag free i just
saw it randomly in the super chat
the one with nana was black free or do
you mean like me alone
like that one had no lag but it did i
have lag today i tried i i i
i i did check before
my stream if the there is lag
it's tradition
no lag today really okay but what was
that about
the btm like the drums being like
delayed or something
i didn't really feel that
damn oh well i feel like this is
something where streamlabs though to be
honest
streamlabs why you do this to me or
actually like um
one thing i i have learned although i
don't know
which words to use to explain that so
i'm using a microphone that is connected
to uh what's it called again
uh what's it called well a cloud lifter
and the cloud lifter is connected to
a focusrite what was that again what was
the phone no it's not a mixer
it's not a mixer and that is the thing
if i had a mixer
then apparently i would have no problems
with um with all the audio delay
um yeah i think what i have is an audio
interface
uh but if i had a mixer then the audio
from the background music would kind of
go through the mixer and my voice would
go for the mixer as well first and
then it would be synced up i think from
what i heard at least it was that way in
the studio and
that's the right way to go but and then
then i i don't know i'm thinking of
buying a mixer but i'm not sure what to
buy now
it looks so complicated
oh yeah
it sounds like a abrupt static is caused
by lack of one do you mean those
i've been wondering about that do you
mean those a little uh
like um sounds sometimes
even even it's not even when i peek it's
just like randomly
is that what you mean
because i've been wondering about that
too like
no matter where i record it it's not
even
only when i stream yeah it's like a
popping a tiny popping sound that
happens every once in a while
and i have no idea why that is because
my microphone is like a really good
microphone
several hundred dollar microphone with a
several hundred dollar
cloud lifter and with a focusrite
are you using the other winch no i'm
using the one that came with the
microphone that was already on it
no but this one is really you said it
was like your last mic i don't know
what you're trying to say but this both
mags are actually really good
but this one is at least uh set up
correctly i just don't know about the
popping sound that's like really um
i i still have to figure that out you
need no i don't that has nothing to do
with it
the pop filter is already on it
oh wow oh well
a lack of a compressor see that is
something that sounds legit
but now i don't know what the hell a
compressor is
oh now let's start reading the super
chats show me
um there's a popping sound yeah it's not
that
not that easily noticeable if you just
listen to me normally
you might not even notice unless you
listen very clearly every now and then a
small
puff sound is in my voice
anyway let's let's go ask kelly for help
oh i did ask her before about this i
think and she didn't really know
what caused it i think if i remember
correctly
anyway let's get started
in
sorry for breaking your sleep schedule
sorry minigamer311 thank you
thank you for the red super chat kiara
is probably continuing her lifelong
quest to make me go broke
jokes aside i'm sticking to my goal of
one super chat for stream so here's a
pre-emptive celebratory
super chat to congratulate you on 500k
it's hard to find words to convey how
proud
we are of you thank you
thank you so sweet of you thank you and
also thank you for like um like uh
doing the thing while you send one
separate in
instead of five million thank you
i'm also a little a little bit proud of
myself for the work i've been doing
recently
and i'm glad that my my dear
loyal kfp employees
acknowledge it as well and are happy to
celebrate with me as well thank you
general piccolin your local hall of fame
girl thank you
yeah you have truly fostered the most
kind positive and accepting community
i've ever seen on youtube i've already
made some incredible friends in kfc who
i never would have met without you we
love you so much
oh that's so sweet yeah i know you guys
are getting along quite well
even doing like kadalke like hours of
karaoke
like um sessions with the members in
in the fan discord from what i have
heard
pretty cute how you guys are getting
along pretty adorable
oh i know who i know
so for everyone who's not in the fan
discord
uh check it out maybe you're gonna have
some fun there and you
maybe um maybe you'll find some friends
as well
just like this person
[Music]
if you look up like uh i think like
something like takanawa
fan discord there's like one that is
like in some kind of wiki i think
or in the if you look up in the in the
whole live
discord the the
of official fan this is it official i
wonder
there if you ask kindly they will lead
you to the
individual fan discords of each girl
i think that's how it works
is it unofficial i wonder i'm not so
sure about that
it seems quite official because it's the
biggest one
but i guess it's unofficial yeah it's
not it's not um
moderated by official cover people
but it's there are
they are quite big so if you're not in
there
and you want to chat with some mutuals
go ahead general piccolo
in general involved next time ted
i'm not sure if you saw but i drew some
panel of you in the king song cause i
did see
that was awesome if you'll be taking
requests i totally love to hear some of
it if not i totally understand
ah i'm not sure if we're allowed to sing
that in karaoke streams
and i don't also i don't know how to
sing the song
but thank you it's seeing that fan art
did inspire me to like
it it made me want to sing the song a
little bit like making
like a cover but everyone everyone
already made a king
cover so i'm like uh
no everyone already did it so
[Music]
no but thank you it was very interesting
to see myself in that pose in that style
pretty cool thank you thank you
suzu and rico 69
[Music]
thank you so much mario's entire family
oh god a name i cannot read uh one
second
that's a long name a long name that i
cannot read
let me translate that uh
one second
vladimir is like a russian name but it's
written in like chinese very interesting
cool cool stuff
thank you so much for youtube premium
yeah i should probably get youtube
premium
do you guys have youtube premium
i wonder should i get youtube premium
wait what exactly comes with youtube
freeman
you don't get ads right and then
apparently there is like some special
programs or is that something else
that you can only watch with youtube
premium or is that youtube red or
something what was that
what else is there with it
ah was that something else you can
download videos oh that's useful
then i don't have to use like some
random
sites on the internet i'm going to
download that's pretty cool you can
watch videos minimize on your phone oh
that's actually also useful oh that is
that
that is a good feature because that is
one thing that annoys me on youtube on
the phone that
you always have to keep open the tab and
can't do anything else
that's a cool thing
okay i'll think about it
and yes i've stopped singing i sang like
for an hour even though i reached 500k
after the first song i stand for
for a whole hour so you're welcome to
watch the archive it's going to be
archived
lord turn up thank you vienna concept
watson
[Music]
thank
i never know if it's a l or a big i or a
small l or a big i
the
[Music]
it's like loaf yeah a low 15.
greetings to australia obviously my home
country
first read super chat for this special
milestone congratulations on half a
million employees
yay i'm so proud of my manager thank you
thank you for all your hard work to me
you've never stopped shining oh well it
would have been quite
uh quick if i already stopped chatting
after like two and a half months
you helped me make my 2020 a better year
but enough's happiness let's party let's
party
thank you so much thank you
cmdr alvin thank you
thank you oh i love bimbo did you get a
kiss
thank you for such a sweet support
sweet message half a million first ever
red super chat definitely
going to my beloved piano see i wouldn't
have known if that was a super chat or
not because i
wasn't sure of the currency thank you
for actually telling me that it is a red
super chat
don't know how much big words and word
limits so may i
just thank you one more time thanks for
everything you bring every moment you be
with us
and everywhere you stay in our hearts
thank you for your support always since
the beginning thank you so much
i'm glad you're here the discharger is
blowing up what
i hope i hope i hope it's not a bad
thing like you know if if like
when a survey gets like too big it might
like get more chaotic and
more fights or whatever i hope it's not
bothersome that i mentioned it
damn it is blowing up oh dear
i opened the floodgates oh dear
well have fun there everyone have fun
plural file thank you so much for your
support thank you soon
i know kfb toaster thank you s17v42
magnus person arctic fox thank you soon
[Music]
oh thank you for letting me know you're
here
i'm glad fabrizio sanchez
[Music]
thank you
so and by the way can i make some tea
how's your mouth still hurts ah
i don't know my jaw is uh
yeah it feels a bit tense right now but
it's all right
it's more like every time i read super
chats
my fruit is like you kiara
i hate you
let's go mix of tea
do you put milk in your tea and no i
don't but i put honey in it
lots and lots of honey squeeze that
honey
oops the honey is on my table
god damn it and i don't have a tissue
right next to me
oh god damn it
hahaha my flavor
of the day is chamomile flowers
just like yesterday
i wasn't licking the table i took my
finger
he took the honey from the table
and then licked my fingers but i did not
lick the table
i did not lick the table okay i mean
it's basically
it ends up being pretty much the same
thing but still
that's not any better
[Music]
excuse me
no
[Music]
thank you i was just about to google
your name but i saw your message
slightly don't go to google the name
reads as alexander smalliff thank you
alexander smalliff thank you not
everyone who works hard has achieved
success but everyone who has succeeded
is a hard worker
whoa
that i wonder if that's true
remind yourself work hard and these 500
000 wonderful employees will support you
no matter what god bless
thank you thank you so much and thank
you for writing down your name that
actually really helps
yeah i wouldn't say that that is always
true i would like to believe that that
is always true but
not sure not sure about that
yeah if the world was a perfect world
with no and uh no unfairness
then yes everyone who succeeds would be
a hard worker but
as far as i know this world it's not
quite true
but let's think it's uh let's think
about it that way yeah
let's think about it positively
and there we go water is cooking
where's my spoon i have no spoon
no i have no spoon upstairs
how do i how do i
mix the honey with the tea now it better
dissolve itself
there is no spoon god damn it
gotta try to mix it with the tea bag
finger it's cooking
can i adjust the microphone of it
what a weird number 260 dollars what a
weird number
500k youtube limits us to 500 per 24
hours so i can't do a
full 500 dollars for 500k just wanted to
let
the most hardworking verb in show
business know that she's an
inspiration to us all ah thank you don't
work yourself too hard though we're
looking forward to many more milestones
with you
thank you
thank you so much for your support ah
you're so sweet i'm also looking forward
to many more milestones with you guys
[Music]
i'm so hungry oh my my stomach just said
hello
feed me hello
[Music]
thank you 77
500k on behalf of all those who can't
super chat and all those who can't make
it to the stream right now but yeah it
was quite
spontaneous probably a lot of people
missed it
and all those who can't make it to the
stream right now thank you for always
entertaining us for never giving up on
your dream and thanks
in advance for all the good times to
come we've got lucky
and kp forever thank you
for your sweet words thank you so much
i mean i've talked about this before
uh in another stream in another super
chat reading
i don't want to go to leave into it but
the thing is i already
did give up on
a dream that i had for like many many
many many many many years
a dream that i worked towards for many
many many many years
but it never really came through the way
i wanted it to be
and so yeah you're saying for never
giving up on your dream the thing is i
did
i did and i was i was pretty done
i was pretty much done with believing
that
things ever go upwards again
i always i was i was like yeah things
only go downhill from here whatever and
that was actually kind of like
accepting the fact that things
only go downhill i accepted it i was
okay with it
i already made up my mind and made up my
mind that if i go back to
australia next year that i'll just go
back to
some kind of boring job and give up on
my dreams i was
i was finished but um
something totally unexpected happened
something totally unexpected came into
my life called holy life
and after all these years of trying so
hard and things never really paying off
finally it just comes so easy to me
which
seems a bit wrong right after
after years and years and years trying
so hard and things just not working the
way i want them to go
i joined whole life and even before our
first stream
we have all these supporters right and
that is totally thanks to whole life
thanks to the
senpais who have uh built
whole life to what it is today
so i am absolutely blessed and lucky
because even if i wasn't even if i would
have done like youtubing
like independently i definitely wouldn't
have come this far by now
definitely no let's be real it is all
thanks to whole life
so i want to thank you all
and her life for giving me another
chance
and giving me hope and dreams back
thank you
[Music]
be
thank you all you guys are so sweet
you guys are so sweet
[Music]
um
thank you
now we cheesy and you are awesome thank
you
yeah i'm glad you're on holiday thank
i'm glad too it is true but
does not mean that someone like you have
no value i mean whole life made
auditions and you were selected thank
you
also i hope you know you keep dreams
alive and others by being here your
experience gives us courage to keep on
going
oh i would hope i would hope that that
is true i hope so
where is the next milestone kiara ah
would say 600
not five i don't want to celebrate 550
we gotta go for bigger milestones now
we gotta go like one day later
600k there ain't no time to celebrate
550.
ain't no time for that
600k here we come
[Music]
in
wow thank you so much thank you thank
you
for your support tai chi thank you
for all my heart thank you
samson
[Music]
is that also a recipient i'm not sure
oh it's hard to figure out if it's a
currency that i don't really understand
let's just say this
thank you thank you for your support
[Music]
what happened
no the window where i read it the window
in
in the youtube uh thingy
when you read the super chats it
literally has no color
it just says the name and then the
currency with the amount
and the text and where and where what
stream they superchatted that
there's no color there and the thing is
uh it's like all kinds of different
currencies so since i don't know every
currency that exists on this world
i sometimes i don't know if it's a rat
or not
youtube please add some color
life is happier with more colors in it
if you use youtube chat filter you can
filter out all the super chat
oh you meant you mean in the chat window
oh that's an interesting
that that would be interesting i guess
i don't know how to use that but that's
that's interesting
[Music]
although for example if i read super
chats from previous streams that will
not really work
only really from the current streams i
think
but i'll think about it for next time if
i read it during the current stream
[Music]
i see i live well thank god
what happened why do you have a ghost
super chatting to me
i don't know if you heard that that was
a triple triple
a triple neck crack
very nice
[Music]
yeah they are really satisfying yeah
especially when you can get all free
yeah you know what i'm talking about
hell yeah poster check poster is
horrible
as always thank you
everyone
thank you for the super chat
to my home country australia congrats on
500k thank you so much thank you for
your support thank you thank you thank
you thank you
spicy chicken tacos
[Music]
thank you so much congrats on 500k you
talk about sticking with you really got
to me
since i had been going through a tough
time too and you helped me to get
through it
call us that start with kiara at her
lowest so you can enjoy watching her so
high ah
thank you yeah
i think um i think especially the people
who
have been here from the start which is
not even that long ago but
especially if the people who have been
here from the start have a
special connection with me
i feel it
i'm sorry for misspelling you confused
me there
how dare you confuse me
i'm ashamed of the fact that i haven't
been here since debut and don't worry
about it
don't worry about everyone everyone who
joins afterwards is also a very special
very special special special part of the
kfp menu
no sorry kfp crew not manual
congratulations on half a million yes
that sounds so crazy doesn't it
you've caught so far and come to mean so
so much to
so many people and i really couldn't be
happier for you kiara you're
truly a blessing and an inspiration and
i'm so proud of you in this whole
community
thank you thank you for your kind words
to a million that's too far away
it's gonna take a while but i'll try
let's try together one day
one million phoenix what 1 million
fin 1 million youtuber phoenix
what
[Music]
by the way i'm trying to get through
this low-key quickly
because i want to take a nap before the
fire on livestream
hope you guys don't mind
i hope you guys don't mind i'm still
reading the big messages and the red
super jets still
that's that
verb always sleepy for real
prime blood stream is today yeah in how
many hours uh
do i start at midnight or at 11 p.m it's
in my schedule just check twitter
it's but it's it's i think in
six hours or five hours something like
that oh dear i got a nap
you know my naps take like four hours
okay maybe two hours i'll take a
two-hour nap
because i want this fire and blame
stream to be quite long
so we can make some progress you know
kfb sanitary officer danke thank you
so much congrats on reaching 500k
subscribers
guerrilla streams for our attention
super chat readings emotional super chat
readings has been a rollercoaster ride
indeed thank you for being on dying and
thank you for being
so i can't read anymore thank you for
being an undying and dedicated star that
shines the most it's always
[Music]
foreign
m
[Music]
makes the best fan art of kiara
and cali like especially takamori but
even like
only kiara i ain't
[Music]
i love you
art of me many many times
best art ever i just i just love i love
her all right so much
so much
so much can't get enough of it
so i guess i can call myself lucky
because mama luni
has seems like to be addicted
to drawing me and kelly so i'm really
blessed
[Music]
thank you thank you
400 oh trunks you okay
thank you for the red super chat but no
text
my brain hurts my brain hurts sends a
super chat with absolutely no text it's
just completely blank
i can't even have a conversation with
you
well thank you for your support
i don't know what to say to you because
there's absolutely no text that i can
react to
thank you for always being there thank
you for always supporting me
[Music]
i hope you're happy thank you
congratulations on 500 000 channel
subscribers we're happy to be able to
share this exciting time
[Music]
500k so proud of everything you've
accomplished so far your talk show is
one of the best ideas i've seen in her
life yet oh
thank you you are the ambassador for us
all come back to we love you thank you
chat i don't know it's a check check-ish
stuff wait let me ah
what's that
wait a second
[Music]
ah probably not this is so confusing
because some currencies have like a
million zeroes
is it uh thank you
found in the chat okay sorry google has
been deceiving me
ah it's a red one ah even though it
converts
i see i see i see that the smart
currency thing that youtube is doing
where some currencies weigh more than
others
congratulations on half a million
subscribers kiana also congratulations
on the original song piccolo club and
the voice back and the talks
thank you yeah there's a lot of stuff
going on you're crossing off debit goal
list so fast
thank you for all the wonderful moments
keep doing what you're doing thank you
so much for your support thank you
hope you're gonna stay with me for much
[Music]
longer
well done kiara you've been working so
hard and it really does show can't wait
to see what else you have in store
much love to kfp's best and most spicy
burb ooh spicy
how do you know i'm spicy
thank you thank you for your support i
hope to have you
around until the end of time
500 super chat holy
thank you so much it's just
it only says congrats so
also not sure how how to respond to that
but thank you for your support thank you
for being part of the kfb
crew thank you for watching my streams
and thank you for deciding to be
part of this amazing amazing community
thank you thank you
logical paradox
[Music]
thank you so so so much you are our
queen
thank you that sounds very fancy
the dark sound thank you vlad
[Music]
you've worked hard for this milestone
continue to do your best each and every
day for us
and we'll be sure to do our best to
support you now disable your limiters
and aim for the
thank you thank you
kilometer canvas night thank you thank
you for the red super chat
mwah congrats on 500k this is happening
on my birthday too
what happy birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you
happy birthday thank you for bringing
all kinds of smiles and laughter into my
life these past few months i can't wait
to see what you'll do over the next year
too
thank you i have
quite some ideas for next year
so i think you can look forward to that
thank you and happy birthday i hope you
have a nice birthday
thank you so much
[Music]
it's been so much fun watching since
your debut and i'm so blessed to be in
one of the best
communities out there very true
every stream is so much fun and the
amount of work you put it in it
is inspiring thank you so much for
everything you do thank you
thank you for supporting me
thank you i'm glad you were one of us
one of us one of us
thank you i hope you'll also be there
for much much longer
tea time
[Music]
today thank you for the red super chat
thank you congratulations on 500k
thank you so much
thank you from the bottom of my heart
thank you for your support
see as a possibility for whole talk in
the future
but at the moment i'm more aiming for
the cutie
the cute girls out there to satisfy
my own wishes and dreams you know
no i have not heard of that um
sounds interesting uh jindrick jin rich
resh thank you gary character
and but thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
congrats on 500k it makes me so happy to
see how much you continue to grow and
reach so many of our hearts for your
hard work and dedication viva la chiara
heard that guys viva
[Music]
thank you so much for your support and
but thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
tyrek thank you thank you message by
nexad oh
congrats for 500k i'm super grateful for
you you have come really far and i look
forward to see more of your dreams come
true
thank you
thank you next second i'm also glad to
have you
i think your support is a is a big part
of
spreading the love of kiara spreading
the words
so i'm really really really glad you
keep on making those videos
if
[Music]
thank you very much for being your
attention i'm legit crying of happiness
for you thank you don't cry
amma will come to lick your tears kind
of creepy you and the cafe community are
the best community i love you all thank
you
so sweet but watch out for
me
i see it as a win
[Music]
cute thank you
it's the start of the era of the phoenix
yes so might as well start
it's in a very good note with the holo
talk the original song and this all this
hard-working and i'm so
so happy to see you grow more and more
after all every week is now canada week
that is true
thank you thank you for your support
so sweet
it is a lot of stuff going on and i have
to say it's um
i'm a bit a bit worried that uh
it will get a bit too much for me at the
moment but
i think after um this week i'll try to
take it a bit easy
easier than before although next week i
have a holo talk
so i gotta prepare quite some stuff for
that and i have another deadline
next week which i cannot really talk
about
so maybe maybe after the next week i can
relax a little bit
with that being said after the next week
we're getting closer and closer for
christmas and obviously i want to
prepare something
for that as well if i can but i'm not
sure
but yeah we will see
i need to do some shorter streams as
well
like one hour streams like one hour
gaming something and then super chat
because i do i do a lot of longer
streams and
i barely have any time for like real
real stuff
in real life you know
but for now i just keep on writing that
uh wave riding the hype it's the era of
the phoenix at least for this week and
next week
and then after that we have to maybe
calm down a little bit
to take care of my health as well you
know i'm i am um
i'm one of those people who do realize
when it's too much
and i mean when when it's so much it's
so much fun streaming
for you guys with if you guys are around
i have so much fun so it's kind of hard
to stop myself but
i have to set priorities gotta get some
stuff done
how often do you visit the doctor for
checkups
once i like not even i don't go for
checkups i only go if there's something
like going on i went like
one time in like january this year
or like a few times in january february
and then once i went to japan i didn't
go a single time
but it's okay it's ok
thank you
good idea on saving that thank you thank
you very smart jaclyn
salad oh thank you owl i say that wrong
i pronounced that wrong thank you for
the memberships guys by the way there's
so many new members today
uh congrats on hitting 500k yeah you
definitely earned all the subs never
forget that you are
you and we follow you because you
brighten our lives ah
question will you have pictures outside
of her life on youtube
no i want it to be only whole life
not saying that i will never collab with
anyone outside of whole life
but for whole talk i wanted to be whole
life members only
but you know one one independent
youtuber that i want to
um collab with eventually
maybe you know her she's quite popular
on twitch
she's called baby and she has the same
papa not not yet she she's getting like
a live 2d model she's been like
in 3d the whole time and she gets like a
lively model made by the same person who
made mine
so i feel like kind of connected and
she's kind of cute
and we follow each other on twitter
so that might happen at some point
v yeah v e i and then b
a e yeah we kind of like
kind of connected by our kefi papa
i mean maybe we're half sisters i
wouldn't say we're sisters
maybe only half sisters
adonis romero gonzalez
[Music]
thank you oh another name i cannot read
let me um let me translate
wait a second i want to know what i'm
saying i hope i'm not saying anything
read
oh interesting name see
[Music]
there's still like a bunch of red super
chess coming in holy
thank you thank you
ali has no contention
super chat the phoenix with a heart of
gold and cell
which burns hotter than the sun ooh very
deep congratulations on 500k subscribe
thank you everyone
how did that start anyway i wasn't even
the one who got that running
the viva
maybe i should turn off the donations
i'm kind of scared this will go on too
long my throat hurts
me oh it's worth you i kind of thought
so
it's a thing now
that honey that sweet sweet honey
ah
wait
thank you general thank you salute
so yeah thank you kp thank you so much
mwah for your support
mr vlt thank you well now i want a blt
sandwich even though it is
a vlt now i want a blt sandwich thank
you
god damn it
hey
[Music]
thank you for your support thank you so
much
your local hollow fangirl thank you
thank you
proxy language and thank you for the red
super chat
[Music]
kevin okay we made it so happy to see
you right like a phoenix and blow all
expectations out of the water you've
worked so hard on everything you
and it's great to see it all pay off
did you pass your exam female qps
so you can read my name like 20 times
really fast
are you gonna do it i mean yeah okay
or are you saying you we're gonna do
that and you decided to not do it
and thank you anyway thank you so much
for always being there
even though you probably should be
focusing on
your uh your inter
intern stuff
i'm happy to have you thank you so much
thank you shane
type 91 thank you
rico
can you sing hello how are you yeah i
want to sing it but we don't have
permission to sing it
uh i think because uh i know some others
sang it before
but that was uh before i think we got
permission for everything
before that i could sing it in an
unarchived kind
which is actually i do want to do that
just keep on reminding me when i say
next time i say i'm going to do an
unarchived karaoke stream tell me to
sing
hallo how are you beforehand
that would be very helpful max 8413
thank you
thank you so much thank you
jonathan graham duncan trevor g oh there
we go
something happened there apparently
trevor g
duncan let's read that thank you for the
red super chat first of all
congratulations on 500k substantial i
have been watching since the beginning
and i have done my best to catch every
stream live whoa
i must confess yes i subscribed before
you debuted
but with your first kikitiki i knew i
made the right choice
is this like this is a proposal wait let
me skip
to this and then go back to the others
and read the rest i mean skip the other
people and then come back to the other
people
continuing i'm very proud of how far you
have come and how you've grown for
everything you've endured to get here
from a potato mic
a potato pc a potato internet service
provider and potato skills and mario
games
what are you talking about i'm a
professional mario kart driver
at least i was in my previous life that
counts as well
you have uh preserve it and i don't know
how to pronounce that
persevered and shown you two words
next one you started insecure about your
capabilities but you have shown
us how capable you are you are more than
just multilingual
you are an artist capable of drawing
beautiful arts singing incredible songs
and bringing smiles inspiration hope to
your viewers
next i can't wait to see what the future
holds for you i'm stoked for your first
single and i'm happy for your collab
with piccolo
me too i want piano products so i buy
your voice pack
if i can make one request i want uh
wants to hear you sing
ring a bell by bonnie pink i don't know
that song something i guess i'm not
that much of a boomer after all
next i grew up in a family of fall
corners
that's awesome what and have always
loved mips so of course the legendary
bird of fire would not
be only the first person i gave my first
second third and fourth and fifth super
chats but also
be my absolute favorite beach broke yeah
i wrote to one million hyped
that's so sweet
damn
thank you i'm so glad to have such a
sweet fan
thank you i mean all of you are damn
sweet
thank you your kind words are
very touching
[Music]
and i am i'm surprised you called every
stream but i guess you don't necessarily
mean you caught every stream live
because that would be
insane because then you would have to
live
exactly the way i live
but thank you for your effort thank you
for watching everything i really really
really appreciate you watching
everything
[Music]
that is one of the best support i can
ask for from you guys is to watch my
streams like every single one of my
streams
so you don't even have to pay any money
just watch my streams
[Music]
watch
i wonder if i can play that song is that
is that a
chiara what's only kyarya song is that
like completely original or was that
made with some copyrighted material i
wonder
because i want to play it
it's original how do you know
well if i get bunked for playing this
then we're gonna have a problem
but i feel like it now
i bet all of you have a girlfriend or
boyfriend
no this is okay
you have me what else could you want you
have
what else did you want what else you
[Music]
watch my streams every day
this is okay this is okay
this is
[Music]
you'll probably not have time for me
anymore your partner will probably be
like
what don't watch kiara
focus on me don't stay with anyone
do whatever makes you happy but i would
say watch my streams every day
what else could you want what else
maximum volume
[Music]
listen to it every day let it be the
hymn that you wake up too
[Music]
how about i play that in the background
no just kidding
i love it it's so funny thank you for
making
that it's such a funny song
[Music]
sorry is that too loud that's probably
too loud is it okay now
my pgm
the kfb anthem
i suppose it is
can you pin it why are you too slow just
look up
uh watch only me hold alive kiara
look that up on youtube you'll find it
you'll find what you're looking for
wow that was a small tangent
so uh trevor g again thank you so much
very very kind of you very generous
thank you thank you thank you i
appreciate it
so so so much thank you
glad to have you
tom blakely
thank you use
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
to the hardest working phoenix in the
showbiz
well i'm the only phoenix in the showbiz
well yeah thank you
thank you so much so much
and
so i'm getting a bit distracted that fan
song was heat
helium was really good
and
[Music]
you can thank you
thank you so much for everything you do
every day has been filled smiles and
happiness from your streams love you
oh thank you so sweet
i love you too
[Music]
congratulations on 5 on this cake here
it really has been a wild ride from
senior
debut till now and i'm proud to say i
was there from the beginning through
loads and heights
i remember the first day you recruited
me into kfp and i've never regretted it
ever since
all of you are so incredibly sweet
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you
we finally reached health a million i'm
proud to be an egg since day one
thank you i'm glad you've been there
since day one what's your gross
is your watching you grow it's just hard
when we look at you now
your struggles made you stronger and
mighty phoenix we know you're sparkling
brighter than the sun i'm so happy
for you thank you
thank you so much
what do we eat cereals before after milk
do you mean
do you mean if i put in the cereals
before after the milk is that what you
mean
i put them in before the milk of course
any other way is wrong however what i do
do sometimes
um sometimes i add extra cereals after
i'm done with the ones
that were already in there and having
like fresh crunchy cereals
i guess i do both i guess i do both
huh i do both
the realization
[Music]
i'm not really great with words but
thank you for everything it's been a
wild ride and it's been
a difficult time for me but watching you
has kept me motivated you're my favorite
picture of akiya
thank you for being here
my heart my heart
feels so warm and fuzzy thank you for
your sweet words
i'm also glad that i'm your favorite i'm
so happy i'm someone's favorite to begin
with
thank you for your kindness
and your generosity all of you
goodbye to whoever goes to sleep don't
worry about it
dragoon three four seven thank you thank
you
kimchi pickle thank you for the red
super chats
months ago you were one of us that is
true one of us one of us one of us
today you reach 500k with your first
single release and dear stand by collab
so soon
best of luck because this is only the
start you'll always be my oh
it's always also my birthday what
happy birthday
happy birthday kfc pick off
thank you for your support
it's gonna be a crazy week it's already
a crazy week
but yeah let's go
thank you
i'm gonna do my best since you seem like
a fan of both me and pekora senpai since
you have pickle in your name i hope
you're going to enjoy the collab as well
be free see thank you in your local hall
of fame girl thank you
thank you thank you so much
[Music]
i woke up and you were streaming your
500k celebration i wish i could have
been
there and i wish i could take i gave my
first ever super chat to you because i
found you inspiring and wholesome
and i still do so here's my first ever
red super chat thank you
[Music]
thank you so much i'm probably not here
anymore but i hope you watched in the
archive
thank you i'm glad to have you
in the kfp crew and now here comes the
flashing super chat so i'm gonna skip
those
[Music]
thank you no rice for you
there we go thank you thank you
yeah there's so much going on this week
right so much
um and this one
one yeah don't worry about it
thank you so much okay so now i can
refresh because i reached
the end which also means i'm going to
i just did disable the super chat super
chat
[Music]
i killed the super chat function
no longer no longer
will i take your super chat thank you
though
f
this is how it ends
okay so i refreshed there we go okay
this should we should be done in like
10 minutes let's go thank you
just some storm trooper thank you duncan
thank you
oh you want me to show the names
i feel like there might be some problems
with that because then people are gonna
troll me by
changing their names into something that
could
get me into trouble and like it's always
like um
there's a red in the flush dear god
why would you send it at such a moment
which one
why would you do that to unfold
yeah where is it what
what is it what's the currency or what's
name
jacqueline didn't i read that already
and that was right before them
right at the start yeah there was a red
at the start from meltyclaw which i did
read
and after that i don't see any reds
is it still here like
in the chat itself
did you troll me
you trolled me
i see nothing else
bunk you got bunked
well back to where i was
functioning
i have to say mike as you have no
solutions to your issue with a mixer
i'll tweet your info like when we talked
about
oh thank you thank you thank you you
mean the issue with the popping
or the issue with the lag or both even
i wonder if i use a mixer and i probably
don't need my focus right anymore
[Music]
thank you so much for being you you are
wonderful and because of you and
kfp i feel like a family have a family
what when it's sad
and cute at the same time it's brought
me so much joy and happiness and so many
wonderful friends i'm sticking with you
to the end
oh thank you come let me give you a hug
thank you i'm glad you found a place
where you feel welcome that's really
that's really great because i also found
that place
[Music]
thank you september
justin m tomato
cmdr wolf jagger
have reached an astronomical achievement
what is it astronomical really
i'm so proud of how far you came and
excited for your future you have truly
blessed us this year from all of us in
the kfp discord thank you for everything
everyone say it with me
[Music]
i agree strongly thank you so much
herbert can umera thank you
the heck woman it's nate made
thanksgiving hammer checkered
cute animals are the best
[Music]
yes i speak fluent german yes i do it's
my first language
hold on
is
what random fact
is a mop that drinks tears of sleeping
birds
dreams i like to catch a final words can
bring despair and happiness
thank you
i can't donate for you because superchat
is not supported in thailand don't worry
about it
it's definitely not necessary i'm just
happy you guys are here watching my
stream
just happy to have you by my side
sorry i don't know how to read the name
it's something like yodoshiro in
japanese but probably different
pronunciation
for you today is my best friend
a-c-p-o-c-c birthday because you say
happy birthday happy birthday
brandon bologna
good morning you better watch the
archive
so proud and always a joy to pass your
streams watch vods thank you so much for
sorry all of your heartbreak for always
making my day better thank you
that's so sweet thank you thank you
and that's thank you oy country gay
redemption
congratulations on 500k i'm glad you got
new dreams and
are now here with us watching it makes
me want to reach for my dreams again too
after being in a dark place for a long
time thank you for being yourself kiara
thank you i'm glad you got a little hope
from watching me i'm very happy
to hear that
[Music]
oh another one pretty much also saying
something like that you and the other
hawaiian girls
pulled me out of a really dark place and
i'm extremely thankful for that congrats
on 500k
thank you well i'm really really happy
to hear that
you're doing better because of us
[Music]
sorry i didn't recognize it right away
because it's just confusing all these
currencies
currencies are so confusing but thank
you for your support thank you very much
bryce kingdom hamster congratulations on
reaching 500k
subscribers really fun watching your
stream such as fire emblem mario
assumption and the other games
thank you i'm glad you enjoyed them your
super chat readings are really fun to
listen to until the end i will continue
to support you all the way
thank you for you kindness thank you for
your support
i'm glad to have you bye emblem
later today hope you're gonna be there
let's get some sleep before that
louis freaking thank you congratulations
upon
racing fabulous k as i first started to
watch during your karaoke stream where
you've seen
some sweet pedicure ending oh wow what a
coincidence
i wanted to ask you what do you think
about put your franchise franchise
i like it i've watched uh
[Music]
not many of them because i guess it's
just a bit too
not exactly my genre but
i like the anime in general i watched
which one was it there's too many
i watched at least one of the animes
but i i do like all the music that
[Music]
the endings of the opening sketch the
music is it's like
bangers bangers like william goddamn
bangers
[Music]
thank you
thank you for the first super chat thank
you so many virgins out there
angry manchester united thank you for
the red super chat from canada
wow congratulations on expanding your
empire to
half a million employees that sounds
again so insane
kfb crew is ready to follow you through
water flame basement enhancements
cooking
wow that is a very
very dangerous adventure you're going
onto with me but
you all are so brave thank you
[Music]
i'm reading it i'm reading it
even though you told me not to read it
well i at least read it in my head
don't worry sweet of you i'm going to
take a little rest after this drink
i have the sweetest supporters ever i
love you all
i love you and you and you and you
and you and you and you and you and you
and you and you
oh thank you so condom duncan i tried
dancing
thank you for the sweet message thank
you i tried thank you shane i'm glad i'm
glad
you opened your eyes on me kfc pekka
thank you
[Music]
thank you and
thank you for the red super chat yes
it's going to be archived yes yes
enjoy watching it
and last but not least
thank you all so much for your support
[Music]
that was fun that was very spontaneous
very fun uh thank you for
celebrating together with me today i'm
gonna go
eat a little bit and uh uh nap a little
bit and i'll see you in the fire emblem
stream later today
fire emblem
thank you thank you we have reached 500k
which makes today an amazing day but
just wait for thanksgiving 26
november this week
first original single releasing on
youtube
and um probably a week later or
something it will be released
on all kinds of music services as well
so i hope for your support
let's let everyone know
what a banger of a song this is going to
be
i mean you guys don't know but i know
it's a banger so
let's spread it all over the world thank
you so much
for today i'll see you later i'll feed
us
in i'll finish in thank you for 500k
subscribers
[Music]
you go to the right ending this time not
to the old ending
kiara kiara
good job good job
[Music]
you