[Music]
so
do
[Music]
the microphone
there we go
oh my god oh my god
surprise surprise it's not really a
surprise we were supposed to be in this
mod these models hello
hello
oh emma listen to the pose this is the
pose you gotta do a mirror a heart are
we doing a heart
there we go
it kind of works wonderful wonderful
well welcome everybody to uh kfp's
dance school
um
disclaimers we will be or look i will be
glitching out a lot
i don't know why we're trying it's okay
i'll imagine it worked perfectly but
yeah you'll see some glitches but don't
mind at least uh disclaimer number two
is a pinned comment but we'll be um
probably having some whoa asthma attacks
don't mind us um
we might have some breathing issues
dancing with a heavy headset is tough
yeah
and yeah so the surprise guess
disclaimer number three i guess it's a
disclaimer is
wait wait a second wait a second is that
really oh my god is that an is that an
egg
is that an
[Laughter]
it's an egg with limbs
damn you got a strong gravitational pull
[\h__\h] i'm glitching out so much one
second uh so today
um is actually uh sorry
today is actually supposed to be kind of
like a celebration of a dreaming youtube
song cover that i did with ame and as
you can maybe notice by the background
as well yay we got the background from
the music video
yay
really cute okay don't mind me
yeah i don't it's okay you keep keep
doing your thing
um and uh originally we we um did
dreaming choo choo but because of uh
well
um
some reasons i decided to not teach
dreaming choo choo dance but we're gonna
be uh learning a different dance it will
be a song that probably all of you guys
know but uh i asked ame if she knows it
she said she doesn't know it our egg
maybe knows a little bit of it
she was a good student and did extra
homework
um but yeah well we're mostly starting
from scratch and i also recorded like a
little bit of an audio um singing over
it and it's not mixed so it's kind of
scuffed but uh so you know that we have
our own version
um yeah and uh
i've never taught someone a dance before
so this might be uh
i don't know not very professional by
the way how's the audio so far uh the
voices of me and ahmed how's it going
chat uh
yeah does it sound good oh i can read
the chat oh is everything good guys 3d
models cute they say
indeed very cute isn't it thanks the
models are from the music video they're
from pre-two the background is um kind
of put it together but seafoam boy made
it in so that it can be used here i
think
uh i think so
so thank you for that
why is this okay
okay a bit muffled well yeah my my vr
headset is um
is a vive but the microphone is a little
bit uh
a little bit scuffed microphone egg is
supposed to be muted who knows if i sit
on the egg maybe it will um hatch
eventually
yeah yeah it looks like uh
it wants to get out i mean it's already
growing limbs so i think it wants to get
out of its shell eventually maybe maybe
we can activate
some hatching process by making it dance
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh god it's already
dancing oh yeah like warm it up
like you start to warm up your body and
that helps the egg hatch
yeah
all right
uh
okay come closer come closer should i um
get in here i think a good way to start
off the lesson is by showing you a full
example once but i'm probably gonna die
oh god oh god oh god i'm probably gonna
die if i was fine for a while
yeah
um
shall we and
after
after showing you the full thing um we
will start doing uh sections one by one
one by one one by one there are a lot of
repetitive patterns so i hope i can get
that across properly
okay um
um yeah maybe maybe let's play it once
and i'll try to show you the full
example oh god i'm gonna die probably
don't don't mind me
okay let's go i mean we'll turn on the
music because she's the only one that
can control it but she's super active
here we go
free egg you can you can
yeah you both can try to um
already
uh
uh copy my moves if you want
it's a psychopathy
[Music]
double
don't mind me
can't do a turn
[Music]
oh
yeah i'm a ballerina
[Music]
i need to adjust my belt
where's my [\h__\h] head
[Music]
that's it so it's kind of a short
version a little bit shortened
i'll be where are you
i was watching hi
i'm a musician
oh thank you you think you can do it to
try you think you can do it yeah yeah
i think so if you learn each move like
one yeah like oh this part you do this
and then you do this
double step i think i could do it okay
okay i'll try my best to explain it
properly but i'm not good with words
either so
yeah well try my best you gotta be good
at okay um
uh observing the body of an idol and
then you can become okay
egg you're
to my right side yeah yeah
okay
so okay
the song starts out in this stance
uh with your hands on your hips yeah
yeah and then there's a little bit of
accounting
and then it starts we start with
sorry i'm already out of breath it will
go back to noble we start out with uh
crossed arms above the chest and with
the left leg uh kind of like
yeah like that a little bit angled and
and this movement happens a lot so
uh you'll be able to use it a lot so it
starts out like uh
where you go from across to
a right leg and to the outer uh to your
shoulders
and
when that means high then you do it to
the bottom you let the arms go to the
bottom and the left leg is uh up again
and then
you've got uh put them up again now we
can't see this because there's no finger
tracking at least for me so it doesn't
matter what your fingers look like um
but uh
supposedly it looks like an aloha uh
sign originally
up
uh and then padded put it you keep on um
switching the the weight on your uh on
your feet the whole time
you may have noticed so it starts out
one more time it starts out with crossed
outside cross down out wait do you move
your again after you don't cross
side cross shoulders back
switch legs when you switch yeah you
switch every time you do a different
move you switch the leg the weight on
the on the legs
it starts out with
the left leg up
so
shoulders
down
up again
and then pat it apart it
put it put
[Music]
the legs are left right left but the
arms are basically the opposite
i think yeah because okay left leg is up
but the hands are on the right side so
it's like
oh god
what's the chat
egg is cute right egg is doing a great
job as well
looking fabulous over there okay um so
let me let me try to go for i always
have to go through the choreography in
my mind for a second uh my name is
it repeats the same movement twice
and then okay and then we go into an
idle step
we go with the
right leg yeah and the left hand a
little bit to the front
and the right hand to the back so really
um big movements for this idle step okay
as if you're like ice skating or skiing
and a happy happy
dab
oh my leg is uh my hand is glitched okay
and then we have the patty putted
movement again don't don't don't do the
same leg movement
and
but here we have it all the way up in
the air like we just don't care and we
go like this
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] wait oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
i'm learning
wait i'll say it again after doing that
movement two times
the crossed outside down up party put it
two times we go over to uh idle step
really big movement with the arm space
oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
a really big idle step a really big one
it hated me out of the out of my own
existence but okay
wait sorry uh without music it's hard
so two steps left to the right with the
arms really big please and then we have
the arms up in the air
uh for this one and we go
potty put it
powder with the hip to the right side uh
middle right side hands also right side
middle right side
okay and then we do another idle step
uh
hands hands there you go we do another
idle step and this time the same
movement but um the hands won't be up in
the air but they will be up on chests
height okay
yeah yeah bye or something like that
that looks or something like that
okay
shall we can we try from the top yeah i
think we'll try it um
once we've uh without music and then
we'll try with music okay
okay wait
i can move closer because we can see the
camera up there
oh yeah yeah
egg has to be on screen too
okay so it starts out like this and the
in the power stats
a certain dominance
and wait a little bit
and here we go
sorry actually that movement was uh to
the other side the first one was to the
right side
and the second one goes to the left side
sorry
goes to the left
and then i don't step okay to the right
bit to the left up in the air
and again
i don't know how i'm doing
okay i'll do it and then you tell me if
i'm doing it right so like
we can do it with the music then yeah
yeah you start out like this okay
all right okay i think i remember
okay
okay what should we try
down up crossed out down up
and then
crossed out down up or down to the left
first is right
okay
you know
realistically speaking especially for
beginners it's not really realistic for
you guys to learn the choreography
perfectly in just a two hour collab or
so so don't beat yourself up it's not
normal um like for a choreography of
this difficulty you would normally
especially as a beginner need a whole
day or two days to learn it properly so
it's okay okay
there's not gonna be a perfect dance
moves uh
right away but let's start the music
once and
just do that one part okay
oh first can we hear your character in
here see right a little bit heart and
then land on either side okay see the
camera up there we can line it up there
beautiful
i'm haruhi
i'm haruhi in this case
oh god help me house oh lord help me
holy jesus
uh
tracking please
be on my side today
oh
wait a second
are you ready we start off with crossed
arms
five four three two one
down to the right cross out down up left
left idle step
up up either step
middle little
and then it continues
this is the next move that we're gonna
do
okay and if we do that then we got the
intro down you wanna wait you wanna play
it one more time
maybe maybe one more time okay okay all
right
well i sound like a choreography
instructor two two three three
four four five five
five four three two one cross side out
up
cross side
hey
[Music]
yeah i want to make sure i'm doing the i
want to make sure i'm doing the idol
yeah i'll step very important for idols
um
let me let me try to repeat that and uh
wait where am i standing there there
there okay so uh after doing you got
these moves down
crosstalk
okay after that i got it
you'll be fine
after doing that you start out with the
right leg
and you make like a movement as if
you're ice skating i i said that to egg
ice skating big eyes oh my god oh big
arms
yeah
it's only two steps one and two and
up in the air
not like that
one and two and in the middle
so it's like one and two and up in the
air one and two and in the middle
one and two and up in the air
one and oh and
you think you got it one and two and up
in the air
one and two and in the middle one and
two and in the middle
wait
let me can you repeat that and i'll look
at you closely
one and two and up in the air yeah one
and two and in the middle yeah but don't
forget the arm is really important here
the left when you when you start out
with the right leg
oh god you gotta really have the left
hand straight basically straight to the
front
and the right hand basically pretty much
somewhere in the back and then swing it
really big
as if you're so ice skating like that
you know
swoosh
okay have you ever been ice skating
no okay today's the day
okay okay
so when you want to try it again with
music
okay okay
hey guy you okay are you following
okay okay okay
i can be the egg whisperer i can hear
what i decided if you have any yeah i'd
like to clarify if you want to ask
something ask my other people you could
tell me nobody nobody's gonna hear
it look like a gremlin egg
what is that dance is that an idol step
made by an egg
you you're both doing great so far
let me calibrate again
all right when you're ready i'll press
it uh
ready ready ready ready ready
one
push
push on three
yeah four power stance five oh
let's go
like you just don't care did you just
break something
no i heard some noise i just i might
my idol step is a little too wide i'm
sorry
i understandable i i sometimes lose
sight of where i am too
one
two
three
four
five hmm
[Music]
i just step but you just don't care
[Laughter]
i got some crazy moves
i know i know okay
um all right i think we got that you're
good
okay
wonderful
yeah you gotta repeat these things many
times in order to make it work can i ask
to chat something do do you guys is it
looking like
is it looking like that
the audio is synced with our dance moves
just curious let me try some water
talking and dancing with vr stuff
i'm so flexible yeah not only my
schedule is flexible now my body is
flexible too yes yes yes okay
okay is it too quiet for you guys to
hear it properly
uh hard to tell it's synced i might not
yeah she will she will sync up
eventually don't worry about that
cute wait let's try something uh uh
stand behind me stand behind me
yeah yeah okay and then we do the choo
choo train thingy okay you gotta do the
hand moving this one while doing it and
then you go after me
like dad oh okay i'll follow you let me
start wait we start in the middle then
then and follows and then egg follows
okay
three two okay one okay
beautiful that is not part of the dance
though but you're doing great
thank you thank you for doing that with
me
i think that's actually do you guys get
the reference
you don't do you no no that's actually
from like a choo-choo train
yeah
the move this choreography i think it
was from a a big japanese
male idol group yeah oh god
there was no bgm just now it was your
imagination
oh
[Music]
okay hydrated so the next move
gosh this is going to take a while huh
next move is you may have seen it
already but i go uh
okay and then we go we start with a big
swing and clap lift your left leg while
doing that
yeah
and it is basically like double bump
right clap left clap and then we clap
clap clap clap three times at the bottom
and then we go like yay okay
right clap so it goes like a clap clap
clap you don't really have to clap your
controllers but yeah and then yang
okay right clap okay left clap when you
clap you lift the other side's leg oh
yeah
down down down yay
beautiful
amazing you got that
you do almost love the egg oh my god
oh my god the egg has raw talent
funny funny
crap crap crap
for you help me
don't worry
wait i feel like
do they even say that in the in the
desktop version
i feel like it makes it a bit more
pretty in the desktop version
it might not it might yeah
um
okay so it's a big clap on the right big
club on the left
uh dab by double bubble three times and
then okay and then we do the same thing
on the other side left clap
right clap double jab by the clap three
times on the bottom
my hands are somewhere else but then you
go yay again and then with that
you'll
don't try to do this at home uh you
after oh god after uh this move you put
the leg the right leg in the front
and you uh slowly
move this arm up like that while giving
it a little bit of a wiggle wiggle move
okay but while doing that you want to
move your hips a little bit
okay so it's like
yay let leg down and then wiggle wiggle
wiggle wiggle basically it's two times
with the hips
okay is that understandable i'm trying
to explain it so it's understandable
so we do it two times or and the wiggle
wiggle you can do as much as you want
but the hips basically okay um
you do two tabs and you see how the legs
okay a little bit too
i go like this
yeah like that okay and then
you go into this stance
with the left hand on your hip and the
right hand this time does the wiggle
from right side to the left side first
we went from up to down and now we go
from right side to whoa left side
wiggle wiggle okay wiggle wiggle wiggle
wiggle okay
so we do the hip thing too or is it only
in the first one no
yeah you do the hip thing too yeah yeah
yeah yeah you should
you should um and then we're almost done
with the intro
stay with me after doing this wiggle
wiggle wiggle
we
she says
right side
you you look there too with your head mo
you open up your arms but at the same
time every time you open up an arm you
um step with your leg as well
and lift that aruno
okay and then after having both hands
out you look to the front
and you clap once in the middle
uncle i don't know
you lift the right leg again
um
so
wait yeah
so we do the idle step
and then we go into the clap
oh yes yes what was in between we start
with the right side clap we go to the
left side club we go to the bottom three
times and yay and then left side close
yeah right side clip bottom three times
and yay and then we do the wiggle wiggle
with the hips
and the wiggle wiggle with the hips to
the side
side and then
do you have a problem
of course yes is basically what she says
do you have okay a problem
yes i do
clap okay
clap up yes
clap up yes okay
okay clap up yes we we can try a few
times with the music and then
uh after a few times you should be able
to you know it's normal after you you
first when you listen it without music
first and it's kind of like what what
what what you gotta do it with the music
a few times to associate the moves with
the sound
that's totally no that makes sense yeah
why don't we take a quick water break
yeah okay before we start with the music
oh yeah okay
i don't want to see you run through i'm
just kidding
get water
everyone who needs to drink water
it's gonna be a long long day
we don't have to do the full dad's the
full song but a lot of the moves are
really repetitive so
uh
i'm sweating under my vr headset huh
how's it going chad are you learning to
dance too
so work out oh yeah they could dance
don't we look cute in the dreaming tutu
uh low poly models i feel like they look
so cute
eggy's gone egg egg is drinking water to
be able to soon hatch
from
the egg
you guys
wonder who is behind the egg
you guys wonder
who could it be
um
egg
you really think yago would be doing
this with us
i doubt it oh egg is bad
how do you do that she's walking for
walls is she a ghost egg
she or he
could be it could be a he could be she
could be a day
could be a
i maybe i'm the egg
are we are we ready to play some music
oh yes okay
positions
do your best
following along i'll do my best to not
glitch out
egg welcome back
you're looking
at
ex
expeditious i don't know what that means
power stance
typewriter or whatever that is
five four three two one cross section
wiggle wiggle
wiggle wiggle my uncle ah that was
actually a different lyrics but that's
okay
got it
we can play the same part again really i
wasn't looking that well
let's do it again
how is dance three
four
egg is winning
oh my god
five four three two one
[Music]
you're delayed do you think you hear the
audio delete or you're just dancing
delayed
probably a mix of both
okay it's supposedly supposed to be
is egg delayed good question
i just
if you don't behave i will sit on you
oh okay
get on your knees
you're my friend
me too me too
thank you for teaching us
[Laughter]
okay let's color out my panties
what color are they
what's going on
oh they're drowning
[Applause]
is being
there we go oh my god
beautiful beautiful
okay what did they say about whether or
not the egg is delayed i don't know
maybe i'm hearing the music too early
oh yeah you do it
but the thing is also that i i
anticipated i know i know what um
i know what moves are coming so maybe
i'm just more ready than you guys are
maybe
oh that's true yeah uh egg is not
delayed egg egg is not
it's delayed me
maybe maybe it's a problem on my side
maybe maybe maybe i'll try to go faster
it's okay i'll go faster okay
okay
um shall we do it again from the
beginning one more time yeah you really
gotta hammer it into your brain
otherwise you won't you won't remember
oh my god
four me five
[Music]
hey wiggle wiggle
wiggle wiggle
[Music]
okay next part is easy one next part is
easy
intro was maybe a little bit advanced
moves
oh yeah
sorry guys i'm gonna be using those
moves for like the rest of the dance
that's okay uh huh what what what
oh uh the movies that we learned at the
start are we going to learn that are we
yes and they use those for like all most
of the song yes they'll be repeated uh
several times
okay so
is that wait i think the pop removal
what was that
isn't that the fortnite dance amazing
but have you guys seen uh have you guys
played yakuza zero or ever see the gif
of yakuza people dancing on the disco
floor
i have i've seen it where they did like
the yeah and at first he goes like we
could do a really cool puzzle
oh my god and then he uh goes like what
was it again
what did he do again
ah he
there you go
those are some easy disco moves if you
ever know how to if you ever want to
know how to dance at the disco
okay isn't that like
oh that's that says different moves oh
there's something flying here wow
you think they don't do they see that
particle cute kill it's like fireflies
you would not believe your eyes if ten
million fireflies
oh there's one here oh
wow
wow do you see this ahmed you see this
one
you're here no you don't see it nice
maybe yeah maybe i'm drunk maybe i have
hallucinations from dancing so much oh
my god okay
okay next next moves it's time to start
the verse number one we have the intro
down we'll probably you guys probably
will forget it until later but it's okay
and so wait how does it go in uh oh yeah
we do some idle steps
uh it starts to the right side
and then left side and then then we do
two times to the right
and then we do the left side right side
and two times to the left okay really
easy
right side left side two times to the
right
left side right side two times to the
left oh i see and keep on lifting your
arms really big because in this dance
they did like to do that
right side
left side always close with your tippy
toes on the bottom and then two times to
the right
left side right side two times to the
left yeah
beautiful beautiful okay uh oh yeah and
after doing that um
the dancer starts overlaying the hands
like in layers like this we start with
the left hand at the bottom and we put
the right hand on top
left right left right the last one is
the right and then you should be all the
way at the top
and then
you turn was it to the back was it to
the front
ah it was downwards you turn the hand
once
all the way back up again
and then you do
this move
two times
choo choo
cha cha
choo choo train okay
and then after doing that twice
you go uh do the same move once on the
left side
how many months i'm dying here
i am going to take a break no
no
okay next
and then and then we go
and the same moves again either step to
the right two tabs
i will step to the left two times and
the same move again with overlaying
when i arrive at the top we do
this turn and then two two
is leaving two last warning
okay
this one's easy all right this one's
easy right we got it we got it we got it
we did from the top for the new sequence
again
yes
uh one second
what do you mean from the top from the
very top just from the from the verse
from the first one
which one do you enjoy from the the one
we were just practicing the new one
obviously
okay okay okay well that's it really
just starts right here uh with the
uh
right leg
lit uh arms up in the air so right
left
right and right and left and right and
left and left okay
and then right yeah two times
you first you first do um one normal
idle step right and then you go two
times to the right and then one normal
idle step to the left
and then two times to the left
okay
oh my god
i feel like i'm swimming when i do my
idol step i need you
okay wait do it again yeah yeah you're
doing you're swimming you're swimming
indeed and not swimming
ice skating ice skating ice skating
imagine you're on an ice rink you go
like dab maybe you can even
you even can uh move your your upper
body a little bit to the front while
you're doing that
also could compare it to skiing okay so
like this try to copy this move this
exact move
um
the
i would say that the weight
is
the weight is on the
on both legs but you kind of stretch out
the left leg um
and then
how do i explain this
we need to perf make this perfect
i'm gonna
try it again
uh
idle step
it's like this try to try to repeat this
only this movement
move the yeah swing those arms
and you can add a little bounce to it if
you want like this
yang
yeah don't hit yourself
but bounce and bounce and bounce and
always close those legs at the bottom
yeah yeah there are different types of
idle steps but this is the one that
we're doing today
okay
i'll try it i think it looked better now
um i think it looked better
so let's do it again from the top
uh from the verse number one verse
number one oh okay yes okay i will hum a
little bit alongside okay
actually was two times sorry was two
times on both sides
just the last one just the last one is
only one time
okay
okay it's not so important it's not so
important do it as many times as you
want
that is that is the first verse and
after that follows the bridge so let's
try this with music shall we okay it
will always start from the top i suppose
but yeah
oh my god i'm gonna get a heart attack
oh my god
egg nailed it i'm sorry that
no problem no problem
power stents
you know what to do
[Music]
two times to the right
to them to the left overlay those arms
down
two times two left
this is the next one
[Music]
sometimes my belt gets uh
uh
it moves around too much okay
ah are we oh you didn't play the music
oh okay please please thank you thank
you oh no no breaks allowed no bracelets
i will not show weakness
[Music]
oh
one two two three three
four
five
egg cannot bend the arms it seems
five four three two one cross out the
[Music]
clap clap
layer those arms and turn it around to
two
yeah and step two times to the right all
right
so there's the left layer those arms
and
two hey
[Music]
let's stop it
we're almost at the chorus and then
we'll take a break
great job egg
i'm not surprised you're an egg
you're one of my people
i'm doing her two right i'm doing it
you're the egg yolk you're the egg yolk
you're necessary
i need you i need you everyone needs an
egg yolk without you my hair is yellow
yes exactly
you're cute you're above
egg
no never practice before the practice
what yeah that's true that's true we
have to give
amid that one
egg says barely they they practice a
little bit
actually the thing is with this song
that i
i never actually actively tried to learn
it i just saw it a million times and
then um i kind of ended up knowing this
this one is just like you hear it and
you see it so many times
you end up learning it without even
wanting to learn it yeah
okay so
after the moves that we just did you saw
that i was doing this move normally they
turn in a circle but i will get wired up
with my cable so i don't want to do that
yeah me too we'll just do uh side steps
okay because they normally they do like
side steps
around uh yeah in a circle but we do it
while looking at the front okay
so you start with your arms like this
um it's like you're leading your elbow
on top of uh you're resting on top of
your hand okay
sorry guys
sorry guys i'm breathing so much
okay so it's okay um we do like
slow really slow idle steps okay it's
like one and two and one and two
and one and two and one and two okay
yeah and
while doing that she sings
someday
okay so now you know the melody um she
sings
when she sings
you lift that hand up
uh
and then you bring it down again while
wiggling your hand okay so imagine like
a sparkling effect basically okay so
sunday
[Music]
one day when the next english word pops
up you switch to the other side
and you do the same thing
the timing is a little bit difficult
here
something like that
bring it up and bring it down okay while
doing those idle steps
okay and then since we're free people
it's perfect because in the original
dance at this part they do something uh
special um oh
yeah
[Music]
and
so
we will have egg go first so you gotta
be fast egg uh
uh
we immediately all go back into this
pose
and then the first one is the egg uh it
goes like this you point to the right
side
and then i go there's another
and then amigos
okay he said we have to practice this
with the music a few times but um egg
egg really has to be fast
um
egg immediately goes to the right side
actually you don't need to do this you
really already go like that and then i
follow
and then abby follows
you move your hand in a circular motion
up in the air and then you
sparkle back to the bottom okay
sparkle back to the ground you you
picked up a star in the air and then you
bring it down and it glitters imagine
that yeah yeah yeah yeah
that was the bridge okay because like
one more time let's live without the
music
uh okay it starts here
someday
and then immediately it goes
uh
okay sorry really difficult without
music what is the timing between egg
going and then you go
is it like it's not even a second it's
like
maybe okay zero point zero point three
seconds
[Music]
you're just gonna make it in time uh to
go uh
up up in the air like this for that
sound okay but even even if we can't do
this one by one
just do it whenever you feel like the
timing is right for you
okay okay okay okay shall we start from
the time yeah let's play the music let's
play that music you know what we can sit
out the if you want i'll say i'm the
sensei i know how to dance this i will
sit out the the beginning part i'll jump
in for you you girls you gotta dance
okay
i'm just gonna chill here
yeah
oh my god
i'm watching you uh-huh
uh-huh
[Music]
i thought i could take a break my my
dance teacher back in the day he didn't
always dance along
three
i'm not as strict as my old dance
teacher he was really strict five four
three two one
[Music]
layer
and turn it around and choo choo let's
go
[Music]
yeah
okay we have to work on that i think we
practice it
[Music]
i like kind of forgot
like in between the middle i kind of
forgot yeah it's okay a little bit we
can we can ignore that part for now
yeah you can ignore that
huh okay but but um uh this this timing
is a little bit difficult to grasp even
for me um
but
it goes
right before the right before the chorus
is just this
just this yeah exactly
exactly exactly
and then we basically start a rodeo i
just always imagine a rodeo here and
but
uh
you have to have your left hand
not like this uh on your on your waist
or on your hip but actually you gotta
lay it like as if you're um whoa
right i'll go
you gotta lay it on on
on top of your hip like as if you're
like stroking it you know what i mean
because
we uh once you're doing the rodeo
one time you will like slap your slap
your waist one time yeah
okay let me show you one time
did you see where i did the slap one
time
you don't have to do it it's a minor
detail you don't really have to do it
but basically we do the rodeo i think i
think we swing it what four times damn
it one two three four i think it's four
times and then we switch to the other
side and we i'm really glitching out
badly now but we do it four times here
too okay
okay okay
um i think we can't take a five minute
break
okay finish we'll finish this chorus but
we might not do the [\h__\h] because i
will be at my limits
um
i can i can do much better without this
vr okay let me let me just tell you that
oh i believe you because i i don't know
what i'm doing here okay it's hard it's
tough yeah but okay so we do the rodeo
on the right side and while you're doing
that try to look at my the way my legs
move
every time i swing it and i kind of
bounce up
and move my hip to the left up
like this
yeah swing it swing
swing it swing
swing swing
it's making me swing it yeah yeah okay
okay good job good job girls and then we
do the same thing on the right side we
switch immediately and we just yeah how
do you switch like how do you switch
from going to this side to this side
you're just um kind of like
throw that right leg that is now in the
back you throw it to the front uh
on the other side
[Music]
and then
and immediately put the pressure
immediately put the weight and your
pressure on that right side so that yeah
it goes to the front
yeah
just do that girls just do that
this yeah exactly
that's a dance move oh my god it's so
heavy i can't even land this vr headset
i need a break i need a [\h__\h] break oh
okay
oh yeah i'm it
five sit ups go
there's a boot camp five five sit ups on
the or the other hand
i can't lean all the way back but i'll
try
i'm sitting on the egg beautiful
yeah
[Music]
you'll you also have to do this
or you can do the other thing the
push-ups or whatever it is
five five of your choice
are you doing it are you doing something
it says that uh the trackers with the
trackers is difficult sure
sure sure
alan was able to do it
you're like twerking
he's twerking
oh yeah twerk twerk five times then
dam's out of hand
oh oh you're floating oh my god well
i guess an egg just first has to evolve
into a proper being and then then egg
can do some stuff too
but egg has been dancing really great i
see the motivation
really motivated egg i'm a toodle i'm a
too
i'm trying my this is the first time
i've ever learned like a choreographed
dance before so i've never like taken a
dance class or anything yeah i remember
when i first um the first time when i
learned the dance uh i was really [\h__\h]
you really gotta dance a lot in order to
look like you're doing something
professional
it takes time and also uh in order to
learn your first choreography it also
takes a lot of time after you've learned
a couple choreographies you'll
eventually um have it down pretty
quickly
but um
but it's okay
it seems like difficult to get it like
to get your movements tight enough
especially if you're syncing up with
like a group
yeah being in sync with a group is also
a thing like if you dance alone people
will not really know this but if you're
in a group it's really difficult you
gotta not only have to have you do you
need to sync up um
the the timing of the moves but also
like if you really want to look like a
proper grip you also gotta sync up the
way you dance because people really
dance very differently um especially if
they have different uh teachers in
different uh training methods and
different dancing styles and all that
you know
so yeah you don't have to i want to
learn yourself better
don't blame yourself it just started out
so good it's normal now it's normal it's
totally normal so i know
i was i was worse than you when i
started out
oh
so if i just practice i'll get better
you'll definitely get better 100
oh by the way i wonder um do you ever go
to like the disco or something like that
or do you ever did you ever go no
no i've never been to a disco or
anything like that before but i've
danced like uh like at um
shows oh my chair
and punk shows
what's pop show a punk show yeah you
dance like
you dance like this to the music wait
hold on let me make sure i have enough
space like this
[Laughter]
with punk music
yeah with some of it but sometimes
people swing their arms like really hard
what egg
what does egg say something
only it seems like only is talking about
are you talking about this one what is
that yeah i think
um
oh
damn you got those moves those groovy
moves man that's rad
that is red it's really fast
i think
i think i know what's that supposed to
be it looks like it
it looks like what it's supposed to be
yeah
and then my hip got turned on yeah yeah
it happens it happens
drinking water
oh i should i should
i'm sitting is so comfortable actually i
have my bed right here
it's really nice my guessing bed i can
do the carlton dance one day emma you'll
sleep on that bed that i was just
sitting on one day
you'll sleep there isn't it like
oh sure
sorry watertime not unusual to be i
don't know how to do it can you shuffle
can you shuffle ammo
no is it like a wait is it like
uh
yeah it's it's like something like that
i can't shuffle either but it looks so
cool
it looks so cool yeah it does look
really cool every day i'm shuffling
can you do the caramel dancing
[Music]
oh i don't hear it why hey gig i thought
you were one of my people i don't hear
you yeah it's okay it's supposed to be
like that
romeo dancing
the one dance that all the people that
go to an anime convention know how to
dance and it unites everyone that's so
easy
okay okay i feel i feel i feel calmer
yeah
yeah can you uh can you walk us like a
quick walkthrough through everything
again so we can't refresh okay no
problem we'll do it without music well
then i have to fix something um
i'm gonna take your time
i have to fix something too alicia
chad how's it going i was looking at you
are you enjoying yourself looking at our
suffering why did i where did i go come
back come back are you enjoying our
suffering
guys do you realize that in
about one week and like what two days or
so
our the concert is happening yeah
i feel ready
i don't know about the other girls
we'll be ready
i'm ready i'm ready yeah yeah yeah yeah
well i did actually practice a dance for
that now that i remember oh i did
practice dancing with that too i've had
foreign
yeah yeah yeah
and and in vr i mean you can't see the
movements that properly either all right
so we started out again from the
beginning
with this this stance yeah yeah
and it goes
and we start with the crossed arms and
leg to the left
out leg to the right down leg to the
left up leg to the right
party put it
yeah
and cross lay to the right
outside leg to the left and then down
and then up and then party party to the
other side exactly
and then we go idle stamp
big idle step only two steps and then up
in the air
big idle step like you just don't care
and then
[Music]
oh yeah yeah exactly
big clap on the right side oh sorry my
shelf uh
all right let me reposition
big clap on the right side big clap on
the left side and while you go to the
left side you kind of have to go for the
bottom but without clapping after you
clap two times you start clapping back
at the bottom yeah yeah yeah okay so
right clap left clap clap clap clap
three times right
okay
i think it starts yeah left click
exactly left clap
right clap clap clap clap and then yay
and then you wiggle it with your hip and
your hands to the bottom
and then change the stance
and you wiggle it to the
left side yeah yeah
okay and then she says
something like do you have a freaking
problem of clap
course
not
yo
yeah and that's where the first verse
starts
uh with simple idol steps uh
step to the right
step to the left
double step
step to the left step to the right
and then you start with the left hand
over layering again
uh a few times
how many times is one two three four
five six
yeah the right hand is the sixth one the
last one and then you turn it to the
bottom to your front yeah
and then to the back and up and then
choo choo
the train is leaving
hurry up
and i will step again same moves
twice to the right
left right twice to the left
and then over layer again
one two five six
and hand to the front one circle
choo choo
we ain't got no time no more so we only
two two once on the left side
it's just for the second time you do
once
um
yeah like when you do it before you do
it twice the very last one is once yeah
and after we did that we go to the
bridge
we start with this this movement and the
hand rests the the elbow rests on the
left hand
uh
and then we start with the right foot
let me recalibrate for a second one
second
okay so this movement yeah right step
slowly
up the hand and then when we go right
again we bring it down
and then we move uh with the left step
we change the hands and we bring it up
again
and we'll bring it down
and then once you've brought it down
supposedly immediately the egg goes to
the right side and then i follow and
then i'mma follows yeah and then we oh
okay uh circle it up to the top
and then we bring it down we sparkle
sparkle sparkle and we change our
position to the right side
with a lifted straight left leg amen
lifted right leg
yeah exactly
and then we're ready for the rodeo we
start swinging that lasso and we slap
our uh our hip once oh god
and then we bring the right leg to the
front and we swing that lasso
and we uh
slap our waist one more time
oh yeah that was the beginning that's
when i stopped teaching you uh
that's where the chorus continues
and then we go a big step to the right
side and we make a big
circular motion oh god
she's going around
exactly we make a
big circular motion and once we're in
the middle
uh we turn it around to the outside
okay once
it was one step and twist it second step
we meet in the middle
and then
we put uh we try to separate our legs
again with this movement we uh die
what's happening
we um i was just uh tying up the thingy
okay
we um put the right hand to the front
uh we put the left hand on top of it
like an x-cross
can you see what i'm doing
we cross the arms in in front okay yeah
yeah like this i can see it yeah and
then you bend it and you bring it to
your heart
i think if i remember correctly
and then you just kind of shake it out
with humming let me come along
[Music]
shake it all out yeah cross it right
hand cross it left hand bring it to the
bring it to the heart
and then shake it all out
and then we start with the rolling pin
[Music]
do you want to you want to turn them off
and turn them back on and then yeah
it'll help i've been doing that too i
i'll get so let's try down thingy i
guess oh in the drop down
yeah and the drop down thingy right
click on them and turn off and then just
turn them on by the button
okay one second
uh meanwhile okay so kara's doing that
egg we could practice yeah exactly you
can turn on the music if you want okay
um
[Music]
three
four five
wait
[Music]
left and overlay it
turn it around
and two one time only and now we do this
[Music]
rodeo
after the second rodeo we do the same
movement with the crosstalk
uh
oh but instead of
instead of shaking it out
we do a big circle like this i'll say it
again for you amen
welcome back
after the second rodeo
[Music]
wait first what the first one is like
this right to the heart and shake it out
and then we start the rodeo again
and we do this big uh two-step circle
movement again
and then we do the over layering the
crossing again
it's really not getting much better
uh
like this
but instead of shaking it out
uh
it's hard without the music what was it
again it was something like
this
[Applause]
[Music]
on your right leg lift the left leg
while you're
putting your hands up in the air
[Music]
i think
it was probably something it probably
ends something like this
a circle like that and then you put the
pressure the weight on the other side
again okay a circle and then okay pose
okay
and that's where we go basically
into the intro again
left to the left big idle step up in the
air
big idol step like we just don't care
and then
it should continue like that supposedly
so
okay let's um
play it again
are you good amen okay okay yeah
okay let's do it one more time from the
very top
getting those introduction moves
hammered into our brains
happy happy
birthday
right
[Music]
understand
up and down
[Music]
make circles
right left and
[Music]
that's where it changes
that's where it changes there's a moon
glad and i told her
and now we clap again
maybe the egg is warmed up enough to
hatch i think the egg can hatch and i
think
i think that's um the point where i will
end the song basically
i think i think it continues like for
one or two more minutes after that
when it repeats should we end like we
could do a pose
we can end it we can end it where it
goes
shortly before you ended the song
just now
because they would they would have
continued with the clap moves just there
but we're gonna okay
for health health reasons we're gonna
end it there so okay egg come here come
here let me sit on you
let me hatch you
it's time you're feeling really hot yeah
oh oh my god
you do your thing i'm just gonna sit on
you and warm you up
yeah egg i think your other form is
ready
are you ready egg whoa a ritual is
starting i'm hatching the egg
nice
yeah yeah rachel secret ritual magical
ritual oh oh she's leaving the egg left
it's hatching in the background
what will it be what will it be
what will it turn into
i'll just chill here come out from under
the heart
oh perhaps yes
uh
i wonder who it is the big reveal who
could it be yaakov
zoom zoom the big moment
the big moment are we going to change
the background to amen
oh yeah we could do that on our last
performance when we think we've got okay
okay
are you ready to come out egg yeah we're
ready egg we're ready
you should be able to hear it when she
yeah
i don't hear her yet ah i could have oh
i don't know if your mouths work that's
okay that's too far away
maybe she's still silent oh yeah i mean
yeah and vr chat in the little thingy
yeah the button
no it's not working i think it might
have the wrong
i think you have the wrong audio input
on vr chat
it's good idea also in low poly it's not
configured
not the dreaming choo-choo outfit but
she also has from the same modeler a low
poly um model as you can see there
cute isn't it with a kind of a yankee
style school uniform yeah
cute
with that jacket yes sandals who wears
sandals to school apparently a shark
does cute pew pew pew pew pew pew pew oh
okay bubba you can focus on us
yeah okay very cute very cute our secret
guest was gouda cause she was uh very
very motivated
to um dance with us you might have if
you've been watching mine and buddha's
streams you might have heard the story
of her asking me to make a hollow myth
boot camp but she couldn't hold it back
she really wanted to dance as soon as
possible that's why she was so motivated
to join today i'm happy to have her here
um but we are amitodi is
but today we are ahmed
yes very too i could change it now
yes let's change it let's change it
while gude is figuring out
how to unmute or or how to change them i
hear you now
i do i do i do it
[Music]
how how did it feel as an egg
how did it feel
it was
moist what
i didn't see that yet i think not in not
like this damn
so cute yeah i love the purple it's so
good this is disco-wish it feels like a
disco here with the disco floor
yeah
i love the lights yeah yeah
yeah yeah disco disco
they both did this yeah thank you for
uploading and for the vr chat team for
uh putting all of this on thank you
wonderful studio thank you thank you so
much
[Music]
before we try to um do our final dance
takes i think we're going to do it like
maybe three more times i want to say i'm
really happy that i'm able to show uh my
hobby of dancing i mean i haven't
honestly i haven't danced in like a long
long long time i used to be um more into
dancing in the past but her life has
kind of eaten up and my time but i'm
happy that i can
share my hobby and
are you are you showing yourself the
middle finger girls no no no no no no no
peace love and harmony in this classroom
otherwise you'll have to do 10 push-ups
no middle fingers how are you even doing
that i can't i can't do it i just i
can't do it either
no maybe
doing that
can someone zoom in on
gouda there can only be one
wow
wow this is an idol everybody
you know i like it because you're so
small and you're like you have that
yankee idol uniform at a school uniform
i like how you're the one who shows us
the middle finger
it's like it has kusogaki vibes i like
it
very very good well thank you preach you
yes you made these and thank you super
last minute yeah
helped us get it into vr chat and ask
someone thank you guys she literally had
like one hour
thank you everybody for making my dance
school so special all right so shall we
go back into dancing
uh now in our final four
you want to be on that side now
okay
but i should be on this side because i
just
you're used to it
yeah i'm used to it
beautiful okay should i start it with
music or should we do dry uh
how do you feel amit
gooda what about you
what
with musical we're back another dry run
through with music oh dry that sounds
cool
okay okay i'll get it okay chiara lead
us again you're really you're really
killing me today but okay let's do it
let's sweat okay we start with the power
stance
i'm glitching out
shake shake shake
and i will start let's go
[Music]
i will step
up in the air
idle step and to the left
and then clap
up
pop head and left and right
hey and i think we'll wait wait i'm
getting confused without music this is
where we are i think this is where we
are wiggle wiggle wiggle wiggle wiggle
wiggle wiggle wiggle i'm not moving at
all anymore
man my batteries are depleting probably
uh and then you could try and respond
it's okay i already did it i already did
it and then after wiggling to the from
right to the left we got
number down
[Music]
so right and left meet in the middle
up yeah you're looking cute
you're cute very cute
and then we start uh
with uh the
verse number one okay it starts with an
idol step to the
your hands
and then turn it around
i just step to the right double step
i just step to the left elbow step up
over lay your heads and turn it around
choo choo choo choo choo choo choo
bridge time
someday
one day
it's fun
it's fine developers have a
good girls before this actually so
i'm gonna i'm gonna try to do the guna
timing one day
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
circle it up in the air sparkle it down
rodeo time
da da da
[Music]
big movement with an idle step
across it
you can
okay it's okay i i need you that's why i
need you girls to learn to dance because
i apparently can't stand still for a
[\h__\h] moment i need you girls to learn
the dance okay uh rodeo
after doing that on the left side we go
cross sit down and to the middle and
shake it out
shake it out rodeo da da da da da
recalibrate and then respawn
respond
respond respawn oh yeah respawn where
will i be spawning
right now elevator oh [\h__\h] okay
brb guys afk
did i do it why oh god
[Music]
oh yeah
floss hello welcome back
yes okay
okay a calibre one more time
one two three go
oh what's your best style of pose yeah
is that your best
um
peace
get closer to me get closer to me let's
do a group chat
fix my leg fix my leg okay cute pose
oh god oh god oh god
i'm losing control over my body let's do
this okay
okay okay you know what turn on the
music turn on the music let's do this
just just follow my lead follow my lead
and you'll be fine
yes move around the camera
oh yeah trigger the good camera
show us what you got camera
hell yeah oh yeah two all right
let's do this four
follow my lead
five four
[Music]
hey
against the walls
what the hell does she want okay
wakey wakey
oh it's it is indeed pretty late over
here
oh well
okay
[Music]
come through the middle
turn it around
[Laughter]
[Music]
hey
big circle
cross your arms
shake it out rodeo
rodeo
circle
[Music]
i don't know
no it feels like the in between
you know it right but your brain is just
three our brains are like 85 you know
yeah yeah i think even practice and then
we could come back and do it but oh yeah
um the thing is this song is really
really
fast paced so it's normal that your
brain can't keep up with it if you just
learned the curry it's totally fine okay
but shall we do it
one last time without my comments we'll
just uh quietly dance
[Music]
for the for them
for the final
yes yes
what's the choo-choo this one what is
this thing
i'm not sure what is it bothering me
and we'll figure it out one day
focus girls i won't do any comments now
[Music]
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
yay
against my table and they smell food
um
it it kind of it kind of spilled over my
electronics but they seemed fine like
kitty kitty kitty kitty fine
that's unfortunate
everything's cool probably but i think
that was the
that was a really um bad uh final
version oh is it oh selfie camera let's
take a selfie
yeah if you want to hold it you can hold
it how do i help
i think i think this is fun wow
yay
cute pose hello
hello
good afternoon
oh yeah you're so small though there we
go camera like kind of uh
how do i hold it i'm gonna squish your
brain
there's nothing in there to begin with
more um angle it so that the the little
yeah yeah
like this
yay
cute oh yeah it's like we're we're
putting out a rap album let's go wrap
poses
we're putting on a rap album let's go
let's go yo yo yo
yo yo yo
hunk
yeah
oh my god
do it
yeah
[Laughter]
oh
it was an accident
amelia but
um
i can't do peace on
i wish i could do a peace sign
let's do back to back like men in black
or something like that
yes yes yes
are we looking cool
this is
there's always that one person that's in
the middle like
they're like looking back
muscles it looks like it looks like me
and ame are from um uh from high school
and gouda is from junior high school
she's our junior schooler
i just signed the middle finger again
[Music]
then i get free oranges at the grocery
store
[Music]
all right um
you can switch to the bubba the bigger
camp yeah yeah free foreign
[Music]
yes um thank you
i'm thinking about doing another one
eventually uh with with the other myth
girls
everyone in low poly hopefully and then
well i was thinking of teaching a
different song that time
yeah yeah
but i'm gonna practice this one in my
free time i'll practice it and then
maybe when we all get together again we
can show off to inna and cali i'm
looking forward to it yes i'll test you
thank you oh and that's so cute but
before before that don't forget next
week saturday sunday
saturday and sunday
we will be on a huge stage in japan and
you can watch it online there's spawn
tickets amen good i will be on day one
and i will be with kelly oh
you know also as well on day one and i
will be with kelly on day two please
check us out
yeah we've practiced really hard before
before we say goodbye ahmed what is your
what is your um motivation and your your
ikigomi i don't know how to properly
translate that word i never know
you're
like
your model for the upcoming concert
tell me oh
my [\h__\h] like a like uh my
motivation yeah your thoughts just your
[\h__\h]
i want to be able to stand on the same
stage as you guys and everybody else in
hell alive even though i'm like my skill
level is down here and everybody else is
like
i want to climb
and dance and
get better too so we can all dance and
be together in the same stage and be
synced up yes yes yes yes yes looking
forward to your performance what the
[\h__\h] you guy
oh sorry i'll have to lower them i want
to
i want to sing on stage since debut i've
dreamed about singing on stage for
everybody and now it's coming true and i
know you know this but the realization
just hit me the other day
i was like
it's finally happening yeah yeah it's
real it's actually happening i think for
people outside of japan
it's difficult to realize thank you for
asking it's difficult to realize that uh
the venue that we're performing at is
[\h__\h] huge makuharimesa that's also
where a tokyo game show happens every
year and also uh some a lot of other uh
idol concerts and events are happening
there yeah so it's huge it's a huge
venue actually um and you you have to
you have to check it out in on spawn
watch our online thing performance yeah
yeah yeah well one day hopefully yes and
we can do a proper uh 3d free debut as
well and look forward to that but i
think we're all really really excited to
perform uh
in 3d for the very first time uh in that
concert i'm really excited about malcolm
x so let's freaking go
oh no no there's like a a finishing
thing maybe we could sync up like one
dance move against the green screen that
was
requested um
and maybe the road we could have a sweet
meat maybe the rodeo
yeah oh green screen work with you
chiara should i i can't i guess you
can't use blue for sure i think it
mostly okay it mostly works
just a little part on my on the tips of
my feathers maybe but that's okay
okay we're gonna do the rodeo there any
like sumo moves
sumo which one oh what
i i know i know do you know soda and
soda
soda and soda
[Music]
you kind of like you you have to stretch
your legs like like that actually oh
oh
saw the comparison they really see it a
bit differently in in the desktop view
it's not so glitchy in the desktop view
oh well okay
oh my god okay they saw that one
we're gonna do the rodeo hopefully with
no glitch
in this position gonna come a bit more
closer
yeah yeah cute you're so small maybe you
should close the middle then the balance
is better no no no no
you're a different color as well yeah
yeah okay
you're in the middle perfect
okay
go get a bit more uh yeah i'll go closer
uh
there we go oh [\h__\h] oh there we go
probably something like that okay
okay
you ready
uh i'll hum it i guess
uh or should we play the music
uh i don't think it okay i can do it
okay
does it matter what part or just from
there
it's the chorus but we can just wait
until the chorus starts
one oh two this will be a fun gift free
shift gif or gift girl scissors gif
forgive
gif gift gift gift okay
well you just gotta wait now
you
[Music]
thank you for watching today this is
like the ending screen roll the credits
roll the credits
roll them down
[Music]
thank you for watching
thanks for dancing with us
[Music]
[Laughter]
what if we singed an idol dance that's
easy
i just want to do this
wait if my hands move correctly yeah
okay ah ah
wait time
[Music]
what if i just freestyle
oh
[Music]
the moment
oh this is cute
[Music]
yeah it's really hard to be synced up i
think like doing it through vr
is the music different for everybody
yeah
song actually ends okay this green hurts
my eyeballs
yeah the void
yeah
so shiny here so shiny
all right do you know love and joy
yes
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
another one would be
oh i love mr music but i don't know the
dance for that one
[Music]
da
floss right maybe gooda knows better
than me how was it
like this
uh can you go like this
i forgot i know what it looks like you
stand forward
and then
you like juggle your
hips in between your arms something like
that
something like that is that correct
oh
it wasn't as cool
you start a little bit earlier hold on
start earlier like uh
midway another person in front of you
okay okay
i'm back
i'm exhausted man i can't even lift up
my arms anymore
yeah that was a good workout though that
was a good workout thank you everybody
for watching today uh secret guest was
good as you can see thank you both of
you i mean good after participating i'll
see you guys hopefully another day
oh you're welcome you're welcome you're
welcome i'm happy you were so motivated
to join so uh last minute thank you and
guys
thank you for having me uh i'll see you
in uh
sometime soon in a few days next few
days i might not be streaming but
i'll see you soon and in german we say
[Music]
guys
[Applause]
thank you for watching
hold on hold on just give it a second
all right
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
do
foreign