[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
did you hear that
spooky laugh who was that
was not me scary
my apartment is haunted Kiki
[Music]
hello
I have chonkers on my head again and
with a car word oh
what is that card
what you got there chunky monkey
um
let me pour some whoa
first of all
Christine chunkers is eating a colored
donkeys wants to play slightest fire
jungles wants to help me
slate Spire well
I bought
I bought uh I stocked up on on uh
fruit candy
so I'm gonna take one right now because
I already failed
crispy in my Prout oh all right didn't
even say a word today
oh oh
Elsa fruit what [\h__\h] was that fruit
candy it's th
r o 80. oh
yeah what was I gonna say Aya Aya can
you guys like remind me
um before we read the super chats later
to make myself a sandwich because I
bought like the bread for it and then I
forgot to like eat it in time today and
tomorrow it will not be good anymore the
bread is fresh so I'll need to eat it
today before I eat like a little bit
more before when I eat my dinner because
if I eat the sandwich after the stream
that's when I eat my dinner so that will
Clash so I have to like squeeze it in
wow
I doesn't need prep it's just like
slapping some salami on it
um
what
um fruit candy
um
we are going to play Oh slash
did you guys see the new
uh uh
new weekly schedule
shall we talk about it first
I'll dislike oh this works so well with
the color scheme everything is so
um harmonizing bam
so I made a tweet
I thought it was quite the Banger tweet
actually deserves that that kiwawa meme
uh with the post striking a post what
does it say what a hit tweet or
something like that oh my God what I hit
tweet
it deserves that
um
um yeah I said uh let me quote myself
[Laughter]
uh wait
I need a reference what did I say
okay I said
as dreamers I love a game to play to
stream it's a girls I don't have
anything to wear when looking at the
full closet of clothes I
oh my God I hate tweet yeah
um so that was me trying to come up with
something this week to stream
and then I just slapped slay the spider
on there because I remembered ah
oh yeah right we don't uh we still
didn't finish Ironclad and then
interestingly enough the rest
of the week is no games at all
not 100 sure though
there might be a gorilla
uh game stream
being added on Friday
um but yeah
um besides that it's actually really no
games besides slay the Spire what the
hell cultural schedule
damn
[Laughter]
that's not a game over yet I guess I
have to get rid of the title I guess I'm
not the gamer anymore this week I am the
talker mostly
um
so
uh so yeah that's today slate Aspire and
tomorrow I want to do 3D karaoke and I
pray I pray and I pray that
my suit will not be a [\h__\h] tomorrow
please everybody pray put your hands
together and say please dear kiwawa Mo
cap suit
be nice to her
and don't be a [\h__\h]
it would be really nice yeah
if it's scuffed like as [\h__\h] then I will
still try to do it
um
yeah
and then on Wednesday we're making lunch
with my airfryer
because I haven't used the airfryer in a
long time only I think I only used it
once
and that's not enough because I paid
good money for it
[Music]
um
so we're gonna make some some we're
gonna attempt to make lunch I don't know
what yet so
[Music]
you guys are welcome to send me recipes
I was already like browsing for YouTube
like airfryer recipes
it would be good if it's something like
simple because
I'm I'm thinking of moving the airfryer
to my office and just do everything here
maybe prepare some ingredients
beforehand like cut it beforehand
whenever I need to cut and pop it in
there so prefer you something simple
with like not too much preparation
either
um
I'm not ripping off this movies
is that what it looks like to you no
oh
concerned for Mexican food on their
fries oh totally like tell me tell me
all about it
just don't be mad if I do it wrong
so uh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and then
I take first day off in preparation for
talk and also probably will be preparing
for the other whole talk as well
um so whole talk with
foreign
ah is on a Friday this time because
weekend just did not work out but
um I asked her
please please I want to
um interview you before the two-year
anniversary of whole talk and this is
the date we came up with now it's
um
two whole talks in one week but that's
okay right
yeah
I think I think it will be worth it and
very entertaining because on the whole
talk on Sunday where
takana
interviews takanashikiara
oh yes I'll be interviewing myself
um there will be a big announcement
um
[Music]
big announcement and
I am gonna do this one in pretty babies
so like I'll be doing it in VR I got the
the office ready to be used in VR pretty
much like I mean some some things are
still being like you know uh prepared uh
but it should all go well hopefully and
then happen on Sunday night this time I
mean I was like well I guess I'm just
interviewing myself so I guess the time
really doesn't have to be the usual
whole talk time
um
instead it's like
yeah this for once you get the whole
talk that's aimed at
n a audience is as much as I can aim for
it in my time zone yeah
yeah yeah
so that's that and yeah as I said on
Friday after a little talk I'll probably
be doing something a stream and on
Saturday
uh I will be
somewhere
but not on YouTube
so
some of you may see me
but not on YouTube
I cannot say anything
uh for sure yet
I mean I can say for sure but I cannot
announce
on my own
not twitch
I don't think twitch no
so uh yeah anyway wait for it ahead
and mm-hmm
but could it possibly be come on chat
foreign
[Laughter]
oh man I can't say anyway but I feel
like there definitely have been correct
answers in the chat I just cannot
confirm nor did I anything at all
everybody looking forward to
uh fun and stressful week for me very
stressful I know there's like seemingly
two days off but
I have much to do
so anyway we're gonna play slime let's
play uh we're gonna play the iron Cloud
because I played Ironclad once before
when I
was doing a members only stream
and
what what what what what what is this
I tried to open slight Aspire but it's
like being weird
what
it's just giving me two black windows
two small black windows
that I cannot
interact with
I feel like I had this before let me
close Steam
foreign
have you guys had this before
opening
hello theme my steam is so [\h__\h] weird
for me recently
okay now it's just
now it just does not work at all
let me close with task commander
uh where's
what are you
and
and now
start
let's Journey update to your graphics
card recently
I don't know why
there we go now Steam Works again
but
what about the slaterspire
now now those two black windows actually
really have something on them they're
gray now and it says play this place
like a spider yeah
these windows they're just black
[Music]
uh so we are going to
Do Do Well
inspired
there it is
probably
uh only gonna be able to squeeze in one
one run again
um judging by how it's been every time
thank you I forgot the starting Twitter
thank you for letting me know
nothing
let's sing Hunty
uh mihongo
[Music]
okay
oh my God I hit Tweed nah that one's not
a hit tweet
thank you for listening
hey I haven't seen you in a while
that's so chat name is so
um
nostalgic to me
you want me to put the logo there all
right all right where did I put it in my
um is it is it here
I saved it before oh there it is
[Music]
when the world most dated him he
returned
is he going to help me
really
[Music]
so we have finished runs of these three
successful finished ones
um this one was public the other two
were members only so if you have access
to my membership you're welcome to watch
them they were pretty fun
and now we're gonna go back to
The Roots and
I don't think I like necessarily did
anything wrong because I'm just gonna
assume you can't really do much wrong
with the iron clad I don't know it seems
so simple to me as a beginner that's the
first character I played obviously
but
after playing you know these other ones
and hearing about you know all these
different ways of playing them
I Wanna Know
is there like did I do something wrong
or can I do something better like what
do I do what do I do with the Ironclad
is there a specific build a deck that I
want to aim for
um
it's got a lot of strength strength
build
strength build aha
okay we're gonna do that then you guys
you shall help me build the deck and
choose the right cards again but I will
try my best to make other choices on my
own as much as I can resist looking at
what Chad says
okay
yes another try what you got for me
um
choose a rare colors card I'm gonna run
it yeah I would go for a random record
maybe I don't know
what should I do
I'm so indecisive
oh yeah I don't have anything unlocked I
guess yeah
one or three
what okay let's see what is that
is this a really good card
it's blocked should we do a block build
someone said something about block build
then we do block build if we can
that sounds like fun
[Music]
now we're gonna do block build
okay can we do that with like you know
all the things that I don't have
unlocked
box
build
okay okay sounds like fun
we got a tank take everything tank the
hell out of it
body slam card uh-huh
okay
[Music]
maybe this route
one
two three three okay I don't know I'll
go here because then there's a shop soon
and I want to see the shop
where's his name whenever you gain block
deal five damage your random enemy
that's interesting
are you gonna do
I'm just gonna go ahead and play that is
that like for the whole fight okay good
cool cool cool cool cool
well I I I will normally attack though
are you hearing the audio fine is it too
quiet
[Music]
of course
uh-huh
see fun deal eight damage apply too
vulnerable ah should have done this
first
oh we're just warming up you know but
you know what I'm gonna fully block him
so I'm just gonna add another block
it's getting no chance that's wonderful
wonderful wonderful that I can uh
[Music]
you know do some damage while blocking
that's nice okay block a block
attack
it's not getting through to me yeah huh
what
ah I don't remember that at all cool
we're getting heels nice
yeah Ironclad actually has a Healer
right like very cool
uh well now we'll just kill you normally
how much did I do five damage okay
I will
what are we okay there's a block of
cards again five block upgrade a card in
the hand in your hand for the rest of
the comments
oh really oh okay
it's busted okay
then I I will do that I'll do what you
say
um
well we have not so much money maybe it
wasn't the smartest thing to go to the
shop
um route
oops
we don't really have much money
oopsie
should I remove a strike
hmm
[Music]
true but we'll probably get that like
eventually anyway
I feel like we're moving yeah so we move
a strike
truck
shrunk really
it's a trunk
[Music]
okay
we're doing a block build I need all the
Block cards go go go go
hello
should I start by putting this out and
then
wow I'm so independent I'm such an
independent woman today oh
did they oh they made me frail those
bastards
a burial
[Music]
this makes me like already feel
like way more confident than the other
characters where I was like what am I
doing because I'm
still I guess
and block build makes sense to me too
like there's not much I have to like
consider I could have killed the green
well
for
Sports
this is
I'm just gonna do this
WOW upgrade strike whoa
like okay
you get an explosive potion and let's
see what do we got
can only be playing if every card in
your hands are attacked you're 14 damage
not gonna happen unless
I mean if I already played all the
defend cards skip
okay
and we're just gonna skip every block
card
every non-block card I mean
and her mama
I already have enough block okay okay
okay
we don't get the little blocking those
damage card in the first hand that's sad
I got it now but
is it worth it yeah
[Music]
see how fast oh my God I'm so fast
still but I know it might be early to
tell but but but but but
nice
at this point in other
um playthroughs
with other characters I was like slow as
[\h__\h] and I I looked at the chat for
every single move yeah yeah
I think I could have done bash I forgot
what bash was
[Music]
yeah well maybe once the cards get more
complicated then I'll be questioning
everything
oh we get another armaments
we could do another armaments I don't
know
one anyway loses two strength exhaust
um okay
really
[Music]
it's insanely strong
okay
just the sound of it doesn't sound too
impressive to me but okay
I don't know where to go
why should I go not to the shop because
I was just there
but
[Music]
I could go to this shop after that
um
right yeah that was my original plan
go right for okay the fire upgrade okay
okay
where are my block cards
here we go
[Music]
um so they're both not going to attack
this now
um
oh [\h__\h] all right okay no no problem
attack the weaker first
hair
oh now I need to go and defend as much
as possible they made me you frail again
I hate them
maybe I can upgrade a defend
[Music]
should I done
I guess that I could have disarmed yeah
I know I was thinking about but I would
prefer to have as much blog as possible
that's the point you got this thank you
okay okay I did a good choice you oh
wonderful
um
19 damage
I can definitely kill him in combination
with the potion though
should I do that
[Music]
I'm like ah
now I mean I can still kill him let me
do this first
[Music]
okay I'm just gonna waste unfortunately
all of my attacks on him but at least
say we didn't have to like Bond it with
the damage
[Music]
okay
yeah gonna do a block deck I guess
because that's the rare card that we got
so
it's helping me make decisions
blood potion oh
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
no no no no no no no
[Music]
straight for blood
heal for 20 of your max HP wow that's
that's quite a lot of heal
oh another disarm
[Music]
this would have been good for a strength
feel be healed
should we still take it
[Music]
skateboard to one or two two two three
three one skip
[Music]
um yep
to insta Peak
okay
I'm I feel like we're gonna end up
having too many cards in Our Deck
anyway let's sniff something
seven damn
I mean we probably want this one right
all cards in your hand for the rest of
the combat
okay I'm going this one first
and then the other one
oh God from one card to all cards oh my
god oh oh
what a starting hand
what a starting end too bad I only have
free energy but
what choice
what else could I ask for
and I upgraded Juggernaut there
damn
okay
um
[Music]
so hello 14 damage you say
wait what
wait what what where
[Music]
sucks oh I should have played this first
gen
forgot I forgot
[Music]
and
we just text oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
uh ah he gained strength
when I play a skill
well
this is also is this a skill but he
loses strength does this like cancel
itself out
[Music]
yeah okay
I thought so okay
um but the fan is not a skill right
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] am I supposed to do
should I not block
oh oh it does say skill oh
okay then I'll just I'll I'll I'll see
you
at least I have a good potion
[Music]
okay chill caps lock bro
chill out okay
I'll Attack
I guess I'll be as aggressive as he is
keep broken really
except on your [\h__\h] keyboard
man all right
but
how much stronger he gets two two
strength if I play one defense
but
two strength adds just well two damage
no oh six six
well done okay then it's not worth it
Dennis Danny
and it is no
[Music]
and this cancels out
well that's [\h__\h] stupid
[Music]
yeah I guess the defend at least also
does damage yeah
[Music]
just play to exhaust it
uh
so we could play badge
the first or we could first play
armaments and damn badge but that would
already be pretty much it or we play in
flame and then Bash
foreign
[Music]
oh in flame and two strikes
yes
[Music]
I mean it doesn't even matter
okay I guess I'm taking all of the
wait the vulnerable already is like
um reflected in the 33 damage right
okay thank God
so should I heal now or after
it heals 20 of my Max HP
so it doesn't really matter but I'll
drink it now
okay ah man I don't like him
[Music]
okay bye bye don't like him at all
I'm seizing top whenever you have no
cards in hand during your turn draw a
card
oh
wow and what if I played that card do I
get another card because I have once
again no cards in my hand what no that
that could not be possible could it
yeah
wow well I mean without energy it does
not really help anyway
bottle cap
[Music]
um
oh it's a block card I get blocked when
I attack oh you want this one
[Music]
drop a card you cannot draw additional
cards this turn
it's free okay
I know we wanted to upgrade but I feel
like I need to hear
[Music]
healing no healing go hard no I have to
heal
I know how fast it feels just let me
heal one
it will be digable
[Laughter]
pick a vlog
I'd miss a vulnerable to take 75 more
damage rather than 50 wow
you can I was just the other day
froggy Wawa probably was talking about
these paper frogs I used to make them
and also use I used to use the the
plastic version of them too and you're
like you touched your butts and dragged
them down and then you let them go and
they jump it's so cute
I still killed it's such a simple toy
you can literally make it with paper
you want to do a stream of origami yeah
yeah I will someday I have like a whole
book
on origami and uh origami paper already
in my apartment ready to go at any time
at some point
what are these little shits
what do you want
do you have any upon receiving attack
damage gains one strength
okay just just him
the rest is like
whatever
[Music]
um
I'll use this because I'm looking for
the card that I did not get
yeah I wanted jug our note
okay well then um
but maybe maybe maybe maybe
didn't that say draw one card
huh
[Music]
gain eight block draw one card I didn't
draw a card did I
I can't draw I'm strong
yeah well okay it was my biggest
blocking card so
I wait
how much do we have the Vlog too much
I'll just block the whole turn
yeah okay
once this one
girl's little [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah
well I need
[Music]
we still didn't get Juggernaut what the
hell
[Music]
so even we do
um
will they ever just not attack
what's their problem
wait well maybe we can we can like kill
one
again
[Music]
well only if I waste two of these
oh wait Oh I thought I still had space
for a block I guess not okay
it is what it is
let's try summoning blue eyes white
dragon
wrong game this suit oh oh now you hear
Golden Boy really now
I've been waiting for you I'm ready for
a super card
[Music]
should I play it now
I don't even have any defend cards right
now what the hell
[Music]
foreign
okay
now
[Music]
so
for him
we wanted to be so that we can kill him
in one or two turns ideally
he already has like a I can't kill him
in this turn I have two little Attack
cards
wait let me play this
no I didn't want that
I'll just I guess
do this
[Music]
strike strike 11 damage well
let me go all out on him
oh
11 11 and 8 is 13 damage I could kill
him oh right I did write math right
what are you guys telling me to do
something else can you not do math
week
look at this perfect kill why would you
tell me to do anything else
huh
and they make fun of me
okay you have 11 11.
[Music]
I could almost kill you
oh
I'm still not playing juggernaut
oh well
it's okay it wasn't a weird fight but
not my fault oh
[Music]
does not really look like
um
skip
okay good yeah we must take care of our
deck
ah hello cute fluffy babies you look
like chunkers right junkers
that card by the way that's my Joker
card if I run out of cards I'll play
that card that junkers has
it's a it's a fire chicken
and what are you doing again
rolls up and gained seven blocks once
per combat oh
where's where's swish
I Attack One
not bad is very good
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] I I get so much damage and
don't get any Block cards I need to get
rid of
it
[Music]
well I Choose You I Choose You
and you guys choose me right right
[Music]
strikes you to go yeah I need better
cards
instead
always of course
thank you oh
sure you little [\h__\h]
except for when probably what kidnapped
us yeah that was
something I will never forgive and never
forget
never
[Music]
um
I killing you
[Music]
and you are giving me time that's very
nice
hmm
I don't even know what to do in this
turn
do I have nothing yet
[Music]
wow
there you go at least we got some damage
out of it
take care of your deck
[Music]
yo are going to horny
chick Alcatraz
second strike horny jail
six
[Music]
what are there no other cards why do I
always see the same cards being offered
to me
flex and armaments I already have our
men that have seen flanks before is this
normal
it's good exhaust one card draw two
cards
and I don't like it
I don't like it
surprised how many of you guys want that
I don't like it I'm an independent woman
I will not go for that but
what do you think guys I will let you
choose this one two question marks or
one question mark
I don't know how to play this game well
you are here to learn just like me
what oh
super like two questions
and for a moment I was like why are you
guys so confused what did I say that did
I say something wrong
hey what
okay we'll go here
oh
[Music]
sitting peacefully atop what is that
it looks incredibly valuable you sure
don't see any traps nearby
oh what is the Trap
is it always the same what it does
wait it just drops gold I don't really
care about that
it's a good Relic it's a trap
trap yeah sorry I got rid of kotoni
because we have a new emote
it's good early yeah I guess that's true
early on later on maybe not so much
okay oh oh I get the choice now what
what
what about no traps yo here it looks
like an owl here it looks
comment
a golden owl
cute maybe not at all maybe it is a
phoenix hey
yeah new emotes
and and just gave it to me out of
nowhere
he
lose six Max HP
yeah
I think that's really not that bad
what you happen upon the grip of what
looks like purple flowers birds dancing
around the bonfire you mean like
literally a Ghibli movie
cute
cute they have faces the spirits toss
small bones and fragments Into the Fire
which brilliantly erupts each time
as you approach the spirit I'll turn to
you expectingly offer a offer receive a
reward based on the offer
I can burn a card oh get rid of this
[\h__\h]
that kitchen
they're ignoring me oh why why
they're giving me the
this one
actually this makes sense right now
because it's that hand I'm safe nobody
will stay oh she has so many hands oh
wait
no stand ones
wait let me fix that okay
I thought I was safe
okay
friend
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
maybe a block would have been better
at least I'm making choices myself that
are not too bad they're not like
completely wrong
[Music]
foreign
yeah
good turn
best choice
Chihuahua smart
so smart
huh
I just wanna block
and then
strike
smooth smooth
almost as smooth as smoothie
oh is that energy that I'm seeing
oh
I like this card because of the energy
but oh you don't even consider it
you forget random enemy three times
if I could just straight away like
replace
um my I strike with that then I like it
but
good right I think it's good like free
HP is not even bad
but that feels like a different kind of
it is actually good in combination with
a defend uh a block uh tactic no because
you're gonna like block all the damage
anyway ideally so then losing your HP is
not even like a problem
[Music]
oh hey
yeah no I don't mean that this will be
blocked
um I just mean that we already block all
the damage incoming from the enemies so
[Music]
we don't have to play and I think it's
just like you know it might be
interesting to use I'll take chicken
and now unfortunately it looks like we
have to rest again because we're right
in front of the boss
too bad
could not upgrade juggernaut
that naughty naughty what is this
mushroom nose card I see you
[Music]
that's slime oh yeah you're the one that
splits okay
what do we start with oh we have
juggernon and if we play armaments first
then we are happy
[Music]
I know I know
goop spray
okay now we don't know what you're doing
but you're not going to attack okay
should I like disarm it
[Music]
to defend
why
[Music]
when the strikes do more damage and he's
not attacking anyway
locking the seven damage
ah yeah because it's upgraded ah
[Music]
because Juggernaut was upgraded
okay
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
why you gotta slime me like that
so we have artifact and and should I use
like
under like a potion
I forgot what energy did
Angie just makes all cards more powerful
or what
use are you gonna use it
[Music]
ah energy
okay it makes a lot of sense
[Music]
oh
I never thought about you know getting
rid of the slimes should I
[Music]
definitely that
no
okay
should have bashed bus yeah I know
the vulnerable yeah I was unsure
[Music]
it's okay this is a boss fight we got
healed afterwards so
as long as we survive it
we cool
[Music]
should I use an energy potion and then
I know
should I yeah
[Music]
worth it
yeah I mean he split but don't let
George
so they both have 36 HP
[Music]
and they're not gonna attack
I'm a man's first yeah
oh bloodline upgraded gives me free
energy
free energy
[Music]
should die
here okay okay
oh I can play it all yay
yes yes
you got the right one yo all my random
hits we're always on the ones so far
that I wanted to hit
sick
one turn nice RNG
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I finally feel like I'm playing
slightest fire
alone in my stream like compared to the
other streams
hmm
these cards
um
offering
more Juggernaut
oh does that stack feel five damage to
random enemy so it does 10 damage or
two times five
for every time I defend
I think that makes you know at least
sense with what we're going for a defend
build
and people are saying that this is like
a damn good card for Ironclad but this
makes more sense with what we're going
for no
yeah
I think so and consistency
um
or very best card in the game
hmm
[Music]
two is too heavy
it looks good right
I hope you're gut feeling my gut feeling
surprisingly says Juggernaut I'm sorry
ectoplasm gained energy at the start of
your turn you can no longer gain gold
[Music]
messes with my bub
astrolabe upon pickup transform free
cards
[Music]
gain energy at the start of your turn
you cannot play more than six cards per
turn
oh
I think I wanna yeah do my strikes with
the Astro
yeah thank you for agreeing
one two three oh what was it why don't I
always get rid of it so fast I can't
look at it combust at the end of your
turn lose one HP and all seven damage
and deal seven damage to all enemies
cool
sexy block whenever you attack this turn
deal six damage back
fit perfect
exhaust all non-attack cards in your
hand because
block for each card exhausted
what
quite quite good
flame area though
wow
sounds sick
good for my build yeah
my RNG my orange team was even like
crazy or I feel like um in the last
play the Spire stream
yeah
pretty good okay what are we looking at
who's this boss have I fought this boss
before
[Music]
shop up okay here
I do have a lot of gold
[Music]
collector
I don't remember what that one was
um
you're the one with the many many blocks
just like me for real for real
Oh wait [\h__\h]
should have done this first
ah
[Music]
just so quiet
foreign
Okay so
ah
I don't know what to play
oh
[Music]
Block versus block
give me a good card
lose one HP until seven damage sure
and then I guess I'll just block for the
sake of
doing damage
[Music]
foreign
okay I need to like figure out how to
use this card by the way like
sauce or non-attack cards in your hand
non-attack how are skill attack skill
I would exhaust them but
mmm looking for myself for each card
exhausted
so that's already better
it makes up for the defend cards for
sure
just question if I would want to like
safe in Flame by using it first
[Music]
ah get rid of status like slam and burn
oh yeah that's cool
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
combo
[Music]
the head panel movement
okay his back is gone let's take him
down 17 can we do 17 damage
um Seven Seventeen can we do 17 damage
[Music]
nine
we can
[Music]
stop
oh we have a block card game five block
D5 damage around according to your hand
it costs zero do 40 damage
skip free free not worth
I mean it makes sense for what we're
doing because
we we actually do 10 damage then
if we have one Juggernaut on because it
also counts for the block
I'll take it
now let's go shopping
hello first of all let me get rid of a
card I'm gonna get rid of my last strike
I guess should I or maybe a different
card actually
[Music]
I choose Flame or was this a card that I
had just because
see relics okay
bag
[Music]
rest
additional 15. whenever you play a power
attack and skill in the same turn remove
all of your debuffs
bag is good
okay
[Music]
oh Purity say so
wow such a Cecil card
yeah I guess
um
what do we remove
[Music]
Bash Bash
yeah no because yeah my vulnerable thing
yeah yeah yeah
they'll get even more vulnerable it
works with my Relic
[Music]
but I don't attack
well but oh
wait
I guess the damage I do From the Block
cards
does not count as an attack
[Music]
oh that's sad
because I don't really do much damage
yeah
besides that
[Music]
okay
I like I like using vulnerable though
but
[Music]
okay
and uh should we buy another Relic
this sounds cool
might be helpful
[Music]
oh
what
let's have money
okay
go next stop fight fight
who is you plated armor
against 14 block at the end of its turn
receiving unblocked damage reduces
attack damage though so that's my my
damage that I do for Block cards also
not count
doesn't that count would be cool
[Music]
I bypass it thick little bell trumps
I might get the energy cardio
I did not get the energy card okay bye
bye
[Music]
now I got it hmm
and okay
[Music]
so I do this
and then
I'm too deep
[Music]
we're doing
now
[Music]
make me swim should we go attack or make
them lose some strength okay
all righty
[Music]
this is the first time I think that we
have double juggernaut
ah I want to play this
[Music]
wait is exactly 16 block
but we don't want
yeah it's cool
[Music]
could have also done differently sure
sure
that's what I was hoping for
[Music]
yeah nice sick lucky [\h__\h]
um does
when I play in flame and get strength
does that help my attacks that I do
through my juggernaut
I'm throwing a block party oh yeah block
27.
I think 90 95 of the people here don't
know what I'm talking about no
oh it's okay that's why I didn't play it
heck
because I thought so
um 26 damage can we do it can we do it
can we do it can we do it
[Music]
thank you
draw first
we have
ooh second wind
[Music]
five blocks for each card exhaust for
all non-attack one two non non attacking
one two
three four
five
times
twelve
right
holy [\h__\h]
how much did that actually do
I Wanna Know
was it five times twelve
okay cool sick that's a lot of damage I
think it's good that we got that card
I'm not asking how much is five times
twelve I'm asking how much it did damage
like as in like you know I didn't want
you to tell me how much 5 times 12 is
I I know how much 5 times 12 is deal
time is equal to your block ooh body
slam
this was cool too but
not nice oh
[Music]
come on and slam to my own archive
karaoke tomorrow
right or left
oh
[Music]
kind of want to go left to
to go here up straight Maybe
or left to go here to to fires
[Music]
and then here's another one oh
add another one oh my God
yeah for upgrading or do we want to like
fight a lot of boss fights we can still
decide for now I'm going left off
I donate card upgrades but once I have
to like too many card upgrades then that
one card will be obsolete
do I have
um
[Music]
okay don't have the upgrade card so
snackle
[Music]
forgot the snack I don't remember was it
evil
[Music]
thank you
our empty enemy
use portion
huh
the gates ah
why not
okay at least I never like actively use
that card it's good
wait what am I playing
dumb
should I do
that's it what were you gonna try to do
her passing perplexing glaze Blaze what
was that again
something we don't want
oh my God
[Music]
pop up
oh you know what these cards aren't
really like that cool
I'll give you this one though
[Music]
I guess I'll play this
oh oh you're right I get another card oh
at the end of your turn loose why don't
you paint yourself okay I'll take the
damage oh and another card no it's over
[Music]
flame is bad for my build
we can next time we get the chance to
kick a card out we can talk about it
and another one and another one and
another one you want to attack for 18.
well that ain't happening
oh
[Music]
wait non attack one two three
three times seven is 21 verses 16.
so second one is better
or we combine it again
[Music]
okay
quick math
this game
is like finally proving everyone
what I can do my potential
seven
I love this card I'm so glad I got it so
helpful
hmm
[Music]
I want to play it smart
um oh I could have uh upgraded
[Music]
ah
foreign
[Music]
oh I don't even there's so much choice
24 yeah okay wow
oh
that was a good play I think a good good
battle that we had there
[Music]
um
I say no to all these cards I think yeah
okay
cool question mark looks interesting to
me
I hope I don't regret it ah it's a
[\h__\h] burglar it's the bandits
[Music]
um I don't like them lose oh my God hell
no
okay what's our strategy who do we focus
on first
foot kill him oh yes I will
[Music]
you know me even if I only had one money
I still wouldn't want to give it to them
kill the bear first
this one
this one first okay
okay
juggernaut
do we also have the upgrade card
[Music]
no I don't see
I mean nothing went to Bear but that was
a strong start
and what did you do
decreases blocking the card
inal what the [\h__\h]
little [\h__\h]
[Music]
um
I kind of want to play shrug it off
before I play Juggernaut because I'm
hoping to get like
um the upgrade card and then play also
bloodletting of course
bug
that's great yay hey we're on the same
wavelength
[Music]
what
I just smacked my forehead because I'm
stupid
I was literally what I want to do and
then I forgot about because I didn't
really see it coming in you know that's
hard
what
[Music]
I get exactly the card I want and then
but hey hey in my mind in my mind I was
gonna use it so
I think I deserve praise for wanting to
do the right thing
oh [\h__\h]
um but okay I will play it anyway uh
more damage if
wait this one's free oh
[Music]
could have probably killed one of them
but you guys told me to go on the bear
[Music]
wait what why
ah because uh the one does oh yeah okay
I'm a little bit like um
confused right now okay
okay now now now now now now
we have to kill this one uh
uh fifth sixth sixteen
disarm the five times two fella
[Music]
but what else do they have okay
okay oh that looks like a really good
hand again
thank you
but I should probably play bloodletting
first
[Music]
arm then blood arm arm arm I'm
one
two it's only two cards now
thank you
let's do that
okay okay
may I kill him
[Music]
yay oh yeah we got weak the red mask
worth it
so with it thanks for the Applause
good and we'll see y'all
um
oh another iron wave
two or skip two two or skip
we have 18 cards right now hmm
I mean
[Music]
not an X2 well not an X2
foreign
[Music]
upgrade
then go here and then we might need to
rest or we might upgrade again and then
rest here
I think I'll go that path
body slam
ah
it becomes free
horizito
[Music]
okay I wanna fight the bosses but
um
I also want to upgrade my stuff
okay
what do we have
[Music]
should I do that now or first draw
another card
[Music]
because then I could upgrade whatever
card if it's better but okay well
[Music]
don't you
I hate these guys why I was domestic the
one that heals this one right so I kill
the Mystic first
[Music]
drawing first would have also made sense
one two two cards
[Music]
I'm not playing is like the best way to
do it but it's a way
oh come on this land and welcome to the
gym
[Applause]
what
that was good though
[Music]
why were some people like oh no
okay second one was waste oh
I didn't have Juggernaut oh oh oopsie I
somehow assumed because that's what we
always play but I have
[Music]
so building up that defense
even without the damage in the end
worked so well
according to kekaku
just believe in me believe in the kiwawa
[Laughter]
shut up when you play the 189 landfill
shut up is that are you trying to say
that I am stupid but just lucky
shut up
it is all according to my candy
so six times free
18.
right so
this arm this arm
foreign
[Music]
gotta play one of those
what is this again
hmm
I got the Vlog man
I kind of want to drink the potion
oh uh-huh
[Music]
this one we already have in our hands in
it it's one of your turn lose one is
petrol
foreign
[Music]
ER
I he won't be angry for long
[Music]
um
come on
[Music]
wait why would I upgrade them if I end
up like throwing them away with second
wind anyway
[Music]
I mean
right
maybe no second wind
because I I went all the way to upgrade
them
[Music]
and then I have two
maybe I still do it I still do it for
the damage
44 block
if only I still had the
block but but we can do something here
so
[Music]
I want cards
foreign
[Music]
that's true okay that way I guess I do
get some cards
[Music]
card
okay oh okay
oh that Relic is so sick so helpful wow
another body slam
[Music]
if I have two in a row in one turn
and let's say I have a [\h__\h] ton of
uh uh block
like let's say just like now in moments
where I have like 40 block I could do 80
damage
I do this because it sounds crazy
okay
now rest or upgrade we can go to another
like fire place right away so it doesn't
matter I'll just go upgrade
and I'll upgrade
[Music]
what was this every time you play free
attacks in a single turn again for a
Blog I don't ever do that
but thanks for the block I guess
maybe it will happen
one time
no no no
[Music]
body slime attack ah okay okay okay
so now I go sleep
I think I'll go sleep
um okay the wiggle question mark
question mark question mark
normal rest or question mark question
mark rest normal rest oh there's two
here
or questionable question mark shop risk
shop
[Music]
[Applause]
I kept both body slams right away
sheesh I don't have I don't have
I did it before yay
I was looking for it
come on and slam and welcome to the gym
oh my God
[Music]
oh my God unbelievable
big turn yeah great first turn
okay next go next
[Music]
and the people who know wixels we cross
I don't know I don't know
I don't know
also card game with cute girls best card
game that exists
[Music]
I do also like the anime
should I
foreign
but okay fine thank you for taking the
um
the decision off of me
slippery hand
my struts has a whole lot that's true I
want more whole life collabs with card
games and I wanted to be specifically
slate Aspire and magic zakaba ring I'm
totally not
biased at all I I just wanted for the
greater good for everybody for the sake
of everyone yeah not for me not for me
just for you guys like I'm so selfless
but I can't I can't imagine Magic the
Gathering doing a collaboration like
that but honestly I haven't been
following Magic the Gathering happening
since I was a small bamboo bubble so I
don't know if it's realistic do they do
stuff like that they did a Miku collab
really
[Music]
they do they do stuff like that
I did a good Zilla collab that does not
really like compare in my opinion
shadow bear is more likely yeah because
Shadow Voice already had
umasso right
they put La pudasa in as a as a card
[Music]
I think
which one is
[Music]
what
that's the Gathering as My Little Pony
cards
[\h__\h]
yeah
okay they make a lot of the race cards
oh that fits I think that fits really
well with magic the Gathering like with
the whole vibe and style
anyway let's kill these idiots
um
[Music]
oh I should have done this first
I feel so cool I feel so cool
oh
they think skip
[Music]
what I wasted for HP
oh
did I still have enough energy
okay a long time to pull the figures can
be seen entering and ah it's the
boob
we've had this one before I forgot what
it does
naturally you join the line and I'll
quickly surrounded by come Thursday nor
you as they Glee fully chant and wave
their weapons around
learned her murder
murder murder
[Music]
bye-bye thank you for the Super Chat
oh I heard the money raining
thus next
oh funny
could remove all my stripes
oh but I refuse to having I don't like
any I didn't even read this text but I
don't like any of this bye bye bye bye
bye bye please don't talk to me anymore
I'm not allowed to talk talk with
strangers my mom
actually never told me to not talk with
strangers
I can't remember
many strangers so if she if she would
have told me to not to talk with
strangers then I'm definitely doing
something wrong here because I'm talking
to all of you and y'all are mostly
strangers I mean maybe maybe the
maybe the ones who are here a lot you
cannot consider a stranger yeah no
maybe a stranger at my debut stream but
not anymore
but not anymore you're my employees
yeah we're past that point
okay what are we doing what do we have
matriaroska
the next two numbers just you open
contain two relics
it's much expensive I'll come pick up
getting two potion sauce um I had that
before
[Music]
oh playing on additional copy of a card
in your deck
[Music]
put mirror body slime we want the double
ones
juggernaut
ooh triple you want to go for triple or
body slam
[Music]
um
I feel like triple Juggernaut is
difficult to play when I have so little
energy
[Music]
foreign
blood
well I think we're gonna remove
um
a card that's for sure should we remove
in flame because we never use it
wait how expensive is it now though a
hundred
[Music]
all right
and then
hmm
do we really I mean it's I'll do it you
know what for fun
yay I'm having this run where I do
things for fun even if not everyone
agrees with it so I think it's just
just accurate bloody slam should we buy
a potion too while we're here
if I play this and then play a really
strong body slam sheesh that would be
insane
get the cheap shrug
hmm
okay maybe
but I have so many cards oh double
Juggernaut oh that would help
foreign
[Music]
no I mean like in the previous streams I
always like made you guys all do all the
decisions but just someone didn't do it
all the time
so
exhaust many cards with the second wind
you mean that's why I should take this
while now I looked at it I know what you
mean but
[Music]
you're making all the choices I would
make
[Music]
having a bigger deck isn't terrible here
oh
[Music]
I'll take
uh not bad second one true good argument
okay I still want
I don't want a potion oh look when did
we get a blog post and I didn't notice
I won't take the duplication portion it
sounds like fun
bye-bye wow we purchased so much can you
guys carry my shopping bags please
they're so heavy and I got noodle arms
you know that
please oh wait we're already at the boss
we gotta use up all the potions
uh what to do oh I guess we'll rest
they're right in front of the bus
[Music]
now
turn-based games I like turn-based games
y'all there let give me time to think
and yeah
but that's also a problem because then I
just um with the time to think I think
too much
Maybe
you think I can make it with 56
it's pee
great
I'm a block build okay that's true
okay okay okay
[Music]
um
finally do juggernaut
should I do something else
ah you you look so fancy
this could be like a calliope Mori album
cover this image right here
oh
[Music]
what does he know what's a special thing
what is a special thing
ah he has minions
okay that indeed combust very smart
I totally knew that
[Music]
for the upgraded juggernaut
remind me to use my pots
[Music]
okay here they are what is that ah okay
you just die when he dies okay well
that's it then
it's manageable
[Music]
horrible afraid of bodies
wait if I do this double and then body
slam if I do this double then I have um
26 times two
the block potion
or yeah should we throw a double on
flame barrier yeah yeah I think so
[Music]
thank you
I can play them all right
[Music]
oh
see I told you this would be fun taking
that potion taking that card
yeah I still have one energy left oh
well
that's that's good [\h__\h] damage right
from the get-go
can't touch this
can't touch it
my mom is watching the stream hi Mommy
Mommy hello Mommy
foreign
[Music]
stream is really cool and genius
actually she remembers how I had
absolutely no idea what I was doing when
I was playing Magic as a child but now
I'm ready for it
mama
I'm sure she's happy seeing you guys
commenting
her mama
okay uh
she has she has she has so little uh HP
already
um
all non-attack cards so
okay okay
[Music]
I'll play I'll play armaments I can
and then then
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm not sure if I even really want
second wind right now
yeah okay that's not the card I wanted
but okay
that case
no okay
[Music]
small boy I'll go follow the collector
minion okay okay
if we're lucky we can kill him in the
coming turn
well we got body slam so let's see what
we can do
we need a card or double body slam okay
okay if only we got a little bit more
energy but okay
I can
I can work with this
[Music]
[Applause]
way too easy it's like they served it to
me on a platter
wow so easy
another joke or not
I don't really want that many though
free Vlog is not oh
I did not even see it
power is mine
gain energy at the start of your turn I
want to see their intense
uh
[Music]
Markov pain
what
this one
[Music]
it seems like the safe option
I'm gonna find as good as
second wind
okay
I'm going to a draw pile
oh man okay
I would not normally go for it but yeah
we got
the [\h__\h] again
uh
[Music]
I don't even know where
to go here
[Music]
so angry hungry
I guess okay maybe me saying that
instead of hungry was my my subconscious
really really saying I'm if I don't eat
soon I'm really gonna be angry that's
how hungry I am
my brain I'm so confused these days
[Music]
where's juggernaut
ah the only drawing card I have is these
it's not what I wanted
[Music]
well
I already have like 16
block on my how did that happen wait we
can add a number 16.
and then buy some Butter Slap or we do
body slime bodies and second wind
[Music]
I think this
oh my God
ah
oh yeah yeah this was those that revive
if I don't um okay hopefully
they don't revive
so annoying
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I should have done this first
sorry
[Music]
okay
I don't know man I have no answers to
give to you
I am
as as much
confused as you are
like
down quite a bit
[Music]
um
should have maybe Shrugged it up first
[Music]
I always make these realizations like
immediately afterwards
[Music]
I get all the wounds but I have yet to
see that card I forgot the name
sick okay
[Music]
wait ah
can we kill him
we're 29 yeah I think we can
yeah now it's only you left
[Music]
oh my god that car the barricade is so
overpowered with body slam
what a build
skip
that's the build
so Opie
so fun when you get the op deck that's
why I enjoyed the last stream so much
with the Watcher
[Music]
uh shop
route
or cuddles will go here
and join to thank you
don't get too much cards yeah
I'm trying I'm trying but also we have
the argument that uh having a lot of
cards actually is good for this deck
with that one card that I have that
didn't show up in the past battle
Second Shop okay yeah but then we still
can go up here
whoa before you lies an elaborate Shrine
to an ancient spirit
[Music]
is there no catch
if I gained a hundred calls
[Music]
that's a great and remove
I remove curse at the shop
huh
okay
[Music]
yeah
something weighs heavily on you the
curse is the curse
okay some of you guys said the second
shop is better so
or now with all that money we could do
double shop though
go both
okay first thing I do is remove that
course I regret nothing
thinking ahead something kiwawa never
does just kidding I I
sometimes do
what do you want let me have here
Lantern ooh additional energy
oh
[Music]
start if you turn gain two strength no
okay don't need that but I think Lantern
for sure
homo strike
well they have battle Trends and
armaments
got some cool cards but uh what
oh wait never mind the first sentence
sounds good but the second sentence not
so much
[Music]
do you have a good potion he's got the
duplicate potion
someone mentioned something about
metallic size what does that do
[Music]
same for next job okay
it's a fight okay I don't mind a little
too fight
[Music]
I'm gonna do a sponge on purpose because
I wanted Juggernaut but I didn't get
juggernaut
[Music]
all right
that one's the one that explodes right
if I don't kill it you know
[Music]
what iron wave first
oh oops
[Music]
I still use it on him that's fine
it doesn't matter it
didn't matter
okay we got double juggernaut
foreign
[Music]
I like this hand
okay
[Music]
yeah that's me that's maybe not even
worth it
[Music]
yeah because the cards I got were not
harmonizing with each other
I'll just do this
[Music]
um
kill him though probably
yeah if I still do this
[Music]
not worth it yes for a bit
ah he will so attack yeah
that's safe more HP
[Music]
as well
let's just do it don't think too much
[Music]
he did not attack
he got killed before he could
okay and you you're not you're just
gonna stand there and do nothing
sounds like it's not lyrics from reflect
[Music]
I don't like this hand
no match for me
oh
someone was asking for this now I
understand
maybe last Card wait 20 bucks ah but
we're going to say yeah yeah yeah
now hopefully no more cards please don't
stop offering me good cards that I don't
want
oh
no no
let's see him
a pair
I can't afford I can only afford the
waffle
which one will heal me and give me more
HP
[Music]
remove
D already did wait what do you mean you
mean the the regret I already did
move the strike
okay
now I really can't afford anything
[Music]
ah the nemesis
what was this thing
nothing particular just having some a
little mini with lots of HP
[Music]
oh where's the
oh yeah
don't have the upgrade card don't have
juggernaut
thank you
truck
ah okay
wait ah I played the wrong card what did
I just play no I played the red card
huh
draw one card but I played battle
transfers yeah that's why I didn't I was
like um
then that was uh not not useful
[Laughter]
okay maybe playing flame burial
[Music]
and then play
I went away
[Music]
what else do we have
oh
a little bit too late
but it's strong
all right no that was really just for
the block though because
now we're gonna slam
okay well I'm happy with that first turn
yeah
foreign
[Music]
thank you
it's got one point cheaper nice
but I guess that canceled itself out
anyway because a lot of other things
costed one
[Music]
hey I want to play them all ah
foreign
[Music]
ever since I've been getting these wound
cards I just never get that exhaust card
anymore
[Music]
oh now you're giving me Burns too all
right all right all right
[Music]
um foreign
use the top what's top
what do you mean with top what is top
[Music]
and burn true
second Relic
oh okay so we were talking about the
same thing
[Music]
oh
I didn't even notice the intangible ah
well
okay I'll just wait
okay oh
[Music]
wow wow wow
where are my pixel sunglasses I want
them to come down and fall on my nose
I feel like I deserve that more pain was
this I'm going to random skills
thanks cool
I will skip though
[Music]
we like the flame barrier but
okay okay but no more no more we cannot
take any more cards no
uh oopsie
we have 63 so we're just gonna upgrade
something
what do we have to upgrade four cards
seven seven
eleven
three
maybe barricade yeah
make it cheaper
[Music]
now which path to always take I would
say probably this one oh that looks good
we have like free fires ahead of us
and a shop
[Music]
you guys wanted the question like I
think my choice is nice too
but thank you for making suggestions oh
oh crack
block gain increases as Malibu's
triggered receptor frame
[Music]
I'm going to use my Potions by the way
tell me to use my potions
[Music]
Maybe
no need here
but hey you're telling me to use my
potions I should use my potions
yeah okay
um
foreign
[Music]
yes
fine we're fine
39 damage
[Music]
good time good night high five
and next high five
[Music]
oh twice playing barrier but no
Juggernaut and no barricade oh wait
maybe we have one
[Music]
oh wow hello
no attacks this turn yeah
thank you
skill potions
yay
[Music]
yeah it would be free anyway
wow
[Music]
wait can I
swim right yeah okay
saved
look and slap that's what I want to do
yeah
[Music]
only I have one more body slam
oh second wind
and metal the size
and battle trans
okay let's start with France
oh
[Music]
is that gonna win oh
smart cookies wow
[Music]
that was a nice move
what do we get it's present time happy
birth to you
self-forming clay when you lose they
speak in free Block extern ah
everything with the word Block in it I
like
hmm
[Music]
nice
streamer r d okay
cool right side
I think I would go right fine but
if you have any problem with it let me
know
you wouldn't block me would you no
no
yeah right side yeah
yeah oh my God clay you like playing
with clay
what the hell is your stream orangey
um please complain to the developers of
the game not me thank you
and I guess we can sleep well we have to
Smith
I don't even have like
anything that I really desperately want
to save
um Play-Doh
[Music]
okay
yeah probably the best choice here by
the way did you guys see
it was announced that
uh
[Music]
mythism
the doing a collaboration
uh with counterside a gotcha game called
got a game called counterside you can
win this I know I think so too
yeah yeah
and the illustrations look so cool right
yeah the art is so pretty I was so happy
with it I have like a really Dynamic
pose and and they have a flying chicken
and they made my weapon really cool into
like like a spare kind of weapon do you
guys want to see wait let me let me try
to pull it up
um a counter is there like a picture
somewhere maybe
counter signed Kiana
oh yes
oh it looks so cool let me show you let
me show you oh this is kind of small but
whatever
ah [\h__\h] and why is it web pee
[\h__\h] webp files
uh
does that make that into a jpeg no [\h__\h]
I hate webp files
oh oh there's actually both of those
Arts oh yeah yeah yeah
let me show you I found
found oh these These are good
save image please save no why does
everything save as [\h__\h] webp
[\h__\h]
just going to information first missions
to get this event yeah
yeah Windows shift s
what is that
window shift yes
oh screenshot wait I did not know about
this I was always using Snipping tool
oh
I've never used that before that was
that saved as an
is an image
this is the Snipping Tool but better
oh wait he's safe
that's kind of small but I imagine new
tab doesn't make it better bigger it
does
[Music]
okay
all of this just because I really want
to show off the beautiful art
and then and this this one
oh sure all of us we did like a lot of
voice acting like we recorded so many
lines I've never recorded so many lines
before
but peanut fine
they're recording so many lines for uh
like anything else before no
so also in the introduction video they
played some lines right
um and I'm I'm I'm I'm talking a little
bit of Korean in my line but that's
that's because you know that was what
was in the script and I'm assuming it's
because I think counterside is like
originally from
Korea I think I might be wrong but I'm
pretty sure I think it's from Korea and
that's why they
um kind of like I guess wanted me to
include some Korean and some lines hmm
yeah but it's the global version of the
game so and you don't have to like know
any Korean don't worry so the
illustration
oh where is it
yeah
well it didn't really
safe as well
wait
sorry here I got it now
uh actually this one I think is the the
default normal one
looks cute look how cool my weapon is
and they have the KFC store in the
background and look at those curves
pretty so yeah we we are apparently like
skins for existing characters and uh uh
yeah so you need a character but the
character that is like behind mine Yuna
Springfield I guess is her name she's
apparently really really really really
really really really really really
really strong and maybe a little bit
hard to get but
um I hope you guys can like get it
anyway
um because the skin is so worth it it
looks so good
I look so good
yeah
I also like what they did with my logo
yeah okay so that's that it looks so
cool and then here so cute look at this
art my weapon is sick
and the dynamic this is what I was
talking about and the chicken flying
you guys can fly bursting out in Flames
so it's with my support you can only fly
with my support Not Alone
um fake into the chicken yeah it looks
pretty fake
wow
so cool so uh I forgot when they said it
would be like starting but starting
probably like soonish and then I hope
you guys will do your best to to give it
a try and get kiwaba for yourself
you can just get the skin first and then
hopefully eventually get the character
at some point maybe who knows if if if
um
if we're lucky and and I also asked for
it maybe there will be a banner
ideally with all the characters that are
behind the skins that are necessary
I asked if that was maybe possible but I
don't know what they're planning
um
because obviously like a lot of new
people gonna start playing the game and
not have any characters
oh my character was apparently on the
band of rap recently well hopefully they
can do it again soon because it would
only make sense right
um
that would be good so let's hope for the
best but all in all I have to say like
they prepared so much for this um
collaboration
um we recorded so much and they also
prepared so much like different Arts
this is not the only art they were like
some cute chibis and so on
um so I think you all should check it
out
it's a great cool Apple
[Music]
just wanted to let you know about this
let's go back the guy
[Music]
it's called counter side Google Google
it's the global version that we will be
on and you can like there's a link maybe
go on their Twitter I retweeted it
there's a link for like pre-regis
register I suppose you probably should
use that
because then maybe they will know you
pretty riches pre-registered because of
us I don't know
I think it's a steam too is it
perhaps maybe it is
anyway we're back into the game
did we just start this fight yeah we did
[Music]
what's this doing again
oh 10 more damage from attacks this turn
sheesh it's such a weak
weak weak enemy
don't impress me at all Second Wind goes
hard here oh
okay
fast no what no
oh yeah I already keep the block nice I
guess should I use this
because we got another card but let's do
it okay
[Laughter]
wait I can exhaust the card though
and then get another card
another card
an avocado oh
so many cards even though I didn't even
wasn't was not even because of the The
Relic
okay I would have liked to use the flame
barrier but okay
[Music]
baby
maybe
[Music]
um
whenever I play any card he gets more so
[Music]
let me use
you're gonna not
Juggernaut Metalized iron wave and then
body slam just everything right
[Music]
foreign
little chicken anymore
who doesn't know what to do
spicy I still got my Vlog this is so
sick oh my God we even got flame barrier
oh my God okay so
I will play this
[Music]
is
full damage
wow
too easy
[Music]
follow tornado open pick up choose a
power card starting to come up with this
card in your hand
don't really want any more cards I
bought this one card that I already have
start each comment barricade through the
barricade all of them are good
okay
[Music]
imagine I have like
by the way imagine that
[Music]
this is really the last card that we're
getting
the dream is real
wow I wanna like
this
forever
so I'm gonna go on forever and ever and
ever and ever and ever
why do we have to lose this perfect run
why so I think I would go this way
[Music]
oh yeah Ascension that would be like
perfect now
[Music]
upgrade the entrench okay
I was hoping for it to go to one I mean
what else would it do
yeah that's say what you got
can't even afford removing a card I can
afford a spoon cartridge
oh this card
we want them to do anyone can we have
something I wanted we wanted them to
astonished
do we want things to exhaust
specifically for some reason
[Music]
corruption corruption corruption correct
oh skills cost zero
[Music]
I think uh yeah maybe a potion instead
we have explosive potion a swift portion
and a dexterity potion
[Music]
corruption is a scam
explosion
okay
I think um that's all that we're gonna
spend our money on
yeah
we're almost at the bus guys almost so
close
yeah nice haircut
what
haircut what what
[Music]
you made a nice haircut why don't why
did
when the two people oh hair cat
I'm just confused my two people in a row
said nice haircut
oh is that the shopkeeper said to go
okay
ah I didn't notice I don't listen to him
[Music]
nice starting card uh a hand I think
thank you
I guess
drunk first
[Music]
oh because I don't then draw more cards
I forgot
ah [\h__\h]
my little designs or another shrug
hello okay yeah yeah we'll be happy
we'll be grateful later on that we did
that
[Music]
that's all I do spicy
I have so many like sex things are we
just gonna save them for the gloss
[Music]
okay
and Trench
[Music]
don't bother okay yeah
back
[Music]
no where's my
where's the card that I want
[Music]
it's where's my body slab
I wanna do a stick body slam
[Music]
um
that would be so cool
and what did I get so much Vlog for and
do you want another body so I'm just
kidding no we're not taking another one
no no
no no no no
wait oh wait we have full HP
can upgrade something
four cards Maybe
oh
what a perfect run it's time for the
donuts
let's go
will this be
like an easy walk in the park like last
time with the water I don't think we can
kill them both in one turn but
but
it will be just as fun
okay we're gonna drink
[Music]
but it doesn't matter but we're gonna
drink
potion
[Music]
right just drink it off all that
okay okay
so
so obviously asleep these
[Music]
no why not
who am I going for first like there was
like one one of them is better to go for
it
the donuts okay
I don't want to exhaust the body slam so
I would use it first oh wait it's a it's
an attack card anyway
[Music]
yeah okay okay
not an endless loop
but we'll get there
hmm
[Music]
frog our bodies
ah there's no match for me
Mommy we don't need to worry at all
there's no way that this can go wrong I
know I might jinx it by saying that but
there's no way
[Music]
to this one first kiwawa
well I was so smart she actually did oh
wait hey elements is so useless right
now
should I put a block
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay now
we're talking
um we have one body slam we have
entrench we have the flame barrier we
have bloodletting and we have a couple
of Defense
[Music]
all paid up yeah save one energy for
entrench yeah
okay so I will start with you
whatever that's not the order does not
really matter so much right
I will
drink this
I guess it works for the defense wait
let me think ahead I have four energy
um one is gone by entrench
we're not playing
combustory not necessarily
okay
oh
my God Maya
mama
achievement impervious why because I
have so much block I have 142 books
[Music]
and I can't find the block I mean I'm
part of it at least a big part
ah
I'm so happy
I love you slayed Inspire yes slay
it's making my day
okay
um
sorry I still my brain is still slow so
I still like take some time to process
everything that I see
wait how much do we have two oh okay
we can just go four
[Music]
I'm pretty yeah almost got him
almost
[Music]
I can't attack though there's no attack
card unless
unless
[\h__\h] sake okay we'll just attack next
time
we will just attack next time just look
at my block
Mama Mia
can we just add another seven block to
it
999 Kenley can we
get an achievement for that
stole isn't it Stephen for it
oh
you want to play that kind of game huh
okay okay we'll we'll stall but I
I could get the block though
[Music]
I don't think
either yeah he just it will die from
juggernaut
oh definitely die yeah
oh sad but we we could have gotten there
so um anyway
it's the 335 damage
[Music]
yeah
what do you want me to do entrance
yeah Overkill oh
[Music]
amazing so can I slay the Spire now
because I did all four I cleared the
game with all four
I heard that only then and only then
wow
the heart squirms and bleeds but is
ultimately still pounding are your
mightiest attacks not enough
on my next run yes because I've never
been here before you feel that you have
dealt a total of three thousand and
fifty four damage to hurt a total of
blah blah blah damage has been doubt by
all who have challenged it the hard
pulses louder and louder as your
Consciousness fades
victory
[Music]
kill achievement
deserved
oh what is this all that money oh prayer
wheel
can drop an additional card reward
Shuffle you can now dig for relics the
rest
that's fun
cute one more run and that's it it
already took two and a half hours
but it was a lot of fun and I'm gonna
read some Super Chat just now I'm gonna
make a sandwich first but that was so
much fun we're gonna my satisfire again
soon hopefully and then finally really
slay the [\h__\h] Spire whoever the Spire
is essentially next time uh no next time
I don't know whatever it takes to do a
run where I clear the game
because now
what is this
we have all three of those things
so that's just a normal Runway that I
would have to do
yeah no the real challenge begins is it
more difficult or is it just a normal
run
was ridiculous little people it was
the
um
much harder there's a fourth floor
oh
a whole extra floor nice
I graduated baby slay this fire and I
wondered like if I do that run I can do
it with whatever character I want right
hmm
I had a lot of fun with Ironclad now
with the block build but I also had a
lot of fun with the Watcher with the
loop built
those two are my favorites I think
I mean there's obviously still builds
that I did not try yet
but
it would be one of those I think
I would try one of those I think yeah
I was like
I don't know I also had fun with the
poison build it felt really easy
especially because it goes through the
block yeah and all that
I don't know about this one I was just
suffering of this one maybe I need to
like do a different build
I had shift build I haven't really
properly tried that one yet
properly
well I'm like a better art for all cards
by beating the hidden Final Act of awful
characters
oh really
[Music]
I did see I was like
uh looking up this late Aspire
um board game kind of wanted
I don't know I wouldn't even have anyone
to play that with probably but
I don't know board games are Charming
I kick-started that board game you you
were the first person right
but yeah I saw they have like a
Kickstarter thing
um we can play solo
oh I guess that makes sense because
that's what's you originally do
I don't really think there's a lot of
board games that you can play solo
it's back at yesterday oh nice timing
hand came so Hand cam solo game yeah
why not
[Music]
loads of board games you can play so I
can't think of a single one right now
I mean you could even play chess solo if
you just play two parts but it's not
really made to be that way
[Music]
now look at that cards
but you will show them to me if I ask
you right
maybe I'll get it maybe look at this
latest fire board game someday
anyway I had a lot of fun
let's play it again sometime I'm gonna
go make a sandwich and then we'll read
some super chats so if you want to stay
then you're welcome to stay
it will take just a
I hope drown you on board games
oh that sounds uncomfortable they have
so many edges and
yeah okay so I make a quick sandwich
won't take long
and see you in a little bit
yeah yay
all right there's no music here right
um there you go
[Music]
oh thank God I still saw that message no
music how about now
how about now
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
are you
ready
[Music]
break I will never again
[Applause]
[Music]
down tonight
could you dance
[Music]
[Applause]
education
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
okay yeah
hello
can you get a key
oh uh
don't look don't look
embarrassing
my music
okay let me like Munch a little bit on
my sandwich please it's good
you know I had some leftover
um gouda from yesterday but it's like uh
no slice but uh Shredded oh it's too
loud
[Music]
so because I don't know what else to do
with it and I don't want to waste it I
poured the shredded gouda on top of my
or like actually on the bottom of my
sandwich it works it works
[Laughter]
wait
[Music]
someone said
we will have this office until Christmas
no I got an update today
[Music]
what's different
from last year I wonder I mean besides
the whole talk stuff and the do you and
four blood and so on being at a beside
stand what's new
[Music]
all right yourself
there's a hole in the window
and some
what is that
some some fabric myself
[Music]
what do you mean what do you mean was
that chicken always
no there's no jump scare here too
it looks like a runner
who wants to who made the hole was it
Casper
and one of the the Fabrics supposed to
mean
[Music]
they're just [\h__\h] with me now there's
no no such thing
[Music]
you guys are freaking me out
oh
yeah
I have tears in my eyes
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] he's an exiled
so it wasn't so she just got in for the
window where she surprised me last time
hmm
[Music]
how did I not notice until you guys told
me
like I feel like it's pretty noticeable
was I always looking at the chat every
time that she peeked through
there she is oh my God it's [\h__\h]
terrifying
in Exile this is supposed to be a
Thanksgiving update and he still puts in
the [\h__\h] jump scares me she just
wanna you just wanna miss me is so mean
it's bullying
[Music]
LOL you think this is funny
I'm crying and you think this is funny
it's a good idea though I'm gonna give
you that
putting her there
um
smart
[Music]
and I looked
in the exact right moment
but the thing is
I didn't expect
any more jump scares because it's the
Thanksgiving Studio update
[Music]
so you know no more spooky season
why would there need to be a jump scare
except only if he wants it don't look
only if you want to bully me
and you guys I thought you were just
like you know joking around
oh man
life is a horror game
[Music]
I should have written no jump scares in
the contract
[Music]
so you were genuinely just warning me
that's so sweet
you guys were having my back
hmm
[Music]
let me show you
new emote
in big
literally me when I saw vampiara down
there
it's me
it's you
[Music]
laughs
hmm
piano wake I don't want that it's too
spooky maybe next Halloween
[Music]
I only have a couple bites left
okay
Happy song
[Music]
works well
laughs
[Music]
um
I'm just putting the hand out to defend
myself
[Music]
[Laughter]
2.5 more bites
[Music]
foreign
I'm not giving her anything
mm-hmm
[Music]
it's so interesting how
this and also the previous one it just
Blends in so nicely that I just don't
even notice until you guys tell me
[Music]
foreign
I got it
Where do I
continue reading
[Music]
is it the member stream maybe on table
water
[Music]
I was scared too
it scared the egg out of you
[Music]
um yeah yeah I was um terrified glass
glass
look look at me
look at me and now
[Music]
look
down there
[Music]
that's why that's why we are in this
current state
I got a heart attack
the first time
glass are you okay are you okay
[Music]
are you alive
dead
don't go
dead oh no it's really dense
and I'm laughing
you didn't exercise look at the damage
you've done
foreign
I want to read them like
in a good speed because I
I really need to fix my sleep schedule a
little bit like at least like go back to
like falling asleep at 3am or 4am versus
going to sleep at
falling asleep at 6am it's
um gotten pretty fast this past days
because I was staying up so long
for several reasons it was
especially that smoke up suit keeping me
up so long
yeah it's too late
so I wanna try to sleep a little bit
earlier today
hopefully okay
[Music]
yeah so where are the membership tryouts
that feels like ages ago
it feels like so long ago good night I
think thank you for coming
both of you
at least I don't have to cook because I
already cooked yesterday
um I have also got the burger turned out
amazing that's my the best burger I've
made so far and I haven't made many but
you know
the only thing I guess I overdid is I I
added way too much oil when I was um
frying the patties so the patties turned
out pretty oily
yeah
I just didn't want them to stick but
yeah then in the middle of cooking or
frying it I I got rid of some oil
but I made the the Patty quite well I
would say like it was
um last time I I did something like this
I think I had the problem that the
inside was still super super super super
pink
and I just uh
could not like get it
properly done
um but this time that didn't happen so I
think I balanced
um the time and the heat quite well
and also I made the Patty by the way
with like
um
with mince meat of course and also
carrots shredded carrots
do this before when you make a Patty you
add carrots I felt like I was making
pasta but the recipe demanded carrots
and honestly I did not like taste
carrots when I was eating the burger but
I'm just guessing it added a a good
special flavor
never tried that I've tried it before Oh
probably nothing like noticeable but
like where I can say oh there's carrots
in this burger patty but
I think it would taste a little bit more
boring if it was without it
[Music]
um
yeah it made it a bit sweeter probably
[Music]
and so it was onion carrot and the
minced meat
and then besides that I had um you know
salad and tomato inside and there was
like a little dip that they had me make
which was a yogurt
yogurt dip but I just added some garlic
to it to make it a bit more interesting
um so pretty simple but
um the
the meat it did take a surprisingly a
good amount of time potatoes easy though
just slice them up put some oil some
salt some pepper on and then the
whatever other uh
herbs you want and then throw them into
the
either airfryer I guess or into the oven
super easy you don't even have to peel
the potatoes because they're fine the
way they are
there's a recipe uh yeah I mean I've
been using hello
Ash for the past
couple months and they sent me the
recipes and the ingredients and that's
what I've been using
so I just do whatever they tell me to do
but sometimes change it up a little bit
if it's possible if I have something to
change it up
[Music]
yeah potato feels healthy
hello what
flesh oh flesh yeah Vampira is looking
for the hello flesh
hmm so since I had this problem with the
oil and I was watching some airfryer
videos today I guess next time I can try
making the Patty in the airfryer if I
feel like it if I feel like getting the
airfryer out it's just like it takes up
a lot of space and I already have like
so many things that take up space in my
kitchen so I've been storing it away for
the last since the last time I've used
it which is like ages ago
like over half a year ago
and then you know even though there's
obviously many things I could do in the
airfryer well first of all the recipe
tells me to do things in the frying pan
and then you know I'm like okay well
I'll do it the way they tell me to do it
because then I can't do anything wrong
and getting out the airfryer then having
to clean it I don't know
[Music]
it's like
butter butter for frying a burger
oh
[Music]
foreign
I did not do the question thing yet no
but uh I guess I'll do it now I was
waiting for
uh
some confirmation but
yeah I'll I'll wait until I wake up
tomorrow and then I'll put up both
question things because I'm still kind
of waiting for confirmation
yeah I'm just gonna collect both are you
gonna you're gonna be able to send
questions to me too I'm not gonna be
thinking up all the questions to myself
myself because that's kind of weird too
[Music]
but I do wonder what to do about the
clips because it's gonna be mostly uh
normal
um whole talk episode as much as it can
be normal
like the order is still gonna be pretty
much the same we're just doing it in 3D
and with myself and with a special
announcement
viewing kiwawa oh but I don't think I'll
translate myself
I think we'll just do the whole
interview in English I don't know should
I
should I translate myself I don't know
Japanese
I don't know
do it in German and Translate
[Music]
nah maybe I will not translate this time
because
I feel like I
just wanna I don't know have this one be
smoother and really just focus on
I don't know the specialness of the
episode
[Music]
for Japan Bros but it is being streamed
at a time that's
pretty [\h__\h] for Japan Bros anyway I mean
they could watch the Vlog but
I still think about it
I'm unsure
yeah
it is gonna be pre-recorded so in theory
I could add subtitles but you know it's
gonna be a long
stream
[Music]
video so
subtitling all of that I wouldn't want
to be the one to do it
foreign
my plan is
[Music]
to have someone
uh stand in for myself when I record the
other part
and then yeah
kind of like put it together I don't
know
[Music]
yeah and one kiwawa will sit on the host
table and one kimawa will sit on the
sofa here we go again tangenting even
though I said I want to do the super
chess fast
foreign
the cool thing though is that
um the studio I'm getting it like so
that I can use it in VR integrated and
um
I'm having the like camera system
integrated as well the one from the
Ahmed Amita very Studio
so the same kind of like
cool
camera moves movements and all that can
be used too
[Music]
when I'm up here appearing on HS talk
show I already did it's like on
anytime's Instagram the full version is
on her Instagram and the short version
is on her Twitter
[Music]
you missed it yeah
go watch it she has a Instagram where
it's uploaded as a as a like real kind
of thing
it's okay you can still watch it
yeah pretty much motion I guess that's
my plan but I did not think too much
about it yet but I think that's how I'll
do it
and then I'll like prepare the questions
and I'll have whoever possesses my body
read out the questions
as the host and then I'll just answer
that and then I'll do a voice over of
the questions
I think that's the smartest way
to do it
in my mind
so that way the host
like still moves and it's like not too
awkward like you know and I can still
like make some cuts and so on of course
if I wanna
okay I'm not a stranger to something all
the time
no no I'm no stranger to
um lip syncing I'll talk
that's what I did
for
[Music]
um
all right let's start with the members
only super chats
um
this fun thumbnail
so much going on so this is
what we'll read
[Music]
um
it was not my idea it was froggy Wawa's
idea moon dog
[Music]
mundong says I still find it hilarious
that you threw me into the usual room
for the frog name even when it was your
idea in chat
let's play since it was members only
thanks for being always so fun to watch
it was not me but yes I will take the
praise of being a genius
I'll silence you I'll throw you all into
the usual room if you say anything
that does not align with what I say
[Music]
Reynolds
thank you for the rest of the chat did
you know
collab with national museum of Korea I
went here there today and it was so nice
I could see the austrian's true passion
for art as shiny as the sparkling
treasures and so envy that you live
alone in the Treasure Trove of Art
yeah
I mean that's cool that they do that but
I'm really unfortunately not like a
person that likes to go to museums a lot
I wish I was more sophisticated and
enjoyed that more
um I went to that museum with with Cali
that fancy [\h__\h] Museum
and I enjoyed it but
yeah it's not really I'm not the type of
person who would go to one without like
a claws like that because I'm showing
someone around or so
um but I'm glad you enjoyed it okay not
[Music]
Korea has a lot of treasures in their
Museum and and besides their Museum in
your home because that Treasures you
I hope that you understand
how I'm hitting on you
up
because I don't think your English is
like 100 fluent but I hope you
understood this
move
oh
[Music]
thank you for the pinky thank you
um
thank you for the pinky had a dream last
night I asked you out and you said no
welcome salty but laughed right after
because I realized I wouldn't date
someone like me either hey
say that by the way how much are those
expensive massages I got a job promo so
I like to shoot my V Booby Baby to one
with me
am I your V for me baby
who is your wee movie baby
[Music]
I think I think you were
trying to
get me a massage right
we will be baby but why am I a baby
it's more like
hey babe I like my back
where is Sandy Sean
[Music]
just gonna assume it was for me
oh thank you I don't like the first part
of your Super Chat because don't say
that
it's like I cannot really judge I can't
tell but I'm sure that there is
plenty of people who would enjoy dating
you
[Music]
yeah
and the massages
I usually
uh pay like I mean it's not like
expensive crazy expensive I just go to a
normal massage place but it's like one
hour
60 to 80 Euro
I think
pencil
I want to go weekly I would if I
had the time and if they had like a
stamp card
if they had a stamp card that would be
nice
can't talk much sorry so it works it's
okay
yeah good luck have fun at work
[Music]
it's reasonable in Japan they were
cheaper though
in Korea I went to this massage place
with Nabi Mama that was apparently
really famous on TV I mean not really
really famous but they were featured on
TV several times
and I think maybe I told this before but
they had this like
um foot bath with the feces inside
and I I don't know these small fishes
they freaked me out so I didn't do it
I feel like I did something like that
before at some point in my life but uh
yeah they tickle a little bit really a
tiny little bit but I don't know I
didn't want to put my feet in there yeah
they eat your dead skin cells yeah I
didn't feel like it though
[Music]
which reminds me oh my God I fell last
night into a rabbit hole that also did
not help my sleep Rhythm
I fell into the fishing YouTube rabbit
hole a little bit but thankfully I was
still able to be rescued by myself
forcing myself to stop watching
but I watched um this video of
this crazy catfish
[Music]
being fished and it was like a huge one
big big catfish and then I watched like
the original
um video
[Music]
and then oh God she's so [\h__\h] scary
that piano stop
no not with their hands but this person
they were apparently a really good
Fisher it was funny because like I was
watching the I was looking at the
comments the comment section and they
were all praising this dude for being
really good at his
[Music]
uh what do you call that when you throw
the thing
there was like a word for it
nothing yeah his casts were apparently
like god-like and really accurate and I
can literally not tell if it was good or
not but apparently it was it was funny
reading some some fishing lingo in the
comments that I also had no uh
understanding of and it's just it was
interesting to see a different world
where you know all these fishing can I
say nerds fishing maniacs
are like speaking in a language I don't
understand but it's kind of cool and
cute and I don't understand but I want
to I want to understand
[Music]
and those fish oh my God the catfish
so ugly
[Laughter]
they're ugly but I don't know the
fishing video was somehow still kind of
like relaxing because the water was so
smooth and pretty and then every time
every time he caught a catfish
it looked like quite difficult to reel
it in
but yeah once he reeled it in he would
always let them go
very interesting catfish and shams
not very nice for me to say
well I mean I guess there's ugly or fish
but
don't they're pretty ugly which is
ironic because most people that catfish
are probably less attractive than uh
faces they catfish with huh
holy [\h__\h] that was such a smart like
you know
that's the point
oh it's a point that you're
that people who fish you know they think
they're fishing something cool but then
they get surprised by a catfish and
they're like disappointed is that a
thing like those catfish specifically
they for some reason they're not popular
but why why though because they're ugly
well then that proves my point
when I said they're ugly and you were
like hey where do catfish are standing
catfish sad that you said that
they breed to lunch
they don't taste good either huh
they don't look like they taste good
yeah
that's so funny
catfish are Godly to eat you seem to be
one of the few ones of the England
unconventionally attractive
I used to eat catfish nuggets what ew
[Music]
also talk about we will thank you I'm
not gonna say happy birthday yet because
it's in six days
but I probably won't read the super chat
today so when I read it it will be
closer to your birthday
foreign
[Music]
there's like fish nuggets
I've never had fish nuggets no way it's
like a fish that is just like a fish
tape here right
I love fish dip yeah that was my
favorite thing as a child
fish fish sticks
oh that's so good
I think I always ate it with mayonnaise
[Music]
you should make fish sticks again can
you make fish sticks in the airfryer but
I I like the the frozen ones from Igloo
that we have
there's like probably more healthier
ones and so on but those are the ones I
always had as a child and
oh they're just perfect
[Music]
you can probably air fry the frozen ones
though right
so I would still use the airfryer hmm
I guess that's one thing with those fish
sticks they always turn out so
they they always it felt like they
turned out so oily
when you throw them in the oven even
though I never put oil on them
but when they're done they they kind of
seem so oily somehow
crystals foreign
[Music]
what is wrong with you
for good hahaha
foreign
fish sticks with vanilla pudding
it's a doctor who reference
oh really I never watched Doctor Who
thank God it's a reference
[Music]
that's just apparently
apparently
[Music]
another parent what's the word I'm
looking for that's just extremely
unhealthy it sounds so unhealthy like I
mean fish sticks are already like
seem kind of unhealthy but with vanilla
pudding like what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
what's with bad Smith what's with Mike
Smith he's
pudding
Oh you mean the actor not not the actor
but the character not the actual person
right
oh he's Doctor Who
I know that um
oh my God
Doctor Who eats oh my God that's
terrible because like a lot of people
watch that show and then think that
that's okay to feed your children
because they saw it on Doctor Who
[Music]
oh strange
it's some weird cramming he had oh only
for like a moment maybe he was sick or
so
anyway anyway we should stop tangenting
I need to read the butchettes God damn
it
thank you for the pinky
pinky just woke up sorry I'm late Angel
no worries I guess the was the members
only like kind of like
late announced
I know that the game was late announced
so did you just
shoot
miss your alarm or song ah I made it one
out early on because otherwise unknown
you would never be late would you
I'm sorry
I'm sorry oh man
uh Bamboozled you
I'm so sorry never land before you know
what this one does not count I'm ruining
his perfect attendance oh
[Laughter]
steak I'm sorry hmm
I mean how can I read Brendan Duncan mud
okay
thank you I hope you will be less poor I
wish you all the best
[Music]
um
did you just wake up onion
[Music]
what do you mean I don't know the
difference between a PS3 and PS4 hello
guard
I mean they're different consoles I know
that what did I say
ultimate mk02 at 203
and silver rattle thank you for the
recipe
[Music]
what did I say
I nearly fell off my bad singing
why are you so like stressed out about
like always seeing me like on time and
never missing even in seconds I mean
that's so sweet and I love you but don't
be so stressed out
chill I always watch the bond
so Silverado says
oh I remember this a little bit hello
Canada today marks exactly one year
since Alice Mathis returns stream and my
start of the long young path had a lot
of fun learned that you are a great
musician fun streamer and a very sincere
person and I'm looking forward to the
next year Watching You are you here
Silverado
oh I've confused them all new
yeah apparently that stream was a year
ago I mean it does feel like quite a
long time ago
there you are I'm so happy that someone
I said this already I think the first
time when I said this when I read the
super chat but I I'll I'm so happy that
there's people who found me through
Alice miles madness returns and then
decided to support me
even the
games the game streams that don't have
like many Watchers there will always be
like some people who jump in and they're
like oh interesting
Hulu
even when you don't expect it
well thank you so much for finding me
and giving me a chance I really
appreciate it thank you I hope you can
stay for a long long long time and who
knows if they ever release that new
Alice madness games game can speak
English today I'm sorry then
I might play it if they release it like
within the next
years
Swedish please rather sooner than later
please
be nice
you're great for what watching thank you
my turn from local to regular shortly
after thank you
thank you Leah thank you
it will come out when portal 4 releases
hey
you could just
[Music]
say and looking for two plus years what
yeah I mean at least you're here though
thank you for watching
last minute I got into watching without
you the one I see the most of thank you
yeah I do think like
I've read about people trickling down to
me
after watching others and then staying
with me I appreciate it thank you so
much
[Music]
one of the earliest dreams I ever
watched was you near automatic finale
oh I wish I could repeat that experience
like the whole new Automotive experience
was a beautiful really cool game even
though I struggled so much true
it's so sad when I play some cool game
and then I can't have that experience
ever again of playing it for the first
time yeah makes me sad
oh Fire Emblem at least Fire Emblem is a
serious and I'll get another Fire Emblem
so soon yay
the [\h__\h] vsync you know
played it without tab from the get-go
it would have made so many things so
much easier I think
I would have made half of the gameplay
so much easier
[Music]
speaking of games I'm a hated it
shouldn't give it a try
I'm a hated new ultimata did you say she
hated it I mean she abandoned it but she
didn't hate it
how can she hates a game where there's a
cute butt in your face the whole time
she hated streaming it
she had a chat
I guess so
and she's missing out on a great game
[Music]
it's not the type of game she wants to
stream
didn't want to stream
oh wow
maybe one day she will stream it or like
play it alone
you're making me yawn too I'm making
myself yawn by yawning
anyway thank you Silverado
I am a team thanks when you changed the
writing of your name huh you felt like
like you know dressing up a little bit
for me
come and see dungeon thank you thank you
for your first
appreciate it
[Music]
Judy duncast
okay a quick super chats from the little
video
that I uploaded
[Music]
um
427 elsewhere
[Music]
oh yeah I did upload that in the middle
of the night because I figured out the
[\h__\h] mocap suit and I was so proud
[Music]
and I wanted to show you guys
so yeah
[Music]
I think
we all appreciated it
shouldn't
uh okay
[Music]
now I'll read trombone champ
s
thank God that was trombone fan art
of me perfect Perfect
[Music]
those kind of fan arts that you can only
use for very specific streams
[Music]
but then when you have them
you really appreciate it
[Music]
enjoyed that stream
I could have done so much better in like
all of the songs that I played like
around the middle
[Music]
if I didn't forget about pushing a key
instead of pushing my left Mouse button
[Music]
you keep a jug of water next to your
desk yes I do I actually not like I have
like a I bought an extra desk a small
one that I can move around a while ago
and that's why I keep some extra stuff
like I want a junk some honey some stuff
I need for tea Etc
I need a space like my monitors and the
girls are everything takes up so much
space on my desk that
um yeah I basically made it into an L
desk yeah
yeah and then when I
um do like a hand cam stream now I use
that one for doing my handcuff stuff
was it yesterday yesterday I realized
you know some cute girls around me
they're into hello projects so I made a
little
um Twitter DM group
with them
Pandora got a little heart attack
[Music]
yeah yeah yes with Wolfie too yeah yeah
I was surprised I had no idea why did
she not tell me until now what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
secret hello DM group yeah and Pandora
who was your ocean
tell me tell me wait don't don't tell me
don't tell me don't tell me don't I'm
curious but no don't tell me
[Music]
don't tell me now
because tell me
tell me if we you know
[Music]
so many yeah
I don't have
that many oh she's in her project I like
them all mostly but like I wouldn't say
I have like so many washes but anyway
we'll talk about it we'll talk about it
privately hey
let's read those trombone Super Chat
when we're reading trump super chats
[Music]
um
sorry that I screamed but I just
remembered to do something
uh
why did I scream like that
[Music]
[\h__\h] someone made me an eggshell hat
come with us
okay props was here
[Music]
foreign
wait a second I'll be right back I mean
I'm here I just need to do something
[Music]
foreign
it's kind of up north okay
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
sounds beautiful right
[Laughter]
[Music]
[\h__\h] that's really difficult
playing this trombone needs a big lung
and I don't have a big lung
Dot
[Music]
I'm talking
I was a trombone version of do you
hope you liked it so
[Music]
no big lunches a big heart oh this
beautiful trombone is made by blue thank
you for making it I I didn't see it
before the trombone stream even though
it was already there before the trombone
stream so I'm so sad I missed it but
here it is okay
[Music]
um
thank you
happy belated birthday
[Music]
happy birthday to Memphis
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
happy birthday to all the others to have
a birthday in 2022
[Music]
you look so beautiful
happy birthday
to Memphis
[Applause]
thank you for supporting me
you're such a sweet chick
to stay the Way You Are
wasn't even a pink Super Chat and I made
a whole [\h__\h] concert for you
that's what you get for being loyal
yay
back to business
[Music]
don't expect me to do this for everybody
okay I'll I'm I'm not a cheap trombone
player
but I will try it at least if there's
any more
um birthday super chats today
since I have the trombone in my hand
already
[Music]
oh yeah it's past midnight oh [\h__\h]
and looking for the top thank you soon
thank you a dark Hood oh rainbow thank
you so much
let's see what this says thanks for
trying to give us 3D dancing a true idea
don't give a buzz meet us underneath at
the strobe lights come alive feel free
to something new we don't need no drinks
tonight I'm not just calling favorite
night I'm being supportive here just
take the Super Chat
I'll take it thank you
and um I I Don't Wanna Give Up forever
let's just hope that I get some access
to a proper Studio
soonish hopefully and then
can show up a bit more Dancing Yeah
look all I'm saying is will be patient
if you want to make the fruity dancing
happen so do you do you say you do feel
the same Sparkles like a flame I know
will never be the same just take the
Super Chat
where are you so I'm taking it I'm
taking it and I'm trying to refuse it
just saying life is only once you make
it you're gonna be okay so go ahead and
do it do it if you want to dance let's
get to it everybody's gonna know your
name because Sparks light the flame play
the Super Chat
are you okay
look I'm just trying to say I need to
tell you that I love you fruit and fruit
oh there's no one else in this world
that I would trade for you
challenge who are hard to take this
picture
look I'm just saying that you will live
to keep on fighting till the dawn hey
hey hey just take the Super Chat
oh thank you
trying to put all my
um all my original songs into Super
Chacos thank you they fit quite well you
could like fool a person it could be
like a a Rick Roll you could send
someone this text someone who doesn't
know my original songs as well as I do
[Music]
thank you guys
who wouldn't notice right away and then
be like Bamboozled at the end like you
just kiwala rolled me
what Kiara
hello
thank you duck hunt
[Music]
there's some dudes for you too
haha
thank you soon
very poetic those lyrics aren't they so
pretty lyrics
[Music]
yeah it should become a term yeah
John Bieber thank you for the recipe
chat
B and D Vietnamese
[Music]
it looks like a new oh
a new currency
[Music]
ah they didn't have super shuttles
before
wow well now you do oh it's nice too
have this spread out to new countries
[Music]
nice soon John Bieber thank you so much
give you one more Super Chat now wow I
guess that's just like
that currency has a lot of zeros damn
that's that's like
a red Super Chat 1 million damn
thank you for the 1 million
million Vietnamese dollars
[Music]
yeah did you change location
or I or did you just always use a VPN or
so are you always there
I'm rich
[Music]
it sure does feel like it's when you
have a currency that has so many zeros
a traveling
[Music]
oh
not forever right well enjoy yourself
there
this is a vacation or a work trip I
don't know but in any case have a good
time
and yeah have a safe trip be careful
um
some good time off to
recharge thank you so much for thinking
of me still
um
beware the wear trombone
when disguised as a trombone they are
very dangerous the tuning slide of the
wear bone is very sharp a friend was
bitten by the were bone with its razor
tuning slide at the end of his set and
made his thumb bleed true story
put that from somewhere down
oh
dear God
written by the were bones
razor tuning slide what
it was a normal trombone
a very dangerous normal trombone
interesting
dangerous well I hopefully won't hurt
myself on this one it looks pretty
smooth everywhere
so pretty the shiny so pretty
and this one I think is safe
little thing there did you see that I
just noticed now
[Music]
hopefully we can keep those wear
trombones
far far away from me gotta be careful
thank you for the pinky here wrist
pieces thank you also for Pinky another
birthday oh
another birthday with caffeine I get the
privilege of witnessing a true bone
performance by jackiana Amadeus Mozart
except my birthday was yesterday well
okay so this is not your birthday today
but still like I'm reading a super chat
right now so
dude
recipes
[Music]
but I appreciate it
[Applause]
[Music]
you are a chicken
[Applause]
that I don't wanna let go
I hope you stay forever
[Music]
am I pronouncing your name right or is
it rhymes please
[Music]
do it with me together
[Applause]
everybody clap your hands if you can't
do too
that was the end I was gonna go on for
even longer
[Music]
hope you enjoyed that you say you sent a
super chat at the right time there who
would have known that you would have
gotten a trombone superche a trombone
concert for you
couldn't have known
happy surprise thanks you buzz
you're welcome
from boncha
[Music]
Flappy boy thank you for the pinky
please don't tell me it's your birthday
too
even after five trombone streams my
first four totes will that be quenched
before I get the authentic awesome
experiments from my favorite color music
star I thank you garlic just now
but will your grind set be strong enough
to actually finish this game I I
considered the game finished so I say
yes
okay I'll finish it properly someday
privately but I don't think it's worth
another stream so
unfortunately
it's finished in math books you added it
to the list
then there's no doubt about it
I am not the trombone champ
Are you seriously saying this after what
you've just witnessed
I mean if I'm not the trombone champ
then I am trombone Empress or something
because
whatever I did was marvelous and you
were lucky to be alive to have witnessed
it
um
[Music]
thank you for the pinky I'm a God yes
your bull God
[Music]
boy
happy birthday
[Music]
happy birthday to another one
how do we have so many
birthdays in just one day
did you all have the same mom or what
happened there I don't get it
happy birthday
[Music]
yes maybe you should take a blood test
to see if you're related
[Music]
to compare some photos
sorry for worrying you
okay
[Music]
yay
happy birthday
[Laughter]
yay
I'm becoming a professional trombone
player
oh my God
[Music]
the fun instrument
please no more
anyway it says um first birthday as a
member of caffeine was yesterday so you
didn't stream so I was able to do my
other birthday Tradition I watched Alice
in every year because it's and I share
the same year and date of birthday
release oh
oh that's cool so we both turned 30
years old this year whoa
cool
and how are you holding up versus
Aladdin
he seems to look the same every year in
the movie doesn't he isn't that
depressing
just kidding
[Music]
Evans l
ol
I know you love me be honest to yourself
it's okay
[Music]
I love you too
I wonder if she knows whenever ah
yeah I guess because they all made love
on Valentine's Day
[Music]
makes sense
oh I'm aware
or is it Christmas
um probably Valentine's Day
[Music]
anyway happy birthday belated birthday
ideas thank you thank you for the pinky
I miss Kiwa so I decided to watch some
old rise of streams while you were gone
oh I ended up buying both games today
and I can't wait to play them oh
[Music]
whoa that's an old stream but yeah those
were all really chill and I think yeah
if you're missing me
those are some nice streams to re-watch
and fall asleep too
um
relaxing
[Music]
rise up free maybe one day we can play
that too
[Music]
but I have a lot of games I want to play
in the coming
couple months so I'm pretty fully booked
right now but I'm glad you're enjoying
the boss good too every once in a while
go back to your favorite VOD and enjoy
it once again especially like if it's
been like two years or so then I think
it will feel pretty fresh to you
enjoy
thank you you got the the wings
two years as a member thank you so much
oh don't even remember but fulfilling
your requests in Mario Sunshine to remix
it to Amish Hicks sold me on joining up
wait
what who fulfilled it
I barely remember that
I know the music that you're hinting too
that that in that level where there's
like you know I fell down so often the
ones with the with the sand
[Music]
but I also I guess I kind of remember
yeah requesting that but who made the
remix anyway thank you
soon
the World Cup is happening
what welcome welcome for what Lucas
Raphael
why do I hear absolutely nothing about
it
[Music]
start yet okay okay
Austria probably did not even qualify
right
[Music]
football
a soccer right
[Music]
starts on the whole talk anniversary
well you will be watching the Hannah
talk anniversary doll
it's controversial
no tell me more later
know why I have not heard anything about
it
is
[Music]
time for you to fulfill your destiny
attention become the transom gem
I think
at the latest by now
I deserve all the trombone titles that
exist thank you thank you thank you
thank you
it's an honor for me and an honor for
all of you here I think
[Music]
the rent or Jake red four thank you soon
Jackson FB thank you for the pinky
Canadian reporting for Duty we already
love Yuki
ah thank you
one of the few
Canadian bronze that I got thank you
there's a couple more showing up in the
Super chats here nice hello Canadians
body Scotch dance thank you VP Channel
thank
you thank you
um
[Music]
I know how to say it correctly
for the pink Super Chat thank you hello
boss thank you for using my drawing as a
thumbnail my loyalty is only for you
[Music]
thank you oh look look
it's exactly the same image
we're the same
but I guess one is so
[Music]
there's the one on on the front they're
holding it with different hands
one left hand of one right hand is baby
just need some glasses oh well
I got some glasses
and now I'm like Superior because she
doesn't have the the mustache
nice yeah
[Music]
Superior dudes yeah the mustache is what
makes a difference because when you doot
in there and you get a little bit of
massage hair into it it helps to give
the sound a very special something to it
[Music]
I was playing it with the Romans
what like because I'm left-handed that
this is not how a left-handed person
plays it but we don't want to you know
complain about it
but uh is that so
how does a left-handed person play the
trombone
I don't even know which one is the left
hand
no you mixed up
crony just posted about anime NYC on
their schedule
I know nothing I know absolutely nothing
I don't know
huh what are you talking about
I was told by the management to wait
um before you know until they announced
something
it's not my fault when someone else
leaks it beforehand
what you don't know any details
anyway I'm not talking asikiwawa I
cannot be scolded for saying anything
you cannot even see my eyes so
[Music]
yeah how is it related potential
it is not that bad
[Music]
anyway continuing thank you please
continue drawing me dance
fruit Batman
Cruz donation
America's biggest donation
why did I censor differently than usual
I guess I'm really not taganasikiwawa I
am
that question there it is
it felt wrong it just felt wrong the
moment I did it
[Music]
my colleague came up with an idea for
you to grow your audience how about to
make content that parents can look for
their baby literally growing them like
lullaby ABC or baby chick Park
careful don't get tag as a kid's Channel
by the way can I have an employee number
[Music]
employee number is
one
[Music]
five
one one
[Music]
for no particular
it's a good number enjoy it
and I don't know if I'm making like
those videos specifically if any videos
of mine
are just just happen to be good for that
kind of stuff then that's cool
but
I know if I would
do it like um like aim for it
[Music]
it's four digits
I might consider it for a [\h__\h] post at
some point if I like need some short
video though I guess
yes Mia
why do you need it today
yours is one four one one
[Music]
so I'll be one four one one
what a coincidence
[Music]
it's a coincidence
be the next style hmm
[Music]
good question you didn't Exile gets
what if mirror are you not happy with
that number no in the next song get some
[Music]
thank you
it's a good number
[Music]
foreign
because that was me when I saw those
jump scares
it's taken
no way
then then you get a 9999
yeah four times
[Music]
okay anyway thank you
96 attacks
Marshall banana
type
[Music]
Maple Leaf thank you for the red super
chat
and three of the Gladiators comes on
but you look like a joke to you am I a
clown to you do I look like a clown
first
nose my big shoes tell you what I'll
pinch your nose
reach red and kick my shoes up here I'll
finish that sentence for you
yeah well that's what I felt like saying
when you guys made me play gladiators
I like the benefit of the doubt for a
while thinking like maybe there's a
reason why you say
this is for me
I did watch some videos of other
rebooters being Bamboozled into this one
it was funny seeing their reactions
makes those sense though because
obviously if anything it would be Blue
Danube
[Music]
good
I'm tired
[Music]
thank you for the red super chato here's
my paycheck Santa it's so fun listening
to your virtuoso performances of
European anthems and baseball songs
foreign
[Music]
if you had a trombone at home they would
probably try to like get inside that big
opening and just get cozy in there
I can imagine if you have a trombone
like
um upwards
of the opening pointing upwards oh they
would totally like just curl themselves
up in there I can imagine
oh so cute
yeah they would do that
[Music]
I've seen a cat make a speaker cone on
her bed oh
I've seen that actually give me the
picture
[Music]
oh your break is over well my stream
will be over soon too so you're not
missing out on anything have fun at work
[Music]
thank you
my cat makes my mouth better bad oh
thank you for the membership oh yeah
thank you spending time
[Music]
[Applause]
crayons thank you for the Pinky Okay I'm
going on a trip soon so I'll be skipping
most of your streams the coming weeks oh
no I know I'll be missing out on a lot
like whole talking through these streams
but that should be compensated by the
fun vacation experiences see you in a
few weeks weeks well if you better watch
the Vlog though and maybe if you have
some time in between you can like watch
it even during your vacation ride you
don't want to miss out on me completely
right
you
you have to watch the vaults there's a
lot of words that are worth watching in
that time I would say
and trombone name uh
Trump
oh
I don't know brain empty
well I'm too
brain empty I'm tired
maybe you guys can think of one
have a fun vacation
[Music]
Optimus Prime dinosaurs
what the [\h__\h] okay it's not so many I
can do it
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
hey boss please skip my last Super Chat
of Pinky I woke up a bit salty
if you do read it well can't say I
didn't see it coming I'd also like if
you could give a kiss to Evan's L for
being a good chicken
I like that guy thanks for the stream
and I hope you had a good day what Super
Chat are you talking about
[Music]
I don't remember a salty pink Super Chat
it's a dream one
dream one
oh don't worry about it what
to where about what the [\h__\h]
that was totally fine
yeah but Evan's out
I guess this kiss is for you I'll kiss
you through the trombone
there you go
[Music]
it's basically a kiss it just arrives
differently
for the Big Horn
[Music]
um
with mustache yeah
[Music]
thank you for the pinky got a decent
raise last week so here's your cut from
feel nice you gotta raise
congratulations you must be working
really hard I think last year you were
on a short trip on my birthdays oh that
might have been France Paris
I'm happy to be able to celebrate it
this year with you and kfb really
appreciate you guys
hello
[Music]
baby
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
it's your birthday
and you even got a rest
isn't it
[Music]
[Applause]
so I'm so sorry
that last year I couldn't be here
but this time I'm here
[Music]
but I hope you enjoyed this song
specifically just for you because
[Music]
well thank God
for the potato and happy birthday once
again hopefully that was the last one
my lips are numb
thank you so much once you're welcome
welcome
I I mean that it's already over but I
hope you spend your birthday in the best
way I hope you got some cake I even have
cake in the fridge I ate some cake for
both for birthday for breakfast
um it's a raspberry
um
raspberry creamy cake very yummy
make for breakfast yeah oh I felt like
having cake
I was looking for something good in the
supermarket
and there was cake
yes
yeah
at least
one day where I did not eat the pancakes
but I might start my pancake diet again
soon
[Music]
your name is uh yeah
yeah
sauce uh but they're not even tell them
what it's in English
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you Thai team
so generous thank you soon I appreciate
it thank you for your support you're
always here always supporting
thank you for the pinky a little for
your rust game payment no no that is
long done done we don't need any more
but thank you for thinking of me trying
to make up for the cost thank you thank
you looking for the top time
[Music]
thank you for the new Emoji too
semester almost ending oh fight oh
yeah
I'm so glad I don't need to go to school
man
perfect
[Music]
thank you for the pinky it's been two
years of membership I have been and I've
been reborn as an adorable Phoenix
chicken now I can Spit hot fire kinda
what powers do I have to look forward to
in the next two years plus can't wait to
be as powerful as you wow
love you thanks for making every day so
fun
you're so sweet sweet thank you
thank you for helping it be fun for
being part of
oh that reminds me spicy chicken but I
did get a spicy chicken boards update
today
but I wasn't 100
like impressed with it maybe I'll get
you know it improved a bit more it's not
like I suddenly have a huge Kim
Kardashian but
um but but uh I was shown an improvement
and they were like so what do you think
and I'm like I'm not sure I
don't see like a huge difference but
it's definitely better I think
um
because I asked for my box to be fixed
and everybody's voices has been heard
but I don't think you will see it
tomorrow because it's not like they did
not update the one that I can access yet
so mine is still normal normal as in
negative but
[Music]
it's too crazy big because like
you still gotta consider the fact that
okay Papa
you know
draws like Slender characters and I
think that's what it was intended to be
like
yeah I got some nice hips and all that
but insane butt size is not really
something he normally
draws I think and you know just general
anime character Aesthetics normally
don't have like huge huge jiggling butts
so that's okay
um I don't expect anything crazy but you
know in some positions it really looked
like it was like a straight line
which was so unnatural so I wanted that
to be fixed yeah
and they're working on it thankfully I
don't know when you'll see it but I got
an update today so that's cool
[Music]
you'll see it at some point
hmm
thanks for everyone reminding me of that
and thank you for the support two years
production you're the best thank you so
much Violet Apple Garden
that's still Violet ever gotten right I
haven't read your name in a while
so it feels like it could be something
else but I think it is
boss I think you are I'm most smart
reachable I know
[Music]
are they making fun of me or are they
seriously I have to recommend one game
for you the name is
[Music]
if you like it or maybe you're just
scared sorry please don't put me on the
menu I'm just a chubby chick gets scared
easily huh
you might like that
um what game is that let me Google
oh
that's different from that other potion
mixing game right there was another one
[Music]
there's a cute girl oh they have like uh
not this Disney disney-ish kind of
graphics
or Style on their faces
what's this name not necessarily Disney
what was the other one
[Music]
Pixar I guess Pixar
cute
I like this style
more than what I've been seeing a lot
um in some indie games it's like
actually I guess I could describe it as
like deviantART edgy
like Western anime kind of style you
know what I mean I've been saying that
here and there and I really don't like
it
so yeah that can honestly be a reason
for me why I don't play a game the art
style is really important for me
let me get it
[Music]
um
you know what I mean
I mean like
um
I don't know like I don't want to like
criticize the art itself but it's just
not something that I I I don't like the
Aesthetics of it that much
in a game at least like seeing it
elsewhere is cool and all but I don't
know
not my personal taste
doesn't appeal to me yeah so this is
kind of like Pixar Disney style is it
looks really cute though I like it but
it's also not my favorite style to see
in a game
[Music]
it's very it's
exaggerated I've seen also like some
Youtubers with um faces like that which
is so cool because they can do so many
expressions and expression especially
that expression where you know they move
their mouths from side to side is so
cute
so cute but also
um not not necessarily something I would
go for if I had the choice
[Music]
I'm tired but um I think I'm like done
with those super chats pretty much
[Music]
um I am watching some Christian Evans
I'll thank you
I'll end it here because I'm tired and I
need to make some I need to fry some
potatoes and warm up my burger
[\h__\h] it's already 1am
sleeping much earlier today
[Music]
at the latest like on Wednesday I Wanna
Wake up a bit earlier though because I I
set a meeting for like
early at all though but I need to fix it
a little bit before 4 AM what
falling asleep now I'm not I think the
most I can do today is 5 a.m like even
if I try to sleep earlier
um I'm tired though I'm so tired now but
once I get up away from the PC I think
I'll be a little bit more awake again
I think it's a screen that makes me
tired and the talking and energy usage
but normally when I'm like so tired on
stream
the moment I end the stream I I gain
back some energy
[Music]
actually yesterday I also could not
sleep early because besides cooking
I also still had to do some other stuff
some work related stuff I got done with
work related things at like 4 AM or so
and my stream was like nine and a half
hours long so directly after I woke up I
started and then I ended and then I
cooked and then I did some work stuff
and then I went to sleep so I literally
had no choice yesterday
um
I had to record and edit something and
then write an important email that took
a while
yeah oh I'm so tired now
[Music]
but I got the things done yesterday in
time so I'm happy
[Music]
don't push yourself I'm okay
hey I just looked I was done at 4 40
with work
damn I got really late
[Music]
mmm good so I'm gonna read the rest of
the super chat
um next time
[Music]
I think I'll try to still upload a
make a reservation for tomorrow's stream
and make a thumbnail before I go to bed
after after I eat I'll be fine
yeah
thank you guys for watching I had a lot
of fun by the way hope you guys had fun
to explain the spiral next time we're
gonna slay him for real
thank you for helping me once again
yeah it was a fun Super Chat reading too
much
[Music]
on archived but if it's hard for you to
make it then don't worry I will
rebroadcast it at a time that is better
for sea time zones specifically so just
wait for that then if it's difficult
okay
hmm
okay okay
and please don't expect too much you'll
probably be super scuffed but
yeah
it will most likely be super scuffed
[Music]
will be some body movement even if it's
delayed and laggy
[Music]
I'll probably be recalibrating every
five minutes
oh man
okay so see you tomorrow and enjoy when
we say I'll be dancing
with
[Music]
okay
nothing wrong with some stuff but it's
gonna be a lot of stuff though like
really
yeah oh well
bye bye
well if I have a nice evening or day or
morning or night
foreign
[Music]