[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
[Laughter]
no it was completely by accident i was
trying i was struggling for them i was
struggling to unmute it
no problem
i generally always feel so bad about
when i do collabs about doing my
kikiriki because it's like it's a
morning car right so it should be filled
with energy but
like i can't just be here and like
right please do please
no worries honestly i need a little like
morning cock-a-doodle-doo you know to
wake me up because right now i'm feeling
it
and i have no caffeine in the house
good morning sunshine good morning
ladies
oh my god
[Music]
yes
it was good for a minute
i just leave it like that it's a
stylistic choice it's not right they're
all right i'm gonna change it to 720p
instead of 180. oh that's better
okay
oh
um is that okay are you cool with that
i think i
i think i am what color did you use
green and it didn't mess with your
feathers so really which green is it can
you tell me like
i gotta go back to the loading screen
two seconds everybody go back to the
loading screen
it looks fine on my stream but i wanted
to look good on yours so you guys are
still here though
i'm not even gonna i'm gonna stay on the
screen but hide
our bodies maybe
hide
the body
the body hide the body we can hear you
my brain is just really slow right now
so okay wait so i feel green
three never worked for me though i'm
surprised you say that works
yeah it's just the best
[Music]
even mine doesn't even my
what's happening um
they're trying to they're trying to do
some stuff and some stuff
crawl my teeth
[Music]
oh what you know what you know what
that's okay that looks okay that looks
good i think
yeah i'm gonna stream it with
okay we can hear you all yes i know i've
got you unmuted
my sweet sweet discord channel because i
don't want to leave you guys alone what
would we do without you that's all right
you don't need to leave us alone just
bring that sentiment right into the game
with you i have to say though my
internet is also not really the bestest
you know your european internet is [\h__\h]
so uh
how does it look like girls oh i haven't
seen it looks good i feel like for now
discord likes to lie to us um
[Music]
really it's okay
everything's fine
is this worse than when cali streamed it
we're not even moving over yeah you you
guys are not moving on my side now by
the way
yeah ellie are
[Music]
you have to have their window open
at all times see here this is the stuff
that we can't actually check before the
stream for if it happens literally
during this break i don't worry about it
it's so scary
and then we started streaming yeah they
don't
don't move for me when i stream to them
oh
no that's just black to me
[Music]
uh oh also cali stopped moving for me
too oh
[Music]
well we found our ghosts
i finally
[Music]
what did you do
sorry are we okay now guys uh well we're
gonna have to work with one fine okay
the final game
i think it was better when charlie named
it because i
apparently like it's [\h__\h] and i also
get silly to move at you
okay we'll try to try kelly one more
time
leave it to me i got this boys
one
[Music]
because i want to go get some
i don't can we stroll for the rest of
this stream please
no
it's time for spooky it's almost
halloween
anyways thanks for coming to our stream
and now we end it just
kidding just kidding we're gonna play
the game now oh no can you do me one
favor
um yes
can you end your screen once and open it
again
yes
[Music]
okay okay
okay is everyone ready to see the 144p
okay
[Music]
anytime anything you need this is a nice
year
what are we going to do here here what
yeah i have an ear right in my face you
have an ear i don't know whose it is
though who's in here oh it might be very
high
hello hi oh baby
oh here wanna see it again
check out these moves i can do
what you got my move
i think the scariest out of all of us
today is bae
like the the one that who's the most
scared i don't like ghosts i don't deal
with ghosts okay they're ghosts they're
in another dimension
i like to live
uh the the rat life in this dimension
okay it's scary
can you tell me how you're dealing with
scary games that this thing that you
told me before the stream
oh obs
tell him i don't look at the game screen
when i play scary games i play the game
by looking at the small obs screen
that's kind of smart though
when it gets real scary in resident evil
in the basement
sometimes i've been known to look at obs
good job we should do we only have two
jobs really surprised that i'm not the
the biggest chicken in the room and it's
bae actually
hey i can play other horror games kind
of not really it's just paranormal is
this fast it's just paranormal stuff
that i can't handle
oh i see it yeah
[Music]
yeah we're all not very good at it but
we're going to try our best here are our
options
yo
62.
i'll go first hello my name is serious
fauna i am the hollow council's keeper
of nature
and i am extremely good at all horror
games
and i'm going to find all the ghosts
thank you very much
wow confidence confidence would like to
inspire me thank you
anything
i can't i can't get no
[Laughter]
oh okay okay
um what's up
bells everybody guys representing
chaos room council what's up hope you're
doing good um
we we stolen i'm gonna stall for as long
as i can okay uh we're gonna catch no
ghost today um
i don't need to stall i'm scared okay
well why did you invite why did you
invite us to play this game though
because i know you guys liked the game
from cali signed no bae invited me to
play uh phasmo and then you and i
said who would want to play and i said
kiara
okay that's the team then
i know it's because you like the game
and florida likes the game and i was
like this could be what do you mean with
you with the first you who did you mean
callie yeah
i've played it a couple times but i
think it's fun i've played it a couple
times in the past it's it's
sacrifice myself is okay
good hallows hallows week hallows weenie
game yeah wait so you're saying right
now you sacrifice yourself so we can use
you today as a sacrifice for the ghosts
like a testing object whenever we need
to you know see if the ghost is going to
attack we're just going to leave you in
the room and we stay in the trees in the
room
that's okay with you right
[Music]
you
that's how i'm gonna be this week when i
play [\h__\h] outlast
right that's a fun one
that's a step up from phantom phobia
you'll have a blast so
so not looking forward to it it's the
worst thing that's happening to me this
whole year
you want to take it away
of course um hello my name is takanashi
kiana from whole life english and i have
set the game's voice recognition to
german on my side so i will be talking
to the ghost and yelling at the ghost in
german today thank you very much
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
all right
i love that oh man
[Music]
last and also least my name is moore
classy i'm the first grouper it's okay
you know it's all right you can just let
it happen i'm the first apprentice of
the grim reaper himself which means
i'm also
uh when it comes to dealing with ghosts
really bad because usually it's my job
to make humans into ghosts uh when it
comes to dealing with the ghosts
um
it's not good and i'm ready to face i'm
ready to live up to my family name and
face full life consequences i'm excited
let's go my specialty in this situation
when it comes to being part of the the
scooby-doo crew
um
is taking a bunch of items into the
house that i don't know how to use and
have no reason for using and then
leaving them there so uh let's see how
that helps us out in the game no don't
don't leave everything that we're all
broke as hell in the game you gotta put
it back into the trackline there's
matches you can even have enough money
to buy flashlights for everything i have
we have one flashlight i can i can buy a
little bit i don't know we already have
one though um how many do we have money
do we need three four flashlights one
costs thirty dollars
pretty expensive let me buy something i
have 74 bucks okay
we can hit the dollar store
i'll get us a flashlight i got some
stuff
i got some stuff here you go
and uh
okay we got we got all flashlights now
we got four
we got a firmware reader okay i got what
mama i need do you have a ghost writing
book
yes it's in there yes that's great oh
okay can we look at this
spirit box a uv light video camera one
of the six photo camera camera one of
the free
emf reader do we need to buy money i'm
one dollar short for a thermometer guys
but we really didn't know probably we
already have one
excellent
we great
another video camera or something
a crucifix perhaps
a glow stick why do we need a glow stick
is there a party here
ghost writing book um it doesn't look
like we have a ghost writing book it's a
zero is anyone oh wait we can buy us why
did i buy four week flashlights when i
could just buy one strong flash
flashlight what what yeah i know right
[Music]
oh wait i have oh i have some stuff here
oh i didn't realize what the hell oh
wait what this is all my stuff yeah oh
oh my god wait oh what does that have
bring it down no no i have nothing uh
i'm gonna add salt two times that's all
i like
i'm gonna add everything
salt is always great oh yeah add
everything you've got i'm contributing
yes
why
because now
all right well this is fine the
equipment list is looking good so let's
just go with it um
all right ladies you're the jobs that we
have
we've got edgefield street house allow
me to narrate
recommended team to a two-story
six-bedroom house with a basement we
have recently received information about
a possible haunting at this location get
there as soon as you can and gather
evidence for the ghost removal team
we'll have more intel when you arrive
location is small recommended items
thermometer and this difficulty is
amateur yeah let's start with amateur
something easy
[Music]
you'll be fine don't worry about it
yes oh that's a great oops sorry sorry
that's okay
[Music]
i feel like i had something
to say oh by the way guys when we're
talking to the ghosts and you're
listening to our stream like on our side
um hello
um
and we start the game
hold on okay when we were trying to talk
to the ghost you will hear us speak
double because we have to input our
voice into the game we're not actually
using bush to talk stay in the dark
yes yes use the trucks i'm not alone why
am i alone
i'm a
blind wait wait wait wait
my game went full screen for a second i
don't like hold on no let me already see
your name
you're playing before
ah
it says voting game 90
that's how it was for me for a while and
it was a long time until it finally why
is base and the oh just kidding
everyone's sanity is kind of fluctuating
he has been angry with me i kicked it
out of my
my closet that i stream from and amazing
my pc has now been
received after newfound lighthouse road
here we go ah all right
[Music]
accordingly before starting the
investigation margaret anderson this
ghost seems to respond to everyone you
should be able to use its name to anger
it and get some paranormal activity i
don't like this this game is making my
game full screen when i don't give it
permission to what
[Music]
you're going down is that bleach can we
bleach the ghosts
capture them the ghosts
again there you go
all right ladies so let's maybe split
this up and someone should use the
camera somebody you should use the pmf
reader someone should use the salt
uh video camera and salt um
how do you use things i don't know what
the controls are someone tell me
what are the controls oh good question e
for picking up items
oh gotcha
you can scroll in between those items i
think like free items is maximum okay
where's the thermometer i want this
thermometer um i actually can't pick up
anything dang it did i change my buttons
go drink some salt milk thermometer i
want the emf reader
oh i have the emf reader hold on dang it
here i want to be useful how do i how do
i pick up anything i don't put it down
just looked at the obvious screen and i
fought the how do i put things down
oh this is for me this is my personal
setting oh i should probably ah are we
going someone open the door okay let's
go
hold on i'm looking at my settings
[Music]
pick up the drop item is uh there's
someone the key is in the in the
[Music]
oh thank you i appreciate it we're good
we're lucky again wait what was that the
emf
oh no this is the thermometer wow i'm
stupid there we go it's okay
wait what was the name of the ghost wait
alphago margaret margaret anderson
margaret margaret anderson
i saw
anything
where am i
i couldn't oh good we just got to figure
out what room she's oh that is very
creepy i need a picture
hello let's turn the light on from the
beginning maybe i don't have a person i
don't have a flashlight can you think
wait there wasn't a flashlight for you
there should be
margaret anderson
are you okay
my double boy spook you yes yeah
[Music]
no could you just stay in your house
please
okay 19 degrees
there's a dirty dirty ass woman here
living here yeah 19 degrees i'll say
that about her clean up your apartment
come on
upstairs oh she must be upstairs then
yeah the emf reader
where is everybody bathroom
that's a beautiful
it's getting cold
oh wait whoa
oh my nose it's downstairs
it's downstairs it's downstairs
what is there it's like a
hold on like right here it's 14 degrees
right here
ah let me see okay
maybe she here
do you see like um like cold
like fumes and stuff that's not cold
enough oh okay
yeah it might not be cold enough okay
okay okay sorry
gotta check every room though babe
because very clearly
sorry the plant looked like the hand i'm
sorry oh my god
how about kitchen kitchen margarita
give us the sign
20 degrees not
with the here room
give us the sign
where's this door oh is this the stuff
backyard i can't open it i don't know
okay um
oh i found a bathroom
where i felt bad oh
i heard a basement guys we have a
basement
we can open it oh just kidding yeah we
can't being very needy today so i might
have to go afk from lunchtime
oh okay
this door's locked have you guys been
upstairs yet no yeah we went up there
but we didn't go in every room
hey come with me let's go check out
every room i have the emf readers so we
should work together
i heard a sound
i don't know i heard it i heard a phone
uh vibrating phone vibrate where this is
me
[Music]
oh children's room oh 13 no okay no give
us give us the sign
okay feel like i heard the breathing in
my ear
oh it's okay it was great
no not this room
even in my ear
i mean not liking
are we all just like really
really bad horror game players might be
give us give us a sign
hello
great placement
[Music]
what's here
this is a big house
[Music]
i'm just gonna put salt everywhere you
always gotta put salt everywhere
yeah very important but here's a room we
haven't been in was someone breathing
like
yeah yeah right i heard that through the
foot wait just then that was me reading
out creepy oh was that you
i'm so scared
maybe in here
bae is the real ghost
and
six degrees
degrees where
where
they're often in the basement where was
that i wanted to click the basement i
wish i had a light on my shoulder
instead of
this teeny tiny like
it's so sweet where did it go to six
degrees the light went out
oh am i out of salt
guys the light went out i'm going oh no
oh
i don't know
it's suddenly very dark okay
the ghost was a little bit active it
seems yes yes i i see it
i'm not getting any emf activities
it must not be a ghost that responds to
emf
you gotta you gotta call it name out
more
[Music]
that's the reason why the
hey
there's nothing going on right now in
the activities
there's no activity
yeah
what is this thing i have in my hand by
the way
emf 4 ladies
i'm going in i gotta you know make
myself stronger for outlast yeah good
idea should we put a camera upstairs
there we go
i got a cross
dots projected
[Music]
guys at the entrance why is it so cold
here we go the doors open
does that mean it's in the what
okay
ooh that's cool
the ghost was blocked
okay margaret anderson
it was okay i think it's at the door
[Music]
it's
for maximum activity
i'ma stand at the door so i can just
back out
someone playing with something a ghost
that's not that sound
oh
margaret anderson [\h__\h] you okay it's
definitely in this room
anderson fish
[Music]
[Laughter]
cheese margaret and okay it's definitely
this front room
margaret anderson come questions
[Music]
i don't even want to know what she's
saying happiness
enough
nothing to do can we set up a camera in
the mark margaret anderson i set up a
camera video camera and uh um
in the entrance room bloody mary bloody
mary
well
oh there is activity i'm running away
yeah something's happening we just gotta
quit being little cowards and gotta get
deeper into the house
are you sure did you see the ghost no
but it went down to three degrees
oh okay well then maybe it's a room
close by
yeah
well it was useful here what is that
you can't really see anything what
margaret anderson is this really the
best place is this really favorite box
is this really what's the best place to
play video camera
margaret anderson [\h__\h]
oh
she didn't like that there are noises
over there
yeah i get her
i have no coward i like
swearing in german
margaret anderson combatants
margaret anderson
oh you scared the [\h__\h] out of me my dude
is that you
it's it's the ghost oh
yeah
you can't get me if i'm outside i
marge
marge margaret
is that something good
oh it's four four degrees
oh my god this is 110
is that is that good i don't know that's
good i saw prince in the garage oh is
that is that so
princess
people give us a sign
please no i'm so scared
no we're fine babe don't worry about it
it's serrated this ghost is a little
coward
i'm gonna go get me something did you
hear that
what do the numbers mean yeah you suck
i'm gonna go get a basement something
yeah oh yeah basement oh yeah basement
you can't open it for some reason i
don't want to go into the basement that
must be the ghost
can we get a camera or something
no wait the ghost is hunting probably oh
guys the door closed the the ghost is
totally hunting
i'll be watching
the door closed
i'm dead
it was me
goodbye
oh
is someone dead
i'm dead wait follow me died
i've died really congratulations i
didn't see anything is the activity over
am i safe
um activity i couldn't tell did two
people die
i heard the door
are you
stop it
i can't open the door you're scaring me
which door are you trying to get out of
here yeah trying to get down okay there
you go
i open the door
you open the door open the door is dead
[Music]
oh my god our sanity is all very low
except for base which means we got to
send bae in again
[Music]
i was uh really not doing good in there
what did you guys see on the camera did
you catch anything no because the camera
wasn't positioned correctly we got to
move the camera light i positioned it
perfectly are you telling your stamp i
didn't position the camera correctly yes
i was saying that this was yes
wait where where did you put the camera
wait what where where on the on the
little table on the entrance on the
little table
huh
okay little on the little table on the
entrance what i can't see right at the
door on the right side
there's weird stuff on the car
oh wait do you have the um the other we
need the other flesh like you know the
purple flashlight that you can look for
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
you have it okay where do you need it
the door closed again oh
oh god that's bad
um the door is locked um
guys i'm not doing this on purpose
yara i took the headphones down i'm not
listening
all right okay i'm back i'm i mean i'm
dead but i'm back no well you can pick
up my items they're all at the door i
gotta i got a photo camera and why
weren't you killed
because i am okay to kill yeah
also uh here uh who is that woman
character
hello is it that bae hello no is that
fauna
oh you did it i don't know
even that's a ghost you got a torch
we can see each other
oh can you tell us
hey it's you and me now
you know you do you want to know where
the camera is the video camera it's uh
yeah thank you stuff away
baby baby stay where you are look to the
right look to the right
that's where it is the video camera
oh i saw the green one oh yeah yeah
let's put it
why don't you carry a picture with you
uh fauna is that you are you doxing it's
it's someone with that
how do you put the camera pad
who is that
okay door's locked oh boy
oh god
[Music]
we are really not doing great
i knew it i knew the ghost is definitely
around this area but
i don't know
i guess the main all right it's up to
you now
um
your
freezing did you guys find freezing
temperatures
no
all right so maybe no freezing
temperatures
i'm not
we gotta see if there's ghost writing
okay
if you go into the van
you can do it actually
[Music]
oh my god
[Applause]
what is happening here guys i don't i
literally don't know what's happening
oh i couldn't tell who was a human and
who was um all right well
let's try a different job guys
it was pretty bad
look at the table we've lost all our
stuff
recommended team size one how about that
guys a small three bedroom single floor
house the basement we've recently
received information about a possible
[Music]
now i want a strong flashlight for money
yeah insurance for dying yeah yeah i
didn't have insurance
oh that's
dead
you always regret it later on that you
didn't get insurance
head mounted camera
should also be good
i'm gonna add a tripod
a little card level eight so we can put
the video camera on it nice idea
what was that green dotty thing that we
plant that i placed in the hallway when
candles are yeah what was that motion
sensor right
really
it doesn't tell us anything
no how how do you
should we bring candles again yeah i
want to see if i can light up some rooms
next time
does someone have three channels so
otherwise i'll buy some
i bought two don't worry enjoy we have a
lighter already
salt never have you can never have too
much salt but i think we have plenty
ink uh do we need a thermometer
always good to have just to check
yeah let me buy one unless someone has
one
i'll go buy
i'll ed you're right
bangle wood street house now we're fully
equipped again and we're probably going
to lose it all again well we can we can
definitely do this i haven't really
okay chad we need your help at least i
need your help come on
we can do it we can do it
the green one it was the dots and it
blinks some of those crosses through it
i saw that happening actually i saw the
green dots like dim a little bit
oh and like yeah and change before i
died
you can see the ghost in it through a
video camera ah
dot's projector is the green thing okay
so it should always be like combined
with a video camera a dodge projector oh
okay well uh bait i know you're feeling
not ready but you should push ready in
the game
all right i'm gonna oh that's me i'm
supposed to start there we go
those have been known to target those
who stay in the lights too long oh no
okay we gotta move into the darkness
we're just
taking your time again that's okay
no worries we got all of that
oh all right here's what we got nurses
only respond when people are alone
that's fun
james moore james moore is that the name
of some famous person
it sounds like a famous person
james moore this ghost also seems to
only respond to people who are alone you
know you heard that bae
you gotta be alone
where's the head cat where's the
head-mounted camera
i think bae is like mentally brain-dead
did i not put all my items in the game
bait did you lose your voice
all right
hey thanks
you're okay you heard me hey okay
good
he's so quiet like a mouse
anyone know where a lighter is yeah
uh lighter light or lighter yeah i could
have sworn we had a lighter lasting
one in there
no it's not this is really weird
i saw it in the no wait no i didn't see
it in the list actually never mind it
was there last time
yeah but i bought new things oh yes
wait but then that means we can't do
this so we can't do [\h__\h] with the
candles
i have the ghost riding book with me and
a torch and that's all i got all right i
got fingerprints
we definitely brought one
i brought one i have an ems reader in my
hand okay
hey i got the momentum
james moore
a bone
[Music]
okay i just have a regular old camera i
would like it to be in the kitchen that
would be nice
okay okay let's go in here
mossy mars
let's set the subway down james
i took a photo of the bone
thank you
[Music]
oh give us a sign
i always wanted someone to exchange
laundry smooth
a little pen pal
yeah
that sounds kind of cute actually
wait i found the ochi ocha
board
i found the board where is it what
uh i have it in my hand
oh ooh is it upstairs i heard something
how do we use this are the doors locked
i heard something now the door oh i
heard something
i don't want to hear anything i heard
these
this is cool is that a rare item i heard
something wait in one of these rooms
don't use it
i'm sad painting
give us a hold on just give us the stuff
oh luigi oh my god
i want to leave right now
get the bone well they gave me the sign
i wanted
the luigi board
i have the words you put but i guess we
can only use it inside oh okay
did you have
a sign
yeah the lights flickered in the kitchen
oh
there's i don't know
there's not running water
i'm
oh yeah temperature just went down a
little bit
oh
wait give us
[Music]
it's it's it's not cold though no it's
not
okay drop it do we have the
emf reader thing
how do i actually i'll take a picture of
this yeah
okay i'm not getting any signs hold up
let me take a picture of the sink i'm
coming
oh
okay good
we can't even clear amateur stuff wait
where's my old job board i think it's
safe to say no emf reading someone stole
my old job board did someone take my
orange out board how about that
how do you get the oh i got the bone
it's gone
yeah cause i picked up the bone you get
money apparently
is this you my dude
maybe it's the basement
no
no it's like you're a pizza delivery
person only like reply to the old stuff
board like in the correct room guys or
someone comments give us a sign
i'm running away all right guys
wait
where are you james moore
[\h__\h] you
i don't think james mole would like that
bloody mary bloody mary bloody mary
bloody mary
ah
fauna can you come to the bathroom with
me
uh
james moore how old are you
are you jamie
where are you
come here everybody come here he's in
the bathroom he's in the toilet he's in
the toilet how do you know
it went down to nine degrees it's good
enough
james more more where there's a little
pistol
in the bathroom oh
james
bistro oh my god are you okay well i can
fix this james james
what should i ask him kim are you okay
i'm i'm using the original board the
question thingy
board can you go to the blog
i want to set up a camera in the toilet
is that james is that violent i said yes
i can say this
to you who has the video camera
um me i do oh oh wait the door
you guys are in trouble oh the door yeah
we are
oh oh oh
i got me down
he got me
as i ran i ran right into the
wait ghost
really went from there turned my head
like wow
you asked him a really personal question
i guess i shouldn't move right
there's there
um it's safe now it's safe now
all right i'll be lookout for you guys
where did you die someone come back
come back in you will no i'm trying to
get them can someone get the tripod i
want to set up i want to set up the
camera it's in the box
you can pick up the camera where i died
which is where are you vol pistol where
are you oh
whoa
by the way the tripod the tripod is in
the truck you guys oh
[Music]
hold on a second um i'm pressing i'm
gonna do something terrible i wanna be
great should i move it won't come in
here it only responds when it's alone
right outside can you give us something
zero
okay i heard it i heard it said
something i heard it i heard i heard it
isn't it hunting
no the door's still open you're in the
clear
come on get out of here
all right
[Applause]
did you die there's two
oh no fana what are we gonna do i have
zero sanity
um the sanity pills are necessary all
the stuff though at the door
you should probably grab it go to the
van and then we just leave and make a
guess
oh open the door
wait i'll try to open it for you
it's hunting again
oh no oh i see it is that the door it's
at the door
why does this happen every time
this is like
it went into the kitchen
before oh i see it it went into the
kitchen be careful
right i'm the only one left alive i'm
just gonna pick up some items and put it
in the truck who is that yeah yeah
oh my god we got oh look it's my dead
body my spirit box
oh yeah oh the spirit box
yeah
am i supposed to be able to see the
other ghosts
why do i see so
who are you what about fingerprints
ghost orb do we get freezing
temperatures
what's happening
hey
temperature in your zombae
uh it was 11 point something
you guys good is everyone dead babe that
is the demon crouching oh it is
the demon's got the flashlight i mean
that's scary
this is the demon crouching
all it is
why does that have a flashlight why does
that have a flashlight
wait oh and this is me
is someone is any ghost in the truck
right now can we can he tell me like
what's like i'll go into the i'll go
into the truck
and go into the truck it's not like the
activity is low it's not it's basically
non-existent right now oh no that's the
dead body oh that's that's not the ghost
i thought that was the ghost oh
this is it that's funny's body oh
you can't save items wait what you don't
you don't have to pick him up you lose
everything
really
every single time you go that doesn't
seem right then we really should get a
right guess here and not keep on losing
our money
all right guys
what do we know about him no emf level
five i was everywhere up in that [\h__\h]
with the emf
reader and i didn't get level five so
none of that
but there was this i put the book
somewhere does anyone know where i put
the book uh
if we get ghost writing
let me just try to find
if
the book again
if the book isn't written in then it's
only two it can only be
one of two
phantom and yoga stella you put it in
the basement oh dear let's see if i can
make it how about oh yeah look out
are you heroes kelly is this you i can't
tell who's who
i'm now entering
fast oh god oh god okay we got you no
worries we got you we got you yes wait
but before we went let's just uh
i'm just wait which one are you guys
going for i want to choose something
before i go in so that i at least have
something oh who is that someone's by
the door
i'm in the door put them outside of it
no no no no no okay
oh no i'm in the basement someone is
hunting oh did someone die
here you died
no no no someone died
but i'm gonna go with um
wait what what what did i do let me read
what did support the guys
dead buddy all right okay guys
flickering lights
mere yokai spirits spirits are very
common ghosts they're for powerful
passives only attacking when they need
to they defend their place of death to
the upmost degree killing anyone will
allow which is very contemporary stopped
by pretty smashing oh okay wait wait
wait it sounds like it could be it wait
i can check the video guys
i can check the book
i mean i did speak with the old
jailboard a lot but he never answered
something
so it's not a phantom where did you put
the book where is the book
uh and oh right i guess the ghost can go
look too huh yeah i can find the
basement in the basement i put the book
like pretty close to the like it's it's
like i don't have a phone on the other
side of the room other side of the room
on the bottom on the ground mm-hmm the
ground i can't see anything on the
ground
it's so dark you might not be able to
see it
you guys can't see the book anytime you
can see
journal oh
i didn't even know this was a thing okay
oh well
on the other
side
right crouching you just can't see the
writing nice try though okay
uh
right i wanna see
one of the most dangerous ghosts
oh there's nothing in the book
there's nothing in the book oh
yeah but apparently ghosts can't see it
anyway even if like you go so dead dead
players can't see it oh that's annoying
um
i'm just gonna go with
a spirit because this is the most common
and we're playing an amateur game i
don't know no but it was increasing
temperatures
but there was freezing pampers really
there or was it just low freezing is
below zero oh no there was no freezing
temperatures
okay um
there's no emf right
i don't think it was the spirit
no emf okay
if there's no emf level five it's not a
spirit
oh
we've got spirit box though
just because
phantom phantom
[Music]
okay well i think maybe a yo guy
i'll choose phantom just to be
contrarian okay okay
we all get people common ghosts that are
attracted to human voices they can
usually be found haunting family home
strengths talking here yokai will anger
at increasing the chances of an attack
oh
yeah yeah it is yeah okay
yeah let's try it
let's try that
it doesn't say emf level 5 is one of the
evidences but i crossed it off for the i
crossed it all
yeah me too but it comes up doesn't it
um well let's let's try i don't think so
i think it's just spirit boxes
all other things
it look like like this
because i didn't see
it i'm not gonna lie guys
my hands starting to turn numb
are you okay
um
i like how
this ghost is called huntu
because i'm like hunting
put your guess in the book i did
did i know it uh
press j okay
i did
and then what do i do
then you click on uh you could go to
evidence go to the evidence tab i did i
put yokai okay okay good then you're
fine please okay all right
look at our super professional van and
we all just suck i love it
oh it's indonesian
unlucky whenever i played before the
ghosts were never so violent
it was a mirror it was so something else
so we messed up some evidence but it's
fine
some photos at least we got some more
money i took the photos
i took the photos
oh
see i don't know there's something kind
of good
all right we're really horrible at this
one
let's do one more game if that's okay
with you guys you have to say last
redemption
i'm gonna get a ghost writing book
because we have nothing anymore
yeah you can watch our activities oh i
got my items i'm gonna add a thermometer
and a tripod that's all i got i'm buying
a strong flashlight
that's so rude okay um
i'm gonna buy i don't know what i'm
gonna buy
what do we buy um
i bought a ton of stuff
oh
uh a light a lighter okay now we have a
lighter
on the candle for the camera
so strong i would love one more candle
if possible guys if i can buy
i got my
good stuff now let's see what jobs we
have do we have how about we do the farm
house because asylum in prison is going
to be no way
the farmers isn't that pretty pink uh
size recommended size is two it's a
two-story three-bedroom farmhouse we can
do either that or the prison recommended
size three and an island recommended
size four
listen can you like refresh that to give
us something smaller yeah no
unfortunately it doesn't it doesn't work
[Music]
i think we'll be fine farmhouse then
yeah let's do it no it's gone
nice
i'm ready wait we only have one out of
four flashlights and one should we have
more i'll buy more yeah yeah i bought a
strong one i buy one you buy one okay
i cannot wait for you what
i can afford exactly one and then
oh my god i was in someone
all right someone just stay with
someone who has a flashlight you can
stick with me or you're gonna
have
now we should have four yeah
and one strong one
okay actually then wait wait wait wait
wait then let me can i
how do i get rid of one damn it
because we don't need five flashlights
because
oh well let's just leave one in the
truck go go
let's go
we can do this guys i know we can
let's just believe it we believe in each
other and we just got to test out
everything okay
and the executives
[Music]
seems to respond to everyone you should
be able to use its name to anger against
some okay we don't have to be alone for
this ghost okay okay
smudge stick so i didn't bring any
smudge sticks at all
[Music]
we have smudge sticks right
oh do we i don't know
um
i've got the camera okay two drivers how
did that happen
yeah i don't know and candle and lighter
actually i'll start off taking candles
and then i'll leave the ghost writing
book here for now if somebody else wants
to use ghost writing book i'm going to
light up some candles in the house
oh yeah i i'm bringing the ghost writing
book cool
okay
and the video camera uh can anyone
bring the tripod
anyone got some free hands um i think
can't wait otherwise i'll leave the book
behind someone someone hit the camera
i'm going i'll get the tripod
oh okay uh well i uh i put the book
right that makes no sense then i'll put
the book down you take the tripod and i
take the camera okay
[Music]
yeah this map is definitely scarier oh
my god that which is the strong
flashlight is it the black one or the
gray one uh the black one
what's his name again george something
georgie
robinson george robinson
i think it's the one that you put on
your shoulder there we go all right
we're good we got a double
flashlight no i put the weak one away
okay
jordy
my dude is winded after two seconds
robinson
wanna set up robinson
13 degrees
16 degrees don't cool
where are the lights
whoa
put it down
that's scary
i'm not down
if you find something sauce tell me i
want to take a photo of it yeah
there's the candle one candle
i'll go get another one oh god i'm just
gonna follow you
i'll check the activity
okay
are you safe
it's still relatively i was i was
shocked by bae
and nothing's really going on right now
i can't tell who is who
[Music]
no not even i'm scared and that means
something no i don't like being in the
dark without being able to see and i
don't like ghosts
at least let me see
another candle
put one upstairs just a kid jump scares
doesn't hurt nobody it hurts the soul
okay it's a bit colder upstairs
ooh okay nothing suspicious yet
yeah i have no emf yet
okay we're not playing a magazine i'm
not looking for anything i left the
tripod hold on
why is the tripod there did i leave that
there
apparently you did until you placed it
yeah breaker's in a really easy to find
spot
hello uh
with this door
i can't pick it up why can't i pick it
up
bedroom nice hat oh do i have to be
holding it the whole time oh i see
i understand
uh george morrison where are you we'll
be still
george morrison where'd you guys go
george morrison give us a sign where'd
you guys go
hello from the bedroom players looks
like it's not george morrison vol pistol
[Music]
george morrison give us a sign
it's okay don't worry scary ghost noises
oh but i don't know um i saw something
flickered downstairs guys
interesting oh maybe my dude was giving
us a sign
how nice of him to help us
progress in the game attic i'm gonna go
to the attic
dad is very brave of you
yeah i probably should have put a candle
up here
give us a sign
why would i see a fingerprints
[Music]
oh no that's me yeah i hear that too
what the hell that was me oh that's you
that was me bae what is that ghost
okay who turned the light off everybody
who just turned me in probably were all
lights
if you
you need the
the purple flashlight
yeah oh
okay okay
give us give us a sign
it was that room
it was that room guys found the room
yeah you're you're good at finding the
rooms which room it was that one which
floor you're right here right here yeah
which floor the second floor
okay there's a bone on the floor
[Music]
wait the second floor is bowling
second floor bathroom
okay where's this bathroom
here
nice got it thank you
okay tripod wait wait wait wait
put the tripod down where you think it
is to the ghost i left the tripod at the
door because i didn't have any hands
wait
i got the breaker
there it is at the end
pick up the bone pick up the bone
you gotta grab that bad boy get that
money
i can't i got four hands man
all right i'm in the kitchen
i uh
is it really up here cause i'm not
getting anything yeah how
[Music]
give us a sign
i'm gonna go grab
can someone put the camera on top of the
tripod here maybe in the hallway when he
yes comes out maybe
we have no ghost writing books so let me
grab this
oh wait i could take it never mind i got
the balloon
uh wait wait wait wait where did you put
the tripod it's right by the stairs
stairs
on the second floor
uh on the second floor stairs down to
the first floor
okay
god it's so dark
i don't see [\h__\h]
yeah i thought i turned on the lights
there we go
i turned the light on oh scandal is out
is it is it filming do you see it hold
on let me check are you in the truck i'm
going to go to the truck and check
give us a sign
chad says they went to emf 3 but
my candle's out i did not see it or hear
it
where
um all right fu
there is
okay the camera's on camera's on
camera's on someone's walk right in
front of the camera
oh what
someone is right in front of the camera
it's me oh
okay
okay okay okay okay okay
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
uh give us a sign
what do we do with this cow we need a
light or when we gonna switch to
um all of the candles i lit up are blown
out um oh
what does that mean should we take a
picture of that does that mean something
because he did something
maybe i mean i probably should just be
whispering
there's no activity at the moment
you know we haven't found the right room
right now wait i swear it was the
bathroom do you want the thermometer
here
yes please well let's maybe go back
upstairs then
okay i'm coming
candles do go out on their own
eventually
maybe we should pull candle upstairs did
you put one upstairs too uh-huh i
brought one with me upstairs
right wait do you have the lighter
oh
yeah i do
yeah i'd like this one
here where
okay right next to the book
yeah
there we go
[Music]
give us a sign
i don't know if george is going to laugh
yeah we gotta talk more to the ghost i
don't think it's reacting to me at all i
think the game doesn't pick up my voice
but okay well i'm gonna go downstairs
and check on your sanity and just look
at the camera because is this is
speeding out of here give us a sign hold
up
let me have a look
all right well
that's right that's what bae said
okay okay
put the video camera down in the ghost
oh yeah there's a little bit of activity
but everybody seems okay hold up
i see give us something
except that stuff here
wait was it the other bathroom is this
the same bathroom no
bathrooms
one under the
it was one near the jordan morrison
doors closed and i got i didn't like i
got scared give us a sign
george james morrison is not an orb
george morrison
is that an orb it's an orb is that an
orb george morrison scheissen find a
ghost orb
george morrison
we're experts no okay no
wait george morrison victory
[Music]
which one is knight
oh george george robinson sorry george
robinson we keep getting the [\h__\h]
names wrong uh the name is george
robinson everybody
george robbie george robinson sorry give
us a second dude
george robinson thank you george
robinson
where's dad give us a sign
he's shy
keep on mixing up those names yeah
oh here
oh bang
chicken yes what's up here um let's i'm
gonna go see if i can
going on there it goes you have nice
sanity yeah no i want to try to say move
the camera into like the bathroom maybe
george anderson this is fine wait forna
found it
what foreign
from the cold temperatures oh okay
oh that's the end for me
oh no
look at my lights
oh i think i'm dead oh oh oh flickering
lights okay
freaking flickering lights flickering
indeed it is flickering flickering
flickering it is uh hunting is that what
it is
[Music]
wait okay so we got do we get freezing
temperatures that's not true
um well i still can't manage to get any
ghost writing so i think it's okay to
rule that out okay no freaking morning
temperatures no freezing temperatures no
freezing temperatures we're just cold
but not free what was the emf emf
just three
okay come on all of these
are useless
no five i mean we have five nard down to
three it's either a phantom banshee or a
yokai
like how do we do we have a spirit box
yeah ghost what do we actually have
ghost orb and something else um i don't
know if there's a ghost or i couldn't
tell
i don't think that where am i didn't
someone say we have a ghost orb i
thought i saw an orb was there an orb
i can't turn on the light
why
oh it's walking around upstairs
it's in the attic ew you creepy
[Music]
that's bad i can't find my flashlight
anymore okay and that's not good
creepy man holding a hatchet
please i just want to get
yeah
i don't know how to turn off the
flashlight lowell
uh
ttt let me open the door i can't
come
oh i see the light
i see the light
come on come here
[Music]
okay all right so let's regroup and
figure out what we know okay you know
there's
ghost orbs apparently yeah what
oh maybe
okay
there's definitely no ghost writing okay
because i was everywhere up in that
[\h__\h] saying that dude's name he didn't
he and comedian do nothing okay so no
ghost writing freezing
temperature god damn it i'm going in
this closest oh okay i'm gonna die
are you kidding me oh yeah
yeah
[Music]
you can try to run or hide
can we see it from the top whoa oh we
see you in the window you see you in the
window
you're doing great he's gonna kill me oh
he's coming he's coming for you
are you taking pictures from the outside
are you taking pictures of kiara getting
hunted
i can't believe it okay okay okay okay
okay
oh
i don't know if they can count as
anything but they're funky whoa did they
have the ghost
on the wall we can have fingerprints
guys apparently
everything that i don't see for me it's
apparently a banshee if we really saw
ghost orbs
whoa interesting
but there's one
did it stop after you took the photos
because
apparently don't wait
don't phantoms disappear after you take
a photo or something wait wait wait wait
yeah taking a photo of the phantom will
make her temporarily disappear yeah it
was about to hunt me now
and that's why it was into the air and
it disappeared
yeah oh
that was smart smart choice
thank you
wait so it was a phantom so it was a
fantastic i'm not sure if it actually
disappeared because i saw it in the
kitchen
oh i don't know it like didn't go into
the room where you were in it went into
the kitchen no but it was at the door
right
um
no it was it went down the stairs and
then went into the kitchen
yeah no it has to be a phantom because
there weren't any ghost storms
there were no there were no ghost storms
i thought you saw a ghost warp i think
that was a flashlight
right oh okay i think i saw a flashlight
just uh one day i'll leave you
a phantom
you can cross out stuff in the journal
if you click it more times
yeah i did i did i did so we have
phantom it's a phantom i'm not how you
idiot you need to uh oh
i'm gonna die
yeah
go back inside
i just wanted to put down some salt i
was feeling salty
yeah come and get me behind this salt
idiot ha ha
where are you
i don't want to know i'm not going one
day
i'll leave you
a phantom dead
oh he's still alive
[Music]
is that you kelly no that's me that's me
okay now kelly kelly
no it's finished
okay yeah it's my little salt garden oh
my oh
wow
i'm so scared okay i'm going outside i'm
saying it's phantom i'm saying
i'm saying it's fantastic all this world
is the secrets of the world are there
written here in this triangle are you
saying it happens can we go guys
yeah okay
i'm scared
come here i'm guarding the door
gutting the door gutting the door making
sure
i'll leave it out you got the door
i guess so okay where's the door where's
the door where's the door where's the
door where's the door where's the door
where's the door where's the door
here
there's not a lot of activity guys i
think it's fine i think the ghost is
kind of sick of us oh
you guys all guessed phantom
wait i'm listening let me check the door
what are you eating
outside i don't want to go inside
it's our activity is going up a bit
okay bye-bye
[Music]
okay
on on the door and lights which is all
well
once again that was a
very uh
eventful at least we didn't we mostly
didn't die 75 of the party is still here
somehow
not bad well three for three right now
that means we won't lose any items at
least at least the people who
would yeah
the people who didn't die
okay
so are we really going for phantom
i guess i don't know what else we should
go for yeah
just gotta help me apparently sorry
maybe we should split
i'll pick and she wait okay why would it
be banshee
i don't know because because the game
always is right and we're always wrong
chased me up the attic even though there
were other people downstairs oh there's
a fancy place it's one person
specifically
oh interesting but wouldn't have sat in
this just pretend something about being
alone because here it says everyone
usually when i was like
who talk to you on this ah
i see
well i'm gonna close the door now
everyone make your decisions
all right i'll just see what happens i'm
i'm joining the black parade today we'll
see what happens
[Music]
all right weird crisscross yeah you suck
weird farmhouse um
that dude was really yanking our chain
for a while
mm-hmm
it was a yo-kai what the [\h__\h]
we just got to get good at fasmo
it really
started it became really difficult after
that stupid update
yeah it did yes i mean last time you
guys played it you also couldn't get a
single win right exactly exactly and we
had some some decent ghost hunters i
would say this is just a game for like
really elite game lords i think which is
fine that's great
games like that should exist um it just
means that we maybe have some trouble
date
coming out tomorrow yeah our timing was
just a bit off but well maybe that was i
thought our
i love spending time with you guys
though don't get me wrong yeah it's just
the game
i'm playing
i mean i'm i'm i personally wouldn't
mind not playing it anymore either
[Laughter]
only fun because you guys are here
yeah me too i enjoyed having uh you guys
around and spending time with you guys
because i
i haven't had much time or like
possibilities to interact with the
council members specifically
unfortunately i'm sorry my heart is
still pumping
i can't feel my arms
i've been trying i was gonna ask you how
to do it because i'm not kidding it
feels like it's coming out of my uh
coming out of my chest i'm not i'm not
kidding i can't feel my arms i can't
feel my legs is this am i having a
heartbeat oh my gosh that's really
intense i didn't know it was that it was
like that you should have a good rest
why are they suggesting
[Music]
it was still fun it wasn't i want to
make sure you're okay i'm okay
did you guys have fun at least no you
can stay you've done it yeah of course
do it again
okay yeah i feel like i'm getting braver
at horror games there are no monsters
under your bed okay should should mommy
fauna check under your
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah tell him you tell him
oh i still had a good time though i'm
extremely hungry but i still had a
really good time with you guys i
actually have to i'm watching horror
movies quote-unquote horror movies oh
yeah right
what's your favorite popcorn callie
movie theater butter
butter salty butter extra buttery
oh
i've had a time where i only wanted to
eat caramel popcorn
but now i'm back to like i don't mind
eating any kind like salty or butter or
uh caramel popcorn i don't mind anything
you probably can stick to that real
quick huh it no i love when it's like
the more caramel is on it the better
it on it the more hair the better yeah
agreed
yeah fana what's your favorite popcorn
um
i like classic buttery as well oh oh
good choice you got some good face how
about you ben
what's your favorite one
what's the question
what's your favorite popcorn
um
i like cheese
you like cheese popcorn yes
you're a wrap but i've i've only seen
cheese popcorn before in japan like i
was in a store where there's like uh 50
different types of popcorn and they're
they all sound weird as [\h__\h] oh yeah
like um like seaweed flavor and stuff
like that even crazier than that that's
that's still super normal for japan's
seaweed
yeah but it was really weird stuff
really interesting cool
that's tasty at least at least they got
different types red red bean flavor oh
yeah that's right and like spicy super
hot
strawberry flavor they had that too
banana flavored they definitely had
banana flavored popcorn that's yummy
actually
pizza
like pizza goldfish
sorry nerdy nut over popcorn a little
bit
i'm glad you're also a popcorn fan kiara
i wouldn't mind whenever i go back to uh
japan
you know what we should do we should
find that store and then get like 20
different types of that popcorn and do a
taste testing yeah blindfolded you guys
can't look at it it's a good idea
oh yeah i mean would be nice to look at
it but i guess popcorn all looks the
same most of the time yeah you gotta
guess the flavor that's the fun of it
though
yeah
they are being quiet sorry sorry i had
to go
you had to go
yelling
cat fact of your cat
yes i was hugging 21 years old so older
more like an insider give me an insider
catfish oh my old man are we talking
about old man
what's an insider cat fact
like uh like something weird about him
that he does
um he sees into the spirit realm that's
cool
and yells into mirrors
that's adorable oh my god whenever i pet
my cat uh my cats on like the part right
above their tail they lick themselves
oh
without fail it's very cute
fana do your cats follow you wherever
you go like as soon as you get up from a
chair do they like run after you
not really but hold on i have to go grab
you know what my one of my cats uh
smoothie you know what's what cute thing
she does um
you know when i'm talking on my stream
like i talk pretty like
like constantly right so when i when i'm
done streaming i immediately stop
talking and smoothie every time i swear
every time i'm done streaming she
immediately comes into my room because
she knows i'm done streaming because i
stopped talking she walks into my room
she says meow and then she falls down on
the floor and she rolls around and says
hello like mommy you're done with
streaming don't play with me
so cute
yeah
she recognizes when i'm done streaming
it's so ah well he's probably figured it
out by now yeah yeah definitely
when mommy is lounge she goes to
different room to sleep and when when
mommy is quiet she comes back and says
hello
he's cute guys
hey do you like cats do you have a good
relationship with cats meow
yeah why rats
yeah do you ever get chased by cats yeah
yeah that's a good answer
well has a cat ever tried to eat you
meow
yeah i don't want to talk about it bae
is brain dead before we all yeah i think
so
oh well oh it's fun ladies thank you for
inviting me i was calming down i think
um okay i'm good thank you for inviting
me um
and bang i'm glad you guys had fun at
least i wanted to i just wanted to i
don't know i i just wanted to play games
playing something not scary
it's not good
we're gonna play scary games that's the
thing it's just this game because i
can't deal with paranormal any other
kind of horror game it's not in the dark
i can i can somewhat i can see
pretty much every horror game
it's fun
this horror game is not dark middle
nightmares
dead by daylight day by day it is not
very it has some uh not dark levels yeah
it says daylight so it's bright
i mean yeah there's like a winter level
that's like pretty bright outside i
don't think it's i don't think it's the
type of scary game that
that you would freak you out bay so i
think it should be fine i'm excited to
play dead by daylight
yeah i also don't like first person
perspective that makes it too real dead
by daylight is third person
[Music]
unless you're the killer but then why
would you be afraid if you were the
killer so yeah you'll be fine you'll be
fine don't you worry about it bae we're
gonna have a great time all right okay
with that being said guys i guess we
better sign off huh okay
all right
thank you that was fun guys yes have fun
i'm thankful for
me
i'm sorry for everyone watching my
stream it was just a lot of fun doing
nothing yeah i'm sorry it's your rpg
i'm sorry teacher gonna be spooky too
this week or uh maybe we'll see it might
just and it depends on how you guys
approach it because
i have a grand master plan but it really
is kind of up to you guys so which way
the stuff that you come up with is like
up until now it was always very scary
and spooky so it's like it's always
halloween and you're teaching everything
i'm glad you at least think that because
right now i feel like everything is very
clownish and very funny well yeah but
that's also scary too a lot of people
yeah
yeah well i hope that you enjoy the next
installment you guys
looking forward to it yes gumbaz gumbot
it's going to be fun
um anyone else got announcements that
they want to shout out um while we have
a chance schedule is out look at it
yeah i had something coming out on
saturday
i'm sorry i'm still trying to find the
feelings in my arms um i hope you guys
will be there
um
of course i'll be there it's a very cool
thing
yeah mm-hmm i know you wait yeah wait
did you say did you like spoiler what
you're what you you know putting out
there no i just said special release
something anything special like not but
not that's it that's all you said yeah
so i know i know more than the audience
yeah
[Music]
you guys do yeah um yeah i'm like
guerrilla stream tonight
maybe i don't know guys what you gonna
play minecraft
minecraft oh
very good for gorilla
that's the gorgeous game
yeah um
[Music]
oh i don't really have anything
i'm taking a little break because
i streamed a lot this week
okay amazing
yeah
[Music]
please hug me
bye all
[Music]
you