foreign
[Music]
this is
thank you
[Music]
this is
all right
[Music]
foreign
thank you
again
yeah
okay
[Music]
hello welcome
to the stream where we slay the Spire
who is the spire
what
what does that mean
s
inspire
ah the top the top of
something because oh ho ho we get up to
the top of the yeah yeah okay
uh-huh
just learned something new um
for a second I thought maybe it's like a
like a a hint to the fact that it's an
endless spiral of
repeating to trying to slay but never
really
successfully slaying anything
but okay that's too deep
it's just a normal Spire okay welcome
[Music]
um
it seems
that's a good way to look at it thank
you
as if ah I have an ongoing run I don't
remember I haven't played it in a while
but apparently
I have an ongoing run
oh sure
so we're gonna look into that first I
don't remember what it is
but
uh I'm curious
okay audio audio you're hearing hearing
the audio yes watch it hard to play
really
oh
really harder than all the others
it was a VOD Oh you mean you mean the
search and totally not live stream
that was members only I've for the
people who are curious I've played slay
the Spire several times uh
in members only what do you see in
statistics
[Music]
hmm oh my God
huh
was it zero
some of them were private I think but in
my private runs I've ever so often many
times
have just canceled my runs because I saw
it's meaningless but then I realized
later on
Olympic I realized later on oh oh oh
when I say that I'm about to die I guess
I should still let it happen if I'm
really abandoning it because I'm still
gonna get
or points right like
there'll be
useful is better than just completely
closing out the game
right is it
yeah you get rewards yeah yeah so also
for the angle for the next run if it
sees that you had a run before even if
it failed It's Gonna Give You better
options right to start
um
to start the the coming run right
oh yeah four a.m run
wow
what's it why did I start playing at 4am
is that correct
did I really start at 4am before oh dear
okay well was this
[Music]
this looks like boobies
cleavage right here
what is this
looking at things I've never looked at
before
addiction is real
yep okay let's look at the Run
um
ah I think
I think this was a private run where
I restarted a million times
but I never
was able to
or maybe not I don't know we can try it
this is the silent but let's try to
finish it you guys can help me I don't
know what I was going for
um okay uh again and yeah at the start
of your turn you can no longer see enemy
intense no I want to see them
at the start of your turn oh that sounds
cool good useful
um no I would go for this one
check deck uh you want to see my deck
before Oh [\h__\h] uh this is my deck
what do you think I was
um going mostly by uh like
guide of which cards are good but
not quite always considering or like
able to understand which cards are good
with each other some cards are good on
its own but nice deck thank you oh thank
you
yes
but I must have abandoned it either
because of I needed to sleep or because
oh I just couldn't get any further I
don't know
um
wait what was I going for in the stick
uh
um
[Music]
uh what was I going for I guess I was
going for no no no okay I understand I
was trying to go for shifts first this
is that run yeah yeah but then I
couldn't get any more shift cards so it
said it was always having poison cards
so as I kind of like did like a mix
um
yeah it's a like all of them I didn't
want to I wanted to go forever or and
then in the beginning I got the shift
cards but no poison cards and then later
I got only poison cards so
I tried my best to mix it somehow but
now it's a little bit more heavy on the
poison side because Helia poison is the
best okay so I would say we'll go for
the flavors color
um
yeah mixed run yeah
you might call it balanced I guess
all right
let's see let's see oh yeah it's also
pretty big yeah 26 cards wait I think
yeah yeah this was where I was getting
[\h__\h] over so many times like I started
to run and the choices I got in the
beginning were like
kind of questionable and I was like you
know what I don't really if I'm going
for a ship run I don't need to starting
Relic from the silence that much is what
I was thinking so I go for the random
boss Relic and the one they give me is
this one
and oh I have a cat here in my mouth
been like I was like okay okay as I'll
try this seems very impossible but I
guess I'll try but look at my HP this is
like the constant state of me
it's
it's I mean I I swear I restarted like
at least five times trying my best here
I think this is the point where in the
next fight I have absolutely no choice
but to die
so I guess we're abandoned in about oh
no wait oh
wait no we're not getting far here I
think
hey okay I'm back to full HP but but but
this is this is uh
where it gets real tough so we don't
need the ones with the red sides because
we can't [\h__\h] rest at them either
anyway but this is why my deck is so
good and so upgraded because I had
nothing else to do in my on my rest
sides
yeah okay
um can't you forge yeah I mean that's
what would still do but
yeah it's not as
helpful as healing
that does explain the upgrades yeah
well dramatic music wow okay so where
should we go I don't remember where I
would always go previously but
um
um I I wanted to avoid as many boss
fights as possible because I don't
[\h__\h] hell
um
okay let's start let's side here
a while
it's been a while let me see if I
remember what I would do uh he attacks
of 10.
[Music]
oh I don't know I have to warm up guys I
have to warm up my brain okay
[Music]
um
wait I should I should just do this
[\h__\h] should have done that person and
some other stuff I
up okay I'm warming up I'm warming up at
least he can't hurt us now
[Music]
yeah give me some time I'm gonna try my
best here 13 damage okay
also what is the rest of your strength
up okay
[Music]
random potion
uh brain is not working yet do I have
more block I only have this
foreign
[Music]
what did I get
vulnerable hmm
okay I don't even want to use it no
[Music]
okay okay it's been a while I thought
that button would be like okay cancel
like not this car just cancel just get
out of that window
I hate myself so much
why is that an option like that I hate
myself great start yeah
[\h__\h] okay wait what
I guess we have to take damage we have
no choice
die die I love this card
so aggressive 21 oh well I will um kill
you I think
[Music]
no I don't think I can kill you
or can I I am okay
[Music]
see I already have so many cards if only
I can discard a bunch of the useless
ones I wouldn't mind taking more but
what do you think
prepared
well I guess yeah it's already a plus
and zero cost so okay
skip a free
um yeah I want to get rid of some of the
strikes and defense and maybe even get
rid of the shift cards if I can
because I guess I'm doing poison after
all I don't know
um
I'll I'll go here I want to avoid
fighting as much as I can oh [\h__\h] I
think I remember this one
as long as it doesn't take my HP I'm
happy
ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm so [\h__\h] again I'm so [\h__\h]
Madness is nice you mean Madness is nice
it's zero okay
[Music]
that would like work well with the
shifts I guess the ship build because I
want everything to be zero cost
[Music]
to Mark again it can't get worse can it
it's a good buff well it's obviously a
debuff though feels like a debuff
I'll go here again please don't hurt me
[Music]
I hate myself
this is just the warm-up brand wait I
can leave Oh Oh I thought oh I I have
but I have no choice okay uh well I'm
not giving you my money okay so this was
a free
Free Run let's go
all right 799 1850 25 25 damage your
quick math wow wow wow
[Music]
I need some cool cards
discard that one this card done I guess
oh maybe I should have been just [\h__\h]
yeah [\h__\h] because I did discard a card
yeah whatever
it's okay it's okay guys it's okay it's
just a warm-up run wake up why because
I I at least kind of understand that I
did something wrong immediately after
doing it it's a little bit too late but
I still realize
okay
um nine and eighteen
can I kill one of you maybe
oh that's perfect
okay
oh wait this one explodes oh [\h__\h] oh
yeah [\h__\h] I need to take him
need to take him down
what the rest is just block
[Music]
my discarding meant uh
this card for the whole run or for the
moment
the whole I mean the whole battle or the
or the moment I forgot just for the turn
okay
I'll add this one hmm wait why did I not
just use this one see I'm I'm I need to
warm up my brain because this one would
give me six uh block for free again next
turn you don't question don't question
too much
we are we are going to kill you now 23
damage let's see
[Music]
we might not be able to kill you
oh [\h__\h] oh we might not be able to kill
him
[Music]
Madness ain't helping me now
okay now I made this for you
what did I just do
um yeah well hmm
not going wow not going well ah
wonderful wonderful
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] I hate this run so much
is that something that weakens uh
amazing vulnerable no
[Music]
what oh oh [\h__\h]
ah well thank you for releasing me from
this [\h__\h] run
see this is why I should really just
finish my runs instead of just
running away from it every time
okay oh
my tiny just killed every fourth room
room is a treasure room
Russian's card removal service now
always costs 50 gold
opposed to what how much is it normally
instead of voodoo doll
[Music]
okay
it was a good warm-up it was a bad
warm-up
okay but we're not playing with that
character today we already I did get a
clear with these two before
um I played this one before but that was
my first time and I didn't get it clear
but we're playing The Watcher today
let's see I have no idea what she does
a blind ascetic
who has come to evaluate the spire
Master of the Divine stances at the
start of each combat add a miracle to
your hand okay
a miracle
you guys have to help me because I
absolutely don't know anything
um
does she have a problem with like low HP
or so
Just Dances oh
yes no kinda yeah
can
HP is usually fine
oh well I'll go for this one though
because uh
[Music]
um
one two okay I think I think I'll just
go here for now
oh yeah one HP let's go okay so what
will uh
what are these Miracles here again
energy okay
and she's used to play cards in your
hands oh so she's like she gives herself
a lot of energy so we can play big cards
is that what's going on
oh on only only once per oh well this
they're they're [\h__\h] dead anyway
already
who can also hang on to it too it
doesn't go into the discard pile at the
end of the turn
not my first time I just said I played
it many times before in members only
this is the first time we're playing it
publicly
create all cards in your hand for the
rest of the comment oh cool
so what are we going for like is there
like different type different ways to
play her like with the silent or
is there just one way
it's all about setup
giveaway which is pretty simple focus on
damage first
build up Mantra
okay A lot of people are saying this one
Raph and calm stand and this one sorry
graphing column stances
the other names when we change
it's retain routine guys I'm not
discarded increases damage
I have four this combat
[Music]
huh so I get the card back and it does
uh seven plus four damage
okay
[Music]
one is really good if you hang on to it
like hold on to it
oh
crash joint stealing damage it was a
skill apply
uh-huh
deal seven damage if the last card
played this combat was an attack
it's cards they want to confuse me you
guys helping me this time right yeah
yeah okay okay
I'll go this way
occult verb just like you guys feels
familiar doesn't it
foreign
[Music]
lots of ones
hello
welcome what you got what do we want
we already have 146 noise oh what's that
this bird looks dead
anything that looks good to you guys
still ate damage I'm gonna play one week
I already have this one I think
retain enter wrath exhaust
remove a car and remove the fan okay
kind of pretty I like this purple
I love purple
this this looks really fancy in this
card
can't get Diva form oh because it's too
expensive
oh no
oh no yeah we can't get much now
uh
Rap On Demand
it's good
crescendo
Crescendo okay
that's I think Italian and can be other
languages too
all green that already looks good as you
come to a dead end and begin to turn
around won't slap down and welcome to
the jam from the ceiling trapping you
free forces materialized from the walls
and speak forget what you know I'll let
you go
I require a change to see a new space
if you want to pass me then you must
grow
remove a card transform a card upgrade a
card oh free upgrade
transform a strike
upgrade
what would you upgrade eruption
Transformer
transforming oh is this
depending on when I push confirm
or not
I don't know what to go for anyway
that's my brain right now all the time
draw two cards exit your stance sounds
interesting
sounds okay
nice
[Applause]
because it gives me control over my
stance I guess
I still don't quite understand like how
I can change my stance but okay
it sounds good
now we upgrade
apparently we want to upgrade probably
with this one
ten five
goes down one cost
eruption okay
yeah yeah okay okay okay
see bro we're speed running right now
okay
now they have normal HP
so
um
oh my God 10 15 18
. so
am I like right now in the calm stance
how do I know my current stance
[Music]
yeah because Raph will give me double
damage I understand that so don't use it
now
I'm a normal stance oh okay
okay
[Music]
all right I think
all right I could
do more but
should I
oh I should have
killed one that does more damage
oh well
okay
that's okay
I accept this challenge oh they're going
full attack again
well definitely defending
[Music]
oh wait we have a Blog potion that would
help now because otherwise I'll take a
lot of damage
hmm
I think I might drink it
yeah good
and
well
I can't
when we're changing Christmas oh [\h__\h] no
I can't use that unless nope
I could
empty mind eh oh this
okay
there are two cars
okay but I can only enter wrath on my
own command
when I wanna like when I use like a
enter wrap like this kind of card
mm-hmm
[Music]
foreign
oh
oh because it says when I exit it I get
more energy so by entering this first
and then switching to a Wrath
I already get extra energy
right so the snap
okay so then we switch to crescendo
right wait what what does comb do just
just that okay
ah this oh
one two nine damage okay this is just
okay okay
uh-huh so now I got two energy back do
you have 14 damage
it was an attack again okay cool so for
example I killed this one
but it's a deal 14 damage that was
already doubling uh with the ref right
that's already the final
the final damage that I get right
and then 12 damage oh no
okay
nice what else can we do I could exit my
stance and draw two cards but not really
worth it I guess
well I think that's it
okay cool I think
I am for
nice
skill potion
and what do we have
the only damage to the last card player
discovers a skill uh-huh play apply one
vulnerable if you're a wrap apply a free
vulnerable to All Enemies otherwise
enter wrap oh sounds cool so drop cars
until your hand is full
oh
scroll oh oh scrub very popular whoa
is that a overpowered good card
um
can I upgrade this to zero to zero cost
shall not do it right away
let's do it
so rare it's yellow aha
so far the run is going well
bottled lightning upon pickup choose a
skill
start each combat with this card in your
hand
[Music]
well scroll
okay
okay I would have just brought that
maybe in the beginning I don't
necessarily I'm not that desperate to
get that many cards right in the
beginning but okay
go next go next oh big slime you're
gonna separate right oh yeah yeah
[Music]
um
you're thinking
so probably Rush down
um
foreign
[Music]
start with Miracle into scroll
oh okay
really
memory fight
wow
should I enter wrap right away
because she's probably gonna attack next
time
and then I get double damage it's not so
nice
I really okay if you say so
wait do I have anything that gives him
vulnerable though no okay
[Music]
okay so now oh
wait what do we have we have 12 damage
12 damage 14 damage
this works because we already attacked
so I should get this costs one but I get
one back right
okay cool
we can do Windmill strike
increase
yeah or normal strikes I guess because
this costs too then this is cheaper
damage then
oh it's gonna separate
okay okay okay
foreign
[Music]
can we kill him one turn 14 damage
18 damage
what happens when I'm already in rap
when it tells me to go into Ralph
nothing right
22 damage
may I use this now
because then I won't hit him
when melon okay okay thinking the same
welcome good
okay we keep one
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] nice
good good fight wasn't even a fight
um the United mouth
another follow-up skip
[Music]
three two three
two three
oh
thanks for saying hi to chonkers I want
a small deck okay I'll skip
okay
sometimes
it's wiser to skippity scoop
[Music]
so I'm gonna do this thing that you guys
told me to always do okay
and
I would like to defend
the damage if we can defend quite a bit
instead of attacking in the Wrath right
away
at which ruins ah intercom
[Music]
and another one and now we're good so
the rest
um
just just uh
go it eruption really
I guess okay I'm I'm keeping the block
yeah but
but I received double damage
I could have one shot it
[Music]
even really
would you mind after
I feel like I'm in danger
wait did I use the wrong card I think I
used the wrong card
did I on it
um
[\h__\h]
but at least I'm not in rap right now so
he won't hurt me too much
okay let's at least there's some damage
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
yeah you told me too late
[Music]
well we could probably kill him now
right
[Music]
um
vigilance why virgin Visions oh ah okay
okay always I understand always try to
um
re-enter
from calm to rap for the extra energy
and the free Block
okay
now this
[Music]
no yes no no no okay
feel nine damage and some rap okay okay
laugh
um
oh
what did would it not have been nice to
have played Rush down first
windmill windmill
I almost killed
[Music]
I'm missing one
empty minded
okay I guess now I'll just add some
block
s yeah
23 okay let me think uh what I would do
no
Maybe
crescendo
and then
[Music]
um
and then windmill strike
yeah okay okay
[Music]
I got that I understand
oh that's that looks like the monster in
the very beginning
even whenever you just cry or turn this
from the discard describe look at the
time
he's got any of them what
crash down again yeah they keep on
wanting to give us Rush down
and halt too they push these two cards
onto US
hmm gain free Block if you are in Wrath
gain nine additional block
[Music]
so that's like when I
I am in Wrath but I urgently need block
I guess
[Music]
not good because for you oh well
uh I think we can
take up an elite
hello who are you again
I don't remember what kind of dude you
are
[Music]
no not this one ah uh I definitely
bought them before but I don't remember
what his thing was
hit this dude
okay this is annoying oh well
[Music]
so maybe
um
eruption
and then we have three more energies so
erupted and then follow up maybe
vegetance first why vigilance oh okay
okay okay okay
it doesn't
I don't even need block though I thought
this cancels itself out
yeah
it doesn't do anything yeah okay
Forge potion all right why not
don't scratch the expensive chair
man Miller chair don't touch the Herman
Miller chair so what did I say I said
eruption
then I said follow up but I don't know
if it's right let me look at the Rose
the damage
nice
yeah I'm just gonna spam the attacks on
him
oh
she did not even get a chance
y'all
yo nice
mommy did it yeah
you want to Slade Aspire too chunky
wonky no time to slay this fire now for
you I'm slaying this fire what is this
if you turn if you end your turn without
block can you go
oh
yes
four for that turn up not the following
right okay cool
[Music]
that's a good Relic I think meow meow
what what
he's looking staring at me yeah if I
don't block it
uh free will come if you aren't calm
draw free cards otherwise intercom oh
yeah that sounds good
that will probably help us
oh [\h__\h] we still have so much HP we can
yeah we can upgrade one more time
[Music]
um
oh oh wait
vicious oh not vicious me I was
Victorious yet okay yeah Victorious yes
ah
[Music]
um
zero cost
11 damage which would turn into 22
damage
um
[Music]
yeah I feel like
I would make this one for you then
yeah because then we don't only enter
rap for free we also get some cards for
free
get it all right cute caterpillars
11 damage
really weak okay exactly
[Music]
we could definitely enter first that
might help
and then
Rush no
ah yeah rest down first to get the two
cards before yeah yeah using eruption
I'm like I don't know who
care
oh you curl up oh
yeah good so far okay
and now we need to do six more damage on
you no problem but what do I want to use
oh 14 damage
oh
[Music]
I don't know who to attack
because my kid killed this one but this
one's not gonna attack
[Music]
oh wow okay
and I wanna kill one of these
[Music]
yeah
oh maybe I shouldn't have done it like
that how much more did that just cost
two or one
[Music]
oopsie oops [\h__\h] ah that cost two oh oh
damn no I'm gonna get double damage
no okay that's okay we can rest
afterwards
that's fine
[Music]
don't worry
don't worry yeah I know I could have
killed oopsie oh is this just lucky
valuate game six block shelf on the
inside
tantrum
pan from op
[Music]
oh do you free damage three times
so nine
to only one enemy I guess enter a wrath
Shuffle this card into your draw pile
yeah okay
sure now we still have so much HP I
don't know we could even risk it and
go for another Smith
I feel like we could risk it
uh-huh
all right
um
[Music]
four times
a drum okay
that's a good Improvement
okay boss
[Music]
shift just like me for real for real
but I don't I have better control over
it than you
okay
okay okay
so now
let's do lots of damage
um
[Music]
wait
I don't have the
ah
[Music]
um
okay now we're using that
mode the defense mode
always add on to that or does he stay
around 20 defense
mind inner peace inner peace empty mind
[Music]
okay
and I just did something okay okay
whenever you play an attack take free
damage ah
okay pain for pain and it's a fair
exchange all right
you interrupt your two cards I am now in
calm and when I exit I get two
energy points nice
[Music]
so first
rest down
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah I would play this one first too
[Music]
foreign
I think I need to go
okay I'm not gonna wait I can uh give
myself some energy if I wanted to we're
at the boss fight so
wait then first I do one more damage
right
intercom
oh
sexy
quite sexy that was sexy
I saved I saved my butts just now all
according to keikaku yeah yeah
spicy
eight times two no no problem
[Music]
oh that sounds good right
we need some cards okay
do I still have this thing
yeah okay I still have this okay
okay
so so uh either eruption or tantrum
[Music]
fan is all okay
okay and I should not have
um
[Music]
hmm
five times four
twenty
Ah that's quite a bit
All In
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
okay
empty mind
[Music]
foreign
block add block here
Oh I wanna go to Safe route or what
I'll still do some damage though
almost almost
[Music]
you were like oh stop this [\h__\h] is
making mistake again oh ah not again
someone stopper
someone stop it
I wish I could hack her computer right
now
eight times two sixteen
I think we should go full attack
[Music]
foreign
I know there's like so many slave Aspire
enthusiasts I was really surprised I
when I first chose this from Emma's only
stream I chose it pretty randomly
[Music]
glad you guys are enjoying it
um okay
[Music]
I think I made a mistake
um did I make a mistake
um
[Music]
okay well even if he does a lot of
damage to us now it's okay we can still
kill him
as long as we survived the fight always
chill
Don't Worry Be Happy
[Applause]
oil no no interrupt
but maybe with empty Minds
okay
[Music]
there we go
and don't make mistake Now 46 damage
holy [\h__\h] how did that happen
yeah whoa cool cards I mean I don't know
to be honest but they look cool
[Music]
please choose a card of your liking chat
you have to teach me how to play those
characters still we're still in tutorial
phase
one
most people say one
if fatal upgrade a random card in your
dad wow
what a finisher card ew
uh oh
[Music]
gain energy at the start of your turn
whenever you open a non-boss chest
obtain a canal
no
[Music]
I don't like the ones that give me
curses [\h__\h] curses
no no no no no no
[Music]
no no no
new map
you guys probably already know what what
boss will be will be fighting right just
by seeing the symbol I don't know though
[Music]
go maybe here
mmm
one
only two
is there no route with free fireplaces
with one two three here
kind of on the right side
[Music]
the champion
ah I feel like I remember
okay
um
yo this dude has so much block but once
we get the block
uh go on then
he's an easy target
um
rushed down first always rush down first
sorry
[Music]
follow up
yo
to
oh
what did it upgrade
that was by random which one did it
upgrade did it upgrade crescendo
[Music]
yeah I did oh
thank you for that y'all
that's so helpful
damn I have to spam that card
um what the [\h__\h] is mantra
when you obtain 10 Mantra enter Divinity
well upon entering stance gain free
energy attack steal triple damage
[Music]
triple
I lack Divinity because okay so that
seems to be like a different way of
playing this character
that sounds like fun
I don't like these birds they think
they're really cool because they spell
their name with a y
something better
no rush down I don't see a rush down
[Music]
but I feel like
let's do like uh
are these
and this oh [\h__\h] wait what
[Music]
receive
receive because they fly
yeah
with a Y no thank you
that looks stupid
[Music]
we can however uh if I remember
yeah yeah you can cancel it we can kind
of stun them
uh
I think that should eventually kill
yeah
I mean I don't know if that was the best
turn but hey we got a freak upgraded
card
yeah whatever
[Music]
yay
wow four times five
five I mean even we go full like block
but then still take a lot of damage or
we try to take this [\h__\h] down [\h__\h]
with a y
one attack was wasted oopsie
can we I want to take him down
wash down in a peace Christian though
[Music]
really
yay
I'm happy with that
um oh I was I was already in rap oh
that's right okay whatever it was free
it's free
now I'm gonna kill you
28 damage
we can do this
[Music]
wow upgrade card is not here right now
okay that's okay follow up 14 or okay
[Music]
foreign
class
at the end of your turn Shuffle and
inside
[Music]
peep
we like to keep our deck small
[Music]
s
um I would go here I like a question
mark oh it's the mask guy
wait is this the one where there's like
a 50 chance and I I read up on it uh
online and like so many people complain
about the fact that like 90 of the time
they always get the bad one
they think that is bugged
[Music]
yeah if that if it really doesn't seem
like 50 then I don't know if I want to
risk it
try it
was roughly 50 50. it shouldn't be
roughly
put it to the test
you want me to try wait but what's the
bad face thing again what's that do
again
I think like in some face faces in some
cases bad face is not even that bad
but um
I'm gonna get the bad face hundred
percent
but I feel like even if we get a bad
face with your help we will still manage
it somehow
what
the next number since you open is empty
okay only the next one only one okay
okay
that's okay only one
it could have been worse
it's really
[Applause]
no it's not the worst
rigged 100 bad
well what can we do
all right next
but
non-bossed chest yeah that's not so bad
that's really not so bad
who do you attack first
who's more dangerous
[Music]
I understand Russian okay so I I have
the first three cards set in stone now
don't worry
um yeah I would enter around
[Music]
at least in the left or like oh [\h__\h]
inner peace before wrap
[Music]
okay next time so so four cards set in
stone
I'll try to remember that
okay
[Music]
um
I don't want to use this now
well this doesn't get him quite out of
the
um out of his block
so one hitting him
[Music]
what this
is 12. oh yeah oh yeah yeah I guess
somehow this would be more useful
[Music]
only
[\h__\h]
okay you choose
my last turn empty mind or so I don't
know inner peace hi
okay
[Music]
hmm
uh they're gonna attack and he's got
like 25 block now so we probably should
block as much as possible
Crescendo what
you want to attack
boom
um
left or right I feel like we even have a
chance to killing the left one even
though we didn't do any damage yet
20 22
yeah easy easy
[Music]
six times four
okay
um
and the rest
oh
[Music]
it's not as much block as I want but
that's okay
okay
ah just two damage it's okay oh we're
gonna finish it with lesson learned we
will do it we will do it no matter what
so tantrum or eruption
[Music]
oh maybe I should have used in the piece
first oh sorry
uh that's
it
[Music]
oh a defend all right okay we're gonna
get rid of the useless cards otherwise
it's gonna upgrade all the useless cards
but that that one defend I'll take that
gladly it's not so bad
what was that I've reality it's so
sparkly a smite
[Music]
interesting
tranquility and to come for free
we're 14.
yeah
and Chad's wedding
I'll take off some clothes
[Music]
I don't know if I am
want to risk two question marks
[Music]
but it's always interesting I feel like
I'm playing gotcha
like a real Godzilla game every time I
enter one of those question marks and
the rash of it just
ah
it's good it's fun oh okay it's a fun
yeah okay fine so Miracle scroll and
then I bring you guys said
inner peace
and brush down right Rush down
and always also inner peace
no I didn't miss it I did do it
what
[Music]
ah first enter calm so then I get the
this is like
unlike the other characters like this
character makes me feel the most like I
have to remember a certain order and
it's always the same
which is not eventually a bad thing
because that makes it easier for my
little burp brain
not internet why not inner
[\h__\h]
[Music]
but why not
I guess we should have done it later
after at the end of our turn
[Music]
a question okay
dude the Mystic does he like heal his
body
or do I misremember
because then I need to take the Mystic
down first
neutral density
of the turn order is in fact beneficial
yeah
he does heal okay
maybe we can take him down
we have five energy
we are in Wrath
wish we could take him down there
I did not attack yet so maybe eruption
follow-up
and then maybe strike and lesson learned
if that wasn't if the
if it wasn't enough vigilance
Focus night first
[Music]
the other starts doing more damage
if I oh
okay
um okay
70 I don't think I can do 77 damage in
one turn though
she still just you
use my final
[Music]
and what you guys are you guys are here
for
[Music]
okay all right let's let's I will try
don't don't hate me if I make a mistake
do I want to do vigilance first
and then go back into rap
or do I just stay the way I am now
strike full of visuals oh my God
a free Block yeah that's what I was
thinking
because they are gonna do a bit of
damage especially if I don't get to kill
one of them I got AJ attached to my hand
and you'll tell me how
I got 80s damage
Monty there
[Music]
foreign
oh God
[Music]
this sucks I want to end it with this
card
I mean
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
16. I guess I'll
um
empty Minds I have to exit unfortunately
no block no nothing left for Block
well okay at least we got them down
thank you
just have to believe
okay
um
inner peacefulness
I always say
no vigilance inner peace
but then I'm already out of
[Music]
all attack what's up
too bad I can't go into Wrath
[Music]
foreign
okay
for the next turn
okay okay 40 damage seems manageable
uh
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] no don't kill that
beautiful
speed potion improves block gain from
cards okay
[Music]
pressure points apply eight Mark well so
many cards or things I don't know what's
Mark who's Mark
[Music]
I should skip this one oh
okay oh never question my
mind another fight yeah okay
twink really teeth
uh if I understand that correctly uh
both I think this order doesn't matter
so much
Tranquility or Rush down the first
[Music]
wait
twin quiz
[Music]
chain enter calm and then because we
have this thing where you interrupt yeah
yeah I could now
do crescendo
right yeah
foreign
six energy
my god
oh wait
[Music]
I want I know I can kill him I just want
to play it smart
[Music]
I guess I guess whatever
yeah
[Music]
vigilance is upgraded but
um
not the one that I already have in my
hand against it starts being upgraded
from the next time I have it in my hand
that's weird
come on
[Music]
okay okay good turn good turn good turn
good turn
12 damage is what we're receiving but
not really because we're gonna kill this
one
empty mind
no eruption
ah maybe I can exit my raft stance at
the end
okay
[Music]
foreign
still free energy
how am I gonna end this maybe
[Music]
should I keep the window one more time
or
um
in a pretty same game
foreign
[Music]
okay
holy [\h__\h] we got so much damage in our
hands I think we'll do just fine
[Music]
okay
okay nice
I I I think so much because I don't want
you guys to get mad when I make a
mistake so excuse me if my turns take a
long time because you guys get like no
no every time I make a mistake it scares
me
[Music]
oh
more Rasta oh okay
really
do you want another one
thank you guys thank you
[Music]
yeah up to me I still have like under 20
cards if you think that's smart then
sure why not
let's go fight this boss
ah wait he's free
I remember
I remember had some troubles of these
mobs in like a older lonely solo run
please help me
why you guys are you guys like
eh
are you guys trolling me or do you
really want to rush down to be the
number one first card
before Miracles girl gets me one more
card
eh
so Rush down miracle
not Miracle Rush down
oh and this stacks
that Stacks I know
all right okay
um
okay I don't know I need to defend a lot
we have
some
but not much
I have only eight block here
[Music]
who do I want to kill first I don't know
who's dangerous here but I'm assuming
the big one is dangerous
I don't know
[Music]
back one what's back for you this one
Becca is the worst
why
26 was she always on 26 26 inch does he
get more damage every time I hit him or
what does that what aggressive means
[Music]
oh oh because of rap oh okay
I was like what the [\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
oh hey we got vigilance that's very
sweet
[Music]
I've saved some damage for you guys
I'm gonna go for the left one next baby
foreign
[Music]
strike
and then vigilance and defend and inner
peace because that actually is enough
[Music]
I think
okay next turn I'm taking at least the
left one down
hmm
wait
did he weaken me oh he didn't look at me
that little [\h__\h]
ah
you little [\h__\h] okay 15.
plus six is what I need
so
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah I'll do it I'll do my
lesson learned yeah there we go strike
we need to get rid of those cards
but okay I mean even that can be helpful
sometimes especially in the beginning
so Mr Mr Mr task master I by the way I'm
kind of like done with Taskmaster until
they release the latest season
I'm so sad it was so good I want to see
more please more
[Music]
it was so good if you guys have not seen
the Taskmaster they have like almost all
of their seasons on YouTube and I really
recommend it
um
yeah series 14 yeah yeah they have yet
to upload the full season
or
14 and maybe not even 13.
on their own channel
don't cool I need my my my
UK comedy please
okay focus focus I am calm
where's my wrath
[\h__\h] I have no Wrath
maybe this empty mind okay okay
oh a wound
[Music]
uh
I
could
I could
go okay
um
[Music]
funny damage yo okay we killed him
obviously
foreign
[Music]
s
thank you
cut through fate Plus
do you line damage just cry we don't
work with scribe
Nirvana
we'll kick scheme
[Music]
you can just remove some cards you that
can be infinite
you mean like an infinite Loop is that
even possible
[Music]
we're going down holy [\h__\h] this
character I'm I'm used to struggling so
much with my previous runs so
this is beautiful also I barely have
anything to upgrade because of that
upgrade card
oh
um I'm eventually gonna have everything
upgraded
the watch experience isn't always this
easy
watch his craft
upgrade
I mean I'll just I'm gonna upgrade the
upgrade cards
more upgrade upgrades and upgrade for
you oh this one will be empty right oh
oh hey at least gold wait at least get
some gold thank you
now now this is okay good use that so no
more oh vampires oh no Twilight I don't
know
ah
navigating an unlit Street you come
across several hooded figures in the
midst of some dark ritual
oh interesting
as you approach
okay refuse
bye bye I will not reach Twilight and I
will not watch Twilight you cannot get
me to do that
oh I'm my dead body
[Music]
that was a Twilight cult person yeah
cultist
okie dokie
Chosen One
I forgot what these two
what's the smartest one to go from first
wait
you guys said Rush down first right
[Music]
I don't understand why
I don't get it
[Music]
foreign
ah because I first have to use up the
cards that I'm gonna use anyway
but wouldn't I then also do Miracle
first okay
that's why that's what you mean
ah okay
[Music]
I understand though
we could
we could drive in more cars but my hand
is pretty much full
so I'm not gonna do that
I'm gonna go into crescendo
[Music]
I actually have to watch this is not my
first STS stream I streamed it like two
or three times on members only and
played privately a little bit yeah
you missed out on some cool stuff
but if you guys like it so much I can
play more science fire publicly too
kenbach thank you
she was addicted TM YTM
[Music]
join membership today
yeah
we still need to get a clear with the
first character though
that's yet to happen I don't know what
to go for I'm so indecisive when I play
this game in on stream because I'm
scared of mistakes
I wish I could kill the this one in one
turn
I don't know if I can
[Music]
26 20 oh this is 46.
I don't know maybe we can
[Music]
in a piece of rapture
for more energy
oh yeah we're back to five
oh that's that's like something only
smart people can do
it's impossible for me
Ohio
[Music]
damn
okay okay okay
um
[Music]
should I just go for some
strike here
and then we can do wait 20 plus
26. I'm believable for him
oh
I am so nice so nice
oh I like I looked at him and I was like
96 I can't do that but what
[Music]
too strong too okay
hey y'all
overall like the whole run yeah I'm
getting like good cards good these
decent relics
um
okay
uh
[Music]
laughs
foreign
do we want this card
we want this
is a rare card
yeah yeah no need but
we do retain a certain card all the time
and that card costs two I think
all right this one so we could get that
down to zero
but we always will have to use this one
first we only have one retain of course
oh it's a good card
it's good if you have a lot of routine
cards
yeah we have one more but that's already
zero
on that one well I guess so
[Music]
okay okay skip skip
60 HP I think we can go to the shop
strawberry
well
yummy I'm getting hungry
um [\h__\h] we have so much money let's go
I'm gonna get rid of a normal strike
upgrade all your cards for the rest of
the combat cool
cool anything that we need
marbles
start off each comment ah yeah I think
I've had this one before
yeah
oh yeah
maybe a potion a nice potion they're
cheap
[Music]
for your potion
it's done here waffle strawberry waffle
waffle
oh
I can afford it yeah
why is this one cost less but is better
like an upgraded version of the
strawberry
what the [\h__\h]
what
[Music]
the cost is random
oh it really I never knew that
he's forgotten I'll tell her in front of
you sits and I'll tell her to a
forgotten God Atop The Altar sits an
ornate female statue of arms
outstretched she calls out to you
demanding sacrifice
huh
that's not very nice but
that still seems like the best option
keep hug
sweet well we're back to like pretty
much the same HP as before the shop
bye bye
oh
another one of those so we go for the
Centurion first again right because if
we kill a mystery then he's gonna go mad
right it's gonna mold
we have no rush down so in this case I
will use Miracle and squirrel
and now we have Rush down
hmm
marble snakes is easier indeed
I remember yeah you're learning so fast
I'm trying thank you thank you trying
like this
no molding please it's a waste of good
wrath wait what what is that a serious
what what do you mean molding
yeah I'm gonna take you down I'm gonna
take you down I don't know yet how but I
will figure it out
okay this is a common combo that we keep
on using as well inner peace and
eruption I'm gonna try to remember that
mad and Bolding oh so you that's what
you were saying okay
I wasn't sure
[Music]
foreign
another strike got upgraded
Flurry of Blows
[Music]
furry card
your wrap I play five volatile to All
Enemies otherwise
[Music]
remember to change status returns from
the
discard pile onto your hand oh I mean I
guess it's free
get it okay sorry
with an upgrade
it's probably gonna do like six damage
[Music]
all right I guess okay so do we rest
do we need
I don't think we need to upgrade because
we keep on upgrading so much all the
time anyway so we have a pretty op
upgraded deck
I think I don't know how strong the dude
is
oh sorry my brain empty sorry empty mind
that's the card that describes my state
of Life constantly
gomanda sorry
[\h__\h]
I dressed
um
yeah I mean
you're probably like even fine without
resting
but yeah I was saying we're already like
deck wise
like it it's like
like what what what else do we want
champ
the champ the champ the champ are you
the trombone champ
I'm finding you on the weekend why are
you here so early
he was so impatient he was like I I have
to see this girl right now
I need to talk to her right now I'm
about to do dudes and the Deep Deeds
where the [\h__\h] is ranch down
I don't have brunch down but I can still
do the inner piece and and a Rapture
combo
[Music]
the baboons I don't know much yet about
the baboons
[Music]
foreign
hey
[Music]
what's that probably strike and then
vigilance
[Music]
right
save the windmill
um
I always think it's just one energy
thank God
I recorded finally something today
well well you will probably never know
what I recorded today but I recorded
something
so I did some work before the Stream
I have to record one more thing tomorrow
probably
what you will also not really know what
I recorded ever probably
mysterious recordings
no no no the ring with Muna it's not
gonna happen that fast
[Music]
okay
um
I feel like I would want to enter Raph
now
with the crescendo and then do the
Tantrum because wouldn't it then do more
damage
[Music]
we get cards
okay that's what I'm saying
oh [\h__\h] he has 20 blocks now
and 24 okay we gotta be very careful
what do I have here by the way
proves block gained from cards but only
for that yeah only that turn
oh we have that twice damn
[Music]
thank you
yeah I will drink one yeah before I
block
[Music]
s
well
I I could
no I don't know ocean waste it wow
[Music]
foreign
yeah okay okay
[Music]
we think alike some of us inner peace
I'm good there's different ways of
reaching the goal
and maybe yours was one percent better
but mine was okay too
um it's good to save when you can
[Music]
um
a funny number 248 out of 420.
can't we take him down probably not in
this turn the
whatever
one of them
[Music]
my hand is full oh
punch on me
foreign
what did I do
[Music]
oh oh yeah right okay it goes back when
it stands back okay
it looks so scary to me like he's gonna
take my life with that Scythe that he
doesn't even really have
boom
[Music]
she's like she can't decide which stance
she wants to be she keeps on Switching
for the sake of her energy
damn
an interesting
strategy
I'm sorry my brain stopped to think I'm
sorry I'm gonna gonna try my best now
wait I don't think I attacked last
uh tantrum
and then this
[Music]
we need more energy well
hello my other one I use lesson learned
even if we don't kill him it's a lot of
damage I did oh that was that's why it's
glows yellow
oh
I didn't look at that before so closely
ah
[Music]
mm-hmm
easy okay I feel like
a nice chance we have lethal maybe maybe
maybe also he won't attack so we don't
have to end with defending
[Music]
foreign
go back to Inner Peace then throw a
tantrum
[Music]
let's do that first empty mind first
yeah
okay
[Music]
really
okay
um options
[Music]
in your pants
Tantra
[Music]
follow up
that maybe maybe not switch like around
again should I like switch around again
or
like go calm and then tantrum again
got lesson out of the way
[Music]
no
ah it's okay it's okay it's okay it's
okay it won't attack we have we have a
Time
[Music]
we have so many cards too 50
holy [\h__\h] we have people at least the
next turn
one of them
uh should I end your call I can't
anymore
defeat impossible face by wrath no you
face my rap I have the real rap you only
have a fake rap and now you're going
down
you're going down but
60.
[Music]
whoa what's that
infero the side of your turn gain energy
and increases gain by one
it doesn't seem so cool and there's
me
yay thank you for your help we have one
more one more map to go
Do's eggs always skip was that
unplayable when you draw this card and
two miracles to your hands miracles
oh yeah those
oh
unplayable
yummy
[Music]
yummy yeah
wow it's a nice way of saying kill them
set their HP to zero
the most
sweet
polite way of saying
destroy kill
um
because of the shield ah true if they
have a lot of blocks then
yeah this would be really helpful I
guess
[Music]
I scored density I decide
yeah they all seem to be decent in
certain ways but you guys
[Music]
um
uniform getting me interested in this
one
ah yeah
what do we get what is this Fusion
Hammer gain energy at the start of your
turn you can no no
oh wait no longer Smith oh you know what
I feel like we really have no need to be
smithing anymore
uh because we have a card that smiffs
everything and we already have a pretty
Swift deck
oh this one is the opposite uh-huh
multiple cards and you know what I guess
we'll go for the yeah Fusion hammer
free energy
[Music]
what's golden
they're beyond ah it's the [\h__\h] dick
and donut again I hate them so much now
they like traumatized me
[Music]
I hate them
so many times they've lost against them
and restarted
but this time I am overpowered they
can't take me down now one two I think I
just might go on the right side which
looks simple but there's no shop
there's no shop on the right side here's
one
okay and then I will just go here
this will be easy
my deck is absolutely stuck to step hell
yeah let's go okay
brush down don't go no rash down
sorry
press down still no rush down
red Miracle oh yeah wait wait we got so
many Royal clothes now
[Music]
oh wait retaining is a good idea too
foreign foreign
[Music]
go away they don't need your private
dating chat girls they have me it's not
so private it's pretty public but yeah
they can chat with this girl
we don't need you here stop advertising
it might not enough
yes why why go private when you have
this
public cutie pie with her ketocatos
okay so these ones they do they do
performance damage so
um well I don't really have
any way to killing them without touching
them do I
I don't have like poison and stuff like
that
I won't have anything like that I have
to touch them
does the Bots do meet and greets
you can Vlog get some block first huh
what why oh that's what okay
yeah okay
um I will
I will
[Music]
go for this one first
um
so
[Music]
uh how about
um
can I do vigilance first and then
eruption because normally we always do
it the other way around but then I have
some block
what the [\h__\h]
some
weird window just opened up for my
printer
okay
[Music]
done
I'm just gonna go for this one oh nice
okay okay okay okay
and next
next oh I'll take you on
I think I can kill you too
[Music]
in theory again but I'll have to use
windmill strike as well
is that worth it
so sad so sad I don't like using so much
damage when they're only like at 4 HP
it hurts me
okay an intercom
okay
what can you do hmm I'm too overpowered
aren't you trembling in fear as you
should
as you should
[Music]
53.
uh interesting cards but yeah okay we
have some block
um
uh yeah
we do some blocking
foreign
[Music]
yeah I'm confused I was just like trying
to set something up but
[Music]
oh
I still got so much energy
[Music]
I did minus 20.
tantrum shredded me oh well yeah
do some damage it's okay guys have you
seen like
how overpowered I am rest down twice now
[Music]
can I get a block before I do this oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay okay in a piece upgraded yeah oh
um concentrate deal eight damage to all
damage for free
all enemies and your train
[Music]
skip
I'm believing I am believing
not good act free cards
they in general seem pretty good though
at least upgraded
[Music]
Russian restaurants
um
okay and
I missed two draws it's a rat
got more than enough cards
hmm
foreign
[Music]
I feel like I could kill him
for for more energy
[Music]
okay
what happens when I got all my cards
upgraded nothing
oh
looks like not so interesting
[Music]
I feel like I'm playing this game in
Easy Mode right now
ain't 10 block actually your stance hmm
in some situations yeah pretty good
baby mode
don't blow that okay okay okay
[Music]
ends up being pretty much the same I'm
going here
uh this
nah should I get the Relic
even if we go to a shop
so much that we would do that we really
desperately need at a shop anymore we
don't really need cards
and yeah until the shop will probably
get a good amount of money again
next shop is still quite a bit away
[Music]
actually interesting
whatever like you get with
we get we get red mask at the start of
each comment and plan one week to all
enemies
leave
[Music]
um okay
oh danger shark ghost shark
do we have Russian yeah
[Music]
I forgot what was that thing you always
combined with vigilance
was it
[Music]
never mind
I remembered
right
no was it wrong
[Music]
in correct order
uh vigilance and denim reaction okay
next time
but I can do visions and then
tranquility
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
so that when I play empty mind
then I have more space for the cards
that was
totally what I was doing
or just you know
the brain you know
see this is this is this is why I was
scared to please play this fire publicly
I have two hands I have mine I'm so big
head I am too ahead
I am two heads ahead of you so far too
ahead I am that yes
[Music]
okay okay
now that we're
um understanding each other
[Music]
um
I feel like I want to save up windmill
strike and this is
hmm I don't know
just a normal strike Maybe
yeah
all right
[Music]
see that's why I eat that's why I am
cleared everything wait we got another
Rush down oh
[Music]
foreign
lesson learned just to get rid of it
since you don't really need any more
questions
oh true
I guess so
an upgrade on follow-up would still be
cool
on the
this one the rest is all upgraded oh my
God
we're just missing one card
after that upgrade yeah I can play it
whenever
nice oh 50.
that's because I'm aggressive don't
worry kiwawa only does 25 damage in
reality
um
[Music]
oh oh two cards oh I didn't see that one
I need block uh cards
[Music]
here's some block
okay
aha I
couldn't even use the news but that's
kind of too late now I guess
I'll wasted
[Music]
should I use my potion
yeah yeah I'll go back into non-wrap of
course
[Music]
oh yeah
it's your lunch
or do can I squeeze in a follow-up yeah
okay
[Music]
I need
uh
maybe one more normal defense
and then vigilance and then we're we're
safe
pretty much
so I wonder is it okay to do one more
like maybe a lesson learned or a
windmill strike
on a normal strike
okay not this one well no there will do
13 okay
and
okay
yeah one HP is
fine no problem
[Music]
oh you want to tantrum first I'm so
sorry
[Music]
I always want to play a Rapture before I
returned from
so close to infinite
[Music]
yeah he weakened me
he weakened and he frailed me what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
foreign
this is just
um a service from you to me so that when
I get my steam deck I can happily play
slate Aspire 10 hours a day in my bed
[Music]
I'm just looking at her
strong guys is not really helping though
she's just weighing
really really heavily on my head
okay we are calm so also he attacks
eight times two so 16.
so we do want to get some defense
as well this turn
I wonder if it's worth using the speed
potion
so that I don't have to use too much
defense cards six weight six six twelve
I guess I would still have to use both
[Music]
yeah
I will drink it
[Music]
I'll drink it
mm-hmm
oh no doors
and then
in the end of course
can I get some more energy somewhere
which is Vigil oh yeah [\h__\h] wait it
gives me 12 block anyway
but I can empty mind my way out of it
[Music]
okay my empty mind is so one okay
follow up
[Music]
yeah
maybe oh rap
me maybe even windmill strike oh you
guys want to still keep it
oh wait no only two only two I have to
do oh no but
why not
um
why can I not just go for this
[Music]
to set up for next turn um
better than being in no stands
well now I have way too much block what
a waste
damn it
[Music]
well it's all right
I might like
wasting so much time with this dude
because he's got so much freaking
HP
[Music]
oh
should I ever play this one
16 windmill
Power Cards
um
which ones are power card skin
like for example
here
[Music]
listen listen not learned wait oh did I
kill him oh I should have learned my
lesson [\h__\h]
rash down Russian is a power card
uh-huh
powers are circular ah
an image
but it might give me a card that's like
not even purple right so it could be
like any really random one
[Music]
flame my next attack deals five
additional damage yeah this looks like a
skip to me
[Music]
buy a Grove
or time to slay the spire
we had Tranquility too
common mistake
in kiwawa stream
intercom
[Music]
where's my tantrum
I got no tantrum
okay
huh
but with the inner peace we might get a
oh yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
there we go eruption
but wait we still need to go back yeah
[Music]
that's
ah we can go back with Tranquility okay
okay okay
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
okay okay okay
[Music]
and a strike
yeah
and one more strike
yeah that's what I would do
okay hey I got him halfway down with my
own choices
so proud
I'm petting my own shoulder right now
good thinking okay you're going down
here is never rush down
and give me some miracles
um
[Music]
from the [\h__\h] out of you
I will
follow that up
26.
I've learned Melissa
I've learned my lesson oh It upgraded
the really pretty rare card what does it
do now it adds three Miracles instead of
two
oh
[Music]
is this better than one of these would
you replace it
we're barely using our potions
the only thing that
I would want is a potion is like a
um a vulnerable one or a weakening one
TBH
okay
oh what is this wave of hand whenever
you gain block
oh
meditate
intercom
no I don't think
no more cards no no but
instead back to 200 monies oh it's the
head
this giant head thinks he's ahead of me
but we've already established I am two
two heads ahead of everybody
I'm not funny
I'm not funny I'm sorry
so bye by the way was there some there's
something oh yeah yeah doesn't he
what was it about this one whenever you
play card
just 10 more damage from attacks this
turn
what
those are oh I wasted some Miracles well
well well
play as many cards as possible avoiding
the damage your cephus receives 30 which
are interesting any card
oh
okay you want you want it all
um
[Music]
I can if I can Loop a lot I could kill
in one turn
calm looping time
throughout the whole deck
can I you should still do rough calming
Cycles you can
oh that would be insane
[Music]
hmm
foreign
[Music]
damage now
um I don't see anything that can help me
with cycling right now so
foreign
at you now
130 holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
um
too many different cars I wish I had a
little bit more Attack cards now
[Music]
when it is up here to strength maybe if
I would have used a strength card
increase the slope oh yeah
[Music]
I use too many
wait this one does
105.
oh then I should have used one more
okay okay good try good try good try
no
we'll try I'll try
yeah yeah
yeah okay okay okay okay so now he's
back to ten uh to zero percent okay
now is it 20 percent
[Music]
can I kill him come on
yeah I'll be
[Music]
which one
skill and Power
skill
inner peace
[Music]
yes
uh
I guess I'll
yeah do this
[Music]
oh yeah right oh yeah right oh oh We're
looping We're looping We're looping
I'm I'm a wrath now so
do me uh
well either inner peace or a vigilance
[Music]
I'm gonna do this one
and this one
and then and then on another
now I'm wrapped so I go back to calm I
could I could
[Music]
oh I could even exit my stance
oh we're good we're good we're good
we're good
[\h__\h] We're looping I'm doing the loafing
endless
just like the Phoenix
never-ending Loop
versus 45
yeah okay
I think no more need for looping
uh
[Music]
dream catcher oh I love dream catchers
whenever you rest oh I'm
I I can still rest at a card but I don't
really need that
but I guess we're taking it for free yay
I did yeah deadhead five what region
region heals HP at the end of your turn
he's sharing regions oh oh that's a nice
healing potion if we ever need it
oh hey the furry is back the one
should I take it now feel for damage
whenever you change stance returns from
the Discord pile to your hand
I don't need it don't need for now yes
yes yes skip
okay no need I'm purposefully rejecting
it
shop
should I get rid of a
block or strike
[Music]
defend
okay
let's see what do we got oh wait I
cannot really afford much none of these
oh man was this good stuff completely
reward screens now contain colors card
whenever you add a power card upgrading
it
oh man that's super amazing
Swift potion might save me
draw free cards
just
[Music]
green
another one of those fatal cards well oh
oh see hey fairy is even on sale
um they really want to get rid of that
card but I'm not taking it I'm not
taking anything here
but
maybe uh one of those
what does hand of great do why you guys
is that a meme
asking what the hand of the great does
it does 20 damage
[Music]
the Yukio meme what where they have a
card that's called the same
pot of greed
and they're just they ask what does pot
of greed do I need to look up this meme
thank you I don't know which potion I
would get rid of maybe um
they all could be useful in the right
situation you know what I don't want to
think too much about it so I'm leaving
and I'm gonna rest yes wow I'm being
forced to rest isn't that
so beautiful I love that so healthy
[Music]
um
interesting dreaming wait is this normal
oh wait it was the drink kind of thing
oh
thank you dream catcher son but I think
we're done with our
Our Deck
um
next door
[Music]
do we want to go to a question mark
wait that's actually useless we just
came from a fireplace
we will go this path I would say
left for the bus oh oh wait I somehow
just did not look at that at all
Gremlin horn whenever an enemy dies gain
energy and draw one card oh
It's Kind of Perfect for our run
let's go
oh more Loop power more power to the
endless cycle of nothingness and damage
yeah
finally some useful relics not all of
these are that ideal but
oh
who is you the Nemesis oh [\h__\h] that
sounds dangerous
he looks dangerous
but he's barely got any HP we could kill
him in one turn Maybe
[Music]
hmm
if we get good cards that is
all right
let's try let's try
um read what he does next turn well yeah
negative effect I don't know what what
exactly it will be probably something
that I'm not gonna be happy about
eh no Wrath
oh
what the [\h__\h]
hmm
[Music]
well
okay I can still do a lot of damage in
either way
strength potion oh
[Music]
I guess I'll just end it with a inner
peace at the end
well
one next turn we're a bit unlucky with
no raft but otherwise I might have
killed him
time this time oh
hey yo hey yo
[Music]
we can do some looping here it's what it
looks like to me
take a sentence Oh [\h__\h] look
we just all damage taking an HP loss to
do this to one this turn no
ah where are my blocks I've got no block
[\h__\h]
I don't have
a [\h__\h]
how do I defend myself now
hmm
[Music]
foreign
that's all I got
six times three eighteen
it's not so bad okay then I I guess
there's no meaning in playing any of
this
Loop to draw more tantrum to draw more
more defense
okay
[Music]
didn't get any
thank you
okay
[Music]
one damage still damaged yeah
I guess okay okay well now
would you please so kindly let me
destroy you
please
oh
foreign
[Music]
yeah but like what's the maximum amount
of cards I can hold
because the burns take up a lot of space
too 10.
one two three four five six seven eight
nine
yeah then
I'll use that
wait
[Music]
um
six seven
okay
and
Play Wind will strike first oh [\h__\h] what
wait how do we where's my refuge
[Music]
I'll go windmill on him now
and then
I'll
no
ah
vigilance
okay ah he's almost
here like the strength potion if it
would have used that
could he have been dead
possibly
will he take one damage only again
intangible yeah but I feel like 12
12 times 1 is possible
[Music]
12 12.
does that mean like for example
one times four okay okay okay
tantrum is four then yeah
all right I don't ride or ride around
so this is
one
[Music]
two
we're doing this right
[Music]
I think I'm doing it right
foreign
[Music]
I think the game is watching the stream
right now
they're watching my stream and they're
like oh oh oh oh let's make it even
better let's make this a perfect run
[Music]
rigged the first time it's rigged in a
in a positive way in my stream usually
if anything's rigged it's only
negatively Explorer Plus
[Music]
play the spider came free and fully
confirmed I would say that's a pretty
strong confirmation
[Music]
turn return this from the discard file
to your hands okay you know what let's
[\h__\h] do it let's do it
mm-hmm okay you are a Pokemon and also a
verbing ripping writing Mass
upon receiving attack damage changes its
intent
every time
okay
games free block block gain increases
the malleable
gain increases as multiple is triggered
let's this dude sounds really [\h__\h]
annoying
resets to free at the start of your turn
I know what's happening I'm just gonna
attack
I don't know what else am I supposed to
do
can only attack oh hey my miracles
[Music]
okay once and C yeah I think that's the
best way of learning
and if it changes its intent every time
we just want to make sure that we end
the turn on having it in uh any
intention besides damaging
mm-hmm
[Music]
it's so damaging but like differently
and it's got the free Block okay
and when I attack again it gets four
blocks
[Music]
all right all right all right all right
random vigilance
let me get into the into the vibe
[Music]
follow up
and then just to get some cards out of
the way
let's try
[Music]
calm
tantrum
[Music]
flurry
oh
[Music]
I'll do another strike
I'll
call oh
flurry before going it before
I'm wasted my after after every stance
change oh but I um
okay I'll think about it again next time
but I thought because it's stronger I
would want it after ref huh
[Music]
yeah I recovered when it changed since
yeah yeah
and um
[Music]
ah I guess like
when I do it now and then I use a
crescendo then I get a new one and then
I get my double damage still but this if
I do it like I did it before I lose this
opportunity for one time six damage
[Music]
uh-huh okay
ha
huh
[Music]
okay okay
really killing it
[Music]
but
um
now I'm out of cards
and the debuff
at the the yeah the intention is
currently at 30 damage
and turn
oh wait what the [\h__\h]
but what if I do another Windmill and it
might go to something else
we can get much worse than 30 damage
yeah and then we can still defend
just defend
[Music]
I know
it looks just about
ah
oh wait is it like
um
it only changes intention for unblocked
damage not for blocked damage
[Music]
foreign
well we're still blocking enough
decent amount
good good good good good good good good
okay and now now now I shall
kill you hopefully
okay I start
live flurry right
[Music]
I go calm
or I go empty mind
or I call lesson learned because it
already kills
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah yeah
was this Shuffle and expunge into a draw
pile you'll nine damage x times
[Music]
we don't play with big sponges
I think
it's fun for some build
not for my deck okay yeah I'm happy I'm
so happy I want to marry my deck
is this mind Bloom while walking and
traversing through the chaos of the
Spire your thoughts suddenly begin to
feel very real
oh imaginings of monsters and riches
begin to manifest themselves into
reality the sensation is quickly
fleeting what do you do I am War find a
boss from Act One obtain where Relic oh
you guys want that one
upgrade the whole guys but we definitely
don't need this
here we don't also don't need that all
right I guess
well not a cute one but the one with the
cute hat
[Music]
nice
nice nice
[\h__\h]
how do I the only way too
make that dog happen is if I really use
up my whole hand at the beginning
hmm
but it was a good starting hand
[Music]
okay okay okay uh I will I will try to
um not take too much time
[Music]
just give me the first step for
tranquility okay I was thinking about
that
you can one turn him yeah
so tall
[Music]
easy
too easy let's get some strikes out of
the way while I am in Wrath oh my God
what
why am I so powerful I don't even need
to Loop
but wait
um
[Music]
stands I know
what the [\h__\h]
there were so many ways to take him out
and that was just one of them
I can no longer become Wicked yo Ginger
I don't like to use ginger too much in
real life but I like this one not that
we get weakened that often but whenever
it happens it's nice to have it
just like it that's me that's me just
like me for real for real
Ginger
[Music]
power God run yeah I mean I'm thinking a
lot of time with it but that's because
I'm learning okay
do we want to go to the shop
or
one of those
what would we even buy we have full
potion slots
my deck
huh we could remove one more strike yeah
but honestly sometimes I'm happy about
having so many strikes on my hands as
many as I have
I feel like I don't even want to remove
them because they can do a lot of damage
too
18 damage oopsie what's happening
oh I went so far back
remove lesson learned oh
oh but even that does some good damage
sometimes okay okay I guess it does
well why not but I guess it's big claws
damage though
really wow
okay
hmm
goodbye you were an amazing card and I
am so grateful
and I love you
okay you've done such a good job at
making this a wonderful run
oh yeah
yeah hello
we've learned our lesson
plenty
hmm all right that's pretty much it the
only thing I could buy is this one
actually
if we want to replace it yeah we've won
this retains
and does four damage twice AKA eight
damage twice
nobody
16. yeah
okay go next the boss is awaiting me
um just missing Rush down
[Music]
just missing Rush down so I'm going for
that first because
of raisins
this one now I get the card back
I hit him again
I'm gonna scroll now
time
okay
that miracle
[Music]
okay Rush down brush down
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
tantrum no
rapture
[Music]
hmm
follow up
dead
number one
down next
I attack
you
oh [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] I'm too powerful I'm too
powerful someone has to
foreign
[Music]
how much I need to nope
no more necessary
okay oh what's this seals 26 damage when
retained lower it's caused by Oneness
combat
okay
26 times two double
no it's a good card though
it would be a good card
Escape okay it takes up some space right
on my hand against so many cards all the
time
okay
last rest for two HP
oh
[Music]
last last option
hey yeah the monsters called and they're
asking if they can have a turn before
you kill them
Savage no but okay I really hate these
two guys they [\h__\h] traumatized me so
I'm kind of scared but we can do it oh
perfect starting end almost almost
perfect
what's up
that was perfect
[Music]
should I use eruption first
play all your potions oh yeah but right
now
not all of them now
[Music]
wait strength stays uh does not get like
that's the strength stay until the end
of the fight
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
oh well we have at the start of each
turn as Smite
deals 12 damage for one cause whenever
card is created during upgrade upcoming
upgraded
lasting game free streaming free
dexterity gain one less energy at the
start of each turn
[Music]
I'm going to start by doing that oh
kill the donuts office wait I just kind
of just went there okay okay I'll move
over to him then okay
[Music]
okay here we go
miracles
[Music]
Rush down
let's see uh
foreign
[Music]
too many options this is what like uh
confuses me sometimes I have too many
options it's not that's so obvious for
me
there's like some offices are slightly
better but does doesn't make the other
ones bad
can't trim to keep looping
[Music]
and now inner peace right
or wait first follow-up oops
oops follow up and now in a piece
is okay
[Music]
or we could bring out a strike first
yeah
in the flurry
and uh
tantrum
[Music]
and
uh
stripe
flurry oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh my God
[Music]
oh my gosh
I'm never ending my turn I'm never
ending my turn
never ending a shift
oh wait now it wouldn't be nice it would
be nice to have this normal strike but
I guess like
vigilance
[Music]
go next
oh my God oh my God I'm gonna [\h__\h]
run around my room if I do this all in
one turn
[Music]
okay wait we are calm right now so let's
um maybe a Rapture yourself into that
and follow it up
and I strike him
maybe calm and then tantrum or eruption
[Music]
huh
but no strike and the flurry
oh my God
I'm sorry and tantrum
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
loaded voted incredible unbelievable
this will be in the history books and in
the newspapers oh my God
that felt so good what those [\h__\h] the
donut [\h__\h] I finally
I got back at them for all the trauma
they applied to me
I have so much confidence now thank you
for giving me confidence
[Music]
gave me obviously so much help but first
try with the Watcher and we cleared it
foreign
continue
you prime your staff with Divine energy
I
damn it this
this thing I could Loop and then
probably kill the thing
realistic man
nice number
222.
[Music]
the boss was like a [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] cockroach maggot
victory victory question mark why am I
dead
why
lies rigged
oh
Overkill cooker wait I want to look at
that that looks so good it said Overkill
and cuckoo combo indeed combo look at
those beautiful cards ooh I want to try
doing like you know this kind of uh The
Watcher run at some point
because I I you we all know that I am
divine
white right Exquisite and divine so I
want to do a Divine run I don't know
what exactly that means but
um
blasphemy is a trap what does that mean
why
ah thank you thank you Divinity is not
triple damage
they're really fun yay more fun than
this
is impossible oh perfect champion
all of those words
praising me and they're yet still not
enough
praise to describe what the events that
just transpired on this legendary stream
of me slaying the Spire I did not only
slay the Spire I ripped it apart and I'm
serving it to my cats for breakfast
[Music]
ah
sheesh
thanks for guiding me in the right
direction everybody
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah I know I know apparently I didn't
Slade Aspire yet but I'm ready I'm so
ready
well
my one turn one run took me so [\h__\h]
long I'm so sorry it seems like I can
really for now for the meantime only the
one play to spy around the pear stream
and when I get a bit better we can maybe
spam the runs maybe we managed to do
two or three runs in one stream
eventually
[Music]
stream next week where we try to finally
clear
the iron clubs because that's the only
one I'm missing and if we're fast then
we can try whatever happens after that
because if I understand correctly after
that you can slay the Spire I don't know
like how much time that takes and all
that
um but that possibly
would be nice and fitting next time
yeah I'm gonna Read Super chats now
though I'm not leaving
so I just think this is a good um point
to end it uh in terms of gameplay yeah
um learn a lot about this game I was
just watching Frost Prime
oh
yeah I wouldn't mind learning like
properly about
how things work
how which build what cards Etc that's
what they can teach me wow foreign
yeah it's so addicting
I've started this whole roguelike Arc
where I play so many Rolex
and damn I can't stop they're really fun
I can't help it
yeah
like dicey dungeons too kind of cute but
then I went back to slay the Spire
because yo yo yo slay the Spire is where
it's at uh I heard there's like a
multiplayer mod I want to play the
multiplayer mod but I don't know if it's
allowed like I heard there's like an
officially
um acknowledged mod is that the one
like I want to play against someone as
if this was like magic
the Gathering
I want I want my deck to go against
someone
it's co-op in multi-mod Co-op Co-op
Co-op
what you're not against each other
ah there's club and versus in the mod
Inspire with friends oh
Cole up I was thinking verses but Co-op
interesting
oh
yeah recently I was making a bit of
Magic the Gathering because I watched um
a video
a YouTube video
damn I forgot what it was about
it was one of those videos that just
tell you about some some things in life
and they use magic cards as a like the
land cards as a graphic example
it's a I had a lot of views but that
reminded me of magic and I'm like ah
nostalgic I want to play
um
what was that about yes cgp gray
I don't know what it was about though
what was that about
oh man I'm surprised you got that yo
I watched some cgp gray videos the other
day but I'm just like what the [\h__\h] I
watched the video about that poem
the behind the scenes of the poem
um
that English poem
yeah Tiffany and yeah hexagons that that
video I watched that one too
I'm I'm I'm I'm
I I don't know what to think about
these videos
so that's the best guns
yeah the videos are definitely very like
high quality and there's like so much
work put into them
so I respect that damn
let me see what did I watch
what
cgp Gray
oh
oh yeah someone dead ruined my life
again
that was the one
about Tiffany I think
how oh how to become Pope
Vatican City explained very interesting
interesting how to become Pope
thank God I'm not planning on becoming
Pope
why Nevada owns less than 20 percent of
Nevada
how to become the British monarch
because I was actually planning on doing
that brief history of the Royal Family
the rings of power explained of course
I'm going to watch that ages ago
metric paper Magic Paper
was the one where I really was like okay
cgp that's where you lose me because
like
I
I got nothing out of this
there's this video where
you would think he I don't know explains
about the history of magic paper or
whatever but no no he just keeps on
folding and unfolding metric paper into
the very tiniest possible size that uh
can be like even thought about in your
tiny
and brain and the biggest size that you
could possibly think about it's such a
weird video
such a weird video
yeah and then for those videos of course
I uh made a little revisit in the
kutzkazakh videos yeah I am
I'd always spirals down to those kind of
videos
you guys know what I'm talking about
right
those kind of like knowledge videos that
make you feel smarter is German by the
way and means uh
a bridge like saying something in a
short tldr
tell VR basically
yes you yes International I I was
just happy to see that they're using a a
German name and and they pronounced it
actually really accurately
you fast track to you being an actual
queen of Pope is to be with Edward who
is Edward because the royal priesthood
of the iron scepter
comes through him what
who's Edward
what from Twilight
Edward's sister
what oh is there is there anyone inside
foreign
huh
glitter you're not really explaining to
me you're not really giving me an answer
there is an Edwin toilet right okay okay
I was not wrong
he's the main vampire okay oh yes okay
see I did not watch [\h__\h] Twilight
I have no knowledge about Twilight I
just know that
it's probably pretty cringe I'm so sorry
[\h__\h] but yeah
I I I I don't think I would take it well
so
um
I think it's the right choice to stay
away from that maybe if I was still like
I don't know
12 or whatever when I was still like
really into Charmed
maybe Twilight would have been good for
me back then but now it's not good for
me
once once you are if you're young
young young teenage girl and you get
into Twilight there's absolutely no way
of saving you you are lost forever
and your life is shaped
and you can never reshape it
once you're lost you lost forever
young teenage girls they all fall into
the Trap of Twilight
did she watch Twilight I guess so she
seems yeah like
she would be into Twilight hmm she's so
sweet
yeah it's too easy to fall into that
trap
[Laughter]
well did they like it
that they like it very much
thank you James that I felt good didn't
it
she was laughing hysterically and that
Twilight let me stay here music video
uh-huh can't relate
they did
they were laughing a lot
it was a comedy stream
okay okay okay so they did not take it
too seriously okay good good then they
might not be lost yet
um
save them save their sanity
I need to watch Elisa let me stay here
Twilight Envy but but uh am I gonna
understand why it's so funny if I didn't
watch Twilight
they've seen free movies they like them
oh
never mind they are lost
I take it back there's still sweet girls
though very sweet girls
[Laughter]
I don't think anyone can save them
laughs
ah
only two silver what movies I don't even
know how many there are anyway let's go
to my office
oh where am I
dead
I want to play more just later more
slayed inspire
but I have to stop
I need to know
when to stop
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
all right guys oopsie we're gonna
reach and demolish the super chats
hopefully they are not endlessly looping
play more respect for the self-control
yeah yeah I deserve that
um
I feel like when they play it privately
I'm in such danger to like
endlessly oh God the eyes are so scary I
just noticed that now
I'm in the big danger to play it
endlessly and and and yeah not being
able to stop myself because when I play
it alone I often fail and and have to
restart and then I'm never satisfied
until I actually win a run which never
happens when I play alone
never happens unless unless maybe the
the poison run
um
poison strategy
I think that's I actually
could be
able to manage alone but yeah
I need you guys I need you guys for
success and then for being able to
escape the addiction forcefully and my
friends mm-hmm
oh shh
yeah next time Ironclad I'm excited
more slate aspire
you need to unlock accuracy for shift ah
was I not ready for a shift build was I
missing like cards or so
um
[Music]
nice
foreign
[Music]
no but uh I I don't want to change it to
Christmas Version yet but I might have
something for in between use
um soonish I forgot that the fact that
last year we apparently used
um like a
a Thanksgiving version but I'm gonna get
like a little bit of an upgraded
uh
Thanksgiving version before
yeah changing yeah yeah
that's where the menu idea for Elena's
Thanksgiving special comes from
um
[Music]
so we have to read super chats from
entropy Center or did I read this
[Music]
oh I sent out the codes for the entropy
Center
to 10 chimpkins
and we're gonna continue playing entry
Center on Sunday
I think I think it was Sunday
[Music]
did you guys see the new schedule
so today we just finished slay the Spire
tomorrow's members only I actually
didn't decide yet what we're doing
I'm not sure
I'll think about it and then the day
after tomorrow Austin snack box with
Bales on her Channel
I hope she likes the things I'll snack
along
and then the rest of the day actually
before the snack box I have a meeting at
like 7 00 a.m and then after the snack
love stream I have a
non-hole lab related uh like tax
person meeting with my tax accountant
person
one last one
yeah so I'm really
um
busy
on that day like around before noon and
around noon
but then after that I'm planning on
testing out like using the rest of the
day to test out my
you know what
the little something that I was sent by
my company
I'm gonna try to set it up so
I needed some time for that
you know what I'm talking about yeah
yeah
hopefully I can make it work
[Music]
Friday
our resting days cause I'm busy on those
days
you will know soon enough why
and then we have trombone champ
because
it's a filler game and then the entropy
Center
yes I know for SCA only entry Center is
bearable oh and the bell the snack box
so sorry I'm sorry
[Music]
hmm
foreign
[Music]
no problem
so that's the schedule for this week and
then you know the week after that I
am
[Music]
just normal
I think pretty normal as normal as it
gets
I think yeah wait not normal week after
that not normal week after that it's two
times total talk that's not that and
it's not quite normal but I'm at least
not going anywhere
foreign
[Music]
very special anniversary episodes
I hope it will go well because I got
some things to prepare for that
[Music]
Pokemon next week Pokemon starts next
week yo I still don't know if I can play
it
I still don't know
um
[Music]
checking
nice bgm you like it thank you Nintendo
games yes but the Pokemon is a different
story that's separate
but yeah
[Music]
I don't know I don't know what the whole
life would do if none of us can play
Pokemon in November
that would be it
a disaster
yeah
I'm I'm so hopeful that they'll come
through of something
okay so let's read some potatoes
I think it's a bit too loud
okay super chats starting from
[Music]
um
I really don't know
[Music]
help
foreign
not Mortuary assistant
[Music]
probably
no I read that one I remember that Patsy
Super Chat
okay entropy Center yeah because
Mortuary assistant had so few that I
just read them really quickly okay
by the way my monitor is flickering
again only the right one
[Music]
I don't know how to fix it
I also reinstalled my
um drivers from my monitors
or my graphics card I don't know which
one that was
[Music]
just I'm just I just won't look at the
right monitor
[Music]
it's not that strong and it's not always
so I will survive
cable
I don't know how to test it out
um
[Music]
resync
I forgot what that was
it gotten worse
um
no
oh no
[Music]
it messes with my refresh rate wait what
am I supposed to do then
turn it on or off
foreign
[Music]
oh interesting one of my monitors might
really be DisplayPort
get a new GPU
tell me in
a tweet
[Music]
check cables okay oh well okay
um
foreign
computer abuse I do not support that
no not in this apartment no no no no
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chair no a
rainbow
oh boy to celebrate my birthday I will
follow the venerable whole life
tradition of offering my gift funds to
my own streaming team right oh you did
not have to presenting to you this token
of appreciation and admiration is after
all the greatest gift I could think of
for myself stop up no
can't be true you have to treat yourself
free virtual girls chat here yes right
here like right here not anywhere else
here
here you can chat with me for free
I love the Bots
[Music]
of course this can never compensate you
for your ceaseless efforts in blessing
the internet with your content on a near
daily basis the only thing I could ever
wish for is for you to take more time to
rest and enjoy the old plan world
oh you're the sweetest
candy
oh
yeah they wanna meet me
famous
[Music]
it looks great by the way the demo was
super fun and you are more than up for
the challenge just has the potential to
become it's legendary as important
playful can't wait to watch The Vault
later thank you I think so Patrol
I feel like it's pretty much
right up there
[Music]
um
I love the entropy Center I I hope that
many people play it and give it lots of
good reviews online yeah thank you
Flappy boy for being such a great
and follower and fan and support her
thank you so much I wish you all the
best for your birthday even though I'm a
few days late but congratulations
[Music]
foreign
I hope I'm not wrong
but congratulations
I hope the birthday was really really
special and enjoyable for you yes yes
yes okay yes yes
thank you thank you
and
it's really sweet
that you want to you know give all your
appreciation and yeah money to me but
don't forget to
give something to yourself too I'm sure
there's something you want for yourself
[Music]
something that would make you happy
something an object
so don't forget about yourself yeah
number one priority
thank you for everything
[Music]
and celebrities beats around a wonderful
kfp fan panel yo yo yo yo yo where's the
recording
and I got to meet so many fun people in
and out of campaign including some of
your our competition at KFC if you want
to play Magic the Gathering arena is
free and very fun we'd love to see it oh
wait this is from me why is this uh
mixed in here
that's the Slate Aspire Super Chat doll
oops it's just in the middle of the
entropy Center super chance makes no
sense
yeah sometimes YouTube studio is a bit
drunk
yeah but where is the recording I really
want to watch it
I want to say what propaganda you guys
are
um spreading over there without my
knowledge and my approval
[Music]
did it get recorded did anyone record it
at all
only facts hopefully they're good facts
he was working on it okay okay okay then
let me know let me know when it's
available okay I really want to watch it
I don't think we recorded sorry oh oh
shut your mouth of course you did
see he recorded it himself they say
so
don't you destroy my hopes
don't you dare
I will get that recording
in some way and if there if the
recording is lost then I demand that it
will be reenacted
[Music]
as if it was a convention
with an audience possibly preferably
[Music]
and recorded at that time
hand over the recording or else
kfbcon I mean sure would be nice but
it's kfbcon if you wanted to be
[Music]
okay so anyway thank you general for the
pinky and I'm glad you guys were rapping
at yomakon once again thank you thank
you
unfortunately this time I couldn't be a
yomicon was I not there like last year
but some other
um whole life members were at Yuma con
right like in not not in person but as a
guest
right
yeah I think I was there last year yeah
and I'm just here with someone else
[Music]
and foreign
the Twilight combo
[Music]
all right I hope you guys enjoyed
yourselves
be careful when you go to conventions
but also paint everything Orange
okay that's your mission
thank you
[Music]
every time I see a Korean Super Chat
I hate myself
for not
for not spending all my time
studying Korean
I need to
at least
a little bit
[Music]
I really wanted to
it's not over yet the year's not over
not over yet
I can still start again restart because
like I already forgot everything I
learned basically
you really have to keep it up
take this from someone who knows a
couple languages fluently if you start
learning a language
you really have to keep it up for like
several weeks and months
yeah otherwise you're gonna quickly
forget what you learned
[Music]
I guess I guess as a bird I am just
naturally
incapable of learning more than three
languages
Tony is burp and I am Tori
um
not everything is like riding a bike
yeah
I mean I think once you get to a search
and really fluent level of a language
then you can pretty much stop studying
and you won't really forget it that's at
least my case for
um Japanese
hmm
anyway J1 says thank you it's been a
year since I joined KFC wow a year
already
and sent you my first ever Super Chat
for my birthday I can't forget every
single moment we spent together this
year oh I'll keep my best supporting you
love you kiwawa P.S can I get the
employee number as a birthday person of
course
of course
ah your birthday
happy birthday
[Music]
day one
my dear Happy Birthday
[Music]
I wish you all the best
please stay happy and healthy and thank
you for supporting me for such a long
time you your number will be
[Music]
one
is this number taken because you're J1
I'll give you one one
one one
one one one one one one one one
three ones
is it taken
[Music]
it's free
nice
okay that's your number enjoy
it's a cool number
if it's taken then we'll do one one one
but that's not today's date yeah I was
so close to giving
that today's date but I felt like you
guys gonna
[Music]
be like
call me out on that so
I went for something else
oh one one is free one one one one the
second okay then you get one one
congratulations
[Music]
the word entropy describes that when
there are two entities at a different
energy level there would be a tendency
for the energy to flow from high to low
until they are even
and no it has nothing to do with this
game
sure
if it has nothing to do with this game
then why did they call it entropy Center
[Music]
maybe it does have something to do with
that
I don't know about that description
multiple definitions
oh okay just sounds like a cool science
team word yeah okay I get that sometimes
you just want to call things some cool
science in word or German word a lot of
people especially like in Japanese anime
and so on they like to give characters
cool German names or songs cool German
titles
or Country School German names or
chernibial attacks
cool German names
what is it about German it's really not
that cool this language is really not
that cool I'm telling you from someone
with a German ear
it's not that cool
[Music]
yeah yeah it's very common
I guess I guess I'm flattered
Mystic has big stone kitchen Randy IJ
thank you now reads dankishun
ah yeah okay I I would say also it
depends on the rice you do not wash rice
when you're making risotto since you
need to dirt aka the excess starch from
the rice to make it properly
there you go so risotto is an exception
that's okay I accept that
thank you
I'm honestly
very very very honored that you still
after all this time
send those wordless silent super chats
and support me for such a long time
thank you
so loyal
and you're still not sick of me thank
you how can I thank you enough
[Music]
thank you
you're an angel
our room flow and Danke Schoen
and the game will create action Lord
canister attack
vlk donation
[Music]
thank you for the pinky keep it up thank
you watching you play puzzle games it's
always so much fun please don't be so
hard on yourself you always do quite
well at these solo games thank you they
are in the entropy Center I was able to
play like mostly by myself without
relying on the chat
figure it out most of it myself unlike
insulator spire
[Music]
yeah so I'm quite happy with that um I
felt
I'm pretty good about that
um
I mean
I do think the puzzles are easier than
portal
but still even in Portal I was like even
with simple puzzles I was having issues
foreign
just a short City trip
but I hope she will enjoy it we're gonna
go eat some really yummy food
and do some sightseeing the sightseeing
is mostly for me and the food is mostly
for her because she's already seen the
places that we're gonna go to I think
well it's been a long time so I think
she'll enjoy seeing it
as again as well
hmm
yeah
gonna Flex her Italian yeah and I'm
gonna laugh at her for the fact that she
said she claimed she claimed that her
Italian was so good and then it turns
out it wasn't that good after all
we'll see we'll see she wants to flex it
on me then all right Flex it Flex it
show me what you got Mommy
[Music]
where's your Italian
how about my Italian
it's not so bad either I can say a lot
of like tourism Hotel related Italian
words and that's
actually as a tourist very useful and
the only Italian you need most of the
time
and I survived my last trip to Italy
quite well
[Music]
it was um
not perfect but that's not because I was
lacking language skills but just because
you know the whole disaster going to the
convention where the convention didn't
happen
um
other than the neck oh that was Grease
You're mixing something up that was
Greece
then you get sunburn in Italy no no no
the recent trip the recent Italy trip
with the convention that was uh all
perfect pretty much I did not get a
sunburn not that I remember
um probably
I think I got like a decent tan but no
big sunburn
[Music]
sunburn was Maldives hell yeah that was
a bad sunburn
oh wow wow wow
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah I probably
increased the chance of me getting skin
cancer
sometime in my life by about 25 percent
[Music]
yeah yeah in Italy I was the only one
the only one who did not get a sunburn
out of my friends
yeah because I I purposefully prepared
uh the 100 100 SPF uh sunscreen that I
got from America
[Music]
wow oh yeah and everyone everyone was
like okay Wawa can I use that
no I didn't have that much I need more
American kfp sent me more of that
sunscreen because I can't find it here
I guess it should exist in some form but
it's more expensive I feel like here oh
well it's not that urgent it's winter
time now anyway and I don't have time to
go to a tropical country this winter
unfortunately
um
[Music]
can't send packages still what what
Oh you mean like into a whole life in
general yeah
[Music]
um
you have a good it's not that urgent but
yeah Bali you want to go
[Music]
back
[Applause]
Jacob 47.
kwj thank you thank you
that was Japanese yeah
um
[Music]
and then we have some flush chats thank
you guys for the Flash
and blue super chats thank you thank you
soon
um
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
hey boss can we get beaches and vacation
areas installed in various locations at
KFC uh
I work space for that it's a normal like
fast forward the restaurant size where
the hell am I supposed to squeeze in
those beaches no
no but you're welcome to try to relocate
yourself to a kfp that's close to a
beach I guess
sounds like a you problem yeah
oh thank you for the support take us
monkey thank you soon
[Music]
yeah my streams have been so long and
super Center's dream was six hours long
minimum damn
I wonder if we can finish it on Sunday
I hope so would be nice
[Music]
what the beep you guys don't know I've
been beeping out that name since like
I know at least a year every time I read
that name I'm beeping it
[Music]
I have to
I'm forced to
it's a thing that name must not be said
out loud
[Music]
it's too vulgar
I I cannot say what it means I cannot
say what it says
I can't
it's impossible because if I say it I'll
get beat
can't help it
[Music]
um
oh
no I have not thought about getting my
own designs on Amazon yet
but yeah I said we talked a little bit
about like whether or not it would be
possible
for Ian like merch like like kind of
like the birthday Merchant stuff to be
on Amazon not like that unfortunately
but I'm sure there will be more
instances like the Halloween merch where
we can put something up on Amazon and
make it so that it's easily accessible
for everybody
um
foreign
[Music]
the first miff T-shirt oh
interesting but at the same time like
reselling it now kind of makes the ones
that have that first t-shirt now less
special
I
I almost wanted to be
stuff like that forever
[Music]
that makes its value also much higher
yeah the one with my artwork yeah maybe
maybe yeah maybe in a different color
like it was black right black only how
about we sell it in white
and then you can still distinct
you kind of get like a different version
of the first ever t-shirt
but you can still see the difference
between the ones who got it the first
time
[Music]
I don't know how much demands there
would be for it but
I'm gonna note it note to Denmark
reselling first ever myth t-shirt the
one I drew
in different color to differentiate from
first edition
on Amazon demand
funk
[Music]
make believe
land thank you for the pinky I am now
AKO Tony thank you for being a part of
my life I've spent two years of you and
I like to spend so many more I love you
always also I think it's about time so
may I have please have an appointment
why don't you why don't you have one
number yet
[Music]
thank you for still being so supportive
always after all this time
all of you who are always here always
here for me no matter what I do thank
you so much
don't leave me
love kiwawa forever okay
[Music]
thank you
free cases for everyone
[Music]
a couple more
foreign
[Music]
I like that guarantee also Julia blunder
your number
[Music]
you strike me as a six six eight
free
[Music]
I feel it you are a 683
enjoy the number
that that was based on nothing I really
just felt like
those are the numbers you'd have thunder
sounds like they need a number that's
spicy
[Music]
sharp I don't know how to explain that
but the number is eight six and three or
six eight and three they feel sharp and
spicy to me
ah
don't know how to explain
[Music]
it is what it is
six eight three
that is nine
which
thank you for the recipe
thanks for the stream today I have to go
to work see you next time stream thank
you buddy
I know all these streams are at a really
shitty time for you
thank you so much for trying your best
to make it to the streams every time
fighting I hope you're doing well you
buddy
and good luck at work always
I hope it's not too stressful
[Music]
um
what's up was that an emoji Maybe
in any case you're not making proper
effective
efficient use of
the letters you could be using to tell
me how much you love me Sanji Sean
[Music]
where is the love
yo what's up fam no no no no no no no no
no
I need you to write something proper in
your super chats next time
we need to communicate where is the love
[Music]
where is the love where is the love the
love the love
I'm counting on you for next time
[Music]
oh another Pinky
the company has arrived and turned on
the stream please send me a message of
denounce so that I can be strong today
as well potential oh I think this means
that you arrived at your job and you
turned on the stream on the side
ah so you can watch Me While working too
well that's perfect
well
a message of support I suppose
what do you mean denounce denounce
sounds more like negative
do you love me
yeah
oh
when you just try your best to watch me
at work I know and if you want to be
denounced then you gotta tell your your
boss over there to denounce you
well now
um
[Music]
foreign
but I had intense pain on my feet
because of some ligament that would
swell up but injection fixed that I
think it's possible to get it in other
parts of your body oh yeah I hear about
like friends going to the top doctor
complaining about pain and getting an
injection and suddenly you have all this
pain relieved all the time but so far no
doctor ever thought of doing that to me
I don't know why
I still think that doctors don't take me
seriously because
I'm a relatively young looking girl so
they ultimately expect that I should be
healthy it's so weird like you would
think a doctor would at least not have
that that weird bias
um but yeah
I'm
next time I go to a doctor I'm gonna
look for a different one anyway
I don't want to go back to the
um other one
I don't like to
start from zero again but
I don't think this one was doing it for
me it was weird
hate shopping for Darkness me too well
dogs don't take women's seriously um
for the year to get her neck pain
diagnosed oh my God what was the
diagnosis and which doctor can I go
there too
[Music]
hmm
yeah yeah they do have a bias
[Music]
because like they they literally make it
vocal to me
sometimes they would mention stuff like
oh but you're so young
[Music]
yeah wait that should not be like
even part of the discussion it doesn't
matter
it doesn't [\h__\h] matter I can still be
in very much pain for very many years
like
matter
yeah we got problems too man
and By ignoring that you're just making
it worse every year and eventually I
will be 50 and then you're finally
taking me seriously but this all could
have been avoided if we would have
probably taken care of it when I was
younger
[Music]
um
exactly
what exactly are you familiar that's
what I'm saying
claim is because you work harder than
them
yeah but I tell them that for my job I
sit mostly in front of a computer and
then they just kind of
the the one thing they always I guess
assume is that okay it's like the like
the typical office back problems
[Music]
which I mean surely is like mixed in
there but
I feel like that's a bit more than that
oh well oh well
[Music]
yeah yeah I always explained that my
pain has a long long history and that
there's like two separate things going
on but I feel like they always just put
it in one box and then they're like
whatever
send them to a physical therapy I've
been through
some burpees and last time I even told
them oh yo I just came out of a physical
therapy literally like a few days ago
just ended one that was going on for a
couple weeks
it did not help so far and this is like
the 10th time I went to one so can we
like maybe do something else find a
different solution oh no
one else do we have a physical therapy
or
oh man
yeah no one really bothers trying to
really figure out what it is
but yeah you remember that
this whole year I wasted so much time
waiting for that one appointment then it
overlapped with my America trip so I had
to move it again for uh the next
appointment was like I don't know four
or five months later and that was like
last month or the month before
so I wasted most of my year waiting for
that [\h__\h] and
I went there and literally all it was
was them telling me Oh well yeah so your
blood is fine
so can't help you here you don't have
the Rheumatic disease or whatever at
least yeah cool good to know but
couldn't you have sent me a [\h__\h]
email about that wouldn't that have been
so much more efficient for both of us
[Music]
literally looks so
useless so unnecessary I could have gone
to a million doctors in those
10 months or so of waiting time
[Music]
so now I'm taking
like I I have to be honest like that
destroyed my motivation again of trying
to get behind this [\h__\h]
so yeah I'm currently not really going
after any solution right now
I'll get back into it probably
eventually because the pain is killing
me and recently it's been even more
painful than usual
my left shoulder is like it feels
so
painful to lie on my left side
at night
[Music]
yeah I'm in constant pain which is cool
ah it sucks but
an MRI on the shoulder no the only thing
even though like at the doctor I would
say like it's like from neck to shoulder
kind of like even extending a little bit
to the upper arm area
um they only ever made one uh
what do you call it again like the scan
not an MRI though I think off
a really close-up section of my
um an x-ray yeah
of
[Music]
well I don't know how to call that
section but if the shoulder was not
really visible at all
so
yeah they made that and then I had to
bring that to the doctor and they said
well you know this and that nothing
special
it's basically like a little bit lower
um then the top of the neck I think the
neck was mostly included
though
but not much of the shoulders
sounds very minimum try to fix it yeah
yeah
I I'm so frustrated about this I I
just expects to live like this for the
rest of my life oh yeah kind of like the
collarbone but like the back side
um
well
so I was thinking when I saw that well
shouldn't you have taken at least a
bigger section
[Music]
of an x-ray like maybe the shoulder even
separately I don't care if you can't
make bigger ones but
the I feel like the shoulder the left
shoulder would have been necessary
because I I
mentioned it quite a lot but it feels
like it comes from my left shoulder
and extends to the neck and the upper
arm
but okay
[Music]
yeah
and then obviously like I I I I'm not a
doctor
so and and doctors would probably not
even want to hear from me when if I go
there and say yo I want this and this
and this they would probably be like
well we're the [\h__\h] doctor not you so
[\h__\h] you stupid little girl
you can't tell us what to do you will
just go and take another physical
therapy
you know what for now for now you just
go physical therapy and then come back
later in two months time when you're
done with that and we'll talk about it
again
it's always the same [\h__\h]
I was just saying
well I will
get back into it and start another try
sometime eventually I another fight back
like what am I supposed to say
I I already tried communicating that
you know certain things just didn't work
and I've been dealing with this for
years and I went to several doctors and
I'm just like so sick of this
and yeah
I've tried
[Music]
um
while
it starts to my heart from houses
foreign
[Music]
Mickey and snipped
see how cool it sounds what my German
[Music]
y
oh nine oh nine
[Music]
yeah yeah it's important saving the
house on Spectrum
yeah anyway uh uh where was I oh
black
thing while you've been streaming I used
to misbehave when I was always around
can you pretend to be mad at me and
pretend to throw me in the usual room so
I can feel nostalgic
Maybe you wouldn't have to feel like
that if you would come to my stream and
and and act like that again so I can
realistically throw you in the usual
room again ah but okay I just assume
that you just
can't time wise launch my streams
anymore I guess whatever sure whatever
whatever it's not like I care I
mean if you're here or not so
you might as well just go to the usual
room
[Music]
this doesn't work like that
I I can't
[Music]
I can't be so serious about it you have
to make me actually angry
God by not being here
not making me angry
One does not simply ask to go to the
usual room
anyway thank you for the pinky though
well at least you didn't forget about me
thank you
what happens
[Music]
and that's it for the entropy Center
thank you guys now I'm gonna read
Luigi's Mansion Super Chat
[Music]
well
yeah I also changed the thumbnail
of the second Luigi's Mansion stream
um
looks really good
[Music]
the game of reduction Sean Eon and thank
you
you also bucket now nice congratulations
thank you
[Music]
nice
nice bucket
oh no no nice bucket nice boob nice nice
Revival burp
ing for the rest of the chat
or salute bus glad to see you today it's
chilly here so the kids are extra cuddly
is also very very cuddly
so cuddly I can't stop coddling that one
they're like and I'm like
as you can see I can't stop so I have
them with me here right now hmm
[Music]
kg you still call them Phoebe and
chunkers like who the [\h__\h] is Phoebe
chunkers with you I can still you know
look past that mistake but who the [\h__\h]
is Phoebe
smoothie
[Music]
her name's smoothie
not Phoebe how would you get to to
Phoebe I don't understand
how what kind of autocorrect is that
it's not the first time you called her
Phoebe
your cat is sleeping on your belly right
now oh oh oh
I want that too
cozy
Tonto and Kyle who the [\h__\h] are
[Music]
[\h__\h] right good morning hello
hello good morning
smelly cat smelling cat what are they
feeding you Smelly Cat Smelly Cat it's
not your fault
[Music]
thank you
stop
my cats will eat you
they love chicken
I'm messing around with their names
you will regret it
thank you spanking High
kfb Thailand thank you soon again
thank you for the Super Chat
Mr kensburg
[Music]
um Mac Chris Taylor language
Tyler km
[Music]
there's a sub mechanophobia a fear of
underwater man-made objects so like
sub submarines
[Music]
ooh boats
Well normally you don't really
have to see them much so oh sunken ships
a fear of sunken ships
hmm I guess because it's like spooky
like thinking about how they sunk
anything submerged
interesting well that feels like it
wouldn't really affect you much in real
life though
hello guys
Joelle thank you thank you sir
thank you
cool name
cool German name here Canadian dude
using a cool German name as their
YouTube name
uh German language
once again follow me everywhere
but that's a cool word actually
[Music]
foreign
thank you
okay a horse for
certain well-behaved girl with the 50k
yo I think she can buy herself the horse
now
that's a good thing about whole life
I think she has the funds to buy herself
a horse if she really wants one and the
violin and whatever she wants yeah
[Music]
it's not the same
let me out of
[Music]
don't don't don't don't remind her of my
it was not
this it was not a serious promise
just forget about it just forget about
it
I will give her a small
um puppet toys
or one of those
he's really small right so how about I
just give it one of those like wobbly
horse that you can like sit on and and
hold on to you know those wooden horses
that go like
you know what I mean yeah
yeah wouldn't that be so cute
she can sit on that like a toddler
wouldn't that be so adorable
[Music]
and sit on it while she's streaming it
will kind of be like one of those yoga
balls that are good to sit on every once
in a while
because you wobble wobble
wobble wobble
yeah I never specified a real living
horse
Mr Bubbles thank you and Justin number
passion thank you soon
[Music]
thank you
motion thank you soon
[Music]
Lux and horror thank you honor thank you
soon May believe
just a friendly smiley face thank you
thank you I don't know why
why I deserve such a simple but kind and
generous super chat but I appreciate it
thank you
[Music]
penguin induction what thank you soon
what
yokia that's nearly that time of the
year again have you picked out your
annual Rammstein song yet I'm kidding
those in still has didn't sit too well
with you what did I ever say that I will
sing a Rammstein song once per year
foreign
[Music]
I did oh ironically saying you did would
be Du Hast in German
the answer would be it was ironically
uh did I do that really
did I say that oh my God I don't want to
and Alana
actually just yesterday when I was
watching Gilmore Girls there was one
episode
um where like the ex-husband of loreline
Gilmore he's in the car and he turns on
the music and it's Du Hast and I'm like
uh of course of course it's too hot
because
everyone thinks Ramstein is so cool but
they're not not as cool as Chihuahua
listen to Four Blood instead
that would be so much better for all of
us
for blood is so much more cultured
um
[Music]
boohoo 723 Don
kitchens
thank you for the recipe chats so what
uh what are you what you're saying is
Myron Luigi you speak Marlene English
because that's the best English in all
of her life I already answered this one
but not quite not quite I think Buddy
he has a bit more vocabulary than Mario
and Luigi
I will have to give her credit for that
credit for credit is due
passion English that's super senpai
as soon as senpai
is one of the members in whole life
English who speaks the best in whole
life English whole life Japan will speak
the best English next to hajama
um she just need confidence
she doesn't believe in her English
skills but they're they're still
somewhere down there
I know it
I think worms proved it yeah that she
could keep up with us yeah
and
[Music]
Maybelline thank you
oh yeah of course yeah
[Music]
I went to sleep woke up and came out is
still streaming I will be heading out
now we'll watch the Vlog when I'm back
and I got you a message I will spread
the word of Kiwa when I go to Austria
I have to have a good rest of this thank
you you know what you should not only
spread the word of kiwawa in Austria but
also in your home country as well yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
well thank you for watching the Vlogs uh
no there was a lot to catch up on
because all the Luigi's um streams were
so long
but at least you can't complain about a
lack of content right
and I think the Luigi's mentioned the
streams were all pretty entertaining so
I hope you guys are enjoying the vods
please watch what everyone if you missed
the stream go go go watch what you have
and Wednesday Thursday I think more than
enough time to watch all the Vlogs you
missed go go go go go go
I will test you I will quiz you when I'm
back
okay
if you're already up to date then it's
cool
well if you're not then you better catch
up I will quiz you and if you fail you
know where you're going
foreign
[Music]
at least that Disco
make me so salty that made me so
but yeah the invention of weeboo bridge
[Music]
I think that was just meant to be
Destiny yeah
I'm glad some other YouTubers picked it
up and made some tweets about hashtag V
booper
and posted close-ups of their boobies
that was nice
you're welcome I think it just won't
work
[Music]
congrats on clearing the game absolutely
adored this play for from start to
finish even saw a few new tricks and an
incredible final hit yeah
let's try my next run and motivated me
to hunt down all the gems and the pools
oh thank you so much for playing also
you didn't do that before well
have fun with that they're actually a
pretty pretty relatively easy to find
not so impossible
I'm getting more and more into deeply
um
like trying to collect everything in all
kinds of games
it's quite addicting
hmm
a little behind of that trend
what trend
the reboot by trend
completionist oh okay well I won't
become completionist
sorry guys I suddenly feel like so tired
my energy is gone
[Music]
family
I have to cook
after this
[Music]
my the meat I have to cook today it
expired yesterday but it's still fine
right
should be fine
it's pork I think
it's probably fine yeah
[Music]
like how could how can they determine
what exact day
[Music]
where they say okay this is the day
where this this goes bad
impossible
[Music]
oh
I will smell it but
I think it's fine yeah
uh Alphonse thank you for the rest of
the 10. thank you so much for playing
the game I worked on kiwawa
what
[Music]
do you mean you worked on it
I'm looking at the channel right now
[Music]
foreign
or like a localizer or something like
that
[Music]
you can't just write that in a Super
Chat and then leave me at that what a
cliffhanger what the [\h__\h]
Escape
[Music]
Alphonse Luigi's
Mansion free
[Music]
I mean that's probably just like a wait
Alphonse do is known for Metroid Prime
Federation Force Mario Strikers badly
glue just mentioned free
[Music]
quality assurance tester
with quality insurance hey I'm back oh
oh I was gone
wait quality assurance tester
someone who tests the game
not quite a death
but still cool
[Music]
uh I was talking to myself for how long
what the [\h__\h]
probably not that long well that was in
the meantime I was just looking up that
person
um
well thanks to you
I found
probably almost no bucks
did I find the bank
or anything weird
I don't remember I already forgot if I
found something and I already forgot
yo what the [\h__\h] just a disco fight was
so like what the [\h__\h]
ah the girls disappeared yeah but I
don't know if that was normal it felt a
little bit off but she came back so
she came back so all is good
um
she was just out get a sandwich in yeah
I got stuck behind something for a
minute
oh
my gosh I escaped right nope no I had to
restart the game in that moment yeah
yeah yeah yeah I did get properly stuck
at some point
Alphonse next time you gotta look a bit
closer for those bugs
just kidding good job thanks for your
support thank you
[Music]
again
those Angel represented yeah but only
just Mansion also there was one moment
where I restarted I think
[Music]
language
thank you
I don't know
[Music]
wanted to say that he was honored to
fight in front of you Hotel business
isn't booming just yet but we got our
first love
why did my brain just auto correct first
hotel guest into First Love Hotel again
I don't know why
[Music]
I guess that after we destroyed it once
it was turned into a love Hotel
to maximize
um profits
we got our
hotel guest with the initials of yls I
feel like it's a Vaseline egg though
with all ghosts
Wireless who is that who is that
[Music]
could that be there's so many yls in the
chat All of You Are Wireless
you you are a little [\h__\h] and you are a
little [\h__\h] and you are a little [\h__\h]
and you too
could be any of you guys
hmm
[Music]
you're a big [\h__\h] no you're a little
[\h__\h]
saying you're a big [\h__\h] that takes the
cuteness out of it so
can't be a big [\h__\h] you are a little
[\h__\h]
doesn't sound good
otherwise
anyway thank you gentlemen
thank you or should I say guiji
thank you soon for the support I'm glad
you enjoyed this little playthrough
maybe one day one day I can play the
GameCube version someday not anytime
soon but if I ever lack a game maybe
next Halloween I can pick up the
GameCube version perhaps
[Music]
um
or is that name I think that's nape
just checking yeah lip comes
thank you looking for the top thank you
that's it for the Luigi's Mansion stream
triple chat
I uh I'm tired and my throat hurts so
I'm gonna end it here it's already long
enough anyway
tomorrow Members Only
and then Bale's Channel and then two
days off this is actually a problem for
my channel
because that means for non-members my
channel will have no update for like
four days I don't like that maybe I'll I
can upload like a clip or something not
a clip but like a
some
something small
I don't like there being no upload for
four days algorithm will be very sad
[Music]
very sad Uncle Rhythm yeah and I'm super
video I can do another zoo video Maybe
what are we doing for members
[Music]
wake up I don't know now I don't want to
think about it
I wanna just make dinner and then go to
sleep
[Music]
hopefully I'm gonna play a game or
something
okay thank you for understanding
so I just fire again
Maybe
I can't I can't possibly play this fire
again
[Music]
no I know most of you enjoy satisfire
but I'm sure there's some people who
don't like it that much so you know for
those people
I should try to not spam it too much
yeah
I'll find something else
okay I'll go make food now
[Music]
now
um
thank you guys very much for watching
and helping me clear The Watcher
wow it was a lot of fun
um I think I can do quite well with that
character on my own from now on
pretty easy
felt quite a bit easier than certain
other characters
like the one with the orbs
that one was fun too though they're all
fun
[Music]
um
well design characters yeah then there
needs to be more
[Music]
I want more
thank you guys for watching so I'm kind
of low energy right now sorry about that
tired I'm so tired right now what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
they probably working on sale Inspire 2.
that would be so cool
um
[Music]
wow okay
bye-bye what in Germany we say good
enough
[Music]
where's me
foreign
[Music]