[Music]
pirate sorry hello hello and a Merry
Christmas to everybody not yet not yet
Merry Christmas but happy not yet yeah
almost almost there kind of
kids
[Music]
everyone hope you guys are doing well
and enjoying the cold season if you're
in Australia New Zealand never mind
I hope you're enjoying the warm season
yeah it's uh which day is this I think
this is day nine of the Advent calendar
presented to you by
morning right next to me hey hey
what to do for this one and then I got
an idea because I wanted to play a
little game so I thought of a
um a kind of Family Feud Style game that
we can play with us too it will be uh
two actually four rounds I guess and
um and I gave Cali two questions with
already some answers that I didn't see
and I have to quit no four four each I
have four questions she has four
questions for one another with the
answers and we're gonna try to guess if
the answers are in the most popular your
answers up there five ounces each each
of us get 10 guesses and then at the end
we'll see how many of us how many points
we get how many questions and answers we
got right yeah no questions all the
answers yeah it says spontaneous uh game
idea but I think it will go well it's
actually Christmas themed so yeah it's
super creative I like it last time I
just kind of I just kind of wrapped and
sang about how I forgot to turn on my
mic last time so I'm I'm glad we're
doing something kind of cool and
game-like yeah she's actually really
neat yes yes everyone so far has been
doing so is creative cute things so yeah
yeah like last time uh crony and and
fauna were making cookies it was really
cute Ah that's so cute I love that and I
gotta step up my game if I want to do
another one of these no no you still
have any chances there's so many days
until Christmas
um
so let's get started let's do it I will
ask you
uh two questions first all right let's
see how far we get
I'm ready I got this question number one
yeah
[Music]
who is the hardest person to shop for
oh okay for Christmas presents I guess
you know
gotcha how many guesses do I get a 10
and there's five advantages that I would
like you to lock in
all right sounds good let's see all
right first thing first guess is your
boss
one of the answers you're correct me
yeah
wow I love Family Feud all right let's
see the next stop all right now it's
gonna get harder
okay let's see who else is hard to shop
for
um distance relative
like a cousin if I have to be more
specific
now that's not on here unfortunately
all right I gotta put it on here
okay how about
um your child
no
all right let's see how about
[Music]
um your grandparents
do I need any more specific no no no
how many guesses has this been four I
think it's been about four yeah you got
one right okay okay you can still do it
you can still do it
even acquaintances
um no what about people you just met
what the
how many types of people are there in
this world that you could know
five more five more okay let me really
really kind of think yes
um all right thank you would you even
buy gifts for is the thing
um you had one accent I was kind of
close to an answer that is on here
so the question is who is it most
difficult to buy gifts for yeah
your significant other
which means like
my friend or girlfriend or even
your your spouse yes
house really it's that hard I can't
imagine it being that hard but okay
apparently apparently I mean you would
probably know that person pretty well so
it shouldn't be too hard but oh well
yeah I get I guess so maybe some people
just have a hard time all right you have
four more guesses and there's three more
answers on here
okay okay let me see
your boss uh how about co-worker
[Music]
no co-workers I guess nobody wants to
even think about getting co-workers
presents they don't even consider it
I feel like you would get one forever
for your your co-worker maybe sometimes
but I mean I uh you're more than just a
co-worker qo I'd get you for Christmas
but yeah I think this is different I
would think like if somebody works at
like a restaurant or so then that'd be
kind of weird yeah maybe yeah not the
kind of cool okay give someone a gift
too but I can't imagine yeah giving a
fellow waiter or a waitress a Christmas
gift it is kind of weird oh let's see
good buddies but yeah three more guesses
okay
[Music]
um let's see how about
um your sibling
brother sister damn it lots of
shut up I don't know what they're
talking about I know right I feel like I
can never buy anything for my little
sister
because she's always like oh that's cool
Cali but you know
we should just give me money something
like that
okay
um how about
[Music]
okay
um maybe think of not just like you know
types of people but also uh age classes
oh I see big help teenagers
yeah teenagers
nice that was a good hint and last one
I'm gonna say
[Music]
um
let's see
babies
but you got three points uh there you
have wrote I wrote it down three points
for that question all right cool now we
turn it around and you give me a
question
all right sounds good here is your
Christmas Family Feud question number
one name a gift that's hard to wrap oh
bicycle
that yes correct ding ding ding bicycle
what else
[Music]
a pet an animal
yes correct
um
[Music]
I mean I wouldn't even try to wrap an
animal obviously yeah not very nice for
the pet
yeah and too obvious a house
let's see
um nope no house definitely would be
difficult there sure would be I think I
couldn't really put any wrapping paper
on it who buys a house for Christmas for
someone it has some really really rich
persons really really rich person a car
yes a car correct oh my God look at it
wait I think I guessed
four times because one was wrong right
yes you've got you guessed four times
and you got three correct holy okay
I'm doing quite well
uh so I have uh six more guesses left
um yeah we had a car animal
and bicycle bicycle
um
[Music]
maybe something liquid but
because that would be hard to rap
my beer unless it's contained yeah
that's not a hit by the way yeah it's
not a hint
now
think about the process of wrapping
Kiara but it's just a pain in the butt
to wrap
everything honestly even the points even
the normal box oh but maybe like um
what else has like maybe ah
has a lot of pointy ends or something
like that
[Music]
is one angle but
um but think about other angles Brown
yeah what about that
a a ball
what kind of ball a soccer ball
I feel like it's not fair for them to
just say basketball so I'm gonna give
them I'm gonna give that to you
basketball okay yeah this one's rather
obscure so good luck one last one it's a
skirt
yeah rather obscure
I don't think I'll get that um
yeah because I don't think you'd buy
this for anyone but go ahead and throw
out some guesses you might not really
buy it for anyone it's kind of a boring
ass gift I wouldn't buy what nobody
would really buy it no one would it's
dumb
[Music]
so specific too probably like how would
I think of it yeah you might just need
to throw out some Rando guesses you
might hit it though
no I'll give up my brain is fried
oh you give up I'll take those four
points for this one all right Four
Points pretty good pretty good so the
last answer my left tell you what it was
yeah
all right last answer was a house plant
[Laughter]
yeah okay look I can see something like
quirky like a cactus or something like
that but like I guess not like anything
kind of yeah houseplant because I'm
trying to make my apartment more green
and yeah I every time I pass by a plant
store I try to get one
I don't know just that's a Christmas
gift they'd kind of be like oh what yeah
but I mean still you should be grateful
no matter what gift you receive yeah oh
this video is already 11 minutes this is
the longest hotel in the video okay
let's go to four but let's do two
questions each sure let's go okay
I have four points okay and next
question for Cali yeah
um
and
[Music]
oh
a name oh I like this question name a
Christmas decoration other than a tree
oh let's see a Christmas decoration
other than a tree okay
um
tinsel
so Ah that's the
ah yeah does that I was freaking obscure
what did I say attend so how do you
write that tuna tinsel
[Music]
t-i-n-s-e-l that comes as a Garland
right yeah Garland tinsel yeah for you
yay okay now we should make this into a
whole stream honestly honestly yeah a
whole Feud would be really cool yeah
with our own questions and stuff we can
pull the viewers
continue continue yeah
um a wreath
[Music]
teeth okay I'm just thinking about
things that I see in my grandparents
house because they love to decorate for
Christmas okay let's see how about
statues of Santa Claus
[Music]
yeah they're just more like little dolls
of Santa yeah okay how about Christmas
Village
I think okay what's written here is like
a miniature questions but let me let me
Google it I think it's like a miniature
Christmas Village
uh okay no not quite I guess no no no no
but that's cute man I love Christmas
Villages I always used to we always used
to use Christmas Villages Christmas
Villages
what's the Christmas Village for you
um it's like a tiny it's like a
miniature little like snowy town with
like a bunch of little buildings and
like you put like some fake cotton snow
underneath it on like a shelf and then
you set up the Christmas Village on top
of the fake snow it's very cute it's
cute yeah it's just a village in snow
any Village indeed yeah
yeah with maybe like children ice
skating around like a fake Santa Claus
or something like that
declaration yes cute
um all right let's see how about
um stockings
surprisingly that's also not on here
that really surprises me yeah what are
you guys putting in your house it should
be what the heck what the hell
definitely very strange you guys I know
it's not you guys though I'm sure you
guys got stockings oh I mean I'm wearing
them
true enough true enough let's see um all
right how about uh now it's getting
harder I'm not really sure
um
Nutcracker yeah classic
[Music]
icon indeed yeah I think I think you got
like five more guesses
okay how about
um Christmas lights
what what
boy Christmas lights are obvious I agree
you know sometimes with the
the answers you look at them and you're
like why on Earth is that honor or why
on Earth is that not on there that's
true what about snowmen no three more
presents uh okay
um let's see what else what else what
else
[Music]
I will give you a hint
okay I think uh more in a religious way
okay
um let's see
what's that menorah
well it's not on here it's for Hanukkah
oh well that's for Hanukkah though maybe
it's not a Christmas candles
yeah yeah those are really pretty but
they're not on here okay
okay
um oh I know the nativity scene
yeah
that's what I was wondering about if
that's if that sounds the same but not
quite because this is a very specific
thing yeah right right right yeah the
only thing that was amazing was
apparently Bose
I see it bows I can kind of imagine that
yeah I still think Christmas lights are
more popular but whatever but that is
for points
yeah all right now I've got one last
question for you yeah this one's kind of
funny okay name a gift the child would
rather not get for Christmas
vegetables
but no vegetables actually I don't think
any think anyone would want to get
vegetables for Christmas
vegetables not on there okay no but no
veggies what a what a child would not
want for Christmas
think about if you're a child and like
you're getting ready to get gifts what
do you not want
homework
do you think about actual gifts think
about actual gifts
but these are all things I think that
you'd still be happy receiving because
you're such a grateful person maybe
yeah does this seem like
um
does it seem to you like this would be
for a young child young child your child
young child or teenager yeah definitely
I mean maybe like 12. you know
I can say what they would like to
receive but I don't know what they would
not like to receive
all right here's the hint yeah yeah
think more on the side of clothing
sucks
Correct sucks that's a big one is there
more cloves on there I don't know maybe
you could guess an ugly Christmas
sweater
oh they're sweaters so I'll go ahead and
give that to you okay that has been four
guesses and two right ones for me so far
yes okay
I'll say a joke one
okay
never mind I'm not saying it's too real
oh gosh all right all right how about
something kind of nerdy something that
only nerds would like
[Music]
good okay but um
hey that's what these people aren't
thinking about I don't know I still
think you would enjoy these two other
things
um
uh um like supplies for like like how to
say what's the word for like yeah
stationery uh no stationery but I like
where your head is at pen
no pens
it's tough
so somewhere in that direction of
stationery
ah kind of think of something that you
definitely would like but like so
someone might receive and be like that's
nerdy I'm never gonna use that
drawing supplies
[Music]
one two three four five six seven you
got three more yeah no maybe I forgot
maybe I should forget about this one and
go in a different direction sure
[Music]
what if you go back to clothes okay
it's kind of something your parents get
you and you're like lame or you don't
want to open in front of other people
um
that's right is the number one answer
yeah if I would open underwear in front
of maybe even friends as a child it
would be very embarrassed embarrassing
indeed okay so that's that's free yes
and I still have two more guesses yes
you do
I'm I'm like thinking you know
[Music]
um like computer computer games would
make children children happy I think to
get
but yes they would it depends on the
child in the end but
I think mostly they at least nowadays
they would enjoy it
like I personally would rather get an
atomic game like a visual novel than uh
yeah I'd prefer that over a
over a dot dot dot dot
over a what about
a board game
so close you're so close this is the not
board game
it is a good guess okay last guess
last one something like a board game
you're so close
correct puzzles are one of them oh
let's go yay puzzles nice so you got one
two three four four points for qawwa the
last answer the last answer was books
books
see I feel like you would like receiving
books no
what but you were the one that wanted to
do a book club
I mean let's be honest I'm not much of a
reader I totally get what I wouldn't be
happy about it if that if you give it to
the right child it would be happy about
it obviously you know I guess it depends
that was fun I think that was in the end
nine points for me and eight for you or
so yup yeah so I guess QA was the first
Total Feud winner
we're tied
so maybe maybe there will be a
continuation of Family Feud sometime I
love that idea if you sponsored that
kind of game I'd definitely play hell
yeah thank you Kelly we're doing this
together
of course and a happy holidays in a ho
ho ho to everybody thanks for enjoying
holy holy days to everybody
account
[Music]
I got a check make sure you let us know
what you thought about it the an advent
it's Halloween thanks guys
bye see you in the hashtags
[Music]