[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
Hickory
[Music]
hi
oh very loud BTM what
[Music]
hello and welcome
it's been so long it has been so long
since our last streamed Tales over rice
that some would count days surely
someone did to then make fun of me
okay
it's been over a year yeah
October 2021
[Music]
so like wouldn't a half year years yeah
oh my God
yeah I thought I would play the rest of
my offline too but so some of you guys
may say that it's an excuse but
um
I
was like hesitating to play it for a
long time
because I just
I didn't want to finish it
you know how long it takes for new Tales
up game to come out
and then again it's just
streaming in games is my job and then
when
I it comes to playing something
privately I'm just not that
like motivated to do it I guess so that
might have been a reason to
sure sure yes
[Music]
and then eventually I was like okay
oh okay but this was really late but
eventually I was like okay I will I will
play this now
[Music]
on my own
and then I've Been Told
because I was starting to play on my own
um doing some side quests and stuff
because I was dragging it out which
should prove you that I just didn't want
it to end
yeah and and then someone told me I can
stream the ending and I was like hey yo
[Music]
well then I should stream it to finish
my playthrough officially for everyone
to see
right
yeah
[Music]
so that's what we're doing today
oh
it came from two sources
it came from desktop audio and from
video capture device but you you you've
been hearing me right
I promise also this bgm goes from quiet
to really loud
but anyway
foreign
[Music]
that is
so not interesting to me
no fishing
so I was trying
um a while ago
um before the year ended I was trying to
figure out if I did all the hoodles and
all the cyclists
they're made so like one or two
left over
in terms of side quests
[Music]
but I did most of it and then eventually
I realized I [\h__\h] up with the one side
quest where you give the like librarian
or so the books
the the weapons the book weapons because
I then I it was so long that I forgot
about the quest and I ended up selling
most of the books
this is not a fishing rod
so uh the sword that I'm carrying which
is not even really a sword it's just a
burning
piece of metal also
is
made by
I would say made by mythin probably may
have done made it themselves and then
[Music]
on my head is by bloodly bloodly blue
and then a blue
and the thumbnail art has been reused
it's from size drew me as kisara
yeah it's a cute hoodle in the kfp
uniform
of course I didn't use the Duolingo cool
because it has nothing to do with this
[Music]
yeah thank you artists for providing
with some cute assets
[Music]
so I've got one cup of tea
also I woke up with a headache and then
I took a
no I took a
aspirin a headache thingy painkiller
um
but then it didn't really do much at
first like I guess it got rid of my
headache more or less but I felt like
weirdly
like a little bit dizzy
um
right now I feel okay enough to stream
so
I think we'll be okay especially because
there's a chance this really will not
take that much time
foreign
Maybe
because yeah I wonder maybe I wasn't
drinking I don't know but you know
yesterday during the member stream like
before right before I was feeling sick
hmm
that went away quickly too but I want to
know what's going on
if I beat this today then it doesn't
matter
I guess it would be 2023
um because I guess you didn't count it
as finished in 2021 before so why do I
know
um
one of the highest difficulties to make
it longer no thank you
so uh do you guys need like a recap
of what has happened I probably needed
to
foreign total
hoodie okay now
yeah
it's been a while it really has been a
while yeah
hey thank you jenma
thank you jenma
we're adding
copyright history description okay
so in assuming that you watched
uh
everything up up until the end of my
last Tales of arise stream
which you guys hopefully did
[Music]
if they have any scenes I can go back oh
is that a thing in this game
I don't see anything here that would
imply that
possible
yes yes yes you did
thank you thank you admire it is
[Music]
so
on the menu once in the game next
hypnosis oh I guess we could read that
too but um no let me explain
we'll look at that too though maybe
later
so
uh remember I I left off and where I was
told to end it by
the sweet sweet Bandai Namco
entertainment
um
where I was like inside
some
it seems like it was some kind of
satellite I guess
and I saw a vision of the past
elephant and now we naori remember not
overe
who is Shield's ancestor who looks
exactly like her so I was like it must
be her but apparently it isn't
yeah and then the spirit channeling
ceremony we saw we saw them doing that
and that got interrupted by now is
mysterious black thorns
and in this cutscene it's revealed that
xeon's Florence come from a unique dark
astral energy and that was the cause of
the Great disaster 300 years ago
and then now they placed
that iron Amnesia mask on elephant that
made him look super edgy and fancy
that he has taken off at this point
though
well yeah that was kind of like I guess
holding back his memories
and the next the crew
my team walks into a chamber
where we learned that ball run that
piece of [\h__\h] is alive
he's the one who tried to
kill us before yeah
but he's alive but he's not really I
guess dangerous because he's being used
in a ritual to charge the redness Alma
mm-hmm you don't remember this guy
I don't remember it either
uh yeah and then the party
gets surprised by those red girls
remember those at least I remember those
the girls in red and they
um then transform from pretty red or
creepier pretty red girls into some
monsters that we end up killing
but
they still managed to steal the alma the
Rena's Alma
yeah and valarram tells us that he was a
Dana who was just pretending to be
Iranian because yeah I don't know why he
was being experimented on like Alvin to
become a sovereign and he also hates
Alvin and he wants to kill him
and then he blows up
yeah and then we leave the space station
and we see more of the red girls
um
and they uh there was a bamboozle and
teleport us off
space
[Music]
um
and then from there we see a new angle
we see that the planet Reina
isn't as healthy as it looked like
it's actually [\h__\h] dead
yeah
looking terrible in bad shape
and it only looks good when you like on
Dana and you look up and Reina looks
like a normal Planet but when you're up
there where we were then it looks dead
really dead
[Music]
so
yeah right now the planet then continues
or starts drinking Dana's Mana MP
squeezing it like a lemon
no I played up until this part probably
yeah I did I probably did
then they were stranded in space
and we get scooped up
and and then they meet a kind of dead
alien
you don't think I did you're not on
stream yeah yeah that's what I'm talking
about you you just learn about what I
did offstream
um
and that alien that half that alien
tells us what's really up
number one
and she on spawns
and
the great disaster and the consumption
of Reina is the great astral spirit and
it is being made from all of Brenda's
astral energy and it always needs more
and it absorbs 90 of rain now because of
it its main goal is to absorb all life
starting with my world Dana
and then the red girls they are mind
controlled slaves from the spirit the
great astral Spirit and the dying alien
that's telling us all this was one of
them but they got separated from the
spirit so it freed its mind and that's
why he's trying to help us
yeah
and Dana's astral NG is also sentient
but not like rainas not so shitty yeah
yeah
so the Arenas that we've met are
actually all daynans that were like
Bamboozled gaslighted into thinking
their demons
no Iranians
yeah the real reasons are all only
aliens there's no like human kind
reignents
yeah
and then you know remember remember the
crown contest that was to gather energy
for the spirit and the ceremony was
there to feed the spirit
but when the spirit attempted to steal
control of xion's ancestor
I an elephant ceremony ritual it
absolutely [\h__\h] up and it delayed uh
it Formed eating Dana until now
so then we go to Arena and no we have to
go to Reyna now and kill the spirits to
create astral Spirit to save all
everything save the world and become
Heroes forever
and alien tells us we can uh easily do
that I guess by doing a ritual but Shion
must die in the ritual because the
spirit would otherwise revive itself
through xion's existence and her forms
however that works don't ask me
and then says [\h__\h] that and we should
use this Reyna's Alma yeah
to contain the great spirit
yes like a Pandora's box or a Pokeball
stay alive
but alien alien friend says Nah not good
idea
um just I mean sacrifice xion because
that's less dangerous and I mean one
life for millions and millions and
millions I mean that's worth it right
so yeah if you don't do this I will not
give you your space trip back
and Alvin says no I don't wanna I'm in
love with this girl not really saying it
but
we all know it that uh the illness
called love has taken him
and he cannot hold it back he wants to
eventually make babies with shields so
he doesn't want to do that he needs her
um
So eventually they get the ship back and
a spaceship and Shion makes Alpha
promise that if they cannot get the
Renaissance he kill her with his with my
this this one this magical burning sword
um to save the world and she would be
fine with it because you know it's for a
good cause
yeah
so
what do we do
we kill the Great
[Music]
when do we do it
now
he leaves
as difficult to pronounce in Japanese
[Music]
so let's see where I ended up privately
oopsie I need to get used to Playstation
controls again
simple explanation
oh come on you're just [\h__\h] with me
now
this is [\h__\h] with me
boom
[Music]
something feels odd here be on your
guard yeah I was I was just doing a [\h__\h]
ton of side quests whatever I could find
that I haven't finished yet
I'd say the animals at the ranch are all
grown now and how's the audio now should
I turn it up a bit maybe yeah
audio good
slack bus in here and probably already
killed it
look at that man water is pretty
so see-through and green
um how do I look at the map again
um no
uh nope
no
[Music]
I took a video I don't know how to
control this [\h__\h]
this [\h__\h] keep on thinking X is back but
no circle is back
do I open the I keep up I don't know I'm
touching the touchpad but
no
Square for map
it doesn't work Maybe not maybe it
doesn't work in the in the water
catching a cold here have this herb I
found earlier I'm fine thanks
okay yeah okay it was because I was in
the water
and
so Reina a world of death look around
the era that's our main quest
I need to figure out how to play how to
play this game first oh man
just play map list there we go
oh
when so was I not done before I wanted
to do here because I still see like a
star here in her sanction
untameable rage
okay I didn't do it all right then let's
do it why did I not do it
I guess I fell asleep or something
oh
[\h__\h] you talked about
how do you know I was here to kill a
slug he must have played the game
recently though all right let's warm up
with the slug
cute
looks cute that's a big Zoo
yeah I'm not sure we can take it really
of us
warming up with a super bus
that's what the side quest I didn't
finish
this thing is so hot really
yo I think I might have by the way
switched to like easy mode or so
when I was playing offline to just get
side quests and all that done quicker
I might have done that how did I check
controls
all righty rent
menu well now it opens probably okay if
I push it like on the side
no wait that was just because I wasn't
alone and now it always opens this okay
what can I see them no
the buttons
settings
story
normally yeah yeah okay I did that I
don't think I played the whole game like
that just until I I was done streaming
it
pretty sure
[Music]
I might keep it this way though because
it's been like over a year and I
remember
him
that's okay right sorry difficulty isn't
that normal no no sorry difficulty was
um easy basic one
uh can we like [\h__\h] warm up with
something more normal
um
oh I also have something here no that's
the that's the
world of death huh
um
something here
which button which button is this one
that's the library [\h__\h] that's the
other one I can't finish
but other than that
you can see
I've been pretty thorough
there's any unsolved quests oh wait ah
pelange has something
yeah but I don't care about that now
I'll just go
[Music]
I've been having fun trying to drag it
out man
okay the mobs here are probably really
low level though oh Starship look at
those Starships
I grind it yeah
finally
if only we could have flown With the
Wind to get here faster we literally
teleported but okay okay you guys want
to be my subject uh let's do this
let's dispose of the trash
get behind me and then we can do these
things
square and triangle is special skills
and I think there was like a second row
of them well then I should probably
think about tonight's menu horse
actresses are loud
for real man uh are you for real
settings
where is that audio control
voice volume excited pathetic
because I'm trying to silence her uh no
uh save and go back
okay man a little bit more quiet for you
you missed these streams me too me too
right here it goes
um
not switching in but using
the others on the sidelines
call them in with their professional
attacks and I remember also the I should
probably think about tonight's menu what
do you call them I wonder those attacks
the com The Duo Duo attack gotta break
through you're mine come on
but whatever
[Music]
let's keep our eyes on the prize
I remember there's like one way I have
to activate it by a mile
different
skills
in a row with no break
while I am in the
are you just going to keep standing
around or what she's just getting
prepped over here
and then there's one where I just have
to do I think one attack and then press
it longer afterwards
she's calling me out but I literally
just stood there for a second
just a second she gets so impatient but
I mean button smashing mashing smashing
smashing same thing seems to work fine
so when you say we check back in on the
ranch no I don't think we're that much
in danger
are we
oh where did I go
yeah
game still tonight
quieter don't you light in the mood for
us
okay how about now
I feel like you probably don't hear
any of the bgm though
uh
take this
[Music]
human Fang
wow
he really hits me with the demon Fang
oops
this thing
do you smell like like my favorite
um Tales of meme now
okay ah I
uh
[Music]
one or two more baths how do I jump
again I knew there is a jumping button I
did that's the one
Peach gel no no thank you because I
guess I'm already full
ah can get down without using the
elevator or what
saw this in there
plenty of battles in the last engine I
guess so
okay and and then I just wonder if
there's anything else I should prepare
before going
can we check on whether or not I really
finished the hoodles like how do I know
if I did somebody in here surely
can help me with that
enough items okay
Doodly Doo
um
where's the
where's The hoodly Doodly there it is
oh [\h__\h]
oh no
sorry switch controls
confuse me
oh no I keep on thinking uh because of
the main quest that this is Reina for
some reason okay let's go
Tiara would know how many the house she
met hey
is something ah
oh the queen
[Music]
did I not finish it
I mean I guess I didn't
yeah but I tried to follow everything in
the
huh
there's still room for some holes on
this perch house
there's still room for someone else
is this room for some house
and it's so original Mouse
there's still room for some house
for the ball
I followed a guide
about which ones I'm missing
[Music]
it must have been lied too
foreign
[Music]
I'm lacking some does that mean so
for every perch I'm missing some really
I add more in endgame so can I is this
some fairy just so possible on the end
game
oh and they're in Boss rooms well done
okay
and then
let's save the world
uh
[Music]
uh here
I don't
I wait
I need to go shopping first mm-hmm
can I shop in in My Starship
where can I go shopping
[Music]
what's a good place to shop at maybe
an in
yeah just kind of make sure
that I've got everything
that was quite the little Adventure we
went on ah so we need every single gel
maximum
okay I have Peach and lemon maximum
uh orange but orange and apple is just
pretty no orange is just 30 and this is
just 400 HP this that's really nothing
but I guess I'll buy
them anyway
okay
um
treat any symptoms
here why not a live spot oh okay we need
definitely a maximum of Life bottles
increasing the battle chain but now I
don't use these things
and the rest is just this kind of stuff
and I think I have yeah all the most all
the best armor pieces for everyone and I
think also the best
um
no sorry I'm prepared but did we have to
spend so much the best
uh weapons I think
that I can make at least
because these ones I can't make
unfortunately
[Music]
um
these ones
oh this one would only if it's a [\h__\h]
carrot
this one would only be better in one
area
I think you're good
all right I also looked at before I've
been at like accessories but even to
this day I don't 100 understand what's
what do you think of that chicken what's
the easiest and best way to do that
stuff
shut up
[Music]
I guess we're good to go
to the scary world easiest way is ignore
it
I renew you
wow
I am after all the tales of a Verizon
ambassador to the English region
well look at this
it's [\h__\h] Epic
that really looks epic also right now I
am wearing the beautiful DLC outfit from
swaf
looks so cool
I love the hair especially I think that
was also part of this outfit
yeah [\h__\h] sick
and now we are looking at
Reina I guess
[Music]
yeah last time I arrived here privately
I just I just arrived and I was like
um that seems like end game
let me go back and do some side quests
yeah
looking good it's not a sponsor stream
now but my first Tales of arise stream
was sponsored
and a couple before the first actual
stream
I'm nervous also I didn't do like a
campfire thingy I wonder if you can do
them while you're here what is this
stuff
maybe there's a campfire place somewhere
is there I wonder
someone new because I I want to cook
and make some stuff I feel like they
would Place something
's related no there wasn't okay well I
guess we don't really need those effects
anyway okay can I go down there no oh
wow
[Music]
oh
um
okay
well then let's use the only possible
teleporter I guess
yeah this is Reina
clock's ticking we must attack and
dethroned God
what is this place oh there's this place
let's go back but no we have to move on
forward what are these panels
hold on
[Music]
why are my footsteps sparkling
you seen that
have like a violent Sparkle to them
[Music]
seven six five four three I'm guessing
that after this there's no return is
there is there can I can I go back to
the normal World while I'm doing my
stuff in here
foreign
yes oh is he okay
[Music]
oh yeah that's what the girls turned
into
guess they don't need their red woman
disguises anymore
wait can you understand us
even if they do they're not gonna help
us
that's for sure there's no use we're not
going to get through to them
so they really are being controlled
in that case
shut up that's what I said
that's just what I said all right here
we go something off here how do I dodge
again no choice but to beat them at
their own time okay but I feel like
elephants Dodge is like super slow
so I have to really like
look into the future and be like I know
that I'm gonna be attacked in five
minutes
oh yeah these probably are
um
armor breaking attack I think
like when he punches them when he
punches heavily armed people
am I over Limited
[Music]
we get toasty
no no it looked like it something was
going on
okay that's the word I was looking for
this
consider yourself finished
foreign
[Music]
give them for what they've done
killing them
they don't even know why they're
fighting they're not humans slaves
perhaps
however if we don't make a choice the
guilt of not doing anything will be that
much worse
why is she feeling pity for them I hate
for it to be like this but if it happens
again
you won't find me hesitating to act
proudly no
no his whole mission is over
I'll stay the course that's really
bright oh my God I like how it's so
bright that our character is hard to see
like good lightning effects
[Music]
wow wow wow wow all the like
fancy effects when fighting and all
those shouting and yelling and
activating stuff
makes me feel so nostalgic man
was a good time oh hello
[Music]
so it's on Giant
is this the zoo it does look like it's
Google but completely uninjured we just
have to see for ourselves if it's really
as ferocious as they say looks crazy
okay
wait it's from a side quest
by the way R1 I thought there'd be more
dirt and rocks and stuff underneath the
hollowed ocean but it's all artificial
I would imagine their remnants left
behind by the helgenquil seeing as
there's little actual land remaining
it's incredible
winner of the planet
hey these guys built lineages remember
I probably did this in a weekend
if they had the power to create things
like this
did they really only use those immense
capabilities to serve the great spirit
or rather was that the only use the
great spirit let them use their
capabilities for
foreign
really quick
let's just not talk about it
[Music]
just don't even mention it
oh I think this one was maybe okay but
let's just let's just let's just change
it
this is okay this is okay
um foreign
[Music]
it's all right oh one more one more skit
we haven't seen anyone here except
helgenquil looks like this place really
is their home planet
the true citizens of Rena what a shame
that they have become nothing more than
puppets to the great spirit
to think of the promise their
accomplishments once held they had the
potential to be great indeed
do you think we could have got along
with them
you know if we had met under different
circumstances like
like all of us you mean I suppose it's
difficult to say for sure
we don't even know if they would see us
as being on an equal level with them or
not I think we may have had the chance
once before the renin great spirit came
along and
changed everything
you and Alvin both share in optimism
strong willingness to Believe In Hope
true
on the contrary I should like myself in
tragedies after Now voice is too low
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I thought you
guys would say that never happened
[Music]
let's look at the size of that thing
the helgenquels technology certainly is
impressive
and they don't seem to do things by
halves either
the past 300 years now even before that
just how many people are looking at the
size of that do you use the thing in the
middle the bright regarding the past
three centuries at least I'd say there's
a good chance that we're the first
also while I get that it's impressive
and all I'm just amazed you're still
standing around gobbing at it at a time
like this sometimes I wonder about your
priorities
I can understand where he's coming from
more to the point does anyone know where
it leads
what do you mean where it leads to the
center of the planet of course and that
doesn't strike you as sounding just a
little bit oh I don't know far there has
to be a quicker way to get there right
yeah
at their fingertips seems pretty
unlikely that they'd make that kind of
Journey David will help us like
reconnect there must be some kind of
device somewhere let's see if we can
figure out how to use it
borrow one of their Contraptions they're
either Brave or out of your mind
if it works for them there's no reason
it wouldn't for us why make things
harder for ourselves you know what he's
like law once he gets an idea in his
head there's no talking him out of it
foreign
[Music]
then the game would have a very Grim
ending
sad one maybe not even a happy ending
all right
you've got a really bad
[Music]
heaven
[Applause]
[Music]
where are you going
uh
Ah that's the weeks
[Music]
I made it louder for uh
dialogue but now make it quieter again
because the battles are so loud
see he's so motivated to smash people
they should really should have put him
into Super Smash Brothers man
[Music]
on the weak point anymore
Divine what's with the camera what what
where was I
what is this
what's he doing
I usually never have problems with the
camera in the game
as far as I remember
form it's teleports oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
they talk so much
oh she killed me that was a big deal
oh
oh yeah I think I taught her like oh
all right Tom are really good healing
skill I think recently
you know I think it looks really cool
these battles and it maybe looks like I
know what I'm doing but I'm just
smashing buttons
oh he's gone
a holy lands mist yeah
sad sad coincidence
can I cancel this teleport with her did
I just do that I don't know
oh let's go in here
rolling rolling
oh [\h__\h] why did I activate that now did
I maybe I actually hit him
even fans
[Music]
a lot of those went hard on hisana
YouTube can't handle all this magic oh
it's the bitrate looking live [\h__\h]
I don't even know what my big friend is
set um
no no
foreign
[Music]
here we go
that's a nice battle
it's comfortable
I wasn't struggling too much oh
beat it in the end let us Harvest what
we can use
do I have to give us the side quests and
cast aside back I'm sad
to the person who gave it to me
is this a dead end it appears this whole
room functions as an elevator oh that
apparatus there is likely what's used to
control it
which operators oh that one
second
I wonder how the renins avoided being
mind controlled like the helgenquil
do you think it might have something to
do with the fact that they were
originally dannon's I'd say it's likely
which is pretty ironic when you think
about it
ironic
the renins have committed grave
injustices against the dannins
but it was all of their own volition not
because they were being controlled
now it turns out they themselves were
once dannon's too
which must mean that the root of their
evil isn't the great spirit but
something inherent in all of us
our free will oh now hang on though it
was that same free will that allowed
Shion and dohalim to choose to fight
alongside us
without it we wouldn't have been able to
beat hatred and Forge all those
connections we've made Free Will is what
saved us right
law is entirely right
in any case it certainly can't hurt to
look on the bright side every now and
then
yeah where there's hope there's a way
wow
what do you say
you said poodle without a doubt
Gotta Love hoodle
okay we're going to upper level second
floor
[Music]
even as the friends were made along the
way
[Music]
you guys can try to compare Poodle's
voice to what we heard yesterday the day
before yesterday in Fire Emblem remember
pesky Airborne Scoundrels same voice
actress that mother from monochrome girl
right
that was the one
fail yeah
so cute Oreo hair girl
hey I missed I missed it
was too fast on it
oh I just noticed that while we're
fighting here the whole time the
elevator is moving
downwards
I was so focused on the enemies in real
life
we're moving
I was
um doing the thing
[Music]
no no no no no
volcanic impact
get done
[Music]
oh the girl's power
walk in the park
[Music]
Shin said I'm even better than ever even
though this is my first day
whoa been a long time
to play this game
is she just
throwing out compliments for free
I don't believe it I don't buy it
I love this move like transitioning from
when you killed an enemy
and you move on to the next one in case
you're still hitting if you don't hit it
doesn't happen
[Applause]
have we arrived
I think so even in such a harsh
environment
is still creatures here you think
they're native torena or could they be
zugal somehow they're
watch yourself
they look like zoukles but I guess
they're they must be aliens
I know
upper level second floor
so this is the last dungeon Ryan you
think that pit stretches all the way to
Rena's core
that's true and if we go down we should
find the great spirit we could get there
even faster if we simply jump down
instead and sound alarmingly serious
when you say that are we going down
I guess we're going down all the way
down
yeah but why not jump
why not just jump we would be so much
faster I actually agree
Shawnee crust Shockwave slash swallow
blade
Dragon floor
I don't even have to look at the screen
oh this one is so cool
now
well we can do a q a guys ask me some
questions
let me answer you some questions
they have been on your mind
oh no here you can jump
see see wait no okay not in battle wait
I think you could jump in battle
it's not the same button
uh
I know I'll find his last name I'll
remember at least
I can try let me open up my notes
um
it will be a little bit interrupted here
and there duh
uh where was it
where is it
I hear this
okay
so uh while I was in Japan maybe you
remember
I was invited to uh Yakiniku which is
like grilling Meat restaurant
where you grill to meet yourself meet
and all kinds of like muscle meat though
other things too though sometimes
um there's like salads and whatever too
but mostly meat with the yellow
Minecraft team Plus for some reason
bales
because she kind of caught wind of it
and asked if she could join
so she was there too and it wasn't all
yellow team members though because some
couldn't come couldn't make it
senpai
elderly
not senpai
and one more
thing uh no way that that may have been
it everyone's still in one piece yep no
it may have been it
sorry I'm so sorry yeah so by the step I
was not there she couldn't make it
um sadly but I met super du simply on
another occasion so oh it's okay should
I go left or down what's this door for
who's not simply
well
that's like a Harry Potter creature what
are you doing in this game
two-headed weird wolf thingy
oh it protects some kind of good looking
treasure so I guess we're gonna go for
it but can I do the small mobs first
though it's all all of them huh okay
wait
Michelle
so yeah I met nanity before I got really
excited to see her again
and Matsu and Senpai also I've met
before was the first time in a long time
it must have been like two years or so
because we did one off collab once a
long time ago if you remember
Mary ate some fried chicken yeah
so cute as ever
so cute
so pretty yeah
so basically
um we first sat down with the couple
girls that were arriving first
so that was
[Music]
Senpai and and main room Senpai and me
and amen so we filled up one table and
then later the ones who joined later
would fill up the
second table
some of them are like a little bit oh
but what
bales
[\h__\h]
now one thing I have to say is at the
end when
you know it was time to leave and we got
the bill
put some uh trying to I think most
people weren't quite listening they were
like all in their conversations and
got a trophy
but then minor Senpai got the the bill
from the
from the staff can mean best okay I'll
change that later
and
people weren't really listening but I I
noticed it and I was like oh I'm gonna
I'm gonna like give you some money
to pay it because it was quite a big big
Bill
but then she was like no no no it's okay
I'm gonna pay it and then I was like no
no way you can't do that no this is way
too much money let me pay something
we're gonna chip in I'm sure
but then I think the other girls like I
got really like loud about it because
it was it was too many zeros on the bill
and I was like no wait a minute
I can't do that no no and then the other
girls were like looking at me kind of
like what is she yelling about
I didn't realize they only noticed later
on that menu Senpai paid for everything
and they were like no matter
we're gonna give you something now and
she still refused
so thank you major senpai
thank you but
[Music]
what a chat yeah but I feel bad it was
really expensive man because it was a
huge group and it was a pretty
good
yakiniko Place hmm
Angel vampire really that
yeah
uh oh yeah so they started by ordering
stuff like UK
so far
so many of the whole live girls that
I've met with they always go for UK
which is that like raw meat with some
raw egg
on top of it and you like mix the raw
meat raw beef by the way
yeah
and they're they're also into it so
that's always the first thing they order
so yeah they started ordering these
things that me and Ahmed weren't not so
eager about but I was like well
we should we should try it anyway
so I tried and it was it was it was
edible
it was okay and then I tried to look
like anything after being a little bit
hesitant
um
and then eventually when we were already
grilling stuff
she put a little bit of the raw beef UK
yeah on top of the grill but then the
grill you know those pieces were really
really really really tiny
like almost like grinded meat and she
would try to grill it but then it fell
almost through the grill
fruit and little holes
but you see I was I was thinking oh
that's funny and it's like not really
something you normally do in Japan
um but I was I couldn't like
be mad or anything because I did
something like this too when I was still
a noob to Japan and where I didn't feel
like eating raw meat
um I would like secretly try to grill it
too when no one was looking
so when I look at her
I really feel this
like interesting way
I know it feels no static it feels like
me when I first came to Japan a little
bit
yeah I see a little bit of myself and
it's just nice to see someone
experiencing Japan for the first time
like that and see how they do things
because it's kind of how I used to do
things
yeah also on that other day when we were
in inoshima right and she was she mixed
uh I think the
the miso soup
with the rice or something something
that you normally don't mix
at least not
not in a situation like this
yeah I mean it works it works but you
normally wouldn't do it in the
restaurant
but then again I I think I like would
try stuff like this too in the past
she was also like normally you eat the
rice that they bring with the dishes
just like you for example you put like a
piece of meat in your mouth and then you
eat that and then you follow it up with
some simple normal ass rice they bring
you a cup of white rice and you just eat
that while you're eating the other
things
but you don't put sauce or anything on
the rice
however yeah she would like try to put
other flavors on the rice by putting
sauces and soups and whatever on top of
it and then yeah I was also thinking
when I saw that I used to do that too
so
it's nice to see
where did I come from oh is that ever
showing me that I came from there nice
let's go to here
yeah the problem is that if you put like
soup or whatever on top of it the rice
will be really hard to pick up after
that oh dear
look
well eventually while we were still
enjoying
the tongue that they ordered grilling
dads and the Yuka at the same time
um the girls for the other table were
arriving and being seated next to us
and they also of course started by
ordering Yuki
but they didn't order normal UK they
ordered Yuka with like uh baguette
you know please get the other thing I
made with the tomatoes but you can make
it with anything
and when I looked over and I heard they
had something with posca I was like oh
hi
I was like oh damn
sounds actually pretty good
maybe that's how I would endure eating
Yuka more
so the waiter heard me being really
excited about the bucket and offered if
I just want to add the baguette extra
to our order and I was like hell yeah
hell yeah and after that me and Emma
were both enjoying it more
Ahmed was also trying to eat it with the
bread so the raw beef on top of the
bread was that
stuffy
better to enjoy
I'm gonna put your tongue on the
Yakiniku Grill if you don't stop
you little piece of [\h__\h]
oh
my God
no don't demolish flare no it still
needs her
she's doing her super special skill
without me
controlling her I'm so proud man
what the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
that's running around like crazy
oh yeah that's bad
one second
don't kill me don't kill me
do it
I thought that's how you do it I thought
Rising my phone
I pushed it longer
how does it work again
I guess not like that okay remember to
tell me if you need healing I expect
you'll be in high demand if that's the
case I'm confused
fuse
it doesn't work
my super art unleashment
hmm
yeah we'll fix this HP right now
actually all of our HP is not looking so
good
um
let's use another one
okay the rest she can heal up
it'll be fine
yeah
oh holding two art buttons
about the five art combo wasn't
necessary I think
that's for the different skill
I mean sure I can do that too but
it was a bit difficult
it has to be five different ones but but
there's also an easier one
yeah
holy cloak
sorry
let me see who needs that I'm actually
the other one too
not you
oh not you
but not you this one holy cloak for you
nice
and then for you the connect nine one
you must really at Alvin okay
so I was um trying to like
get Emma to talk a bit I was like
translating things between them I asked
them I told them oh if you want to talk
to Amy I can translate so don't worry
didn't want her to feel like she didn't
belong here or felt left out or
something so I was helping
or translation
and where am I
ah there okay
well
and oh and actually
um I already had this planned beforehand
when I met major standby like two or
three days before that I asked her
because there were so many members
coming if maybe we can do something like
switch seats after a while like speed
dating but doesn't have to be so Speedy
just because
um some of them I haven't met before and
Emma as well and this way we could like
get to know everyone
yeah so when it came to the actual
dinner
eventually I was like okay maybe now's a
good time
switch because we just finished a plate
of
meat and before we order anything more
how about we switch now
walked over and we got Bales to switch
with us
so Bears went to the other table and we
we went to where Bells was
that's where I sat down next
foreign
because she was a little bit surprised
that we were suddenly switching
and I explained to her that I I just
wanted to
and get to know her because I never you
know talked with her before same with
doing
and she was like no problem no problem
she was eating
already but
yeah and ah she's she's pretty
cute
what just happened
[\h__\h] right here I'm paralyzed
TMT yes very TMT
harder
okay so once I sat down next to her
um
I don't know it felt like we were vibing
on that table and and
kind of got hyped up and we talked a lot
and I was again translating for Amit too
and then eventually toss Empire for some
reason
noticed my head oh I think I know why
it's because I was like oh all you girls
have some pretty nails and me and Mama
we're we have like so such plain boring
nails
I feel like you guys are so girly and
we're not and then because of that TOA
looks at my hands and she starts
squeezing them and she's like so
fascinated like oh my God why are your
hands so so soft like not soft like in
terms of you know oh I just use the hand
lotion stuff but she meant that the the
meat on my hands was like squishy soft
and she like couldn't stop
squeezing my hands
constantly and she was like no no that's
to the other girls on the table
what's this and then you will understand
what I mean like this is this is not
normal and she also compared it to the
other girl's hands
and said look look he wow his hands are
so much more like squishy soft
and I'm like I was never told this
before it was a close thing
I'm really surprised you're saying that
because I never use hand creams or
anything I've never got complimented for
having nice feeling hands before I think
so excited about it
I think she really likes hands yeah
and another thing
she
I don't know what we were talking about
but
um
oh what could it have been did I write
it down
no I didn't I didn't write it down but I
got like really excited or like agitated
about something like jokingly angry
about something I was like
[Music]
I was like ranting venting
um and towards if I just started
laughing
hysterically at me and I'm like and what
what did I
why is she laughing like that and I felt
like embarrassed but she said and she's
laughing because she likes how
passionate I get about everything like
the whole time
it seems like I was I was very
passionate in the conversation about
anything and I would also use my hands a
lot talking with big gestures
anymore
yeah but I mean uh in hindsight after
she said that I was like you know what I
guess you're right with that
they felt a little bit embarrassed but
seems like she was enjoying it
the Sprout stuff like later face
would start showing off like pictures of
our pets
to the other girls uh and everyone got
like really excited
and we talked about like Japan I kept on
translating like oh I mean what did you
eat in Japan so far what do you want to
do what did you do so far where did you
go
Etc
um
yeah yeah
so I think everyone had a good time
on that table
and for some reason I really bonded with
two lesson
over my hands and other things
oh
yeah
[Music]
um
oh yeah I also gave presents to everyone
you know those chocolates
presents told you guys before
so all of those members
they all got something special from me
yummy German Austrian chocolates but
those were the ones that I had to
um
she does it again I'm I'm fascinated
thank you
the ones that you don't control I feel
like they often don't use their skills
what was I just saying
I forgot what I was saying
[Music]
um I wanted to go over to ninity because
she was sitting on the other side of the
table and the whole time I feel like we
weren't like talking that much
and I wanted to talk more with an energy
so I went over to her sat next to her
and we were like
you know
to chatting a bit next to each other
holding hands and then I wanted to take
a picture with her for commemoration
let me try to do this again
it doesn't work
no I wanna I don't want to strike I want
to do my special attack
it was two buttons I forgot to do it
again
so so we started like taking cute
pictures with like Beauty abs and she
was like oh what beauty app are you
using and then I showed her mine and
then she shows me her beauty app you
know every girl has their own favorite
Beauty app and we have to like exchange
information about it because some beauty
apps are better than others
Senpai she caught wind of what we were
doing because she was sitting um kind of
like next to us
and she like moved over to us and she
was like I want to take pictures
together too so we took some pictures
with the three of us and and then I took
some peaches only with bartoni Senpai
and yeah we took like pictures and all
kinds of combinations and while we were
doing this the other girls were like
kind of helping us because it was kind
of dark in this place
so they would like pull up like free
phones
turn on the torchlights of their phones
and lighten us from different angles so
that we could would get the the perfect
selfies they were like supporting us
laughs it was like a photo session
[Laughter]
that was funny
yeah and then eventually yeah this was
already around the time where we were
done eating so then
we look at everything oh [\h__\h]
um
yeah we were starting to leave and
we were gathering outside again and then
dance was like oh I want to hang out and
then some of the other girls were like
oh sorry I'm going home really really
and
someone else
they were both like nah we're going
sorry good night and I was like
uh well I guess we're going to enoshima
tomorrow but if it's not too late just
yet so I guess I can tag alone along a
little bit but we're like
a lot a lot of us
uh and I'm I was a bit worried about
going to two crowded places
with all of us
so I recommend that we go to karaoke
because it would be in a closed room
um but Bales I think she wanted to go to
like a maid Cafe
well generally like whatever
but one of their other suggestions was
made cafes
and and arcades and stuff
but I felt like I made a cafe at this
time was kind of weird so we were just
we just started walking trying to find
something where we could go
and that like ended up being kind of
dragged out for a while because we just
couldn't find anything we walked and
walked and
I couldn't find anything for a while
so and especially because no one really
seemed to really want to go into a
karaoke
um
eventually I I just said okay never mind
guys I'm gonna go Olivia guys
because I didn't feel
like it would be such a smart idea
to yeah go to such public crowded places
with all of us and then when I said I
was leaving Hami also said she was
leaving
so we left together
um I looked for a taxi
but eventually Amma ended up
finding them again because she was like
just going through arcades and arcades
yeah so she hung out with them in the
end after all it seems but before I left
I was saying goodbye to everyone and I
got a special goodbye from Matsu
recently
because I saw her
um
I saw her giving uh a kiss on the cheek
to someone and I was like oh I ain't
killing the one one two and then she
looks at me and I look at her
and we stare in each other's eyes and
we're wearing we're wearing masks at
this point yeah
but then
I feel like with our eyes we were
telling each other
that
a kiss on the cheek wasn't enough so
we kissed each other on the mouth
through the mask
thank you
I got so excited
I was jumping and squeaking and
squealing
I'm really excited but can you blame me
more romantic than on this version
really what did she say
s oh she says I never miss but she
literally missed we saw her missing
just in that moment
you didn't hear about the lip thing
he was a bit jealous really
oh is she gonna go for it again she's
like so
on the roll Santa on a row
look at her
I'm not doing so well
yeah so that was basically it I went
home earlier than the others they got
drunk after that apparently and went to
maid Cafe and and arcades and whatever
right
thanks for attention you're welcome
yeah that was uh the yellow team yucky
nicotan we had a good time
I think
during the dinner and I got to know some
of them better so that's nice
yeah cool story bro thanks
sounds like a good night yeah
I hope I can meet Thomas and play again
or all of them of course
but I did meet Louis again after that
and I did meet hachama again after that
and I did meet major sample several
times and I did meet Nancy again after
that
and did me AME again after that
you made me angry oh oh we made her
angry the only one that I had
didn't see again it was tour senpai
oh actually I was like
and when I sat right next to her and we
started talking I think I kind of I was
like
I'm sorry we didn't really interact so
much until now it's just like I guess I
don't play the kind of games that you
like like FPS games
say no more
yeah but I said it's not I don't know I
was that doesn't mean I'm not interested
in you or anything
Dragon Blood
yeah so hopefully even without FPS games
maybe we can call up sometime
she wants to
now I'm not gonna go on an FPS Arc hell
no
and they've got so many of these doggos
around here
someone also
hiding a good item over there
I don't know yeah
well it's hiding the path to the next
area all right this is where the good
stuff is
based thank you
Minecraft on the new server oh yeah I
saw that that's going on but some
equipment
I don't know I I don't really feel like
going back into that at the moment
um
yeah
I wouldn't know what to do
because if I understand correctly in the
old service still exists and are
connected
and so what's I don't know what the
purpose is
you can start over from scratch but
um
I would say that en still had things to
do anyway on our server
there were I would say plenty things
that we didn't do yet
now we are still planning to do
yes it's not really a real new server
because we can even bring our things
over right
um
and Minecraft has been dead for so long
now mostly in in the whole life
members community
that I don't know now it feels kind of
awkward to go back into it
yeah but we do want to do the river but
I know when how
foreign
wants to do it now
good as in Japan now as you know and I'm
not sure if she can
play Minecraft from there she probably
can I mean but she's still on the break
so
that's probably not an option right now
and she was supposed to be part of the
group
to find the Wither
but originally I also invited Ina before
asked her if she would want to join when
she was like right before no right after
she went on a break
um I asked her before collab she wants
me to Maybe
joined with the fight and back to hand
she couldn't do it
now maybe now she would do it because
she's back now
I could include her in the weather fight
but Kura is not available so hmm
hmm
Ben why do CP like
get used up so quickly
[Music]
um
yeah well the river will have to wait
for another day
are you are you
no you didn't see me yet
I couldn't even skip it huh
do I need the levels because I feel like
I've been
okay
so far and man all these fights are kind
of just the same
I'm gonna skip this one
just this one
pretty good on levels well what level
did you guys have when you did the final
boss do you remember
because I'm around all around 55 now
16. hmm
but you guys probably were on normal
mode right
I assume you guys were on normal mode
not on easy or maybe even hard yeah
and so
it'd be fun I was around 40 and on
normal was hard well 40 is way too low
what the [\h__\h]
yeah maybe I'll skip some things then
and what was I gonna do
ah I was gonna use that Astro
whatever that was whatever sound again
the actual flower huh oh no wait I guess
it just does that I don't have to
activate it doesn't automatically
okay but we had an armor piece
I think it was for you
no
for you maybe
the rare plate
there we go
and let's look at the skill panel I was
trying to do
um like not one here one here one here
and so on because I realized that I
should finish
each circle properly to get the bonus
effect that you get for the completion
bonus
so I was aiming for that here and there
um
this one's kind of close to completion
soon what's the bonus defense Plus 50.
so I wasn't even looking at anymore at
what the single ones do because I guess
somehow all of them are
helpful useful right so whatever
1700 was this Elemental attack was 50
penetration plus 50. hmm
makes it easy to inflict physical
ailments on enemies
sure seems like a basic one
and this one
uh 800 oh we can do this one
um
increased boost strike damage oh yes
1200 points oh
it's almost finished this one let's do
next time we can do this one and then we
get elemental defense Plus 20.
oh this one's this one I can finish and
we get penetration Plus 40. and increase
blue strike damage and reduced Awakening
requirements
[Music]
oh you were you were preferring
prioritizing the single things yeah
[Music]
I was doing that for most of the time
but eventually I just wanted to finish
them too
oh a new skill would be good too
although I don't use dohaling much on
the actual Battlefield
okay
used up the points
next battle
oh there's one room over here
of a treasure I suppose
oh yeah
oh yeah that's probably another armor
piece right
Maybe
it's kind of hard to use really I mean I
wasn't I wouldn't even like use it
myself but
just put him in there as an NPC
I have fun little Helen
he's a backup healer yeah I guess I
forgot about that that's true
wait a second I think I'm gonna go to
one of the small ones
oh I have just vegan okay
can I do it now oh
at least the basic one
Scarlet Albert no it said Outburst at
the top
he's calling it Inferno
as long as I can do I can do the basic
one
I guess
we good
oh
kneeling Circle
it is
oh she's gonna show us her Mystic art
again
although the battle is almost done
anyway
oh you should go
you're getting the itch yeah the combat
is fun
it's just so flashy
it's not an overlay but she's always an
over limit
okay
some good equipment
what was that for
um for you
from the body bloody code to the
elemental cape that sounds better less
stinky
button mashy it's easy for me I guess if
you want more of a challenge you can
turn heart mode on but
I am pretty satisfied this way it's not
too frustrating
yeah our game should be enjoyed I mean
some certain degree of struggling
I think is important to keep you engaged
in the game and make you feel challenged
we're not babies after all we're
professional gamers
it's running it's running it's running
it's running
what
that's a rare one
is she gonna use her Mystic art do it no
no I understand it sassy
shut him down
why
I wish they would use it properly
oh
[Music]
yeah
yeah some some characters just don't use
their Mystic Arts
kind of annoying but it's fine I'm fine
without
I'm too powerful already anyway oh is
that
what is that for healing yes touch
oh
wait the fact that that's here
makes me worry a little bit
it's definitely not the final battle but
maybe the one of one of the final
battles
look at the dates
that's look at the the thumbnails that's
the one where I stopped playing I think
and then for some reason I did some
extra saves
mm-hmm this this 2022 December this is
where I picked up again
uh yeah I played like I played like 10
ever since that
stream ended
mm-hmm
yeah
foreign
but I did play
I want you guys to shut up about it
already
about me not finishing
pills over eyes
oh wait my hand why didn't you tell me
my hands has been floating
for a while
I didn't know Mifflin how to attach this
one was this one was this your plan to
put up one of my hands like this the
fist pose oh
oh the aliens what the hell are they
asleep
no they appear to be well preserved
however they are all
dead they're like pickles in a jar
so this is
a mass grave
looks that way
however none of them appear to be
helgenquil
bear in mind that renins were originally
dannon's who were remade and sent to
live on lennogus
knowing that they would have needed a
place to perform the procedure somewhere
and that place is here I assume
so what you're saying is that all of
these are Dannon or rather renin bodies
most likely yes
it must have been abandoned for one
reason or another
what if we open them up now
there are so many of them
they were all taken away but never given
the chance to wake are we doing that now
doesn't sound very safe
oh I was just gonna let them go for them
being like so pitiful of everyone here
if they would just let it go that would
be actually kind of untypical for them
I mean I wouldn't mind just letting them
go because I feel like if we wake them
up they're all kind of attack us they're
dead
but I thought if you put something in a
pickle jar it's gonna be good forever
and you guys should put me in a pickle
jar
and I will stay in whole life forever
someone coming from behind or from above
[Laughter]
I anticipated that
oh [\h__\h]
are all those weak spots
how am I even gonna reach what is that
thing
something we have to fight if we want to
get across it seems
be careful it's huge what was that
um freaking Morty mean pickled brick
pickle oh they made me into a pickle or
something like that what is that funny
okay what the actual [\h__\h] though like
what do I attack oh there's nothing to
attack
that much is damn sure
oh my God
[Music]
yo this thing is really weak
some of the previous animes were more
challenging than this one that'll bring
you down
[Music]
[Applause]
like not hitting them
[Music]
but I guess I am it just feels like I'm
not
because I'm just below
I need some healing
what's going on
he's almost dead
there we go Frozen
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I think it was a joke that was made here
and somehow managed to survive even
after all this time not that there's any
way of knowing now
what's wrong
I just suddenly found myself
contemplating what might have happened
to the sovereigns that were meant to
emerge from the crown contests
what do you mean
you see the winners of the past Christ
we staggered most of the fight strong
astral Arts practitioners
that enemy we just fought appeared to be
composed of several human bodies it was
certainly nothing one would find in
nature
you're saying those were the remains of
the winners that they forgot who they
once were
I'm merely saying it's a possibility
that's absolutely gruesome how long had
the helgenquil been at this it was
Rena's great spirit that made them do
all of this anything to get its astral
energy
is not amused
I certainly hope not after hearing
darling's suggestion it's all red down
there what to say I assure you all I was
merely stating the possibility
[Music]
so looks like the helgenquil have been
engineering zugals too why doesn't that
surprise me at this point
the creatures we've been encountering
here have been a little different to
what we're used to fighting yeah but I'm
pretty sure they're zoogles too I guess
so do you think they were engineered
using creatures native to the area
indeed however based on the current
circumstances I would guess these zugals
are all that's left of the planet's
fauna now
[Music]
here once upon a time too
so cute
I love hoodoo
[Music]
is this the right way or this is where I
came from no it's the right way it's
like everything's so symmetric
it's hard to see
oh worth it
Sasuke
wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait I don't want to waste that
opportunity pineapple gel wait was that
CP or
I was sleepy let me use it then and then
pick up this one
I Wanna Be wasteful here what's being
offered to me by the fauna I shall take
minute
what's next
oh [\h__\h] should I have saved oh didn't I
say I saved before the big fight huh let
me save again
that wasn't even such a big fight it
felt like nothing it's a piece of cake
again
[Music]
I used the big CP item because
um otherwise I wouldn't be able to pick
up the new one
it's a win-win
kind of
okay uh now I guess we're going to the
area where everything's red
oh but we might have to get it
in version room
mysterious what's an inversion room what
does that mean
[Music]
s
let me see again if there's something
here
[Music]
okay maybe on the other side
did the teleporter fail or something oh
that something feels off about it yeah
look everything's upside down yeah
it's really inverted no you're right the
whole room slipped on its head so what
was once down is now up and vice versa
suppose the teleporter reversed our
orientation then
[Music]
well that's trippy
didn't realize I never finished this
I mean a lot of circumstances led to
this but in the end I think in the end
I'm happy that I stalled so long until I
found out that I eventually got perms to
finish it because I didn't have it from
the start you know but then
yeah I just didn't catch wind of it
being changed
uh actually I could have finished it I
guess like a year ago
right
possibly but that's okay at least I
noticed
what's this
[Music]
what's she eating teleport to the
entrance is now active Okay so now I
could go back all the way to the
beginning
wait if there's a teleporter here for
the entrance then
judging by RPG rules that means that
behind this door there's something big
right
just using typical RPG logic
I might be wrong
yeah she only eats a lot
her like what's it called not standby uh
motion what's what do they call this
kind of stuff
oh God you guys always know what I mean
I don't yeah
I know idle motion
animation I guess this is the flip side
of that pathway we were walking on just
a little while ago
that is that crazy who knew such amazing
technology existed everything stops you
Turvy and that's all you can think about
bear in mind the core of Rena now sits
above us
pray that we won't encounter many stairs
along the way oh
okay let's see
what awaits this place is so pretty
though by the way
for being such a dooming
evil place
they did a good job building this
[Music]
how are we looking in terms of health
and all that all good
right here it goes
this guy he goes right outside and it
doesn't waste any time and I went in
there too early
regretted spaghetti
[Music]
talking to you
it's not a multiplayer right no I wish
that was possible
that would be so cool
but that will take away a lot from like
what I have to do in a battle because
the whole time I'm like controlling the
others
throwing them in there
you take that away
by multiplayer I guess I have like way
too much time on my hands
but it would be nice because I remember
you know playing because of symphonium
back in the day
with my older brother
that was nice
I was I was the
I was on the sidelines and my brother
was like the main gamer
can't get out of this oh why do I keep
on I don't know why
after this
I'll have to pick up my charger really
quick one second because I
we're at the moment for some reason I
probably like left it somewhere or my
brother took my charger who knows but I
only have one charger right now so I
keep on like bringing it over to my
bedroom and then back here one second
[Music]
foreign
I came back with a charger and some
kitkats yay
[Music]
okay okay
no it's actually chocolates
I know that's confusing because I often
call my cats kitokatoa
what flavor just a normal basic one I
really like the basic KitKat flavor
KitKat is like in the days where oh
where I would like live in Japan and for
a long time and then miss the taste of
European chocolate
I would often go for KitKat in Japan
because even though it tasted still a
little bit different
then uh European chocolate it was pretty
close to its European
um
recipe I guess
how it would taste in Europe the
Japanese KitKat was kind of close to it
as opposed to other chocolates that are
available overseas and just generally
Japanese chocolates why do I stop moving
the whole time what's what's up with
that
really recently this
ever since I updated it it's not working
nicely
I keep on opening and closing it let's
see for how long it works this time
Hickory kick flavor what would that
taste like
a pretty close to a huge chocolate taste
yeah that's that's what I thought at
least like the the main one
so
whenever I felt really desperate about
it what what's going on
I would go for people
it would have a punch for sure
like getting kicked in the mouth
yeah why is it so
um
if I switch to an
a different one than my problem is that
I can't put on all these accessories and
I want The hoodly Doodly though
three two one
until I stop moving no oh
maybe we're good maybe we're good
okay we might be fine this time around
The Little Owl it's a it's a hoodle it's
from the game but it's wearing my
uniform
[Music]
um
let me first start this
thank you
oh good
huh
wait a second
[Music]
um
foreign
not too shabby if I do say so myself far
more than the power I can conjure alone
that's for sure was that a compliment
all right oh there's a lot of thorns
here
with roses
pretty roses
and a door that looks like a face
what are those they look like that's
what you're saying with flowers too
not real ones though they're just like
that flower growing out of Rena
let's be getting close to the great
spirit now
hey renwell what was that thing you said
about how a little bit of danna's great
spirit is inside all of us right huh
that's why Dana's great spirit is so
much more diluted huh weak even I
definitely was a choice so it didn't
overpower others or just the way it is
is anyone's guess
if that's true and wouldn't it mean
Dana's will could never form under
natural conditions
yeah sounds like that's probably the
case
so if Dana exists within all of us then
what if something occurred that brought
everyone's hearts and Minds together as
one
that Unity could potentially act as Dan
as will
you mean if everybody was like thinking
the exact same thing at the exact same
time come on there's no way we could
pull that off
um I know it's a long shot
but it might work
let's assume that's even possible for a
second
would it even be enough to fight back
against Rena's great spirit how would we
know I've tested out if nothing else it
might be an option if we can't use the
Rena Salma
things are different here than on the
surface that's
How Deeply we ventured into Rena and
come to the League it's between me and
she and you don't know where to look
Charming
so here's a question we came all this
way to Rena on the Assumption the
Renaissance here right don't just don't
say it law
yeah but I'm just saying
I said don't what is he saying
I can understand why you might what was
your son's law but you need to remember
that there are people it affects more
directly than you
um they keep on panning over to the
silent Shield oh
sorry
we've managed to make it this far
believing losing faith now won't do us
any good we're better off focusing our
anxiety elsewhere
such as
the great spirit
if hefewrecked 35s to be believed our
enemy won't just be handing over the
renus alma to us at least I think that's
the alien that we talked to right
not only that but that same enemy just
gulped down more than an entire world's
worth of Astral energy
hmm point taken it may be strange to say
but when I'm fighting or at least know
what needs to be done it helps me a lot
I don't doubt myself as much
so thanks both of you
[Music]
the floor's on the ceiling and the
ceilings on the floor this whole thing's
making my head spin why would they even
do something like this it doesn't look
like the ceiling is developer can bend
life forms of their will nothing they
could do with this apparently surprised
me
ceiling is on the floor that doesn't
weird you out what good is a team made
up of members who all share the same
opinions on everything
and besides when you get to be at my
ripe old age one begins to consider it
quite uncouth to show one's true
emotions at times
oh come on Grandpa you can't be that
sands of time wait for none of us lad
yeah we'll see
I guess I'll have to live long enough to
get as old as you first huh
unfortunately you will and when the time
comes I look forward to hearing you
change your tune can't matter deal of
this
[Music]
a little little piece of [\h__\h]
I
don't know
[Music]
I can't add accessories anymore but
oh well I'll at least add poodle on obs
better than nothing
[Music]
I think the sword just won't work well
if I just place it there we can try it
stay
[Music]
I mean I guess it's all right
just the hand is floating
[Music]
like I would have to do it like this so
that it doesn't look too weird
with the hand up but yeah oh well yeah
we don't mind right Raymond style
[Music]
it's okay it's all right if you don't
look too closely you wouldn't notice and
you're supposed to look at the main
screen in the middle anyway
foreign
what are you protecting over there huh
seriously is this a joke
[Music]
shut them down
at least yeah
uh
I know but that's just because they have
this dual theme going on I guess
yeah
I think if I look back on other tales
off games the enemies had way more like
different designs um
we can really make weapons with this
just one thing that stood out to me I
guess but
it's not a problem one second
oh
okay
I felt that was Vesperia really
was it like that in Vesperia
I'm not sure I don't remember the
enemies from there that well hmm
breath of the wild at the same thing
lots of palettes palette swap enemies
yeah that's true too but I feel like
just they still had more variety in like
in the enemies
anyway
pineapple Joe
Apple just give me like some other ones
I don't need all these CP pineapple gels
looks like that and most of them no I
don't think so I don't know great
full of Gray
oh okay first to this side I'm gonna
ignore this dude
[Music]
see
run run run oh wait that's it
yeah
that's the barrier
I've started to do the thing that I used
to do back in the day when I played
Tales of games alone I run from all the
enemies because I'm too lazy to do the
grinding I ring reduces the CP cost of
Arts in long run out fights it can give
the wearer The crucial Edge they needed
to win
um
indeed should I give that someone to
wear
oh dear okay I mean I love those glowy
parts of those designs though
they look cool and I think that's wrong
they're actually gonna go here
but to tell you
satsuko chameleon
okay left first
[Music]
that's why I hate Random Encounters
damn it I couldn't run away from it
all right you will regret that
[Music]
is
oh
it's not like the Headstones
hit
when it's invisible
would that look like it didn't hit
and I'm poisoned again
the famous One
it's like jump jumping rope and I jumped
over the tongue perfectly
oh
I don't even notice that she was over
limit
never disappointing
she's always
100 if not 120 with her mind in battle
oh I should stop using it when it's like
on the move
[Music]
hear my calls
he keeps demolishing flare oh no you'll
hurt yourself oh no
I'm sorry for that senpai
say no more
stops him when he does that
well that would need her to be ready to
use it at that exact moment
[Music]
um
oh dear look at those oh
oh they look powerful I feel like I
could skip them though
I couldn't
look so strong
[Music]
nice break
yeah they really don't look normal
it's a calm it's a conversation right
now
Focus
[Music]
wow that second one hit me
she's ticked off
mommy is coming to the rescue
I love her
you know what I'm glad I'm glad I kept
some Tales of a rise to myself
to enjoy
now
I mean we just started Fire Emblem so it
wasn't really necessary but it's nice
to be back in the jrpg
vibe
because this way
I kind of like breached the time it will
take for the next tails off game a
little bit
for myself
yeah now you can see me finish it on
stream
even though I'm kind of like
disconnected or just yeah this
disconnected from the story quite a bit
emotionally there's like the build up is
kind of dead unfortunately
it's okay I still think it will be epic
and big
and I'll feel sad
yourself finished
there you go it's time to end this
battle I'm right beside you
know
that'll bring you down oh everyone's
ready go go go go
all of you
[Music]
oh
nothing
we're both we're both but it's already
too late we're both in uh what's it
called over limits
and none of us got to use it more energy
than I expected
open this weird looking Treasure Chest
come on
[Music]
inside Mystic Crest a crescent reduces
the casting time for astral Arts it's
coveted by astral artists for all kinds
of for all kinds for its applications
with every variety of artwork how do I
use that
or is this one
is this like a like a ring accessory
when I put on
renwell Maybe
equip it okay
you played Diablo I um played it
no no I'm not dealing with that [\h__\h] no
First Fleet I played it on the stream
before Diablo II
yeah mccroney
[Music]
so okay let's put that on renewal
because that actually makes sense
oh she's currently
using a stamina ring I don't know if
that ever made sense on her
[Music]
Mr Crest oh minus 20 yo
penetration
alexandroid
um
Warrior emblem 15 20.
I know they seem like relatively basic
well I don't know
oh
nice Dodge
[Music]
Which element would you like to have a
push strike with
how would you name the attack
um huh
blue strike with Cali
want to Post strike with Cali
I would name it
um
Eternal damnation isn't that a word
damnation I feel like I've heard it
before
Etsy
[Music]
that sounds so powerful
that is an attack that Persia gets no
way
no way
I'll have to look that up
Tales of Symphonia
eternal
it's called in Japanese
oh
I could I could be a in charge of naming
these kind of special attacks because it
seems like I have the same kind of like
edgy
naming sense
because I I didn't put hands up some
phone here for years and when I played
it I played it in Germany in German in
German so there's no way that I would
have gotten it from
the game before that was all me
that was all me
okay
this should be easy
I just wanted to check if in theory you
could flee this battle because
there's no way to clean right no you
can't
makes sense
you grew up on this yeah oh what are you
trying to say I played it in German
but I totally get like the naming sense
for the Arts yeah
prepare to crumble
you're fine
oh I guess the voice acting was English
yeah but I don't think I heard that once
that specific one very much because if
you also remember recall I never even
finished Tales of Symphonia alone when I
was younger
[Music]
and I probably also didn't know how to
activate Mystic Arts
was a Mystic art for Persia if I just
read correctly
thank you
yeah I I think I remember I was telling
you guys that I went through these games
without knowing how to use these things
for most of the time Mystic Arts just
always use basic attacks
probably one of the reasons why I was
always having such a hard time
deny
denied now we're never
hear my calls
what am I fighting what the [\h__\h] there's
nothing there turn around
oh oh
too late
I never used Mystic Gardens before it
yeah yeah me neither I was just too
young to even like understand
I feel like I completely skipped the
part where they would explain it
yeah the old the ultimate
attacks
that's what I mean the big ones with the
fancy animation
form
s
keep on pushing the same buttons
yo why is it so long they keep on coming
since we're like inverted now going
upside down shouldn't we be crushing
everyone with the elevator oh no
I guess not
[Music]
here we go Victory we have arrived toe
chaku
so where the hell are we now like one
there
yeah if you're young
and play these games when you're really
young
yeah I definitely missed all the details
I didn't know what was going on it was
fun anyway though even when I didn't
know what was going on I still had a
great time oh
we're outside again
oh wait if it's inverted are we going up
or down right now I'm so confused
and I hear audio crackling let me fix it
we're going up now
don't think about it too hard
ah yeah I guess we're going up then why
what what are we trying to escape right
now what what's going on
skip these These are easy to skip
um see the map oh there's two question
marks maybe this is just um item
treasure room hopefully
looks like destination is near
am I far am I close to the
end of the dungeon because that would
mean I'm close to the end of the game
those red alien thingies
they look like they're like straight out
of out of Evangelion to me
but just sized down
so as expected that was a
treasure room he fought the same
yeah another eight to ten hours excuse
me
don't troll me like that there's no way
is it the wings gonna hit me no
oh we're going up we're gonna climb
up the same foreign
disturbing
she owns peace
I replayed air Final Fantasy game on
SNES
yeah as an adult obviously like you get
the best of both worlds because you get
the Nostalgia from playing it as a child
and then also
you get the enjoyment of finally being
able to really understand everything
and like optimize everything get the
most out of the game
like also as a child I would not care
about completion stuff or side quests
and all that and dialogue also wasn't
like that interesting to me but I think
as an adult adult you like put way more
attention to everything hmm
so yes I should replay Tales of
Symphonia just for all of that
there's so much
and I yet have to really see
I feel like it might also almost be as
if I play it for the first time who
knows
lots of materials here
[Music]
I thought it was gonna be a treasure but
no
mysterious fragment
hmm yeah all of this is good for
crafting the weapons but there's no shop
and I think I'm fine even without
crafting new stuff
be fine right
[Music]
unless right before the boss for some
reason it offers me a shop then I'll
take it but
I'm not going back on purpose I failed I
feel fine I feel ready
I'm prepared
[Music]
oh treasure right there I have to fight
them
a dozen times
oh you're also gonna replay it when the
remaster is out
I wish it was a remake though
but even as a remaster it looks pretty
nice
[Music]
[Applause]
thanks for the healing Circle
I would like I don't know I would
I would give anything for a remake
if they would make a Tales of Symphonia
remake I would eat my hat
if you get what I mean
if you catch my drift
which one
the white one
I like the red one
quite a lot
the white ones I wouldn't mind
getting rid of that one
but don't worry I'll buy a new hat
I'll go hat shopping
okay right now my hat is total don't
worry I don't consider that a hat
look at those eyes look at those puppy
peeing eyes how could I eat or even
consider eating poodle
adamantine tendon
totally totally do
odly doodly
okay
Google's here are putting up a real
fight you guys are supposed to be eaten
I said I'll try and eat him why would I
ever say such a thing that's slander I
would never oh there's a star there
places
perhaps they simply thrived freely here
under such harsh conditions I don't give
a damn why they're here we'll burn it
all to the crowd
here it comes what comes
well it's so pretty
uh
what's gonna happen just promise some
story dumped though right
I don't feel like we would fight here
[Music]
in case
the astral energy here is so dense it's
always trying to walk through water is
that what they're trying to show us the
great spirits wheels in the center of
Rena but with the world in this state
the entire planet has become its body
right so doesn't that mean we're already
inside it I would say that is
horrifyingly correct after all the
further we climb the denser the astral
energy becomes
foreign
what's the matter renwell are you not
feeling all right she has a headache
from the big ass noodle on her head it's
nothing like that it just feels like the
energy here is a little more intense
than it was before
you mean Rena's energy yeah it's like
when I made contact but Dan is Will in
the wedge it's almost as though I can
understand what Rena's will is thinking
but Rena's will is supposed to be a lot
stronger aren't we risking the great
spirit controlling us if we interact
with it directly
I don't think we have to worry about
that Brenna's will is only supposed to
control true renins like the helgenquil
if we can discern what the great spirit
is thinking too we might learn something
a weakness but just to be safe let me
contact it alone are you insane
[Music]
didn't even think about it
just go straight in
these
Darkness
wait hold on it's home safe on the other
side there was only meant to be one
world oh
which is which one and your goal is to
make them one
hmm
it sounds nice
fear
what just happened are you jealous are
you all right we're well are you okay
I'm fine I think what were you thinking
you could have gotten yourself killed
he's right you had us all terrified
renwell
I'm sorry I really really am but but I
know now I know how the great spirit
thinks I know what it wants how it feels
just one's a head Pat
Rena's great spirit wants to complete
the world so suddenly it's good what's
that supposed to mean and you say it's
trying to make something
yes exactly originally
was meant to be one world
but that never happened they've stayed
separated and the great spirit wants to
finish the process what do you mean one
world how is that even possible I don't
know but its will is clear that's what
the great spirit is trying to accomplish
the only problem is that since Rena's
energy isn't evenly spread like danus it
seems like it'll vanish before that
happens naturally
so it's trying to absorb Dana while it
still can so that it can force the two
planets to unite is that what you're
saying
the great spirit is scared but it's not
scared the way a rational person would
be it's more raw and undiluted like just
pure fear okay like an animal acting out
of instinct although admittedly an
animal would be easier to communicate
with
at the very least I have my doubts that
it recognizes us as sentient beings with
a reason for coming here
earth water fire and wind energy exist
in both worlds but only Darkness and
Light can be found within Rena and Dana
respectively
the rennis alma as far as we know the
only host capable of harvesting the
astral energy is composed of all six
knowing all that
renwell's findings do sound plausible
I agree but that sounds a lot like
shion's Thorns doesn't it the whole
reason the great spirit is trying to
unite Dana and Rena into one world is in
order to save itself
and if her Thorns are part of the great
spirit then they must also
trying to save themselves
alphan what is it
we thought the only way to free your
Thorns was for you to die
yet despite that they seem to be doing
everything in their power to stop that
from happening to you
screenshot
something wasn't adding up
then I just realized something if the
great spirit doesn't want to die then
neither would your thorns those same
emotions that fear that determination
and its energy must have been the same
thing that was keeping you alive you
were its vessel
in that case is that why her Thorns
caused so much pain to anyone who
touched her because they were trying to
protect themselves
if that's all true then
well it's more than a little ironic
the great spirit merely expresses its
desires I imagine it was the helgenquil
who were likely tasked with putting
together and implementing an actual plan
[Music]
see on
I'm okay we need to hurry and clean this
mess up before it gets out of hand
still even if the current state of the
world is wrong like you said does that
really make everything okay hmm
if the world had been whole from the
start as it should have been
there'd be no Dana and no Runner the
Masters are slaves no Lords no Crown
contest maybe just peace
maybe it might have its own problems
but yeah
a lot of the core problems they have now
will of course be gone
but in order to merge them now
there's a lot of sacrifices that we
would make no
so I don't know why we're all like happy
now
[Music]
to think all this started because of the
great spirit's desire to keep living
the only reason it craves energy is
because it's dying from starvation
you think about it like that maybe the
things that's done aren't so strange
after all
if Rena had been more like Dana things
would have worked out a whole lot better
it's like heverick 35 told us
the Dannon and renin Spirits are meant
to be completely different beings
Rena's energy amassing in one place led
to its developing a powerful will
but that also made it crave energy
sapping Rena dry until it perished
whereas Dana's energy is dispersed
meaning its will never developed to the
same extent and without that hunger Dana
the planet was spared as for which is
correct well I'm not sure it's our place
to even say
still I can't help but think it reminds
me a lot of the dichotomy of The Human
Condition
[Music]
dichotomy what do you mean those who
know not satisfaction are driven to keep
devouring without limit but those who
are content with their lot in life
rarely fulfill their potential
I imagine it's likely that the larger
Rena's great spirit grew the more and
more powerful its hunger also became
everything in my in mauration
when all said and done maybe that's the
hardest thing for people to learn
but even if
we combine it into one world
would like humans like us live there or
those Evangelion aliens
or both
because we both lived there
[Music]
because at least right now they're all
trying to kill us
[Music]
foreign
spirit being
yeah starved
and needing to be in defensive and
aggressive mode right now
[Music]
yeah I'm allowed to play it to the end
that's what I'm doing right now
even though we're all kind of like
struggling to remember what's going on
you're welcome to stand
to struggle together
I refuse
[Music]
is
here oh that's the really good stuff
and they respond and yet
they're unable to catch me
this
is confident we have to kill that one
though unless we can take your detail
around it yeah but nah
[Music]
little help I feel like a above
the skies
[Music]
keep on trying to lower the volume when
I'm fighting and then make it higher
when I'm not fighting
it just got so loud in the fights guys
I mean in my ears it's not so bad I'm
just lowering it on OBS balancing it out
but on your side apparently
needs some adjustments
by the way I got the clean
art it's not really art like
[Music]
um
promotional Idol outfit
this is pretty
I can upload it later on Twitter if you
guys want and also I didn't notice this
maybe it was already available earlier
but I saw it through like elfie's tweet
quite necessary when creating
that on The Deco Hollow 27
page you can see like the illustrations
the full body illustrations that were
made
for our each of our songs did you see
mine the key visual basically
yeah they wrote low five
I can't believe it
at this point it must be on purpose
it's impressive but she was joking about
it so she wouldn't want to live here
with all of this around
I know what you mean there are no fish
here I couldn't cook any of my delicious
dinners for you all if we lived here huh
clearly the worst Point against it no
fish so we can't live here exactly
low 5 15. maybe she should just
officially change her name to Lo-Fi
foreign
[Music]
did you guys notice
but it's not that noticeable I think for
most people it's hard to catch
they would they wrote Kiara instead of
kiwawa
what's up with that
oh yeah it's like friction what are you
thinking of Bangor
did you see a mistake that I didn't even
know about
okay we're about to check
oh
he's doing way more missing cards than
I'm doing today how does she do it
[Music]
I did it again
consider yourself finished
oh
I actually don't know
you're the one who did the heavy lifting
I was gonna decide on my set list and
practice tomorrow because the stream is
really late so I was going to do it
during the day
um
but there's definitely more Christmas
songs
[Music]
um that would be unarchived so it's
probably gonna be on our time
foreign
that's a long Corridor do you see that
also all of these look like cookies to
me
[Music]
um
I feel like the end is close
[Music]
is that a treasure or just a
no that's just a material okay never
mind what
what
can I just walk through a place
sirs excuse me um you look like you
enjoy beer I can maybe provide you with
some beer um I'll make it myself I have
a lot of wheat I think that's how you
make beer
I mean I see your
with your bellies not trying to link
be mean or rude or anything but
seriously they felt insulted
sorry for assuming
that you guys enjoy it a good fresh cold
beer on the summer day
[Music]
you guys
know I don't like any kind of alcohol
I
tried like some kind of wines before and
some cocktails and all that but beer I
never tried because I already knew it
was the smell that I wouldn't like it
don't drink I enjoy beer wine is better
outside it was good oh yeah outside of
my friends like spider
I guess cider is very easy
enjoyable for people who don't like
a whole much
can be very yummy from what other Paris
well maybe beer doesn't smell at all
I wouldn't say that
[Music]
austrians make very good beer from what
I've heard from my mom
and they all smell like beards
be your smell
I mean if you like beer then you
probably will grow to like the smell too
and then it doesn't even bother you
that again is probably just a matter of
whether or not you force yourself to get
used to it which I could do but I don't
wanna
be down
I like beer that's all right here let me
help should we eat your own it's just
I'm kind of like weird about all kinds
of alcohol
it's just me
that's just me
blah blah
oh
nice for what
she was just talking about it
and then she got ready to do it right in
that moment
don't make this probably more reasons
than just the taste
for me it's probably also my
subconscious deciding for me that it's
disgusting
but I'm happy with that decision so
I'm not gonna attempt to change it
[Music]
beer is way too bitter wine is bitter
too though
alcohol just in general tastes bitter
too many bullseyes
Magic
foreign
[Music]
okay
oh we're done
yo weaklings
looks like we came out on top we just
need to make sure we stay right
here
I probably just want some snacks
didn't bring my cat food sorry
sure you would enjoy it though
[Music]
poison [\h__\h]
isn't that voice on the ground no never
mind I guess not
hey
thanks for your patience
[Music]
here we go again
hey
that's what my cats are for thank you
Sarah their Arts were interrupted
too
oh
by the way
my date of when I'm going back is pretty
much set now I'm not gonna tell you
exactly that
it's set in stone and it's gonna be
yeah a whole a whole month wow very busy
this is really something okay not that
busy though don't worry I'm gonna when I
say very busy
it'll mean like last time
most likely but but only a small
fragment of it in the big picture it's a
long time but also a lot of
opportunities
to bond with that much pointy the girls
who are there
Kelly and
who knows who else
yeah because last time we had that
opportunity it was a long time ago
in the in the western big lands
no gooda doesn't live in Japan
we're all just like going there
or yeah
temporary but kind of a long stay uh
what is this Elemental attack
maybe for rain well
at stage Max HP
[Music]
and win well need some more
craziest attack
a mental attack greatly
hope for this morning you mean Japanese
morning streams
I'll try to stream like maybe around
Japanese noon time or so every now and
then
[Music]
raises Stevens
when I streams are like night when you
say night do you mean in the middle of
the night after midnight or
[Music]
four or five a.m for us and yeah yeah I
know
I guess you should be used to it by now
this is just
such as the life of a kfp
there's always some streams that are
shitty to catch
but you really shouldn't be complaining
I live in you I do so many streams that
are good for you
like actually always
some start a bit early and just because
they're gonna be in Long streams but
you can't you can't complain now this
looks like kind of like an important
spot um
I'll save
yeah it's not forever it's just
for a while
you know some other people can
maybe come to my streams for once
um
you think I will be fine in terms of
healing items
um
I'm not going back now
saved anyway I
don't so what are these
astral energies separated
first I guess I'm going
this way
oh okay is there a special order
what is this fire astral energy
separator okay let's let's follow this
[Music]
many bosses got ahead of this area
okay that uh
little fights in every area all right
all right this doesn't look so
challenging though it's just normal
enemies and he's I guess sleeping on the
thing I have to activate
display for this one
thingy maybe it's not that that
normal
going
can't get out of things
so we gotta do this like six times
okay does that mean six more times until
the big bus or six more times until more
or more smaller
annoying moms
there are still more left
different types of enemies
see tea time is good for me I'm doing
work at night
[Music]
this case it's good yeah
all night through your ships
[Music]
not take responsibility for that
some jobs don't need much attention oh
thank God
uh we can really make weapons with this
who's this oh more armor equipment
should come in handy
wait I didn't even activate anything
here
[Music]
me killing the enemy
what does the trick
the enemy artist here okay
hmm
when job says no phones
[Music]
are you working for FedEx
I heard no phones at FedEx
oh my God
we haven't seen that one before I think
what the [\h__\h]
I bet that one could give me a decent
workout planning to fight it alone no
way I need your help
uh
well it'll be fine
Sword Dancer
oh my God
[Music]
it thinks two extra hands is enough to
beat me
sorely mistaken let's just focus on
what's important
let's see
do I have enough attention I think I do
have enough attention
Stay With Me
[Music]
wait what did you see yesterday
in the middle of the night it was like I
think 2 A.M my time
thank you
wasn't allowed to say anything
beforehand so I kept real quiet
yeah but I was so happy that she wanted
me to call in
so excited about it it was so fast it
was so quick and uh
[Music]
as much time as I was allowed to maybe I
was just at the end when
when I knew oh oh I gotta go I just need
to squeeze in one more the width request
because that one was important I had
that one planned I had that one written
down because I was of course once again
preparing but anytime when I get that's
true participate in something like this
for like
pull his request I always
think about it beforehand
about what I would want them to do
because I don't want to do the same
thing that everyone else asks for and I
don't want to ask for anything boring I
want to ask for something special it up
you only get this opportunity
in rare occasions
remember when foreign
I did like some kind of
Western meme Recreation
[Music]
that was a big deal suddenly
I was at 1hp for like half a second
is it the promo that's a great service
she was so cute
and I I saw later in screenshots first
of all there was like one Godly
screenshot that I saw from the whipping
she was winking at the same time and the
whip was just also perfectly positioned
I was like oh my God I I didn't take the
screenshot but I'm the one who made this
happen so I'm a genius
is her fairy diapers Bloomers actually
boots
[Music]
yeah
uh
got some good screenshots from that too
huh
wait what the other enemy didn't do [\h__\h]
like this
not the code soon
not by a long time
Where do I
hey it seems to be inside of its mouth
maybe
I I think I see it yeah it's inside
that's a special block compared to
another five oh okay so the other five
will be more like the first one I met
I keep on rolling keep on rolling roll
back roll back roll back
okay
thanks for the mattresses
this one actually looks very different
from the other Google so I appreciate it
but it's [\h__\h] creepy
relatively words playing Dark Souls
[Music]
I guess
but then everybody was like no stop it
you're not supposed to do that
Scarlet Inferno oh that was a normal one
right because I didn't do anything
another 10 memberships wow thank you 15
in total but different people right
thank you thank you
so sweet
yeah all the lurkers now also get
memberships so say something in the chat
I think I'm getting stronger
say something
I'm giving up why the [\h__\h] do I have
five mentions what's going on
speaking of the devil I got five
messages from Pomo
[Music]
as if she knew but no no it wasn't about
what I was just talking about I don't
think she's listening a wedding dress
what
you guys aren't gonna comment on that
um no comment on this one
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
so um mundane this one we got before
wedding dresses for her
address board when exchanging vows with
that special someone they'll cumbersome
to fight and it nevertheless feels aware
of determination
okay I guess that is
more protective than the other things we
have
interestingly
so I think
oh we might have well one of those new
armor pieces for everyone now
one each
[Music]
interesting that that's the one piece
they gave us at the very end of the game
as if we're preparing xion to get
married right after this
hahaha
I think you are playing Taylor swift
arrest final now is just to see Shield's
feet again no I don't give a [\h__\h] about
shion's feet what
oh
what's so good about her for all those I
never even noticed that she is like
showing her toes in this outfit I like
her boots though
hmm
uh why didn't I go in yet you probably
[Music]
clip
no I don't give a [\h__\h] about her feet
no whatever I said before was
exaggerated
holy [\h__\h] is down
on the floor
[Music]
in the weeks before
you
be angry
oh my God
and they were all funny also Puma was
dancing a lot was killed
dance
you're cute I want to dance with her
I'll just give myself a small heel
because the rest Shield is supposed to
be taken care of
them but we're getting a little bit
wrecked right now what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
up
from me and Richard takes up from the
enemy
keep on dodging keep on dodging
what's that
the game again
did you guys notice that too or is it
just me
you made me angry oh stop that was a bad
idea
oh you guys know this too huh
it's too many special effects I guess
for my PS3
I laughed
of the stream too oh maybe that was my
PC then
[Music]
oh that's scary wait when I had
something like this before didn't my PC
kind of like
blue screen I was still after that
like like not directly after but do not
do it
come on it's time
something like that happens
no further
oh it's a PS4 never mind
I have a piece of peaceful though
somewhere buried on the Shelf
no idea I don't know I've never checked
that
it's probably fine
a whirling struggle and I got another
mansion
that wasn't pomodo
[Music]
no more
oh another one
I must say though I feel like the
battles are so much longer
like for example battles and Tales of
Symphonia or is that just mean
s battle feels like really really really
really really long
time
earlier
[Music]
but yeah these ones might be
awesome
wildfire
I want to see more of that
when when someone like Greenwell is
charging a spell
and then I interrupt her with the the
special attacks on the hard one Victory
on the pad thingy
does that interrupt her spell too or is
that like separate
so did I pick up an item no
and the Raptor
because like I heard her like spelling
something
while I was doing
that and I thought oh oh maybe I just
interrupted something important
it does
well I can't really pay attention to
what everyone's doing she's usually kind
of in the back and
doing whatever
ah my phone just restarted itself
m
which one did I go in first this one or
this one
light or Earth
well if I go in I will see there's no
more enemy right if I already did it
hopefully
this one I've not been in yet
um okay
a couple more this might be the the
fourth one four out of six
yeah this is the fourth I think
prepare to crumble oh this one I don't
see nothing
[Music]
shot
every fight is chaotic in this game
it's just the style
here she goes again
[Music]
what was it yesterday
and it was supposed to be at least two
servings but as I told you on the memory
stream I kind of [\h__\h] up some of the
if it's in the chicken schnitzels
kind of wasted some proof there I guess
let's see so I might just cook the next
recipe
it's already Saturday anyway
[Music]
she chose it myself
I'm proud I miss the members
a chill and fun stream until it wasn't
anymore
but even then I was still having a good
time but now the game that we played it
was nice for like an hour or two
okay but then okay thanks I've got
enough of this now
not enough
you can really make weapons with this
and it seems like it's not only me
experiences a lack of cats probably what
now it means you should give them some
critique about that
so who gets the new stuff Fortress armor
no
Spirit roll
and I feel like we got one more
[Music]
is this the new one but it's just not as
good as the rare plate
huh
didn't we get another one besides the
stage bro
it was the Fortress armor
it's only a little bit weaker
did we get the rare plate also in this
dungeon
it's a bit of an exaggeration though
isn't that weird
yeah we got it earlier there's no way
that you can get this one before the
other one and yet it's weaker
[Music]
image
huh
[Music]
which makes no sense
all right this side should be done
oh I think I'm missing the the middle
one maybe and that one over there maybe
[Music]
ah no this one looks opened
there's no enemies
a middle one taken
I need to do light and dark
okay
good job guys paying attention taking
notes
is this light and darkness water
fire dark
best armor comes from our quest for her
um I did so many quests
I don't think I got that at least the
rare plate was better
than anything else I have
put dispose of the trash
it's not happening before I go back to
Japan after all
do it uh and since I don't want to do it
in Japan it's also not gonna happen
it's gonna be a break again
I mean I don't want such a long break
though but I'll be in Japan
[Music]
if we could do it at the end of February
but I'll be in Japan at the end of
February
[Music]
I'll think about it though because I
don't want such a long break
about it
slow-mo Matrix
[Music]
uh if you mean like doing it in an
actual Studio
that's pretty impossible we could do it
in VR but as far as I know most Japanese
members don't have a VR setup
I was thinking of using it for when I
interview
myth and ID because they have VR setups
most of them most of ideas first
generally I think
kissing
[Music]
corruption
here I come out
maybe I can inspired them to get a VR
set up though like maybe they were
planning on getting one eventually and I
can be like the reason why they actually
do get it
[Music]
I'll offer them to do it in 3D but
they'll need VR
I got to borrow Luna's VR setup or
Dana's vrself you know
that's the good thing when I guess you
live somewhat in reach to others unlike
en
foreign
am I right or am I right
I wanna heal now my clothes
really okay that's that doesn't seem
like something you care about
assistant makes distance makes the heart
grow thumb oh wait no actually
in collabs even as you may have seen
before with
a shiny mood because
they played around with it hey and even
with that
I wouldn't be able to do like all the
camera angles and all that
it's better to just use VR for that and
have someone control the camera angles
and then
you know yeah
but we have yet to play around with that
up and like um that
option to use
pretty as a collab
I don't know if it works really properly
yet though but
um
[Music]
I did a whole VR chat famous most a day
but it might have not even been full
um body pretty
I could just do it from the PC
I don't know the day I never saw
something like that
well thank you
say no more
well done
I like
um yeah white bread but like I feel like
not the one that would be like typical
in America or or Japan even
not the typical like toast bread or so
I mean I feel like just in Europe
red is like a whole culture
of its own and we have really [\h__\h]
good bread especially in I don't know
Central but I think all of you
I like smelly bread I also like them uh
what's it called
again it's kind of like a brown looking
bread on the outside but inside it's
white
magic is there I don't even know if you
guys have that in other continents
no uh no it's like like the Britain the
pretzels but we have it not only for
pretzels but also um
but also for like normal
shaped bread but it basically tastes and
looks like what pretzels look like
with pretzels you know there's more
holes than there is bread to them
so you can't make a proper sandwich with
it
so we invented
normal like rolls of bread
with that
so good player demolisher
there's just one kind of bread that I
feel like we don't really do much here
in Europe and I've just never had it
before it it probably exists but we just
I I would say we don't like it much here
always talk about cornbread
I I can't imagine get friendly with that
but maybe also just because
we don't see it much here I don't see it
at all
look sharp
is cornbread even bread or is it just
one of those things where they use a
word and it's not really what they say
it is valuable as I think it is
bread
why do they give us like two sets of new
armor throughout the whole dungeon how
about like giving us something else
weirdos
this one's better than the produce one
this one's also better
like a side dish oh yeah yeah I think
you guys told me before
potato bread
[Music]
potatoes I love potatoes
cornbread with Branch it's different
barbecue
[Music]
but one thing I always have to say I
think maybe in America they're not so
bad either but our croissants are goat
croissants in Japan are more often myths
than they are hit
there's some
good bakeries that do good croissants
but what's pretty rare is I as far as my
experience can tell
is croissants with fillings while here
we have that like everywhere
like croissants with chocolate filling
or jam and so on
and in Japan
I don't see it so often anyway even when
I do the chocolate they fill it with
often it doesn't taste so good but then
we're back to the topic of chocolate
in Japan
and when I say it doesn't taste so good
again that's just like me with what my
taste buds are used to
[Music]
same would be probably the other way
around I mean
the Japanese people who have given like
European chocolate they all really liked
it
[Music]
even though they must be used to
Japanese chocolate
[Music]
I guess you can't just dislike such a
high quality chocolate
yeah
it just is better
but
the hotel I stayed at
um in my last trip
I never used the breakfast I had there
because I just always woke up too late
but there was a a bakery super close and
I went to so many times and they
actually made really good bread
but again the croissants that I tried
then the the chocolate they they used
was like so I ended up not buying it a
second time but one thing they did
really good was like a salty buttery
bread white bread
almost like a salad but like it reminded
me of the sidestanna but it's not really
that
the satch dangan are less buttery and
more crunchy and this one was a little
bit less spongy but it has a good and
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
discussing
discussing bread with someone who said
an opinion that was wrong
yeah
we're gonna start the officers
today I ate I ate a pretzel actually
and what I just said was I wanted to eat
it with some like um sliced sausage uh
what do you call it again in English
but instead of cutting the Bread open
since there's like barely any surface to
put it on because the pretzel is so slim
cold cuts
uh nobody even told me that but I
thought of it myself cold cuts yeah so
instead of cutting it open and putting
the cold cuts inside I just wrapped it
around the pretzel
put like a
um what would you call it like a blanket
big brain yeah it works it works if it
works it works what these
safety of Astral energy separators are
confirmed activate transference device
to surface and what
happens when I get sacked with it what
that mean
s
this sounds really important but I don't
know what it means
and this is how I leave to the beginning
okay
ah okay I just activated it that's what
I wanted okay so to save save
[Music]
you just phrase it more easily please
don't understand
um
I should probably full heal before going
in should I
[Music]
go
okay I mean that looks good
wait did I did I use all the
armors did I give that to everybody
[Music]
yeah I think so
um anymore
items that I can use consumables nope
okay
[Music]
I guess
this might be it
seems like we're at the source
[Music]
did I hear myself after saving or before
saving
should have just looked to the right
side waist
ah whatever after well at least it can
save my my CP
I wanna
go back
to my save file
foreign
[Music]
why don't we just use this
wait what are you gonna do please
scare me like that what is there
something wrong with it
no it's not that
it's just this is it
whatever it is we're about to find out
[Music]
there's no turning back now till we've
won
either we get through this or we vanish
along with the rest of the world as we
know it oh [\h__\h] is everyone ready um
well now I say we knock this thing out
and head back home
it's time to relegate the path to where
it belongs it's been a long journey
getting here but it ends now
this isn't the end
once we've over
a world without divisions where no one
cares whether you're Dannon or renin or
if you have magic or not you're right we
have to win this
[Music]
let's get going then after all our
future awaits
[Music]
our future one free of tyranny and
exploitation
for the freedom to live with those we
hold dear and for a new era sounds too
good to be true
let's go
[Music]
once you proceed past this point there's
no turning back
didn't you tell me that before that's
the Astro stream and proceed onward
let's go
cool cutscenes here we go
[Music]
well what
is this close-up
[Music]
so close I can see her nose hairs
hold on I'm probably on her hand but
covered by the bigger
[Music]
foreign
where's the big boss
[Music]
you must manifest into something
are we on that giant flower
finally here then
then where is the core of the great
spirit
or the Renaissance for that matter
according to have Rec 35
this should be where we find the core
renwell do you sense anything
definitely where the energy of the great
spirit is strongest but what's giving
off the most energy is the flower we're
standing on hmm
that said we're not going to be able to
destroy something this huge
you want me to hit it see what happens
hey look huh
foreign
[Music]
what
stay sharp something's coming up
[Music]
once it's gone it has so much anger
all of its fear has evolved into hatred
maybe give it a Snickers
in order to fight us
ing on this phone
can it not I'm certain of it
this is the source of my Thorns and of
my visions
darkness that will consume all
not that vision is too loud
[Music]
what do we do now run us
run aside
[Music]
now this is physical form cutting
through is what we'll do
yeah
we can do this
it's manageable
I like how it's waiting for us
great experience
that's very clear
however if you're planning on destroying
everything
first you'll have to get through us
[Music]
everyone
she'll go for you that way
humankind has a right to determine them
okay
sounds like anguish from our world that
it may be filled with joy and peace once
again
[Music]
right here right now
dreams
[Music]
wait
come on
down
like energy balls
I have to take care of I guess
being surprised I said we destroy it and
quit
alive
[Music]
blah blah blah
don't you think I'm serious
[Music]
I know what it is
you as well
transform into something even more crazy
after list
okay
no go for it prepare to crumble you
think we overdid it okay okay
[Music]
four hours
through
[Music]
yeah that's the wrong one
let me help me
please
the only one that was like he's like
pretty much dead
no way
here
[Music]
this ends now consider yourself fitted
finishing blow beautiful with
she on an elephant
buddy
but after all that it's still standing
just how strong is this thing it doesn't
matter
just have to keep kicking its ass until
it Bites the Dust
wow
it looks the same you want a transform
into something cooler oh damn
serving its energy for an escape that
faster took off with the Renaissance
almost stand here and wait for it to
come back
we'll have to follow it through there
for the whole
effect is always happens
yeah eventually you like matter what we
can't let it get away go into another
dimension all right
let's go
darkened
spooky and but is this another like
dungeon where please no
[Music]
I'm surprised we can stand here at all
what did we walk in this place oh it's
me I've never seen anything like it this
is not quite without taking off but
where's the great spirit look already
works
oh
[Music]
I've got roses
oh this is bad it looks like it's
regaining all of its energy it's going
to grow even bigger than me
come on we've got to find a way to watch
out something's heading our way
what's that this looks like a disc for
my PC yes they're here to try to start
Drive there's so many of them that means
we've got it Running Scared let's take
these out and keep moving
get out of
too loud
installing me
so it can evolve yeah that's the problem
protagonists will never learn
they will never get it they always just
wait for their enemies to grow stronger
and stronger
and then we'll be like oh my god wow
oh you can barely hear the attacks oh I
made it a little bit too quiet huh
Powell
policing wipers
make it quick nowadays boring stall mobs
player demolisher
let's go to colorful island in the
middle of space
I feel like what happens often in tails
off games is like at the end where you
look for the final boss
you end up in some kind of like space
avoid like place
where you have to go for portals that
are kind of like a maze
and eventually you finally end up at the
bus
yeah that's all they are pitching
I feel like it happens definitely for
um
what was it uh Tails uh
it's one of my favorites I forgot the
name
mine's empty
head empty
okay
Celia two definitely had that
[Music]
my favorite
maybe maybe yeah
but that just proves my point
that's funny
rise up was a volcano
Google search what do you Google Search
for which kills off games end in space
that's such a weird thing to Google
Grace's was in space yeah Grace's was in
space
I remember going to space Oh that was
like an like an attraction in Disney
just now
you know where you sit in like a keynote
movie theater seat and like moves along
and you're like on a on a ride of like a
like an airplane or so I'm not like a
airplane more like a jet plane
we caught up to it
there we go
looks the same as five minutes ago
[Music]
yeah yeah it does the simulator hold on
why did it stop absorbing the energy
from Dana like it or not it lacks the
means to do so whilst fighting us we've
become the bigger threat and forced its
hand
all right then let's get to work so we
can take back the renaissama
this one has weak spots on its arms and
hands
subsumer is the name
no right now right now and
huh this time
for some reason that's
natural
hell I'm just getting warmed up you
ain't seen nothing yet
stay on your toes everyone
our damage output has been
closing on you
ready
[Music]
I mean honestly though that's my my
fault I can't expect too much because I
got it on sorry man try harder
you and me
from here on out
[Music]
oh okay one hand dead okay yeah it is
step by step
all that actual energy
[Music]
down
here
it told me a special one but I was like
out of what was that
I guess
let's do it
different from usual
oh
a new weird hole on the ground
we did it wait there's one black hole
and one universe
where are you going
[Music]
oh oh no no no no
it's just making it bigger but is there
a timer
here let me heal you
this is it this ends now oh
I think it wanted me to do specific ones
whoa whoa that's all that's left
of winner
or are we somewhere we're somewhere else
but something else right just a fighting
platform
another face well I would welcome it
and we were on that thing that's for
sure
and then see us falling down or anything
though
long black screen
still alive
let's go
fine with me
oh but we got the Renaissance
we're going to start the ceremony now
before it can recover it's all just like
[\h__\h]
I have that thing as merch by the way
got that as a special gift
of being an ambassador
[Applause]
what's his name
yeah
I've returned just as I told you I was
so cool
he did the great spirit is Reviving
itself
amateurs
should have changed her clothes into
them
the other ones
dress
[Music]
shielding the great spirit
oh
apologies oh I can't suppress it for all
very long
painful
laughs
she won't
hand it over right now okay
plan to use this to defeat the great
spirit
which is precisely why I'm here
stand aside and watch
chill
remember what we're doing before no
how did
his Justice while it's you and your
sorry a lot the great spirit that tried
to control me will be annihilated won't
let you do that you do it I shall and
there's nothing you can do to stop me
[Music]
bastard which one fill my duty as a
ruler 101
with this power I'll bury that woman and
the great spirit then this charade will
finally end
s
[Applause]
come at me bro
oh
hey I've been no no he's the real one
I want you
save everyone
and see us
[Music]
that's it this is so you can rule over
all existence just because
[Music]
oh my headache is coming back
a sovereign
[Music]
oh
we have enough gels
[Music]
for that
pressing the Dodge button like five
years before that
[Music]
will beg me for mercy
but you will know but not today
wait
[Music]
I can't I can't let him use that but I
don't have really interesting
[Music]
foreign
don't you understand
[Music]
the ending destruction
the weakness disgusting my hand hurts
you're wrong
[Music]
takes true power
to forgive [\h__\h]
[Music]
good cutscene
this strong shall always Triumph here it
goes like one of those fighting games
[Music]
you can't have been alone your whole
life
strikes spreading the scheme of fire
across my back the Masters who killed
and the slaves who sacrificed their
compatriots that they might live so much
is there no way for you to see this
difference
[Music]
maybe it is selfish of me to want to
save her but I swore that I would let no
one else be sacrificed in this battle I
can't death
[Music]
try this you picked the wrong fight
script it try this I am the truth shall
be banished
[Music]
right now
the power cion has been stowed upon me
down you picked the wrong [\h__\h] flame
inside me though
it's over
practical impeding my progress
[Music]
that's my line I'll show you the limits
of your solitude
[Music]
oh so intense
RTX off
hmm
[Music]
what you've done to people
there's no denying that oh we have mercy
I know you didn't walk your path out of
weakness but merely from misguided
strength
misguided because you were alone
you had no friends to keep you on a
straight and narrow
no one to use all that strength for
other than yourself
that loneliness could make a monster out
of anyone
[Music]
it's me
I understand and I forgive you full run
I don't need your Victor's pity
choke on your vain forgiveness
what
why are we so stupid to be so nice this
world
to make your selfish dreams into reality
if you choose to walk that path you
choose a path of betrayal Despair and
Corruption and in the Darkness at the
end I'll be waiting for you
[Applause]
bad end game over
foreign
[Music]
don't we need that thing
don't we need it though I'm sorry
the rain is almost
[\h__\h] gone
but you still
the Blazing Sword
it may not be quite as strong as the
Renaissance
but nonetheless
I can't I would never it would kill you
my Thorns there
soon the great astral spirit will break
free
and when that happens no one will be
spared
[Music]
Badness
that's exactly what we've been fighting
to prevent
I promised I would find a way to save
you
[Music]
and you failed because you were too
[\h__\h] nice I know
I don't want you to die either
[Music]
don't let
end of the world no
[Music]
no way
gosh
[Music]
no Cleaver trust today
no no
[Music]
that's not the ending is it
let's
look
the past Dennis energy flowed through
still open
we can use it to call out to Dennis will
Alvin
what are you saying what are you saying
don't you remember
rinwell said there was a little bit of
Dennis will inside all of us
there is a way everyone can come
together to form Dana's will
and maybe we can ask for it to help us
to find us a way out of this
[Music]
all of Dana thinks of saving us it will
become the will of the planet itself
it's Madness
maybe so but it's the only way we can
see
[Music]
a new way to save
Morena that's right renas will never had
evil intent
saving everyone
that includes them
I don't want to live in a world without
you see on it
I'm tired of living a life built on
death
[Music]
I'm with you
Collective will of Danna hear my plea
I wanna save xion
and I want to save Brenna too
I want to end this cycle of one Joy
constantly being sacrificed for
another's pain
so please
grant us your strength
[Music]
oh that got me
that was good voice actor
foreign
[Music]
thank you
blame if it happens
[Music]
foreign
need to make a lives
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
basketball
too
[Music]
good job guys
character development
[Music]
this one was not a good dude our first
boss thanks for
not being too hard on us
[Music]
kind of forgot about it
if only she wasn't evil we could have
been best friends forever
[Music]
evil protagonists
keep going
[Music]
I had to walk
foreign
world now
looks like it
is
more
aftermath
xiaomi
please
wow it's also anime
good morning
[Music]
to grow up in
now y'all also got a old kiss at least
rainbow in law
[Music]
where where is she
that looked like a big Hood
[Music]
pretty
oh no
oh yeah thanks
[Music]
foreign
makes me happy
[Music]
just like the flowers
so let's tell me
[Music]
about yeah just like the flowers
[Applause]
I know I know I know
[Music]
tomorrow
[Applause]
[Music]
one more
oh it's just calm sad song
well well well well it's a bit difficult
to say
uh my thoughts but I think I kind of
said it at the end of like the original
ending it's difficult to say it now
because it's hard to remember what I
felt but I'm pretty sure it was mostly
positive feelings
yeah it's satisfying to see it until the
end now
it's a happy ending and good one I feel
like
um the the fight at the end against
Wolverine was like totally unexpected uh
and it being one-on-one
made me feel a little bit challenged
there uh until the end where I was
suddenly
unbeatable
but that was really cool
um
I like those kinds of fights they're way
more challenging because you're on your
own with no healer yeah yeah yeah and it
feels like kind of like he's our mirror
our evil mirror
since he looks similar to us and he has
like the opposite element and all that
[Music]
um
I was a it was a nice showdown at the
end and I like that they really like let
she on an elephant get it on at the end
because like I feel like in a lot of
games and animes
they don't take that step they like
always just like
hint
that
and pick the the whatever the main
characters or whatever are made to be
together forever in the future but they
never like
yeah kids they just hug at most yeah
so so say so always but that's the case
come on
and
it made me feel Doki Doki
wait for the question yeah I'm waiting
I'm waiting I'm waiting
they finally smooched
it was it was fun I kind of made it easy
for me
by using story mode but that way it was
smoother
um I guess a normal or hard mode
you would have
felt uh it all as a bit more of a
challenge so if you're into that then go
for that but I think it's okay to just
enjoy the story too right yeah yeah
finished it in a good amount of time
four and a half hours noise
and there was one tails off game I think
maybe
I don't want to say anything wrong but
there was one tails off game where like
one of the main characters
ends up like in the ending just becoming
the God and watching over it might have
been
it might have been look sillier one
episode
and that kind of made me sad because
they can't like be with the rest of
their group but it wasn't their Syria oh
can't be with the rest of their group at
the end like after everything has been
done to save the world and
you want to like live out the happy life
together right but
whatever game that was because you guys
are seeing different ones but
I guess it's very cereal
yeah that that was just uh got renting
and heartbreaking but this way
is I mean
I liked it because that was different
and it's not the perfect happy ending
and
you know often jrpg's endings can just
be too ideal Too Perfect it's nice to
bring something in where it's not
perfect
yeah something about Celia too was
definitely very different too I I
everything about cilia 2 was very
different but the ending too hmm
as well yeah
[Music]
um so this brings it back to a little
bit more of a classic tales off ending
but
it was still very very very enjoyable
enjoyable and I really liked it man
now they can all
just be happy and live a normal life
that they deserve
super nice and welcomed yeah
well the originally I wasn't planned to
be a tails game huh
what
[Music]
I cannot believe Jim would die at the
end you know I I
kind of fun Soto and I would have
accepted it because
you know it would have been different
and dramatic oh seems to be the end
foreign
[Music]
now we get some colored
well I use the concept Arts
[Music]
the light mode is on no more dark mode
sorry guys for your eyes
hello
well we also cannot forget about the
fact that I was or am the English
uh World whatever
um oh killed kasara
um Ambassador official Ambassador and it
was an honor for me to represent this
game promote this game
to some more people I think a lot of you
guys
bought the game because of me and are
now even also playing it again because
of me some of you guys
so yeah I'm really glad to bring tales
off closer to some more people who
weren't
you know that much intrigued by it just
yet but this was a great great honor for
me I'm not in the credits but
hmm
maybe maybe next time huh no
I really like
I've been into tales off games for such
a long time and they played a big role
for me to
how my whole connection with Japan was
created
so being able to give back a little bit
acute
give back a little bit as the Ambassador
just makes me happy yeah it's just a
full circle by that
um
oh I would love to like maybe voice act
something even just a sad character one
day yeah
then then maybe we come full circle in
the second Circle
I love poodle so much food will
definitely my favorite
mascot of all tears off games ever
[Music]
and don't what was its name Rolo I think
a cat from cilia I think
so we have two
was you know just by being a cat
quite something but um
I love hoodly doodly do
[Music]
yeah there's a cute companion mascots in
general oh
hell I'm playing the violin again
[Music]
with his friends
no and we're watching in the back
it's kind of a fancy violin man
that looks expensive as hell
[Music]
hey what else I'm just here
yo
maybe you were listening to my well when
I just said that I would I would love to
I don't know voice act uh even a side
character one day
wait what I can't see
uh must be like a green name right
every
[Applause]
[Music]
so long
I I I I feel like I need to um justify
why it took so long let's
[Music]
listen okay I can't stream it now
anymore anyway so I'll just take my time
so I took my time and then I just kind
of you know she didn't want to continue
because I didn't want it to end because
then I would have to wait so long but
then also at the same time you know
let's try to opening a streamer who
plays games for your job and
[Music]
um
look at them
cute making plans for something
yeah and then I recently found out
I can actually play the ending so here
we are
so where's their baby
where's the baby
can I get to know the baby
[Music]
I love this I don't think in any tales
off game they've ever went that far
[Music]
oh my God
we're having protagonists or like the
main characters Mary oh my God
[Music]
they've implied marriage but they've
never shown it so bold oh
[Music]
so sweet they've made it
in the beginning
I was like
ah no one could touch xion but now she's
so happy she can hug everyone and all
that hmm
you finished the game
yes I did I did finally
I did it
oh
it was a great finale
I really like the boss fight
Wolverine was
was very intense
but Alpha needs he's just too nice he he
who should have just
freaking take it learned a lesson not to
trust Warren but okay he's just he's
just a nice guy yeah
round two
ah new quest for brand new adventures
and Encounters of it the clear data save
point is right before the final battle
ah you have also unlocked the new game
plus mode on title screening on
flashlight to carry over you cleared it
into new games yeah yeah
ah
say
I'll just put it into another one oh
they have the image in the background
oh
do we get a different like
starting screen image too
[Music]
I feel like this one was dangerous to
play on stream
it was then we'll cut this one out later
because if you want to watch it just
Google it on YouTube YouTube it on
YouTube I guess
oh no this seems like the same image as
before
[Music]
well
I'm glad we finished it I did actually
early
I do have a headache again
[Music]
I might just
um
fight through it
I'll Escape
no no no no no
Sebastian
all right there's like a boss Rush
that we never did that one like Tower or
something like that right
um
[Music]
exactly caught up yeah no I'll I'll read
some super chats yeah yeah
well then let's go to my office
[Music]
goodbye to hoodle little forever my love
look at this little baby
[Music]
I love him
ah
having him on my head held back the
headache for the whole stream Until the
End thank you very much
uh
[Music]
I don't want to fall back too much again
on Super Chat
surely it won't take too long
where am I
where is she
oops
oh
did I miss like another message from
from
Bandai Namco Sun
or did they not write any more
afterwards you guys have a no I didn't
okay okay I just don't want to miss
anything
oopsie
okay chat is ready to go
okay if you wanted to have a clone
stream getting the rest of the holes and
chatting I wouldn't mind I saw yeah I
guess I'm still messing some missing
some hoodles hmm
but I don't think I'll make another
stream out of it no
[Music]
hold on let me let me sit down hold up
on the table oh
foreign
if you would put a hat on him I feel
like you wouldn't know the difference
and that there's a TV there can't put
them on the TV
he's sitting on my table right next to
me
spin-off title World adventure
oh they can even just put it out as a
phone game I I would play that normally
don't like phone games but that that I
would play
all right so actually I would have to
start by reading some
um members only super chats yeah
um
but let me find some music
hoodle fighting no we don't want to see
who's fighting
I want a game where I can have poodle as
like a Tamagotchi
feed him bathe him
play with him oh that would be that
would be lovely
audio
[Music]
what about this one
so like I called it a lurking stealth
cute dot MP3
laughs
perfect description right it's
mischievous
Lookers this is my gem
hold your life oh please please
give me give me
[Music]
I can't it kind of gives me a Luigi's
Mansion Vibes now
[Music]
Mario
foreign
[Music]
is if I can find it
there it is
[Music]
thank you Mary Pippins
um you guys are so generous thank you
soon
[Music]
I think my members were
okay with it almost unless you will say
you're not okay with it space wonderful
did you send a Super Chat that you don't
want to be read here
[Music]
and I read it now
it's fun right
I'm okay with it all right oh my oh okay
totally fine okay
okay all right then
and Nicolas know the Stars thanks for
the pinky what 20 minutes memberships
thank you
Zerg
Shen who are the lucky ones
Nicolas says oh Kiana mother of chickens
hers is the fire replying your question
I sent the letter on August 2022 and
used wikiHow for property
fan letter manager proper on the side
note yesterday I remembered my favorite
Phoenix since I had a patient named
kihara
with the same writing
had to think of me how is on your mind
well no wonder cave Pizza is always on
my mind too
just like me for real for real
[Music]
gave me me some more letters when I was
in Japan
but I think I left them in Japan
yeah now I don't know which letter you
mean Nicolas though I'm confused this
seems like we had this conversation ages
ago
what kind of like what's going on sorry
[Music]
get them back well I'm going back so
yeah I'll get them when I go back to
Japan I didn't forget but I'm really I
guess I was just I left some things in
Japan on purpose because I knew I was
coming back soon anyway hmm
ah he didn't know he could send another
so he didn't yet okay well then I'm
waiting for thing for it Nicholas
thanks for the pinky that code thank you
for the rest of the chat and you were
great in the outfit reveal stream
I got kicking kicked in the heart again
merch looks great you look super cute in
your idol outfit I love the skirt
pattern I have my streaming ticket I'm
ready to set my pen light to Orange and
heart to Doki Doki
[Music]
yeah
ah I'm so excited for it already but
there's still so much time yeah
hopefully it will go by fast right
well in the meantime I'll try my best to
bridge the time with my streams
hopefully that works out thank you that
could and I'm glad you guys wanna like
use pen lights even when you're watching
at home thank you you didn't have to
because I wouldn't know anyway but
thank you
changing bgm
[Music]
also that good I've been watching gamer
girls on and off as well you know that
right so
oh I just watched like the ending of
season four beginning of season five and
I feel like once you get there oh my God
we'll have to talk again because that's
a very shocking
development
[Music]
that's when Rory goes
crazy
when you really wonder why we Rory Rory
I guess every teenager has to make
mistakes at some point can't be the
perfect dollar Forever
okay yeah you should check up Gilmore
Girls do it do it do it not Golden Girls
gimbal girls
we will gossip hell yeah
I'm talking about the Roaring Dean
situation which I will not save anymore
[Music]
when I get free time I watch it on
Netflix or you'll get so deep into the
rabbit hole of Gilmore Girls
you'll thank me later
Sarah wrap thanks for the pinky so many
of us camping in a live crowd I hope you
know we'll be all watching you on that
stage you've worked so hard for that
stunning outfit to be on a stage where
people adore you and cheer I'm proud to
watch your dreams come true good luck
thank you well actually do you guys know
that starting from today
they're again selling tickets but you
know not for overseas but just generally
like before but before also some
overseas kfp made it into the general
selection
so before it was like senko which is
like pre-sale tickets and now it's like
the actual things but is that just for
the Expo I wasn't sure
well you could try again to get Expo
tickets then
it sold out in 10 seconds
but I thought that was also uh
uh a lottery
is already gone
well I don't know anything but maybe for
overseas tickets maybe there will be
also one more round
I really don't know though I haven't
asked but it kind of sounded like it
Monday like wrote in a tweet before
didn't it
[Music]
sold out immediately
General sale oh was it for overseas two
that one
and it was written first round right
for the en tweet
so
um
[Music]
sold out in two minutes oh man
your investing in a friend actually won
the second raffle
good for them
just sad that so many kfps didn't make
it even though they tried
[Music]
oh but you know what I'm excited
they announced like today before the
concert that it's okay to use your voice
finally
which wasn't the thing for the previous
concert
um last year the whole concert and then
maybe that means
four four fans we can share too
I really hope so so this is
[Music]
I mean there's still like what a month
time or so
what no no there's more than a mouth
yeah
yeah so
things could still change but for now
yeah there was restrictions on people
cheering in concerts in Japan for like
ages now especially big venues
they have to follow
rules and guidelines
[Music]
so now they can share but they still
have to use a mask
which I think is fine they're used to it
anyway
yeah I want to hear the crowd too
I want them to just cheer how they
normally would
yes
so let's hope it doesn't change
[Music]
that was me after seeing my cameosi in
an idol outfit and I can't
wait to see you performing it I'm so
happy for you and kfp if we survive
it'll be wonderful you'll be amazing
it's so cute okay I stopped now Kiki I'm
so happy
now that we got an idol outfit now
[Music]
um
I do have the image as I said I'll
upload it later okay
[Music]
I don't know a long time no see sorry
only took over 2.5 years yeah it's a
little bit long but
finally and they look good don't they
[Music]
decided to use them those outfits from
now on
thank you bro for Doncaster and look
forward to seeing it in motion motion
mention
[Music]
Ed
Tomatoes
I've been smiling ever since your stream
with Anton
yeah we revealed way more exciting
things than just the idol outfit
but that one stayed in everyone's mind
didn't this
yeah but overall many exciting things to
look forward to
um
did a great job at being the emcee but
she's so used to it at this point
[Music]
the venue is going to have a huge
fubodzilla I was wondering like
um
how's that what are they gonna make it
out of
hmm
and I don't want her since we saw on the
map there was like a ankimo walking
around if they're gonna have the same
mascots again or different ones
I haven't heard anything about
kfp being made into a mascot so I don't
think that's gonna happen but
it's gonna be the same ones
or different ones small diamond was
really cute though so
um
I feel like if they would make a
different one from Ian then it would
probably be like
something from console race
but who knows
[Music]
I really do nothing so I'm not leaking
anything
[Music]
I know nothing
ah froggy llama would be dope so yeah
that would be so cute I would die oh
right so free thank you for the pinky hi
thank you here is my red envelope for
Chinese New Year sorry I left it a bit
late so late that the envelope
[Laughter]
yeah it's pink
don't worry about it thank you so much
[Music]
actually they are in Great British
pounds
very British
thank you for the British red envelope
thank you
right also did I forget the kiss for
Studio Rob I'm not sure Studio Rock I
love you listening but
thank you for watching the Stream
the official one Lord
[Music]
thanks
appreciated
for the pinky hey boss did you see the
new trailer for Grand blue action RPG
they finally said it's coming out this
year after seven years of development
also I'm so excited to finally see a new
Idol outfit I'm even more excited to see
on stage again
thank you first of all I know I didn't
what the [\h__\h] no
want to watch it now
[Music]
but maybe I've seen like an old one
before
let me see
Grand blue what's it called just Grand
Blue Ash and Jerry
what is it called a re-link for oh five
days ago let me mute real quick
oh it's three minutes long let me see
best to have
gameplay footage
did they give a release date
weird dragon bunny Fox mascot
oh it looks pretty damn
blue haired girl cute
I had a twin tale girls cute too
and there's like a girl that reminds me
of kisara
because she's like
wearing armor and she's blonde
oh
okay I'm gonna stop it there watch the
rest later Rick's looks really good
very interesting I think I would play
that
um
[Music]
even on stream but wait did it ever give
a release date at the end of the ah 2023
that is so rough
so I assume winter
December November something like that
[Music]
. it's better than nothing than we had
before previously coming 2018 oh my God
yeah but 2023 they released so many
jrpgs that I'm interested in stop
stop it
[Music]
all right very interesting though
Solstice Spanish for the pinky hey this
may be off topic but I made a promise of
whoever I used to beat stage one heart
of Hulk here I donate to so have this
thank you
who did you make the promise you to
yourself
you didn't have to thank you
I guess you know now that the Chihuahua
is stronger than she was in the
beginning
not so difficult to use here to eat for
like a a hard run
noise wow it's wrong yeah there's an
update coming soon on what the 10th or
so was it
it's not quite next week
when was it the 8th or
[Music]
yeah we have to play it again then
let's try it out again
see what's what's up with the new
characters yeah
on Solstice you will probably try to
so
help me and foreign
still hoping for the Christmas outfit
though ah can't wait to see you in
action again well I'm surprised you
didn't mention like a swimsuit outfit
Holo summer for whole lifeenglish.com
that's the real question you have to ask
because summer comes first
so
hmm
[Music]
oh yeah yeah the the swimsuit version of
my
oh casual outfit too
it's like you know previously
I found out it's actually possible
but they didn't do it for whatever
reason
so they told me another time I'm like
okay
so for this summer I'm gonna try to get
them
to arrange it for me
it shouldn't be too difficult right yeah
you just remove the shirt it's like one
layer still the same movement because
the boobies are already animated
hmm I'll get it okay I'll wait
[Music]
yeah oh yeah that's right my example I
was able to do it so I was wondering
like oh
can I do it too
no
jiggle physics already included
no other shirts no they're already open
that's enough we don't have to take them
off there's nothing underneath there
that's like actually drawn so
at least not as far as I know Garden
Park
tickets
thank you
imaginate oh and another one
now you get a kiss
your final streams convinced me to buy
the game oh the Chihuahua effect so I'll
be going out to get it once the stream
Ends by the way seems like Bae and Lamy
will also be starting it in a few hours
also if you can avoid idle meetings
while streaming maybe dream about
streaming
yeah I think I already kind of replied
to all of this
um
I do dream about streaming personally or
more like about work so
been weird and it's been fun at the same
time
store was closed last night
[Music]
I'm gonna go well you shouldn't go to a
game store at night
open
we have to go during the day
or just buy it in the online shop or you
want the physical version
I've been always buying my games online
because it's just faster
too annoying to go to the store or order
online I just want to decide
spontaneously
and I I've bought so many games since I
debuted if I had them all in a physical
version I would need a whole freaking
huge shelf for it
I can resell the physical
that's true
[Music]
prefer physical they can never take
those away from you well that's ironic
to compared to the other statement I
just read Because of course it can take
those away especially if someone robs
you don't you mean you prefer
non-physical because those can actually
never be taken away from you Rick are
you a little bit confused
[Music]
what if a burglar goes into your
apartment and takes yours
[Music]
I mean if you get the
um physical one then I guess if someone
steals your switch they're also taken
away
[Music]
well in the end
I don't know just
how about get both
you can provoke your license why would
they do that though you're saying
something that's so unrealistic guys
that's way more unrealistic like why
would the Pokemon company for example
suddenly revoke the license to your
Pokemon Arceus game that you have bought
on your switch
they've done it the one
what
[Music]
to everyone who already owned the game
they just took it away from them
[Music]
well but then what happened after that
couldn't they just like buy it again
were they not refunded and bought it
again or so I don't know
foreign
[Music]
okay I don't know the full story but
generally
[Music]
oh games are still a little easier to
like lose or break what if you break the
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] breaking data that is inside
your switch or so
the CD or whatever card or so you insert
in whatever console you're playing with
what if you
what if you or if you spill some water
over it or your dog eats it or so
that can happen
[Music]
so so
I would say I win the argument
[Music]
you suck
of course it's easier to like break
cartridges or whatever
[Music]
what is this like battle we're trying to
win anyway
well if it hits your switch it probably
also hits you
[Music]
you started it no yeah
I'm stupid
[Music]
you know what
because you're stupid I'm gonna shake
you
know what you gonna do about that huh
what you gonna do about that getting
dizzy huh feeling like throwing up huh
you're not gonna stop it's not gonna
stop until I decide
wow wow wow I'm gonna shake your
eyeballs out you're not gonna have any
eyes anymore and and you're gonna lose
all your liquids I'm just gonna
[Music]
well now you don't even know anymore if
the world is upside down or what what's
going on who am I oh it's my my nose now
my belly button who knows
so what do we learn
listen to kiwawa kiwawa is always right
laughs
What notes hey
don't question my nose
okay super chats from this stream
[Music]
chat really looking forward to your
official ending of this game Mrs
Ambassador also congrats again on your
first aisle outfit thank you
yeah in the end it was more or less my
duty to finish it on stream for all of
you guys as the Ambassador yeah
another game finished
wow 2023 just begun and I finished
Tales of her eyes super long jrpg
[Music]
thank you copy episode I'm for watching
me throughout this whole journey done
kitchen hope you enjoyed it
oh yeah I heard you got two Expo tickets
have fun wait so you're gonna if you got
two Expo tickets you mean for two days
or for one day for two people
[Music]
oh I see a new promo picture
[Laughter]
I just saw that now cause my chat window
doesn't have profile pictures but my
Super Chat window does
but there's no like insulting whatsoever
of Colette so we're good we're all good
[Music]
UF mod you send the Super Chat
I didn't see him scrolling down again
[Music]
don't you think it's like still upcoming
because I don't see it in the members
only super chats that I just finished
reading
[Music]
I'm pretty sure I got them all covered
yeah she's cute in that picture
that the fee ones not there what
yeah don't thank your Super Chat really
went through
or do you mean the the green ones the
members the monthly members one they
don't show up here I never said I would
read those
because they don't count as like super
chance
sometimes I see them when they're just
like come through while I'm streaming
and I'm paying attention to the chat in
that moment
yeah but often I don't
I don't really uh
catch them
I see you
[Music]
um
the rainbow
thank you
oh what is this some customers from
Reina came into kf3 to order some cotoni
burgers they also promised to make me a
Southern Chicken so I could always
protect the orange Mason
well they messed up and made me into a
crispy bucket instead oh did you just
um turn into the bucket
now I can no longer feel pain they put a
metal lid over my bucket and threw me
out the window what what the [\h__\h]
oh my god when I landed I used geogester
to figure out where I was and it appears
I'm on Dana is that in Austria
I've also already had to run from these
Doodles who want my blazing meat
mmm yummy that comes fried right
[Music]
anyway I found out about the crispy
contest held on Dana
even if I win I will become a true
Sovereign and can reunite with my once
you love the orange Maiden along the way
I have liberated some oppressed chickens
they started calling me iron bucket uh
as opposed to Iron Mask I think
anyway I'll find you again orange Maiden
after I become a true sovereign
love into this
hmm
wow the lore the lore you could make a
whole game out of this
you should be
Quest the side question Tales of arise
thank you that God
I got many Chuckles on me
well I think you're reunited with the
orange Maiden in case you meant me of
course
[Music]
so much green in my chat
okay
thank you ah so sweet thanks for the
beautiful rainbow I appreciate it
thank you take its monkeys
glad to see you get to finish this I was
the it was the first game I 100 in a
long time oh it was such a great ride
would have forgotten about the series if
it wasn't for you being such a great
Ambassador thank you
next time
[Music]
edmg7 thank you
Don more than a year ago I became an egg
during one of your tastes of a rice
streams feel so nostalgic being back
here now and already a few months old
packet yay it to be nostalgic thank you
for joining the membership back then I'm
still being one now
thanks guys thanks guys
yeah the conclusion was noise hmm Ricky
mccr or how to say that Max
yeah
and Ricky everything
you playing got me to finish the game
yesterday attention oh you also waited a
long time didn't you
still haven't beaten the boss in the
Wind Tower
loved the game overall if you're
interested you can get people's second
Mystic art if you complete the campfire
oh I was wondering if they have more
than one
oh
you would have liked to see those damn
it
damn it
I wonder how far away I was from those
hmm
you say down those Christmas decorations
now it's it's still super wintery and
cold here
[Music]
broken man thank you
looking for the top down cushion
but I preached sorry black virgin nugget
but I have another chance
fourth event is
eventually
[Music]
old enough
employee number
[Music]
laughs
foreign
[Music]
but it's another date
a different one
[Music]
the fourth Fest
day one date
[Music]
which will hopefully
give you the luck that you need sanitang
to get that
ticket
um
[Music]
good luck
oh oh yes yeah yeah yeah I knew I knew
it all along
[Music]
I'm so happy you've gotten to spend so
much time in Japan and got to see so
many Japanese hormones I'm excited for
your idol outfit in an upcoming show so
much has happened in such a short time
cheers thank you yeah I was really
packed everything was like so much for
me and even though like the streams for
you guys it was short
like for me the whole day I was out and
about so
um
I'm really glad to be back at home right
now
one really of course she had the
Comforts of home after being on a long
vacation that's at least if it's not
like a
Resort a vacation although Japan had a
lot of Comforts too like 24 7 shops and
convenience stores and all that which we
don't have here
it's a little bit less Comfort but
it's okay I got hellofresh
one another thank you for the pinky
thank you for the tour tangent even if
you hadn't told it I was already super
happy just knowing you and the hair got
to talk and hang out ever since you
debuted I'd helped you meet her one day
so it was like a dream come true help
you meet again
it's not like we have like any kind of
connection or so but I guess you just
really wanted that to happen because we
are both your ooshies and yet
you don't have the chicken emoji in your
Twitter name even to this day
which is weird because uh you've been
supporting me so much since the
beginning but okay you do you
honey
I guess I can add yeah it's that easy I
was always making that like if you like
me so much why why am I not why is my
icon not in your name I guess you don't
like me that much
like that
well about them
[Music]
I'm looking forward to seeing two icons
there I'm sure towards them if I won't
mind
oh wow
[Music]
becoming less and less symptom
what's going on am I still did I switch
Dimensions or so am I in a different
timeline
foreign
[Music]
was that like a reference
intels of a rise to that one sir 956
donkey show and Hildegard thank you sir
thank you 0956
Future Super Chat since no signal in the
mountains oh
that's you you know what you got to do
when you're up on the mountains you're
gonna yodel and also you gotta yell
[Music]
Ed
please do that for me
thank you
it's an Austrian thing
don't question it
is
more important
[Music]
They're copying
I'm so hungry now oh my God I gotta get
down here
[Music]
can oh
the rest of the chat
Congress on beating the game finally I
mean assuming it doesn't have enough
final form game which always completes
her games well I don't know when exactly
you said that super chat but I'm
assuming it was really at the end
I love how in these kind of games
just like or I guess in almost all all
games that have a boss
I love the the guessing of oh I wonder
how many forms it has no way it only has
one form there must be more but wait
there's more but wait could there be
even more
discounts
[Music]
yeah it had another final boss that was
cool
[Music]
which I I would say is just not another
form of that first boss but I see it as
another face
yeah so that was pretty sick pretty cool
I loved all the like animations 3D and
2D
like you can really see they put a lot
of work into
finalizing this game I see so much love
in it you know Ohio
[Music]
you when game developers
take their time to polish the game and
put all the work necessary into it which
would be the norm right I think it's all
I think it is the norm
I feel like I've
seen something else the other day but I
I think it's a norm I think it's a norm
um
[Music]
so glad you got to finish it on stream
it's such a fantastic game one of my
all-time favorite series and games and
so many special memories looking for
free
I wish I could like shake hands and hug
you some Tracy just like me for real for
real man
it was a lot of love until next hour
definitely was a lot of love into it
I've heard that just recently they found
even more secrets in the game
that weren't known for the longest time
it's fascinating absolutely fascinating
what the [\h__\h]
crazy
[Music]
now
people keep on finding things still
that's insane
maybe even 10 years from now they still
find things
Platinum path
no no no no no
there was an update recently what did
they update
[Music]
yeah I love indie games
anyway thank you
thank you for waiting so long and being
here on the final finale second finale I
appreciate it hopefully we can play
another tails off game besides Symphonia
within my time here I would love that
man what's why do I have a headache to
hold it like normally I'm not the type
of person to get headaches or anything
like that
um what is it what could it be guys why
do I have a headache I've been drinking
more today trying to fix it with water
but
um
no I wasn't up that late no no
[Music]
I slept plenty
foreign
[Music]
's baby through connecting with her
by playing the game
can't get pregnant by playing tears of
her eyes
Google says I'm dying
I am always dying I'm not surprised
about that
[Music]
try using your mind in the light bar to
reduce ice cream
that's what it's supposed to do I
thought it would be the opposite and
make everything so bright right in front
of my eyes that it would like hurt my
eyes what
[Music]
what
I kissed much it was a mask between us
two masks
[Music]
Google says I don't own an airfryer
what's wrong
yeah it kind of slides down lie
downwards I get that but how does that
help
it's already like my room is pretty
bright I have always the light on and
then my monitors are very bright I would
say
[Music]
but they're brighter than
the rest of my room I guess a little bit
[Music]
you should like start doing that like
those blue filter whatever glasses
because I I do it as a job but is that
just a myth
knows help do they really help
[Music]
uh hello myth but that's just a Hollow
myth
okay oh I've had ones before but I
probably have threw them away or so I
lost them
okay okay
um thanks for
text me please again reminds me how much
I love playing this game and watching
you playing at the same time I'm glad
you are finally able to finish this game
Jerry produce are so much fun I hope we
can get another tale of gaming soon yeah
well Tesla Symphonia remaster is coming
soon and if you if anyone here hasn't
played Tales of Symphonia before
I highly recommend it I mean you know
Graphics are a little bit older but you
guys don't mind that anyway right and
it's
[Music]
I think the game that got the Tails of
game that got the most
overseas fans
into tails off I feel like
I might be wrong but I feel like so many
people have told me that they've started
with Tales of Symphonia
you know
[Music]
Ramada has pretty much everything called
advice just thanks to 60 FPS of the
GameCube version oh
[Music]
I plan on playing it yeah I wanna check
it out yeah
I did for sure just like me for real for
real you're starting to look sillia damn
that's a good start too though any tails
off game is a good start
for Syria recently crisis Grace is also
popular she started with hands up the
world right in mythology well that's
that just makes absolutely no sense
[Music]
I mean I enjoyed that one but that makes
like no sense oh man
oh poor Miyako
you started at the absolutely wrong game
but then I guess every every tails off
game you would have played after that
would have left and even way better
impression than radiant Mythology like I
really liked it that's not the game you
start with
I didn't know any of the Tails games and
it's been my favorite
well okay I'm glad but you played others
since then right
I really like the pink haired
protagonist
and Elise and tells of the world random
mythology you can make your own
character
that's why it's so cool
fantastic wow
two Fantasia peeps here
man there's so many in the chat who have
experience with Tales of wow that makes
me so happy
damn
foreign
I feel like I'm among my peers just like
me for real for real man
oh man
I am so happy
yeah chat with laser streamer that's
probably the thing
I don't think you could find so many
tails off fans and like I don't know I
miss chat
for example
[Music]
right
gotta ask their teammates sometimes hi
teammates how you doing
[Music]
you guys should play tails off games
games trust me trust me bro let's give
it a try
give it a try please
[Music]
or maybe takudachis so Taco Dutch is
like jrpgs foreign
[Music]
thank you glad you enjoyed it author
Hilda guide also thank you
the gamer created
thank you donations
[Music]
sci-fi game of tales of arise
do you still think you hate that genre
Mass Effect next
joking is like a fake
joking
nice you're able to find the city and I
only played this game because of you and
I was sure you would like to kiss
you guys well managed to not mention
that to me
who knows if you would have told me this
like eight months ago that they were
gonna kiss maybe I would have
immediately rushed to play until the end
then I would have been mad that you guys
spoiled at me
[Music]
I guess there's some sci-fi in it but I
can you really consider it sci-fi
[Music]
got spaceships you got Universe you got
aliens
I guess so
closer to the end yeah
sci-fi and fantasy damn it's like mixing
Lord of the Rings of Star Wars
that feels like you mix
that's like that's like I don't know
putting potato fries salted potato fries
or or a sausage dipping it in Nutella
what dear Lord
dear Lord save me some people like it
but it shouldn't be considered a normal
thing right
[Music]
yeah like french fries and ice cream but
that one's more generally accepted by
people interestingly
Alex now that question thank you
foreign
[Music]
series at that yeah it did a really good
job building towards the end of my
opinion and I see why the director
wanted to cast the cast to be a
dysfunctional giving the game's message
oh yeah at the end they didn't seem like
that at all anymore huh they definitely
were like so unfitting to be a group in
the beginning
so yeah that is a really really nice
development yeah lovely well thank you
for watching Mary Pippins it does really
feel nice to be able to play games that
are
just so close to my heart I was
questioning corn pizza oh my God
it's like super normal here okay
[Music]
or corn pizza with like pineapples or
corn pizza with something else like I
don't know
diabolo pizza with corn or so
combinations
corn
or so yeah don't question corn corn is
amazing on Pizza really
[Music]
it goes so well with everything
some people just don't get it you
wouldn't get it
it can't be more controversial than
pineapple and peas all right
[Music]
thank you
I think you should write one yeah
I don't really have a backlog on letters
no no
thank you for the recipe is
[Music]
foreign
for the rest of it
did you already book everything I try to
meet other kfps
that sounds like a well-planned trip so
far I mean it surprises me that you're
starting with Yokohama
but you I've been to Yokohama a couple
times it's nice
I think you'll find something to do
it's interesting to start with that well
have fun there
and definitely gotta make time
for a watch party you guys could if
you're if some kfps are in Japan I think
you could do a watch party in like a big
karaoke room too maybe
somehow I feel like you could rent that
for that but the question is how do you
play
oh maybe I wonder if you can bring your
laptop and then put an HDMI cable and
then the karaoke screen shows that one
of the best possible in any kind of
hookers gotta ask maybe some Japanese
Bros
because I've never tried that
[Music]
but in general I feel like big karaoke
rooms are
a good way of getting everyone together
to watch something like that
[Music]
um
random cod zombies players for the rest
of the chat first time don't love your
content keep up the great work oh thank
you oh I'm pushing it done
glad you like Chihuahua Channel please
watch more I gladly have you around we
finished House of our eyes today
tomorrow karaoke and then next week some
more Fire Emblem and some other stuff
yeah look far into it thank you for the
generous support
[Music]
looking for the top donation
no no no
I am starting to feel sick Dragon birdie
Duncan black virgin danger soon
I'm feeling sick because I haven't eaten
so now I must go
and in Germany
I'm gonna I guess make some food now
guys
thank you
tomorrow might not be free
we'll see we'll see we'll see as I said
maybe pretty so maybe not pretty we'll
see we'll see
I'll be dancing thanks for watching
with that Unthinkable they all doubted
me care if we lost hope in me they
didn't believe in me that you thought I
had no more integrity
but
that is hopefully back you hopefully
trust me again you hopefully respect me
again
how we can finally take it off the list
right
[Music]
I'm so sorry it took so long
bye
[Music]
wrote something again big thank you to
all the listeners in English speaking
world who support the tales of seriously
again somewhere
thank you
they really watched the whole Super Chat
rating
[Music]
now I'm embarrassed
I always have to think they're always
watching
did they say something bad afterwards no
right
but I promoted a different jrpg
oops
[Music]
well I only praised the game yeah yeah
it's embarrassing yeah I wasn't
sponsored
all good okay going to kiwawa kitchen
now
[Music]
foreign