hello hello
hello we're back
can you guys see this let us know
oh i don't see any uh i know i think i
see something
wow a lot of people are waiting a lot of
people came over
we're we're starting we're getting right
back into it no no intro no anything so
for those of those of you who are
watching the archive
um my internet uh likes to do a thing
where
sometime at what is not supposed to be
prime time uh where i where i live where
i exist
where i dwell um is it likes to just uh
cut the internet completely
um and then i go it's not even slow
internet i go and i check
i go and i check the speed when i
reconnect and it's still perfect
so i don't know what's going on i don't
know if the internet demons are having a
problem with how i have
how i have purchased their internet from
them i don't really get it
uh there's nothing we can do about it
except maybe start up a fourth stream
so that's why there are two way out
streams right next to each other
uh asmr stream is just going to be moved
please uh
look out for my updated schedule i'm
going to post a whole new image with a
new schedule after all this is over
so for now let's finish the game
we're going to finish the game today
we're going to continue in the middle of
a fire party let's go
let's go let's go i hope we don't have
to start all the way over if we do i'll
cry
i won't cry but i'll be upset it
definitely saved somewhere in between
yeah come on come on
whoa what the hell is going no huh
that's from the beginning from the very
beginning
oh no all right you know what speed run
speed run tactics
okay speed run tactics kiara
i'm just to go in and start blasting
everyone in my mouth what the hell
let's just go ahead and start blasting
what
oh dear go ahead and start blasting
nowhere yeah it's not oh
hello you're right here huh there's a
guy behind you
i get to use my my sniper rifle i'll get
my kiara that's the good that's the only
good part
[Music]
i don't think it took us back to the
very start but it did take us back quite
a ways
i got a lot of practice with this now
this is fun
i'll take some high ground
okay with you
it's fine just start blasting
what happened to the dude from the back
oh you're still able to hit me i don't
like that
ah ah
there you go got him
point blank my dude right in front of me
i'll just kill you right here there we
go i'm not as careful as i used to be
yeah not quite huh all right watch out
for these guys
welcome back everyone for everyone who's
still coming in
welcome back we're in the middle of a
party
you've missed nothing because we have to
redo this
it's fine we're a lot more aggressive
now which is good
that has its own merits oh yes i'm
indeed very aggressive yeah you can
trust because
he is for sure i mean i'm always
aggressive but because it's what he's
especially aggressive today
yay all right let's push this car
the car thing yeah yeah yeah hello all
right help me with this
oh yes okay you can go
and push
all right all right actually after this
after playing this game i do
feel like i would maybe give a f uh an
fps game a try something like apex or
something right that's good
yeah that's have a watson teach you
you'll be fine
okay she will be very frustrated with me
but that's okay yeah but she'll be nice
this is where we left off because i was
asking should we change the weapon or
not
let's hope nothing curse happens again
all right here we go you are going to
change it okay you're going for close
combat i think it's the
right choice i like the fast ones
i don't want it oh wait do we have to i
have to change
uh you don't have to if you don't want
to
oh oh i want to take um
every hair on his arm nice well rendered
my boy okay
where do we go now um great question i
wonder if we can go this way
nope all right so we go the other way
okey-dokey
let's go
yes last spurt that's right that's what
it's called
i think
oh yeah i just roll the hallway
okay i'm confused this is where we came
from no it sure is break lock okay just
kidding we go down to the gate we have
to break
oh it did not prompt you to do anything
yeah it didn't
uh i was supposed to shoot it ah good
you know what yeah that's probably it
ah well now it shows me something it
didn't before
see well that wasn't our fault
yeah that's right that's right open
three
two one
we have infiltrated the the gangster or
whatever i don't know what this
is they're hiding
is that what you call a gangster i mean
probably
how are you shooting through the oh
they're shooting through the holes i get
it
sneaky sneaky i've seen that in movies
just roll yeah maybe i
maybe maybe i should have brought a
sniper
let's wait a minute
just don't get hit i can probably make
it over to those barrels ah there you go
oh no it's okay there's a tactical
there's a tactical way to do this we got
this return for the sniper i will turn
if i can i can't
damn it no shame oh god oh sorry
it's it's okay tony you're real good at
getting killed we all know this it's not
a surprise it's nothing new for us
it's my hobby it would seem so
you like it a little too much all right
now
what did we do about this situation oh
wait what no
i should have read chat oh god i'm so
dumb super chats will definitely be red
at the end of the stream because i
cancelled asmr so
just yeah yeah it's okay if you twist
you don't feel bad don't feel bad i
deserve that
okay hold on okay i was just standing
there letting myself get railed
inside you were safe there but there's
no place where you are
but there's a lot of nice wine bottles
here maybe you want to get one of those
maybe tasty i was eyeing those i gotta
say
watch outside am i gonna recover from
that yeah you might be fine you just
gotta wait
oh okay
all right now leave it to me i got him
now they're dead
i mean happens to the best of us
oh nice going that's quite extreme
hello i like it i like the way that you
think
okay they're super dead
they exploded into a bunch of pieces
right let's go and put it down
what the hell that was awesome
this is we saw this in the cutscene i
can disturb
um we are here i booked the vacation in
the penthouse suite for 40k
cali uh was gonna cancel it but i i
i came anyway this reminds me of a scene
in breaking bad
it's party time where are you oh my gosh
they're still able to hit you you got to
get somewhere else
i saw that one coming i don't know how
but i might be a psychic or something
because i saw that one coming
oh this will be an easy one
good it's all good going down here
no
oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god
nice yeah you get him get him killer
get him killer oh my friends a little
refreshing
dip in the pool i'm sorry yeah you
that's yup definitely that's what it is
this is fun i understand now why i'm
gonna play so many fps films
i mean there is something a bit
addictive about uh shooting people in
the head
and again i prefer swinging my scythe
irl but you know it is what it is it is
what it is all tangled with some
firearms
hello some more people i guess i'm just
going to take a swim
oh my god
me too me too let's swim together let's
swim together
this game is crazy oh my i
cannot believe it is the gun gonna be
fine does the water not do anything to
it
what the hell am i doing this game oh my
god guess i did that again
that was fun we we double dipped into
the pool
unbelievable nice all right growing are
we going for that
i guess so no all right let's break it
um no
yes no maybe so nope
i didn't say r i said it's different you
did it you did it you did say in a
different
context it's it's not the sexy i got it
what the [\h__\h] right yeah uh uh-huh yeah
auditing different
contexts why is there there's a little
thing in here it says
it's like it's like a yellow
it's a yellow dot i can't do anything
though i wonder if i'm waiting for you
oh okay okay little homie
okey-dokey taking your sweet time
what i'm here though how do you do
maybe we have to go up somehow
it's fine the game will start feeling
bad for us and give us a hint at some
point
yep please suck
i wouldn't mind maybe maybe one supposed
to swim a bit more
yeah just a couple more different ways
isn't that door
it's probably this is the store
listen help me okay honeymoon is over
it sure is
yeah say hello to my little friends
what is that
he's going he's ruining his new museum
museum i love that i just feel like this
game is referencing so many films and
shows that i like
i should have brought a sniper gun oh
dammit
rude
wait what
a grenade launcher wait no
no get down heel heel heel
yeah we got to keep moving apparently it
seems though
what is going on grenades
oh my gosh oh my
[Music]
i'm trying to help i just really can't
aim for [\h__\h]
get covered get covered oh my gosh that
was right on me
ugh
oh my gosh he's going insane
absolutely insane i mean yeah
i expected no less from our big bad
that was a nice slide my dude however
time to kill you
oh grenade you can see him fly too he's
flying oh
no no he's going to be great
i thought the game was gonna go a little
bit into the fantasy
uh genre harvey starts flying
okay yeah i mean i'd be down for it
oh god let's just try and take out the
guys as quickly as possible
yeah oh my god i have this problem that
uh sometimes because my my thing is
windowed it's just
my mouse moves outside of the the screen
no worries and taps out
it's okay we'll get we'll get him this
time for sure
i'm going back here guy [\h__\h]
right next it's too easy
oh my god oh my god
it seems like he's mostly aiming for you
that's kind of rude it is rude do you
have a problem with
phoenix i mean it seems so
oh there you are hey homie we
[Applause]
i have a whole army go with that and a
general a general that is a drunkard but
that's
that's it still works and the dead pizza
will help too
oh oh my god oh too easy loser two
easy
really there we go no problem all right
we got him
let's move oh my god i haven't i'm
coming
here to help ah yeah
oh wow he's strong
wow nice aim idiot it's dude it's insane
yeah gotta follow him
shake him down what does he know it's
over
it's over dude say your prayers it's
november i hope your life was worth it
you idiot
yeah look at him oh big boss till the
end
don't even think about it slide it over
i think he could kill us easily but
in that position oh no i don't trust i
don't trust
no he's got another gun under the table
i bet well maybe
he has like a button that a button that
explodes the whole apart of the whole
penthouse
could be i wonder what we should should
we confront him with you or
should i approach do you want to get the
sucker
i go with you okay
i'll handle it
okay i'll do my
oh i best the golden gun fantasy it does
look fancy hope you get to keep it
no as uh yeah
yeah a little murder souvenir
hello sir you've been a bad man
shut the [\h__\h] up one more word from you
and i'll put a bullet in your face
wait i don't even have patience for this
just kill him leo
oh i still got it oh that's what you're
here for right
the diamond i don't care about the
diamonds just care about this kind of
forgot if i
was gonna say i think we kind of forgot
about it yeah [\h__\h] the diamond
come on get up go
we want the diamond down your life sir
can we get both of those please
and and maybe the house the villa
can you give us the deed so you can
party like rock stars every weekend
okay
he's got some maybe he got another gun
in there he does he does have a gun
are you he's not going oh he's he's he's
definitely gonna take that
oh my god oh my god maybe that's a fake
one too
he didn't take the gun out oh no he did
what the [\h__\h] god
what do i do what do i do what do i do i
gotta push this
i can't do anything ah
yeah you suck get him now's your shot
now's your chance now's your chance
oh i'm super oh sorry
[Applause]
put it okay now oh man
all right oh yeah
we hate you well done
we're out of the fruit
well done oh my god look at him that's a
sight to behold
oh my god that's his [\h__\h] game yes
in the head
there he goes uh going down like a true
mob bus
yes
because i'm used to it this is like a
normal day's work for me
but i'm glad to hear that you're
enjoying uh dipping your
dipping your toes into a fun side i
enjoy your business it's so fun business
they got more people where were they
they let their boss die they don't even
know that he's dead right now i think
i bet they don't that's the only reason
they're still fighting otherwise they
could lose
ah
shot first there went a little padding
but now it's just fun
nice you know
stay off the road or else they're gonna
keep shooting at us
where which one is the word there's so
much blood on me everywhere i'm getting
shot so badly
oh yeah you're behind me huh so i'm
taking all the fire
oh my god all right let's go
stay off the road
those bikes are insanely uh like
how do you say sterile uh durable sturdy
and durable you just made a combination
word you came up with a new word
sterling sturdy and dirty
i knew that sometimes
action
this baby fun
slow motion two stunts at the same time
this is so ridiculous
definitely or maybe we just are still in
sync
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god you got this
stop shooting that's so beautiful i have
a bad feeling about this
ah no they started shooting at me oh my
god what the hell was that
grenades oh no
i'm flying look at me get this air
look at him
oh my gosh this is getting so much air
oh my god oh my god
oh my god
this is not not
neither to be honest running away on a
bike with you there i go i'm dead
i'm blocked for real yeah
it's fine we got this okay stop shooting
easy peasy
second second time is gonna be better
it's okay it was about time that i died
what the hell am i doing after i got so
much air too let's go on the beach oh
they'll never find me here
try and stay as far off the road as
possible i guess
i mean which one is the road though good
question
i know i don't know oh my goodness
oh my god
what's going on
you got this that was supposed to happen
okay getting serious air again there you
are okay for you
come on come on come on come on
get on let's go
oh
okay yeah you definitely got this i
trust your driving skills yeah
leave it to me oh my god this is sam
this is very tight this is very hard to
aim
i can imagine with my driving oh oh no
another quiet oh no
no no no i'm not good at this watch what
is happening
what was that
what was that it was probably not
supposed to happen that's okay it's fine
no worries hey i think you're shooting
very well thank you my god
oh my god what is happening
what on earth was that
okay stay focused callie don't look at
the chat don't look at the stream
are you looking at the chat i was i was
looking at the stream actually this time
i think i'm slightly smaller than you
and it's bothering me
it happens it happens we're really about
to die
hold on it's probably black and white
again
i don't like it when it's black and
white let us heal please
uh-oh there's the plane
oh really yeah
yeah you gotta you gotta ruin it you
gotta hit
do i shoot it
here i'll get us on the other side okay
sorry it's my fault all right
i got this
i'm coming back sick move
must be like racing so bad hey everybody
here's the trunk reaper driving a
motorcycle crazy
vincent you're going to have to pay me
triple for this now we're operating
through
anyway yeah exactly there you go you're
not going to hear me say this often
but thanks wait do we have the diamond
by the way did we bring it with us
i'm pretty sure one of us slipped it in
the pocket maybe
you know what i think i'm going to write
that letter to carol
oh it's a great idea write the carol
letter write it right
you have a pen and paper wait no yeah
why not
it's a long way home good idea you got
anything better to do
oh my god we sure did
all right but it's not over i think okay
still more to go
whether you're writing i don't know i'd
like to know vincent what are you
writing in your letter
i love you i love you i love you i love
you i love you
sorry that i'm apparently not a good guy
sorry that i got thrown in prison um
how are we doing we should be landing in
10 minutes wow let's
ask what's you up to sleep
got time to wake him up then yeah
what's going to happen once we land yeah
you sure yeah i'm fine
leo what
yeah we there yet yeah what's gonna
happen
no maybe go see my kid
are they gonna welcome us no no one's
here okay
or you would think no one is there but
i hear dramatic music oppo the gay
statue
strum aware son
we do a sneaky sneak oh [\h__\h] of course
yep they're definitely here to arrest
us no please put them up
no [\h__\h] i didn't know i wonder if we
just kind of knew it was gonna happen
i guess so the ambulance came too that's
nice of them
i got a little ouchy
are we accepting our fate i guess so
what's she doing
did she wait are you with the police
did she how do you call it in english to
tell
somebody snitch oh did you snitch on us
it just gets stitched everybody stand
down
the look that she gave to the police i
mean that's obviously what
yep alright this [\h__\h] everyone's a
[\h__\h] what the hell
what is it
good job vincent
what
i didn't know what the [\h__\h] oh
huh i can't i can't
i can't believe it was i mr omawari-san
too i was a k-statsu
which means possibly no what no way
are you [\h__\h] kidding me no way honey
no ray are you watching this
in your police car
are you i see this is shining to you in
style
lenny national
trucking inc oh
am i an investigator are you from the
athlete
must be but you killed people too
what the hell i definitely killed some
dudes
[Music]
huh
about right of course it is you can
always trust me
i'm not trusting nobody my friend but i
don't understand
like i'm a trustable guy ciao
like what was the thing between you and
your wife
i guess the wife knew was wrong what's
this
maybe she didn't know because you're not
supposed to tell even your spouse's
about what you're working on
that's right maybe that's why they had
problems
i did watch this game before but i
watched it about three years ago so i
forgot
everything i just knew someone betrayed
someone
i didn't know who officer somebody get a
damn ambulance
gary stay with me oh no
i'm sorry
oh it was a big undercover thing
everyone was ganging up on me
where's harvey where's the black orlov
what are you deaf
oh you think you're funny don't you
what do you think you just go and sell
it on the street corner what are you
stupid
you that stupid i'm smart i'm a big
brain burp
so they say don't underestimate him
brother i'm sorry i'm sorry
i didn't hear that though i didn't hear
them say that that was who it was
i don't think it worked i did maybe you
know it later yeah
i don't know there's only one option now
your boy won't look at
you i'll get someone on it
james if you want harvey in the black
orlov
this is the only way just put me in a
cell next to him
you're too close to this vincent you
better sit this one out
i am so mad my flesh and blood
and he's dead because of me i put him in
that situation
i need to do this and you know it
just make it happen james
you're under arrest leo
it's over but we were boys
the betrayal in his eyes nobody you
paint that
song oh [\h__\h] good only making it
worse for yourself
i am so mad okay what am i supposed to
do
i'm not gonna lie am i going to the car
what's
come on leo please listen that was my
brother come on you're gonna have to do
this
you're gonna pay for this yes
come on man i smile get in the car
get in the [\h__\h] car go
where you're going now kelly if you want
me
oh come on
i [\h__\h] trusted you vince i did i know
we were boys
calm down are you serious i'm fine you
like me i know you're angry
angry you haven't seen me angry yet
you're
shut up just shut the [\h__\h] up
come on man stop the car oh
i have to drive the first time i drive
in this game there's still a chance for
you to do
the right thing come on do the right
thing the only right thing
here is me pointing the gun right out of
your face
so shut up what is my goal though
what is my goal i'm really sorry for
everything
please stop the car i don't believe it
like literally i'm sorry i'm sorry i am
sorry i didn't mean to
i didn't know that venison was doing
this
over the entire police force is after
you
there's no way out of this i swear
vincent
ah way out they said the name kind of
yeah let's dive together i'm taking you
with me
you're so angry look at your face your
face is angry too
i am so mad
what am i tapping for you forgot to tap
we gotta get up kelly
oh why was that a good idea why was that
ever a good idea
reminds me of my minecraft it yesterday
oh dear
oh my gosh
oh [\h__\h]
oh i can't let you get away
innocence my boy i can't
are you hanging on to my no you're
swimming okay
oh man
that's my friend i have friends they're
police
what does sprattle mean we need him
what is his name
we need you alive
okay give me a like i can kill you no
okay you can get me alive i will kill
you
no why is my boat so i need to ask you
some questions
oh man can i not go faster
get the engine get the engine
down it goes we're almost there
[Music]
chat will help me someone in chat knows
german
she's so mad look at her face
are you laughing at me kelly just a
little
there down on the right that's
yeah right over there i just want to
talk to him a little bit
i'll take good care of your son i'll
take him out to play basketball every
day
you can count on me
come on hurry i thought my internet went
out she just started responding to me
because she's so mad
we'll play basketball every day and then
think of you
don't worry you don't touch
my son i'll leave your wife alone i
already have a wife
you're right no you won't you're from
the grave good luck
from your jail cell i don't think so get
out of here oh no
go don't do anything stupid leo shut up
just go i don't want to kill you
i'm gonna kill everyone don't [\h__\h]
push it this is between me and vincent
now get the hell out it's the first
place oh my god
go hey look if it's my choice we'd be
friends till the end but it
can't happen [\h__\h] done
done [\h__\h] please stop this
how's it feel to snap someone in the
back i know you're disappointed
but harvey killed my brother i had no
choice
you're just playing your psychic mental
brainwashing fbi tricks on me i don't
believe you good dead man you piece of
[\h__\h] what about your son
alex shut the [\h__\h] up don't you mention
his name
you don't get to mention yes i do we're
gonna play basketball every day
i'll teach you how to shoot a
three-pointer
look cali
all right you and me now buddy oh my god
is this like
a two too often thingy kelly i'm going
to kill you i'm going to kill you uh
that's not how this works usually
between you and me
do you know how this is gonna [\h__\h]
yeah you know how this sounds talking
about
you know how this ends where are you huh
i wonder where that pig is hiding
ah
[Music]
you know how this ends where are we at
leo
let's put it up to this
[Music]
oh
on out
come on out
come on i see you're going for the
strategy of not moving huh
are you scared no i'm not scared i just
i'm in a good position right now why
would i why would i change that
come on come on out
the hawk is watching come on you're just
camping huh
this will not end well right
come on you're not scared are ya
i'm not i'm chilling i'm waiting for you
literally where you know
guys know how this ends where are you i
lost
i lost my sense of direction this is
where you were before
uh-huh
wait but you must be
[Music]
wait what where are you what the [\h__\h]
where are you
i see you okay
what you're behind me
you didn't know if a
sense of direction be like
listen listen i know i'm not good with
directions
i could be in a better spot right now
you know where you were
i'm just getting started you're gonna
pay for this
there you go i know it hurts
it hurts
it hurts i'm coming for you that was
nothing come on
you've done this enough times quiet
all right
damn it had enough i got plenty more
[Music]
bullets
you know your character is trying to be
nice and all
kind different from how you're playing
the game right now
i'm just doing what i have to do i'm
doing what the game is telling me to do
and also what i do
[Music]
i know it hurts everyone [\h__\h] you over
this is not the time to lose the game
you show us what you can do
stop it no no
drop it throw it away get rid of the gun
no
you have to get rid of the gun we were
friends but
listen i said i'd get your time reduced
i'll come visit you every day
that's [\h__\h] there's all lines come
on
everything has been in line everything
you told me was a lie
all the nice words the fishes we caught
together
that wasn't a lie it was all a line no
it wasn't i just had
stuff to do i had a different mission
come on man
i thought we were on the same path kelly
we were but
it was this path this is how it was
always supposed to be
come on man
where are you
okay okay i see i see
i see i see
[Music]
come here
i see your head i see a cute little
haircut
your cute little haircut you're not even
trying to hide right now huh
nope i'm waiting for you
our health is like super close yeah it's
gonna
it's gonna be a close one
is this supposed to happen in the game
though that it keeps on like being me
suffering
or is this because uh because we have
the same health i'm i don't
i wonder if this is appropriate it's
pretty scripted who could say i don't
know if this game has multiple enemies
i've only seen one a long time ago no
they say
no no it's because i'm losing what
are we going to fisticuff now there's
multiple it says
i'm not going to read the chat anymore
oh why are we taking them off though we
got to battle it out like men
come here come here buddy they're a sock
em uh
suck em could you not
ouch you gotta go you gotta go leo
i love you man listen you you were my
favorite you i liked you more than
venison but listen
this is just ridiculous
no game don't
you're thinking you see my baby you
think you can choose a happy life but
take it away from me listen man uh-uh
it's just business
i have a family too you know can we call
a truce
no
[Music]
no wait i'm not i'll get your sentence
reduced
come on man we were brothers
that's what i thought i thought so too
listen we can still be brothers just
with you in jail come on man
that's not gonna work we're enemies
no wherever no after all we went through
we took out scarface together come on
man
i gotta oh don't show me the little boy
ah
your son exactly
i don't know i'm starting to have some
strange feelings now some changed
emotions
had the same situation i wonder too
i don't know i gotta go watch theirs
after this there's a gun
i'm gonna take it i'm gonna baby crawl
over
it's there
i'm sorry no we've done this many times
before krista tori
uh
[Music]
i i did not deserve this
why does it hurt so much more this time
no come with me please there's still
time
there's still time no there's still time
come on
i don't wanna take my hand
come on there's still time
please
come on
[Music]
are you gonna tell my wife what you did
to me
and my my son i didn't mean the
basketball thing i'm not gonna go play
basketball with him
you better don't i didn't mean it i
thought i was gonna die
you weren't telling my i didn't think it
was gonna be me
hi can i come in
sure
hi hey alex are you going to tell him no
wait a minute vincent don't
that's rebellion is daddy linda
we need to talk can we quit the game now
can we play can we play a different
ending
you gotta face it this is what you did
no
but you killed me i just did what the
game wanted me to do i understand what
the game wanted me to do hey listen man
this is my job okay
listen it's just my job and you want to
run away from what's coming at the end
from explaining what you did you're
going to right
now
it's my job what about him
[Music]
you could have chosen not to shoot says
what are you serious i don't believe
that i don't believe that i do not
believe that i could have chosen not to
shoot you
often no you can't choose you can't
choose to
there is no way there is no way
okay there is no way
how are you gonna how are you gonna make
my wife happy again huh
there's no way to cheer her up anymore
[\h__\h] up
i mean
uh even so i kind of want to redo the
game
i didn't actually want vincent to win
come on man
[Music]
i mean i know he has a he has a child
but like
oh god no no not the basketball i didn't
mean that
i did not mean it about the basketball
[Music]
hmm
i'm sorry accusatory it's my job
i have to do it i literally have to
he looks dumb with a mustang
[Music]
hey carol
here
what's this it's my resignation from the
bureau
[Music]
it's over carol i'm out
please just give me one more chance
and andrew julie
it's a beautiful name
yeah and she's got your eyes too
sorry
[Music]
i know you are
you want to come in
i'd love to
i'm happy for you i'm happy for vincent
but i want leo back
oh why
[Music]
you were just doing your job
it's okay but i still feel bad
normally i don't feel bad but i feel bad
now
[Music]
i played basketball with your son and
how did i repay you i killed you
hmm you let me play b-ball with your son
[Music]
when
[Applause]
um
[Music]
oh
ah god that hurts
ah that really hurts
[Music]
i don't know how to feel
is there not a way to save them both
should have never played the game no
come on kiana you forgot the journey
don't forget the journey kiana
that was a lie no it wasn't
was the line no it wasn't that connect
four man those darts
that was real listen listen
you can't just forget all that
[Music]
now it's either one or the other god i
hate that
[Music]
oh man
kind of wish i didn't win to be honest
but i mean it's
it's that's how it's
i know i'm supposed to probably the
right way listen i really didn't think i
was gonna win
i thought that the game had one ending
okay i wanna know
uh for amma and guna who played uh
leo and did leo die or did vincent oh i
know how it ended for them i just don't
wanna spoil it for anyone in chat but
um oh yeah i mean i think
you should go watch i'll tell you
afterward kiara leo
left vincent died
i guess
uh sorry sorry you guys have you wanted
to go watch theirs
it's okay they did both they played both
endings why don't we play both because
i'm done with this game
oh okay i don't need to play the other
one
i kind of wish it ended the other way
but i mean at least i um have an
interest in shooting games now
i mean that's a good thing you got out
of it but but kiara
you can't you can't forget the journey
you know
life's a big journey and even though
at the end yeah every life kind of gets
a sad end because everybody dies but
i had a lot of fun along the way didn't
we the first stream that we did was a
lot of fun
yeah i liked all of them i liked the
whole journey
i liked when you were in the laundry
cart and you were being my baby
and now i was like and i surprised the
guard for his birthday
and then we weren't climbing up the
shaft back to back that was fun
and then i held up my hand for you to
get into the vent and you just you
wouldn't take it and i just wouldn't
forget to take it but you had to move
one one step forward but we're doing
that
we were doing the the picture
yeah exactly yep and then
and then the thing about the ted
i i i always knew there was no ted
yep remember when we stole that couple's
truck
in the ranch and they got really upset
we stole their guns and it was super fun
and then you started talking to the
chickens and you taught me how to speak
to them
you talked to my chicken i remember it
now
bro
i remember the language of my people yep
see there you go
it's the journey it's the journey kiara
[Music]
every journey's gotten ending it's
usually pretty sad
you know it was i had a i had a good
time while i was thinking
that i could trust you and you were my
friends that that that was a nice
time we can't trust vincent and
vincent's not your friend but i'm your
friend
okay remember that okay
are you are you my morty
ah yeah i guess so okay
yeah i mean you gotta remember i'm
everyone's i'm everyone's maury but yeah
you too i guess
you are my money too yeah
don't feel bad can i can i have a hug
the next time we meet
okay if you want
i will only because you're sad after
this game okay
well that's the only reason i will i
will grant you that if
vincent is not a great guy but me i'm
okay
okay i only kill you because it's my job
and i know you'll come back
so yeah it's like that
don't cry
it's just the intro of a brand new story
one wish
that i can't pretend this song isn't
going anywhere
is there an after credit scene nope
there isn't
that's just how well it was a it was a
good game
wasn't it fun up until the end it was
fun yeah
it was fun yeah so there you go that's
the important part we had a lot of fun
it's a good game i had i had i i
had some fun thank you kelly yeah
don't be so down kusatori we still gotta
go on a vacation
yes soon and i won't kill you on that
don't worry
on on another on a happy note uh
uh in about i don't know how many hours
uh 24 minus
in 19 hours i think or 18 hours
something like that
uh on my channel we have a a
collaboration a
a song cover coming out on my channel me
and kelly
and uh prepared uh we've been preparing
it for a while
and it's it's finally coming out on my
channel it's a wow wow world's coming
out
soon i'll i'll probably reserve the
premiere
sometime soon and then cloudy can
probably
we tweeted and you guys can all come
over and have
a nice premiere party uh-huh
yes finally the first takamori
uh song collaboration is coming to you
guys
yeah we worked really hard kiara did
most of the work though this sounds
really good
yeah i worked really hard your
rap sounds so good once again it's just
perfect
thank you but you did all the heavy
lifting so big ups to you for real
the video though the video is so normal
people are gonna love it so
um i hope everyone is gonna check it out
world coming out 8 a.m japanese standard
time
on the the 1st of january for us but for
many americans it should still be the
31st in the evening time
so check it out yeah go check it out you
guys
yeah um i'm gonna probably read super
chats in five minutes here but
uh okay yeah so we'll go ahead and cut
the standby screen so i can say goodbye
to you
okey dokey yeah all right guys well i'll
catch you on the flip side i'm your more
you hope you remember me you want to
sign off kiana
oh well um it's been nice
a nice journey a fun game i hope we can
play more
more fun games together you and me and
auf wiedersehen thank you thank you bye
yeah bye bye bye everyone see ya and for
those staying for super chat see you
soon
bye
[Music]
my ub was giving up on me
do me a favor
um
[Music]
your face looks a bit scary though
okay
[Music]
all right you
i didn't mean to betray you listen i
didn't know they could hear
[Music]
is
all right
[Music]
my
do
[Music]
go hello oh why is
it oh hold on sorry sorry it was only in
one year there
i was trying to work on my asmr mic
setup and it messed up a whole bunch of
things
now i have to have discord as a separate
mic and then my other audio my computer
audio is a separate mic
and then i have my my mic that's that's
in mono or rather that has stereo
separation as one mic
and then i have my other regular mic as
one mic it's just very strange
it's a weird setup i have to get it
figured out um
yeah i have to get it figured out during
the reaper reset yep
um but sorry i had to move the asmr
stream let me go to my room really quick
hold on
ah oh no you can see you can see
the inner workings of my camera i'm here
though
now we can't get anything to work right
today let's see
i know half my body is missing we'll fix
it hang on
there we go it's better now wait what
why is there two of me
fix that goodbye
i suppose a little scuff is in order i
mean we surely have had a lot of it
today haven't we ha ha
no that not that i know you guys could
hear kiara's mic
but it's okay
no worries bonus content if anything
yep yeah
don't worry we didn't say anything
embarrassing
we don't we don't have any girl talk
until the stream is definitely off
co-wink
no but really it's all good it's all
good oh okay
no worries no worries kiara's okay
kiara's okay i feel really bad
i didn't think it was gonna end that way
all of you who are here you you watched
the game you know how it ended
i thought that it was going to force it
to be the other way
because it's been a long time since i
saw that game play so i
i just thought to myself i'll go all out
i'll do my job um i'm not going to throw
the game i'm going to try my best to win
um and i'll probably still lose um
and it did not work out that way it
really didn't yeah
i thought you saw guras i did but i
didn't know who was playing who
yeah so then once we got
once we got to the middle i think that
kia actually read the chat and said
someone mentioned who was who
and so from that i knew how it was going
to end because i referenced back to
their gameplay and i thought oh okay
it'll probably end that way and then it
didn't
oh well i went full mlg
i was just doing my job the reaper is
not supposed to throw the game
you know this i'm not going to
purposefully try to lose
but i do like leo better as a character
i like his story better i like his
family better so i don't know it just
yeah left kind of a bad taste to my
mouth i mean i still would have felt bad
no matter how it ended but
yeah but you know like i said like i
said when i was trying to cheer up
kisatori
to novell in the beginning um it's about
the journey
yeah all those connect fours and playing
b-ball with your son
god uh i hope you guys do something
cheerful for the new year
i still got a lot of work to do
undercover this whole time who could say
who could say
yeah yeah oh well
anyway it's time to give some shout outs
so that i can go and
do some more business um be sure to
check i'm gonna post an image with
rescheduled stream stuff
um within the day
that we'll have new time slash date uh
for wine party
uh asmr reset etc just depending because
i think i mentioned this before but
the reaper fam wants to call um
for the new year and and i feel like uh
uh some time with them is in order yeah
so
anyway let me give some shout outs from
the super chat we got
from ghostwriter one two three four five
six seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
fifteen sixteen
seventeen that's that is huge
thank you ghost rider tori sugarino
ghost rider
thank you very much and ghostwriter also
left some on the asmr
uh on the asmr
live stream that has been banished to
hell just kidding hold on one two three
four five six six more
uh six more super chats um
from ghostwriter
[Music]
thank you very much asmr one
how because it was up for a while it was
it was waiting room pre-chat you know oh
gosh i didn't turn hold on i didn't turn
them off
let me turn them off
try again
is scroll down again
[Music]
we're almost there
anyway uh let's see and in the middle of
that we got one from vannafreya who says
hey
yeah big ups to claro thanks for the
rainbow claro
and a recorder for you
um and then let's see i know i have the
kazoo somewhere
um i oh i got really angry and i played
it and i threw it so it's on the other
side of the room now i'm not gonna go
get it
anyway big ups to claro claro is the one
who made uh the sand liopy
emote that will only be here for two
weeks uh so big ups to you claro thanks
for the rainbow
even though it's on the asmr on the asmr
live stream that was banished to hell
i greatly appreciate you
all right big ups too looking for the
top
synapse lord reverend thanks for the
august but takamori fans
expectations chicken uh with a ring
reality
um a knife
well lord revan you're not wrong
[Music]
why was i angry at my kazoo i wasn't i
was angry that kiara won connect four
and i threw it
um anyway big ups and thank you lord
brevin pick up such as q
with aqua spa and no message what a chad
big ups to you chazz q hope you didn't
cry too hard at the ending there
pick up decay hibiki
vince theo mendoza fabian
latino link razzies dazzies looking for
the top
the kevin kfp's deadbeat
spangenheim nuclear chesburger385
pickups to elias we're lands
i can't read this one but arigato
gozaimasu flim flammable
injury to insult slick otter k
looking for the top tyler bong jorge
rivera
linker talonflame 100.
hold on we need the text that says i'm
reading the super chats
for those who just arrive okay uh big
upstairs for firefang92
looking for the top and so rachel
daydream fox carl
liberian the kevin kfp's deadbeat
napoleon madrid mac
burning phoenix 39 the kevin kippy's
deadbeat
james byrne artie chan arsakar
sunny winter doomsday dan michael
[Music]
kfb accountant kawaiipedia
seth plays electrics23
mentally unstable tacos burritos
k youtube ai pants
k lord revin
mg d nintendo dan sweaty lumpia
kyle amber k ringy
zackbot kfp usual room uh there's a g
i'm guessing
it's probably guard xenomorph john
dent cool skull pants
okay rozzy's dazzies k
lewis not lou
[Music]
grenades richard johnson
slick otter jessie kiffer
jacob jacob angel padilla
dude where's the pizza summer okay danny
devito
thanks for the office but good to have
you back i see the stream made a chiara
impression
or is it the ea server that was
temporarily burnt to ash
you got me there view toy ski you got me
there i don't know what was up with my
isp today
or the other day as well they've been
doing this to me recently i don't know
what's going on
anyway it is what it is i'll check with
the internet demons later
big ups to dave killer
m from amateur engineering
degenerate.exe tachibana music channel
amateur engineering electrics 23
another akka super from v toy ski
usually it's kiara who's driving cali up
a tree but i guess callie is the more
little reminded person
you got me there view toy ski thanks for
all the akuspos and i hope you don't
feel too bad that i looked away from the
game to see your cats
it's fine it's fine it all turned out
okay in the end but nothing turned out
okay in the end but you're all good
vitoysky bring us to james byrne
bonbon tyler lee lavelanchula
davey killer sean r me and my friends
rozzy's dazzies imagine breaker luca
umbriel
yen ray imagine breaker zephyr kitten
kfb
real cat slick otter geringi
michael elay the last airbender ryan
sagalo
empty cacoon matthew wetherell
misfit jonesy johnsypoo
macarena james byrne bonbon
gundam jeff chan ernesto felix
el trotsky deadbeat exponent tie
dakuma kfp basement cert something or
something maybe surveyor
caden stewart jesse jer torres
hunter vasquez the d-doc
jade drago 14 unlucky fiver
waluigi cubed mac arena clay evans
kikaroo
miante hashtag denshana cancer fan flame
dna
kyo amber the kevin kfp's deadbeat
diago v shadowbolt tv
von0924 dragonfly
with the l mars ravel commie chaos
miguel bottom left manager
slick otter starry night five five five
oblitery two bruno schubert
nathaniel line clay evans
helen bluff lock kfp scrub frosty
khan felix sanchez drankie
fabian ramirez
jan ray the amazing zanatanium
jorge sweaty lumpia kawaiipedia
k forest garrett
orchid felix sanchez thiago tgm
pants luca umbriel
our cult arc lone thank you very much
for the akka spa i can't believe she
didn't choose to spare vince
what do you mean did you mean uh do you
mean
uh leo because we couldn't it's not
possible you can't do that
but thank you very much arcola and i
appreciate it
maybe we could have chosen to spare
vincent the uh the guilt that he would
have to carry for the rest of his life
and just you know let leo kill him
that's what i would have preferred
honestly thinking about it now but i
don't know well
did we have to do i'm a [\h__\h] gummies
just doing my job
big ups too sergeant hawk not so
deadpool
missed fist sky x piercer
lambo feels nightmare pretty
let's see hunt hunter vazquez
slick otter mars ravel lettuce
fussy killer man 16.
unlucky fiber minisha
and alco bow
very airy wander zander
kikuru 29
not a good username 360. sabre lilly
miguel macchias xp
miante hashtag nonchala conscious
spanking heim thanks for the arka spa as
a deadbeat and a kfp employee i feel
somewhat conflicted right now
i feel you there spanking heim i just
did what i had to do though i hope you
can forgive me
i gotta make it up to kiara somehow i'll
think of something biggest
thiago tgm the el
atlantian gamer christian thorne
geoff of the masks canvas night thanks
for the august but you won kelly but
what did it cost
everything i have to agree with you
there my dude i have to agree with you
it's a shame but i did what i had to do
listen don't hate me
don't hate me i kind of wish that the
the turntables turned on me
and the kusa toy could have had to swing
at me but it's just not how fate works
my man just know how fate works
big ups too flim flammable during edward
lee
doomsday dan michael calvin not so
deadpool
magical girl basil faulty
vampiric otaku 2021 cbd slayer
duo zero curdled wizard sean
r flynn kyle ember xenomorph
matthew wetherill roland's exes 27
cooley d i can't read this name but
thank you very much
c j r r carlos rodriguez
gerandi thanks for the occupy this help
with the therapy oh i'm gonna need it
i think that's what he is too maybe
they'll do it for both of us at the same
time
so we can work out our differences i
really do feel bad because to flash zero
five one two
oh zero five one two tacos burritos
resmo
[Music]
straw man flaming tp thanks for the
akaspa
bates never forget
that's right what a nice sentiment thank
you flaming tp
big ups to pants alrighty
chad big of super lens thank you for the
akaspa
is she your little pog champ i mean
i guess i don't know you guys seem to
like that a lot maybe possibly
thank you very much for the occupants
appreciate that biggest sean r
the real oyashiro paul mao
the kevin kfp is deadbeat
felladai yvonne
[Music]
kfb mascot bto demon
job 8891 star creator
just some stormtrooper with i can't read
the rest twitching bells
jose joshua h
kenshin 491 primal maniacs
shizu sumire gelato kfp scientist
kyo amber thank you very much been
saving this akka for first asmr stream
but it is what it is they say red is a
lucky color for the new year so here's
one for wishing you a wonderful new year
ahead but with laughter success and
accomplishment
thank you callie and kiara for the
stream thank you kaio ember appreciate
you
the unknown fighter thank you uh
room disco flynn pierce
deadbeat si sigefried
curtis or siegfried i'm not sure it's
one of those
marsup that
is smell nice nice i mean i know what
you're trying to do
selfies thank you very much that's all
yay
[Music]
we did it hooray we got through i feel
i feel pretty good about this being kind
of the last
the last stream of the year on my
channel to be honest it was nice to
spend it with kisatori in a fun and very
sad
game yeah i don't know we'll see if i
have time for
another i might do a gorilla stream just
just for fun why not
i need to look at my schedule though
because i don't know what the reaper fam
is doing
i'm also exhausted and i have other
things i have to do
uh i gotta run and do a bunch of chores
and
it's a lot going on but the whole live
event check it out
i think it's maybe like six or so hours
from now
on the main holo live channel gotta
check it out there
yep me and acoustic toy will be making a
guest appearance to
do some things and do some some new year
stuff yeah look forward to it
it's like that in the meantime i gotta
make a new thumbnail
i'll probably make one hold on let me
get us out
i think i'll probably make um a new
thumbnail
um no turn that off um out of whatever
kind of fan art comes out of this out of
this stream
surely someone someone might draw
something and maybe i'll ask permission
to use that but um
for now it is what it is i don't like
having the same thumbnail
it makes me feel weird
but hey at least i had a decent amount
of time on the last stream that kind of
you know got
f'd up
and do done said and done after all said
and done
it was a fun game and i know the ending
was sad and there was no way the ending
wasn't going to be sad
you know that's the point of the game i
think is to to make you like the
the two characters the relationship and
then be like well guess what you don't
get to choose a happy ending
you know sometimes sometimes in reality
too you don't get to choose a happy
ending
it's a very real game yeah i mean you
know for a game that's full of like
matrix you know matrix-esque
tricks and and uh scarface references
and uh shawshank references
it's a very real game everybody's chat
machine learning
i really enjoyed it i think it was a fun
game for me to play with
i hope she doesn't take it too hard
really because it really is all about
the journey
it's not about the end i feel like kusa
tori gets it though better than any
other being a phoenix
you know she always comes back so
in that way if there really are no
actual endings i mean but there are a
bunch of endings i suppose for kusa
she's probably used to it just give her
a little time yeah she gets emotional
sometimes but
everyone it's all right i just still
feel bad though kind of want to go back
in time and make sure leo makes it
instead of vincent vincent
you know i actually thought that vincent
was a criminal that's why this i was
like oh venison hahaha but what if he's
actually a really bad criminal
he's trying to mess with leo but then he
ended up being the fuzz
that was a fun game i'm glad that we
played it i recommend it i mean i know
it's
it's kind of difficult to recommend
because now you know the ending but
maybe kusatori and i can choose a
different game to play in the future
maybe a more lighthearted one
i don't know we'll look into it uh for
the meantime uh happy end of 2020
everyone i'm imori hope you'll remember
me and i hope we can still hang out next
year and have lots of fun together
i'll be waiting you know where to find
me but for now
it's peace out to 2020. bye-bye
[Music]
you again sometimes
[\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it
[\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it
[\h__\h]
[Music]