[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
let me try something
foreign
wow
soda
drink microphone drink it
you need to stay hydrated
I drink my drink my drink or I'm gonna
[\h__\h] water board you [\h__\h]
oh
okay
waterboarding is not torture
not in my books
I'm torturous am I
[Music]
um
what the [\h__\h] yeah
ah
Kenny key
and anything weird what do you mean as
my what I didn't hear anything
[Music]
oh
I think that's the old old chat
where is my new chat
oh no
[Music]
no oh
so that makes me make small verbs I
don't want to make small burp
I will not burp no
foreign
[Music]
something only Germans and austrians
will recognize I think
is that the German or Austrian brand
[Laughter]
it's carbonated yeah but it's like it's
it's it has no color but it has like all
kinds of different like fruit flavors
that are oh kind of nice
I've been drinking it since that was a
teenager
it's Austrian Oh I thought so yeah I
think I see it more in Austria than
and Germany
um
it's like Sprite yeah but less like it
tastes less unhealthy than Sprite
and it has really interesting
combinations
um
of flavors I'm drinking pear uh
uh pear bomb
bomb whoa I never knew what the word is
for Melissa in a lemon balm okay that
kind of
completes it uh never knew that that was
the English translation
lemon balm pear
[Music]
L
bum bum
um
okay guys
[Music]
saw the snare we're gonna play Minecraft
today sorry for the confusion uh I did
an oopsie again when with latency of my
chat
so I had to make a new stream
But Here we are now and I shall
try to open the game
let's see
if it's gonna work there's a new upgrade
update and it looks so cool on the
banner but we don't have it yet
sad
but hey I was seeing the seraphim yeah
I've been getting more and more into the
seraphim but new jeans number one
uh I like I've too but I don't know
there's just something about if that
feels unrelatable they it's like they
have this like Diva
um Aura surrounding them while a
seraphim is just dorky uh with like
badass songs and choreography and then
and then new jeans is just fun and fresh
and cute
[Music]
mm-hmm
G Idol I haven't been able to get into
like at all it's not I know it's like a
popular group but yeah
yeah I think her alone
like she has enough Diva Aura for the
whole group
I do really
remember like um
wait was it yunjin or Eugene you
it's confusing because I think there's
another in in the seraphim oh my God the
similar names
okay
[Music]
and twice yet twice you started the New
World Tour I saw some footage I could
probably get like last minute tickets
for their uh they still have European
concerts right did yeah pretty sure but
I don't know if I wanna cause like
I'm gonna feel so out of place probably
because I I know how to you know vibe to
oh
vibe to J-pop
uh to do otage but the chance for Kpop I
do not know I don't know I don't know if
I should I don't know I'll think about
it
yeah they already had LA and Oakland now
I don't know where Oakland is
um
that's what YouTube is for you won't
learn if you never go I don't know if I
even want to learn like does everybody
have to do those chants like when I went
to J-pop concerts like Idol concerts
there are always a few quiet dudes like
50 year old dudes in audience who are
just watching quietly without moving or
saying a word just like observing
and then there were 15 year old dudes
who else dancing though yeah it's
nothing to do with the age
um but you know there's different types
of people
uh yeah usually I was always like
dancing along and all that but I don't
know
I don't know it's in intimidating which
I guess no I think the twice ah twice
like K-pop chance of to me more
intimidating than like hello product
chance how the project is just like
intuition
you you know what to do if you feel if
you hear the Rhythm
but you know that's just idle talk again
that most people will be like what the
[\h__\h] is she talking about so
okay
[Music]
now I didn't even like that song that
much before
but now it's stuck in my hand
da
da da da da da da
foreign
[Music]
she's still streaming I saw she was like
doing a pretty late Minecraft stream
what's Autumn is greeting again oh
what
is it that is
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't even know how to write that
oh
anyone
ah so listen there
she's is she still streaming
I know she was building something
saw it I was like I wonder if we're
gonna overlap
no games are ass [\h__\h]
ah it's nothing special it's just hugs
anyway
um so today oh she only started now go
what
oh I want first of all okay first things
first
um I need one more name tag uh but I
don't have any left right uh
uh okay wait name tag uh
bye bye yeah we're gonna name Jeff
because Jeff exists
uh also we should
um
put on bgm
don't worry I got you I got you fam
boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom
boom boom now
[Music]
sorry I'm so confused today
I look at things
the whole time and I'm like huh what
what
happened
what your first time in the Chihuahua
stream after a year where have you been
you missed so much exciting [\h__\h]
how how can you leave me for so long
bgm do you want
hey now
you cannot leave again I left him in the
usual no but that makes no sense you can
still uh comment and watch on while
you're in the usual room that is no
excuse
hey I haven't had this one in a while I
think
yeah it's like my version of The Pickled
uh track
[Music]
okay I'm gonna use this for a while
because I really like the there's like
some kind of like pecoran music oh
fakes you know like this one like they
give off the same Vibe and I [\h__\h]
love it
oh
[Music]
um
okay uh yeah well what uh how uh we need
name tag right what what what are we
training again for name tag wait wait
wait wait wait name tag emeralds right
what are we training for emeralds
um
what could we try we could trade iron
iron
who trained iron but wait we have don't
we have like an iron specifically iron
trading guy because he's not good for
anything else armor
decent decent mining I mean maybe yeah
[Music]
how many emeralds sorry this makes me so
happy
how many emeralds I don't
okay I'm gonna [\h__\h] permaban everyone
who says
um you realize that I built this Phoenix
Sun right if I am not gonna use
my own
income of emeralds
then I can [\h__\h] burn this [\h__\h] down
can I not
and I'm literally standing right here
anyway
so uh what am I um
who gets who makes name tags
it's like I haven't played in a million
years cat hair on my hair on my nose
no they were talking about emeralds and
I'm like why why why why why why why why
would I
okay I need uh eight more emeralds good
good
I'll go get more
let's see what we could ride
what did I forget
[Music]
um
says something in these
yeah
[Music]
the melon Lord my Lord doesn't exist
anymore though right look he's gone I
don't know what happened
down
[Music]
all right
yeah
I think I have no choice oh and then I I
gotta go pick up some stuff for
fireworks because I think I ran out of
fireworks okay
[Music]
both blocking not good
need like uh what do you call the guys
that park your car
Parker no uh
I catch a live stream for once yeah a
ballet whoa fancy name
[Music]
for someone who [\h__\h] ripped me off in
LA
did I tell you I think I'm pretty sure
told you because I tell you every single
thing that happens in my life
yeah remember
man
it didn't even Park and like five
seconds after giving um the money why
did we
end up not uh parking there I think
something with the restaurant
that we were even at the wrong
restaurant or something like that
me and my friend like she was driving
the car okay let's tell the story from
the beginning you guys gotta help me me
and my friends not a whole life friend
uh
well we were driving for La going to a
restaurant ah we broke the wrong date so
anyway we drive up to the restaurant
and
um
and there's a valet so we're like okay
because they're gonna Park our car for
us because there was no other option
anyway
um no I'll take a couple more why not
and and and
uh so I give them the money
and then I go in while my friend is
still in the car
and I go in and like hey we have a
reservation
and then they tell me oh but that's not
for today maybe it was for like the
following day or the following month or
whatever we made a mistake in the
reservation
so I go back like literally only it's
only been a minute or so and we're like
sorry we're not gonna Park here after
all because reservation was wrong
can we get the money back and they're
like nope
hand I think
are all the lights
or what are you link are released like
that desperate
I mean come on it was a pretty popular
spot too I can't imagine them not making
not getting enough customers
yeah that's just America no refunds
literally been like a minute it's so
ridiculous it's not like there was
receipts or anything it's not like he's
like nah nah oh yeah I think he said
something like it's in our system which
was just [\h__\h] because there was no
system
something like that I'm like what I was
trying I was about to start to argue
like what's what do you mean what
systems just didn't do anything
[Music]
ah common fingernaily I am not
them
we don't even do I mean okay maybe in
like high-end hotels we have ballets
here
yeah but besides that I don't ever see
villains
in Austria
it's not that big of a thing here
thank you
you say I don't need faunas Emerald Farm
it might be cool but I am the owner of
Phoenix and okay everybody else whatever
go to fauna but I
so because if I wouldn't then
you know it's just it just makes no
sense anyway I'm I'm I need to let them
out of the boat so that they can restock
huh
hold us now
let's just
2.6 000 Emerald blocks sitting there
unused yeah but I'm not gonna take them
am I not being clear am I not being
clear with you guys
what am I looking for ah name 10.
so let's find Jeff yeah
Jeff for people who don't know because
Minecraft streams usually I think have
some more none
um everyday viewers non-regular viewers
[Music]
basically when I started a building
Phoenix done
when I finished I don't know when it
exactly happened but so someone in the
Super Chat started
while playing no it's real
um as Jeff so Jeff would keep on sending
me super chats uh who is a villager of
my town you know
and I could name look I could name one
of these guys
and he would you know be really
appreciative of me which I really
appreciated back
yeah and eventually I made him the mayor
and you know we have we were having back
and forth every time
when I did a Minecraft stream
however last time when I was doing a
purge
[Music]
didn't happen
um she didn't he didn't uh he didn't say
anything
so people were saying I killed him too
which is not true it's not true it's not
true
it's not true
I'm telling you it's not true
[Music]
[Applause]
and you want to see proof you want to
see proof
[Music]
sure I'll give you proof
I picked her name through it
yeah Jeff the man here it is oh there he
is this is ah there he is uh no need to
worry them
ah Jeff is here then all is good that's
why I couldn't find him because I rarely
go over here you know it's it's just so
so calm and quiet over here
he's not trapped oh look they're
actually sleeping
we should name these people too I
suppose but no I don't know
where is the melon maybe the melon Lord
is stuck somewhere he's not here right
let me check let me check the melon Lord
melod had a name tag right I'm going
here
[Music]
no no names
but could you consider this guy a melon
Lord
[Music]
well holy [\h__\h]
price just those prices
[Music]
the mayor
how do I get out again hmm
[Music]
um well
I can fly no I have no fireworks uh
um can I ride in alpaca was that a
possibility
yes okay
god
wow there's a gate yeah but then maybe
others will try to get out
[Music]
anyway
some iron oh you didn't want it
ah there's someone over there
who is this guy
masako
no way
[Music]
my Lord
what
I thought you were dead
you were stuck somewhere oh what do I do
with you oh
open up here probably
[Music]
what happened
how'd you get there
come on yeah
[Music]
was looking for him I gave up on him no
[\h__\h] idiot
what
Maybe
hello
wait what did he no
[Music]
he didn't die right
what
what have we just had a reunion
[Music]
he disappeared disappeared into the
night what
melon
my Lord
and
did he just die from that tiny fall no
way he must have like already had damage
or something then right
uh
can you
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] oh he's dead no he's not he's
dead no he's not
how did she get there so fast because
when I saw him taking damage
[Music]
oh my God
okay how do I how do I
okay I have both
um but this path over there is like
pretty
pretty difficult to overcome
maybe best to try to bring him here open
up a little bit
so let me prepare this
for my Lord I will not lose him again
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
I believe this
[Music]
unbelievable what it's like a little
four four comma manga
yonkoma manga daimo
he's having nightmares he's turning in
his sleep
okay
[Music]
um
should I wait for him to wake up
I'll do it now I want to do it now I
want to do it now what do you mean
[Music]
everybody's coming back to me
okay
um yeah mobs might be dangerous but
actually they're keeping away from the
light
so we're so good
at least here I have a bed too let me
sleep
I hope I can control him though
once he wakes up
as long as I keep on talking to him
my Lord my Lord my Lord wait wait why
are you walking away when I'm trying to
trade hey
[Music]
we have found ourselves uh a quest what
no can you not make it difficult for me
thank you thank you thank you thank you
no no no
come on my Lord oh
[Music]
I must protect my Lord the melon Lord
he's always got the best prices yo okay
[Music]
I am just
the best
oh but how how ah
[Music]
um
[Applause]
not the best really
um I wish
I wish you could make like slides
Minecraft please
should we make those like what do you
call them those things that go like
bloop upwards
[Music]
hmm
I could make
yeah piston okay you stay here now I got
you in the
in the
uh boat so he should be good how to make
piston what do I need
let me try to find a
uh
uh crafting table really quickly
[Music]
slime
okay I
um don't I mean I might have somewhere
randomly one piece of slime Maybe
at home
do I need one or more
I don't need slime for this
oh okay oh let me see
um
where's my
what's my crafting table
piston
ah there's a slimy piston
and a normal piston oh okay
we can make this
[Music]
how many was that free
yeah
we'll see
all right interesting I've never used
this before at four okay and Redstone
Redstone
oh maybe I have some at all
I never use normal is enough okay good
[Music]
Ness
why not simply pour what
water to paddle
okay okay
well that might work for that section
but is it gonna work for everything but
actually that's such a
decent idea
wait a second
we don't have to make this
ah
wait that works huh
that works I think right
damn it
that might really indeed be easier
okay it means I need a bug cat uh we can
make a bucket
[Music]
please don't Squirtle
we make up the water you need to switch
to that no no now we have ditched the
idea of that
but let's
oh do you need some iron
your iron deficiency fixed I am a doctor
almost
[Music]
um happy birthday congratulations
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you the reason it's so difficult for me
to get out is because it should be
difficult for anyone to get out of here
for their own safety you know
okay
um
water water
[Music]
then we got water
beautiful fresh water
well one bucket dinner
basically
we're gonna
pour some water here
[Music]
maybe some more huh
make it a bit easier
and then I'm gonna try to solve the
problem of you know
that didn't help what am I doing
um the problem of having all the people
in boats right now so they can't restock
we'll try to fix that
should I pour it on top of the ledge
okay
yeah maybe here's some more
[Music]
but I'm glad we found something to do
already something that I feel pretty
motivated to do
for the sake of uh Phoenix Suns
a better life for the Phoenix tonians
is worth this effort
[Music]
how you guys doing today by the way are
you guys being productive huh huh I was
being productive today
because I did like a lot of recordings
and
one of the managers who was in charge of
like a certain project
was like damn Kiara you you submitted
everything
so early what thank you
then like no problem
you're welcome
hahaha
whoa
[Music]
whoa what happened
bulldoggle both sunk why
not as I wanted it to go
explain guys
[Music]
come on get my Lord in there you cannot
drown don't let him know
what the [\h__\h]
should I make the water even
uh
[Music]
um
I put too much random water
okay
um
trying to place it
get in here get in here come on please
please please please please please
please
it drowns me it drowns me
[Music]
please don't go away my Lord I need you
right now
um
I'm a bit clueless right now try to make
it even okay
[Music]
should have made more buckets
oh food oh I ran out of food
my Lord what's he doing can you do me a
favor and just get in the boat
yeah
nice oh
but it seems like he's staying in the
water
put water at the bottom of the hole like
under the water
more water inside the water
melod can you sell me some food
I don't want to run away to get some
food right now
wonderful thank you oh and awesome
good food supply
um
okay so water down there
oh oh did it change
I know
water in the water
[Music]
come on maybe here
hey it didn't change I think but
fill the hole with blocks okay
[Music]
um let me get the boat again
on here
let's get some
lockerrinos
[Music]
how am I only picking up so few
they keep on coming
weird magic going on
laughs
okay as long as you're still here I'm
good
um here
[Music]
um
and then
you're currently in kind of a
bad spot my friend also
you realize it's night time it's kind of
dangerous
[Music]
um
did I get you stuck
oh no oh no let's sleep
what
bam
[Music]
dude freaking me out
come on
[Music]
give her some privacy please
foreign
[Music]
okay oh wait I should have tried to stay
on that level oh well
oh wow
yeah yeah it's okay it's okay
and we will continue to leave him in
there and try to kill it's like a like
those doggos paddling in the water even
though they're above water I'm gonna
continue trying to fill
the whole
filling this up again
maybe like
here Wada
take this water and take this water
put this water here take this water put
this water here they just is this is
something
is this changing something
no
what do you think maybe if I fill up
this part
maybe that's good enough
foreign
[Music]
here this okay
this could work no or is this
overflowing bad possibly hmm
yeah now how about now
drowning Hazard hazard
[Music]
I think this could work let me try
okay
fill the hole make it so that there are
no walls of water
I'll make it work I'll make it work
[Music]
we zoom over the water though
hey but like how am I supposed to do
this
thing is though it goes down a level
here again
hmm
I could
mine my way through
okay we'll do that okay we gave up one
enough maybe I should have made a
freaking piston
I thought when somebody said in the
comments Water Works that that would be
easy it sounded easy and too good to be
true
apparently it's too good to be true
okay I'll go here and then I think I'll
open up right here
and then these fields from these fields
I think he can already work
I don't know if he could go back into
the house but he saved there supposedly
just a bit more difficult to find Maybe
okay
this is enough space right
[Music]
we'll do it this way
workstation is inside then we might just
bring it outside
if that's what needs to be done
now there's no villagers there
it might be good to place someone there
I'm cold so after always
[Music]
we got him back inside baby
okay question is do you really want to
leave him here or do we want to attempt
to get him up there
no no the answer is no he's staying here
he's got fields to farm here isn't that
nice
fix the Escape Route
it doesn't need to be fixed right it's
outside the walls
what okay
you can do it by moving his bed here
he's bad they don't have like specific
beds right they don't just they just
sleep on whatever beds right
let me pour The Water Somewhere it
bothers me
break his back oh
[Music]
okay so the green bed was his okay no
problem
no problem
he'll be bound to it really
I thought they were only like kind of
picky about their workstations
oh oh it's disappearing okay nice
[Music]
I filled this up
they'll try to claim another well yeah
oh that's not a problem though
I could just give him a different bed no
laughs
[Music]
oh wait do you mean with Escape Route
uh where he originally escaped that
that's what I should fix
um
[Music]
or I'll just I'll just make the area
because it rarely happens like that
I don't know
[Music]
I can just try to make the area where he
will be now safer
one second
[Music]
okay
I think that jump is possible
well you see security is not that bad
here
[Music]
missing Mason please return to base
house
[Music]
what does this mean
who's Mason
these are all my people why would they
be returned to
she think I stole a Mason of hers
he said faunas they had a villager who
came to me look how
name him then name him give him a name
tag how would I know which one is who
you wandered up
not my problem sounds like a her problem
you know what I'll make him a little
little shed or something doesn't that
sound cute
wow another thing to do wow wow wow a
hit tweet amazing
I'll give him his own little house
because he's famous you know
he deserves it
[Music]
let's see what tools we have we'll build
it with Oak so it fits the the rest
where does lava bucket come from Mrs
always here
thank God I didn't accidentally use it
[Music]
was a love story oh okay
seems like we always built the roof with
lighter
wood and then actually I remember I was
the one who built this whole thing
and the rest was from my mommy partially
I continued building onto it though so
but yeah the roof is lighter than the
actual house
so that's it
oh
already mistake
yeah it's quite a long time ago
that stream of my mommy
no that's okay
okay A little shed for him
oh how many
Rose free roses enough right
[Music]
and then
can I make it look pretty or is it just
gonna be basic as [\h__\h]
mostly
let's have window too
I'm so nice I'm giving him a private
house
just for him
you know what let me give it a little
bit of accent
a little bit of an accent
as if it's like from Germany you know
funny ah no it's been away around
whatever no one will look
foreign
[Music]
okay and then
oh over at his floor his floor
[Music]
what did I is it just normal wood
I kind of want to give him carpet
flooring I'm a builder now he wow the
Builder couldn't be an unstopper
okay FPS
how do you make carpets again out of the
wool it's been too long you put you just
put them in here
[Music]
um
ah wait here ah
[Music]
yeah 12 is enough I think we'll give
them yellow carpet
foreign
birds can not be on carpet right oh that
is so stupid that is so stupid but okay
it doesn't stand out too weirdly
[Music]
then
a door
it's getting dark
[Music]
scary
uh maybe not one more window in the
front though
[Music]
I'll probably replace these with uh
lanterns but
for now
for security reason
how about this
foreign
[Music]
Phoenix 10 okay
okay and now oh [\h__\h] we on the roof how
to build a roof
[Music]
um
Fink kiwala think
[Music]
I know how to build a roof yeah
wrong thing again
wanted place it the wrong way
do I need to get some
what do you call it again
not not not a ladder what do you call it
again
do we have any anywhere hmm
[Music]
scaffolding yeah
he's scaffolding revealing yourself to
me
no scaffolding
if you guys see scaffolding
yell at me
no scaffolding
[Music]
I'll scaffolding
I don't think I have any scaffolding
here
maybe a hole
for scaffolding
I can work with that
just oh dirt yeah okay I could have used
anything
real scaffolding
[Music]
Professional Building
uh if
are you telling me you cannot put
scaffolding on this ground really
ah come on
oh wait shouldn't it be like one
one more behind
okay
[Music]
um
should I do it like this what
okay for now for now let's let me just
do the outer
one
I've seen zombies outside I closed up
everything right
that is incorrect I think
[Music]
third paths aren't full blocks so no oh
man do I have something to tell you guys
I'm looking forward to finally receiving
a hellofresh order today again I haven't
cooked in a while like not properly
and today is Tuesday my hellofresh day
so I think actually I missed out on
making an actual order so it would be a
surprise
I don't know what I'm getting I swear if
they put mushrooms in my order again I
wish you could just like generally
for like when you get automated normally
you can choose your recipes yourself but
before that happens you can get like
automated uh suggestions like you know
sets and then if you don't change it
that's what you'll get
I wish you could just like yeah say hey
um this these ingredients uh are not
good for me so please don't include them
you know like a system
a filter in their system so that it
never happens
and but that you can't State an allergy
what you can do of course is just you
know put on put choose this recipes
choose the recipes on your own
[Music]
and make sure you're not getting that
there we go
but I want to add on to it I'm like why
does it do that
[Music]
how do I uh
do I need slabs
[Music]
how did I do that aim for the lower half
of the block of this one of this one
right
okay thank you
it's been a while you know I haven't
built things
in a long time
hey this is kind of
night building a house here maybe people
will know oh there might be one more
person over here
that's worth checking out
[Music]
who is the is the fence gonna be a
problem
[Music]
um maybe
did I build it too close
well not necessarily
leave the back no no no no no
it looks cute
and I like it
[Music]
sure
that's kind of [\h__\h] up but no one will
see that
a little comfy house yeah
foreign
like something I guess a workplace but
this is this is his workplace right like
one of these could be his work was but
he might need his own right but but
normally like this would be his thing
right
but who knows maybe he'll just adapt one
of these because I don't think these are
being used
don't forget torches yeah and lanterns
foreign
[Music]
things here
don't end Rod also glow don't end Rod
also glow
don't and rods also glow
sorry I'm
I'm making fun of my own English
they do maybe if I don't find Lantern I
could use those but I don't know
lanterns are prettier why the [\h__\h] is
more my lanterns I thought I had some
let's sleeping goo
don't Kiara English
you can buy them oh who sells them
I have glowstone Oh you mean in one of
these boxes
[Music]
how to Lantern
[Applause]
I remember
anxious oh okay
[Music]
nice
iron nuggets nuggets
[Music]
Lantern
fish go
[Music]
more Lantern
to Lantern more Lantern
[Music]
more Lantern
now I'll enter
[Music]
how
hello did you guys see hanama's recent
King Wawa cosplay
[Music]
I guess I in my tweet I say no I said no
maidens but I guess I was wrong I got I
got quite the maiden
[Music]
I wanna make
so inspired what the [\h__\h]
I wanna get a trap though and have it as
a table
trapdoor I'm sure I have a trap door
somewhere for free so I don't have to
make it I know I could make it but if I
have like random [\h__\h] items
everywhere I want to
use them up trapdoor
trapdoor
[Music]
rap door
no trapdoor
[Music]
a wood you made one of me you made a
wood bed for us
a trapdoor
[Music]
um
make this
huh
[Music]
okay this works
coffee sleep mmm
[Music]
I'm getting embarrassed
has a question
oh no
okay how
I could even put a flower in here oh
wait I want to make a flower I think you
can make it with bricks
flower pot I mean
oh my god wow
I don't know why I'm making it so pretty
I had bricks I know that
flower same break
[Music]
a clay
wait
oh lie I I have what I need
um
okay let me eat this
and then I need a flower
[Music]
even though I hate building I'm getting
pretty into this huh
okay here is uh
the flower pot
ah
oh can I not put it on there
I thought that works
um
oh really
[Music]
shift
huh and maybe before
[Music]
I'm holding [\h__\h]
huh
no
[Music]
[\h__\h] wait
hold him
[Music]
what
hello I'm bouncing whatever let me try
the other shift
oh the other ship doesn't make me bounce
interesting
but
[Music]
it doesn't work
aim at the wall
um
no doesn't work
[Music]
okay
is my sneak toggled uh yes
[Music]
I have to put the trap to one block
lower
okay what maybe if we first place
these
can still place this
but one block lower it makes no sense
how's it gonna be at the height that I
want it to be
[Music]
pop-up Puff
aim at the top half
I went
Celebration Time come on
[Music]
I can't play stuff
so Sunny oh okay no worries lower I have
a solution
[Music]
okay works
okay okay okay okay okay and then
a nice
[Music]
um
are there can't place Lantern why
uh
what's going on
[Music]
can I know
I need ceiling
if I wanted to play some I guess
they don't do side uh lamp sound in this
game
okay okay
[Music]
let's finish the roof then
with how
uh
saw the snare
need to place block
[Music]
then I can place it on top
is gonna Place Kingdom Hearts it's gonna
play Kingdom Hearts what the [\h__\h]
I was like what the [\h__\h] what what
that was the one game that we all
thought was never gonna happen for us
right
damn
but that's Square Enix right Square Enix
I know Ina wants to play it too but
don't get your hopes up guys for Ian
playing Kingdom Hearts I've never played
a kids game before
I kind of don't like how long the roof
is but oh well
it's fine I guess I I guess it doesn't
fit with the proportion of the house
being so low
or is it just maybe I should
make the roof actually
um lower too would that look better
[Music]
just ended on this level
kind of cringy but also fun
please play the first one if possible
well you know as I just said don't get
your hopes up but
it's nice that at least Japanese
Japanese members can play it good for
them
[Music]
um
oh yeah 12 weeks it will be I used to
play that when I was younger
oh nice
nice Cottage well that's cool we give
him ah we don't then we didn't give him
a flower yet is there any flowers here
I have the Golems taking them all
because they like flowers don't they
I'm gonna find the flower there must be
like a single flower somewhere here
we isn't as good it's not about you know
something
being better
[Music]
each game has its own charm you know and
it's like good in its own way
but I I I have found memories of touring
but you know I was so young when I had
that on the DS that you know back in the
day I never finished playing games
because I was just not good at them
didn't know how to properly play and
finish games
[Music]
I don't think there's a single game I
ever finished
[Music]
I am the flower delivery person
here comes the flower
what should we give them windows here
too
probably won't see much here but
yeah why not
looks kind of nice
um I mean this is the view that a lot of
Tokyo Apartments have
um
[Music]
this is Tokyo
and probably a lot of other countries
who are which are like built this close
no
[Music]
yes
your house is pretty much finished dude
pretty much I mean when I'll play some
like lanterns here
[Applause]
related to the Halloween sisters like oh
my God or maybe I am because I built
this
[Music]
damn
Good Times joke from me right
oh
I want to fix this let me get some dirt
no no no no no no no
went over your head
yeah I put so much effort into it
I'll kind of just go over your head
[Music]
I don't think I need the Wood anymore
oh
okay oh
I thought it was uh
the llamas make sounds like the shulker
boxes kind of don't they
am I going crazy
[Music]
can I have some more melons
um melon cake
pumpkin pie
[Music]
yeah they're like sound yeah because
they both spit
[Music]
incredible I just realized that
because I thought is there an enemy
there
thank God there wasn't
okay let me fix some paths
um I was gonna
[Music]
make everything a bit more
organized I suppose
in that case let's get rid of this
[Music]
maintenance at Phoenix Sun I think this
is making my mommy very happy that I'm
working
on Phoenix Sun again
I haven't completely given up
no no no I never have I never will
[Music]
that wasn't zombie though
the zombie maybe Underground
[Music]
I know a zombie sound when I hear one
how much placement wait let's place this
I know it's unbelievable that I'm doing
this but one two three four five one no
maybe more one two three
one two three
one two three one two three one two
three one two three one two three
wow
that what if I sleep in his bed is this
then not his bed anymore
let's not um
provoke it
I'll go sleep
in one of these beds oh I can okay
um
can't get an adorable carpet
you're telling me he won't be able to
get in
no way
hey
really
[Music]
ah no okay oh that's fine that's fine
I'll just Place locks everywhere
that's fine
BRB getting the the wall blocks
okay
[Music]
it was worth an attempt
you know I'm just thinking realistically
I'm just I'm just I haven't been playing
Minecraft so much so my brain likes to
do things in a realistic way
such as
you know no real house has a full block
of wool as their corporate
just
sense
[Music]
okay
oh
I got the red amount
just about the right amount
perfect this one this should work right
I actually I
you know what I'll just have this be
normal wood
[Music]
yeah looks nice too
I like that the other way around
I don't know why
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
okay are you ready is he gonna know that
that's his house I hope he knows but let
me just make sure that everything
he can't jump up here
uh let me fill this a little bit up
I shouldn't fill it up anymore though
right otherwise yeah it could be able to
jump
better feng shui
put some mouse on top Ah that's kind of
cute it could like be a sign that this
is the melon house yeah you know what
yeah I like that idea
um but I think I don't really have like
you know
like that so let me go to
um where there are lemons
cute also like as a decoration
um melons
where is that
where's the starting area
[Music]
go back home and then take the train
[\h__\h] off
looks like Henry
[Music]
are sure
let's go let's go come on
I wonder I want her cats never
you know me
we should do game
[Music]
oh this area is so pretty
oh man let me my brain is so empty today
guys
I'm sorry
that I'm not like throwing topics out
there I was tattooing so much yesterday
during my Super Chat reading
I guess that's where it all went
[Music]
any more stars with Henry's Cube owner
oh
let me check my phone
if I wrote something else down
oh
[Music]
wow
the day after tomorrow we'll get the
update damn it should have played
Minecraft then
I just saw him
I will get the update on the 15th but it
seems so expect Minecraft streams from
all Japanese members
the one we have here ate I myself made
pastel oh she made me squash it was the
first time I had squash thank God I'm
writing down these things what am I
doing oh well I'll walk
I've never had squash before and like
squash pumpkin squash supers
no never had that
[Music]
the pumpkin
butternut squash yeah
it's like a orange pumpkin and people
like to make soup out of it right
um made it as like a like a vegetable
side
and it was the first time I ate it and I
realized oh this is like a mix of
pumpkin and zucchini
I mean I guess zucchini isn't isn't
zucchini like kind of a pumpkin though
anyway but butternut squash I'm just
saying kind of tastes a little bit like
zucchini
oh wait maybe butternut squash is a
zucchini I don't know they're definitely
related
[Music]
there's squant what's squash
extra kind of different
similar like you know like a mix you
know
okay here here I am making use of this
uh melon house again out of slices I can
make a whole melon right
you know what I'll bring a couple of
these and put them in a box
for people to trade with him if they
don't have anything to trade wouldn't
that be nice
actually kind of Genius
[Music]
but I don't have so much space I mean
the Shocker box here I have an empty
shocker box
ing another stream
[Music]
all right
okay more
[Music]
what Fonda needs material for her tree
what does she need
[Music]
S I know she's making a huge [\h__\h]
treat so I'm guessing she needs uh like
dark because it looked pretty dark dark
Spruce or what
I'll leave a shulker box there with a
sign that says feel free to trade this
with the melon Lord if you need emeralds
what a genius
he's filling the leaves now so it's all
bright stuff oh she needs orange wool
and glass
oh orange wool and glass
well we have a wool farm and there's
wolf arms on the Japanese server too I
don't think I can particularly help much
more than you know
maybe make some glass but um
what am I doing oh yeah
[Music]
damn it I wouldn't have minded to hunt
down some trees
give her some Spruce some tree parts
but she's making this kind of like egg
dressle kind of tree right
you know I thought when I was playing
Tales of Symphonia
that because like there's a Grassle Tree
in Tales of Symphonia and I was really
young I was like I don't know 14 15 or
so and I was playing that
so in my mind I was like
thinking that a dress a little tree is
like has a Symphonia thing and then
later on I sometimes would see that kind
of tree and other RPG stories and so on
and I'm like oh okay I guess it's like a
general concept
hmm
yeah world tree
[Music]
my gunpowder no
it's Viking religion
what do you mean it's my mythology
there's many mythologies
Scandinavian
[Music]
like Scandinavian mythology is so cool
We need oh we need you know how ume is
you know in charge of whatever Humanity
or something like that I guess
civilization
uh we need someone who's in charge of
Mythology
which is a weird thing to say because
there's a whole myth but none of us is
really like in charge of like mythology
the concept of morphology
but it would be cool to have someone
like that who then could tell us about
mythology
isn't that you guys right but no
maybe I should make a stream on
mythology I should like inform myself
about it and then yeah
I know
isn't that ama's job
um
I mean we could say isn't this Emma's
job or isn't this Dino's job Etc about
many things
did I eat all of my pie
[Music]
just another creation of people
technology falls on the moon you think
so
um
told me she can't do like history
streams right even though I always talk
about history
but I feel like mythology should be fine
right because like
story okay it's like maybe there's like
I don't know
something controversial or so about some
of it maybe but I mean mythology whether
or not any of that is like true so
obviously it's a myth so
if you can't talk about mythology then
you can't talk about Hollow myth
right I don't know just trying to apply
my logic here to make it work
[Music]
the history of a potato don't [\h__\h]
wave
I did talk a little bit about this a
moment I'm like hey I talk about history
all the time
I'm just gonna you just gotta you know
let it out like you know in the middle
of a stream not dedicate a whole stream
to it just you know you know
Senpai advice
how to do things
I would be interested in hearing the
history of a potato
am I running
I feel like why am I not isn't Ctrl
running is this running am I I don't
feel fast to myself
foreign
[Music]
interesting history or is there like a
whole like fight about who invented the
potato or so and that could be
controversial claiming that it's from
run one country rather than from another
country who gives a [\h__\h] who where does
the [\h__\h] a potato comes from
no need to fight over it
oh no there isn't well then even more
cell
then there's no problem
[Music]
nature oh yeah see in the end
everything's invented by fauna
[Music]
okay I'll wait
melon
[Music]
how many should I make
I think I'm a Mac like four
and then I'll climb up
foreign
[Music]
Center
I guess it's free and six
[Music]
nine nine
right
before five six seven eight nine
math
math uh one two three x yeah
what am I supposed to do about that
hmm
turning into them
[Music]
slices
no
[Music]
whatever wait
no
[Music]
nine times three
nine times three doesn't know but with
this the uh the other problem I have I'm
just making the roof bigger again
which I didn't really want what makes it
look weird
but let me
let me think
well if it's just one melon
melon Tower no
ah
[Music]
um
let me Place ah this should have been a
green shulker box
by the way
or should I place it it would be nice to
have it inside but then people are not
even gonna find it
I mean who's gonna come here anyway
right but hmm
[Music]
maybe next to it then
it looks pink right now
[Music]
melon melon melon whatever I'm making it
like this
it is what it is
[Music]
what if I like
it's like a melon birthday cake up there
it's the melon house think it's very
noticeable at least I'm gonna place the
melon inside here too so he knows what
he's all about
I want one more more melons
[Music]
come on that one's
melon hair melon there
maybe part of the house is a melon like
his house broke once and he fixed it
with a melon
then it kind of broke again on another
spot and he doesn't have woods and no
money so he keeps on fixing it with
melons
wouldn't that be so cute wait
ah cute cute is even getting a backstory
ah
you're another melon
yep that's how you fix houses I mean I
would say melons can be pretty sturdy
and if you really running out of food
then you'll always have some secret
rations in your house actually that is
such a cute pattern like a wallpaper
pattern almost oh my God you could use
this as a wallpaper pattern for like
inside if you're like actually trying to
make a build that looks like it has a
wallpaper pad you know what I mean you
know what I mean what if we make this
whole thing out of the ceiling what if
the whole ceiling is wallpaper
melon just real melon
so he when he sleeps he can look up and
he sees a melon Sky a sky made out of
melons whoa how many do I need
one two three four five six seven eight
wait three times four right one two
three three times one twelve
twelve
one two three four five six seven eight
nine
whoa
Mountain House
[\h__\h] the real nice guy we want melon ah
[Music]
um do we want the stripes
although we want these like this pattern
maybe we can do both
[Music]
wait
wait wait
um How do I
how do I make it sideways
uh oh I can't anyway really
[Music]
oh
no way melon can't be put sideways
maybe they're supposed to be rounds so I
don't know they always roll to that side
nah
nah okay
at least you can still put lamps on it
[Music]
but that is so cute though it kind of
looks like mosaic
it looks like those Mosaic patterns and
and colors and everything that you can
also get on Minecraft though but it's
like a cheap
good cheap version of it
[Music]
yeah that's cool
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] I don't think anyone
in her life ever considered using melons
as a pattern
for decoration
[Music]
as a design element oh my God how do you
dye shulka boxes can you do it in here
how's that look again
oh okay genius so she has you know good
taste for that kind of stuff she gets it
one brain cell with Lena
[Music]
um
how to how to make this green again
[Music]
I don't mean like a whole melon themed
house I just mean like you know using
this as flooring or so
not making it all Mountain themed but
you know green dye and then throw it
together in a
[Music]
green dye
flowers Disney flowers green flowers I
think I have some at home
you should share wedding rings next
we said that fistmas Mrs what happened
to your name
[Music]
don't tell me it's always business you
cannot fool me
[Music]
let me go
Cactus yeah but I think I do have some
dye
at home
Opposite Day
is it backwards day this is something to
do with formula
oh uh-huh
ah what if I say you have to change your
name to something who are you gonna
listen to um
[Music]
you are at her whims aren't you
oh here I have a green chocolate box
here
uh green dye we have lime dye and green
diamonds
green dye
I'll just take one again I like this wow
wow genius
it's not genius and so like
happy with myself today
will you make us change our names well I
mean I kind of did I gave you guys
titles and all that
many of you are using it
which I appreciate
here's John
[Music]
the only person I can buy with over
coaching Market oh it's been obvious
today I was kind of kind of kind of
watching Capcom
showcase
uh I wasn't paying attention through all
of it
because it didn't seem like much was
going on the chat also was absolute
cancer
but this seems to be normal right that
this kind of
YouTube chat
for like big showcases like this
chat absolute cancer like everybody's
crying
[Music]
is terrible
but they already say it after five
minutes
can I
change the color while there's stuff in
it
[Music]
we shall test
oh noise
okay
I'll pop it here
well that [\h__\h] up the ground but and we
need a sign I saw a sign somewhere
probably not here though
[Music]
part of the building no because then it
doesn't open oh unless it could open to
the front I don't know
but it's okay
[Music]
so I would like to have a bright
the the lightest colored wood actually
so it kind of stands out nicely
foreign
[Music]
there's even lighter ones in this one
right
[Music]
sorry guys going home again
so anyway the first one didn't even seem
to be a new announcement but I kind of
thought that looked nice what was that
even I forgot the name
first game they showed that I've tweeted
about too
what was that
oh one second
actually you know what I'll just ignore
it because yeah if I ignore it they just
put it there but okay I should probably
pick it okay I'll be right back
[Music]
foreign
that's my face I'll be making when I
look at the recipes I have in my hello
beatbox
[Music]
where am I on which side am I
think the right side huh am I where was
I going where was I where was I well oh
yeah
Birch the birch
[Music]
wood
although I'm also kind of low on wood I
think generally yeah
but I have some Birch
okay let's make a sign
merch sign
and [\h__\h] stick
[Music]
Toco no [\h__\h] sticks
stick less I'm stickless
I may have some maidens but I'm
stickless
sad
[Music]
uh maidens in my brain
sign
there we go out
first thanks super strap door okay let's
go
so yeah what was that game called and
it's winded about the first one
what is that called
[Music]
can you start paying us so I don't have
to work to jump
I wish I could
always
I'm trying to pay you guys with
entertainment at least
[Music]
kind of looks good to me I don't know if
I would stream it but is it coming out
anyway is there a release date
but it was like one of the two things
that spoke to me during the Showcase
um
no date oh okay this year next year do
we know
looked like it was pretty far been
development but so I guess not
20 24 hmm
but that was already announced right
there was nothing new
[Music]
okay
feel free
to trade these melons in
for emeralds
[Music]
nice not wonderful
word
[Music]
ah well
we could do them a favor to make all
those melons into proper melons
but that's okay because I just realized
he doesn't take slices
man okay
one second
[Music]
I am so nice
No One's Gonna [\h__\h] use this but I
will see I will see if the melons
disappear after one and somebody is
using it and then I'll be happy do you
think anybody will use this
besides me will be the only reason why
things are disappearing
[Music]
glue them melons together
your show and suddenly it's way less
oh wow
that was that's not even one for
chocolate box but okay at least it has a
cute color right
you got to sukunai
maybe I'll bring more
[Music]
maybe I will bring more
hmm
huh
oh well people know where to get
um
melons from yeah okay uh yeah so let me
check real quick again if this area is
safe for him so he can escape
[Music]
I think that's safe
look safe a button here
we kind of want to block it off
completely right or
um
but he wait what they can they can go up
one block right okay wait can it I'm
confused I don't even know anymore
can they
[Music]
can yeah right okay sorry big confusion
moment
I saw him I literally saw him doing that
but if I get rid
of this
[Music]
scene
too much
if I just got rid of this area
[Music]
wouldn't that be
solving the problem
[Music]
now wait wait I mean okay I'll have to
lock it up here
possibly with a fence
okay uh
uh
[Music]
what did I do
foreign
[Music]
there's a chance someone will use it
cannot connect us
well that's lame really
[Music]
because it's also
hmm
[Music]
it's not getting on an icon
walls and fans don't connect
don't cry
okay third block it is
safe and yeah
can't jump here can't jump if I can't
jump then they can jump okay but here
[\h__\h]
[Music]
but this is safe right
bombing festive
[Music]
blank is probably at this point the
reason for 50 of my current memberships
just kidding not that much but thank you
thank you so much
I want to do more pathing
packing is fun
[Music]
makes it so pretty
right wow pretty wow amazing
[Music]
oh he got you he got you
oh yeah and Dragon's Dogma
if that comes out I will stream it if I
get perms
um
I have a feeling it might actually be
played by a lot of other members too I
feel like it it could create a kind of
like Elden ring effect
don't you think
I don't think you guys will be lacking
Dragon's Dogma streams but
[Music]
who knows
hype is gonna be huge yeah I I have
never heard of the game before but yeah
you guys typing it up
made me realize it exists
okay my Lord are you ready to be set
free
set me free
foreign
[Music]
let's go
this land is all yours to farm
have fun oh he wants to sleep right away
understandable
[Music]
he
go
wanna take a photo wait oh let me get a
little bit more
fourth quick profile oh
whoa
I'm gonna look for Peak for the window
maybe no that's not good
but here we have
the new house
taking screenshots by the way the new
house from my Lord
and a note for everybody
maybe I'll make a tweet about it maybe
some Hollow members will see it and and
save the information in their brain
okay
cute wait it's such a cute like melon
bed oh and it just so turns out to be
that his bed was already green
oh man makes me happy and I want to see
if he like properly restocks and
everything
let's check that out because he had some
things that were
um unstocked right so we'll see I'll go
to bed
otherwise we'll have to find out like
what to do
red carpet it might be even better yeah
but yeah that's okay
for now
oh
[Music]
my Lord is that you working already
come on
all right it's not race and wait no that
wasn't ah yeah not restocked yet but
he's standing there is he trying to use
it do I need to get rid of this
suppose so oh
so that he can use it
[Music]
he's a mountain field nah
[\h__\h] I mean not for real right
you're just saying you know
maybe he'll make it though there's some
where are you going where you want to go
[Music]
not restock yet
I'm waiting for you to do your thing
he's exploring so write the old one the
thing is I don't know which one is this
old one
[Music]
foreign
the first one are you sure
[Music]
okay I'll break it
or I'll break them all
and that resets it right
[Music]
so now I'll choose a new one
oh oh she seems busy oh
isn't that so beautiful oh that's so
nice seeing that actually work are you
seeing this fauna
[Music]
shouldn't you be supporting this you
know
having Farmers through actual farming
work on on Nature's grounds
why farmer because she won't let her
people actually do it look at him oh my
God
because tires are all stuck they don't
get to actually enjoy the joy of work
you know he's enjoying it oh my God he's
like glowing and he restocked
I feel like I just
changed his whole life you know for the
better
and and I just gave him a purpose
while I'm a goddess
[Music]
amazing maybe I should leave that there
for people who want to change melons
into melons
[Music]
or I'll leave one like in here and you
can place it yourself
let me get some melons
[Music]
like a mother sending her son to college
no not quite not quite but similar
[Music]
ah
you're free and you still don't restock
and you never
does that mean
what does that mean
what does that mean guys
[Applause]
[Music]
they look accessible
this is their workstation right is it is
it a blast furnace
one yeah but that that doesn't mean
anything right
wow is it plus I think it's these ones
are are these just decorations
[Music]
these ones
okay is this one so hard to break
[Music]
is my why they're not even moving it's
actually my my my game
crashing right now or
why are they not moving that's actually
the weird thing up I moved them
but they don't move this is like a lag
right
now
[Music]
all right
could it be the Bell
LaBelle
this belt
[Applause]
they like the Bell
[Music]
what what why what what what's going on
going on
[Music]
and I mean
I'm gonna place these like here
I just replace all the workstations but
it's kind of weird man
[Music]
uh I don't know about these ones
reset the dead people beds oh hey you
think the beds are making them bug out
[Music]
very mysterious stuff going on here
I feel like
and maybe it's like I don't know
[Music]
oh
I'm still not moving what's going on
wait are you moving
is this bothering you
no
um help hey bro what's going on
[Applause]
[Music]
would you guys move if I let you go is
it safe to let him go let me check
do I need to change anything actually I
kind of I don't know
I want to make extra sure before London
everybody go
that the maintenance time is over
I want to make more of this flooring
what's it called again deep slate brick
slab thank you guys by the way
I might not
I might not have any more
I have all these like
brick stairs
[Music]
what's this pass out
um
we use the very fancy material didn't we
are all the library oh good question let
me see that
well my Lord was moving happily
yeah
[\h__\h]
they are ones moving what about them
yeah yeah they're moving okay
[Music]
all the riptide is also kind of
chilling
oh
anyway let me check my home if I have
some deep slate bricks Just A Smith to
Twitter yeah they're bugged out can I
reset them somehow maybe if I put them
in a boat I don't know
foreign
at this hour oh no problems my European
prime time slots
yeah what time 8 P.M I am at your
service
UK friendly stream time
I am very happy if I could get more
European
continent viewers or anything close by
just feel like a lot of them just watch
Twitch you know there's this like twitch
culture in Europe
I feel like they're hard to be convinced
to come over here
how do you what did I say
do I need Blackstone
Blackstone brick was it that what was
that what it is
[Music]
deep slate
ah [\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
guy
have that where do you get that from
again
I guess we'll go mining
when Europe didn't know there was a
twitch culture I've I've been like
coming in there is
I feel like there's a lot of YouTuber
viewers on Twitch at least that's what
I've noticed
yeah twitch is definitely bigger as a
like for people who want to watch
streamers
where do you get the stone I'm looking
for
uh
what am I what was it called creep slate
right
deep slide is uh
not in the never it's just very low
right in the underground not in the
underground but in the on the you know
deep sleep brick slump
okay
time to dig a little beat
then let me clean up my inventory but
[Music]
uh
foreign
[Music]
YouTube has ads too
planning let's see
wait uh one thing I need to do
is make some of fireworks
just in general
[Music]
thank you
they actually actively tried to counter
at the oh
yeah I've seen there was some like
uh uh out
what's the word people were crying on
Twitter about twitch changing things I
saw the drama
I always see drama on on Twitter so much
drama oh wait there are fireworks here
oh
if I ever ask again if I have fireworks
guys tell me they are here
[Music]
but didn't they like kind of apologize
and say oh sorry wait wait wait wait I
didn't mean it like that
funny
so maybe they're changing it again who
knows
[Music]
they're just taking
us too far they can go you know
just gotta
see how much you can afford to [\h__\h] with
your community
just put this here for now okay we will
go and
get some deep slate shouldn't be too
much necessary I think
foreign
oh I have some more name tags there
[Music]
oh ah I'm a Roblox
okay should I take a shulker this is
almost empty it's a good shocker box
keep my shell
[Music]
there's a Reddit thing now too what is
what is Reddit doing
[Music]
hmm
ah a bunch of shokos on top true true
yeah my my model orange you're calling
it model home because
that is actually a correct way to
describe it I suppose
yeah
where should I dig do
I have to go far away out
do I have to go to newly loaded
territory or will it spawn everywhere on
the ground
[Music]
soon the old server and I'm kind of on
the new server it's just connected no no
I mean you know no but I just want to be
here you know I'm comfortable here
yeah I should be able to dig here too
right
thank God like started digging here
before oh yeah oh wait torches oh I did
bring torches genius genius
maybe I shouldn't have brought my
my wings but oh well
uh which one is the silk touch okay
[Music]
well done
the digging shawl commence
[Music]
help I will find my way back out there's
light here at the end of the tunnel
this is probably connected to our
Subway anyway huh oh yeah that looks
like it could lead to the subway
oh oh where does this lead
[Music]
s
oh no
it's scary no scary noises
no
no no no no no no
okay I'm gonna I'm gonna go this way ah
ah
for sure okay
we're doing what the title of the game
says
I watched a video of a guy
[Music]
looking pretty young like some teenager
uh creating the world of breath of the
wild in
Minecraft
pretty incredible
taking ages
yeah but but but apparently like he used
some kind of bass there was like some
bass I think no no really there's like a
height model apparently
not just for Minecraft but it's just a
general height model of
was that wait maybe I'm mixing up things
because I also watched the video of a
guy creating a model of uh breath of the
wild world
um
uh
not in Minecraft just in real life as
like a
um what was he using he was using resin
and I don't know what the main material
was uh
what was that foam probably foam
so just I'm just I don't know I got
these recommendations of people trying
to recreate breath of the wild world in
whatever
yeah but it was all pretty impressive
and cool
I want to work with resin you know the
material that
can
be used for crafting cool things
see-through things or you mix it with
colors and it's like looks like a gem
so pretty I always wanted to learn how
to use that
it's very interesting
I was filling the the waters the rivers
with that it looked really nice
it's toxic when you sand it be careful
cool
good to know
[Music]
it's easy to use literally you just put
it important stuff like hard and there
you go yeah it looks rather easy oh we
have arrived at the Deep Side
nice sells fast
hi Redstone how you doing redstone
and I didn't even encounter any enemies
[Music]
oh but it's just a little but if we go
deeper there will be more right this is
just confirming
they played should I use
it's like TouchWiz is okay Cobble tea
plate
maybe it will be good to use my
because then
yeah then I can make it the the bricks
straight out of the deep slate right
oh genius kiwawa
mommy mommy mommy mommy mommy mommy
mommy
huh
[Music]
I'm okay
brightness scares me
[Music]
well there's really not that much here
well I don't know how much I'll need
actually
the more the merrier for whenever I need
to fix something in that area I guess it
should be cobbled
well I can remind it right with my
normal pickaxe and I thought it was ah
Oh I thought it would be good to have a
to have it be
[Music]
um
yeah
deep sleep straight up
scared scared
[Music]
I think now I'm using the normal one
I'm scared
[Music]
get up pick it up
I'm so scared right now
just because I met lava once I didn't
expect it at all
but doesn't seem to be too common
right now
[Music]
okay
honestly I'm so jumpy nah I'm not so
jumpy today
I've had jumpier days
I'm checking my notes
[Music]
um you know uh how last year when I went
to America
um
I had
an interesting conversation with the
immigration officer right
I was a bit nervous this time as well
but
since it did work out last time even
though I fumbled so much I thought oh it
should be no problem this time either
but still you know
um I didn't think about it much about
what to say until very last minute when
I was already standing there because I
completely forgot about that
so yeah no no different person of course
what what would the odds be
nowhere this was a different person and
it went well I would say grab of well
um but like I let me try to remember I I
went up it was it was a lady
and so I gave her my
passport and I showed her my esta thingy
you know when you go to America as a
non-american
you have to sign up for an esta thingy
but that uh if you do it once it will
work for a couple of years
[Music]
okay
um
she's like what is this I don't need
this
okay so yeah she was checking
my passport and she asked me
um
how many times I've been to America
before so I tell him this is my third
time I think
and then she asked me uh what are you
here for so the question the question
for one million dollars
what are you here for
good question I said um
meeting with friends
that's what I said she said oh what kind
of friend ah
to ask what kind of friend all the time
uh the first first you asked female or
male as a female girl she said what kind
of friend I said
um
uh a friend from work she said what kind
of work that's that's what a moment was
for a moment she was like you know she
was looking the down the whole time and
the moment I mentioned the word work she
looks up is quiet for like half a second
or one second and she's like what kind
of work
yeah yeah
I know it's dangerous word
you know being honest so she says what
kind of work I say uh
uh we both work for a Japanese company
and she's like okay and surprisingly it
ended there this time
she didn't ask anything after that she
was like oh Japanese company oh okay huh
I thought she would ask me more
but actually that was it she was like
okay well
she didn't even ask what my
[Music]
job was
nope
oh another would move along
nah
[Music]
that was quite relieved that is when so
easy this time
thankfully
[Music]
thank you
so it seems like you know you can say
the word work you know it's not
immediately bad and even last time
you know
what I was saying kind of implied that I
was working during the time I was in
America but
oh hello basically
if I received the money at home
and it comes from Japanese company to my
European bank account
at another time while I'm not in America
then you know it doesn't really
cause an issue I suppose
seems like it didn't
cause any issues so
well
so all good
I'm getting used to this talking to
immigration officers I mean I used to
talk a lot to immigration officers in
Japan because I used to go to Japan even
when I was
um underage
oh I'm still on the right stuff
uh and y'all I was getting questions so
much I could never just enter Japan
without being questioned in a separate
room
[Music]
um and if there's any people in the chat
who don't travel who haven't traveled
ever before
but normally when you enter a country
you always have to go for immigration
unless it's like within Europe and you
go from European country to European
country but if Xiao your passport you
show your thing
thumb prints fingerprints
um we have to fill out some forms this
and that usually it's however quite easy
like nothing happens you just have to
give them all your information
um
and uh oh mine I was mine yeah and and
and
um
yeah
normally it's no problem you go there as
a tourist and you just have to give them
some info and then you go through
[Music]
um and there's like usually several
counters you know several lines
would stand in a line
for half an hour then it would be my
turn I go to the counter I show them my
stuff and they're like they make a call
to a colleague and they're like follow
this colleague and they would bring me
to a separate room so many times and
every time I would [\h__\h] my pain
I wouldn't but it was always kind of
scary and I'm like why every time
I'm just why why must you always
you know treat me differently
just let me fruit
[Music]
eventually they stopped after a while
like after a couple years of this
repeating
they were like okay well we have our
eyes on you but
um we understand that this has been
going on for a long time now so from now
on we won't do this to you anymore okay
and I'm like thank you
they legit after a couple years said
this to me
[Music]
I'm like thank God yeah honestly like
I'm I'm so sick of it please
give me a break
[Music]
nothing wrong it's just like the age
that
and me traveling alone
that made them sassy
I had work visas to
[Music]
sometimes like in the beginning it was
tourist visa which was also totally
like legal I wasn't doing anything wrong
and then later on I went with
um
a specific type of
work visa
and then after Wilding
that's when I had to go to different
kind of immigration anyway
not the airport immigration hmm
[Music]
yeah they were just suspicious
what you're so young what are you doing
alone in Japan huh
thank God I'm not being sussed out
anymore
it always makes us so nervous
I'm almost there in the presence of like
also like police officers or so
even when I didn't do anything
it's always
I'm sure you guys can relate right right
yeah
authorities almost intimidating right
because I mean
it even when you didn't do anything
wrong sometimes you know they do claim
you did something wrong right cases like
this
always are
think not that's not lying I don't think
that's why I get nervous though not that
I'm thinking that this will happen but
still
if you think about it it could happen
[Music]
um
I think I have it so let's get out of
here
there's nothing wrong now
America is
[Music]
I don't know
nothing wrong thank you guys you won't
stand for me right
in court
in court one day
when the day comes
I don't know what day but when the day
comes
[\h__\h] scary noises
where's the exit
[Music]
oh here
nice what the [\h__\h] are I heard a baby
cry
[Music]
no it's just a sheep
hey let's go
I saw him this way on the KFC bucket to
tell nothing but the truth
nothing and nothing but the truth
our own truth the truth in my heart
okay
but that was Bank Minecraft
[Music]
I got one
of those but wait a second now though
maybe
I don't think I'll need that much anyway
so
let me put the the Deep slate in here
um
[Music]
in case I needed
uh
yeah okay
hmm
and then bricks
deep slate right
uh what
breaks them these are the ones right
deep slate brick slab
is that what I was using
but first need to make deep slate
got it
how to make deep side this is cup of
deep slate what wait what the [\h__\h] I
mean go really quickly
I need to check I need to confirm oh you
guys said a new cobbled
huh Cobble Deep Side brick
Stone cut down oh yeah right but you can
do it also on the normal
work
Bass
chot tomato
figure it out
[Music]
and I think there might be a stone
clutter in Phoenix soon
[Music]
foreign
influx of cats here what's going on
now check if they're moving again
did you guys restock
oh see
yes
okay all is good all is well over here
wonderful good to see
is there a stone cutter here is this a
song cutter yeah
uh but wait
[Music]
you little shits
okay
no problem no problem guys
no problem
we're good we're good
[Music]
I just wanted to say
the magical word
you understand right
[Music]
okay here we go let's fill this up so it
looks nice
oh I like to sound I'm placing these
well finally finishing up this area too
Mommy will be so happy let's sleep
though
oh it's it's snowing
is it night time no
okay
so dark I hate this weather
[Music]
I don't think you can use that door
anymore oh no one's using that anyway
[Music]
but okay
um
okay
[Music]
what do I do about light can they be
placed on top of the slabs no right
[Music]
oh this is probably an issue too
um gotta Place some torches maybe I'll
make some more torches then
and not torches I mean
lanterns
[Music]
how did I make lanterns again the iron
right
I think I left all my iron at home now
damn it
didn't I leave it all at home
did
I disappoint myself every day
[Music]
uh
all right it's it's daytime oh wait they
don't spawn on half blocks let's go okay
then maybe for now we're good but I
still wanna
you know place at least some so it looks
nicer
Dean hi Henry where's Wellington how did
you did you fight him
this time I got so close to Wellington
I'm so happy I was like recording some
stuff and uh Amy's computer
and Emma was like somewhere
and when I like stopped recording for a
little bit I was being quiet everything
was quiet I didn't hear Amy I didn't
hear anything
and then
I was just checking some stuff on
Discord and then suddenly Wellington
enters the room
[Music]
and and he's just like hello
and when I was there last year you know
I
never really befriended Wellington
because he he always ran away no matter
how slowly I would walk up to him he
always ran away
but yeah he was really curious and open
this time there was less noise on the
first day there was so much noise
um because like Mama's dogs were so
excited
they were so excited wait actually I
need
um nuggets anyway
don't need all this
yeah my dogs is so excited and like loud
the whole day
um
Bubba did get some I tried okay I tried
to give them more attention also that so
that I wouldn't feel bad it was more bad
for me it was more personally more about
making Anna happy than making bubba
happy
[Music]
so yeah she was she was like very proud
of or like you know she was telling me
look look I gave him a haircut and I she
even actually showed me she sent me a
picture before I even flew over
sent me pictures of Bubba and she was
like look I I uh I gave him a bath and I
cut his hair so that you will like you
know like him more
oh and that's what I felt really bad I
was like
does I meant
did that really affect her
okay okay
it's time to step up my game
felt kind of bad
[Music]
I mean it was really funny to see though
because like Bubba also to me like he's
at some point you know he remembered oh
this is that lady so he would be very
careful with me and just
um ah [\h__\h] can't place it on here if I
thought I could place it on there um but
I can place it here
that's nice that's nice too
hmm
I guess that works
[Music]
I was like oh that lady okay I'll I'll
be I'll be careful so
you would sometimes he would forget and
then be kind of aggressive again which
is what I really don't like about dogs
when they like jump at you
and yeah
like you
I've seen
when you when you're like bare legged
and then they attack you
just it hurts
or when I wear tights and then they jump
on you and the tights
uh
yeah also break
a million I don't know dogs are just
[Music]
but they're also funny like I can
I enjoyed watching I'm interact with
Bubba that's like I enjoy watching Bubba
more than like touching him yeah okay
[Music]
oh
but I tried to give him more love this
time okay so
give me credit for that
[Music]
unfollowing what
no
no I tried my best okay I Gotta See
forever thank you
there definitely was effort
[Music]
why is there the stairs here why is it
not just slap
[Music]
is there a reason
maybe so it looks nicer here oh well I
want to use the slap now see how shiny
it is
oh
[Music]
looked neat kind of dead oh well I
destroyed it what you gonna do what you
gonna do
[Music]
foreign
but honestly I think the cats were happy
to receive more attention because I feel
like the dogs usually with all their
energy and all that they always
like overpower everything and whatever
it is
like with visitors or
I feel like automatically when a dog
jumps at you you give the dog attention
and then the cats are also I saw like
the cats being kind of intimidated go
they go away when the dogs
like run around and back my backpack so
when they end up hiding a lot
so
then there's kiwawa who specifically
gives love to the to the ones that are
often
suffering by the
aggressions of dogs
[Music]
said and I I am you know I made it
actually better
[Music]
yet Bubba loves you well I appreciate it
you can't love everyone back though
[Music]
this is this is bothersome isn't it
this is gray wool
[Music]
hmm gray wolf
let me fix that too
[Music]
I want the fixer
beautiful
a couple more slabs maybe I can put them
here
I'm saying [\h__\h]
that's a block right what is it
[Music]
foreign
yeah it's that kind of
reply I'm sorry
but I I was nice to him
maybe Emma can approve if you guys ask
her
I think she would approve
she would she would say yeah she tried
her best this time
[Music]
vampirina was always good at like giving
Bubba the attention so that I could
focus on Henry
on this time there was no Inna so it was
all on me
[Music]
damn it
hmm
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait uh
guys tell me how many pets Emma has
checking with you guys
okay good
just wondering if there's some people
who don't know what but yeah
um for madness
yeah the other dog that she has
that one I was actually
um petting more because that dog is less
yeah Mickey Mickey yeah Mickey is less
aggressive
and she's she's kind of she has an
interesting personality
so so very cute watching Nikki uh
interactive amen
and Nikki is so noisy like noisy not in
like way but Nikki would just like like
the whole time Nikki makes like
you know grumbling noises and that kind
of stuff
hmm
just to get attention I guess I don't
know oh wait they can jump over this now
ah
when I can make it a a double fence I
don't know can I
oh and then I get stuck in there like me
hold on
dig it up
[Music]
foreign
let me put some stuff and
all these shulkers
for the future if I need it
um
let's make some deeply towels
outside
wall
so many different ones man
okay
[Music]
Mickey Mickey begging for attention yeah
Emma doesn't say she does Mickey gets on
the Microsoft
oh
[Music]
cause usually it's always Bubba who you
hear right and I'm in streams
Bubba is so
like his presence
so overpowering
[Music]
but Mickey is quite the interesting
character too I must say
okay
okay okay wow
I Want To Praise myself
because I fixed this back part that
people are not gonna pay attention to
but overall you know in the big picture
The Big Picture People Are Gonna think
wow
everything is so proper
isn't it
yeah look at this
oh
marvelous marvelous
can we don't talk about the second floor
someone might appreciate the program my
mom definitely will appreciate the fix
back
if anyone will it will be her these cats
really want out and what if I open the
door for you
here
oh okay your fault then not my problem
I want to place more lanterns on the
ground but it's difficult
um
can I
can what could we make where we could
place it on
just a normal
brick brick
this one looks cool too but I guess also
just like a single wall
you can place lanterns and fence walls
yeah
but this is kind of like floating
[Music]
um
hmm I guess it's fine because it won't
spawn there right because it's
because it's half business slabs so they
won't spawn right right
shall we
just add one more slap oh
yes
[Music]
where exactly though I don't want it to
look too randomly scattered
[Music]
so Random
um like maybe at least one around here
[Music]
nah never mind it's okay it's okay
um
[Music]
gonna play store
materials in there actually
that was a better box
okay if I ever need to to fix something
maybe because of a creeper or whatever
there will be more materials in there
and the wool too actually
so I think I am finally ready to set
everybody free once again from their
boats to stay true to my model of
freedom
radar villagers and workers
[Music]
I thought I'd make it easy for myself
for once still no was that
to get rid of the bones by just getting
it with one click
with an ax
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't like your idea of freedom
meaning
yeah
me neither I'm always scared when
getting rid of boats man I'm always so
uh
I don't think he was too oh [\h__\h] oh okay
I don't think it was too important right
and this dude really needs to be
brought back there huh
can't do that now
although I should have been I should
have done that now but oh well
Bring It From Below what about his trade
I don't know who was that oh
tell me that was dead so it wasn't tetsu
oh I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm
I'm gonna commit Minecraft suicide if
that was tetsuo because no
no he didn't look like tetsuo
[Music]
no no no no no wait wait wait wait
where's no it's not no no no no no no
it's not it wasn't no is it Tesla
somewhere like specifically safe
[Music]
people scaring me like that here's
that's all
no um
[Music]
scared the [\h__\h] out of me
we can check in an archive from a
previous stream who we put there
I don't think it was someone
too important
[Music]
um
so nice
so nice letting them roam freely enable
hitboxes no I'm good I'm good
I'm good I'm good I'm good I'm good I'm
good I'm good
why
doesn't undo what I've done I mean I'm
sh I'm so ashamed
[Music]
Freedom she says
got them all I think
yay
happy
what
ah these guys
[Music]
power five and uh I'm breaking
I well all of you kind of want to go
elsewhere huh
um
let me try
all right all right one more thing I
guess this is fixing Phoenix 10 episode
two
um I'm gonna pour some water
I will try to bring these people in
their correct departments
foreign
this one might because I think I
probably destroyed his workplace
[Music]
see I should have left them in boats and
uh done this while they were all in
boats
they should walk back on their own
they seem very eager to go to a specific
place don't they
okay okay okay I will I will let you if
I get rid of the trap door it would do
let them through right but um
can they go through here
from from this direction
or do I have to remove this here too
gotta be fast there's no one here right
okay
[Music]
break both
but then I also have to do something
about the door there
but the efforts they'll go in that
direction right
okay okay
nice oh he did it from outside
[Music]
where did the other trapped
okay uh aha was that your trap that your
your workplace outside cool and you were
trying to get in or
[Music]
no I mean
was he
did he have something on stock because
he's not he stalked now
that might have been his
or her it's just a hurry but everybody
prices are kind of high though
zombies they're probably underground
damn
they did see what
yeah I'll leave them outside and since
they're the only ones and there'll be a
mess why do you one eyes in your beds
now or what
do you want to go outside now I won't
let you
[Music]
know because there's enough beds for the
exact amount of the people here
um yeah but no bets for them ah but wait
they have access to these beds don't
they aren't there beds in here
there's one in here
[Music]
they could no only one they could use
that bed for example and that house
might be claimed
well should I make them new beds or
they're not important for restocking
break them and bring them over
[Music]
well I don't know which one is theirs
should I break all of them all of the
beds in here again
we did that already they haven't even
slept in here since the last time I
broke them
so can that even be the issue
[Music]
two million views on four blocks
um upstairs
I don't think they had access to that to
be honest
maybe these ones
[Music]
you know what I'll bring them two beds
and just leave them outside for them
[Music]
foreign actually yesterday I had a
meeting
would you like this bed can he even go
on that when it's floating
yesterday I had a meeting with um my
lyric writer for album
can they sleep or not
[Music]
probably not and
um we were discussing you know what
theme
these remaining songs I don't have
lyrics yet should be
and
yo I'll make you one here there's more
Lantern lecterns here
want to sleep on this one maybe we'll
see if they use it I guess
how's it coming
uh
actually like two songs are like pretty
pretty much yeah 100 finalized now
oh he still wants to leave
yeah
the beds are here now
he was dumb
okay let me try this again
[Music]
um what was that going to say anyway why
did I get this idea to talk about this
anyway
I don't remember what what my point was
going to be
let's see
ah four blood oh yeah and then we were
talking a little bit about four blood as
well because
um
even them like Kira and my lyric writer
money
they all they're like uh yeah Fort blood
is your song now
[Music]
see your song blossio
you did so well
[Music]
hell yeah oh [\h__\h] I wanted to see if
they do end up sleeping in their beds
now
hmm
they're trying to escape why do they
want us game I'll get it why are you not
happy here
why are they maybe they made such good I
mean they've been over there for a while
they probably made really good friends
and I was trying to talk
[Music]
with their old Buddies
I mean they're also weird for trying to
go to the other side
hmm
[Music]
oopsie
let me check here
if I open that
well
[Music]
there's only two beds here and I would
hope it's your guys's beds
[Music]
foreign
but let me just reset them just in case
[Music]
where you guys again Aerosmith and some
random dude
safe safe safe okay
[Music]
why do they even want to go outside
during Daytime Nighttime I understand
but oh
[Music]
hmm
I don't have any lecterns over there I
think
[Music]
man why would the Golems attack me
I'm the creator of this place they
respect me as they should
um
yeah okay well whatever as long as they
restock I guess is fine
because I murdered someone they always
want to be away from me is that what
you're saying
at least they're working kind of
overpriced but you know it's not too bad
they know where their workspace is so
I think all is good okay
[Music]
so
anything else to do
[Music]
we made that house
I bet yeah I was gonna I was gonna
transport this guy
[Music]
but I think I will use the Piston now
wait I was I just finished transporting
these two so now he's left over
I don't know if he'll automatically go
over there do you think he will
[Music]
yeah let's let him out of the first
store and see where he goes from there
because it's not like he can completely
Escape The Village I think
[Music]
does he even still have a desire to
leave
huh
not real
[Music]
oh
we try and just change occupation no
he's still talking to a friend ah why
should I like force him to go elsewhere
when he's happy here
um
[Music]
he wants to socialize
yeah I see that
[\h__\h] Enderman what the [\h__\h] get out
of here
chill
[Music]
make a new compost should I put one
there
[Music]
because it will be kind of a pain in the
ass to move him over here now though
these steps you can at least
walk up on his own right he wouldn't
even need my help so it's only getting
him into this
half
that's the only
issue which isn't too big of an issue
okay
waiting for him to jump down
[Music]
he's so fast
boy aren't you
[Music]
can get the boat
[\h__\h]
[Music]
where'd he go
I'm just trying to get you into
the place where you work at
[Music]
[Applause]
get into that boat engine fan
and ever gets a name tag from me it will
be Shinji
[Music]
[\h__\h] hell if you could only put them
on a leash that would be really great
but it it even maybe even for Minecraft
standards that's just kind of I don't
know distasteful
[Music]
you're gonna get in the boat and you're
gonna get it yeah
okay
Phoenix both taxi service yay
okay here we go I'm gonna
uh but I'll need a piston for this right
because I don't know there will always
be like one level higher
I'm not gonna mess around with water
again
[Music]
piston
needs uh we've got Redstone Cobblestone
I have
iron hat I have planks
I can bring okay it's a redstone
don't think I saw any Redstone in here
okay
what's the difference between
the slimy one
and the non-slimy one
why would I want to use a slimy one
[Music]
it will stick to blocks the other one
doesn't
okay I guess that's like good for
building
certain things okay
okay all right still endorse
[Music]
okay getting tired why am I so tired I
didn't have a nap today long nappy time
oh I saw uh like YouTube recommended me
videos
of like high school live of certain
like country students and this one was I
think from a Chinese student yeah
pretty sure it was a Chinese student and
I was
absolutely
shook head
[Music]
um I even wrote it down because I wanted
to talk about it
and I write it down yeah
so the student would get up at 5 00 am
and come back
home at 10 pm
while not wasting any time in between
and spending all of this time at school
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] right so 5am getting up
then kind of quickly preparing at home
and quickly actually pretty or soon
leaving uh home and the commute was
maybe maximum an hour so it's not like
it's the commute that's taking so long
no no no
[Music]
yeah then getting to school and you know
this and that they start also with like
exercises that the whole school has to
do this and had so much to do
and there's like this is a high school
and and yet
they have uh like what was it 40 minutes
40 minutes 50 minutes of nap time
calculated into their school day which
see first seemed like what the [\h__\h] why
because it wasn't around like maybe noon
or or early afternoon or so but it made
sense later on when you realize that
they're still at school at like 7 P.M
you know
and then it seems kind of uh necessary
don't you think for students to keep up
the [\h__\h] concentration
Yeah so basically
you get home at 10 pm but then you wake
up again at 5am
so you're getting like seven hours sleep
if you fall asleep right away
but they eat breakfast
dinner and a breakfast lunch and dinner
I think all meals at school
and they just do everything like oh my
God there's so much [\h__\h] it's it's
it's yeah
I cannot imagine
being at school for 95 of my day for 95
of my school life or like teenager life
sounds terrible right but it's not only
China apparently that then it's like
this
huh
[Music]
I do not envy them
it's crazy
[Music]
but it's like normal there and
that's just how it is so
no complaints
and their son
no childhood yeah that's what I was
thinking and then I was like thinking
about how long I used to stay in school
uh
when I was a teenager in high school and
and Junior High School
and I mean at least we don't have this
whole like uh culture of everybody has
to be at an after-school activities Club
because that was also a little bit part
of why they were at school so long
everybody had something to do oh and
also there was like a study time as well
in school for
people who don't you know don't have a
space at home because it's too noisy or
it's just no space to study so pretty
much almost all the students also stayed
for that I don't know if they have to
Pistol
or things just want to but yeah
most of them stayed until like 10 pm
um
kind of crazy
[Music]
what did I do did I kill a cat
I'm not gonna try to get this guy again
in the boat by destroying the bow
get out of there
I'm sorry but
[Music]
I'm sorry no
oh
[Music]
no I can't do it
[\h__\h] cat
I can't do it
[Laughter]
I have a [\h__\h] sake
[Music]
it's been let's remember this is his bed
at least we know that now
[Music]
yeah anyway I was thinking I think so I
would get up pretty early for some
schools I went to because I was just
pretty far but my school would start at
8am
I think
yeah and then oh hi why are you looking
so much at me we're going on a trip now
follow me
[Music]
and then I mean it depends really on the
day
but uh oh is this gonna work
how's this even work do I need a button
[Music]
that's [\h__\h] annoying
lever
okay
[Music]
laughs
ah
yeah Sundays I think I was only the best
days would be like school until 1pm
so like I think um maybe like five six
hours
those were the good days
and then the longest days would be and
when I say hours it's like the the
classes were like 50 minutes and then 5
to 10 to 15 minutes in between break
depending on like if it was a big break
or a small break Etc
but it's not like full hours yeah
so yeah the longer days were
Maybe
I think the longest I had in high school
was like 10 hours maybe
yeah
I think the longest was 10 hours
and then I would get home at like maybe
6 pm
but that was like once in a week
[Music]
and if between the usually I think if we
have one or two hours of
free time in between I think sometimes
we had two
two hours in between
on those longer days maybe I'm not 100
sure anymore but the longer days they
weren't too bad
[Music]
um
they weren't too bad they tried the
teachers tried to give us a schedule
where
um
the longer days would be kind of
bearable
okay I cannot place the lever anywhere
well here but
that's not gonna work
[Music]
I guess I'll have to destroy this [\h__\h]
okay
hope this works look at how to get the
guy in the boat again
racy
[Music]
right here this time
where is he hiding
I know
wait a second did I
no it's okay
hello moshi moshi farmer Guy where are
you
ah
oh now you want to go
elsewhere come on
remove the Trap otherwise you'll get
hurt okay
um one night run can you please go also
maybe I should wait until night
so they won't get in the way is this
gonna work
please no one intrude I will [\h__\h]
kill you guys
accidentally probably oh
[Music]
I'll bring him extra clothes this this
Uber service brings you to your doorstep
[Music]
and it was I was trying to say that like
European or maybe like not everyone in
Europe but mostly
in Europe our culture
of how long we keep the students in
school and all that it's pretty healthy
and yeah I guess it's like a maybe an
Asian thing to keep the students
in school forever
okay imagine though like man
sacrificing my whole childhood teenager
to that
but that's why I guess most of them are
like pretty well educated look at
him
see I was oh we got that I was thinking
that you know here they're just wearing
many
workers
and now I fixed this problem I returned
two of them
[Music]
here it's just at the University there's
nothing of that in high schools
oh okay I don't know how much it bothers
them if it's only yeah if it's the only
life they know I was thinking that too
it's probably just
how it is for them
[Music]
for Japan for what I've seen from Japan
it's not as bad that they have to stay
until 10 pm
not that level of that
but yeah I think China might just be
extra special
[Music]
let me just reset this bed
because I saw he was sleeping in it and
now we should be good right
I wonder when they find time to learn
what interests they have
um
hell like Hobbies or man
I guess you don't need to have hobbies
as a as a teenager
I mean even I already felt like I was
out of school too long but when I think
of no okay wait this is okay
[Music]
stuck
nice nice
Jeff is also same
it's very nice
very
um
satisfying hmm
look at him go
damn he's finally taking care of this
place that I've been neglecting
you graduated high school a few weeks
ago nice good for you good job I don't
even think it's very efficient you can
only learn so much in a day your brain
needs time to process and yourself
dude
[Music]
[\h__\h] hell you're not gonna be able to
get back
ah
this wasn't safe
well
um you [\h__\h] it up buddy you [\h__\h] it
up
[Music]
why must you make things so difficult
for me
[Music]
no problem
almost hit you
problem no problem no problem
[Music]
one of the delinquents
I should be able to go over there
mother
this should work
okay the carpet down
[Music]
can I get can I can I get in
thank you
[Music]
even though it's lower in theory
okay now stay in the boat I'll just make
this so that you can't escape
make it higher but then it will be also
problematic for me to get over in the
future damn it
[Music]
um
who are you up
[\h__\h] you like multiplied
sorry for missing with your land don't
worry about it um
I'm just
um okay I I
okay I didn't I just placed a gate here
right that's that's only yeah can can
they not open Gates
jumpy oh don't let me a little bit
[Music]
suddenly my Lord he's so curious
we need gate open start
[Music]
okay
um
how long ago you guys in like America
Canada and so on
staying in school per day
[Music]
how oh wait I should love him for first
uh he'll probably try to go to sleep
right
if I let him go now
like what time usually does school end
[Music]
are you guys usually like at school
uh always until the same time or is it
also mixed 3 P.M
4 or 5 PM
3 P.M usually
3 30 4 P.M okay okay that seems very
humane
3 P.M
3 40.
the people who are saying it very exact
are probably in school like right now I
mean like
apparently School goers school going
people because otherwise I wouldn't
remember
the exact time
Wednesdays were 12 30. oh that must have
been a fond memory to you
oh I think it was technically 255.
okay you better go up there otherwise
I'll be mad
okay
and closed
no more escapees now I hope
very much hope so
I can't put two Gates next to each other
right
[Music]
place my carpet again
foreign
[Music]
okay
beautiful
[Music]
the guy who's stuck at the wall forever
is I don't know I feel bad for him but I
can't help him I tried to help him
[Music]
didn't I even try to burn him but even
that didn't work I don't know
maybe I need to try harder
I may have attempted that yes
so what
someone
rock star got my rock
[Music]
I'm all right
sorry
[Music]
another mission for another time will be
to get rid of all this and put it
somewhere else
and clean my [\h__\h] inventory
at home
everything needs to be cleaned
[Music]
see I'm already starting
it triggers me too I'll be honest with
you guys triggers me too
laughs
no I can't even stop myself
I'm color coding it now
[Music]
okay I I couldn't stop myself
it's happening it's happening
[Music]
why do I have so many boats
ah because of those people
um
[Music]
that was City got me I'm lost forever I
thought it couldn't get me I thought I
was
immune
should I leave the orange terracotta
there maybe for now but not forever
[Music]
this will be the gray box
the gray and maybe the black
foreign
so it's not even sorted by materials not
really
[Music]
you'll have to think what color is the
object of my
desire
and then now it's already already too
much in there
[Music]
oh Brown wait I mean there's two
different Browns
okay well this is more like the reddish
Browns Maybe
this could go in here it's a little bit
of a stretch but
oh there's the whites
here's this
some iron
the clay balls
[Music]
and then and then you know placing it a
little bit more with a system
that's how you do things right that's
how you do it
[Music]
I have OCD and this isn't what okay yeah
I mean I don't know I guess I feel kind
of bad because like OCD is being
kind of made into somewhat of a joke
sometimes like this
sorry about that I don't know if that's
maybe insulting to people who actually
have OCD
[Music]
I'm gonna put the train here
in the book yes
actually I could bring some of this wood
back home though
[Music]
foreign
okay
that's when people say I'm depressed or
got depression as a joke when they don't
know what it's like
yeah but I guess there's many such cases
so in the end
I also must say that in some cases I do
sometimes feel like okay loosen up
like
you know one can't always be like
careful not to step on anybody's toes at
all there's always somebody's toes to be
stepped on
um so many things to be mindful of and
we can always try but if somebody then
does happen to step on someone's toes
who's already trying though to make an
effort then I think the the stepped on
person could also be trying to
understand that you know hey this person
tried to not step on my toes but they
did okay but I see they're making an
effort so let's not be
who stepped on you know what I mean oh
[Music]
they didn't mean it like that you know
many things are also just like uh
what's the what's the word
um just a saying and then like over the
years it became a saying and lost its
original meaning so it's like hard to
hard to
yeah think of the original meaning
[Music]
which is of course not ideal month
oh
who is to blame for that Society we live
in a society you know
we live in the [\h__\h] society
[Music]
a chicken and egg thing is it a chicken
and egg thing
I don't know about that
foreign
[Music]
why am I doing this now
sorry guys I I can't help myself
I'm gonna have myself right now
this feels good though it feels good
today I am Minecrafting correctly in the
intended way as God wanted me to
Minecraft
bring this home we'll bring this this
home
we'll bring this home
bring this home
bring these home because I don't know
where else to put them
eh
I've corded the creeper gods
crafting and Mining just like our
forefathers as much as the intended yeah
[Music]
it's green here I cannot accept this
this girls here and maybe the Dior ride
could go here right I think that works
wow
[Music]
where was it
yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
I'm shaking
Minecraft Minecraft
[Applause]
colors
of colors
beautiful colors
tools
[Music]
tools tools
tools
[Music]
can be saved I'm lost
ah what's this doing here anyway
let me bring this let me bring this
I bring this
[Music]
foreign
speedrun I'm trying my best here
I know must be hard to look at my
inventory all the time
it's hard for me too
let her cook boys I will be cooking
today what time is it 10 p.m I think
it's time to start cooking some soups
move move
it's like a puzzle game yeah oh maybe
that's why people like Minecraft or this
is aspect of Minecraft maybe it's like a
feeling of puzzling and maybe those
people really enjoy puzzling too and
like Tetris stuff like that
[Music]
what's happening tomorrow uh member
stream right
just asking for my own confirmation
[Music]
we're gonna play tapping lost Epic
and how far are we
I don't think we can finish it tomorrow
but
you know
we'll see how it goes hopefully we'll
get pretty far
but we're starting pretty late so I
don't know no promises
no way I can finish it yes that's so
motivational
no way you can finish it
I'm fine
[Music]
I'm even sorting here now
oh
um
I'm sure this this can still stay what
is bamboo I don't know what to do
you reduce things I'll think about
another time but
um okay
ah wait
[Music]
okay
I put this here I'm just cleaning up now
guys I'm sorry I got so quiet I'm I'm my
brain I was just so empty head empty day
today sometimes you have those days
don't you
[Music]
this is one of those days
perfect day for Minecraft
I guess so but usually I appreciate
Minecraft for giving me a lot of like
space to
um tangent without having to pay much
attention to the game because like
in other games maybe things go wrong
when I
tangent I'm just bad at multitasking
I'm really actually bad at multitasking
[Music]
even when it sounds like I'm
successfully tangenting oftentimes
[Music]
foreign
not tangenting as well as I could when I
would have
an empty
or unoccupied mind
[Music]
everybody's bad at multitasking our
brains literally aren't designed for it
I love that sentiment
I love that
it's very reassuring
[Music]
I'll do something Unthinkable now I'm
sorry guys I'm sorry guys but it really
bothers me how much it sticks out
so what's what's really bad oh this is
what
I have
PTSD from losing shocker boxes don't
leave me
so this doesn't work out
maybe if I put it in the ground though
it can work but you have to orient it oh
okay okay okay okay okay okay
you gave me hope
silence so wait first I place it like
this what if I place it like this
no
um
what sideways
[Music]
a block behind
I'll have to do it from outside
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
beautiful okay I was gonna put like oh
my God
more like yeah of like what is supposed
to be in here but this is like
everything else so
it's kind of all over the place
so I will put like some fancy
weird Building Materials in there how
about that although not that one
[Music]
um
this
news
maybe this
huh
[Music]
obsidian okay
and then there's more space here again
oh actually oh I do have a shulk box in
here already with stone stuff we should
do the same thing with that one then
[Music]
um
maybe here
never like a little more or less but not
necessarily oh that looks kind of cute
that pattern is kind of cute
[Music]
I don't mind that pattern there
shock a butt swirl
yeah but this one will be a different
color but you know this house isn't
supposed to be pretty anyway right so
no
judgmental okay oh I haven't opened up
the stroker box in a long time
um I don't know
it's mostly normal stones in there
good to know
[Music]
um
should I put Basalt in there
we'll just end the Stream
why you gotta why you gotta drag it out
like this Wawa
[Music]
and the Stream
okay okay well
wow okay okay
[Music]
wait
I will I will I will I will I will I
will I will
just let me
um
put the last few things here around ah
what's this ah I broke this oh
hmm okay
fine
it's nice being back in here many many
many memories true you mean this house
yeah
we already sorted this last time this is
me being like trying to sort everything
is not only a today thing it's a recent
thing
more and more my heart screams
that I want to clean out
all this dirt
that is like messing with on my brain
[Music]
to fix everything
okay okay let me just fix the the back
side okay
maybe I'll do this off screen I should
do this off screen it's kind of relaxing
I give you that
[Music]
just a little bit
Maybe
foreign
[Music]
makes me happy okay I'm being Trinidad
freaking Minecraft
no I'm not
[Music]
that's it that's it it is a Super Chat
though reading time we're gonna finish
those super chats hopefully
[Music]
do I have any more fruit candies there
my mom kind of like tried to continue
cleaning my my apartment and then she
went to my office too
found one
[Music]
some fruit candy
just been talking so much and
oh
yesterday I talked so much and then
today I did a lot of recording like two
hours of recording but not um not
singing recording
so I guess it was actually less
straining I think than talking recording
[Music]
okay
jenma is also cleaning and
Chihuahua this card is actually like
recently or a couple
um maybe two or three months ago or so
Jenna made a Discord server just for my
projects because it's just you know we
tried to keep everything in like our
whole life
Discord but then the threads were
overflowing and I guess that motivated
genma to make a server
and there's
a [\h__\h] ton of
[\h__\h] ton of threads in the server now
but yeah at least it's all
in one server
um and now I told her can you arcade
this one so now she's cleaning up
that Discord too but only one there's
too many friends
too many things to do too many ongoing
projects
um
but at least we're keeping things
organized trying to not forget things
ah
Modern Problems require modern solutions
that's right
um
[Music]
you know when when was this
was it yesterday
the day before yesterday I think when I
was I think I told you guys I was
recording things
[Music]
um trying to
because I had the deadline right like I
own the 10 for 11th or so
I was trying to get things
just in time for that extended deadline
because there was extended because I was
you know traveling to America and this
and that
and then I thought I had it but it was
like two or three am and I was about to
go to sleep and then I I found one more
that was like buried because some
friends they just closed itself right so
that's why I didn't find it but I knew
it was urgent and I kind of had it in
the back of my head I just didn't find a
friend anymore
I thought and I was like
[Music]
see
I could
and just go to bed now and do this
tomorrow but no they really need it now
so
I mean not probably not in that very
moment but when they wake up
I'd probably appreciate having it right
away and rather than waiting for me to
wake up so
um so at 3am on that day I did another
recording
um
and jenma really appreciated it though
yeah for getting all my freaking
deadlines done now at least I don't have
I don't think I have anything
[Music]
yeah I also delivered another thing that
was like
um past deadline but not because of me
but because there were delays in link on
their side so I delivered that too today
and another thing super early where
management was like yo kiwawa score what
are they for you will know you will know
right now there's like so many projects
going on
that I'm sure you will see the result of
and the the fruits that it bears
um
one after another
and I think now why should not
have anything left
[Music]
there's one thing but that's not really
urgent yeah
one more thing
but the deadline is kind of far away I
think I think yeah
[Music]
for a moment I thought I didn't have
anything
but I cleaned up nicely
um
[Music]
I'm all caught up not quite but almost
if you close one eye then it looks like
I'm caught up if you close both eyes
then it definitely looks like I'm caught
up because then you're not seeing the
deadlines hmm
OS yeah
[Music]
because both eyes don't exist nothing
exists I am not here I don't exist
either
I do not see it there's no problem if I
do not see it
doesn't exist I don't look at it it
doesn't exist
wouldn't it be wonderful if things just
disappear When You Close Your Eyes
yeah
[Music]
Adam's side out of mine
and leave this mess behind
okay let's go when should we go
[Music]
to my room
it's still fresh wow big wow hello
thank you for watching The Chill
Minecraft stream today I would say
Phoenix Sun was like
good to go now
I can't think of anything like really
important that needs to be done at this
point
all right chat is not refreshing
there you go
I think
like everything is pretty accessible
everything is cleaned up the uh
the important dudes are named
huh
would have added more melon Tomatoes but
it looks way better at least you know
there's there's some guys there you know
[Music]
aren't they working it's functional yeah
we could we could maybe make a couple
more Farmers I know if there's really a
[Music]
um
what's the word another word for need
[Music]
a demand yeah
if there's really a demand for it do you
think they realize a demand for it
um
probably not so we'll leave it like that
[Music]
um oh but wait
if fauna needs a lot of wool I guess
what could have been useful is like Wool
Wool Wool people
but she can make her own right she has
her own like
[Music]
a human Farm
want to put to put signs maybe something
like a directory yeah but I feel like
people will just walk by not see the
signs
unless like I said before if I make them
as big as that sign under the icebridge
maybe but that'll kind of like ruin the
aesthetic maybe unless I guess I could
make it out of like cobbled Blackstone
or something like that again for the
like mining
blacksmith District
yeah I mean yeah
[Music]
ah right in front of the water elevators
oh
does anyone besides me use the water
elevator
because it's like quite the direct
direction to my home
yeah I would think most people fly over
there
I think most people fly though
[Music]
I what what iron Vader
I don't know what you're talking about
I'm good to my people how can you make
fun make fun of how I trained Phoenix
sunny phoenixsonians when there's you
know look at pecora look at fauna
damn and then compare what they do to
what I do it's a paradise in Phoenix
then
take these jokes
foreign
if I did anything wrong the Golems would
hit me
the lava
was an accident
[Music]
it's not my fault
repeat after me
Kiana is not at fault
yada it's not at fault your name
repeat after me
Kiana is not at fault you'll never if
you want this you can add the yone for
effect good effect
[Music]
Kiana is not at fault
you know
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
yay
hello
it's me
thank you for waiting sorry
weird spooky stuff going on hi
hi it's weird I bonked my go XLR
I just moved like a a centimeter by
touching it
and then
go Explorer just let the program goes
like I'm a gag oh my God Panic telling
me like oh this disconnected or
something like that blue
but yeah then
I thought I fixed this because I I still
hear myself in my headphones and I see
the Galaxy are the microphone thing is
like showing me that uh the microphone
is working
but then on OBS it doesn't want to
connect and go exercise like crashing
the the program uh the girls learning
program is crashing and you know they're
having a fight and then you know again
like last time tltk my
my face also stops moving it's like
weird like
spooky
how oops one little one little thing can
mess everything up so much that I have
to restart my PC
um
no the Ghostlight
and it wants me and it wants me to
I'm not turning you guys against me
foreign
now that we had to restart the stream
and my bgm is gone I will use a
different one anyway
two words
go
[Music]
foreign
yesterday let's see
how far did we get
[Music]
we don't I think I know
um
the dancing and singing one and so we
continue with Zelda TI ortike this now
bring up the thumbnail
[Music]
this one
hmm
[Music]
let's go almost caught up it's already
from this week or like okay now it's
Tuesday but you know what I mean
[Music]
thanks for the pinky
oh I see we're back to ARS I watched
your dance over and over again I can't
get enough of it the way you gracefully
dance is so amazing so elegant talented
and cute I shouldn't it shouldn't even
be possible to be this cute and so proud
that would be awesome figure also MD
hype oh yeah my figure is that no I
don't think we even talked about it on
stream yet right
I think yeah wait which one is this one
what's it what's it called
um
what is this one called
pop-up parade yeah
Papa parade figure if you guys want to
get it uh for the people who don't have
an idea what we're talking about maybe
let me show you guys a picture
it was in the works for a long time
my time scrolling through my Twitter
the best way to get it
scroll scroll Scrolls Scrolls ah There
It Is Well that's the
Japanese announcement graphic but
whatever
oh oh apparently yeah the reservation
there's a deadline apparently the 5th of
July
I don't know if you can still get it
afterwards I would assume yeah this is
just like reservation to get earlier or
so I don't know but look it's so bright
so saturated it's beautiful
I look like a Barbie doll
cute
I like the uh gradiation and the like
the hair strands next to my eyes
sounds really smooth
as your birthday oh
so wait uh gura Cali already have Papa
parade figures right am I the third one
or
I don't think I saw Ina's figure and um
did I say almost figure
am I the third one
[Music]
ah the ribbon cute the ribbon was
something that I
added afterwards wasn't even originally
in the design but when I think I told
you guys when it came to creating my 3D
model cookie Papa was like so yeah about
the backside is there anything you know
you you want me to add I'm like can we
add like a ribbon and These Wings
so the the blue wings and the Rhythm
were from me before that it was just I
think completely empty
yeah I thought it would be a nice
addition to also make the backside cuter
and worth looking at
genius right
so if you want as a memoir of our time
together to get this super special
figure
please head over to
the good smile company I think there's
other places to get it too that may be
better depending on from where you're
ordering from right
I've heard oh it depends
I don't know really any details but
Ami Ami oh yeah people have been
praising Ami Ami or otaku mode
because oh figure figure in Germany has
two mm-hmm
is very reliable there you go guys so if
you oh you ordered in a local store wow
okay
if you guys have some issues for some
reason then check out those places
um
yeah thank you so much for the support I
hope I get one too
can you with these figures can you move
the limbs they don't really look like
you can move them is this like a this
type of figure is this just like stuck
in this position
ah okay that'll be a figma which we're
also getting I think right
eventually
so this is stuck in this particular
position but it's very pretty it's still
a pose that Ina Drew
of all of us
she only like Drew like a top body upper
body illustration before that was around
debut time
[Music]
yeah it was modeled after that
illustration yeah yay finally
final finally it took like forever
it took forever
you know Elyria Elyria even dm'd me
about this was like oh my God your
figure is so beautiful I'm like thank
you I know right
hmm
I'm post my poster is so good in this
figure
yeah so wait maybe I should keep it up
oh well
oh wow
[Music]
what a nice figure on my figure I know I
know
[Music]
guys for everybody who already ordered
it yeah meanwhile how do you know
I have my Lego
thank you for one two three red super
chats and one of them is a double holy
[\h__\h] what happened was it a special day
I guess it was my return day but
oh
I did I was trying to find the cool song
emoji and that's happened they kept on
typing was oh no way and the Emoji
searched confused when I couldn't find
the closest
oh man you are too brainwashed
thanks boss now it will always be
croissant in my brain
goes to Bakery can I have a cuazo
[Music]
sorry I'm in a cool song
can I dedicate my last kiss to Blue and
may I also Last Kiss ah because there's
so many
um
okay that sounds like
one of your messages got lost
[Music]
may I also purchased two more kisses one
for gero and one for Evans there was
spreading the glory of kfb every day and
Evan's memes every day with gushing love
for his orange juice
yeah yeah he does all upstanding Jenkins
and finally One More Kiss dedicated to
the rest of the timkins I've seen lots
of prayer circle survival to get better
and lots of patiently waiting supportive
jimkins understanding well as schedule
adjustments as you heal it will love you
but yeah thank you guys so much for
waiting
I felt bad about taking days off but I
also felt happy that you guys were so
understanding and just waited with no
pressure applied to me thank you very
very much yeah it was nice to use them
not stream for a few days too but uh if
only if only I wasn't sick
thank you for waiting everybody and kiss
to Blue
for always making super cute
stuff for me but I'm sorry I didn't go
for the druid
but you know what you could make me like
um for the class I'm doing now the
sorcerers I guess you could make a
headpiece
for my forehead
I just put it on top of my bags maybe
that could work
I don't know
if there's anything else with a
sorceress would wear on her head
typically
besides that maybe a hand with like a
skull yeah or some other fancy
circle thing
yeah
yeah I guess the weapons could be hand
um
of assets yeah
but take your time blue and next time I
don't know if you heard it last time but
just
just a hint
maybe don't make the elbows or the arms
themselves so short
I always feel like when I put them on
the um the proportions are a little bit
off
to like how my arms are
oh
thank you thank you it doesn't matter so
much when I cut it off
um quite a bit
so it's not that big of an issue but
just saying for future things if you
create something
you know
T-Rexes
it would probably work for like
different
characters who have different
proportions but yeah
[\h__\h] you
and then
Twitter shows me
sometimes the tweets that you write
indeed so I see it thank you and Evans
also thank you you crazy chicken so
crazy what's so funny
thank you everybody
and also to all the other chickens who
were waiting for me
it's
thank you guys
for giving me time to rest
I hope I don't get sick again anytime
soon really
I'll try to take better care of myself
I don't want to get sick it's so
frustrating
and I don't know these past months years
when I get sick somehow it's always like
if I get sick I get really sick it's not
just like a sniffle
or a little cough no
why is it always so extreme
why
why you gotta be so extreme all the time
yeah when it hits it hits hard no little
headache no no It's gotta be like really
strong
not enough sun to boost the defenses
yeah I mean I'm very aware of why this
is happening I know that it's like you
know my lifestyle and my work keeps me
at home all the time
makes me weak and then when I do go
outside
I'm like
suddenly confronted with
so many people and germs and all that
uh and then an easy target
for that
suddenly my
my shield my health Shield
is just so weakened from always being
and working inside indoors
yeah yeah clearly the solution is to
navigate through
[Music]
Plains lights also weaken the body quite
a lot
um
I guess so yeah my immune system is just
it's always been good before her life I
swear I would never get sick before
whole life
[Music]
foreign
my body generally just got so much
weaker
from moving less moving my body less
not getting enough vitamins not getting
enough Sun
not getting enough dreams all the time
you know like a baby
that would make me stronger against
germs in general I guess
[Music]
well well
it's not time to return
no no no
I don't know where is Jim the Jim Jim is
at my keyboard
Jim is that keyboard down here I am at
gym right now
and he's working
out his arms so we are working out with
Jim
look at him look at him go
he's hit I'm I will not hit the gym gym
will cry if I hit him but I am at the
gym at least
[Music]
yeah we have Jim at home
just so happens to be called Jim
bamboozly boozly Boo
found a loophole yeah
dumbbells dumbbells will not strengthen
my immune system they may strengthen my
noodle arms but not my immune system
good got him
[Music]
foreign
you crazy babysitter thank you so much
for the huge huge support that's
absolutely insane
you're crazy but I really appreciate it
thank you
hope you're doing well these days Jake
catch monkey dancing
Jim Tracy thank you for a recipe Chad
I've been reborn I now have the infinite
power of a lighter for real though it's
crazy to think I've been in kfb for two
years now so many good times and great
memories can't wait to see what the
future holds and this awesome group love
you both thank you oh I love you too
you're here for such a long time hi Jim
hi Jim I'm not gonna hit you either you
don't want to be hit right wait you're
here at the keyboard right now hi Jim
Tracy it's you wait I never made that
connection
and that was you
you don't need to tell me this for a
Super Chat when you're right there why
don't you tell me directly
shy I guess
thank you Jim Tracy thank you wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
[Music]
there's your keys
oh you guys must be so jealous
[Music]
on the back of his head
burning from jealousy oh no that's just
the the oil
sorry don't misunderstand
uh
thank you
light thank you for the pinky hi Kiana
alurker here and first pinky just wanted
to say that I finally got my first
full-time job I may not be able to catch
the start and the end of streams now but
I will try to catch up with the Vlogs I
can now support you more than before
yeah thank you I I I mean
oh hi Raiders I'm glad you got your job
I wonder what it is I hope you have fun
there I hope they are nice to you your
colleagues I hope you feel comfortable
and happy
and that you can keep the job for a long
time as long as you want at least
um
and yeah thank you for at least trying
to go see the vods I appreciate it very
much
thank you good luck at work
hope it's not too busy not too stressful
yeah don't overwork yourself
always know your limits
you're welcome
[Music]
but you didn't eat it with
um
vanilla sauce did you and you didn't eat
it with Vanilla Ice
so I was like what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
thanks for the memberships
yeah I was like
why when you go through those efforts
why leave it at that why only go halfway
[Music]
we're not at the vanilla sauce and the
Vanilla Ice
that wasn't even that difficult
so as it happened I don't know if you're
here
but I hope you hear this message
it must be conveyed
and then you must retry
do it
for me do it for me
so such a waste it's multi-9
[Music]
or to the pit not the usual room
hey do it for me
yeah okay it's not that wholesome guys
Nathan cartoon Franco's
action thank you
happy belated birthday for Tariq
um
chance 18. wow so young
mad arcade thank you
little l or a I or a boohoo 73 Duncan
a green a green L John Doug
[Music]
um
thank you
big nothing monster man thank you for
the rest of the chat hi thank you for
always being cute sweet silly and great
to us
we love you very much you make Beethoven
feel special it's been a blessing to
watch your journey so far thank you for
letting us be a part of it
team
thank you for following me on the
journey even though it's a long journey
hopefully it's a long journey
but you you are here by my side and that
makes it
a fun Journey
thank you so much for supporting me and
you know there's so many YouTubers out
there you choose me
you choose me
thank you for that
Richard Gideon certainly Andrew Martinez
lunchbox
[Music]
please feel free to take as much break
as you need anytime you need attention
you're being sick doesn't even count as
taking a break I think so too you still
should take a break and go to the spa I
really hope you will be back to 100 to
help you soon love you thank you I'm
thinking of going to a massage tomorrow
before the stream no wait I have a
during the day I mean I guess I could do
it after I do have a meeting tomorrow I
think
oh yeah
was I supposed to prepare something for
that because I am
I have a meeting with a financial
advisor remember last year when I was
trying to
hook up with a financial advice as in I
was trying to get something going I
don't know if I told you guys but then I
gave up on her because she was kind of
really annoying
um and then recently
um my friend recommended me in their
financial advisor
uh because my friend was very worried
about me
in many ways and then yeah I I was like
yeah yeah
[Music]
I'm worried about me too
yeah
and this financial advisor even said he
could help me with I actually no he even
I think he is like decent because he
told me I shouldn't
that's like better not unless I'm really
prepared for it uh try to buy an
apartment and rent it out
which I just saw as an option you know
maybe I could do that as like a passive
income maybe in the future after whole
life I don't know
um just got this idea you know
and yeah he said maybe that's not so
good because
it's not as easy as it sounds and it's
kind of a hassle and I said oh but I can
hire someone no I thought you could hire
people who take care of it and he said
yeah but then you know in the end you're
losing more money to them I'm like yeah
I thought it's not that much oh well
anyway so he kind of told me
that's not the best idea but he he said
he could help me
um
you know with the plan of purchasing a
house slash apartment
for myself
um
[Music]
because I
want to do that
I'm wasting so much money on my current
apartment
and it makes no sense
and I want a garden
no probably not a lake house probably
not
probably not
unfortunately but it's okay
the thing is I'd probably
I don't know maybe in the future for now
something less
uh aspiring I don't know
and then I could still later sell
whatever I have and then and then
you know
um
but he wants me to buy some
dogs I think
and then just let them run for 20 30
years is what he said
he said that is usually a very safe
investment
um yeah
stop
stop no he really believes in that so
okay I'm like okay
sure
stocks oh I should invest in a whole
life
it's in a whole life
oh
is that illegal
yeah I can no
no I don't know it's just a joke anyway
wouldn't do it oh polka said she's not
allowed to legally really
oh really
you can I'm an Insider
see that's what I thought that must be
there must be a reason why that's
probably illegal
um
okay no stunks
for whole life
depends on the country
[Music]
you're part of the End branch that's not
inside
yeah who knows how inside I really am
well anyway let's not talk about that
just say I have a meeting tomorrow for
that maybe afterwards I can take a
massage
[Music]
would be nice
try
don't know how long the meeting is
though
hmm
I already talked to him once so this is
the second one
we're just getting things started now
hmm
the spa well massage to me is already
like like a mini spa massage itself is
the Highlight for me at a spa anyway
it's the main thing the main event
just when I came back from America I was
like in excruciating pain so I went to a
massage immediately
and it's been a week now
and well
I am still in pain
it's maybe 10 less excruciating
than it was when I came back from
America
so very [\h__\h] painful
painful so
go to my awesome skin
squishinating
that's what I said that's what I said
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
what kind of massage you like oh I've
tried so many different ones already
um I think my to go massage is kind of
the Thai massage
because I like how sometimes they will
stretch your body a bit and also at the
end they always crack
[Music]
because
um
sometimes massages when I when I have a
Thai massage in Japan it's always with
clothes
but when I get a Thai massage here it's
always of oil so Nikki Nikki
and so when you turn around
obviously they will pull the towel on
you right when you were lady yeah oh
okay but then at the end so you start
with your bag then you turn around and
then at the end they make you sit up to
then like you know have your hands
behind your head and then they like pull
you back and crack crack and then turn
you turn you and you know they do all
the stuff while you're sitting with
cross legs
and the thing is when when my hands are
up there and she's like turning and
twisting me
obviously the towel is gonna fall down
and I'm like exposed but I'm trying to
not think about it because I'm trying to
relax and the ladies behind me anyway
and well she's probably seen a lot of
boobies in their life
oh yeah
oh dear oh dear
[Music]
I don't want to
look like that kind of
um
squeaky
annoying
lady you know it has a Cassie but um
let's hope she doesn't look because
she's behind me
only red if you make it weird yeah
that's what I'm thinking
yeah so Thai massage and I had like
sport massage like once or twice in my
life that was pretty good and I had like
one or two deep tissue massage
oftentimes those massages they're not on
the menu where I go to so I don't get
them much but
[Music]
um
deep tissue massages like
[Music]
nice
oh I feel like I would say only do deep
tissue on my back and then the rest of
my body normally plays because like
especially my noodle arms there's
so sensitive I noticed when I tell them
to go strong on my back and I
specifically say on my back and my
shoulders they apply the same strength
elsewhere too though and that's [\h__\h]
hurts
[Music]
um
and I try to say it but then when I say
that then they go weaker overall my
whole body don't have to say again okay
but here's stronger again please and the
back and forth is just so annoying so
most of the time I try to um just say
nothing and wait it out wait through the
pain
um
[Music]
time to get buff
the answer is the gym gym is the answer
Jim do you have the answer he says no
or maybe I should have gym
massage me
[Music]
just massaging my shoulder now
okay next to the voice
yeah honestly you have no technique Jim
you don't have a future in the massage
uh place sorry
he's just like slapping it that doesn't
work
anyway thank you
ah
I'll go get a massage tomorrow Crow's
Duncan Mountain thanks with a pinky
welcome back to Angel really enjoyed
older I'm a Tony we got yeah I think it
was time to catch up on some amatory
I'm a totally
haven't had amatory in a while so I
think it's good to be registered in a in
a really extra big doses right
quite a few game announcements lately
did you see that a lot of the Rings
returned to Moria game trailer they even
got game lead to voices what what and
for the whole story tomorrow right so
this is not the uh Golem one right
this is a different one right
okay interesting
[Music]
is there a release date
3D Fortress defense game
[Music]
I would just like to have an RPG game
but okay
[Music]
good for cop
okay
um
ones are pretty right
phone Clips are so funny go check them
out and send them to me guys on Twitter
fall 2023 oh okay
it's pretty soon that's nice okay
I'll look into it when the time comes I
should look into it earlier and ask for
permission already
oh you were not a one-time only thing
huh thank you spanking hand thank you
for the Pinkie Pie
mom come home
oh you know in the break when I was
restarting my PC guess who came by
to
yeah run into my room meowingly and then
flop on the carpet right next to me
and expect belly rubs smooth very new
yeah
movie TV
[Music]
so demanding she thought it was over not
yet
not quite almost Brandon Duncan cast
from Five Finger for the pinky hello boy
have a birthday earlier this week uh wow
27 what an unremarkable number
anyway I'd like to recommend my 300 plus
hour addiction game that is satisfactory
it's really well designed and I think
you could enjoy it too
satisfactory
um
oh no wait of course I have this thing
with Yahoo search again and I've been
too lazy to fix it
uh satisfactory
ah upcoming Factory upcoming this is
upcoming on YouTube but on YouTube on
Google but it's been released since
2019.
Factory simulation getting created by
Swedish video game developer first it is
a free first person open world
exploration and Factory building them
[Music]
that sounds indeed like a game where you
can put a lot of time into
well
oh
Early Access it's almost it's not
what is that 2019 release date then
[Music]
how do you have printed hours on an
early access game
whoa
[Music]
Nina did crazy long streams too whoa
oh wow seems addicting them
[Music]
I don't know it looks like fun
but I don't know if I want to play
oh I need a little bit more
push that well thanks for the
recommendation though
I hope you enjoyed your birthday
congratulations that's more important
congratulations please stay healthy and
happy take care of yourself
and you're getting closer to 30 so oh uh
good luck uh and not becoming depressed
I guess
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah yeah
no you still got time
you still got time
so got three years that's that's a lot
of time
make the best out of it
um
[Music]
fruit is nothing for men oh yeah
actually Freddie is a good age for men
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah
I would agree with that
Fred Panthers
[Music]
oh you learned from me
oh thank you I've actually seen a video
where
somebody was using Dazzle fruit in the
underground in totk against anything you
can literally use basil fruit against
anything in the underground
life hack
that's where you should be using all
your Dazzle fruits at
it's like an insta kill for all
underground enemies basically have fun
gdaction
s
and Liz thank you for the red super chat
from New Zealand thank you for the
streams you don't need to worry when you
take a break once in a while and we know
you're working hard
thank you
that is a relief when you say that thank
you very much I appreciate it thank you
Sharon for watching and supporting and
having my back
could you while you're having my back
could you like
you know with your thumb like push push
right in there yeah yeah yeah right
behind the yeah that's the spot thank
you thank you could you go like one
centimeter down
thanks thanks oh yeah and now like in a
circular motion thank you thank you
that's amazing can you do that on the
other side too
thanks thank you so much endless
thank you wow
I appreciate that
man this is a Wendy's
is it no it's a kfp
and in kfp you do what I say so
you said we don't have thumbs well maybe
you have elbows
massage people use their elbows a lot
really [\h__\h] good
it's really good
thank you endless huh
I think you have something that like
resembles an elbow at least no the wings
Bend so
I would think
[Music]
what
yeah
something like an elbow
I could massage you but it might tickle
oh yeah that sounds ticklish
Evans
[Music]
that's on the tutk superchandise
and you know what I am
cheeky
cheeky little
chicken no Phoenix
I'll end it there
because I'm tired I make food now I'll
see what's in my hello beep box
beatbox
[Music]
but
um
[Music]
did I do the dishes
we'll see we'll see
thank you guys for watching I'll see you
tomorrow
[Music]
we'll be playing
lost epic continuing last epic tomorrow
so I'll see you there in the evening
good night everybody have a good rest
thanks for watching today in German we
say
I'll be dancing
now endless could you go come back to my
back and you know have my back a little
bit more bags
[Music]
bye
foreign
[Music]