[Music]
T
yeay
What a great sound! Welcome to Arisaba.
Wow!
This building is super cool.
Thank you everyone for your hard work. Wait,
did your seniors build this? Yes, it's all Jor
Ade.  This is so cool that they made it,
and it's a real building,
and it's so real, and there's this building, too, and
there's this scary zombie thing, and I can
see a little bit of a zombie that I didn't hear. Where is this?
Yes, there is a dog named Borobururu who
has this building.It's from Indonesia.Oh, it
's an amazing famous shield.Oh, it's a famous building.Oh
yeah, it's one after another.Oh,
this is dangerous.Okay, let's
climb up.  Yes,
[Music]
Oh, wow, that's amazing. Looks
beautiful. Looks like Apo-chan is already inside. I see.
I guess she's been waiting. She has an amazing jump. She can
fly so high. It looks like she's using a lot of buffs.
Wow, here.  Oh, and
um, here's a quiz. Okay, I wonder if this is Kanade-chan. Why is this
red and white? I
understand.
Eori-senpai's colors are very similar, but that's
not it. No, Kokki, etc. This
is Indonesia's flag color, oh
yeah.  Yoneori-senpai was holding it in his hand,
so yeah,
yeah, I see. Let's go in. Well, I can almost see my senior's name.
Not from there, but from below. It's
dangerous, so I understand it's from below. It's
dangerous from there,
okay?  Take care and be careful Oh, wow,
what's this?
Hmm, what did you do now? Well, uh, this is Indonesian magic.
Wow, that's
amazing. So get off here,
oh
hello.
[Music]
Maga
[Music.  ]
Where is Akoba-chan here? Oh wow, it's
over there. It's so big and spacious.
Everyone did their best.
Amo ba
kana
[Music]
Eh,
boi, boi, boi, me
[Music] Go, go,
OK,
havejustJust
as-guy
[Music]
Oh yeah, yeah yeah  Yeah, I'm going to be the director today.
Oh, I'm fine with the brief here. Oh,
well, today, there's 5 mini-games.
At first, it's called Treasure Hunt,
but I haven't done that yet.
[Music]
No, no, but for now, the rules for Resin
are to look for treasure. Oh,
some seniors do it.
[Music]
Do it outside of Bobble, not inside Bobble.
No, no, yes.
[Music]
Yes, that's all.
Yes, that's right.
Regi Hunt.  I'm going to do it tomorrow, so I'm going to do it tomorrow,
and I'm going to
go ahead and read the rules,
and
then I'm going to say Hae and
Sans.
Well, each pair will be on stage to
show their presence.
Yes, all the
talent will have to learn a few simple initial numbers beforehand. It's so
easy!  Is it easy or doesn't matter
? Yes, it's okay. Teams will win
emeralds based on how well they follow the instructions.
Oh, okay.
Ok.
Tabo Japanese is okay.
So, um, English, Indonesian, etc.
I need to explain,
wow, everything is fine, no, yes,
no, no, I'm a genius. Yes, it
's no problem, hey, I don't have any questions.
Yes, it's okay, it's okay.
Genius TE
[Music]
Indonesia, uh, genius, genius, no, no, no,
no, no, Tigger.
Eretz
go Indonesian
da tension
Take hai atigai iiakuseka ee ya kai
ii sanka sanka ee anji
ji ji
niji stop, stop, stop, stop te yep
yep yep yep I want to
practice hard already I want to do it I want to
follow you here  Sokaji-
chan, stand here okay Kobo
Stand yes, I brought a cheat sheet
soBofyouhavetogo
THthesamecomm uh,
please listen to the same command okay yes, there
are 3 stages let's do it while watching this
yes yes yes
yes yes I
also memorized the words.
[Music]
What is it?
What's going on
? Do you remember?
[Music]
joh
[Music] I
'll give you the command
startwiththefirstcomok
O doitafterIKadaUm Please
do it after the countdown OK OK
OK OK
So, Maju
Saka 3
Towa
Maju
Boro
But is this a sign?
Yes, I
[Music] I
guess I can't move unless I say something
[Music]
Real
G
simonimasu
[Music]
Let's turn it already
[Music]  No,
no, no, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, move, don't worry about it, I
want it.
[Music]
Yeah, are you okay?
Even the first command is questionable, the keyboard ah,
yeah,
yeah, yeah, it's the next command, yeah, yeah, uhm.
Please go back to the first place. I see, yes, the first place is
not the first place. Well, if you can do it, the
other spaces are fine.
That's fine.
[Music] The
next one will also be difficult.
Please leave
it to me Oh, listen, Ronpa Gakari is three Tsuwahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  Oh, I understand.
Well, it was 3. I can
go.
Oh, and no hints.
Command Jonko Doa Kaswa
[Music]
Yay, nice,
nice, ya,
and uhm, it's stage 2. Let's do stage 2.
Let's go men, let's
go men. Okay, Jinko Ruaka Boku.
Yes, please listen to me,
Jonko
[Music]
Three
Tsuwa
ga
Omaka
[Music] I'm
sorry, I made a mistake. I
made a mistake.  [
Music]
[Music]
What's
up? [Music]
Oh, I can hear you.
[Music]
It's no good. I'm sorry. Do you
have any questions? It's
okay.
It's okay.  Yes,
no, the next mini-game is a bit difficult,
but please follow me
What's the next game? What's the next game? Hey,
what, what, this, this,
this, this is so big, this is so big.
Hey, what's this?
So what is this?
It's Fightin' Well, it looks like Fightin. Yeah yeah [Music] Yeah, this is the one that changes the color. [Music] Well, I'll explain the rules. [Music] Yeah, this is a game called Ron. Yes, the team is Uruka.  It
consists of a foreman.
Yes, the foreman is on the floor with colorful wool, and the
full cutter cuts off the wool from the top at the limit.
Yes, the wool cutter cuts off the wool from the top. The
perman must step on the sucked hole in the team's color.  You
can also drop your opponent's Aman into the world by destroying it.
[Music] It's going to be
a little tough without a partner, so I
'll participate.
[Music]
Leave it to me, Senpai.
Leave it to me,
paok.  Let's play, then Foreman
stays and the color of the chim is more and one more chim
wins.
Yeah
, I understand, this is yes. If I drop it, I lose? Well, this is, yes, this is the upper floor,
and this is.  LOWER FLOOR LOWER FLOOR
Yeah, let's do it. It's
a little hard to explain, but let's do it. Let's play a
game. Either way, let's do it.
[Music]  There
's Shia here.
[Music]
Scissors, yeah, yeah, the body's gotta get the block, uh,
when it's a forman, it's
okay to bring the block, okay,
but right now, yeah, yeah, well, I don't need it,
here.  I'll do my
best
[Music] I
'll drop Ogo-senpai. It's no good.
Do your best, Senpai. Do your best. I'm
sure the sky can destroy the enemy's blocks,
but I feel like Senpai was only able to destroy the white ones.
[Music]  ]
puur
[Music]
PUDIA
[Music] I was
wondering if it's okay. You can't
just use Chim. That
's
right.
And
if A-chan falls, Tim
loses, so make sure he doesn't fall.
[Music] [
Music]
[  [Music]
Why are you holding a Ha in both hands?
Oh, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it. Oh yeah, that's right, and Kanade-chan, Kanade-chan,
press F1, let's move F1. Yeah,
it's
difficult.  What's going to happen? I ah, I'm going to
do this here. I see. I'm going to
do it so you can't see it. Okay, Okay. Easy. Let's
do this. It's upside down.
[Music]
What
happened? Team
Kill
Fufu.
[Music]
[Music] I'm so
excited that I won the combo with my nose.  [
Music]
knowyou
[Music]
Oh, uh, Ka to
Boswitch Okay have
the
[Music]
Oh, where
takeAndHoldItLikeme
HoldIt
[Music]
inak
It doesn't have to be FF.
Okay, it's starting
, it's starting, it's starting!
[Music]
[Music] It's
scary, it's
scary, it's scary.
RedI thinkwe do that. Yeah, that's
nice. [Music] [Music] Oh from Bom28for YELL. 13 17 19 20Ithinkwehave24on.  There
are 3 people on the top and 3 on the bottom.
Well, actually, there are 6 people on the top, 6 people on the bottom. No, no,
all of them are 6 on the top, 6 on the bottom, and 6 of them,
so there will be 12 people participating.  Yes, I
see, that sounds difficult.
[Music]
Oi,
Chichimasu,
Ah,
this scissor
is fine. Have you put the scissors back? Okay,
okay, go ahead, play the next game. You're not a kid, you're a
kid. Yeah,
you're a kid, you're a mallet. Go, you're
amazing.
Bed.  Please touch me
[Music]
Okay, after this, I'll play
chess with you and move your luggage.
[Music] It's almost all
in there
.
[Music]
Okay,
ok, I'll put in as much as I can, and I don't
have any weapons. [Music
]
[Music] Okay, but before that, let's try to see if we can use the group voice Yes, I know how to use it.  It
's ready, I'm not downloading a new one.
No, no, no, it
's the same thing. Yes, take it.
[Music] Is
this it? Yes, press B.
Yes, and ah, I
see.
[Music]
Create a password.  Are
you giving it to me? Hey, there's something in it. What's this? It's all
VC and
this. Oh, it's so
cool. Ah, that's right, this is Orbi, and it's
me. But, uh, your
group is like that too.
[Music]
Yeah, I
understand.
Understand
[Music]
me
wantneedknow
somethingLetmeknowi
iwantTRANSforImake
youfeellikenot
sayingsaying
WellIwouldlove
Oh please, thank
you, I'm going to join a
group chat with my partner from my team.  I
have to make one,
but I think Kubo-chan probably knows how to do it,
so it's not that difficult. So,
for now, I
'll explain the rules of Maze Fight. Yes,
Ako,
Mefa
, Patty. Well, the Maze Fight team is a
fighter and a navigator.  The
navigator guides the fighters through a maze that changes upwards by one size. The
navigator's mission is to
help the fighters defeat the opposing fighters.
Okay, so the point is, the fighter is
important. If the fighter dies, it
's the end of the team.
But if the navigator dies, well, I
can't help you, but the team
is still okay.
Are you okay? Are you okay? Do you have any questions?  It
's a drumstick
[Music] It looks like it's going to be
tough.
Yeah has
[Music]
helphashelp
the
FIGHTERTHE
[Music]
TEINtheTESAthenavig
Help
[Music]
theDieThe
Aerun
[Music]
NavigatorITU
Navigator
yesanDIABIG
[Music] It's okay, it's okay [Music]
[Music] [Music]
Oh, if you're really in it, uh, please bring me a sword.What
is Sugi?  It
's a lot of pressure because it adds up to the overall value of the event.
Wow, that's right. It's okay. I can go. Yes, I can fight. Yes, I can go. Yes, I can go. Thank you.
Yes, Kanade-chan, what is this? This is the last
game, and up until this point
in the game, I
can earn those emeralds.  So I used the
emeralds I earned to bring back that sword for this battle.I
see, if I did
n't have that many emeralds, I think all I could do was use those small fry.
Can I buy diamonds? Yes, I
can buy diamonds. If Deka-chan is
going to be that navigator, then yes, it's already
been decided.
That weapon. This is the
only weapon I have. If my senior who has no choice but dies, I won't try my best. If she doesn't, then
okay, okay, Ish.
Well,
yeah, you have to get rich first.Okay,
please bring me the oboe.Good job,
just the fighter.Good
luck.I don't have that equipment for Leatherite.Sorry, I
forgot.  This is here, this is here, please
put it away. Throw
this away and put it on.
[Music]
Alright, there's no place to put it in.
Garbage,
garbage, trash. Is it okay
now? It's okay, it's okay. So, let's go
here.
Oh, here,
oh, wow, this is the navigator's place. Ice cream, and this is the food Kobo. Let's
go to the locomotive. Wow will from ah, it's moving down here. Oh, I see. Oh, oh. Let's move on to the group chat.
[Music]
Oh, thank you very much.
Thank you. Let's step
out and make room. I'll
wait.
[Music]
I'm normal. Eori-
senpai is here. I can't hear you, Senpai. Is it okay to attack from here? He's a
fighter,
kefa, ah,
ah, punch,
fight.  I don't know, hey
, this means I'm going in. Let's go let's go
[Music]
Leg Go Cabo
Cabo
[Music]
Ohhh
[Laughter]
[Music]
Leg Go, you can't leave this place.  Oh, I can't guess
from here, can't I go
?
Eddie
, no, no, oh, okay, okay,
please, please, okay, please, yes, I
see.  Damn it's not sweet
Waaah Purple Papa Poor Ori-senpai Pupu
Ori-senpai, it's so close, so close I
see, yes, yes Yes See Wasa
fight, fight, go go go go
go Chikushi, attack you
Demon
Maji Murray Let
's
[Music]
Go Mechaya It's stabbing me  What is
this? You, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you.
I
oh oh
kochiko ssu uh ah there
's no sword uh this this a
[Music]
Where is it
Howthe
for
ah how im
Kiki oh oh thank you oh yes ah
aloo Okay yes thank you yes thank you No's
food food rice food this food
wait a minute  The
food is here, here, here, here,
okay, this is a fighter, I've got some food, roti roti roti is
here.
]
Lady, why don't we go this way? Oh,
pink purpo, oh,
lady, lady,
let's go, F and luck, F1F, wait a minute,
wait a minute,
F1, I ca
n't see this.
Now,
okay, oh, oh, Ettri is pink, pink,
pink.  It
hurts, painful and do my best to do my best
[Applause] It's so
hard that it
's okay. It's
okay.  Yes,
yes, I understand Yes, it's a difficult fighter. It's
difficult.
[Music]
Hey, Otsu.
Ah, even though it was a difficult fighter, you were good. You were also good at Monkey.
Yay,
PR. I'm
sorry. It's
okay. Jou
[Music]
Cute  No, it's okay, it's okay
[Music] Oh, let's put it back here. Alright, let's play another game. [Music]
Okay, Ka-chan. Did you notice that I was
aiming at Ka-chan because she wouldn't come out of the door? I
was aiming at her.  I
just realized that this is called spawn camping.
Spawn camping.
Yeah, that was good.
[Music]
thisone
WORKSyougivethemA
Word and They just try to as fast as possible
like one of them
have
[Music] Just
put this back.
Anything's fine.  Okay color,
pink, red
one
[Music]
Stick 2 Stereo
Otoh,
where are you? They've even made an amazing floor
design. It's
amazing, it's really amazing, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's
going, follow me, okay,
flow.  Flow
Flow
[Music]
Mua Moona
Senpai Mu
Kaisei Hello
[Music] It
's easy Yeah Yeah Gamma
Yay one of the pair is given the name of the stage
Well they name the stage within a minute
Another player tries to guess what it is.
Oh, pairs are awarded emeralds based on the times. I
see.
[Music]
Who makes it first?
Oh, I can't hear you
.  [Music]
Dako Etka-chan Yes, we're here. Yeah, what should we make? Cat, make it. Cat. Okay, cat. I-Sue. Leave it to me here. Yeah, okay. On the floor, on top, whatever. Okay, okay.
[Music]  ]
ady
Su
[Music]
2Apple
Bunny
[Applause] I
got it from Bunny
because it has something like ears
Which cat is it?
[Music] I
want to make it again.  I want to make it.Okay, let's
meet.Oh, I broke this.I
picked this up on the floor.Thank
you, thank you, I bought it for you.So,
what is wine wine or wine?Um,
this is this.This is like that grass.That's
right.  That's right, wine,
wine,
wine, okay, okay, wine vine tree,
hey, let's go, come on, let's
go, come on, do your best, come on, do your best, that's what I said.
E
forSWORD
SWORDohmygod
TallWhatisthis
VitaminCspoonletgo
hormonestrent
[Music]
Go
[Music]  Let's
go here and see,
let's go, uh, kana
[Music] I wonder if
Kirao can say it in English
[Music]
Oh, wait, wait, I can't mute it,
let's go
[Music] I ca
n't hear you with this, no,
anti-funden  What's that?
Daehun Ah, let's buy mute, I see. Let's
buy mute,
let's go. Okay, that means unmuting.
Okay, ok, yeah, ok, get
ready. I'm going to mess up here. Okay, get ready.
Okay.
[Music]
321 I guess that's it. Ao,
what should we do?  Oh, I'm also
looking at Christmas,
Reno Arrow, this is a crane fly, Erotic
Ah, Pispics, I
said I got it from Kuspi Chaku-chan,
oh,
sorry, it's okay, I think the answer could probably
be in Japanese, though
[Music]  ]
Hey
, it's okay, it's okay
. Thank you. And Lulu has
n't decided yet, so please believe me.
Yes, there may be changes, but it's
mostly like this.
Thank you, I
understand. It's easy. That's all.  That's it, it's already
over. Or do you still
want to practice?
KAN
[Music]
Thank you for leaving it to me. Thank you for today's practice.
Thank you, teacher. Yes.
Adore
[Applause]
Senkyu It's
okay. It's okay. It's okay. We're okay.
Yes, let's win, senpai, let's do it, yes, yes,
it's okay, ojou.
[Music]
[Music] I'm
No. 1,
so
[Music]
Ooh, yeah
[Music] Good luck, of
course, of course,
of course, of course, what's
up
[Music]
Oh,
oh, oh, here's
what's going
on?
Shaleo is now a teacher, Mr. Sensei,
yes, thank you. Then yes, do you remember this Kirikamaru?
No, then this is your time.
Ah
[Music]
Remember, okay,
yes. Ah, then look at this. Yes, this is Jinko.
Jinko. Yes, this is Jinko.  It's like Jinko's name
Geo Yes, I get it Okay
Ronba Ronba
Ronbajika
[Music]
Chandeu
[Music] It's
hard
[Music]
Meao
justo
Ronparonpa
Jinpokopokopokopokokorekopo Popopo
Oronpa
Ronpa Jinku Jinkopo
Popopopo Okay no no uh Larry
Rally Rally Rally Rally Rally Run away O
Rally run away Isee
from What do I have to run away from
Run
[Music]
Nora
for What is it?
Eh, Rally is Run
Run Run Lao Control Run Run Oh yeah Oh
Oran
Running Rally is easy Rally  Rally
ok oh ok keron paropa chinko chiko ko
Rari
Okay is aaah [Music] Ah, I
understand.  Oh, one time, one time, that's right.
Genius Genius Saka Karikari is a clam. Oh yes.
Luaka, two times, two times. Oh, then the clue is three times.
Shirimakari is five times.
Yeah, it's four times.
[Music] It's
four times. Nice, nice, nice.  I know,
yeah, yeah
[Music]
Taifutai, middle
school Joe, yeah, yeah, no, it's not like that.
Ji is 7.
77 I don't know,
off to 5, up to 5. Eda, ya, ya,
jinko, jinko,
ochinka, ropa,
ropapo, rally, rally, rally, yeah.  Oh
Lampadore
Kari
Ronpa Door
Kari Yes
Ronpa No Jump Twice Almost Yes What's
ok
[Music]
Well it's ok it's throat I'm
sure it's still lilin but it's ok yo
wind it
's not okay it's okay thank you it's not cough it's
ok adobo
[Music]
[Music] I
went to learn quickly
[Music]
Oh
DIE no no
[Music]
Good
[Music] I
hope your thighs heal. Take
a break.
[Music] Please take a break. [Music]
Oh, wait a minute.
Ekika na dopodo talent
saijin
rima rima
[Music]
Oh, genius, genius, oh, genius, genius,
then I'm
already a genius, I'm good at it.
Left
OK, OK for Mio Okay,
different different right left.
Seriously, the back of the giona
is left, left, right, back, back, left,
left, back, back, back, back,
kirikirimagindle dolf
Okeokae Yeah, I remembered I
remembered  Kanan
Kanan
kiiuuURUROkOkRonparabako Rari
Rally yes ok genius
genius ok Nice teach here here here here oh
uh practice practice ok oh uh
maju sakari seriously
sasakari
sasaka
this is
it yes
old saka yes
npae
o
[music]
Wow
ok seriously  Sapoko
[Music]
Maji Maji
Saka Podoa Nice I
did it Sleep Suri Suri
Sleepi Where are you going to sleep
[Music]
Where's the bed
Daaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Lepareparepa, lepareparepa
Lepa Lepare
ah throw
[Music]
Throwing Rampa Rampa Yes
Derepa
[Music]
Oh yes this is Lepa
Get used to it [Music] Losing
streak
[Music] Looks
like it's going to be a series of losses
Hijapa I'm going to
take it off I'll take it off I'll take it off I'll
throw it to the right  It's like a head,
easy to remember
Yes, it's easy to remember Yes, it's right. It's definitely a hatakiri. The one
on the left is pointing. Haa
, the more you turn on the left, the
more you
turn.
[Music] Oh no, no, no, no,
no [Music] What's the point?
Wait,
hey, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, Burakan-o,
wait a minute, wait a minute,
wait a minute, Kirio, then cut it to the left, right? [
Music]
Okay, okay ha
[Music]
Here, uh,
Merawana,
Merawana Merawanamera  Ah,
isn't there a red block there
? Yes, I
say "Waname Mera", and then I think I have to go back to that red block.
Oh, I see, that's right. Yeah, ok, it's a bad color. The
color Mera is red, yeah, yeah.
Waron Merawan, ok,
oh.  I didn't hear that.
Thank you
. I didn't tell you. Don't tell me. Don't tell me. Just
here. Just here. Just here.
Nice, nice.
Nice. After it's over. After we're done, we'll practice before the actual performance. Thanks for the cue.  Thank you, now I don't
have to cheat anymore.
Haribachi, Yabachiri
[Music]
[Music] I
went seriously
Koko and Pukupukukia Senpai Pukupuku
Pukupuku Pokopokopukupuku
Pukupuku and Bokoboko are similar, are
n't they?  Tell me, I
've taught you [ __ ], you're a genius
. You're so talented. Okay, okay,
then.
After this
MayIwillrest.
I
have a sore throat. SLEtime. My
sleep time.
No, please take a break. Thank you for your rest. Louis.
No.
[Music]
Thank you.  I made it
Kanakana Aoh I see
[Music]
Naka
Titi-
o I guess I should call you Bokoboko-chan
Bokoboko Boko-chan Bokobobo
Boko I'm scared
Bokobokobokobokobokoboko-chan
[Music]
Thank you, yes, are you happy?
Pokopoko Chanbokoboko-senpai  Bokoboko Senpai Bokoboko
I often call Kobobo Bokobo
Abokoboe Bokobobokobo There's a synergy in this So the sense
is similar Teru Bokobo Poko Poko Poko Poko Senpai Pok Poku Senior Senpai Kira
Senpai La Senpai Ae
Wow Sparkle Aa Kira Kira Ara Ara Senpai Ara Ara
Senpai Ara Ara No  Ah, it's
okay with Nono Wow Wawa. Wawawa
Wawama Kiara has become Kiara and Kiwa
has become a Wow.
Omai Goto
Rishi
[Music]
Kakashi
Yeah, it's
not Aashi, it's not Rishi Sorishi
Thank you, thank you,
Ebo Bobo Gotoo, do I
have to be here when the game starts?
Tomorrow, I'll be honest, I don't know, but I'll
be fine.  I understand. Thank you very much. It was fun.
Baba, let's do our best.
Baba thanyouBye
[Music]
[Applause]
ByeHV
[Music]