[Music]
n
ky ky hello I have a
headache I had it even before coming to
my computer so let me take cuz this is
going to be a long stream let me take
a uh pink color oh I still have some
from my injury
from my neck
injury
remember yeah I I I have a lot of pain
killers left from
that okay let's let's hope let's hope it
works
okay so good good morning everyone good
[Music]
evening I feel like I'm slowly turning
into Japanese life member by forcing
myself to stream when I'm not feeling
well but it's okay it's not that bad
it's just a tiny headache so
whatever it's just a headache it's just
a headache that will probably go away
with the pink color and then I'm fine I
don't know I've just been having
headaches a lot these
days uh hm
yeah uh no I think I have to wait a
second ah but ah I want to take my pants
off but I can't
because the mailman is about to come
so let's suffer a little bit uh while
wearing
pants I don't know I just can't stream
with uh pants on because it's just too
hot
man looking forward to Winter cuz I want
to be cfy you know I like I like the
comfiness of pajama pants but uh I don't
know it's just too hot and I I it's it's
not even that hot in my room it's so
weird because
um I uh I had the window open for the
whole night and a lot of cool air should
have come in uh look at these games by
the way yo never actually really played
Monster Hunter rise oh Okami oh yeah I
have Okami on
here this one I want to play sometime
[Music]
too okay well today we're doing
zala now my room like the temperature in
my room is not like that high it's like
decent
decent but for some reason I want the
moment I sit down in front of my PC with
my pajama pants oh my God
what uh I feel I don't know weirdly
overheated and my head hurts what's
going on thank you for renewing your
membership
boo uh again crispy sound what the hell
is the matter with this um cter card
uh sound
capture can I explain something to you I
have this Elgato capture card pretty old
one
hd60s and um shut up shut
up and uh uh so normally like it they
there like when I installed that you
have you have to open the game capture
window to look at right yeah right now
that reminds me I'm looking at OBS right
now uh the game capture window so on the
game capture window you can also like
change the the volume of the audio and
all that uh why is this window so small
there you go and uh yeah so then there's
another like I guess I installed it
together but there's another thing uh
which is the the sound capture there's a
sound capture window that comes I guess
when you install all
uh the the program and so when the sound
gets crisp like normally you don't have
to have that open you only need to have
the game capture thingy open you don't
have to have the sound capture thingy
open but when I have the game capture
thingy open at some point sometimes the
sound will get like really really crispy
as you might have noticed before and uh
so I open the sound capture window and
then in the sound capture window there's
like a few options like
uh uh wait where where did it go where
did it go sound
capture there there it is so there's
some some options you can do like uh
music or PC gaming or team chat or
off and when I switch between those the
the chrisen as usually gets fixed but
let's say I switch from off to PC gaming
it gets fixed but the then later on for
some reason sometimes it turn like the
the crispiness happens again so I switch
back from PC gaming to off and then it's
gone again so like it's just like I
think I need to reset it in order to get
rid of the crispiness that happens
randomly at random times for no reason
uh and the the actual setting of The
Sound capture has no specific connection
to the crispiness it seems you know what
I mean it's so weird so I just wanted to
explain that to you for no reason which
it's not going to help you or me but I
wanted you to did I press no I wanted
[Music]
to I want you to understand why I'm uh
struggling okay
[Music]
uh is it too
noisy I think she'll be fine I need to
keep one headphone ear off of my ear
because I need to listen when the
mailman is coming the post office guy
okay uh before we continue with the
story I think it would be smart to um do
some side quests if we find
some
uh how do I do this
again oh oh there it is okay that took
you a while
uh get cored to deal with the mailman
wait wait what was what was that why
does that sound familiar wait
what uh yes yeah I wanted to go to the
sky but it didn't react the thing he
didn't react
first ah dog
[Music]
h okay where shall we go do we have
anything uh
no ah you know what else I want I need
to go to faren Woods ah but I can do
that with a with a with a thingy
uh no yeah no I have to go inside okay
wait let's get the cubes from the tree
uh from the big
[Music]
tree
I don't know
[Music]
that traffic in the air is
insane no not really it's not really not
that bad y
so back into the the woods this music is
always cool yeah I agree Point your
prefer descent area yes yes
um uh treat the great treat I suppose is
probably hopefully the
top wait wait now we don't even have to
necessarily do it that way because now
we also have
the this thing oh I was thinking we have
to fall down but okay anyway let let's
get that one I guess by falling down and
I think there's one over here oh yeah
there both of them I think are reachable
with the claws right the whatever that
is oh then I didn't have to do it though
oh well I will I will
anyway
uh hi wait what about wasn't there a
heart container here
too heart
Challenger or am I going
crazy was there a chest of a heart
contain on here no I'm going crazy am I
going crazy hook shot hook shot thank
you okay we we got that one thank
God this
[Music]
one what do you want what do you
want sorry a little Panic a little panic
but I'm
okay up here right yeah okay so how do
we I have I have uh not really use them
yet
so uh aha go
[Music]
it up to the
sky noise calm or Panic stream today
only
Panic what are you talking about there's
like my Zelda streams are never calm
even if I want them to be
calm so was there anything else I should
be getting here help me chat cuz I don't
want to come back here ever again
I don't want to come back
here another Cube another
one doco where did where the hell did I
miss a
cube there's another Cube near the tree
okay that I can reach with my claw shot
shut
[Music]
up kill me n what the [\h__\h] back and
front did did you see
that I didn't see the enemy I was having
a hard time focusing on this one and
while looking to that side I kind of
shot that back to the holy [\h__\h] you want
to
me I just saw something what what
happened yo
hello hello
hello wow okay sometimes I just bust out
these moves that no one sees
coming I want those uh
could I fly away if I come go there too
[Music]
fast wait how did I fight
again wait stop not reacting
[Music]
properly
okay now um everyone calm
down why you guys so Panic kids calm
down
chat just look at me take an example of
me and be
calm take a chill pill Chad oh my God
you guys just such drama drama
queens okay we C okay okay I'm Cal I'm C
I don't know about you I don't know
about you man where is this other super
special goddess
Cube I can't find it
whatever tries to look for for two
minutes I give
[Music]
up thank you Jimmy for the pinky
what you don't want to be eaten well
that's fine with me that's
fine you decide your own destiny
probably maybe I don't know maybe not no
no you can't you can't
[Music]
oh chicken's pretending to be cats
excuse me so like def I get
done
sorry I don't know what what's wrong
with
me did you see that I learned a new
skill Pro
[Music]
game there we go y you destroyed my
shield you
[\h__\h] oh Hearts nice so
many what's there
go down when you want link to go down
but he just doesn't he just refuses
to where someone said there's another
like how do you even know that there
that there's another one that
I haven't seen yet another Cube maybe
there isn't maybe there never was
another Cube getting
dizzy
M ah wait I need some
uh
[Music]
uh can I cut them down with with the
thingy can I speak English
what no I want I want uh I want
uh I want the things for my
thing so I need to I need to warm up my
brain first
okay I my brain is not functioning yet I
want
um I want a Canon Canon Canon Canon
that's so
cute I dropped it on
[Music]
myself
a delivery link
delivery it I
wanted I
wanted I wanted uh what the [\h__\h] is the
word for
it English Doo ego
Musashi ego
Musashi
he go see yes thank you go
GOI people said don't do it that
way [\h__\h]
[Music]
you what am I even doing here right now
I'm just trying to find a cube by
accident but this is not happening let's
go
[Music]
um uh hello okay uh we're going to the
sky and then we're going
to
the to
home oh no oh no how do I how do I do
anything let's see where are we we got
one here and the other one I guess
spawned inside skyloft so let's turn
[Music]
around ch
ch I forget English words all the time
and it's my only language okay that
makes me feel a bit better
[Music]
our ambassador for the English shut up
that's that's a different story okay
that's Tales of arise and that's like
something else I don't need that much
English to be the English region
official Ambassador for Tales of arise
okay so where is this oh do I have to
land right in there oh God oh God I
don't know how
[Music]
to so not
it's is it in that
hole okay turn
around what what is
that what is that
what wait a
second
yo what you I'm doing
link there's a hole
there oh was that actually I didn't even
need to go through that
hole
oh maybe
not
[Music]
and
hello hello new friend what kind of
voice did I do for you Bo I don't
remember thank you
they say it's possible to summon fairies
by drawing tree free triangles upon
certain walls free triangles so you mean
the the the the the
thingy uh the thing the thing with the
three
triangles the thing the tramples let's
go I knew that I was testing you
guys dum
oh
[Music]
yes wait did I just gain a new
heart did I just gain a new
[Music]
one oh no I didn't that was uh we need
one
more okay one
more
o never I never looked so closely uh
into that inventory all right does that
mean we can
leave it seems so hello are
I controller is low battery or what's
going on I I charged them through the
night though what the
hell they feel a little
[Music]
better
I hello uh what's your
problem what's your
problem ice to see you remember Char
ever since that happened I've been very
careful to charge them before the
stream but even if I ever forget it
again even then
honestly um shouldn't be much of a big
deal cuz uh playing a little bit with
the Pro Controller was fine previously
before as
well previously on the handmaid
tail I need to finish that series I need
to watch it I need to watch that
series uh what what do we okay guys do
you know any any side quests any new
ones that I could
do uh
here oh wait yeah wait the wait wait
wait wait wait I need to go
there
uh
open the map yes yes item shop girl at
night
okay which item shop
girl here right am I going the right
direction two chests ah oh there's one
here too ah I didn't see that one okay
okay okay
okay
[Music]
main Crystal so we do some cubes then we
do side quests as many as we can find
and then we
[Music]
do main quest again hopefully we can do
like one dungeon what the hell is
that he's it's missing an eye is that is
that something like a quest as
well
check in with the nerdy guy at the
Academy ah you mean the one who I gave
the
potion oh it's over there how do
I do I have to go through here waterfall
spoy was I here
before before
[Music]
ohce get get out of there
what am I supposed to
be wait put it
away am I supposed to be scared or
something hello come
here where is
it even with the big
net I'm having huge issues it's up so
high come
down oh where did it
go
okay
wait is there do I even reach that
Island by going through this cave I have
a feeling the answer is
no I don't I go back to where I
was oh but hey we found a little chest
that I
apparently have not found before
okay
oh no I a
[Music]
COR wasn't that the one that fauna has
an issue with anyway doesn't fauna have
issues with
grasshoppers I think that was one I Did
It For
Fun okay let me get out of here I hate
this
place look right and up once you get
up what
oh ah that's where you reached that
gratitude
poop or no no maybe not oh yeah what is
this
place
my would the simplest option be to fall
down here and then play back
up wrong exit
yeah aha it won't let me land there okay
fine so we're back here this probably
faster this way so someone
said I don't see
anything ah
aha ahuh
aha
go
[Music]
aha the vine you can grab on to the
vines huh n to the Hodo oh there's
another one but can't get that one so
that's
fine I guess I want oh my God oh my God
BRB
[Music]
hey I'm
back you Amazon thank
you I I uh received some things that
some of them were are for the cooking
stream tomorrow so really had to um make
sure that that comes in time mhm
mhm
[Music]
pants off ey you right I could take my
pants
off
oh you're a weird one climbing all the
way up here you're
weird hey if you tried to dive off the
LED here I bet you could land in the
nest on top of tower down there what do
I know I'm a
stone
Nest he doesn't he doesn't mean the
chest does
he anyone let's get the chest
[Music]
oh yo nice what's in
there t
oo money
Noise Okay
okay yes stks
okay
what
you you you all that
way okay
um
Ababa
Ababa there we
go okay what do we want to do next ah
take get the other chest
perhaps which is on the other side can
we get it the same
way
is it that
one wait that's no this one that one is
so far with his that
[Music]
anyway how do I reach
that
from
here no there's nothing to hold on to
jump for
it can I really make
it
jump okay I will give it a
try what really
[Music]
I'm
see what do we get what do we
get more
money 100
rupees and now we can Pro
probably yes
okay I'm not even trying to use the sail
club who needs that not
me just face planted yep yep it is what
it is okay uh wait are this fre three
butterflies no
[Music]
two hey Dar link um I've been training
hard at night since you gave me that
stamina potion but I don't know it's
started feeling like maybe I've reached
my Peak like maybe I'm just wasting my
time I am Timeless I don't know if I'll
ever be as strong as you link still
there's nothing to be gained from
feeling sorry for myself so I'll keep
working out every night come by and give
me pointers
anytime
okay I'm
Dallas all right we'll come by at night
so I shall go sleep
now l
[Music]
I hate you I got him though for
once
[Music]
okay
another
one oh
[Music]
really
I love this bgm
too wait let me see do I have okay I
have one empty one okay at least I don't
have to use up anything that I already
have in my
botles nice is that a oh
[Music]
be
be ha finally oh it's the first time oh
first time Beetle Sky stag
[Music]
beetle uh here
right oh my head hurts
[Music]
man hello en is the green one one
right contion stamina potion this one
right I think he wants this one
okay IU I'm fine fine fine fine
fine
probably probably more water let's drink
more
water
H and I have this I have this one
particular really really stinky feeling
in my
throat like guess like one needle one
big fat needle is in my Thro every time
I try to swallow
something it
[Music]
hurts
it's probably
nothing yeah tomorrow is Doctor day yes
let's
go a fish basically well yeah it feels
[Music]
like is this my room doesn't look like
my
room
it feels like there's a this is my
room like there's
a fish
B in my
[Music]
FR today's my birthday happy
birthday
yay getting
older aren't
you okay where's my
friend yeah right his name is fledge
right what we didn't make any not sound
oh there you
are
55 56
57 oh I'm sweating up a storm good
evening link I've been training hard
ever since we last spoke but I still
feel so [\h__\h]
maybe I've just run out of
energy link is down a stamina potion
would you mind if I had some take it
it's all for
you really oh thank you Goku Goku go go
go Goku
Goku now he can do
[Music]
the oo that's a stu it's like a
refreshing splash of energy
sometimes I worried to all this training
and no results how long do I need to
train before I start to get stronger
what do you think link how many push-ups
do you think I need to get
strong it's not about numbers
buddy where is
it is
it should will be nice and say it's not
about
numbers
thousand it's not about the numbers no
it's it's not about the numbers of
course you mean I should just keep
adding until I forgotten how many I've
Done
Right my guess that makes sense now that
I know that I'll definitely start
getting stronger come back so soon this
is still not done you kidding me
better give me some money for
that oh come
on
[Music]
my when the hell are you going to get
stronger
dude all right let's see what else can
we do at
night oh
[\h__\h] need to go I hate that I need to go
upstairs just to get out of this
place H
H uh I can go into Z's room how
how is there
some
secret with my yeah with my claw shot
home H Target on the
roof
huh what I found a
[Music]
secret did you guys know that
LOL LOL I have to say it that is a l
moment for
me
oh beetle beetle
first
LLY
okay thank you for the Super
Chat thank you thank you thank you uh
what are we doing this
one can I get here God Dam
it I God Dam
it there we go okay so I'm here now is
this the first time I've been
here oh what do I see what do my eyes
see
here
okay I'm on the
roof what
now he a
bird
chimney
chimney is that a a
chimney oh that's supposed to be a
chimney not a hold
on let's
go
oh does he not notice me when I'm
running around here does he think it's
just mice or or something in the
roof hello h
Hello what if I place a bump can I place
a bump
no
okay who is that who the hell even is
[Laughter]
that we're in Zelda's
room Zelda's D
ah I the old
dude
okay well is that
it oh let's go wait that's the last one
we needed oh we got a new heart we got a
new heart can I what if I sleep in this
and then wake up in the morning am I
going to get in
trouble I can read her diary oh
what
this is Z's Journal one of the entries
is unfinished read the entry yes hell
yeah I
guess tomorrow's the big day and I'm
going to open up a snack right now yeah
let's go miss
miss miss the best there you guys can
read that on your own right mhm
m
[Music]
M
mhm I'm using my cutest voice yeah you
better
nice oh that's a cute picture
[Music]
y anyway I
continue yeah that was not
me requests from people available at
night in the town okay
interesting I want to check that
out Z's going to be
piss the thing that I was just eating is
one of my favorite snacks
ever I mean it it barely fills up my
stomach but it's so good it's such a
such a
um
addicting sweet
snack soting miss it it's so simple
though it's so
simple but I love it okay
where do be those uh side quest
H maybe in here Cookie's house now we
already did a Quest
[Music]
right hello hello is your child
okay oh oh I heard you're the one
responsible for finding cookie thank you
so much just look at her she puts her
parents through all that we and heart
and now she's out like a light cute are
you sure she's not
[Music]
dead link thank you so much for finding
cookier I'll need to be sure blah blah
blah blah oh
[Music]
H okay that
was I already opened that one that was
not oh my God the crazy cat the crazy
cat it saw me from so far away
is it still following me
no oh my God it's so
scary so scary this is like the scariest
enemy in this whole game I'm
telling what do we have
[Music]
[Laughter]
here I'm sorry I'm
sorry hey it's like bowling and I got
all of the pins I got all the pins
where's my
reward shut up what the hell
[Music]
man it doesn't look like I'll get much
sleep tonight again
why sorry to are you the baby just goes
on and on like this all night I haven't
slle a wink in uh I don't even know how
long the baby usually sleeps like a stck
of rocks but that was before we lost it
you know what what
[Music]
the baby's
rattle we had that you know what then
the baby would settle down but we lost
it the other day a bird picked it up in
its beak and flew off of it maybe the
bird thought it was food I don't
know of course a bird wouldn't have
eaten it so I think it must still be
somewhere here and town I just don't
know where for [\h__\h] sake safe me this
[\h__\h] shot is driving me
insane time
i' sure would be nice if someone would
find it for
me otherwise I'm going to throw this
baby into the
fire okay okay okay stop you don't have
to do that I'll help you uh I will help
you what
did he mean what do you
mean where is the rattle how do I find
it how do I find it put the baby into
the step number one put the baby into
the no please do guys do not put any
babies into any oven okay can we get
another side quest what's in
[Music]
here oh dear
oh that's your home oh hey kid I hope
you good putting old scrap good use he's
got a bit of a mouth on it but he's a
robot with a good heart well if robot
Hearts just remember to treat him kindly
and everything will work out fine uhuh
he doesn't have a side quest huh
hello oh good grief will you talk to
that boy of mine for me I thought he
would settle down a bit and maybe even
watch his hands now that he's got that R
up and running but he's still tinkering
away I'm telling you that boy will never
get that grease out of out from beneath
his disgusting fingernails and he thinks
he can get a girlfriend with those
fingernails
e is that not a quest really well see
what I can destroy
here
no
[Laughter]
no no ah this is a anti proof
[Music]
proof
uh oh o balance
ooh I thought that was connection was
weird but actually I guess it doesn't do
anything
I oh what's this
place I been in here
[Music]
before hello hey
he what do you need shopping you want to
do some shopping just come back to the
shop
tomorrow but you have a quest
no
uh so when you say that means you don't
have a good reason to be here huh what
you think I'm being R you think I'm
totally different during the day well I
get tired of having to be a smiley
shopkeeper all day all I just don't
think that this is a real me anyway
enough of that you're here to make some
money at my night market am I right
night
market ah it's your first time here
isn't it oh well not just when I do my
buying see I buy treasure but that's not
to say I'll buy just any old thing I
only deal in specific types of treasure
right let's get on with this shall we
well today I'm buying these treasers
lizard Dale D GR ornamental skull
goddess plume just these four so what do
you want to do no I need
them all really okay well hopefully
you'll come back against some done
really really you really want me to come
back oh I see an
opportunity finally someone reacts to
me no how could
you you
[Applause]
we didn't we didn't you guys see that
coming it broke my a t that's it you
breaking
[Music]
you let me see now that was oh only 20
okay those very expensive antique so
about 20 rupees should suffice ah come
for the red super chat oh what's that
look for oh you think I'm just making
that number that's really nothing though
I thought you were going to say like 300
or so oh that's ridiculous I know the
value of every item in my possession and
I tend to be compensated in
full that's okay I have way more than
that next time that happens we're going
to have
words can I do it again want to see me
do it
again oh M nice
decoration I don't want to do it again
I want to do it again if I go back in is
it respawned
already post check you thank you but I'm
always I always have a bad potion but
I'm glad someone still thinks about oh
let's
go
no you broke my
present yes I did H that's meet
yeah sorry I
[Laughter]
can't that was a very valuable item so
you're going to have to pay me freed is
there anything like at the end of doing
this a few times do I get like anything
out of
this 30 rupees or so and I didn't just
made that number
up can we do it
again is this is this I want to do it
again try when I don't have
money keep trying see if this is the
case let's find
[Music]
out this oh my wait did she upgrade
those where were these always looking so
expensive
anyway okay I didn't destroy everything
on the right side there's two left
okay consider that me lady you broke my
precious and take that was pretty
expensive item so you going to
20 so didn't break all of it what
[Laughter]
[Applause]
about
[Music]
[Laughter]
you know I just woke up today and I
wanted to see the world
burn start a fire today don't stop don't
stop just go your own
way SC
[Music]
spikes
yo did I do something horrible to you in
the past life why are you punishing me
like
this that was a very valuable item so
you're going to have to pay me 30 rupees
or so and I didn't just make that number
up boring boring
[Music]
boring
[Laughter]
[Music]
I got them all yay
jackpot simply
[Music]
get how could you you yeah you always
say the same
thing
[Music]
10 I broke everything and she only wants
10 Rupees what's going
[Music]
on why why was that maybe she starts to
like me maybe she likes
me maybe she has a thing for
me all
right I'll talk to her first
I love to collect antiques you know all
the things you see in my house are very
old and valuable make sure you don't
break anything uhhuh a
[Music]
[\h__\h] how course you you broke my
precious an that was a very valuable
item so I'm going to have to pay fre
[Music]
h
H nothing's happening I'm
[Laughter]
disappointed at
all
okay I'm going to give up for now I'm
going to try again and like whenever I
don't have any money I'm going to give
it another try uh thank you thank you
everyone for your
patience Maybe may she asks me to uh pay
her back in a different kind of
way no did I not just see a does that
despawn so fast did I not see like a
little jelly item down
there how could I despawn that fast I
can't even pick them
up okay
anyway anyway
[Music]
um
anyway uh where's that uh where's that
uh thingy the baby uh thingy that will
oh
what we got to go to that dude again at
some
point the the
baby
the huh
next I can dive
into ah the wonder that the stat you was
talking about wait what the hell was
that
uh over there
perhaps can I do that at night too does
that
matter
y nice
hit
is that cat following me
again no it's flying back
okay thank God terrifying my cats are
much much
sweeter was it
here oh
yeah hi hi hi hi
reminds me last night or this night last
night the previous
night I uh oh man I mean I cdle love my
cats every night but last night was just
special because smoothie was sleeping on
on on top of the pillow on top of the
pillow um o that was uh next to my
pillow
and I was trying to pet her and then she
wrapped her like she used my arm as like
a duim
makura she wrapped her arms and around
my around my arm and had her head
resting on my arm it was so damn cute I
was literally her DOI makura and know I
was in pain but I tried to stay in that
position as long as
possible it was so cute and she actually
fell asleep cuz I noticed her like uh
twitching and stuff oh this is really
hard to see what the
[\h__\h] ah wait I see wait that's way way
to far away what the
hell how I can't even say that at night
can you even do that at
night what no
a I feel like I
could
[Music]
I was never good with those gliding
controls shut
up Demon
Cat yeah me and smoovie we have been
really hitting it off these
days
I can use a Beacon ah yeah maybe that
helps maybe
maybe oh
God everything for the baby right
everything for little
baby sure
oh is it that that brown spot I'm not
even
[Music]
sure yeah yeah yeah yeah it looks like
it's in it okay it's so
dark no I can't do it what the [\h__\h]
man I hate
this press y before driving
okay no don't annoy me no don't annoy me
you you waited there until the moment
that I actually was able to
leave that's when you attack
me I see I see you're Savage Savage bat
that's your
name oh good night
though if you're going to sleep thank
you for
watchingo
go go link come
on I don't want to do I don't want to
come up here another
time if I if I fail again I'll just I'm
going to try to do it off screen off
stream off
screen I
just I'm not sure how to control it
anyway no I don't [\h__\h] sh me
[Music]
[Applause]
okay I'm not doing it
today the baby has to suffer and the dad
has to suffer I do not
care [\h__\h] you I'm going to
sleep side quest Arc is over cuz I can't
do
[\h__\h] what's with all these crazy demon
cats is there anything else oh my God
is there anything
else that I could have
done in the night
time go to the graveyard graveyard
[Music]
graveyard
uh hey ah byebye bye bye bye bye bye bye
[Music]
bye okay graveyard is uh
here everyone is insane here at
night
shut they didn't mean you got into that
way what am
I coming here
for oh man so
many give me some of those jelly items
please
do I have to do
the this thing
here or should I go inside of that
place
ouch I mean I do this for the Granit
crystals I guess
so look at the
wall why hello
friend uh I don't remember how I did
your
[Music]
voice oh oh yeah oh yeah something like
this um yeah oh next come and see me
when you've gaed F of
them you're not giving me
[Music]
anything
sucks
wait how do I get
I I'm I'm almost out for what is
that what is
that what does that
mean what does that
mean that opens that door
oh is that always
there someone said look at the wall I'm
what am I looking
at look at the
wall there's nothing here
nothing on the wall didn't you say look
at the
wall this very
nice ah okay okay okay sleepy down can I
sleep in someone else's house please I
don't want to look
back hey I don't want to go what the
hell is this place
[Music]
what e ew This is disgusting
ew what's the matter with
you link welcome so here's the thing
link my house is terribly dirty I see
that P is always telling me to do some
dusting around here but I just can't
bring myself to what what what does it
take for you to clean this [\h__\h]
up even I would have cleaned this place
a long time ago if I were living
here but I just can't bring myself to do
it that's why I wanted to ask you if you
would't mind cleaning it for me I'll
even pay you
okay you will oh great I knew you
wouldn't leave me to sit in this Dusty
house link what's that a broom you know
I don't even remember where we keep that
crazy thing or if we ever owned one most
most of the time I just wait for a good
strong wind to come along and
blow so look I don't really care how you
get the job done I just want you to blow
it I understand you don't you can't stop
hinting at me I understand I
understand oh I didn't even have to
equip it what's going
[Music]
on did you just
say sorry I'm breaking some things
though
not on purpose totally not on
[Music]
purpose oh well I mean this was about to
happen I can't do anything about
that I'm going to sleep in this bed
afterwards that's okay
[Music]
lady let's get this place cleaned up um
how particular are they
about each
[Music]
spot I hope not very
particular what's what's the matter with
you
[Music]
lady am I done
H there we go I'm done oh my there's no
more dust in my home thank you link you
brightened my day come over here let me
pay you
uh-huh oh thank you so much link my home
is sparkling clean again it feels so
much better when the place isn't under a
blanket of dust
oh what about the money though five oh
now we can go back to the gra uh
graveyard
cuz now I think we have 30 yes yes yes
yes I can't let you go your reward but
20 that's
nothing that's
nothing oh I can do it again at some
point oh one more thing don't tell
pippet about this he'll only get angry
at me for spending money on something he
thinks I should be doing myself you can
keep a secret right
I guess St
uh
yeah
okay okay what a weird
lady oh you're
in don't say that this is
funny okay so now we go back to the
dude oh oh
oh let's see what he will give me
haven't been to him in a long time
except for just
now hello I'm
back o you've gathered quite a lot of
gratitude Chrystal haven't you how
magnificent oh divine please take this
as a token of this Demon's deep best
[Music]
appreciation you have made such
magnificent progress Gathering Gratitude
Crystals please just continue helping me
a be
longer okay
[Music]
what let's go
okay no I beg you stop that just is not
to open under any circumstances there's
something unspeakable inside I want to I
said
M that chest contains the infamous evil
of the Dragon curs metal if you carry
that metal with you you'll find more
rupes than ever before you'll even have
better chances of discovering treasure
you you'll oh don't let you say
it say
what it gets worse fall
for S poor soul who holds that metal
will find himself unable to open his
pouch no matter how badly you want to
use your potions or Shields they will be
denied to you can you imagine a one some
feet
H please push any for this chest out of
your mind forever you must never think
of it again I never used the metal
before is that maybe I don't want it do
want what hard
mode I guess I guess I don't need it
okay I leave that chest un open
then
okay okay so what the hell is
that now you want to see it opened even
more I'm not opening it yes I'm not
he asked me to not open
it one second let me eat some more um I
got the I got um um bu what you
bu
grapes
mhm okay
now we sleep I guess I could have picked
it up without using it I guess so but I
don't need it anyway
so maybe I'll take it next
[Music]
time so can I sleep in your in your bed
now or what
[Music]
should I break some things can I read
this
no I don't want
[Music]
please the way he like goes to bed is so
satisfying
you have to explain that to me you have
to explain to me how that
happened when I went to how long did I
[Music]
sleep what the hell happened here can I
clean it
again yeah sure what the
hell
what did you do while I was asleep what
what what what what did you just say at
the end you want me what why did
you oh nothing okay are you uh not CET
I'm not done what would happen if I say
I'm
done window shelves yeah yeah I know I
know I know I know don't worry I got it
I got it
w hi I speed cleaning let's go we got to
make uh get back that money that we uh
wasted on that antique
[Music]
lady I I I totally knew about the side
quest that's that's why I was like oh
whatever it doesn't
matter I'll just play around with the
antique lady a little bit it was it was
all according to
Kaku
mhm all according to my
[Music]
K I was waiting for you guys to write
that translat no take A's
[Music]
plan okay right there we go oh my
there's no more dust in my whole thing
thank
you yeah play pay me pay up
[\h__\h] pay
up mhm what do I get 20
okay is this a quest you can do
endlessly it seems
so it seems
[Music]
so it really blow me away K
oh
it's repeatedly repeat endlessly repeat
okay okay okay okay I understand is
there anything new we can buy in the
item shop
there I wonder I don't want to get
kicked out you
know can I do it
with
[Music]
you can go to the nest from
there from the item
shop wait where is
[Music]
it I need 5200 for the new pouch oh okay
then whatever I guess shall we go to the
next area wherever that is um
that settles because it was okay I guess
that actually makes
sense star mes that actually makes a lot
of sense I don't think that the game was
actually like considering that because
they act as if
this actually they like it blows it away
but it acts as if it's sucking it in and
and makes it disappear but that makes so
much sense
how goes it that sounds like someone
translated German language directly into
English you want me to visit again well
is he in love with me is he in love with
me let's go one of the more unique areas
in the
game
[Music]
okay
let's go
then he's trying hard to impress me I
think so too
yeah who wouldn't be love of you a I
love you very sweet of
you uh star
time apparently we need to go to Lau
[Music]
desert this way
why are you trying to fly into me
[Music]
[Applause]
again best area in the game Star music I
kind of get that yeah I see where you're
coming
from
Main and let me eat get some
snacks I prepared a lot of snacks for
this
stream so that I um would survive also
my headache is fine now I think yeah I'm
feeling fine I have um
chocolate uh poofy poofy rice waffle
thingies again
good snack open up open up you're about
to go into my
tummy
s where should I
go where's the closest point although in
the desert I think right now we have a
lot of um things to explore
anyway
still with the with the claws hook
shot Westt
M
okay
mhm ah speaking of snacks I'm so
[Music]
mad I'm so mad
because Chi
CH not
[Music]
Sensei
because
um
M I think I told my members about it
only right until
now uh oh
dear so I might want to um explain that
first
[Music]
I you get me every time every time
man okay so uh wait let me explore a
little
bit nice Parry thank you thank you so
basically um I wanted to uh do a
monthly worldwide International snackbox
review and I found this uh website where
you can basically do that you can make a
subscription and they send you monthly
um every month a different uh snack box
from a different country and when I got
the idea it was the end of July it was
one of the last two days of July I think
so it was pretty late yes but it still
had the the July uh snack box available
on the homepage which was the Canada
snack
box
um that
one can't reach from
here
so H it said that if you order um at the
end of the month then you'll just get it
in the beginning of the next month how
ah I see a CBE however I have waited and
waited and waited and nothing arrived so
I
messaged I I notified
them and was like yo where is my snack
box it's it's it should have arrived
like ages
ago
and um actually the August snack box
should have August yeah August snack box
should have arrived also during this
month but it did not
come so they got back to me and they
said they only said something about the
July snack box they ignored this the the
August snack box for some reason oh my
god um nice dad do there was apparently
some issue with my payment which is not
true my payment went through but I have
this um sus suspicion
suspection I am suspicious because I
think what happened is it was so late at
the end of the month that they ran out
of ingredients and snack boxes for that
month since I ordered at the last two
days of that month and they just were
like [\h__\h] we don't have any anything
left so we can't send her the snack box
so we're going to tell her that her
payment didn't go
through they refunded me
but um it's a bit weird uh I don't
understand the logic right now I think I
have to think about it for a little
moment but the subscription that I have
is like a 6 month
subscription uh for 6 months six snack
boxes and the first one for the first
month is basically you get it for free
[Music]
um and um it's so weird uh they refunded
me like5
$5
uh I don't know how to explain
this every month you pay a certain
amount but for the first month you only
pay I think the
shipping which was like $5 or $6
and they refunded that but that means
that I'm paying for the first box which
will be I guess the August box which I
still don't
have uh I'm still paying the full price
even though the first box should be uh
for free they refunded me basically
nothing because the first box was free
and I never received the first box you
get you understand what I'm
saying so shouldn't the August box be
refunded you know what I mean shouldn't
that one be the refunded one
because my first box should be free and
they refunded me only the
shipping so I'm like
what yeah so I will write them another
email ask where my August snack boox is
and how the hell that refund
Works cuz I'm very confused right
[Music]
now no I wouldn't say it's a scam I mean
I they're like I don't know they don't
seem like a
scam they don't they don't seem like a
scam to me Al where the hell am I
supposed to go I want to go over there
how do I get
there uh ah do I have to turn back time
ah no wait I can just oh yeah R I can
just go up by uh going there oh I forgot
that was a
shortcut that's a scam no I wouldn't say
it's a scam they just don't they just
don't know what they're
doing
am I supposed to go in
there
yeah maybe they're confused too maybe
they just don't know what they're
doing the N caves
oh okay I see a lot of bombs and
[Music]
dude
anyway um no no no no wait
uh yep there we go there we go that's
that's the one
unleash somebody BLS carry a monster
horn on their waist if you latch onto it
and pull it with your whip uh it is
possible to claim it and watch me neigh
neigh Watch Me Whip watch me neigh neigh
watch me whip whip watch me nigh
[Music]
neigh oh oh thank you boy
Bo they they say somewhere in this vast
desert there's a dragon who loves
putting the abilities of those who visit
him to some kind of test if you can
Master the challenges he throws at you
you'll be rewarded with a shield
stronger than any other oh does that
mean I don't get um a shield and another
sword extension I next time I get a
shield uh level up or something like
that is that
it
why why am I even able to pick these up
I still don't
[Music]
get y wait what happens when I Chain
Reaction there he goes oh byebye oh
that's why there's a hole up
theree bye bye bye bye bye bye bye-bye
oh it came back are you going to tell me
something
different uh no uh what the hell why did
you do that that freaking hurt me
dude please go somewhere else you scare
me bullying is not
cool don't bully me
please okay I got you don't worry I'm a
good
person let's blow up everything else
then
you didn't know that that can happen
really well now you know H sorry dude oh
oh
[Music]
God o I almost never get visitors my
name is go and I'm researching The
Legend of the free dragons one of which
is said to live here at first glance it
would seem that there's nothing in this
area but I know there's something here I
would just keep on looking
so your name is link I see not the
easiest name to say is it but how about
you link why are you here you're looking
for a sacred flame that sounds like
something I have heard of before but
maybe not sweet qu I remember now I read
something about it in the ancient
Scrolls that spoke of the Lalu
Sans I do not remember all the details
but you can get to the sensey if you
just go straight through here ah huh
it's really difficult to make that
voice if you want to get to sansy I'm
cheating I'm cheating you are going to
need to
SK a than you SMY oh so sweet of him to
help me out there oh good luck to you oh
thank God thank
you oh nice I appreciate it a hole oh I
need to roll another bomb in there I
think bowling
baby
why yeah you can't hide that from
me
and do you want me to throw another bomb
in
there was that really necessary free
bumps free
boms
really and that's not even worth
[Music]
it okay you and speed
crawl by the way guys I don't know if
you knew that but now you know the more
you know pick it up put it in pick it up
put it in your
pocket uh anything else I needed to
explode wait a second did he say I
should go that way what about what about
that
way that's that's what the key is for
[Music]
no but I I guess I'll you
on I came from
[Music]
there no I came from there
H or did
I wait so I came from here what does the
other path lead to though I need to see
that
let me check
first
oh
n uh oops no is this a
secret not much of a
secret there up okay let's practice our
clown shot skills
by the way in German we call this enter
hacken enter
hacken up there very useful
uh-huh there we go okay where does that
lead
us nice
shot
there wait I want to get you don't run
[Music]
away ah thank
God nice is this the beginning area of
like some place I I remember this
place oh but there's a chest there's a
chest
though side
[Music]
chest okay that's
it
seems like it okay going
back going
back yeah right we got to use the claw
shot everyone why did you not see that
coming
huh you should have known that you used
the clashot who is
chat why did you not use the
clashot I knew it I of course knew it I
was hoping for you guys to remember
it because I want to include you in this
game play to make it more fun for
you
yeah I don't it would be so selfish of
me if I was always the only one playing
you know sorry boss it's okay it's okay
it's okay it's
[Music]
okay can I even get up
there
[Music]
no can I get up there oh that's really
heavy can I get up there with if I put
that clot oh for God's sake why is that
so heavy what's there's nothing inside
why is it so
heavy not more hard than
I claw shot always think about the claw
[Music]
shot m
M
no I'm so
sorry is there anything else I can help
you with oh he doesn't even react then
can I go past you
move go wait why is
this did I not blow that one up yet I
feel like I
did what about the other hold though I
can't reach
it
that's probably going to be like a blue
rues so
[Music]
whatever I never blew that up
what
what okay guys it is time for us to move
on no more side quests wasting
time it is time
for this
stuff yes yes
this is lario sansi this whole area was
once an ocean but the water has all
evaporated and now the area is a sea of
sand
W
no signs indicate that this place
functioned as a port linking the land to
the
sea oh that's huge
[Music]
uhhuh this area operated on a new form
of power there is a 90% probability that
the sacred flame is located ahead I
recommend exploring the sand seat can
you stop talking so fast I can't read
that fast when I'm reading out
loud and try to be in
character all
righty
[Music]
I really love how your voice feet thank
you I'm glad you like it thank
[Music]
you don't fall down don't look
down uh and then I'll be
fine I love this area really these look
like giant Raper sticks I agree they
reminded me of something like that
too the ones that you h
[Music]
ah the ones that you eat with ice cream
right hey that looked like you could
possibly jump over it it looked like it
don't blame
me let's see what do we have
[Music]
uh w w w
oh oh don't talk them when they're
electric
nice they never drop items what the
hell
[Music]
okay right nothing
there again another
one
can I blow that up
no oh there nothing here either
ah why what did you do to the real
K well there we go here I
am there we go I was not in character
you
know
a at once not in character stop it stop
it at
once okay real kada is
back stop it stop it
okay Shield almost said no it's not no
no no no not even at all no no no uh
hello it's dead oh we got another one of
those
crystals oh can I there we
go ah all right this one restores oh
yeah right that was a thing nice very
useful what
w
a
ah
o uh why you some human who am
I I am the proud Skipper of the ship
that protects n's flame
sh SEL looks different no this is sel in
her true
form it was the day of the storm F my
crew and I were navigating the scenes as
usual and then those brutes the Pirates
suddenly attacked
us they were after night's Flames my
crew was in prison and I was thrown into
the
sea I drifted on the curent to this
port after that I took this boat and
went searching for my ship and crew but
there were nowhere to be
found it hunts me wondering where my
ship could
beep i' bet my had that have turned the
ship invisible and are hiding out
somewhere you can't see it
aha
invisible in order to protect Na's Flame
the ship has function has a function
that allows it to become invisible sleep
you say you searching for n's flame so
you need N Flame to find someone
important to
you in that case you should help me
search for my ship and crew
free if you'll help me with then I guess
I'll like you on my boat of course I'll
help this reminds me of Wind Waker let's
go really well in that
case there's something weird about that
map of yours if you're going to navigate
these treacherous Waters then you need a
proper sea do
we there's a sea in my shack at Skippers
Retreat so first you need to go on this
boat and set a course for skiers
Retreat tell we show off let's go
all right let's go
Su welcome to the stream
hello my circuit [\h__\h] your life in the S
Air Boom it feels good to take to the
Sea again after so long but let's see if
I can remember how to navigate press L
to move Press B to speed okay set AR
ready the cannon press set R again to
fire ah I have a
cannon I placed the an X mik over on the
island where my house is from there's a
pier on the island where we can
du
uhhuh let's
go yeah let's go oh fun cor
pretty we test
ah
okay yeah okay for now I don't need it
are we going to the right
direction this is so pretty the waters
are so
pretty let's go see
it natu natu
natu beautiful can I could I I would
love to swim in this can I go without
the
boat it's
[Music]
pretty uh
aha wait over
there no that's something else
me
beautiful oh can I go for
here I think I I should be able to no
okay a I can speed up oh yeah
[Music]
right I should probably stop
here nice boat thank you thank you I
know I know I know
[Music]
H uh we've arrived
V oh is that you my shack is at the very
top of room I want a house like that too
when where the whole Mountain looks like
my face
nice it does look like him the seart we
need is in my shack it's but you're the
only one you're the one who will have to
go get it there are monsters about uh
more monsters about than before so we
I can't land to fall from the boat so I
just stay
here
okay that's true you die if you wonder
off so stay there I will
safe H safe
Mountain new Minecraft build a mountain
that looks like my face that has to be a
big mountain man that sounds really
difficult can I get those hearts thank
you
very helpful I appreciate it oh dear
okay you going to shoot something at
me oh
yeah one more one
more a [\h__\h] oh wait I can't oh fight I'm
back at
you or is my timing just off no I think
I can't
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
failure yeah I guess I need to use those
stupid bombs
again I got it okay I understand what if
I use the claw shle how does that how do
you like those stop
it oh interesting it uh kind of like at
least confuses
him uh
bumps
ah oh here are bombs in case I want to
use my my B
huh okay eat this no it's way too
far oh yeah you know what I'm going to
use my
Beetle I will indeed use my Beetle y
nice
range
and drop it nice
that took me too much
[Music]
time that's because I wanted the heart
come
on
okay what what that's not being greedy
that's just trying to stay alive you
know what how do I fight you is there I
don't see a bomb this is not a bomb be
versus oh oh I can open it to give me
hearts not
hold
okay let me open another one cuz I do
need those hearts right now [\h__\h] damn it
what if I just bunk
you uh not a
Hodel am I too
far or will be do the trick oh it
worked okay so now we need to
[Music]
clashot oh hello there what's here
nothing okay okay a chest
though okay before I deal with those
thingies let me try to wait how can I
even reach it from here it doesn't seem
to have a cloth strot thingy over there
okay never mind
[Music]
Focus there we
go what is that flying thingy over
there I need to catch on to that
one it seems so oh
dear Bo boing
Bo oo bumb
time
[Music]
chill
okay I officially hate that enemy
[Music]
now I wanted to heart but okay so I
guess that kind of gives me any kind of
[Music]
present what's in
there everything m
future be patient with them I can't cuz
if I'm patient oh God they they form one
thing again we don't want
that oh my
[Music]
God okay we
good
oh I wonder if I could like fly down
there but I don't want to I don't want
to risk it I'll just
[Music]
I'll just hope maybe from a higher point
it would be
easier okay this one this one and
then uhhuh ah
you I do this
it okay hello hello hello we have some
holes to dig oh oh wait wait
what the hell how am I even supposed to
react that
[Music]
fast that is so
stupid
[Music]
[Applause]
okay thank you I just wanted the heart
give it to me no no
no can someone build a freaking fence
there oh the
[Music]
the
a ah
nothing
okay oh
[Music]
dear
uh present fo you oh it went so far oh
God it rolled off the
[Music]
edge oh
God is he scared of me too
I what the hell
what
the
okay uh he has the iron shield now
[Music]
why I'm about to fall
off I'm behind his shield in his wobble
double wobble double is his stomach
interesting actually did I take any
damage this time I feel like I didn't
wow not
[Music]
bad
Tak warri let's
[Music]
go he said ask for for Mission before
entering someone's wobble gobble it's
wobble double not wobble gobble
according to me
uh sound like a shortcut for
L wait what is this stuff also I want
that Cube over there ah CH
M CH
[Music]
M now hold
ony can I use this yeah
okay hey got this
Cube it really looks like
the the
holoen cube doesn't it it really
does there it
[Music]
goes okay from here I could maybe try to
fall down there but no I want to
continue moving I'm upwards upwards I
want to make
progress
uh
okay
and
T this must be so much fun to
use wait what does do I have to use my
whip no kind of looks like
the whip Works a bit oh wait can I hang
on to this I can no no no no
no oh there it is
oh
oh that actually works even though it's
like the future now and everything here
is like dead can I go back up too I
can oh
okay cool
Co
okay h ah wait here's a here's a
spot it didn't even notice
me oops sorry I did not intend to hurt
you unless you try to hurt me and that's
a whole different story oh
dear okay wait wait did this before
let's do it
again show me a tail let's
go there we go easy Target only drops
one Ruby
lame
[Music]
okay
Bo what does it do uhhuh I can hang on
to it again in but where does that
wait no no no
no wait wait for me wait for me wait for
me there we
go am I going
here stop
moving there we
go lots of cute bugs are you the
butterflies of the
desert come back I'm nice I swear I
swear trust me I'm your friend
no really bad at
this a I got one is the other one got no
that one is still here okay let me try
to get
you
no
what wor
it what
[Laughter]
it oh that one is
bad do you want me to jump off the cliff
for you too
what what else am I doing up here ah
[Music]
okay uh that's kind of worries me will
that attack me the moment sus sus very
sus where
is what I send the beetle to
yeah smart kada
no think I will fall for that trap hell
no hell
no all right uh oh my God it's a welcome
parade oh God two it
[Music]
one oh
dear can you like the other one
[Music]
maybe okay that one's
dead Give me give
me
and other one oh don't don't don't spit
fire at me you know who you're messing
with the real Phoenix you're just a fake
one okay we're almost at the top but
to the t uh we go there
first by the way guys I saw
something I had a YouTube advertisement
for a
movie on Amazon Prime and it's kind of
tacky
um but I was wondering if you're going
to watch it with me if I do it in the
members only stream next week would you
watch it with
me would you um watch a tack
Disney movie with me I think it's a
Disney movie yeah it's it's a newa
Cinderella movie didn't one just come
out like a few years
ago it's a new Cinderella
movie yeah and I don't know looks looks
kind of cute so I want to watch I was I
was going to watch it so I was thinking
well might as well might as well invite
you
guys why why not you
[Music]
know you you don't you don't don't have
to and I Ste C from you what the [\h__\h]
no of course
[Music]
not it's on
Amazon oh wait so I guess that was
produced by Amazon not by Disney
ah where are we going buddy I want to oh
nice it's with the one who sings
Havana to of my heart is in
Havana oh my heart is in there's
something
[Music]
about
yeah cam something Camila Cabello is
that her
name I love that
[Music]
song
oh that's the perfect spot to jump down
from
mhm okay I've reached the end it seems
gramy right there thank you
C Cabo what what is
c not you
again do I need to clean up this place
let me take a seat first very kind oh
hello
I recommend waiting until after you have
achieved your objective
before
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] are you for real
now is she for
real I was trying to heal myself [\h__\h]
you want me to die or what she wants me
to die I
think is what's going on clean that [\h__\h]
up is that R be
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay no no no no no no the Japanese bro
is saying well it's a Japanese game and
in Japan you don't take rest
you don't take a break I guess that
makes
sense I guess that does make sense a lot
of sense so where is that
aha no but what the hell that was so
weird like why why is she telling me
that when like I was why why doesn't she
tell me that when I'm doing side quests
huh like hey instead doing sad Quest how
about you go do the [\h__\h] main
quest I'm taking care of my health here
here oh de Captain thanks for everything
yours the grou
a
[Music]
ah yeah I walked in I sat down at the
moment she I sit down she says no no
rest for you
[Music]
Beach I'm try I'm trying to find the
[\h__\h] map or whatever we're looking
[Music]
for also everyone's dead here so I love
that that thing here though what do you
call it in English it's an Anor Anka in
German so I guess it's in
here anchor oh was pretty
similar I see CH there we go oh look at
that cute picture over there looks like
chickens but it's not chickens on the on
the ship on the left
side yes fee what do you
want cute they're doing Titan oh my God
are they doing Titanic on that picture
oops sorry ignore that that is the ship
containing nus flame there is a 90%
chance that the synthetic life forms
assembled here are the
crew this image would indicate that the
ship's Captain spent many happy days
among his many crew
members you're telling me that but you
telling me I can't even sit down to take
a 2-minute break really really really
really you're not
helpful you're not being
helpful there something if I go up here
no okay well I shall go back down I
guess these dudes stay dead so
bye-bye oh no breaks for Heroes yeah
unfortunately link that is the reality
we have to get used to it is there
anything else up here that I might want
to get
or I mean I hear SAS
again thank you for the pinky yeah [\h__\h]
sand man [\h__\h] it so sick of
sand wait why can I not get up here
[Music]
anymore
ah okay so next week
for for the members of tell me we watch
a movie a cute movie tacky movie
Cinderella y yay
have so if I jump down from here I
should be able to get the chest
[Music]
right cute movies are good yeah I
agreed wait can I hello can I use my you
[\h__\h] kidding me where do you spawn me
where are you going to spawn me where
are you going to Spa
me okay okay that's good that's good
that's good I like that that works for
me what the hell was
that I'm I'm not doing this on purpose
okay am I losing Hearts when I do this
oh my god did you see that at the very
end how it like swooped over to one
side I don't know why I did
that scares
me money money
[Music]
money
wonder if there's a Japanese version for
that already if there's like
[Music]
subtitles almost as much as I spend on
the antique PS
today you have enough for the adventure
pouch let's go oh was that 1,200
stop
[Music]
it you got me there buddy
oh okay well we shall get it
eventually uh hey
buddy was a pain in the ass but I got
your
thing you got the sea boom now we can
finally navigate PR
let's go look for my ship okay shall we
set sail set sa let's go
[Music]
baby it's
Japanese Bros say that they can't like
it's not released on that their Amazon I
[Music]
guess wait that's sad I want to want to
watch it when everyone's able to watch
it wonder if there's a Japanese release
date that's like
later
[Music]
uh ah the anime watch along I still want
to do that sometime
you open up to see T you
B the shipyard is at this location first
let me Mark it for you with an
X oh yes
[Music]
me but I would I would think they would
already release it with like subtitle
for like some languages first
September oh in
[Music]
Japan in Italy oh okay so maybe in Japan
as
[Music]
well wait I think it's not even
available in my country either yet
probably I don't
know yeah so we can a worldwide ah so
it's not even out yet for some reason I
thought it was already out cuz I was
getting the ad advertisement
okay the shipyard is where we used to
build our ships food my ship was built
there too if you go to the shipyard you
might find some Clues to the location of
my
ship
okay
ah this my want to play wind wer
it will be out
[Music]
tomorrow oh there's
a this boat has stamina too not
H oh
oh can I back go back yeah
okay I love wind wer it's my favorite
yeah I think I would agree with
that why do I hear Boss
music oh
dear
wo a
hi hi R
Kiana can I get that heart please how
why can I not get that heart
hey what happens if I shoot
that
nothing
shoot this is
fun this is fun it reminds me of the
ship games
so the ones where you like I don't
know shoot other ships down it's some
really old game I played that
before
a battleships yeah yeah yeah yeah oh
dear
explosion
[Music]
mini Wind Waker yeah this is mini Wind
Waker oh I can duck here is this where I
wanted to go yeah okay I was having so
much
[Music]
fun okay okay that reminds me of it
takes
two because in It Takes Two it was it
takes to was
it there was so much rail riding as well
and it takes two
[Music]
we this is the island where we used to
make our ships you'll find the shipyard
here as well as the town where the
workers
[Music]
lived that building is the constuction
bay
huh but the entrance is closed room
looks like you can't get
in each location on the island is linked
to the others via mine cart Minecraft
track you might be able to get to the
back door of the construction Bay if you
can get around to the other side of it
using a mine card
uhuh there's a minecart station over
there okay you should head to the
station first I'll wait here okay
byebye I'm
CED H let me save for a
moment
safe
[Music]
so
ah have I ever fought those
before have I
ever what could be
[Music]
useful oh they're easy oh
byebye oh not so easy
anymore hey oh no problem for ATT I
think I got a tail too from him oh the
other one fell down unfortunately that
[Music]
sucks trick or
treat oh my God Halloween is actually
this year year's Halloween is going to
be the second Halloween ever since I
joined her life aw I remember last year
we did that snack thingy
right for
Halloween that's so long ago so long ago
what if I sit down is free going to
[\h__\h] at me
again no okay now you're going to [\h__\h]
at me come on give me your break you're
standing there anyway you're not
sitting o
is my seat nobody sh the rear end of my
me got it excuse me I'm the hero of this
whole
[Music]
game the station here was used by folks
heading into the old mines people still
ride the mine carts all over the place
[Music]
though I love
I am probably supposed to tell you
there's some safety information about
using the cards posted on the w cart
riding can be a dangerous times so I
would suggest you give that stuff a
quick read it does not only remind me of
itex 2 but it also reminds me of Super
Mario
Sunshine okay I will
read approach the card press a to get on
lean your body to balance the weight of
the card oh dear if you move into V plus
press
jump to clear jump what's the button for
jumping
though what in this game you jump
automatically what's the button for it
then all right whatever let's let's
roll R CL I'm scared on
on you don't like these kind of things
that
much uh oh my
God
okay oh I can speed why would I want to
do that why would
I
wait I like that anime speed
effect hey it's going fine can I fall
down from
then she
is oh my God oh my God oh my God
w repeat
[Laughter]
intens that was fun thank you for that
ride
mhm first
try how close s sometimes it's uh pretty
hard to
see okay that was my fault cuz I started
running can you guys come back please
what the hell is that
ah wow so
many hello hello hello I hear the crispy
sound let me fix it crispy chicken Yum
Yum Yum M crispy chicken m yesterday I
watched a cooking
video of how to make like KFC like
crispy chicken like I I would usually
make it with like bread
um crumbs
thingies but like he used like batter
for it interesting yeah that's a
different kind of crispy chicken right
mhm interesting I shall try that kind of
uh batter at some point yeah like
panle
pkle okay just stay calm K okay we got
two I'm happy I could get that one too
probably nice finally some success when
catching beet
up I watched it yesterday too from you
to recommend
really are you sure you watched it for
you YouTube recommend and not because I
posted it on
Twitter which way do we go
[Music]
is this the the same way I came no is
that a different wait which way do I
want to
go can I even go there yes I can
um this is to go back okay so it should
be I saw the Twitter
post yeah yeah yeah okay what does it
say
nothing okay and now one
but wait for
it wait for
[Music]
it
let's
[Music]
[Applause]
boy
[Music]
[Applause]
woohoo the
[\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
hey let
go
[Music]
I made it too loud I made it too loud I
made it too
loud let's
go
[Music]
but your repeat has to be loud am I
right or am I right so I think going
right was uh the better option at
first
yeah and
right
oh are you cly tell me quick
[Music]
Li and Truth come to light at the break
of day I've been try oh
no y let's
go stream he
on so fast where the hell are we going
anyway oh my
[Music]
God wait we have reached I think the
[Laughter]
end holy [\h__\h] those jumps those jumps
freak me out
[Music]
man oh my God that's so much fun
Imagine you know it would be so much fun
to like go on a on a roller coaster and
then have that music play and then me
trying the challenge is me trying to
sing uh
H while being on an actual real roller
coaster and that reminds me I was like I
was in when I was in Japan um this year
uh I was at this um like
indoor uh amusement park and they did
have some kind of musical roller coaster
where you like it was all Hudson and M
themed and in that musical roller
coaster you had to like it's it was like
a rhythm game in a roller
coaster yeah yeah that would that would
be so cool to have with like whole life
but I wonder because actually H live did
have uh a joy
po collaboration
[Music]
right
collaboration I think I think the I
think it was uh like in in in
Spring I
think you need to go there with good I
see would going insane she would love it
[Music]
yeah and I wonder if like during that
whole life collaboration with that with
that uh amus indoor amusement park
[Music]
f
sorry I'm I'm I'm discussing whether or
not that actually was a thing or I'm
imagining it no I think I think
it yeah yeah yeah so that that um indoor
amusement parket has like collaborations
with like companies so first the the
time when I went it was hat of De was
volcaloid
and uh later on they had one with h life
too yeah yeah yeah so I wonder if that
um Riven game roller
coaster was playing whole life songs CU
When I went was playing vocal
[Music]
songs I want to go again that was so
cool like an indoor amusement park it
was so well
made I really like that um amusement
park m
H if you guys are ever in Japan in Tokyo
and then maybe on one day there's like
bad weather and you don't know what to
do um you should go to Joy
Pais write that down if you ever plan on
having a vacation in Japan and it's like
super rainy or something like that and
your pans your plans are cancelled you
go to Joy
Palace yeah I really recommend it I
think it is like like close to
um I think
Oda yeah it's like at at at some kind of
bay yeah yeah yeah when your pants
again I miss spoke
excuse okay so I guess wait we're doing
another roller
coaster oh that did I just come from
there ah ah I came from there now we're
going for here I wanted to go on another
[Music]
one oh yeah
hello finally you stop wasting time you
keep on talking about other things even
though you should just focus on the
freaking game aren't you planning to
finish it in two streams including this
one that's not going to happen if you
continue wasting my [\h__\h] time and
please remind yourself you're also
wasting your own time not only my time I
couldn't care less if you were only
wasting my time but really think about
it it's about you and your time cuz tell
of arise is releasing soon on the 10th
of September and you're supposed to play
it so you wanted to finish it before
then then let's just get to [\h__\h] work
[\h__\h] anyway mastera we have arrived at
the shipyard construction
Bay
beautiful with the passing of many years
this structure has filled with
sand I recommend looking in the sand for
a clue that may direct you to the
location of the
[Music]
ship okay let's fight you guys first so
you don't annoy the hell out of me what
was that that sound that sound is so
[Music]
scary all right now we can clean this
[\h__\h]
up is there a crystal behind us
no
what what the
[\h__\h] what the hell
man
[Music]
a am I hitting it properly or do I need
to
stop that came like out of nowhere that
the whole mob what the
hell okay I think I'm hitting it prople
I think I
am
nice
or am
I
nice nice oh okay one to go yeah
baby open
your ain't happening that ain't
happening okay I guess it
is
hey open
up woohoo
all right
baby come back come back
here no hidey
hidy want to see what's going
on how do I heal myself here is there
any
hearts wait do I stab you I I tried I
tried and I did
it [\h__\h] I'm trying Mar
out don't mess with me
now can you get out of here right
now I got I got him I got him I
got get out of
here
[Music]
[\h__\h] yay
baby that was not bad that was not bad
that was not bad I need more Hearts than
that what the [\h__\h] do you
want Master it would appear that in the
many years this Factory went unused
monsters have moved in and built a nest
uh-huh
I now estimate the chance of finding a
clue in the stand here
as ship's location is extremely low you
suck thing you
suck quit quit
in you forio so first you tell me to
what no I I'm so sick of this
lady oh my God maybe that was maybe that
was all according to her
Kaka we here now are it a now the door's
open uhhuh so what now she didn't tell
me where else to
look I need some uh Hearts by the way
maybe I can get one from this
flower yes please don't fall
down
yeah and there it goes and there it
goes no I don't need Hearts
anyway I don't need Hearts
anyway now my ship wasn't here then
there is only one place left for us to
look for
Clues this could be scary but we have to
head for the stronghold of the Pirates
Who sto my ship sleep so let's not waste
any time let's
go I can pick up hearts with the hook
shot really
oh I am a heart Challenger after
all this is pretty scary the pirate
Captain is a mechanical Maniac he's got
no shortage of evil underlings too V I
never wanted to lay eyes on him again
but if we want to take the ship back
then we have no choice for
me pirate stronghold is here at this X
let's
go Tien up whatever you humans have
instead of bolts and let's go going
a should I go to the skyloft
Or
Nah why the hell would I do
that
SHO down
Sho
Sho Sho thank you for the membership
welcome
baby
ouch in the sea what the
[\h__\h] is it
dead now it definitely is I didn't see
that one
coming you got nothing on me
nothing well that's kind of scary
though that's a bit
scary is this where I get uh
my flame my super special
flame pirate stronghold I see your
goddess Cube
wow nose holes as big
as s's feet when she's off her
[Music]
limiter that is a good question why did
we not just go straight here good
question if you think about it they
should all be dead the only reason I'm
up and about like this is because of
that time shift Stone on the boat pH so
I have nothing to worry about I feel
better now link so so it's time for you
to go look for my ships I'll wait here
of course you stay I will be fine in
there but I don't quite trust
that because why would they why why
would they make it so
[Music]
easy should I buy this game well if you
like Z games and you enjoy me playing it
watching that then maybe
yes oh I hear SAS and there's also one
in that nose oh I think I just saw
it or is that just
a I I know that's just where is the
s whatuh oh there you are there you
are quiet everyone quiet
now no words just dreams hush
now
okay can we go inside
already oh heart
please
I didn't see that sand there
y
ma why the hell is there quick sand
right there why why why why
why okay oh thank you for that is there
anything
here no oh my
[Music]
God
[Applause]
why do I keep on piing fights with you
[Music]
guys it makes no
sense not it makes absolutely no sense
yeah
oh
okay I'm so done here I'm so done
[Music]
here
h
what is this place anyway how do I get
in
there I'm about to
[Music]
die wait do I so I don't see anything to
pull myself up
there why how do I get in
there I need some Heights by the
way
how surprising that they don't get blown
up if I pick them up like
that check the walls they
say I don't see anything on the
walls ah
o
dungeon is this considered a
dungeon master please take a
look this device looks like it is meant
to hold a Time shift Stone but there is
not one currently installed there's a
95% chance that is the same you think
you think I believe any of your stupid
percentages and
anymore the way
you messed with me just now with that
scorpion I don't believe a word you say
me
lady but okay you want me to get that
stupid time shift
Stone no
problem she's always wrong yeah the
whole look for daa she's over there I'm
sure of it it was all wrong it was
always too late
[Music]
oh God I only have five um okay you know
what I'll I'll actually use my
potion for once I will use my potion
[Music]
ah
yes I will hopefully not need it
anymore
[Music]
hello ah
oh they're fast oh
[Music]
God what they got fire oh my God they're
[\h__\h] me
[Music]
over okay oh thank
God oh my God that was uh a bit
unnecessary sorry for my shitty uh
fighting and my shitty controls okay I
see you I see you I see you I know what
you want you want my bump
huh y take this hey
quack quack she
says
even if you know how to deal with them
those are
annoying okay oh is that the one I'm we
supposed to take
that Master please take a look even
though it's obvious but look at it look
in enhance this object is called a Time
shift orbs I conjecture that unlike the
time shift Stones we've seen this device
was designed to be carried around and
installed in different
locations ah
useful I shall take it
oh
o oh that's cool I really like the
design of this place oh here
uh uhuh
you are too
weak I shouldn't even be fighting
you that's
like waste of time for me another one
you want to
fight you couldn't do [\h__\h] without your
electricity thingy you would be useless
without it
mhm so is this actually actually
considered the fifth
dungeon cuz someone just said the
dungeon is cool does this mean this is
the fifth
dungeon oh de oh oh oh
ah no pretty dungeon God damn
it um I'm in a bit of a pickle
now oh no not this [\h__\h]
again
finally I had my hand hand on the right
side like this but it every time I was
like about to stand up again it it would
only be on this side even though I have
my hand here you know what I mean pisses
me off that's why you can never recover
that easily once it hits you really
annoys
me
spin oh yeah I could
spiny oh yeah I could buy the the thing
the the the the the the the
thing aha oh
[Music]
flower I want to go up
there oh m
I can throw it
too go
[\h__\h] no go just go down
normally anything else ah another oh
nice
okay you can oh I can't jump of it
oh not a hold
[Music]
I
a
[\h__\h] sorry we have to do it
[Music]
again okay okay go then to this side and
then to that side and then to this side
and then oh [\h__\h] sorry we have to do it
again go go go go my platforming skills
are showing and they are
non-existent okay I'll do it
slowly and
Y easy first try
y
ah I I mean I could roll now wait maybe
I can open the that door from this side
oh
yes I understand yeah would not be good
at Mario well well well I played Super
Mario 64 and Super Mario Sunshine on my
channel and I have to say sometimes
sometimes I was good remember when I was
killing the samper killing was I killing
him I don't know but
um uh I did a good job at that one I
would say
oh hey
what oh do I just run I guess I just run
go go go go go you can do it
link did you finish them no but never
I've never said I
would if you want to see someone finish
those games watch Amelia
Watson she'll make you happy for
[Music]
sure
I watched a clip that she uploaded
today it was so funny I guess that's
just a clip from one of her
streams I loved
it I hope you guys saw it
too I wonder if that's what she uh hired
those uh clippers for like a while ago
quite a while
ago oh my God can you
[Music]
not oh
dear oh dear okay let's deal of them I'm
[Applause]
[Music]
here okay free at once is a little bit
tough
[Music]
okay this is easy easy easy
clap bombs I could have to I like the
Parry I like the
Parry okay these [\h__\h] are really
giving me a hard
time yes I hope this stays yes stay the
skeleton
[Music]
good what are you
doing why is there so
[Music]
many so many of
them I'm just trying to pass through
okay that was I mean that was pro pro
gamer move got to say
that small Ian with regular Ian
collab by the way
the
the oh never
mind uh where do I go first where do I
go first I don't know where to go first
is this close when I go there no oh
God haha you can't go here can
you uhhuh was that something I wanted to
do
oh oh yeah yeah yeah yeah uh oh I need
to I need a box so well I I'll kill you
from here from the future and you die in
the
past no future for
you
uh-oh a
frog all the way
around is what I'm looking at here not
future is this not the F uh the the past
I mean and this is the
future that's the way I I understood
it it's time travel sure
easy well yes for
[Music]
me I am right okay okay that's what I
thought so I kill him in the future that
makes him dead in the
past oh do I even a yes I need to bother
with him
okay
this
uh go go go go go okay
nice oh
God stop
an give me hearts come
on come
on I need
hearts come on
[Music]
please Hearts where hearts hearts
hearts fairy give me thank
you I already have one fairy in a bottle
so I don't think there was a need to
capture it I why did I do that oh my
[Music]
God
okay oh no what's happening what what
what what are you telling
me Skyward try to knock down the shocky
boys without touching the Sparky
stick okay I like the way you you
described all of
[Music]
that I could use some Heights
I could really use a heart right now H
right now H right
now can you believe oh
no oh
no did you guys just see what I I saw
these
boys oh
no okay K just be calm when you're calm
you can do it right if you you can do it
you can wait what what do I want me to
do I can't pass through maybe if I roll
it
what does that do
anything I don't know I can't roll with
much at
all oh wait this one
disappears oh different room ah okay
okay okay well let me carry uh this
inside then maybe they can help
me oh what the hell is
[Music]
this
I thought those were those robot
friends oh my God give me a breaking
[Music]
break
a that is the one perfect spot isn't it
I'm not ready to fight those boys right
now though I need I need help what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
well we have a fairy I'm going to
survive but I might need to go back to
skyop afterwards if there's much more
danger waiting
afterwards okay how do I find those
boards again with the with the windy
thingy right and then I stab stabby stab
yes
okay okay I guess uh they're going to be
activated when I do this
all the door stays open okay now I can
get the the the this one and I'll wake
them up purposefully I guess I can fight
one at time oh that's true that's true
there we go
hi let's get ready to
rumble
hello
[\h__\h] okay oh okay okay okay oh I almost
had it actually ah I wonder if you can
do it in one
[Laughter]
turn okay okay okay okay I got him I got
him I got him I got him I got
him on to the next
[Music]
one
go go go
go go I'm ready wake wake him up wakey
wakey wakey okay
hello friend you're a friend
right hey
okay if you're fast enough I think you
can do it in one in one in one
go yeah okay that was not that bad
oh than
[Music]
G I got please no more enemies please no
more trouble
please
o o
thank you for the membership thank
[Music]
you oh my God I report Master the power
of the time shift orb appears to have
caused a change in the
structure I recommend going outside to
further assess the situation I was going
to don't need to tell me that uh
um okay do I not need the orb
anymore uh
uh-huh
[Music]
okay he wants to talk to me but I don't
want to talk to her I want
to I have information to report Master
please take a
[Music]
look there's a 60% that's pretty
low you're even wrong with 95% you want
me to trust the 60%
probability H there's a 60% probability
that these masks and these Sails are
from the ship that protects n's
flame you can now set your dowsing
ability to search for the ship that
holds nao's Flame
uhhuh isn't it right here in front of
me anyway I want to go back to Skyla to
heal
myself and get a new potion
maybe and oh yeah update my my my
thingy if you know what I
mean sounds like a plan oh yeah we can
go to oh wait is there a cube here and I
can activate before I go
like wasn't there one up there what can
I reach it right now grab the kill first
uh-huh ah wait I
think maybe if I grab that and then I
grab this
[Music]
yeah that was easy
okay I see you were in the sky
[Music]
then okay back to
Sky
mhm and save once as
well
yeah how many languages can you speak I
speak my my first language is German my
second language is English and my uh
third one is
Japanese taught Japanese myself learned
English in
school yeah stamina potions you think I
need stamina
potions it I wasn't planning on getting
any stamina potions do you think I'll
need them for this
dungeon you don't need
okay okay oh wait a second ah two over
[Music]
there have you been there
before okay let's go
[Music]
can I fly through this one no of course
not can speak Spanish
[Music]
nope unfortunately
not a tiny bit of Italian
though oh wait it's right here
right when I don't see
it was
here ah it's
not ah that one up
there my uh thingy was not very accurate
what is that am I supposed to land on
that
no what what the hell is
it ah here there it
is okay okay okay
okay yeah that's not
happening
a yeah that was
funny
[Music]
navigation oh my God I'm getting dis it
in where the hell is
[Music]
it above
me
[Music]
[Applause]
you deserve that link you deserve
that hi hi hi hi hi
hi hi
[Music]
hi
H it's only been 3 hours and it feels
like I've been playing for 6 hours
today who needs
that yeah okay what
now m
[Music]
ah okay I was confused there for a
moment so wait there's one more where ah
I know where I hang
[Music]
down you better have
some something
useful okay okay calm down calm
down don't be so angry at the game the
game didn't do anything
[Music]
wrong I mean you could have better
motion controls but
[Music]
no one needs
that
okay that's it uh okay back to skyloft
we
go and I'm on one and a half hearts this
whole
time
painful very very much pain
part time
youtiful
[Music]
but that's a
heart that was the heart
container I don't know for some reason
it looked like a Heart Medal to me one
of those heart medals that was a heart
[Applause]
container no it
wasn't yeah it's just a heart metal okay
why didn't why are a bunch of people
like freaking out because yo it's a hard
container though y it was a hard metal
right yeah yeah no it's not a hard
container what am I saying it was a hard
[Music]
metal I mean yeah if I have it then I
guess I get one more heart but that's a
hard metal not a hard
[Music]
container h
H stream heart
[Music]
metal first of all get me some of those
hearts yeah that feels good sit on that
goddamn bench right now and Fe better
not talk to me right
now if she wants me to die then
okay I understand but you would think
that she doesn't want
[Music]
that you carry a chair with him yeah or
just sit on the [\h__\h]
ground why does he not just have the
ability to sit on the
floor
M okay what do we
want I guess we could check for upgrades
and then for
[Music]
potions blue bird feather
[\h__\h] bird feather blue
[Music]
for but don't I get like a like a new
Shield any
anywhere after the
[Music]
dungeon have nothing that I can
upgrade
nice hat thank
[Music]
you oh new Shield is from Cy oh
okay I thought I get a shield upgrade
from the
dungeon oh
H am I mixing up some
things anyway
yeah want a heart potion
[Music]
please yes please thank
you
uhhm
mhm
no anything
else ah
beetle
beetle oh where are
[Music]
you
bill can get me to the nest but how how
how how how how how how
how give me give me me thanks for the
membership
[Music]
welcome
H just wait for him to fly over
M
[Music]
okay
okay but won't that take a long
time well the island is uh the The Nest
is that one over there so I just Camp
here okay we'll wait a little bit
hopefully he comes soon oh
beetle beetle waiting for Beetle as
well calm down come on don't be
shy now not try not try
ity come on come
on you're up too
high Roll On The
Wall yo that's so
smart
oh get though where is he he's coming
he's on his
way
M how do I do
this
yeah that better be the right
[Music]
spot I never gotten this
what no
there's two ways to get in there so one
of them should
be
manageable um please one more please one
more
please please I am an idiot I can't help
it back
back Jumping from the island is easy
what
really you're telling me that this is
going to be a difficult
is your headache better yes but I kind
of need to go to an idle
meeting I need to get like on top of the
roof right I'm
guessing I can't
though I'm about to
here how would
I does it circle around this building
and then I would be able to jump there
from here I missed the timing for God's
sake is it too late or too
early are you going to circle
[Music]
it R Val wrong down the game
buddy you're not going to circle it
huh
okay okay uh never mind
[Music]
then never never mind I'm all right I
don't I don't need
it you need the platform to be lined
[Music]
upy
okay ah switching to the Pro Controller
just for diving down that actually
sounds like it could work better yeah
but
we are going back to the sand land land
of sand sea sand sand
sea uh here we're going
here and when we arrive I
go to an idle meeting for 2 minutes if
that's okay for you guys oh and I have I
have chocolate milk in the fridge and
iced tea and I want one of those I'm not
sure which one I'm in the mood for
though I want both should I mix them ice
choco
milk ice tea tea choco te choco iced tea
chocolo
milk absolutely not okay hey
rude do not mix them yeah you know what
I will not mix them I'm not crazy like
that I want to enjoy them one by one I'm
like one of those people that like when
there's like a dis a dinner or a meal or
whatever I usually when there's like
sides like like like like for example
potatoes and and veggies and stuff I eat
everything one by one like I don't I
usually I'm not the type to mix
everything and eat it like mixed I eat
first I
eat the thing that looks the
tastiest then I eat the thing that looks
the second
tastiest and then I eat the thing that
looks the third
tastiest
yeah
that is the correct way to eat really
who said that who said that hello hello
hello we're going to Pirate stronghold
right you let's
go The Best For Last I know I eat the
best
first all right guys I'll see you in 2
minutes I'm I'm going to be back soon
soon soon soon please stay please
[Music]
stay
e
[Music]
Cat
movie meow
byebye
[Music]
bye-bye
sorry I'm
back I brought iced
[Music]
tea
oh yeah that's the good stuff M I love
iced
tea love iced tea could drink it all day
every day let me check on my DMs real
quick I got some
DMS
uh
[Music]
okay all right
guys wow are you ready for the dungeon I
wonder how long this one will be but we
should be able to finish
it
right yes
let's
[Music]
go those are some funny
faces funny
[Music]
figures let's
go the fifth dungeon five out of
seven wa oh
no I am too slow oh
[\h__\h] oh what wait there's so many
here y
okay almost didn't see
them another one finally some justice
for taka Niki the beetle
collector am I supposed to go in here
isn't this where I came from am I
supposed to go up I think I'm supposed
to go up I came out of the that place
so that's
oh oh there oh that's not the next dunge
oh oh you're right I was supposed to use
dowsing H whatever
what
huh I'm supposed to go in the boat again
or
so it's not here
oh well that was antil climatic
climactic climatic climatic
climactic all right then you ready to go
sh
[Music]
go
M to
sing uh shut
up shut
up what you're saying this ship might
not be
visible you mean are you are you saying
Ghost
Ship are you saying that could be a
ghost
ship invisible
ship h happy birthday timy membership
expired so I would humbly like to
request the job title can't be fired and
disgruntled thank you for the red super
chat happy happy birthday to
you happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you happy birthday dear Timmy right
is it Timmy let me
see dear
Timmy happy birthday to you yeah oh dear
oh God oh God wait I need to I need to
fight
go go nice
okay oh there's so
many this is
fun I should play one of
those but bhips on the sea fighting war
games
fun yesterday actually I was going
through um
games uh on Steam I was looking for
co-op games that are kind of like um
like bomb diffusal game or I don't know
stuff like that you know easy quick
quick kind of cute fun
game
um and I didn't really find much that I
didn't already know
about really nothing at all to be honest
but
but I did find a game that I played
before and I kind of feel like playing
that one
too later alligator it's really
cute you guys might have seen I'm going
play it oh is that a shadow from the
ship
no I guess
not I'm just going crazy CU it's just
clouds yeah I was wondering if you guys
would like me to play it cuz I want to
play it so I guess it doesn't matter if
you guys want me to play it or not I'm
going to play
it
h later alligator is the name of the
game
it looks really cute like it's like a
it's a pretty simple
game but it's really really funny
apparently has a lot of humor and it's
like H they're very easy going click
click click a game you click lot of lot
of dialogue I
think there's that [\h__\h]
ship oh is it behind me I lost track of
it it's right
there I guess it really is
invisible
shoot is it not right
here I have this feeling it's right
here does it
move
[Music]
keeps on moving what the
hell how fast does it
move oh oh it's right it's right here I
saw it oh that's
cool I I saw it me get the
H wait wait what do I have to shoot
shoot it more
often huh
huh
[Music]
[Applause]
go freaking controls man
oh you can't run from
me y there we
go
[Applause]
[Music]
you oh ghost
chip
oh that's pretty cool I like that idea
yeah oo nice
shot
spoy
[Music]
time sand ship that's a ghost ship not a
sand
[Music]
ship interesting
music
okay well well well here we are we have
arrived I guess cuz I see stuff like
this we're going to play with like time
shift orbs
[Music]
again oh there's a hole here I can't go
up
here no there must be something for
yes h
wait a second can I activate
that no but I can probably maybe go up
the stairs like this the the not the
stairs the ladder
no I'm going to get there don't
[Music]
worry oh wait
there
right that reminds me of Super Mario
64 that room with the
teresas boohoo wait it's only Teresa in
Japanese I was confused a little bit now
right it's only Teresa in
Japanese the Boos yeah in in German we
call them boohoo too but for some reason
right now I thought it must be uh Teresa
in English no that was Japanese why did
I call that ghost
[Music]
Teresa I see I need to play my HP huh no
problem Bo come out of
there all
there you are
ah I think we want money uh last time
when I drew Hearts it turned into bombs
for some reason even though my drawing
was pretty good I would say but we want
money rupes okay I think I it worked
[Music]
before
so can I
redo that will be bombs right yeah
okay
um can I do it
again
yeah I get that one but I don't get the
one where I threw a heart and it turned
into bums that one made no
sense this is
sus sus dead end I don't believe it I
don't believe
it I
this this sign sus everything here
sus
SS this door is sus the bats are sus I'm
sus Fe sus that's for
sure M you want the bom
H that's okay I got more than enough of
them even though I wanted
money take them take
them
mhm okay I need to run over all
righty he self Fe
venting vote her out vote her out she's
sus obviously she's lying
always you wouldn't lie if you didn't
have anything to hide
[Music]
right a little bit of
cleaning what you dropped
jelly they dropped
jelly
ew oh my God what the [\h__\h] that is
cursed
[Music]
well this is a farm uh monster Farm exp
Farm PP let's
[Music]
go did I get all of
them don't hug me I'm not here for hugs
I mean I love hugs generally but I don't
need one from
you not the babies what can I do when
they attack me oh my best friend is over
there
huh what what do you want
yesy this large door here is sealed
shut this door must lead to an important
room in the ship um yeah
okay
okay I will have to get through all of
these doors anyway Fe are you real
[Music]
that okay I can still not activate T do
that's okay another open door okay
we'll have to deal with him when we go
back with the bosy I
suppose
uhuh
uhhuh interesting uhhuh is that supposed
to be some secret
code aha
red blue on that side
uh-huh
uhhuh sounds like a secret
coat
just cleaning minding my own business I
wonder if I wouldn't have uh cleaned up
here if this mob later would not
actually come back to
life oh wait a
second oh I have to the riddle is right
there you only have to hit the
bottom what
no sand will disappear so no effect oh
wait I think I understand cuz it turned
to that side now so now I have to hit
the left
side come on you can do it and now I
have to hit the top [\h__\h] yeah that's not
what I wanted I was trying to hit the
top okay okay so
bottom
left top right that's it
right oh faking
it that was such a good solution
though again maybe what I don't know
what you want from
me that's what I take from wait maybe I
clean up the other room as
well maybe that helps
okay wait a second maybe we find another
one of those S oh we find a lot of them
aha oh three of
them
[Music]
okay you walk around I don't know I
don't
know
[Music]
I don't
know why is
it
ah but from which direction do I look at
one two how do I look at it from this
time Direction so that would
be that would be
left
right uh left
down red is the upper part ah so
down
up
right wait what was that that
down up down right down up down right
down up down right no
way uh down up down
right that was
fast
n she doesn't add H at all no I do I do
I do I do oh
chest what do I get what did I get the
the the the ball the ball the time shift
ball no
okay okay it's just a small key okay
I'll take it I'll take everything I can
get to finish this dungeon ASAP uh do I
need that for the
store
no I guess I'll be coming back here
[Music]
soon don't be hasty
CH leave me alone leave me alone bad
friends one hit easy easy easy W look at
all those chests are those traps those
can't be real chests
right nah you can't fool
me
nah-uh so with backtracking cuz now we
got a key and I don't know where to use
it
[Music]
mhm
no wait can I turn
this I can yo wait should I have done
this before did I did I just ignore this
even though I should have gone somewhere
else does this open up something
what is this doing what is this
doing did it open the
door no I would have heard probably like
a sound like
[Music]
that wait but this must have some kind
of
meaning it just spins I'll understand
later
okay
a wait where do I use the
key I came from here
no perhaps the meaning is in the past oh
don't say something so cool
sounding it would show me on the map
right if there was a door that needs the
key
I don't
[Music]
understand uper floor was there a way to
get
up up up to the second
floor that's really not sense your [\h__\h]
path come
on the door need entrance
okay done ah
wait wait is this where I came
[Music]
from there it was there it was there it
was I think right that's that must yeah
that's it that's
it
aha knock knock who's there
Tak your
destiny
and you're destined to die oh
dear oh that's that's funny I see what
we're doing plank fight all righty hello
pirate
a oh dear he's got electric
[Music]
stuff this is
fun
H what happened to your electric
[Music]
stuff there that was easy it
must round
two ah easy easy easy
[Music]
easy oh you're getting more aggressive
okay
[Music]
Bud hey that was
fun oh surprised you lost your hand I'm
so sorry you need another hook huh it
seems you need another
[Music]
hook fun
fun fun fun
[Music]
fun that's the best fight I ever had in
this game
right very
decent master that synthetic life form
there is a 99% chance that it was a
pirate described by the captain I can't
help but admire the tenacity it has
displayed in staying alive and
functional all these
years okay cool cool Sorry
Fe fire ain't no match for
me
what that's very
interesting that's I'm I'm like super
surprised
okay I don't know why but like compared
to everything we got until now the bow
is like feels like something we should
have gotten
[Music]
[Laughter]
earlier master I report about the bow
you just you have just obtained your
both elasticity can Propel arrows for
the air with great force allowing you to
strike your targets from afar to confirm
the controls associated with your bow
Raise Your Bow by pressing z r and then
press right
okay you can also shoot arrows to strike
certain devices in order to activate
[Music]
them what the
[\h__\h] I have confirmed that such a device
exists on the
deck however it will be to Target it
from here so I recommend you return to
the deck yeah it's because for this
effect I have like an autotune effect on
and like it's I think it's works like
supposedly it adjusts my voice to
whatever B Jam playing on my PC
apparently so I don't know what it
adjusted my voice to just now
but it's like my voice cracked but but
like in a in a really weird
way all
right oh I don't want to waste it right
now
but I want to
shoot Tiana is back let's
[Music]
go so I have to go outside now that's
fine I'm right
here so
uh how accurate do I have to be with
this aha oh wait can I zoom
ah
wow okay so it zooms in if I charge
it aha I think I can shoot that from
down here master I have important
information for you there is a 90%
chance
[Music]
you sure it's not
100% I think I think it's drifting why
you drifting
there we
go oh no I never said slingshot is
useless wow back in
[Music]
time you don't want me to shoot that
again huh oh dear we can't go inside
anymore oh well we'll fight everyone
outside then
yay
[Music]
a come let's have a paty y
y never had so many issues with one of
you
guys
[Music]
okay it's so colorful I really like the
look of this
o I like the look of this uh boat is
what I wanted to say oh thank you 10
arrows oh but my maximum is 20 oh
yeah can I go anywhere with that am I
ever going anywhere with
that I need a key here I see I see okay
but I think I need to go to the other
side
oops can I wait a no I think
I did I miss something just
[Music]
now climb the mask
oh I guess I can now
[Music]
yeah what do we have up
there oh
dear get rid of
you oh oh thank
you I just had a much more difficult
enemy who did the same thing to me
but you want to play the same game huh
oh
[Music]
dear can we
yo I'm not even moving and you can't hit
me huh weak
boom head
shot boom head
shot yeah
baby you guys want to get hit
too makes it easier for me I
this
[Music]
oh that was not a head shot that was
something else I'm sorry about that
buddy who who's still shooting
me where's that coming from ah what no
he doesn't have an arrow but
[Music]
anyway there we go what someone's
shooting
me ah from up there
ah oh so
[Music]
yes could be wor to go back to
um [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
sake to go back
to the
shop oh my
God to get an upgrade and be able to
carry more arrows yeah
[Music]
oh my
God stop
stop stop
[Music]
moving
can I not hit it from
[Music]
here
oh that was below
though that felt like it was below the
target but okay oh wa there's one down
there
too should I hit that one too right now
I will I
will if it would stop moving that
[Music]
much okay I was trying to hit the middle
but the side seems fine as well okay so
that's probably for later okay okay we
activated everything that I could see I
think
now we can hang on to that
[Music]
ah joyon dto the one type of dto that we
don't
like I only have three
[Music]
left we should upgrade the the arrow
thingy I trying to go up
there
huh uh two
oh God I got to make these
count oh come
[Music]
on and that one counts
really no I don't quite agree with that
but okay I kind of wanted to shoot that
one down before I went up but I have no
choice I hope he gives me
arrows hey
[Music]
buddy
no
he yeah he dropped a
rupe what do we have
here what do you what you do is stick in
my
oh
[Music]
huh
huh was I supposed to know some secret
code for this
or do I come back later with the secret
code I push afterwards
uh ah oh I was moving my hand but it's
just press a okay all right all right
all right thank good job yeah yeah thank
you now the ship looks just like it used
to that makes me so happy now I just
need you to go rescue my vep I'm pretty
sure they're being held in the brick
inside the sheep sheep sheep sheep vep
ah did you just give me the map for the
dungeon uhuh okay it's still pretty
dangerous but you can do it
beep rescue my seep please
beep okay
um I wonder if I can afford an upgrade
as in if I have the materials for it
Where Do We Go From Here we just jump
[Music]
down thank God you don't need an arrow
for that
one but I can't reach it how would I
reach
that from
here yeah baby
[Music]
oh what am I
doing uh do I want
to drop down
here what
now okay that's it chest and a Bo boing
aha I found something
precious
yay van heart
container now I got a new heart finally
I think
yeah that was uh that was uh yeah oh no
wait we got one last time oh no okay I'm
confused ignore whatever I'm
[Music]
saying o o o why is it why is he not
coming there he is oh can I get rupes
this time please come
on or wait can I ask for
arrows how uh I I would I would guess
it's drawing an
everal but like what does this I cannot
let go right I have to do it in one ah
wait oh
God oh
God don't get me Crooked Arrows no that
is not a heart you [\h__\h] kidding me
this game is rigged no no no
no I mean that was that didn't look like
a arrow either but still still though
I never get what I want from these
things it's sad very very
sad never get what I want pain yeah how
was that a heart if anything that could
have been a bump because someone wasti
something was sticking out there you
must be kidding
me if I draw bombs I'll get arrows
probably yeah that would make sense
right so anyway we're going back to
skyloft we're going back so often right
now oh my God I can't even go
back wait but is there wasn't there a
safe but I have to go
[Music]
outside
inside but it doesn't that count as
inside a dungeon and then it tells me to
go
outside
oh
okay
[Music]
okay I am here what do you
want
what M my body
my
body
feels exhausted um I
need is there going to be a safe statue
over there underneath the ship cuz I
need
no why is it all
reset
no tell me I'll have to do all that
again later
on I I I need to I need to I need to go
back up where is the
closest statue chipyard wait did I get
shown ancient Harbor I
suppose I can just hit the stone with
the arrow okay okay okay
okay
let me please go
backwards I want to see if I can get an
upgrade uh
hello I today today my joy joycons
really are acting a little bit
weird I don't know
[Music]
why
s CL
[Applause]
down no my my dog is really close recal
you mean the why I keep on doing that I
am doing it but
still they act weird nonetheless why did
I do that why did I do that I didn't
want to press that I wanted to press
X go birdie go
[Applause]
[Music]
non
Joy
uh I don't know I don't know about the
drift you guys seem to to know more
about that than
me
okay
upgrade hey
please please tell me you can do it come
[Music]
on okay but wait that's uh that's not
the ah that just upgrades the bow but I
maybe do you have what I need yester do
this is what I
want five more okay 150 for
that wow I'm I'm broke man I'm
broke ah five more I mean that's
actually quite a lot in if you think
about it five already makes a big
difference so shall we go to the desert
quickly to get some tumble
[Music]
weeds I would need two tumble weeds in
order to do an upgrade it's not that
much we can do that fairly quickly
upgrade the quiv I can upgrade the
quiver wait let me see what I need from
the was an antique lady now a AF the
quiver okay
okay okay I'll see if I can do
that
hey oh
[Music]
upgrade
ah I can do
it and I very very kidy Kitty have
enough money for
it one ruy left I think it's time to go
to the antique
lady can I skip this
good cutting it
close it was all calculated all
according to my
Kaku saying that a lot
today yeah yeah yeah shut
up wow we've got some like
blue blue decoration now wait what
happens if
I no okay these are see see if you don't
want me to break your stuff then you got
to you know secure them like
this no I take no
complaints we got a
new we got a new chest
there uh anti lady is there I think
could be wrong CIO no not
CIO
[Music]
was it the other house right
there no was there was no
[Music]
house M be
there one of
those I suppose that
is O sh on the
bir no PE
no this
one I
think all right let's
go you're
welcome oh you broke my precious
untake that was a pretty expensive item
so you're going to have to pay me about
20 rupees and I didn't just made that
number up
but you don't even have enough to pay oh
that live then I
just what what have on me what yeah yeah
that works for me wait what if I break
some
more no how could you ew did I do
something horrible to you in a past life
what hi
J oh baby hi
you why are you punishing like this look
I already know you don't have even a
thing a r name so stop breaking things
get out of
here can I break some I can still break
this
[Music]
[Laughter]
plant
what a great day what a beautiful day
what a wonderful
day yeah tanos
tanos oh
wonderful
I smash all the pots oh why is your
house so clean I came to make some money
useless useless absolutely
useless Ching my inner
cat okay let's go back I guess wait I
how many arrows do I have anyway right
now so 10 okay 10 where did I get 10
from okay let's hope I get more over
there cuz I don't have any money to buy
any I five I got five on the upgrade and
five on the F
ahuh wait do I want to go get some
tumble
[Applause]
weats don't really don't really need the
actual bow upgrade right so at least not
now so let's go back
to Desert oh I forgot to get the chest
God damn it oh
[Music]
well I want to clear this
dungeon next time for the next uh zaa
stream I think before the stream I'm
going to try to do some side quests so
at least we don't have to do that on
stream if that's okay for you
guys
um yeah going I do some side quests but
besides that I think I will I will do no
more I mean I would like to so that we
don't have to do so much on stream but
in the end I'm going to like I'm going
to have sorry I moved the microphone I'm
going to have to play the game anyway so
it doesn't matter if I do it off stream
or on stream I guess
except for the fact that it's a bit
exhausting to talk so much wait I
cannot I cannot teleport to the boat so
I guess ancient Howard would be the
smartest to get on my
boat okay glad you're having fun with
Skyward Sword well yeah generally I'm
having fun there's a lot of frustrating
moments in this game but it is kind of
worth it because it's still
fun I I am honest with you
guys I am enjoying
it oh are you going to give me a
shortcut oh well that's okay see that's
smart that's nice that's very nice of
you I appreciate that very
much wa I have to shoot
something oh there it is could I not hit
it with my
[Music]
beetle
that's a long way to go I feel like it's
not
impossible um let me try
[Music]
again no go straight
upwards
ah so
close okay whatever I do it a
slingshot
okay all the enemies are back well maybe
they dropped me some
arrows
[Music]
no no arrows for me oh man that sucks
arrows yo let's
go there we go now we're talking okay
how do I enter this place again where am
I supposed to go in
here am I supposed to go in here he
wants me to rescue his friend his crew
mates now
right okay let's do this oh wait I was
here before no this is another I need to
go down I think yep oh was there any
secret here by the
way no doesn't look like
[Music]
it y homies are you funny
y
homies oh I see this in color which way
do we want to
go must be this way has to
be yeah I saw some of them dead before
too yeah yeah I mean dead as in
older not nice not
nice yeah thank you for that
[Music]
so sick of you electric
dudes oh my
[Music]
God what Fe is trying to tell me
something I don't want to listen but
okay let's see what is it Master look
uhhuh uh okay okay that's actually maybe
a nice hint
okay but I might have to hit it from
here in order to get through that
electric
spot
okay
uh there we go somewhere from up there
still shooting at me I saw an arrow
flying at
me can you go for a door link or
not useful for people of tunnel vision
that is true so people like me oh
dungeon map
okay uh-huh oh secret
rooms or not so secret they're not
really secret I've seen
them okay I want to turn it back though
I think that's probably the way to
go cuz all doors were closed anyway in
the future so let me go A Link to the
Past Link to the Past there we
go it's a funny reference isn't it
because you know keep it off
oh hopefully not that the
whole a link to the Future that one
doesn't work well cuz that's not a
game that doesn't work well I don't like
it
m why did I why am I why am
I why am
I aren't the doors closed like
this
faster why would I want
that the
fan now I can shoot
through through the calm down link drama
queen
aha could I not have done this in the
past that's not oh
God
hello nice
shot 10 out of
heart to
sneeze
[Music]
T ahuh I can shoot that from here I
think
probably you guys leave me alone I want
that I want that sorry I have to get
that before it
disappears um
hello
okay now I'm ready to
shoot oh thank you for this need chest
oh wait I can't actually get it from
here
okay uhhuh from here
but
oh
a From Below wait from below from here
through
that
ah oh wait wait I have to stand on
it ah y
[Music]
chill
wow bless you thank you
g that's not how you spell that oh I
already shot that one before okay wait
did something open up the other door
from
oh from that
side that sounds like a like a um
chemical object thingy chemical
thingy like I don't know pyronite or
something like that which is funny cuz
pirate P pirate night Pirate no it's not
funny I was I was trying to make
connections okay what is this what do I
do
here huh wait do I have to shoot
anything from
[Music]
here gun the sneeze
element wait did I miss something
stick this in that didn't look I thought
that okay that didn't look like to me
that I could stick something in but
okay I got to see it from a different
point of
[Music]
[Laughter]
view I can't I can't stick it in I
can't me hi baby
hi
baby you're too far away I can't hit you
from here got to come here
[Music]
chunkers you want the belly pets don't J
but you got to get closer I'm going to
come closer no I can't I can't I can't
stick it in
wait I can't do it hi CH
hi hi
baby you're such a weirdo I can't do it
time Stone time Stone and now you want
me to turn it back
on
uhhuh okay oh
will that was was that that
door where was
that here
okay back to the link to the past yes
yes yes
yeah
shoot
[Music]
nice and then o we can enter that room
oh dear
hello obliterate
it I wish I could fight you from here
come closer come here come here try me
try
me
[Music]
that's funny that's
funny uh oh yeah now I can stick it
in
PR
wow everything activated let's freaking
go everyone care be we winning as always
y master I'm detecting very strong
vibrations not the good kind signs
indicate that activating this mechanism
has caused something within the ship to
begin moving the current situation is
difficult to accurately assess but I
suggest hurrying to the crew in the
break and Fring them
first
uh yeah that was my
plan
uh I find it
interesting that if I open the doors in
the future they are also open in the
past I find that ironic do I also have
to do something in this
room the cut scene oh wait what happens
if I do this in the in the past
nothing
really what did something wait did
something something did move but like
the
like I can't see [\h__\h]
ah sure I I I would need to put
something on
there I'm done here okay okay let's see
ah wait wait this door is open oh
what when did you open up oh
[Music]
hello oh come
on sometimes my Panic moves the fast
ones work better than when I slowly try
to attack them oh happy birthday happy
birthday
okay Buton
o thank you for the membership
[Music]
welcome okay that's enough I
think we can see the
sea
funny let's go
down where am I
[Music]
going ooh
ooh that's with the electric sound and
those thingies on the on the walls here
reminds me of Super Mario
Sunshine I don't know why but that level
from the amusement
park thanks for the membership
welcome enjoy I guess you're gifting
yourself a birthday present and that is
the membership I think that's a good
choice wait I can't do [\h__\h] here should
I have H
turn back to the oh wait I see you maybe
I can shoot through these holes to do
[Music]
something of course I can of course I
can not sure what though the lamp there
the lamp need to be turned
on
area is what go
back
okay the whip
oh I guess that doesn't
work I think the whip doesn't work
through um these kind of slim
uh think yeah it's a bit too too far
away that's too far
away uh thank you for the Super Chat
what no I didn't say anything I didn't
no you were deceived I didn't say
anything
was it the other window I had to look
through oh yes it was oh I'm on the
little boat now oh but it doesn't do
anything for me
either how if I look
up
no
is that other door open
[Music]
now
no think
boss I'm
trying I go
down oh no I already went
huh do I want to cut the
[Music]
robes
oh my
God
hi what do you see
I
MH oh
that's yeah it was a little bit
difficult to see in that
angle can't blame me come on wait wait
wait don't matter wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait let me
drink some I
[Music]
see
okay
so we are outside now now
what I don't have a key do I
mhm
so many arrows
everywhere nice can I shoot like from I
can't even get up there come on link was
able to go up higher spots
before do I need to activate wait do I
want to go back to the future by
activating this
first then activating the
boat oh yeah chat is saying the same
thing
n
it's getting very uh complicated
here oh my God
yes Back to the
Future wait there was a movie that's
called that
right there's a movie that has that
title
no can I move this no I can go through
here now yo
but I can't stick it in here uh unless
it's the past I can only stick it in in
the
past but I can open the door from here
no no but but but but I see it yes yes I
see I
see leave me alone I'm
busy there we go now I go outside hi hi
baby hi chunkers
hi what you
want what is it you desire is it Snick
snacks or is it belly
pets a skylight I
what byebye
[Music]
baby I don't see
[\h__\h]
it ah there it
is
and we'll always love my cats
o my cats are so
cute
uh-huh m
[Music]
master I'm detecting strong vibrations
again the current situation is difficult
to accurately assess but I suggest
hurrying to the area beneath the crew in
the
breakast yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah you
this the second time you tell me
that so what what I I mean what what
where do you want me to go
tell me again tell me again
fee you you want me to go down here
right
window where are
we there's a
fire wait are those chests available now
or
not important thing to clear up first
no out there oh he doesn't see me he
doesn't see
me oh no oh no I didn't have any
stamina other than that it would have
been
perfect well no chest for me just
yet that door is
open
interesting oh yeah oh yeah is this
there's another Open Door is this place
not interesting for me yet you guys told
me to go to the
window but this place I can continue
here
too oh there's nothing here
oh electric therapy that sounds like
something I would want to try out though
that shoot down was from here
activate something there
door oh there you guys
are you're a human and so how did you
get in here
be you came with Captain to save us we
I'm so happy but we can't go out of here
while that Sparky thing blocks the
exit Rescue Mission I almost forgot to
mention it but the engine room is right
below this break
mhm uhhuh yeah yeah I understand I
understand there's a car that from the
engine room that connects this breake
room please let me out I haven't seen
Mar SEL in a long time and I really miss
looks like the engine room is up and
running boom did you turn on the power
be yes it did okay then I'm sure you can
get through the engine room to here now
ah I will be waiting for
we
I want to see my 30y old horny Central
please come
[Music]
on I understand don't
worry window window
window window it
is who is only 17 yes yes of course
in in in Phoenix age that would be 30
yes that's why I said that uh which form
has the
[Music]
windows uh
ah this
one I'm
confused oh I'm in the wrong room
[Music]
ders
baby there's these times where she like
sleeps all the time and then there's
times where she just really really comes
checking up on me several times because
she obviously want wants belly pets and
love and attention she's like stop
playing games now Mommy please
[Music]
please
oh oh oh
I
understand oh my
God finally we need the other things as
well
what do I just want to go to the other
side or do I want to go to there I I
want to try to get there I wish I was
that cat a lot of people wish they were
my cats Wait no that's not going to work
is it cuz it keeps on stopping me over
there a lot of people wish they wear my
cats thank you for the
membership oh oh I can just fall down
here
okay I thought that was the
abyss can you blame them no I mean I
would even like to be my own
cat because you're so Floy and live the
best
life and soft and
ah do I want to go that way
o adrenalin let's go no no no no no no
no no no no no no or do I want to go I
don't know
no why is that thing for the whip there
do I want to go on top
P
hello oh my
God I think the ones would to go on top
of
them [\h__\h] or does it not otherwise there
would the the thing ah I need to go on
top of it because over there it will
serve as a platform for getting to the
other side okay I think I
understand
wait okay
yes
uh ah when it's down I jump down I
suppose this one moves much faster or
slower faster this one moves faster ah
just don't listen to me just don't
listen to
me the door is open my dear crew mates
what is this
hole
uhhuh no time to waste link Fe is going
to be mad again and we're scared of
Fe what I opened up no you're free guys
you really came to save us my circuits
are glooming glowing with happiness
Bo really you came on board to find N's
flame if you want to reveal a n's flame
you have to go you're going to have to
regain control of the ship the control
room is next to the break but it's huge
door is still charge and you'll need a
key to open it oh maybe you guys are the
key your hats look kind of suspicious
first you should head to the captain's
cabin the control room key is should be
in there don't use us as the key
please that's harassment please don't do
it please take this key as a p oh small
key a
[Music]
than you can get to the captain's cabin
through a door on the deck in the back
what or a door on the deck in the back
or a door in in the deck in the back
what you free enjoy your
[Music]
freedom the
crew it's free wait I saw only one
leaving wasn't there more than one in
there anyway
anyway
[Music]
you it ain't over
yet it ain't over just
yet when I reach free what do you mean
are you not happy with your life at
kfp are you not
happy uh do we have any more business
here or can I go back
up I need to go back there I feel like
there was something over
there yeah that that room over there
right [\h__\h]
no oh wait oh oh I'm scared
ah
wait ouch wait where am
I become a
Patty become as
Patty come
on oh my
[Music]
God become
pancake
oh is that the door where I wanted to go
to I mean I've been here before but
there seems to be one room that I
haven't visited
yet no actually never mind that's just
outside
oh I'm so
confused I am confused but okay go back
treasure I missed it so I was not wrong
after
all
anything
here I missed the
[Music]
treasure go back so you can get the
other path in the engine
room it's on the
swing this place this place is confusing
me
swing
[Music]
this way which not this
way okay but I have to go this way right
H wait wait but can I even go that way
cuz like the furthest one in the back
will come down and stomp me by the time
I am over
there oh man I'm I'm
exhausted too much brain
power what the hell that was my Pro
Controller
oopsie BL being stomped will
work
really really I'll give it a try then if
you say
so
Elder over there I see I see
[Music]
it
you were
right it seemed like I couldn't get
enough uh movement out of this still
when I was trying
to get to this side but I will
try okay it was
enough and I just really not TRS are
those really not
[Music]
traps wait the the sound is crackling
again why the [\h__\h] are you crackling
again let
go another
one there not is one of them a trap is
only one of them a trap
[Music]
am I being too suspicious I don't know
this looks suspicious so can you blame
[Music]
me okay the middle one is left they're
all safe
what what pirate loot oh let's
go okay this one is not so special but
okay thank you very much for this nice
treasure yeah we wouldn't want to have
missed out on that one huh wait can I go
back from here do I want to go back from
here does it
matter wait no I can't go back but do I
want to go left or right from here
uh right
May
that kill
[Music]
me mass it's like a massage you
know at this point it feels nice getting
my bones cracked and stuff
M
yeah uh ah I can just pass through right
ah oh my God
scared die and revive
Just Like a Phoenix link are you a
phoenix like
me at the moment it looks like it you
can't really deny it
link and you don't need
[Music]
to where am I now aha the
window
okay so we have the small key for the
door that leads to to the boss key and
that will lead us to the boss door so
small key I use a
[Music]
logo Coco this n so I am currently in B1
I want to go
[Music]
upstairs up up up I want to go right
from B1 to one F okay
can I go upstairs
here what a is that from outside
accessible on the deck where am
I where the hell am I
aha I
here oh man what do you guys think of
the boss for this dungeon is it a good
one
am I going to have troubles with
it
easy why are there some weird answers
epic not as good as gck does pretty
[Music]
fun Zelda bosses are easy yeah
generally generally once you have an
idea of how they work it's so easy and
you're usually able to figure out so
fast how they
work boss design is hectic oh dear I'm
always hectic even if the boss design
isn't hectic so that's going to be fun
which door am I going
for the other one this
one Health bch
yeah uh over there okay outside huh no
need to pick a fight with me me not
weing you
little I just said down on the H
fch okay your friend will pay for that I
will kill your
friend at least you'll have someone to
hang out
with in the
Underworld if you even have an afterlife
you know bad people don't might not get
that one hit
wow ah here we are wait let let's get
some stuff from
here
[Music]
okay open
up oh
yeah
uhhuh
[Music]
uh uhhuh hi friends hi can I like shoot
you from here can I shoot into his eye
from
here would be fun if I
could if only this wouldn't move so
much
[Music]
it
works what it explodes just like that
the whole thing yo that's
[Music]
fun wait a second a
it wait a second I we supposed to shoot
something here
anyway huh does that one do I have to go
here uh uh after first Going Back to the
Future
outside I think
so that's the only
[Music]
way oh shut
up shut
up that's why it's the last weapon
ah cuz it's so strong
it's funny though cuz like in most s
games it's like such a basic weapon that
you maybe even have from the beginning
from the
GetGo or or like as the first dungeon
item or so I mean I could be wrong maybe
I'm just maybe I'm just uh remembering
it wrong
[Music]
but hello oh oh they're dead here oh
well I killed one in
the in the past so now in the future it
doesn't exist that's
[Music]
nice okay
um
oh but that thing is in the
way uh
[Music]
uh stop that's not going to work wait a
second what if I ah Sky
ah mhy mhy which way is
that which way is
it
hello
[Music]
hello I don't see
anything there it is there it is there
it
is
shut
ah
okay
hey hey hey hey link focus focus not on
this one are you [\h__\h]
stop oh my God oh my God I'm I'm going
to I'm going to go mad I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm mad I'm I'm really
mad right now can
[Music]
you okay that
Dad I wish you could I mean maybe you
can but I don't I wouldn't know about it
how to switch my
focus I wanted to focus on the [\h__\h]
thing here in the
middle oh there's another one here I'm
going I'm going to take care of
you oh look over here
friend look look look over here my AR
Arch Enemy come on
quickly release and press set
L too late for
that why did you see that shot
yo did you see
that
y
maybe FPS game are just my destiny and I
just didn't know
yet maybe it's my fate maybe I was
always maybe I I'm going to be a pro
player if I oh
dear if I play FPS
games oh
baby
[Music]
die
oh P's Instinct sleeps within you yeah
might really be true that might be
[Music]
true there's
potential Apex with Vol
no no no
Apex no
Apex all right we have the
key we have the boss key uh wait is
there a bench what hell is bench is it
upstairs
we got
it
ah you got
the ID how many times do I have to kill
[Music]
you Hearts would be nice too I only get
arrows
now uh where the hell is the
bus inside here
right s only
nice bench
first drink some ice tea everyone H
duration time and then we go to the bus
yayay
Borderlands Borderlands RPG yeah I think
I've looked at one up before
I think I checked that one out
before okay
safe tomb ra yeah yeah we wanted to do
that one
[Music]
too well well the
future is always near always one step
ahead of us who knows maybe in the
future I'll be playing one of those
games which way which way which
way where is the boss door here we are
currently in one F I want to go down two
floors
[Music]
okay where are the stairs to go down
here horor game face gooda again wrote
to me
yesterday she's really eager about uh
Outlast I'm really scared the more she
asks me the more I'm scared she asked me
yesterday like what are we doing can we
do it next week and I was like no next
week is so busy like we have the
anniversary and I don't have the heart
monitor thingy yet so I told her maybe
the week after that but I'm not looking
forward to
it but she's I don't know why she's
never been like so eager to do like a
collab of me like I mean I mean she
didn't dislike doing collabs with me but
she's never been so eager that on her
own she would like continue reminding
me I don't know why she she's not even
the one playing I don't know why she
wants me to do it that
bad okay we already saved right so let's
go looks like a skull oh that's pretty
no actually it isn't pretty looks like a
tentacle key I don't know looks
weird looks weird what the hell is this
disgusting it looks like those uh sucky
thingies from
[Music]
Pentacles well this going to take a
while everyone lean
back oh what about this what about this
no
what if I training this thing is also
quite a challenge what about this oh
this should be it no no wait I feel like
I'm
close to the
Taco eni is the
key oh what about what about
this
uh sus that eye is so sus should that
eye be
pointing H what about this oh I got it I
got it I got
it
oh open up
kfp I'm
scared did this dungeon only have
one uh in between boss oh dear what the
[\h__\h] is
that I'm not fighting that oh God oh my
what we were just talking about you ah
the key looks like your tentacles that's
funny what what are we doing am we going
to shoot
them come back to me what's happening
nothing's happening what is the game
bugged is the game
bugged
hello this feels like a FPS game now go
outside
what
oh what why did I not what is the ship
moving
what what is this oh wait the fight is
actually happening
in happening out what is going on a
report Master think I have [\h__\h] time
for this right now judging by their size
these tentacles belong to a monster of
considerable size uhhuh the current
situation is difficult to determine with
complete accuracy but shut up shut up if
we didn't know shut up shut up shut shut
shut
up sacred power I I know what you mean
okay Holy Light protect me and let me go
forth oh that's funny oh wait that's a
funny interesting
uh actually non hectic uh boss but maybe
that's only for
now maybe only for
now oh dear
what now that reminds me of that horror
game that we played which was not much
of a horror
game uh when we are trying to escape the
mansion oh dear is that going to fall
down oh Donkey Kong Vibes as well so
much going on oh my God you
uh Holy Light protect me and give me the
power power
kfp Kiana FR
[Music]
[Applause]
power okay oh my God the ship is like
destroyed already what
happened he is power p is what I want it
to be f as well K is mostly K though K
is mostly K Waring mastera uh-huh okay
mhm I sense an evil presence on the
other side of this
door there is
90% I didn't do anything it just
happened W chill I suggest making all
this preparations before accident to
the she's losing it Fe is losing it Fe
absolutely losing
[Music]
it oh dear it's raining man hallelujah
it's raining man oh yeah well your ship
is dead uh my dear robot buddy um your
ship is no more I'm sorry but at least
your crew is
rescued
what
[Music]
what by
surpr that's youa when she wakes up
after sleeping on the floor for too
long also known as
ABIA okay nice to meet you Ena um calm
down okay I'll bring you some cup
noodles okay and some Dr oopsy will you
be happy then oh God how do I fight this
thing
oh how
I can can I uh do the thing
sideways I I don't even have time to
like uh load it
up I guess I can walk why I'm doing it
but it's
WR that's what you meant by hectic huh
charge it it won't start Char
charging ah
okay I don't like this I don't like this
okay let's try it on this one there we
go okay we cut one have to cut another
one okay okay okay okay easy not so
bad [\h__\h] I
[Music]
missed no I'm trying to CH my
blade leave me
alone
[Music]
how many tactical do you
have touch
touch there it
is okay I think I think eni is happy for
now I demand more more oh I
do I'm so sick of oh wait I have to
shoot you in your eye huh wait wait wait
wait oh
God
wait
wait wait wait wait wait the controls
are horrible
ah there we go okay actually once he
hits the ground with his tentacles
actually that might be oh
no
[Music]
ah that might be the way to go yeah cuz
then his eye is somewhat calm at least
are we doing the tentacle thing
again whatever you want buddy whatever
you want I'm here for you Ena you're
always so so nice and you listen to my
worries and all that I I will listen to
yours now what happened huh are you
still mad I mean you never was mad but
are you mad did I make that that stream
about you uh when you over slap huh I'm
sorry I'm sorry it's okay it was just a
joke it was just a j don't be mad at me
you look beautiful by the way just the
way you are just right after waking up
you look beautiful you don't need any
makeup or
anything
okay no hey I'll just I just want to
give you some what that okay you've been
stressed out and you've been working
hard no he wants to give me a hug is
that what it is are you mad that I that
I don't like show you the same kind
of I just saw you in the chat I got
distracted w why that box up there oh my
God okay Ina Ina why are you even here
charge
PL you know if those tentacles are too
heavy for you I will help you I will I
will I will I will take them off of you
I will I will carry some of the weight
that you always carry I know it's heavy
I know it's tough but there's so many
tentacles a heavy burden to carry I
know but you're not the only one whole
life English meth is five girls and we
will always be five girls and together
we're
strong strong strong we
are don't let the evilness from the
ancient ones overcome you I know you're
you're a good
person I don't know they're on vacation
right now I'm not responsible
for oh you're not controlling them right
now you have to control your freaking
tentacles that's like having a dog and
not controlling a dog letting to run
around
really I gu is going to do some
bamboozle on people it's not good that's
not good you have to control you got
that T I got two I want you all right
all right all right next phase let's go
oh my god oh you're coming from here now
okay that's fine with me wake UPA you're
telling me that this is not you Ena I
see more than just
tentacles I see more than just tentacles
you can't fool me oh my
God ouch she got me she got
me oh she's looking at me she's looking
at
me did you that
blop cute blop sound blop
blop okay
go I got him I got him
calm down Ena it's all good I'm going to
give you a special eye
massage this is this is the good stuff I
know that by looking at the computer for
too long your eyes hurt just just chill
for a moment Ena no need to stress so
much this is suck why is that here oh
God again with the tacles can you think
of anything
else this is
unoriginal
okay oh my God okay sword up high come
on
link oh my God I'm high up h
[Music]
no okay now there we have
it
okay come on probably five five right
five tentacles it feels like it's five
tentacles I got
two ew
disgusting and here She is again good
morning
sunshine oh dear oh dear w w whoa w w
what's the matter what's the matter
what's the matter come come on we can
talk about it
h what are you
doinga what are you doing
I got it calm
down let me Rush your
hair I'll give you all the love that you
looking for I
promise taco t is
real you
don't you don't think it's you because
of the existing chest okay I guess
that's an argument yes
ah but is this one of your friends then
who is
this
help oh God okay no problem no problem
she looks very scary looks like Medusa
somehow oh I was freaking up
[Music]
okay oh it is actually is like a c
version of
Medusa wait do I have to ignore them and
shoot him in the eye or do I just do
this for a while oh God I'm going to die
I have a I have a I do have oh God I
have a fairy I have a
fa okay okay okay we got it we got it we
got it now shoot the eye
okay got
it come
[Music]
here okay okay one more I'm sure you
want to do one more of that right I know
you enjoy it come at
me did I just Parry oh I can Parry them
I can't carry so many at once oh I can
hide from I want I want to hide it's not
worth it it's not worth
it I lose a hide I get a hide
wonderful
[Music]
no oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God okay time to shoot time to shoot
Focus good job
come here
buddy I'm free you from the
suffering
y
yay
[Music]
nice yeah hell yeah
baby now give me those sacred flame that
I so much
desire wow in the heart container yes I
forgot about that
one oh yay yeah thank you thank you that
was a Indie tactic it was fun though I
like how you were how you needed to get
from inside of the ship to outside and
the ship kept on being attacked and
destroyed and then you have this big
epic fight on top of the ship I like
that I do like
that hi
container stream hi
container I love you guys oh man this
ship is
wrecked that is
sad that is so sad well you know what we
got to do
[Music]
guys fee come here Fe I know you want to
talk to me I know you want to talk to
the audience I know you
do
[Music]
oh are we putting the sword in there
again
yes that feels good
baby
[Music]
bomb
incoming
boom I told
you amazing huh
mhm beautiful
yes
sword extension again oh
no looks kind of like
stronger she can now help you use your
dcing ability to search for more objects
oh finally those spots wait but these
are always like so useful I never
useless I never needed more than one
thing at
once is it longer
again or did it just change its color
kind of it's like silverish
now
it is longer
oh the try Voice number
[Music]
two
w with your sword enhanced you can learn
a new Melody I recommend we return to
the aisle of sun
sounds good to
me the free triangle swing
yeah thank you for getting my ship back
even though you completely destroyed it
but I guess it's not your fault uh
whatever at least I have my crew thank
you for that we will now finally be able
to see Mar Central
again yay it may have been half right
but my crew and I got it shaved up to
almost proper working order in no time I
wish you good luck in finding who
whomever it is you're looking for beep
come visit again you're welcome anytime
beep thank you can I take the
boat I will have to I think no wait are
we oh wait we're at the harbor now ah
we're here okay okay okay now
hold uh let me save first and
foremost now we
shall uh go to get our new m
[Music]
mhm
Sky could it be K is not reading the
text entirely
accurately don't know what you're
talking
about maybe you don't know how to read
and I
do all
[Applause]
righty we need to go in here
also why do I always need to see this
like his face here like I don't like
[Music]
[Applause]
it because I didn't teach you properly I
guess I guess I guess I was in charge
huh cuz I adopted you from a very early
stage
huh do I have to go through that tiny
hole here or can I just go through the
clouds I wonder well I'm going through
I'm I'm trying to I'm trying to
yes hello it is me once again I have
come to receive a song Holy
song could be hinotori could be heart
Challa could be
Sparks or could
be something better than
[Music]
that feel the air in my
FS
I wonder if a birds flying in the rain
is
fun thank you I will not punish you no
it's your
birthday I
remember
hello what happens if I jump
down
okay
I swear to make 100% sure just got to
make it got to be very very sure about
these
things I don't know I expected exactly
that
actually what do we hear
today master link I have important
information when you struck the crest
with a skyward Strike from your sword a
message from the goddess awakened deep
within my memory the goddess intended
this message for you master these are
her
[Music]
words he who seeks the sacred Flames
listen well for I am the one guiding you
from my place at the edge of
[Music]
time the last of the sacred flame still
elud you to obtain it you must claim
another sacred
gift for each trial you overcome you
shall be blessed with another
[Music]
gift make use of the power of these
gifts and you will most only find the
path to the sacred
FL now I bestow onto you another Melody
let it serve as a key to unlocking your
final
trial it way to upon elen
volan Charity
B
[Music]
oh
oh I like this one it's not as cheerful
as the others but I like it a
lot has a nice vibe
[Music]
according to my records
Accord funny music that song you just
heard is called Den's power use the song
of Might to locate the last
trial I learn Dan
power
I have committed Den's power to my
memory now you have the ability to use
dowsing to locate the gate to the final
trial final trial I suggest you travel
to the elen
volcano I'll probably have to do one of
those
uh uh the ones with the tears one of
those test again right I want to do that
at least
um
I don't think I'll go into the next
dungeon but I want to do at least that
before uh ending today yeah another
Spirit
trial yes
hello yeah silent
BR yeah a little bit a little bit tired
it's a bit you
know a bit tiring to play the game in
general I think it's kind of ridiculous
but just by doing all these hand
movements in this game maybe that's the
reason why it's a bit more tiring than
other games to
me and it it does use quite some brain
power because of the RS and stuff
they're not that difficult but still I
still have to focus and use my brain a
little bit right so that was a
combination of actually having to use
my
arms and actually actually the movements
really do matter when fighting just
still
[Music]
so and as always you know talking so
much during a stream it is a little bit
exhausting so we just want to do the
trial so I'll just go straight to the
elen
volcano
[Music]
um this isn't your typical grind and
chill J
yeah yeah skip superat for today yeah
probably I'll see how I feel at the end
and how much longer the trial takes
me yeah cuz it's not I I was about to
say
that yeah but you guys I think a lot of
people don't realize from the people who
watch how exhausting it is
to talk so much for a
stream especially cuz like it's not like
like as a streamer you want to speak
clearly and loudly and all that so I do
put a lot of like energy into my voice
as I speak throughout the whole stream
like for hours and hours so it is really
exhausting where do we want to go please
tell me so I we we can do it
faster or do we know where to go does
anyone
know the volcano area kind of seems like
it will be difficult to do the trial in
though there's so many narrow paths
volcano asent okay thank
you thank
you hard to plan to be entertaining
you probably speak as much in a single
stream as I do in an entire
year my voice starts giving out if I
have to talk longer than 6 hours 6 hours
is already if we speak non-stop for 6
hours that is quite
impressive I see
yeah it is pretty a tiring game but I do
have to say I like the pacing of it the
pacing feels really
fast
I like the the fast pacing of the game
like there's not much like I mean if you
want to do sa Quest sure but other than
that you can just quickly go from trial
to pre- dungeon to dungeon to trial to
pre- dungeon to dungeon and all that so
I do like that mhm 12h Hour Super Chat
reading I I can't believe I really did
something like
that thinking about that now makes me
feel like who the [\h__\h] did that like how
how did I survive survive that how did I
survive
that oh dear ah there it is
oh 12 hour Super Chat rating how did I
survive
that oh my god oh no here we go
again really bad at this for some
reason oh it's beautiful wait did the
melody change on my heart hey I'm moving
it
[Music]
okay now you start singing
hello um
okay
[Music]
finally
I guess it didn't that makes no sense
the harp sound changing oh there we
[Music]
go I like that
wow
thrust your sword into the center of the
mark and open the way to a new Silent
Realm let's go I actually enjoyed them
the silent realms I I was scared of them
but they're actually not that
bad I know I can't use them in the
silent real but I'm still going to pick
them up here can you not pick them
up no put away the harp for God's sake
oh my God he really wants to play the
harp he really wants to anyway we have a
full full inventory anyway now all right
then ready sword and fr
FR
yeah okay guys the last maybe the last s
unless there's something before the boss
dungeon but it makes no sense right this
is probably the last one oh
God yeah that one looks really
difficult I knew this one would be tough
it looks look tough it looks very
tough master link this one is going to
be a pain in the ass but you can do it
believe in yourself you stand within
then's Silent Realm theer trial it will
test the limits of your powers to locate
the last plane that will enhance your
sword you must first complete this final
Challenge and Achieve spiritual growth
once
[Music]
again
I see something
there when your vessel is full your
spirit will grow and you will be
entrusted with a new power by the
goddess do you have any questions
no understood
master master I await your return in the
outside
world oh god well I did really well in
the last two ones so really above on
first it saves you a lot of time and
effort the above ones you mean uh I
don't know which direction I guess this
this direction is above yeah yeah MH oh
god um oh
God uh maybe I should
uh is there one right here okay we good
we good we
good okay uh wait those ones
were the ones that fill it up right okay
uh was that maybe a bad
choice this is like right ah don't don't
don't kill me don't kill
me can you not run in circles around it
please okay
so uh 90 seconds 90 seconds 90 seconds
that's like
nothing
okay yeah time
him upwards we go
right
okay uh it it's closed
here what about the heat here does it
not
matter ah I guess I go up can I go
up ah found
on okay that's it
here uh I guess we can go down here
[Music]
good good oh oh oh no that water there
uh where do we go first uh I'll go up
here okay there's a one on the left side
two on the left side nothing on the
right side okay it's dangerous danger I
can't go
there
okay I didn't want to touch
it y a go [\h__\h] idiot you [\h__\h]
idiot are you going to be waiting for me
there hopefully not oh yeah I need I
need one I need one I need come on what
the
[\h__\h] hang down there hang down there and
you'll get one come on
up
wasn't that one right here like one one
buddy trying to kill me I I saw it I saw
it okay come down um one over
there
okay okay nothing this way
okay uh I need to go up one more time
and then I can get the ones below I
suppose there's nothing else besides
those two on the on the slide right on
the top I hope I hope I
hope really need to plan your route yeah
I mean I kind of have a plan I kind of
have it planned out I got this one
so other than that it should just be oh
can you what the [\h__\h] are you doing
hello Link Link Link Link Link Link Link
you idiot you idiot
no okay I guess I have to go one more
time oh thank God I
I no you
idiot daddy oh no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
no no they can't hit they can't hit me
I'll be [\h__\h] if they hit
me oh my God oh my God I need to fly up
for one of those I need to fly up for
one of
those oh God hello hello um um um um um
okay okay okay
okay where do I go where do I go where
do I go where do I go can I go here is
this where I want to go no this is not
where I want to
go how do I get there wait this is not
the way this is not the way to get there
yeah where are they anyway I'm sure they
like following me I don't know where
they
[Applause]
are God okay oh hello um hi hi hi hi no
no no no
no
okay yeah that's
okay
[Music]
shut
up good strategies to find but then
deliberately not pick up the most
accessible okay yeah shut up shut up
shut up shut up shut up just shut up
shut up shut up just shut up shut up oh
no no no
no stop the talking baby I stop walking
baby stop the talking baby without
working baby yeah
yeah no no no no okay so uh give me one
of the those thank
you okay we do it again um so I guess
only one is accessible by going left and
then there should be two accessible why
going right but I just have to jump on
top yeah that song is from black at PE I
have to jump on
top uh one of the middle platforms oh
wait there would have one one there up
well up there as well but we will go
there
again okay uh let's go left first
maybe my controller is so bad for some
reason
wa move hello
move yeah I got nothing out of that
wonderful it it does [\h__\h]
move he's L there's one there's one
here he doesn't
move we so mad so
mad I'm getting this one now
distressed Squad shut up can I change
the controller for this one I don't know
I don't have to fight so controller
might be easier
maybe I can get both from the right side
yeah but there's one that I definitely
have to get from the left side there's
three there
three yeah the T give
the this one left because I activated it
once
doesn't come back there was a dude here
to protect this area he's
gone
uh so where do we go
there's huh is this one I haven't gotten
yet but I've seen so it marks it marks
it on my on my
map never realized that so if I maybe I
I mean I got it before from going to
that side but I guess I can just try to
go for the
middle and then jump on uh try to jump
on that platform there there's one
platform here I think shouldn't there be
another one there oh man
okay don't [\h__\h] around now link please
please I'm so mad already I'm so mad at
you I have no patience no [\h__\h] no
chills where do I go where do I go
middle and then here okay okay okay
that's
manageable no how how
how how can you miss
that chill I didn't activate anything
it's all okay I didn't activate
anything I didn't activate
anything I didn't activate anything it's
all
good relax taking
easy hey I'm trying okay I'm trying
don't blame this one on me the motion
controls are not making this any easier
right
now this slide is a freaking pain in the
ass no no no no no no
no okay through the middle stop being an
[\h__\h] no no I
was no it's
not I'm
[Music]
cry what to cry I'm don't cry I hate
this so much right now my [\h__\h] I told
you today my toy Gs are really [\h__\h]
weird and I don't know where you can
that want hand don't just kill me I
don't care just kill me just kill me
whatever kill
me that's it I'm switching to Pro
Controller [\h__\h]
thisit [\h__\h] this
[Music]
crap
have to get used to
it that's all I need that's all the
controls I
needed
okay where am I going W there's one here
oh with the camera the camera movement
here though ah God no I can't use
Supreme control I'm not used the camera
control
here hello hello hello I'm trying to use
my thank you thank you thank
you should
I I shouldn't try to go up here right
now
right or should
I okay no never mind
should
I may as well yeah a I have it oh God oh
God they're going to catch me what how
soos to do
this how are you supposed to do
[Laughter]
this oh God is this supposed to be like
the last one or
something okay okay I got one there uh
what the hell was that how what what is
that placement is that the last one up
there or is is there one at the very
very
[Music]
top is there one at the very
top I don't see any light coming from
there but I had to go up again oh God
but like how can you not activate those
[\h__\h] there's one up there oh God I
have a bad feeling going up there I have
a really bad feeling oh God oh God oh
God oh God maybe this is where the
stamina potion would actually be useful
oh no oh no no
no I made it I made it I made
it are you are you hiding something
behind you no oh my God I made ah there
it
is there it is okay that's the one
that's the high us up right there's no
more here and then well the slides where
the hell am I now where am
I slide down oh God oh God they're going
to catch me let to slide
down quick y y y y
y I need I need one to save my ass
quickly
okay yeah stamina potion really would be
nice
now okay no I see um yeah we have to go
to that side I have to finish those
freaking I have to finish them so which
ones are we missing all of them in the
slide I think we're still missing all of
them
cuz I keep on messing up but no I will
not blame myself for this cuz it's not
my fault not my
fault okay go left go left go slightly
left not too much left and left left
left I told you to go [\h__\h] left oh my
god
dude it's not moving it's not
moving
it's not fun but at
least I was going to say at least they
catching up with me but it's like
literally it was waiting and in that Sho
was waiting for
[Music]
me
God what she got
you
oh why why does it oh [\h__\h] the middle
I'm going to the left again it seems
more manageable to go to the left and to
the middle cuz my [\h__\h] controller
won't react and I'm so mad I'm just
going to throw it all in the trash
[Music]
afterward this is the worst Spirit trial
I'll I'll give it one more
try okay yeah
finally come
on finally be careful how many more up
there how many more are waiting for me
there
one okay we got to go get it oh my
[Music]
[Laughter]
God we can do
it we can do it one on the
right on the right no it's a platform on
the left side no I's see it
[Music]
no I will see it I will see it and
decide uh
spontaneously oh God uh he's like really
on the left
though I don't know where to go I don't
know where to go I don't know no I
wasn't sure like I saw it like on the
left side I have to go left in the very
beginning
no got I'm running out of time
again it's from right to left very right
side
okay accessible on the
right
this this was always so much fun until
now why is the last one's so
painful oh God oh
[Music]
God oh
God
huh I went to the
right what if I go
here that's actually the way to go oh
thank God I was
like
maybe oh God okay I thought I already
messed up
again all right okay we're done with
that part right we have everything in
the upper part or is there something
here that I'm
missing no that area is not accessible
right this just like grayish area and
this lava area is not accessible either
I would
say no more sliding I
[Music]
hope only down okay
okay so
uh no
I don't I didn't want you to leave there
I wanted you to just calmly calmly jump
down
yes oh my
God good thing lava doesn't make you
fail
yes uh wait how do I reach that thing
over there
[Music]
oh
God okay that one was also quite
annoying let's see if there's something
up
here
oh there's one here I jump
down
[Music]
okay uh I need to use the the
Rope
okay no time to
[Music]
lose I need to use the rope it look like
I could just
no oh come
on painful day it is today
huh a painful
day oh my God I'm getting
[Music]
hungry oh my God okay calm down sh stop
moving
[Applause]
[Music]
hit
[Applause]
h
[Music]
ah there's a thing on the tree oh
well I should I try to get it cuz it's
ah I already jumped
down almost there oh two more only oh
it's actually quite soon well well
well
what do we have
[Music]
here I kind of want to try getting done
thing before I finish it so oh God we
have to
balance
[Music]
ah oh the things that trigger me to
today are
endless I love
ropes I love
them go
[Music]
move oh you almost jumped into the lava
you wanted to scare me Hing you wanted
to give me a little bamboozle
yeah no thank you no need for that um I
will actually run try to run back to uh
I
can to get the purple
[Music]
thingy should be over there yeah on the
tree cuz they
valuable and then we have one more to
uh
go get okay the last one was somewhere
over there I see it easy to get pry Easy
Go should be very easy it's right there
I can literally smell
[Music]
it
yep oh I have to go back oh
no how the hell do I get back
there this path is
blocked
uh uh oh Link Link why did you double
jump no one told you to double jump no
one literally no
one is it you're either demons or
what dear
God can I get back though through
here uh through here yes yes yes yes yes
this must be it
[Music]
ah we did
it wait I still have time let me um
there was one more on the slide not this
slide
since we still have a lot of time wait
is the time even going it's not ticking
anymore right once you have all of the
pearls the time doesn't go go by
anymore that worth it it is it is
there's infinite time now so why the
hell
not
okay I wonder what happens if I activate
it again the this this stuff then I
can't deactivated anymore right unless I
get to the to the thing oh well anyway
here we are this is what I wanted I
literally can't speak English today I
apologize I
[Music]
apolog
what
yeah um I just wanted a little bit more
of a challenge you know
was all too easy all too no I can't I
can't die now I can't I literally I you
cannot do this to me no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no I wanted a
little bit
[Music]
adrenaline
oh
my
earrings [\h__\h] earrings they give me
freaking earrings I can't take it I
can't I can't I
[Music]
can't that was so
[Laughter]
stressful got that drip the drip oh
fry a shield earrings with these you can
stand any heat without what about
lava H this is one of the fre sacred
gifts left by the
goddess lava is still going to hurt me
right so
[Music]
man welcome back
Master why do you look so angry
something happened was that not fun for
you I thought slides and stuff were fun
what's the problem H you got a problem
with slides come on link normally you
always always so childish and now you
have a problem with that kind of
stuff welcome back Master by the way
nice strip you got there I see it on
your ear at conjecture your newly
acquired fire Shield earrings will allow
you to safely travel in extremely hard
areas
ah ah and that makes me able to go over
there where they always told me it's too
hot and that will be the new area
ah I recommend continuing a search for
the saet flame no I'm so so done for
today my dear
fee it was so much
fun playing with you today Fe but for
today I must I must end it
here no no just no
no
no oh man oh
man well we did progress we have one
more dungeon to go and then I guess
something like a boss dungeon or
something like that um can I ask you
guys for
something does
someone do you guys maybe want to um
make a a bingo card you guys like making
Bingo cards right for my streams my sim
streams for example I I've seen those
bingo cards can you make one about my
debut
stream because I was thinking while we
watch my debut stream on the anniversary
stream we could use the bingo
card
I don't know how that would work we
would probably all get Bingle at the
same time but
still I think that I don't know I
thought of that last night and I thought
it would be funny so if anyone wants to
watch the debut stream and then put
together a bingo
card cuz if I watch it again
then I don't know if I make the bingo
card on my own then I already know when
I'll get Bingo and
stuff yeah exactly bingo cards only work
if you don't know what happens and I
don't remember so any anyone anyone from
kfp who wants to like put a bingo card
together um maybe some of you can I
don't know work
together which
de the first one the first
one the first one please the first
one all right I'll leave that to you I
know you guys can do it I trust
you so just whenever you're done with
that maybe put it in the Arts of Ashes
tag but don't make too many one or two
different ones don't make like a million
Bingle cards
please want two I'm fine yeah if if you
want you can make like two two different
ones um and I'll use both of them and
then put them in the artashes tag so I
can find them okay that will be really
cool yeah art of No Eyes Of Ashes not
Eyes Of
Ashes reaction or de Bingle what ah oh
oh maybe that's a good idea one one
Bingle card for for my for my
reactions I guess if you can't even
think of enough things or like I guess
yeah you could put in things like kiata
tells old kiata to shut the [\h__\h] up or
kiata uh uh pauses the video because she
can't listen to it anymore or
[Music]
k
uh I don't know actually I can't think
of so many things maybe you can maybe
you guys can if that's the case then we
could do one Bingo for my reactions and
one Bingo for just the debut video
itself
yeah I guess you could put in random
stuff like K uh uh tends to her cats in
between the deut thingy and K tangents
while watching her debut stream stuff
like
that make the free space scuffed mic I
don't know how a
cringes ah what where's the free space
how did that work that is that just the
one that is definitely going to show up
anyway is that is it those that are a
given oh 20 five spaces will be free
spaces yeah basically
yeah most likely most
likely I see okay okay well have fun
with that no need to rush it it's still
like a week to go more than a week to go
um and I'll be doing my I'll be
conducting my uh anniversary stream on a
Sunday it'll probably be like 2 hours or
something cuz I think every every one of
us wants to do do a anniversary stream
and then we'll follow it up by a collab
anniversary stream and I think cie will
be the first one to do the solo
anniversary stream and I'll be the I'll
be the second one yeah uh so look
forward to that
[Music]
yeah yeah probably wasn't actually
planned that way but it seems to
be yeah I I have a feeling like at least
me and CI already planned
our
W I don't know I can't speak to I just
can't I can't I can't I need to go I
think I need to
[Music]
go um okay I will I will I will I will
make food
now
and
yes tomorrow I have my doctor's
appointment and I have to buy groceries
for for the for the cooking Stream So
cooking stream tomorrow oh my God I
don't know if I'm ready for
it I don't know if I'm ready for it
yum you did great today despite the SC
control thank
you thank you good luck on the
appointment thank thank you oh God don't
make me nervous I don't want to think
about it I'll think about it when I wake
up
tomorrow I'm nervous about it yeah
yeah thank you thank you thank you
everyone tomorrow I'll be making an oh
Australian this H that will hopefully
also go well it will be a little bit
thaen I'm so hungry right
now what are you making I'm making
a I think it has two
names it's it's it it seems simple but
it's going to be fun to make it cuz I'm
going to make um it all by myself I mean
yes of course that that sounds like it's
a good
but there's there's this part of of the
dish the noodle looking things they're
not noodles but I'm going to make those
from scratch as well yes yes M yum yum
yum yum yum yum oh I'm looking forward
to eating that
tomorrow yeah mac and cheese no it's not
mac and cheese but it's l it's there is
a lot of cheese yes M like noi M no no
no no no it doesn't really have the same
texture or batter as noi
either spiders no no spiders in the
[Music]
ingredients will we be be getting the
rough sketch for the anniversary what do
you mean rough
sketch rough sketch you mean you
mean what what do you what do you
mean do you mean the the drawing that I
talked about
[Music]
before Oh you you really mean
that or maybe the backro yeah well you
um I have a lot
of material from Hook Papa to show you
guys not only not only the reference
sheet but maybe perhaps there will
be
um ideas how I could have how else I
could have looked
like so like steps until I became who I
am you know what I
mean I got a lot of
those they look interesting thing yeah
so we definitely got to come I'm
planning a lot of things for my
anniversary stream I want to
do I want to do the the watching my
debut stream which will take 1 hour I
guess I don't know did GAA do the whole
thing like she already did it ages ago I
think at the health year anniversary but
did she do the whole 1
hour maybe we should speed it up I mean
we could we could skip the part where I
sing but that
she had to skip part of it she had
to she had to skip her song why why did
she have to do that she cut out the
song what
what she only skipped the part where she
sang A DMC Oh I thought that song was
okay oh okay oh okay right on time yeah
but okay anyway okay I see so she did
the whole thing but she skipped the song
okay I guess we can do the same that's
still going to be a long long ride oh
God I don't want to watch
[Laughter]
it but okay okay okay okay so one hour
of that and then probably another hour
of a lot of other activities
so yeah I'm excited for
it yes also um next week I'm going to do
another Minecraft collab with my mommy
because the portal portal creation and
uh the connection thing is going to
happen quite soon and as I told you guys
before uh probably the mommy collapse
cannot happen anymore after that so yeah
uh I'm going to rush it and do another
Mama Minecraft collab next week yes yes
probably on Wednesday it's probably
going to be much much earlier than the
last one cuz we're going to be building
a lot so it's probably going to be a
long stream
so it's going to start at like 2:00 p.m.
my time something like that I think or
p.m. so
yeah
yes uh maybe a lot of you have to wake
up early for it
[Music]
yeah Mama
cab on her server I that's not of server
but uh yeah we can still play Minecraft
together afterwards yeah yeah
yeah I always wake up for you thank you
waking up early is my specialty
wow okay 4:00 a.m. stream for me don't
force yourself okay you don't have to
you can watch archive part of it cuz
it's going to be a long stream you can
wake up like later and then uh check in
in between and then watch the beginning
in archive still no voice CH yes yes
for that for that Minecraft stream no
voice yet no no no
no looking forward to it thank
you all right so I guess I'll leave you
guys here thank you everyone for
watching and for um yeah
bearing bear bearing with
me uh
today I had some moments where I was
losing my [\h__\h]
especially towards the
end um but it was fun
nonetheless yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah thank you
everyone oh yeah also I got I got
collabs lined up with uh free
three
three of the council
members yeah oh also I think there's
something happening on
Sunday
uh a collab that's not on my schedule
but it's like not really 100% like
decided yet at what time we're doing it
I'm still waiting for
that there might be another stream on
Sunday so yeah look forward to that as
well surprise collab yeah with some with
some fun
members okay then H thank you for
watching today everyone please have a
rest I will rest too and I'll see you
tomorrow for the cooking stream yeah and
in German we
say h
[Music]
v thank you
yeah
[Music]
byebye