[Music]
so
hello
[Music]
i'm back home
i've been away so long
but i'm back
hello
sorry to keep you waiting
a new week has started
and i'm back
choice everybody
that hat works so well right yeah
it's like you know cause in dokomi i was
wearing my my
uniform so now i'm back home i'm like
oh i changed my clothes
but i forgot to take off my uniform hat
that's the kind of look i was going for
you know
half uniform half
uh casual
totally not on purpose totally on
[Music]
i'm purpose in full voice yeah
i haven't streamed since
last
wednesday yeah wednesday i was gonna
stream something on thursday
uh like mario kart before my flight but
it didn't really
it didn't want me like it wasn't really
realistic
i wanted to but i was
really stressed out and busy
uh it was probably a good choice to not
do it
so wait how many days is that
first day friday saturday sunday four
days
maybe like four and a half days actually
because like it's already 8 p.m here on
monday
damn
yeah
i'm glad you didn't push yourself i mean
i still kind of did but that's okay
attention i missed you i miss you guys
too
i missed this setup
and my cats and my home my cozy my
coziness in my home
um although i mean it was also of course
sad to leave um
germany because it was just
really really cool experience and we're
going to talk about it today that's
that's the topic of today i will let you
know i will let you in on what i was
doing because i had
you know i was thinking maybe if
sometime in between i could stream from
the hotel but no oh my god i had
absolutely no time at all
i woke up early every day
nah no quarantine no no no i'm so good
but even if i had to i mean i stayed
home all day anyway
um but i was saying uh i woke up early
like every day
i had to kind of like early i mean
okay maybe not
not that early but
but yeah and i had to
sleep for asap but um every every night
but
um
i mean i slept i slept earlier than
usually
when i'm at home that that's for sure i
didn't stay up until like 6 a.m or so
although we're gonna fall back into our
usual pattern starting from today
because this week there are some things
that like for example the hololeon
collab that starts at midnight for me
and then i have like a rehearsal at 2
a.m my time for
uh the
megacon orlando
at megacon orlando itself also starts at
i think mid mid
midnight for me
and the rehearsal is like
two days before that or so i think at
two a.m like after yeah actually it's
like after the holo uh en collaboration
that starts at midnight at 2 a.m me and
i'mma have the rehearsal
so there will there is a fixed time when
the halloween collab has to end because
we have a rehearsal um i just hope it
doesn't go as long as the ax reversal
[Music]
yeah cause that took like pretty much
the whole day
no but as far as i know it should be a
short one
i
hope
could you always use that hat with that
model yeah
i i used it before too but not that
often um but today i felt like mixing
and matching
mix and match
yeah the whole day last time but i think
this time should be like more decent
short hopefully compact and short
it's a great combo right yeah i agree
um
[Music]
so yeah that's why uh i will already
we're in my sleep schedule
so bad this week i i don't i don't have
hope anymore this is just
this is the life i'm living now
i don't have hope
oh man
it's like generally like i guess it's
okay cause like i don't really
like if i had like a normal job like a
side job or so
where i had to go to work at a decent
time during the day then then it would
be then i would be
but well i don't i don't really have any
sad business going on or so
so yeah i guess it's fine oh my god did
you see
iris was playing minecraft
i just saw a tiny tiny tiny snippet of
it because someone sent it to me on
twitter she fell into my hole
you know
months ago i was playing minecraft and i
had like all this like cool stuff
and i was running around
and i think i was running to
oh my god wasn't i already running
towards
towards somewhere else where i died
and then i on the way to running trying
to find where else i dined i i think
that was it uh i fell into the hole and
died again like a really long haul like
a one black hole that is like really
really really really really really deep
yeah i was going to the village because
i died there first i think
but then on the way to there i died too
so i couldn't pick up my things in the
hole
uh in the in the original spot i think
and i also was
was i ever able to pick up my things in
the hole maybe i did but anyway
i don't know who made that hole but it's
like a one block someone must have
straight down or straight up
nah but if you dig straight up someone
something would have to be on like to
jump on and take off higher
yeah i think i guess someone
dug down
must have my husband's uh dog
dig it down
i think logically thinking anyway so i
fell down there
wait didn't i fall down there two times
like what i
i ran there trying to find it and then
fell down and died and i tried to find
the spot carefully and then i fell down
again by accident even though i wanted
to do it with water or something that
time but i fell down and and i died
again and i was absolutely stupid
absolutely stupid but i was so mad that
i was like whoever made that
hole
how does it feel the same pain as i did
so i kept it i kept the hole
but i thought
someone from hollow myth would
fall into it
and so much time has passed and no one
fell into it
until iris fell into it
[Music]
and she has nothing to do with it she
she's innocent she didn't even exist
when that hole was made
uh
they got the wrong person the officer
they got the wrong person
that was that that's um
ah that's ironic
it's uh
unfortunate
unfortunate happening
that happened while i was gone
well i was gone so i couldn't i couldn't
protect her
and there was nothing i could do
did you go to berlin no i went to
dusseldorf in germany
uh which is like hmm
i guess it's like in this
center like loki center like not really
center center but it's like it's not in
the north it's not in the south it's
like in the center
west center
west
ghana
are you listening
it's like in the west center of germany
yeah
um kinda in the west i guess so yeah
kind of left right yeah somewhere there
it's a pretty pretty big city yeah let's
get talking let's go talking about
dokomi and dusseldorf
it is a pretty big city in germany
uh has a big airport too uh has lots of
connection flights too
uh and i've been to dusseldorf a couple
times before
mostly for dokomi but once uh just for
fun too
because dusseldorf is awesome
it's it's like
one of my two favorite cities in germany
and probably the number one
because dusseldorf the thing that makes
this stuff so special
is that it has the biggest
um
inhabitants of
japanese people
yeah and uh
they have a ton of really authentic
japanese restaurants even one japanese
classic hotel that's called hotel nicole
nico it's a really like common hotel in
japan and they have it there and they
have a lot of like companies um
uh yeah sit seat
side side quarters
in dusseldorf as well
and actually i asked i asked we had a we
had like a like a guide assistant to the
staff
for look at me
and
like i kind of like loki had an image of
why why there were so many japanese
people
uh
in dusseldorf but the assistant uh
corrected me because i wasn't quite
correct so basically
uh uh back in the day a long time ago
coal mining was a thing uh into kodov
uh and
japan sent people
to dusseldorf
to study coal mining i think
and
to train it pretty young people
and they were there for a few years to
train it and then supposedly like they
came from big big companies and they
were supposed to come back to japan
after finishing their training
however
after they finished their training japan
was like coal mining we're not
doing that anymore
and then the japanese people in
disneyland were like well what what the
hell man
what what you're kidding me bro dude
what's up with that
so they stayed in dusseldorf because
that mean they got used to it and i
guess they liked it they liked it too
um and and yeah they were able to stay
uh they you know made families
and
yeah just kind of stayed in this bluff i
actually know they they stayed like
originally they stayed like they were
doing they were living and mining around
dusseldorf but this was very close so
uh they decided to go for this look yeah
what's my history lesson isn't this cool
i can give you actual cool knowledge
mitsubishi yeah yeah companies like that
[Laughter]
[Music]
dude
i flew to germany on first day
in the early evening i think
and i came back today
in the early morning
after i came back i made my schedule and
everything and i took a nap and i
cuddled with my cat so i'm full energy
and feeling awesome right now
but yeah just
let me tell you from the beginning
so
this is the um second time that i'm kind
of working with the dokomi people
because the tokumi people the dokomi is
a convention
in germany the biggest anime manga
convention in germany
uh one of the biggest in
europe only topped by
i guess japan expo in france which is
really huge but japan expo is like a
little bit more than anime and manga
it's like whole japanese culture like
everything like fighting sports uh
martial arts and stuff and anything
um
anyway
so dokum is really really big usually
usually um dokomi has been around for
like 10 years
around 10 years
and uh it's it's just
i've been there privately a bunch of
times and i really really like it it's
like my favorite convention in germany
for
reasons
such as
it's big it's fun it has the best
outside location ever to hang out with
your friends so when you were in dokomi
in the
location
in the convention center you might think
like whoa this is big so many people ha
ha but then you go outside into the park
next door which is absolutely huge
and there's like even more people there
thousands and thousands of people are in
that park it has like an english garden
a japanese garden huge fountains
big grass locations uh it's called north
park
there is like it's insane it's it's huge
yeah yeah yeah
and so and and that combined with you
know having
so so so so many japanese restaurants
and also really good korean restaurants
and all that uh very close by
it's like after the con you everyone
goes like to all these japanese
restaurants um together and it's like an
amazing experience because there's no
other city in germany that has so many
authentic amazing japanese restaurants
and combining you know the the
convention experience with the good food
is is is
so nice yeah
so um that's what that's why i guess
it's my favorite it is a long trip from
australia
but yeah it's really really dope
i wonderland of culture mixing yeah yeah
yeah yeah
and and
so
where was i so i flew over there uh
on first day and
um
yeah soon
i checked in and then soon as soon very
soon after
manychat
my managers
managers manager manager
i mean there was more than there were
more than just um
uh genma but i will not say who else was
there anyway there was definitely genma
um and i was so so so so so so so so so
so happy to see genma you know i was i
was in my room in a uh
like like a few minutes after me uh
genma arrived at the hotel as well and i
i i ran down
i got out of the elevator and jenna was
standing in front of the reception
talking to the other
uh cover staff members
and i ran over there with full speed i
was like
and i gave her a big big hug
and everyone was looking at us the cover
staff and the reception staff were
looking at us like
pepe
oh so happy i haven't seen her since
what
end of february
i think
in february i think so
wow it's been such a long time
i was very very excited no yaga was not
there
yanko was not there yeah she brought me
a lot of stuff like i asked her she
asked me if she should bring something
for me from japan so i asked for ramen
noodles
um and
she brought me some
merchandise that
i asked for um previously and she was
like storing for me for a while um
and uh
she brought me letters
yes
yeah masks masks masks as well i asked
her for masks because japan has more
like types of masks in your fancy uh and
yeah she
[Music]
no no birthday merch no actually
i asked if i can get the samples that
were shown that jaguar was showing but
no i i can't get that either they need
that in the company's apparent in the
company apparently so i cannot have that
unfortunately i have to wait as long as
you guys have to wait
yeah ah that's that's a bummer but let
me drink my my mama mama
orange
yeah
jago claimed it yago needs them ya go
hoarding it younger wearing it at home
no walking around in a kfba oh man nope
not yet no kfb airplane yet no kfp
slippers yet no not for me anyway that's
okay that's okay but she brought me so
so many things
i think now after bringing me all these
things her
suitcase must be empty
so uh so we met and then
um
i think
because i wanted to just eat with gen mo
uh the other the other stuff
uh went somewhere else and i just wanted
to eat with general
so me and genma had dinner
um
it was already pretty late and
uh
well
yeah so we didn't go anywhere too
special
it was a basic dinner but it was fun
because i had it with gemma
um
yeah and we ate
uh schnitzel
you see the thing is like me coming to
dusseldorf after a long time not being
in japan what i come for is for japanese
food yeah i want to eat japanese food
when i'm in dusseldorf but genma
just came from japan so
what she should eat in this love is
german food obviously or like european
food so yeah for the first night um
i let let her eat
german slash australian food because
schnitzel is australian
although i have to say
um
digital
in australia is a million times better
than the one that we had uh
in that place
i mean i'm sure there's a like good
schnitzel in somewhere in germany too
i'm sure of it but the one that we had
was really meh at least from my
perspective from her perspective it was
probably good
uh but
yeah
um
this is not the first time she ate uh
schnitzel though i had her eat it in
japan before because i i brought her to
an australian restaurant in japan which
i found and i was so proud of finding it
because it was actually good food in
japan i mean like good australian food
in japan where you you can't find that
anyone else normally oh my god i'm
already dancing
naturally of course
vienna vienna schnitzel uh
anyway so it was it was i think she
enjoyed it and yeah we had dinner and it
was nice and
then
yeah it was already bedtime so
we parted ways until
on the next day
on friday actually so
i i i also had lots of friends uh
uh coming to
the
coming to dokomi so on friday
uh
because i really missed this you know
convention
experience
that
i haven't been able to experience for a
long time because of reasons first of
all me not being in uh europe in the
first place for a whole year
and then second of all
well
deceiving
yeah
so
i hung out on friday most of all with my
friends and then later on in the evening
i had rehearsal
for dokomi because dokomi starts at
saturday it goes on until sunday
and on friday uh was rehearsal day
um had to be on friday so we did we did
it on friday and then we also after the
rehearsal we um
had like a welcome dinner for me
yeah rehearsal was
interesting
but in the end it
it went well i i guess
it went just fine could have gone worse
everything could have gone much much
worse but we kind of we managed to
get everything working the way it should
i brought my
my super new
alienware laptop by the way which is
super sexy my alienware laptop i got i
got it in like a white
white color
it's a white beautiful alienware laptop
that was uh pretty expensive but it's
like really really good hashtag nuts but
not sponsored
but i got this a while ago because my
current laptop is like first of all
too weak to begin with
and second of all uh
like kind of dying for some reason like
i can't even use it if it's not charged
it will immediately turn itself off
[Music]
so
batteries wear out yeah but it's only
been like what two years
since i had that
laptop and i i'm i feel sad because it's
like so cute it's like a pink like a
rose
rose uh
metallic rose
um
tiny tiny small short uh
light weighted laptop
yeah and i've been using it for a while
two users about right these days eh
rose gold
i don't know if i would call it rose
gold
nah i don't think it's rose gold no
not exactly
buy and change the battery i don't know
i mean i gotta i got a new laptop now
anyway because like my my the other
laptop wouldn't be good enough to use
for travel
um
so
we did that on friday and now we reach
the day
that is important saturday so i was i
was a guest on saturday only
uh
by my choice
and
and on saturday so the program was as
you have seen probably because i had my
waiting room
up on youtube
and
was uh
i decided with a podcast
um
the podcast was the second thing on the
program very early still uh right after
the opening ceremony was the podcast
with um the organizers of
dokomi
and
and like they they did uh some kind of
like
interview
slash chit chat
and like like a game that we did in
digikommi as well remember did you call
me that was something i wanted to say a
few moments ago but i
uh interrupted myself i think did you
call me dickie comey is um
that online convention that i was on a
while ago
when was that a few months ago
and it was on twitch remember
i did some stuff there
but i did that from home because it's an
only online convention
and it was like a thing that dokomi came
up with because of the see thing
um
to still you know bring out some kind of
content and
that was like an online convention and
that was fun that was fun that was the
first time i worked with them
but they also invited me to the real
convention which i was the most excited
about and was really looking forward to
mm-hmm
so
we did something there and on the
economy that we also did on tokumi the
otaku exposed thingy anyway let me show
you some pictures
i hope you guys watched some of it on
twitch though
because uh i mean it was fully german
but there were thank you translated
in the chat
and uh i think especially the karaoke
you don't really need to know german for
it
uh the podcast i can understand but yeah
i mean
i don't have that many like
different kind of pictures but
they're mostly from inside of the little
concert hall
and
so okay well oh well i got i guess we're
gonna show this
um
there was a there was a opening ceremony
i oh my god it's huge i wasn't really
even aware that they introduced me there
but
so it was like that
big stage
oh wait is that a different room
[Music]
is that is that not the main concert
room thing because i just realized the
stage kind of looks different
i guess they have two
that looks eh
black stage oh
oh they had a different stage room as
well
makes sense
i think i've seen it
that was a different one and then that
after that opening ceremony ended is
when the podcast started
and the podcast the podcast was like
a
was like these
oh
small oops it's small
[Music]
small
okay there we go okay
so um
i was on this big screen
and we just talked talked a lot about
like convention things
and like the general uh topic was um
convention fever
this was streamed on twitch and of
course shown there in the
convention and like
i i prepared some stories beforehand to
tell them
uh
i i only knew that the topic would be
convention fever i wasn't exactly
aware of what exactly where
we're gonna talk about so i just wrote
down a few things that i thought of
uh from my experiences of going to
conventions do you guys want to hear
them in english because i taught them in
in german do you want to hear them
i got called an eternal boom
shut up
yeah okay so hmm
[Music]
yeah one thing
that i told
uh
was
oh yeah that like when you're like on a
convention
you walk you you want to go somewhere
from point a to point b
and um
the guys on the stage they are uh the
organizers of the convention for many
years
for many many years since the beginning
and they were like part of the podcast
anyway so yeah you want to go from point
a to point b
and then
uh you walk
and then you meet someone five meters
later
and then you chit-chat cause you can't
you can't ignore them
and then you keep on walking after a
while and you see people again and you
talk to them for 20 minutes and then you
finally get to walk again and then five
minute meters five meters later again
you see someone and it just keeps on
going on like that and going on and
going on and going on
yeah the walking tangent kind of yeah
you never get to where you want to go
because you keep on getting interrupted
by knowing so many people that is a
little bit of an issue and that
definitely is something that i
experienced on sunday as well
yeah
um
it's like going shopping with your
mother
i cannot
confirm that or deny that because i
cannot relate
uh yeah so anyway
that was a story that i told
um
and then we also talked about like what
was your first convention ever and my
first convention ever was actually not a
convention in australia
but one in germany which
i i was super super young
so
um going to a big convention in germany
instead of just going to a small one or
so in your own country is kind of weird
um but like i had a uh two friends back
then
um
who
uh
already went there before i think like a
year before and they were gonna go again
and they were my senpai's at school
and they wanted to go and
and i asked if uh i could go with them i
guess and then we went there it's many
many years ago and it was uh in in
leipzig
in germany it was actually a book fair
leipzig book fair but
um the leipzig book fair has a huge
haul for like anime stuff like it's
basically its own anime convention
and has a big big big visiting of like
weebs and uh
cosplayers and all that kind of people
so it's basically like an anime
convention even though it's called book
fair
and the people the normal people who go
to the book fair they they're like
always like so whoa what's going on here
what's with all these people in these
costumes so
it's a it's a huge like culture shock
for the normies who come there and not
knowing it although it is
nowadays it is quite famous so the
people who live in leipzig and go to the
book fair they know that at the book
fair they will meet all these costumed
people and so on and
so like they they go there and they
they ask everyone for pictures and so on
so it's really funny yeah because
you don't see that kind of cultural
exchange in uh normal conventions you
only see that in like these kind of book
fairs i think
it's it's really interesting so that was
my first convention and i really really
liked it even but it was a it was a huge
huge new world that opened up for me
yeah um
so that was that and then
um oh yeah that was
it was one story that i want to tell you
um
i i kind of threw that topic in the room
because i wrote that story down and i
don't know how else i'm gonna tell the
story so i was like yo what's what's
your
convention with the worst weather ever
what's what's in the conventional
experience with the worst convention
tell me
and i was like for example for me
um
there was again a leipzig book fair uh
i think like maybe
three years ago
probably
um i went there with my friends again um
with with a car it was a road trip it
took like 10 hours or so
and um
we were driving it was march
uh and
in germany slash
australia
in march
um
it doesn't snow in april it does
sometimes because like we have april
weather i told you guys before about
this phenomenon
um
uh where in april the weather keeps on
changing between summer weather and
winter weather and all that but then in
march it's normally normal
yeah april is where spring starts and
march is already like
no wait no
wait wait
wait what am i
no wait
wait march is before april what the hell
eh wait a second
lexic book fair was in march right
wait what was it in may
i'm i'm confusing things do i mean may
when was lactic book fair actually
does someone actually know i wasn't
march
it's usually in march but then well then
i guess
well it was still it was still unusual
because it was not just like a tiny
little bit of snow but it was so much
snow so we were driving in this
really old car
uh for some reason it was not heating up
we were freezing our asses off we had
like five blankets on top of us i was
sitting in the back
squeezed in between my friends
and uh yeah we had a full car with lots
of luggage and lots of people and uh
oh so it was so freaking cold and
we were driving and then we arrived and
it was freaking cold and everyone got
into their airbnbs and
um
uh
in life in life take there was like five
meters tall snow
it was crazy it was crazy because we
never had that before i've been to
leipzig book fair so many times and the
weather was always like it was kind of
chilly cool but it was never bad weather
it was never snowing was never really
raining or so
but
okay five meters is probably
exaggerating
but it was really really really really
so much snow
and uh
yeah anyway so this was really
surprising to because aft so many years
of livestick book fair have passed and
there was no snow
never never was there ever snow
so yeah anyway we were there and uh we
went into the convention hall
and in in leipzig book fair there's this
huge
huge um like entrance hall
from where on you can go to all these
other halls and that's where like
everyone hangs out usually like me and
my friends usually hung out there
and um
the hall inside was uh warm it was
pretty warm outside was freezing cold
ton of snow but inside it was warm
so
oh we we thought oh this is nice we
don't go outside anyway we're always in
this hall so whatever
but
the whole time
because of i guess like all the snow
outside and then the people warming up
inside i guess i don't know how exactly
this happens chemistry physics whatever
uh but the hole is like really really
tall it's like a glass hole
that that's like kind of round and
really really tall and from the top
water was dripping from the top
it's like yeah
condensation a shaken of water it really
was like as if it was raining
because it was not just a little bit it
was quite a lot the whole time
it yeah it kind of like started raining
inside the hall
and um
people in the hall were being amused and
joking about it because we were like oh
this is the sweat of everyone like if
you think about it it's like everyone's
sweat i don't know i i don't
we were joking about it but i guess it's
not really but it's like yeah you know
condensation whatever whatever i see
but yeah it was going on like that for
two days that was funny yeah so i told
them that story
it was just cold man out i was
dying ah oh my god it was so cold
that was the worst car drive road trip
to a convention and back home that i've
ever had
because there was literally no heating
in the car no matter how many blankets i
put on myself i was freezing and we were
driving like for 10 hours through the
night and you would think that you would
want to sleep right but how can you
sleep if you're freezing your ass off
yeah that was painful
anyway so i was telling them some
stories like that and uh
uh yeah i'm gonna keep it at that so
that was the podcast and now we did some
uh otaku x post which was like they gave
us a question like uh what was one of
the questions um
can you sleep before a convention
uh yes or no or something like that and
then we had to we had to say our answer
and also we like if you ever get so
excited that you can't sleep at
a convention we have to answer the
question and then we have to guess the
percentage
of what the twitch viewers
uh would uh answer like 60 or whatever
yeah so we did that that was fun that
was fun there was one hour um
and then after that
um oh by the way let me say one thing uh
the convention usually is much much much
like bigger as in it has more visitors
but for obvious reasons it had less uh
it was only allowed to let in less
people than usually there is a
limitation obviously and um
well
still even then it was big like
even then it was really crowded
uh
i don't know if i'm allowed to say the
number so i'm not going to say it but
uh it was fully booked
saturday was already fully booked before
my appearance was even announced anyway
so
yeah it was fully booked it was full
capacity and for like
i would let you know for you know
see thing uh security reasons don't
worry
like at the in the concert hall for
example
um
they had to keep on seats
spaced in between
they did not let in the full capacity
capacity that the concert hall could
actually take because you know you
wouldn't want it to be fully packed this
is for security reasons um people
unfortunately not everyone who wanted in
was let in i heard some people were
trying to get into the concert hall i'm
sorry about that
um
but it is for regulations and stuff to
make sense right so
sorry about that but yeah i think i
think that's good because you know
dokomi is taking it seriously if they
wouldn't then dokomi would not be able
to
happen in the first place um they took
it very seriously and then and at the
entrance they checked every every
visitor who was entering
for
you know if they had
some kind of you know something
and yeah so after that after the podcast
that was uh 12
p.m right
p.m not a.m
and
and then at after that two hours later
well it ended at 1 p.m so i had one hour
break until the meet and greet which
happened at 2 p.m
and the meet and greet was basically
and let me see
[Music]
let me check one thing
if i can show that picture
it was a room
it was not that small
um
a decent sized room
and and in there was a monster with a
microphone and a webcam
so i could see you guys
and hear you guys properly
and it looked like these
this the person that's in there at that
photo is someone who interviewed me some
some oopsie what the hell was that some
media person
uh
from some media
so this is okay to show
and so it looks like this i was on two
screens actually
in the back on the table there were some
presents thank you guys
um
yeah so this is how it was it was one
room there was always a staff member
inside who um every time someone left
the room she was
this this
she was like
alcoholizing the room
she was disinfecting is that the word in
english what's the word in english
yeah she desanitized it yes she was
de-sanitizing everything and then the
next person could come in so
every time the door opens i gave
everyone a big loud cake
[Music]
it was so much fun everyone had like
approximately three minutes four minutes
but
um
around around three minutes i was always
like yo you want to quickly take a
selfie uh because the other people
didn't usually want to do it it's the
only chance you'll get so
usually it was a little bit more than
three minutes
but that's okay we're not that strict
yeah um but mostly three minutes
and and and
[Music]
yeah we talked there so
um
i think like
a lot of them a lot of you guys were
very nervous
uh which is totally fine i can
understand i was nervous too
i was pretty nervous too
yeah but i warmed up after
uh
i guess the first i think after the
first person i was already warmed up the
first chicken
but i was nervous and uh
it was it was uh
such a
different experience like
being able to
talk
to you guys one-on-one
with voice
having a conversation like that was so
special so
so i was nervous as oh me too
yo some of you guys are here in the chat
hello
anyway it was so so so so so so special
and i you know i thought
i'm a good tanto i know you chickens
would chicken out so i knew you guys
would be nervous and maybe um completely
blank out when i would ask you
like
like um
but
i was thinking like there's some some of
you guys prepared like a had like a
whole plan of what to tell me but but
some of you guys were really chickening
out nervous and blanking out and i i i
usually would ask like
do you have something to tell me or
should i help you out
and a lot of them would say like oh yeah
uh please help me
[Laughter]
so i am i helped out no problem i i
asked stuff like so where are you from
and they were actually not everyone uh
was from germany there were um some
people from like
um the netherlands so so in
america
even um so yeah some other places in
europe uh mostly germany though of
course mostly germany
but dokomi is usually a convention that
is visited by people all around europe
it's very popular for like you know
usually there's a lot of people from
france a lot of people from australia a
lot of people from netherlands and
belgium and so on yeah yeah yeah so
this time of course again a lot of
different countries coming to see me
yeah
no we also with some of them i talked in
english as well um because not everyone
spoke german but that was fine so
yeah
this dude is not me
someone else if that's me no it's not me
um
so yeah we were talking and i'll ask
things like where you're from and how
long have you been watching my streams
and
so many of them said from the beginning
a lot of them i would say like
17 60 70 percent
said they were uh in it from the
beginning
a few ones like maybe half a year
or so
and
the tiniest amount was very recently
like one or two months that was a tiny
amount
[Music]
but the most of them were from the
beginning so
i was so
like
moved and like
emotionally moved
to hear that and a bunch of them um
already liked whole life and were
watching her live before
whole live english as well and some of
them just jumped in right at the time
when the whole life english came out so
yeah i don't know it was it was so
special and i asked them like what kind
of streams they like the most that i do
and and some of them like said like
karaoke
one of them said my fire emblem streams
i was like yo what
yeah and uh
oh yeah well some of them said for their
favorite streams like um members only
movie watch along specifically uh one of
them said um lord of the the lord of the
rings watch the lungs and i was like
that's the one you choose for your
favorite stream wow okay cool thank you
that was really special for me too
yeah and another one was like i like you
i liked your um kimi no nava your name
movie watch along the most from the
recent ones i guess yeah yeah yeah
yeah there were um there was a lot of
interesting choices there that i would
have not expected um
[Music]
yeah
also
oh my god
some of them came in the
um
the
the whole myth t-shirts that i designed
a long time ago that came out like
months ago
you know the black t-shirt with my art
on it some of them were wearing it it's
so perfect the perfect occasion to wear
it right
um i was so happy to see that and and
some of them had like self-made uh or
like uh purchased somewhere else uh uh
whole live holy myth merchandise like um
some of them were wearing i think
self-made kfp hats
and i saw someone wearing like um
a kiana t-shirt and someone uh brought
actually and gifted it to me but this is
also i guess self-made merchandise um
a kfp bucket if you
if you look closely in the background
you see it
you see it on on the very left
and okay it was only on one side it's
juggle on the other side it was my face
and it was self-made and really really
cool really pretty
yeah it was really cute like um seeing
these people there were some um who also
were cosplaying and some were dressed
just normally which is totally fine of
course as well uh not having any of that
merchandise is totally fine maybe you
also left it at home maybe you didn't
receive it yet whatever no problem but
it was cool to see
people wearing the merchandise coming to
the convention representing kfp
representing her alive i was so excited
to see that yeah
that's not a sheep that's an alpaca
because i i said i like alpacas
actually to the guy who brought me the
bucket i was like
well you're giving me the bucket
shouldn't you keep it because you're
gonna need it soon
you're gonna be in that bucket soon
but no uh he gave it to me you cannot
escape the bucket though don't think you
can escape it it's not an option
[Music]
um
what else what else oh yeah a bunch of
you guys
again brought me presents thank you very
much we looked through them already um
this was like the only the only um
current possibility to give me any
presence because i mean whole life
english
um for their birth dates we were never
able to receive presents and then
um now they got like turned off
completely even for whole life japan so
no presents for us but i asked if like
we could make it a possibility to just
uh make an exception for dokomi and
you know
um
yeah say it's okay then check it at the
spot and and yeah so uh genma went for
all the presents i already looked for
them too but i had no space in my
suitcase so we're sending it um to my
home
it shouldn't take too long because from
germany to australia it really only
takes like three to four days or so i
think but i already took a look
yeah
no no nothing nothing bad everyone was
being good
thank you thank you oh yeah that reminds
me um i mentioned it briefly but genma
also gave me the letters that have uh
stacked up uh since the last time i
received fan letters in japan um
yeah yeah i received them as well thank
you very much everyone
yeah it was really sweet a lot of your
gifts were really um adorable and
thoughtful a bunch of self-made ones as
well
very cute
thank you everyone
[Music]
thank
and you know it was fun after after
every person that came in
uh when the time came
um
uh to say goodbye
i
i would always go like and in german we
say
and they all said from there on their
own without me saying it they all said
au vida
yeah
i was so happy
i'm so happy that already made me so
happy to hear that um
[Music]
oh man the brainwashing is working no
it's not brainwashing we're saying
goodbye okay it's nothing bad
[Music]
oh man
that was fun that was so much fun the
greeting
the talk the ending everything was fun
about it
was there anything else i wanted to say
i think that was
i i also heard that like
uh
i was so happy today it's like kfb
meeting great visitors we're bonding
because like they they went to dinner
together and stuff on the previous day
before the meeting great and i guess
they also hung out after the meet and
greet and after the concert and all that
so
sweet
oh man
so sweet i'm so happy to hear that yeah
we're a family you guys are a family
[Music]
i'm so happy that you guys are so
friendly with one another and i think
like some of you guys already knew one
another but i also heard that some of
you guys who didn't know one another
uh made friends as well and um like got
to know each other and found like new
new cool people in the kfc community so
ah
i'm so happy to hear that
oh man
oh man it's so wholesome
so
that's it
[Music]
birds of a feather flock together
exactly thank you for the super chat
thank you
ah
oh man so this meet and greet was so so
special i was um
i was i was so so glad i could do this
and it was my idea originally because i
saw that japanese members and whole life
japan in japan did this a bunch of times
already um it is not such an uncommon
thing um
they did it previously and i was asking
if we could do it in in dokomi because i
thought it would be a nice uh
opportunity to do it and um to make it
even more special to have some more
stuff beside the podcast and the karaoke
and yeah they they thankfully agreed and
uh
helped set it all up
and it went really well um
it went really well and i will never
forget this this was so special i mean
it was so fast it was so so so so fast
now like it felt so it like
afterwards like during the meet and
greet it didn't feel like that insanely
fast but afterwards it was like
it's already over oh no
oh no
why
but yeah yes i think there will be more
chances in the future um
this is actually something that you
could even do if you're not there in
person i guess
you could totally do it
but
um
so yeah i think we don't yeah we don't
even have to be there in person
i was there in person but
still you could do it
even if you're not there in person so um
everyone who was not able to go
especially because it was sold out at
the moment when i was already announced
um sorry about that if you couldn't go
and if you couldn't go to germany to
begin with if that was the problem if
you're like far far away don't worry
don't worry i think there will be more
opportunities
i can't wait to make a question but one
day i'd love to meet you i'm sure there
will be a day like that just don't give
up yet um
so that was the meet and greet it went
on for like approximately an hour or so
and afterwards
it was the concert uh so this ended at 3
p.m
and then the concert was at 5 00 p.m so
i had a little bit of time in between
but
uh i was uh very very busy no break
because i was first of all it was a
surprise for every participant
this was not
said beforehand but
everyone got
these kind of
other personally personalized
autographed
uh postcards
guys
these ones are um for the organizers i
just took a photo of those i took a
photo of the others as well but um i
don't know
these ones are safe to show and still i
oh i still pixelated them
sensitive just in case uh but this is
also the first time that
you guys saw my signature
i had it ready for a while already uh
it's not so easy to see here because i
was riding with a shiny silver pen
um but the tea is like it has wings
and then
the a's have little chickens inside
yeah that was a surprise for all the
meet and greet visitors they all
received one of those so after the meet
and greet i was busy writing um a
message and and the autograph for each
one of them and they were given out to
everyone um i think
before
the concert perhaps
is
and you guys liked it i saw you guys
talking about it on twitter
i'm glad you guys like it uh the
signature it's a it's a bit childish uh
i still i still want to kind of improve
it a little bit but
this is this is how it is right now
that is really rare that's really
special yeah
really special so big big thank you to
everyone who participated in the meet
and greet and don't worry everyone else
i'm sure you'll get a chance to uh if
you wanna if you want it you just gotta
keep an eye out for conventions where
hello live english will be appearing and
i'm sure um we can make it happen at
some point yeah
so that was that
and
i received them
a bunch of really cute gifts that i
don't know if i should show this
but one of the gifts that
um they were all super special i love
them all but one of them that i want to
mention is i received like an art book a
really proper uh properly made beautiful
art book
um
um that had like all kinds of
uh kfp
um fan art and takanawa fan art in it
from all the kfc fan artists it's really
really beautiful really pretty i love it
i love it
and it's like i guess it's a one of a
kind um it had like a special message on
the first page
um
uh that was like
seemed to be particularly tailored for
one of dokomi
kind art book just for me thank you guys
all the other presents were amazing i'm
so happy but i can't wait that day um i
can't wait until they arrive soon
i'm
waiting i'm waiting until they arrive at
my home
yeah that was the meet and greet and
then
after signing those cards and uh
preparing
[Music]
and preparing the
this was also streamed on twitch and you
can still watch it if you wanna you can
even go to twitch or i think there have
been clips being uploaded on on youtube
already and i think dokomi will also
upload the archive on youtube eventually
um but yeah you can also watch it if you
missed it the wave was wild i wanted to
do the waves the waves so bad yeah i was
so excited to do it so
um again
well
the there had to be like seats
[Music]
free in between but it was filled up
there were so many people i was so
excited i was so excited
hey i'll show you like um
[Music]
um
yeah
look
it's filled up so many people thank you
everyone for coming
yeah i'm so excited so many people came
yeah and on twitch also so many people
are watching on twitch as well i
actually have a second laptop uh open
next to my own uh with the twitch stream
open to see what the people on twitte on
the twitch stream were writing because i
was curious about the comments i was
actually watching
although i was multitasking so bad um
because like this this setup was really
really different for me and it was kind
of difficult um i have to say it was it
was really difficult to stream with this
different setup different microphone um
only one screen
only one laptop screen where i had to
have everything open like the music and
obs and the lyrics and the set list uh
my memos everything had to be opened
there um
so that's why i had one my laptop opened
on the side with the twitch uh page to
look at what's going on there um
yeah yeah but it was thai hen totem
hotel
let me show
[Music]
i was uh basically
uh oh yeah wait wait i didn't tell you
but if you've seen the cinema you
already know about it but the background
that you see here that i'm showing here
um that i'm on there is a new karaoke
concert background that i commissioned
um a little while ago to use generally
but i wanted it in time for dokomi to um
like show it for the first time ever at
dokomi have like i wanted a proper
backdrop not just some
boring backdrop that i used normally
so i got this um a concert hall
background with chickens and they're
moving and the lights are moving there
too
and i will show you because this week we
have a karaoke concert um
the day after tomorrow i'm doing a
karaoke stream so you can check it out
in full action but yes
[Applause]
[Music]
mastery i was so excited i really wanted
like a cool stage of my own that's like
personalized in the background there's a
screen that's moving um the takanasi
kiana the blue one i mean and then
there's in the four
in front of that there's another screen
moving the chickens are moving some of
them slacking off some of them partying
one of them is djing the lights are
super cool
yeah and i can i can make myself small
and stand like in full body on it if i
wanna and i can be in close up depends
on how i want to do it yeah
yeah so i was singing a bunch of whole
life songs
and also
um
my originals three of my originals
uh hinotonii sparks and her challenger
heart challenger i actually sang twice
because they wanted an ankuru i sang
heart challenge as the first song
and then at the end when i was done
people asked for for an
encore and i was like
i actually i didn't think about it
i i completely
ignored the possibility that that could
happen i didn't think about it at all so
i didn't prepare anything at all i
didn't if i would be on my current pc
then i could quickly whip out something
but on um
on the new laptop that i literally just
set up a day before
uh i had nothing i only had the the
songs and i was preparing
to begin with so i had to sing another
song that i already had song so i sang
heart challenger that i sang at the
beginning i sang it again at the end
which i think in the end was fine
because um
i think on twitch i don't i don't know
if it was the same in the concert hall i
hope not but on twitch the the audio
quality was really really bad in the
beginning sorry about that so
um to make up for that i guess singing
heart challenger again at the end uh the
audio was better then so
that that was good so apparently yeah
midway through the
the the audio improved
[Music]
yeah i
i i i'm sorry about it but but like i
think both dokomi and me
and
it was a very very new experience we
for both parties it was
something new a new challenge
uh
so i guess we all learned something from
it hopefully
and hopefully the next time we can
improve
on what went wrong but i think generally
i'm just i'm just really happy that
generally it worked out
there were other issues that we fixed
and i'm just really happy that for most
of it uh it went fine and um
we safely managed to deliver a concert
so i i'm glad about that mm-hmm
yeah so there were actually people
with glow sticks there
um
i was oh my god you guys have no idea
like i didn't know that there would be
people with those things and i didn't
expect it but i was like sometimes i was
peeking over to the twitch stream and
that's when i saw the glow sticks
and
you have no idea how
how special that was to me not only the
glowsticks but also just generally like
hearing everyone's cheering voices
oh man
it gave me so many feels
it it just
threw me back
oh
i was out i was really moved oh my god
hey cuz like it normal cuddles i don't
see you guys but in this one i saw you
guys and
it was so special
[Music]
i was so glad i could do it
thank you for cheering me on i know it
must have been i don't know maybe
somebody was shy or someone everyone was
like doing their best to cheer me on
when i was doing my stupid like oh
and like
it was it was really really cool it was
like
it was like a deja vu
it was like flashbacks and
it was amazing i i am
i am amazed um
that this was possible
so cool
i hope we can do this more often i want
to do it more often
i i felt something inside of me
some fire
that sparked
it sparked really i'm a more
it sparked really a lot
it was i was having fireworks inside of
myself yeah i started a fire on that day
ah
it
ah it's
it's um
so different from you know sitting here
and streaming this is fun too this is
fun too and great
a great job for every day but in between
having something like this
i don't even know what to say anymore
oh
[Music]
foreign
thank you guys so much and i think next
time i didn't i didn't think about the
pen lights like i didn't think about
many things as it seems but
next time i want to like like have every
i want i want everyone to have pen
lights so either either i will prepare
them maybe have like pen light
merchandise or something like that i
don't know or you guys he goes on
hikosan is in the chat
made the stage
because i want to take to make it and
[Music]
she's the one who draws pikula artwork
every day
thank you for this cool saints the
chickens are so cute
[Music]
yeah but did you know this is kind of
like stream streams like
screencaption screen stream strap
caption
because
um
i'm on the screen
on a screen
on the screen if you were watching
twitch
if you are watching twitch anyone we're
watching me
on the screen on the screen perhaps even
on the screen because on twitch there
were um they were switching angles which
i found really cool they were showing my
my direct feed from um what you see here
on the screen
uh
which is i guess actually not a screen
is actually a beamer
a projector but still let's call it a
screen so they were showing the direct
feed but they were also showing the the
the audience
and like
the audience point of view still with
the screen on there as well
so that really gave a nice feeling of
hey i'm actually like at a real
convention
yeah
actually this is the first time
in a long time that someone from whole
life did a like in-person concert with
real people there again
first time in a long time
and for for i mean for whole life
english of course it's the first time to
begin with so
i will treasure
this super special experience forever
i i i i
i cannot forget it anyway
i'm also really happy about the lola
wave and the footage from that i love it
i love it so much when everyone gets up
and does like they froze their hands up
in the air like they just don't care
yeah
and then they go down again but i was
having so much fun that i quickly went
from one side to another
like swoosh swoosh swoosh and
they could barely keep up because
phoenix goes
speed yeah but they did their best to
keeping up and i'm really excited
because i have to say
um
it is generally not that easy to animate
a crowd
and at conventions especially like from
what i've seen like i don't go much to
like concerts and conventions and like
panels and conventions stuff like that
but whenever i was in one and was like
in the audience
everyone was like meh barely even
clapping after like a song or after some
kind of performance
oh everyone is very shy yeah they don't
they um yeah so i think like shouting
something like time yay
during a song
was also
a big step and i am i'm i am so excited
that you guys were participating so much
and
thank you i really felt the passion and
the excitement and the heat i felt it
it made me feel so proud of kfp
i was so proud i was so proud i was so
proud
uh because like
because because i asked i must think
that you know the
the organizers and so on must must have
been really happy to see that too
and i'm just happy to make others happy
to have their satisfaction yeah
and and on the next day actually i saw a
clip of that when um
on the next man on the next day um
um um they were um
there was like another opening ceremony
or something like that i guess where
they reflected on what happened the
previous day and the the the mc the
moderator girl was talking about my
concert and she said it was really cool
everyone was so passionate and so hyped
up and excited they were doing that wave
it was so much fun yeah
yeah
i was i was happy to hear all that
feedback
maybe they were shocked to see how
passionate we were i i think that might
be true yeah
[Music]
oh someone i think in the comments was
like uh
was it really only kfb though i actually
like in between like the songs i asked
uh like who knows who live who knows me
and stuff and from what i heard like i
had i had feedback from the audience
not in the very beginning in the
beginning was turned off um on twitch
end for me
uh when i was like when i was on screen
for the first second it was like hey do
you guys hear me
and i heard nothing
and i was like okay i guess you do
probably probably
she started singing that was really
awkward but the feedback was turned on
later afterwards during the concert i
don't know at what point but in the
beginning was turned up so
it was not really that awkward
so
anyway so at some point i was asking the
audience questions like you you know how
live they know takanashikiya blah blah
blah it seemed like
i i barely heard any any no's any nines
i barely heard any
so i don't know maybe my feedback was
too quiet but uh i didn't hear anything
so
um
[Music]
that was wait wasn't that uh during the
podcast that was in the very beginning
but i wasn't sure if they were hearing
me i was like tested
the whole time just behind me i had the
sound check guy
uh
talking in walkie talkies
i was like this is this is just waiting
until he gives me the okay yeah they
hear you
says yes i was doing that for a couple
minutes
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah they didn't react
i don't know i wasn't sure if they hear
me anyway they heard me eventually
yeah oh man so
i also sang two anime songs by the way i
sang uh what time because i thought
it would be great to have the audience
shout for for a time with me and because
i thought people know that song
and i also sang i was gonna know
rhapsody
uh which is just uh i think a song that
usually maybe showcases my singing
skills also it's a song that pretty much
everyone knows and it's a cute song
and yeah
so
i hope you guys like the song choices um
mixed in uh whole live songs one of them
i never sang before
and i was i was happy to
[Music]
i sang two
two which one was it uh the one that i
didn't sang before was out
i was on a clear sky
wait was that the title the australian
rhapsody confuses me right now
no i was on a blue sky
clear sky blue
oh
i saw you know
blue
clear sky
okay that anime song confused me i'm
sorry blue skyrim
heart conqueror heart conquering
stream sparks challenger we like mixing
up our
names yeah the color blue what is it
with blue oh my god blue
blue challenger blue clapper
heart clapper blue
heart clapper all over again
yeah um i have to say i was very nervous
uh i messed up kiddo maggie writer a lot
i will i will sing it better next time i
was pretty nervous
uh
and i didn't
um
i didn't have
i didn't really have feedback uh in my
headphones of my own voice
uh so i had to take up one ear
and i was like trying to listen to my
own voice through one ear and on the
other on the headphone one ear of the
headphone i was listening to the music
i hope it was okay
because again it was very different from
my usual setup but i i hope it was okay
where can i find that twitch channel
it's uh dokomi dokomitv
twitch.tv slash dokomitv i think
you nailed it
i think everything besides kinda make it
rather was okay
but
well in the beginning the audio quality
i think wasn't so good so i don't know
if you could even notice
[Music]
ah
yeah anyway i think i think i think all
in all it was uh great
i'm very very happy with this experience
i think
i did everything i could and i had so
much fun i had an absolute blast i will
never forget this i'm proud of myself
and i'm proud of you guys i'm proud of
my audience so so much
and uh
yeah it was amazing so that was saturday
afterwards after the concert well
i cleaned up stuff
and then i actually went to dinner with
my friends
or i wanted to go to a certain place but
it was closed and i was really
disappointed so one thing that i was
looking forward to the most
uh
was a certain tonkatsu place
because like in my city
um well we have ramen places so that's
cool but we don't have any
like
tonkatsu places that's not a thing
that's not a thing it seems and tonkatsu
is basically my favorite japanese food
so i went i went to this tonkatsu place
recently like previously when i went to
um dokomi
and
i was so excited to go there again this
time
but
dokumi this year was held at a different
time that it usually is um happening on
usually it's in
in spring
and this time it wasn't summer and that
tonkatsu place apparently
went on a summer break i don't
know if they do that every year
but i was so
so sad
i was so sad tonkatsu in this love it's
called uh tonkatsu gonta
it's really good and they don't only
have tonkatsu now this is really weird
because the tonkatsu place would never
sell this
but they also had honey tosto
it's like a really big toast
with fruit and ice cream and all kinds
of
really yummy they usually have that in
like karaoke places in japan and i don't
know why they combined that but
it's uh i
i was really looking forward to eating
that as well
[Music]
for me
i was so sad i was so sad i was so
unlucky so i'm planning to just
privately privately next month or
whatever go privately to dusseldorf
for one day a one day trip
eat the freaking tonkatsu and ate the
freaking honey tails because i i i no no
this was just besides the the the
concert and the meet and greet and all
that this was the one thing that i was
looking forward to the most and meeting
genma of course
but this was the other thing that i was
looking forward to the most
i wanted it so bad and i couldn't get it
it was taken away from me and i don't
deserve that so i'll go there
again
yes
although i guess i will be eating alone
because i don't have friends and
dusseldorf and my friends here in my
city i doubt that they will make the
trip with me
oh wait i could i guess i hm maybe maybe
some dokomi staff can go with me
i guess some of them live in this love
maybe
yeah treat yourself yeah get that
tonkatsu
they have like really authentic tonkatsu
so i was so excited for it
yeah and my friends they were actually
really excited for it too because on the
previous year
um
when
when we went there it was the first
first document year where it was
actually like there because they opened
up newly
er
and it had it
taught it
and when i opened up newly and um i
brought i dragged my friends in there
um
and uh
and they uh
uh sorry brain is currently turning
itself off and restarting for some
reason
but they really really liked it and i
was so happy to have brought them to a
place that they really enjoyed
it
[Music]
yeah windows windows installed
ah so anyway next time on that day we
ended up um going to a place like um
uh i i ate ramen
and they ate okonomiyaki
which
is also something you only really get in
dusseldorf i don't think there is any
other city
in germany or australia where there is a
restaurant where you can eat legit
okonomiyaki
you only get that kind of stuff in
dusseldorf
yeah it
really well the fingers i actually
i'm not like a huge fan of oklahoma so i
just went for that
diamond
[Music]
oh my god dude like oh my god okay so
we're getting into the after convention
talk now
dusseldorf
during dokomi
is absolutely insane there is this this
and i told you guys it's district where
there's a lot of japanese restaurants
and it is so crowded during
dokomi
after like in the evening time also
during the day i guess too but after the
convention is over
everyone goes there
everyone goes there and there's
miles of lines standing there in front
of each japanese restaurant trying to
get in the non-japanese dress there's
that district is mostly japanese
restaurants there are some non-japanese
restaurants and those don't have any
lines
usually those don't really have any
limes except for like some korean uh
restaurants for example
yeah but
mostly the japanese restaurants are so
packed and there's really a lot of them
but they're so packed there's miles lots
of lines and if you stand in line then
you usually have to wait
one to two hours like i've uh on the
previous year i was um waiting in front
of this uh popular ramen restaurant
called naniwa and i waited for one hour
[Music]
to get a freaking ramen and then uh
yesterday for example
um we went to
uh actually we went to
to a korean restaurant korean barbecue
uh
and uh
the line was not that long and we even
no wait no i'm mixing up some things no
no no we didn't wait for that one we
only waited on saturday
uh
for the
yeah cause for the korean barbecue we
had a reservation but for the other one
we did not have a reservation because we
failed on the tonkatsu and now we had to
wait for one hour and actually more i
think
oh my god we waited in line for one and
a half hours or so
even though the line wasn't even that
long and then we got in we got our seats
and we waited 20 minutes until they took
our our um
our uh
food
orders and then until the food came it
took
another hour
i was so hungry
i gotta think this is this is
understandable because
normally these restaurants don't get
that many visitors they're not like
staffed for so many visitors but i mean
they kind of know they're they know that
at dokomi it goes crazy they know
it but yeah so
you have to if you go to to me if you go
to this love you have to be prepared you
have to have this mindset you have to
know
that you will be waiting hours for your
food
so many people so many people i don't
blame the restaurants because it's just
so so many freaking people
yeah i pretty much always end up kind of
starving when i go to conventions me too
during a convention during a convention
i never eat actually on saturday
um
like i had the possibility to eat lunch
in between my my things my program
points but i couldn't eat because i was
nervous
and
like when i'm like doing something like
that i just don't have the mind
space open to eat
i just don't feel like eating so yeah
i didn't eat until late late late in the
evening which made it even worse that i
had to wait one hour in line and one
hour to get my food
because i didn't have lunch
uh i was really hungry
um yeah yeah yeah
um anyway so
that was saturday uh waiting long time
for food going back home absolutely
exhausted back home back to the hotel
absolutely exhausted
and uh going to sleep after reading
everyone's like uh feedback on it for
hours as well
because i was still so hyped up
and then on sunday and i had a private
day i hung out with my friends it all
went well it was cool and i was mostly
undercover
and
yeah secretive i was hiding most of the
time but i still had my fun
um but
i have to say i definitely noticed
that conventions
are never gonna be the same for me i
guess
yeah
uh
that's a bit unfortunate but at the same
time
it has its good signs of course like i
can do stuff like this i can do concerts
and stuff that's awesome but on sunday
when i was trying to
enjoy it with my friends
most of it most of it was just normal
but i i definitely
noticed that
it's it's not gonna be exactly the same
because like the friends that i hang out
with they have to be
um careful too right so i told them be
careful
you understand
you understand right
um
so i feel like i'm kind of like
burdening them a little bit um
by you know having them be careful um
it is also a little bit stressful
um
yeah
and a little bit a little bit
lonelier than usual because as i told
you before normally on conventions i i
would walk around and every five minutes
i would talk to people
but yesterday
i didn't talk to anyone
besides the group that i was with
like people
some people that i know from long before
they uh talked to me
and like tried to talk to me and i just
i just kept on walking i was like
i was like really paranoid like really
really paranoid this is one issue that's
like maybe more on the mental side but
i was just really scared that
you know
whoever
would talk to me
i don't know i don't know man even if
it's someone that i know i i still felt
like and i know
i can't do this now i was so anxious
um
anyway yeah yeah yeah the rain did hit
me
oh yeah i forgot to say this like before
i flew to um
dokomi and i looked at the weather
report
and it said
[Music]
it said friday saturday sunday
every day
chance of rain
from
from morning till evening
throughout the whole convention it was
supposed to rain
so much
so
i was like well
well well i'm on saturday i'll be inside
so that's okay the other day is but
i i will not i will not give up so on
friday i was already like hanging out
with my friends but
and we were like oh my god it's probably
gonna rain
but it didn't it didn't run it rained at
all
[Music]
so friday no rain
and then saturday i was inside but i
think there was
no real rain either from what i've heard
yeah
so
again we lucked out on that one but then
i was like okay on sunday it must rain
right and on sunday it did rain but not
for the whole day how it was like
reported in the weather report not for
the whole day only like two times really
really strong
for like five minutes each it was
raining so much uh but like around the
the noon time
and
genma told me oh my god someone told me
though on sunday they were also able to
check out the convention
uh like privately
and um
i i told i told gemma she should check
out like the outside location because
it's really cool there's a lot of people
there too
maybe she would find me and and
supposedly she they were trying to reach
that park
that huge pike and
they had a really bad timing because the
moment they went there
was exactly when that freaking rain hit
super super strong
so they gave up on it they didn't really
enter it at all
yeah
unfortunately but i was i was hiding um
under you know umbrellas and trees and
everything i was safe
uh and then it was fun though because
like
the rain hit out of nowhere for five
minutes really strong
and then everyone was like trying to
run under the trees to take cover it was
so funny everyone was panicking um
so that that happened twice in the noon
time but besides that it didn't rain
anymore the the the weather was amazing
so no
no it was not too hot
it was uh not too cold
it was comfortable
there was no rain most
yeah it was like everyone's scattered
and actually not scattered everyone
gathered not scattered
yeah i was really blessed
saturday was a bit on the hot side oh i
didn't know that because i was inside
yeah well i think it went well
thankfully it was not raining the whole
weekend that would have been very sad oh
very very sad
i walked through that rain like a bus
did you not have an umbrella
you're trying to look cool right i mean
i mean rain doesn't hurt you if you're a
chicken
right so
yeah a little bit of rain doesn't hurt
no one
um
that was sunday that was sunday i i
can't really you know tell you too much
what happened on sunday was my private
day uh but i had i had my fun
again i have to say it was
not
not the usual document experience i i
i guess i will never have that usual
document experience again
that's okay though because what i'm
giving up for it is rewarded
uh by so many other great things that
i'm really really happy
grateful for
i just um feel a bit sorry for my
friends because i guess they also
got affected by it a little bit
uh
yeah but
they had a lot of fun my friends had a
lot of fun actually the reasons why my
friends went there to begin with
like they originally didn't plan to go
but i pushed them to go with me
uh
because i just wanted you know it's been
so long it's been such a long time
to
have first of all a real convention and
second of all be together on a
convention like that with my friends
so i pushed them to go i put up i i
discussed so long with them
and thankfully they came
um we stayed on different places they
had like an airbnb together
and they also didn't fly with me they
went there separately which
uh usually we would always go together
on a long road trip and the long road
trips would also always be like so much
fun normally
um but i'm glad i went with the plane
it was so much faster and so much
simpler actually i was really surprised
going from australia to germany was
like there was no trouble at all i did
okay this is gonna surprise a lot of you
i guess this is pretty
normal actually
uh when you fly from australia to
germany but i didn't even have to show
my passport or any idea at all
from like arriving at the airport
in in my city
and arriving at the airport in the in
this love
not even once did i have to show any id
or anything at all i didn't like i
didn't anything uh the only thing i did
is scan my ticket
yeah it was really really chill
really chill
yeah i stressed myself out so much
because of the current situation i was
like yeah
but it's still very chill
yeah the power of the schengen zone
yeah they call it schengen agreement
the perks
europe travel picks yeah yeah yeah yeah
definitely really really cool stuff i
appreciate that
thank you for the meet and greet anyway
were you part of yeah your name
i recall thank you for coming oh my god
i'm so
i'm gonna go back on sunday i i really
wanted to like when i i got up kind of
late on sunday i wanted to like wake up
earlier but i was like i woke up and i
had like no motivation
actually
because i was so exhausted from the day
before and the days before and the weeks
before
i was so exhausted this is also the
first time in a long time that i was not
just doing streaming from home but doing
stuff physically and stuff
i was so excited i didn't want to get up
and um i was like i just wanna just do a
meet and greet again i wanna really do
another meet and greet that was fun that
was fun i wanna do that again
[Music]
more reading greens yeah we need them
you know after the meet and greet i
regret it
not recording everything
because i want to listen to it again
[Music]
cause like when things happen so fast
three minutes only and everyone i meet
for the first time
like even though i don't want to forget
it
i will forget it
i will like lose my memory a bit so fast
i should have recorded my screen
i should have recorded your faces
um yeah i wanted to record the
conversations god damn it
god damn it
with constant yeah sure
just from my personal collection you
know i didn't record it though because i
was like i'll be fine but now i'm like
why did i not do it
i want to watch it like a month later
and two months later and three months
later and four months later and one year
later and two years later and three
years later
goddammit
well at least at least we got the
selfies yeah at least we have i think
everyone but one
uh took a selfie that one person i i i
was like you don't want to take a selfie
and he was like i have it in my brain
you sure you sure
apparently that person had photographic
memory or something like that
everyone else took a selfie
it's in my brain i saved it in my brain
i have a memory card in there i don't
need it i wish i had that
i wish i had a memory card in my brain i
wish i could have like recorded
everything in my brain
oh man
yeah
i hope you guys uh
um
felt fine talking to me i hope i didn't
like
push you to do anything you didn't want
to do
oh but it was so special every one of
you was so sweet
every one of you was so sweet
so kind
and cute
and sweet
yeah
potential is in control i was i was
really much controlling the room most of
the time
yeah oh no i didn't make anyone do more
and more but i made everyone do a
final scene
yeah was there anything else oh yeah
there were whole live cosplayers
there were whole live cosplayers they
were um
amen
i saw uh mikko mikuchi
and kiara
and they were i think one two two gurus
or three good
uh that i i me and my manager saw at
least
and uh
uh
yeah one mikoti
yeah one amen
i know
[Music]
unfortunately at least i didn't see
anything
i was really surprised about the mikoti
it was a
it was a beard at me could see
the good that i saw was also bearded
was still dope man
and the posing was so good
the poses
yo they really had it in themselves they
had the passion they had the elite
mikoti and the cute could have passion
yo
ah
anything else i wanted to say
[Music]
i think
actually that was uh that was also
um
you see i think
even the whole life is very popular
overseas already in germany i think it
has not quite
reached just yet i mean there are a lot
of people who already know youtubers and
who already know whole life but not not
not that much i would say so
um at dokomi there's a lot of uh artist
boobs
and
and i was wondering like there would
probably be no whole live merchandise
but it actually was there was at least
one booth that i know of
um that had uh
kiara and takamori keychains and stuff
and i actually got them um i didn't go
by myself to buy them
but i uh had them been be
i i had them purchased for me
yeah so i got some really cute
takanawa and takamori keychains
yeah more next time more and more whole
live merchandise don't know me next time
please
please it's kind of weird like
to like i don't know
i feel like buying this to support the
artists but it's not like i can really
use them because
i'm not going to put the keychain
my like a taken as a keychain on my own
bag like
as much as i would like to
yeah actually my manager gemma she
actually bought uh brought me um
merchandise from
japan from for example from uh
there was this uh
or still is this whole live thing going
on in atole right so she actually bought
me bought me stuff from there
and
i i had like i have this whole lot this
super new super special
a whole life t-shirt for life english
t-shirt and i was wearing that as my
pajamas
in the hotel
only inside my room not outside
can we see the merch well i i didn't
really um
take many pictures of it yet but there's
wait there's one picture around that i
can share
[Music]
one second
let me get them from my phone to you
guys
[Music]
loading really slow
yeah that might have been in motion
i'm watching this in school oh thank you
cute and comfy shirts are the best to
sleep also they are the best to stream
i always wear like pickled t-shirts and
and like other kinds of like
big comfy t-shirts
to stream hmm
hi i'm just woke up what's up oh well i
just finished like most of the talking
uh about the whole the whole trip
[Music]
so let me show you
okay
yeah i think this one is fine
book that i talked about
oh it's huge big
big
i want to show you i mean everything is
so special but i think it would be um
like i may be too too private to show
like every every present i received i
feel like maybe some of you guys
wouldn't want me to show it or whatever
so i'm just going to show this one
as a sample but i got this heart hot
what do you call this uh like a
hardcover uh book fan art book
and that had like uh from all kinds of
fan artists and but this was not being
sold at dokomi this was something that
was just made for me and given to me at
the meet and greet thank you wait
uh
[Music]
wait
i took a image a photo of the first page
[Music]
and this is the first page
as the seasons change and our journey
moves into a new chapter the community
has come to seize the opportunities in
hand or wing
and show our collective might and pride
as employees of the grand camp
from the artist of the kfb compiled by
the employees of the kfb huh
we have put together a book potential
for our attention takadashikiana in a
world which is mostly digital may you
enjoy a gift which is a bit more
tangible in commemoration of dokomi 2021
hashtag stringsbox why the is that
in comic sense
trying to trigger me or what who was the
graphic designer you have some passion
don't you
you have some passion for graphic design
i see
are you trying to trigger me
this iceberg is purely fan-made and
includes artworks from volunteering
artists this is not a product of or
associated with a live cover crop or
document
that's right it's really good quality
it's really pretty
i love it
i want to show my mommy
my mom is also visiting this week by the
way
my mom is visiting this week
um to help me out with some stuff in my
apartment
i'm so busy
i have no moment to chill this week
either
um but my mom is coming and she's gonna
help me we're gonna probably get some
plants we're gonna build some furniture
and all that on the day on the one day
that i have off
uh
yeah but
next week
it is happening
minecraft with mama
next week we're doing it
we're doing it guys we're finally doing
it
it's happening it's happening i got
permission
[Music]
yet as i mentioned before but uh she
will be
there and she will be helping she will
be doing stuff with me in minecraft and
show her skills
so
okay
this is something
a mixture of things
a mixture
you show
that my manager brought me
so um okay at the very top
is
a a beautiful beautiful takarashikiara
wall scroll
that
i
personally wanted and purchased
and
wait my brain cannot think of the
artist's name right now uh uh uh
uh uh uh help me out here you guys
probably know the big one the nice one
uh
what was again
do you guys know you guys know you guys
know you guys know wait i can look it up
i probably have it uh saved
no
not no nope nope wait i'll look it up
[Music]
my brain is empty
uh
[Music]
this was by the way fan fan made not
official merchandise
it's much bigger than that it's just
like rolled up together and i'll put it
somewhere in my apartment it's so it's
so pretty
i retweeted it before
anyway underneath that is
hi to
a special live
[Music]
edition there there are i think three
different versions of this
um
i think this came out just before
uh my manager uh came to germany
and uh she bought it for me i love hai
chu actually it's like a like a chewing
uh chewy chewy not a chewing gum but a
chewy
gum
a chewy uh candy a chewy candy
[Music]
and then underneath that is something
that was purchased for me
at the uh convention
um some really cute keychains
uh
that are uh that were being sold at a
dokomi booth
i don't know if they maybe have like a
online shop as well but the name is ama
yeah
pretty damn cute i would say these are
just some of the things actually uh
manager son brought me many more things
like ramen noodles and stuff
yeah
arigato
arigato thank you
and i also received like a lot of
merchandise that was just like
uh a bunch of dokomi merchandise i
received that from the organizers
uh
it's not not whole live related but like
all kinds of document merchandise
thank you
let me drink water
jmt jmt oh yeah well
today
i left germany
very early in the morning
jmt woke up for me after three four
hours of sleep
to say goodbye to me
unbelievable i told her to go back to
sleep but she said no i have work to do
she works too much give her a
break
she just works way too much
um
so yeah she
she
saw me off
it's so sad it's so sad but but we're
gonna see each other hopefully again
sometime this year maybe
um i hope so hopefully but i was just
really happy that this was possible in
the first place because when when this
whole dokami
talk started
um
it was like the talk of getting
uh gemma to
germany to help out and protect me
was
uh
a topic it was already like
a past like we wanted to do it but we
were really unsure if it would be
possible
and i mean it wouldn't have happened
probably even without the cover staff
coming
and nonetheless
but
um much better that she came because
without her i would have been so lost
during the during saturday she helped me
out so much best manager ever
i'm so happy she came i was so happy to
see her she she gave me this
um feeling of safety
and mental support and uh physical
support i guess
yeah
one of a kind definitely one-of-a-kind
manager and um
what was i gonna say uh
i forgot
i forgot but it's okay
um
[Music]
yeah i hope she enjoyed germany i hope
she enjoyed the trip
and the convention i think she did i
think it was a very special
uh
opportunity for all of us
and i hope we can do it again yeah
i'm gonna miss her
really happy we did it
okay
i hope she also gets back to japan
safely with no issues and no troubles
but i told her if she gets stuck in
europe she's welcome to come to
australia and meet my cats
yeah um
oh yeah i remember what i wanted to say
by the
by gemma and the cover staff being there
uh it felt like
it felt like a little bit like i was
back in japan
it gave me flashbacks to
you know the time where i lived in japan
where i was always with these people
and uh always able to see them
it felt nostalgic in a way
and really cool
[Music]
yeah so
i guess that pretty much concludes my
talk about the dokomi we can read super
chats now and have some more like
unrelated talk and tangents and stuff
and whatever you guys might uh
ignite
from sending me super chats
and thanks again for coming to my ted
talk yeah
hope you enjoyed it tomorrow we're doing
uh
minecraft
and
[Music]
um
what is the english name we're doing a
read along of uh bloom into you yeah
yeah yeah
i know we wanted to do like a read along
for a long time
finally we got it to happen
uh
it's happening on cali's channel
uh so check it out guys you guys are
really hyped up about that
it's crazy
i saw the reactions on twitter you guys
are going like insane like what's up
guys
you said you really wanted it that badly
i'm like shook what what what's going on
wait what we're just reading a manga
i know it's like a popular one but
what
but i i uh i know that like uh ame and
cali and so on they did read alongs
already but i never did one i don't know
how
how we gonna do it should we like
because i guess there's like two main
characters
should we like
like separate and like split and like
one of us reads one character or so i
don't really imagine like i can't
imagine how to do it
i guess we'll do it like that yeah it's
gonna be embarrassing
it's gonna be very embarrassing
it
and then who raised the side characters
though i have a lot of voices i can read
some side characters
i guess we're going to split the side
characters too
i hope there's not so many side
characters i hope it says most of the
time only those two girls
so that
we don't have to wait too many side
characters
voice acting time yeah
hey which one who should read which one
[Music]
should i i i should be tolco
that is
i should be coco
okay i'll remember that
that that
that's the girl that looks a bit more
mature right and cali should be the no
wait let me look it up
bloom into you characters
yeah toku is the black haired one
and you is the a little bit more like
childish or small looking one with the
pink twin tails okay
pinkish oranges peaches
[Music]
okay no problem we'll do it like that i
guess
because it seems that um
uh
it seems like it's fitting
it's gonna be embarrassing oh
i'm nervous
i'm nervous but then afterwards i will
have a minecraft stream and then
yeah look at the schedule i uploaded it
on twitter i have to still upload it on
the youtube community board i'll do that
too um
thank you for the membership for new wow
i'm not sure what to do on minecraft um
to be honest uh
i squeezed that in there because i felt
like
i have to stream because i've been
not streaming
much for the past few days
um
and i wanted to stream for the sake of
streaming
i'm not sure yet what to do on minecraft
i guess we'll just go on an adventure
um we'll go
with the
elite
yeah
but
i hope i survived this week
there's not even much that i can cancel
uh a lot of things are so fixed that i
cannot cancel them
so let's do our best
and to not over exhaust ourselves shall
we
a woodland mansion that would be fun to
find yeah and and
ah right i want to find the the that new
biome that i haven't seen yet
uh
mesa mesa bayony i want to find that one
so we can try to find either one of
those we just fly out there and we'll
not give up until we find one of them
that sounds good to me so hasta was
oh yeah and oh my god the garlic phone
i'm sorry there's gonna be three garlic
phone streams this week but i think you
guys will enjoy each and every single
one of them
we start out with
artists
fan artists this time
planned beforehand
all stars edition
and
99 95 of the artists are
ones that did not participate last time
and
the lineup is quite insane
i'm not gonna spoil anything
but the lineup is his angel
um there will be people participating
from all over the world so english
speakers and japanese speakers
so that's why it's an uh maybe an
awkward time maybe kind of early for
american time zones i'm sorry about that
but we had to make it work for everyone
and i'm so hyped up oh my god
there's so many great artists
no no no vocal no vocal participation
nope nope
only only uh drawing
but i'm gonna turn off the
um time limit
because
due to
there being people who don't speak
japanese and people who don't speak
english
uh
i thought there might be you know stress
if there is not enough time to translate
when you're trying to write so basically
no time limit and then i told them to
like
if they want to write a prompt
um
like for example gouda fishing fish
they should put it into google translate
i only really told that the japanese
participants
so that they should translate it to
english simple english and then put it
uh copy paste it into there it should be
that should be easy enough
so
and then whenever they see an english
prompt they will have no time limit so
they can uh put it into google translate
to try to understand what it means if
they don't understand but i think we'll
we'll have like simple words basic words
and so it shouldn't be too difficult but
they can use they have enough time to
use google translate if they wanna and
um
what else was i gonna say
i forgot
yeah but it's gonna be fine it's gonna
be fun and it's gonna be lots of fun i
thought yeah oh yeah that's what i
wanted to say thank you uh yeah if even
if something gets misunderstood
and then written in like
up google translate interest yeah
it's gonna be interesting results and
it's gonna be even more funny
yeah it's gonna be even better
like stream is delivery yeah yeah yeah
if you if you translate stream
the japanese word for stream in uh to
english it will be delivery in english
is yeah gonna be interesting
[Music]
now
because i'm done with my chit chatting i
hope you enjoyed the
the talk about dokomi and i hope it made
you guys feel excited about possible
future conventions with whole live
english and me
and maybe maybe once in person and maybe
digital ones next week this week this
week is also one uh a digital one well
i'll i'll not be there in person but it
is an in-person convention
um for me it's digital for you guys it's
not if you're going there megacon in
orlando me and amy will be there but
we'll be there on separate days emma
will be there on friday i will be there
on saturday so
i'm looking forward to that too and many
many more conventions in the future so
uh thank you again for everyone who came
to my performances at dokomi and also
everyone who watched it on twitch as
well if you didn't if you missed it and
you didn't watch it yet then you're
welcome to check it out on twitch or
look for the clips on youtube that's
fine too
i know
uh twitches twitch.tv
tv i think
then you should be able to watch the
archive although it's only saturday i
was only there on saturday
moving on
a bit sad to move on because i i
i don't
wanna
i didn't want this experience to end but
it ended so it's uh time to move on
let's read the superchat
so we have to read
right pop up please hello
eh it doesn't open
uh
pop arms are allowed
eh it doesn't open
they're broken
oh i'm not the only one who has this
problem right now
ah
oh oh
today super chat era what the hell
oh
[Laughter]
um okay you know what uh
[Music]
well i'll sing a song for you then
on my new stage how about that
how about that i'll give you a little
taste
of the song that i just learned
[Music]
wait my stage
is here
[Music]
this should this should work
right
why is it
uh
okay let's see what happens if i go
there
oh nice where am i
oh my god
you didn't see that
all right
welcome to my stage
[Music]
i didn't plan on doing this so this is a
scarf beginning
[Music]
should i be big do you want me to be big
let me try to figure this out ah michael
you can separate this microphone
let's do big mike
yeah
i'll just be big should i put you guys
in the background yeah i should wait let
me get the chat
[Music]
wait does it go back
i have to uh not not from here maybe
actually
wait actually i can do it in studio mode
the chat
this one this one is good
okay coming back
[Music]
yeah i'll make myself bigger one second
but i'll put you there i'm gonna put you
guys on the screen
and you can be like mama look i'm on tv
it's not disabled
there you are
hello
[Music]
okay
maybe
should i go to the side so oh this side
this is my new stage
sheen
[Applause]
it's really cute i showed it to my
members before
uh but none members see it maybe
also not for the first time if you watch
dokomi then you always saw it but yeah
look it's so cool it has like fire going
on in the background and the the
subwoofers are woofing the chickens are
cheering one is sleeping what is djing
the screen in the back is moving on this
on the screen in the front i can put
anything i want yeah
and then there's even reflections
shout out to good ass reflect which is a
banger
yeah isn't it nice
mama look i'm on tv i'm the sleeping one
then wake the up what the hell
okay so
because we cannot read super chats for a
stupid reason stupid reason wait can i
eat a cookie
i bought these cookies
in the supermarket um you know there's a
there's these cookies um that usually
are always being made during the winter
time for christmas and christmas cookies
um but i guess they also sell it outside
of christmas they're called linsa augen
i think they're they're australian
cookies lindsay augen
lindsay algen can someone write it in
the chat so other people who don't know
about it can look it up on you on google
because they're really yummy they're
they have like they have marmalade
inside of them and they're really good
and i really like them so i bought them
today as a snack and i'm gonna eat them
hmm
[Music]
um they taste even better during
christmas season
but they're good now too
okay let me um find the uh the karaoke
sound and the lyrics for you guys um
to be honest i just want to eat cookies
[Music]
okay
this christmas season i want to make
christmas cookies winter winter
christmas why not kicks it christmas
cookies on stream joel how about
it
let me check the audio
i never made them like all alone before
though i made them with my sister before
yes i have a sister
and
and besides that
i don't think i ever made cookies
besides that before
yeah i never really talk about her
is she single oh my god
what about gemma guys what about genma
before you were like i want to marry
emma i want to marry jenna
i want to meet gemma and dokomi i want
to find jama or dokomi can i propose to
her and dopamine and now and now you're
like what what
my sister you guys are you guys are
insane
dnd she actually uh does like um
she wrote to me did i tell you guys when
i when i when we started doing the ttrpg
with uh cali my sister wrote in our like
whatsapp group like oh damn i wish i had
someone to um uh play uh that one with
what's it called again that specific
ttrpg uh
some darkness something darkness
yeah i think i mentioned that one
apparently she really wants to do that
that specific one world of darkness yeah
yeah yeah she was like damn i want to
play with someone and also when i
because my sister is also a gamer just
like my mom and me and my brother and
everyone and when she saw that i was
playing the diablo to um
yeah be able to remake uh
thingy on string
she was also
going to be jealous
yeah we all we all played stuff like
that
back in the day
yes i have a brother yes
i talk about my brother a lot why is
this why is this a surprise
um
sister is big sister
brother is big brother
chiara is
small kiara
is he single
no comment
no comments
are you smart smart kiana
all right
let's sing
[Music]
me
is
[Music]
a
m
[Music]
hey
is
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
ah
foreign
[Music]
is
a
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
yay
thank you thank you
i don't hear it anymore i don't hear the
clapping anymore where did it go where
did the cheering go i heard it i heard
it two days ago now i don't hear it
anymore
oh man
it's okay
i see you guys i see you guys sharing
hey
thank you
i still see you
even though i can't hear you
i can imagine it
imagination
this song is so beautiful
when i first heard it um at the bloom
wow
i think it was their closing song
actually
um they sang it at the very end
and it just had this
ah huge emotion coming up inside me
[Music]
so emotional so beautiful
so that was my little uh sorry for not
being able to read super chats but
that's not even my choice and not my
fault um what the hell youtube what's
wrong with you
anyway well i guess we'll read it
tomorrow bro after minecraft gotta cut
minecraft maybe a little bit short
uh because i think something piled up
because we have
uh also some super chats from the
raiding waiting room
and uh
yeah this one you guys were also very
supportive thank you very much so maybe
minecraft will uh i mean if we're lucky
we find the the things that i want to
find immediately
and you know takanasi and
takanashi and
and luck they go hand in hand
thank you for the membership thank you
soon
thank you the waiting room was wholesome
yeah i tried to um
say hello in the waiting room every once
in a while it was up for quite a long
time and thank you guys for being there
i could share my nervous diversity
every time i say that people are like
what the are you saying is that not
a word
no do i just say it wrongly
no no
i think that's a word though
nervousness what the man
[Laughter]
it's not a word
it sounds like it it looks it looks like
it could be a word
nervousness nervousness on the other
side just looks like i don't know you
put you you desperately try to put these
two things together
because there's no proper way to else
describe it so you add nest to it and
you're like whatever this should do it
this should do the trick nervosity is
more like it i would say it's a word now
yeah hell yeah
let's make the word let's go
it is a word now
always has been
well well well guys uh thank you for
watching thank you for all the support
and the love you gave me during dokomi
even if you couldn't go honestly seeing
you guys on twitch in such big numbers
as well meant a lot to me really
really it meant so much to me
yeah i know that a lot of you guys could
not be there in person for obvious
reasons uh but seeing you guys on twitch
as well was was really really important
and big to me very meaningful thank you
i saw you guys cheering there even
though you guys probably thought that
i'm not looking at the chat but i was
looking every once in a while
[Music]
yeah i mean live audience is absolutely
amazing but
i like both worlds you know virtual the
virtual world is quite comfy
it's really comfy
to be here
in front of you with you guys at any
given time and you're always here for me
and i can i can be in the comfiest
surroundings ever with my kitty cats
eh
anyway i have another cutter okay this
week so
and please check that out too
and
yeah it's weird that i'm leaving this
was such a short stream what the
it's not even three hours what the hell
uh
where to live so early what the hell
more does that i kind of ran out of
dokomi stories
was there anything else i could say
oh oh yeah oh my god it's a korean
barbecue
you know um
uh i
i ordered
i ordered wagyu
and there was like um there were there
were like free choices of wagyu there
was like a 29 year old vagyo
and there was a 39 euro wagyu and then
there was a 49 year old vlogging so 50
bucks
and my friends were eyeing it while we
were looking at the menu and they were
like oh lucky would be so nice
damn yeah it's so expensive oh man will
i ever invoke you
and i was like hmm
i should trade myself after this after
this uh
awesome awesome performance at dokomi i
should treat myself shouldn't i
so i actually got wagyu the most
expensive one for myself
i got myself a 50 year old vacuum
hey they had also really amazing food
they actually had way more like
different kinds of meats because like
after the vacuum i ordered um something
additionally because like the vagina was
a little bit too little
um not enough to fill my belly so i
ordered one more like
plate of meat just for myself but i
didn't know what to order and the one
that i ordered was maybe not as good as
the stuff that the others had
but at least i had vaguely
but yeah they have they had so much
different kinds of meat um that was my
first time doing korean barbecue i went
to japanese yaki nuku so many times it
was my first time doing korean barbecue
it is quite different kim oh my god my
my freaking wagyu
came with
well something that looked like a
um
a pepper a paprika pepper
and
i trusted it i trusted it
because i like peppers and i bit into it
and it was so hot
yeah i meant bell peppers but it was a
it was a uh
what do you call yeah it was so
hot
[Music]
i only took like a small bite it was
dying because you guys know i usually
like i don't eat spicy food because i
just generally a jalapeno something like
that but a really big one damn
yeah
i usually don't eat spicy food because
like i can't i can't handle it
chili pepper something like that it was
it looked like a paprika like a bell
pepper it looked like a normal bell
pepper
paper
because that yeah korean wants to hit i
knew it yeah i knew it i was careful
like when my friend said oh we want to
go to korean bbq i was like
yeah okay
they probably have a of spicy food
i'm gonna have a hard time finding uh
non-spicy food probably um actually no
the meat and generally uh the meat
generally was not spicy
um
like also the meat that the others got i
think were not spicy so yeah mostly was
fine but damn that pepper
oh my god
uh
[Laughter]
whatever the hell that was
i died once when i got revived
immediately huh
that sort of warned me what the hell i
thought it was just normal um veggies
because they also have like uh on on the
same plates like i guess like low-key as
decoration but also as like please eat
it they had uh mushrooms uh they're on
on the plate as well with the wagyu i
don't like mushrooms so i gave it to my
friend but i was like i like bell
peppers let's eat the bell pepper i need
some something besides meat in my mouth
so i ate the bell pepper
and i regretted it because it was not a
bell pepper
yeah maybe it was a habanero whatever
the hell that is
um
yeah how did i get to that oh yeah i
want to talk about the vague so i have
to say um i guess it was vague but the
value that i ate in
you know
it might also have been that i
had to uh
uh grill it myself
um but i didn't put it on the grill too
long no don't worry it was really soft
and it wasn't on there too long but
still i guess there's a it still makes a
difference from having it being prepared
by a professional a teppanyaki a cook
chef
in japan compared to making it yourself
um but also
i think
i think the the laggy that i ate in
japan might have just been better
quality it was still good though it was
really good and
there was like a uh quite a thick part
of it was uh like um um
uh
a brain rebooting uh at
a fat
uh
well what's fat in
yeah fat
fat
so i was like hmm
hey
uh of my friends who wants a vague fat
and they actually were like yeah let me
try
so my friends were grilling the the fat
the wagyu fat on the grill for a while
made it into tiny bits and grilled it
made it a little bit crunchy and they
ate my vagina fat
[Music]
i ate some of it too like that was like
mixed in with the meat but like there
was just a big chunk of it and i was
like
you guys wanna
sharing is caring okay
offering only the fat
hey they had so much other meat okay
gotta treat myself with some ragio
don't worry don't worry one day they'll
get a taste of the real lucky they
should eat it in japan anyway they
should eat the real thing in japan made
by a real
uh
cook in front of your eyes
i did that a few times
a bunch of times with cali a bunch of
times alone bunch of times with other
people
yeah yeah
but uh yeah the the barbecue was nice it
was really yummy the people in there the
staff were also so
so kind i tipped them so much
they were
wow i was really impressed by the
customer service yeah
damn it was really good customer service
i spent a lot of money
in that korean barbecue
allison actually okay you guys being
like oh you only gave them the vlog you
fat that's the only thing you shared
well i actually also invited one of my
friends i paid for the bill of one of my
friends not all of them that would have
been like 600 bucks or something
but i paid for one of my friends bills
okay
i i i am nice to my friends okay
welcome back here we miss you thank you
i'm also glad to be back but the stream
is ending here because um i did all my
dokomi talk and super chat's well i'll
try i'll try it again i'll try it again
refresh come on
nope
nope it's not working
i only see the top six
super chats
that's all i see unfortunately oh well
then i have time to make food i guess
and eat and uh you know
wind down a little bit for my trip
yeah i guess that's okay too
i'll see you tomorrow on cali's channel
first and then on my channel uh i don't
want to say goodbye
are you can i hear are you noticing that
i kind of like try to
um stay
it's too short i haven't talked to you
guys in such a long time
[Music]
i could like talk so much with you guys
let me eat one more cookie no i should
just say i should leave i should leave i
should make use of the free time i have
for god's sake
[Music]
eh
a thing planned for this month
for august
well the collab of mama i think is very
special
other than that i guess some more hollow
um
test override streams
other than that i actually don't have
much
planned
i think
i'll still do something amazing ah the
mario kart oh yeah right i have to okay
now that i'm back from germany i have to
organize that
properly
uh when's the next whole talk next week
next week
next week next we'll talk
um
what's your favorite cosplay look oh
good question good question good
question okay so
i mean there's a lot of great cosplays
but one one cosplay
just just
at some point
there was a cosplayer behind me
who was wearing
a jon snow cosplay
and the moment i looked at him he was
looking down
so when he was looking down
he looked exactly like jon snow
he looked exactly like him and he had a
real sword with him i don't know how he
probably shouldn't have a real sword
with you but
he had a real sword real look definitely
really i don't know what a rental sword
looks like he had a real story with him
anyway his cosplay looked so good he was
tall too and he had that then jon snow
hairstyle and he when he was looking
down i told him yo when you look down
when i see mostly your forehead you look
exactly like jon snow
i was fangirling so much
he had no like daenerys or so though
damn
but oh my god he
yeah i told him i took
i couldn't hold back i told him yo you
look exactly jon snow
oh my god his forehead looks like
joshua's forehead
oh man
jon snow
i don't know like when i was watching
game of thrones it's not like i was like
a big like fan of jon snow as a
character it's not like he was my
favorite or anything but seeing a real
looking jon snow there i was like
did he
i keep on seeing these comments like did
he know anything and i was like
wondering if you guys meant like if you
know that i was kiara and that was i was
like ignoring those comments but
now i get what you mean
now i understand but he was really happy
to hear the compliments
yeah
i'm happy that he was happy oh my god
jon snow
sorry i'm fangirling
um
okay
you know nothing jon snow you're stupid
go back to school
okay um
well i guess i gotta go i guess uh
i guess i
i guess i gotta go
um
[Music]
oh my god hearing ankuru
was so special too
you have no idea
hearing i'm called a man
from a live real audience
i'm good
now you guys are doing it too
what what what do you want uncle to
talking or singing
i don't know if i can talk anymore i
can't think of anything
brain empty hardest too
sparks
uncle sparks
okay
all right all right all right all right
all right
i'm caught up i'm gonna
i'm cold up
i'm called up
[Music]
oh yeah
where's my carol division
um
sparks
this is it
okay
is it so loud i think it is
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do
hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do oh the storm hits hard when you're
losing your way
just take a chance and dance in the rain
cause you got the key never throw it
away don't forget don't forget what i
said
get out of your head life is only once
you make it you're gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know your name
[Music]
afraid oh my god
you know what next time i sing spikes to
the concert like that can you guys do
the part like don't stop don't stop just
go your own way so that i don't have to
sing it and like keep up keep up and
never be afraid
i want you guys to do that part okay
okay let's go
[Music]
wait a little hard when you confuse me
right now go back
[Music]
[Applause]
kick your feet against the table
[Music]
[Applause]
is only what you make it
[Music]
[Applause]
dance don't die choose the future you'll
define even when the flames burn too
bright you will light from
[Music]
how did you do that with your legs
should i pay for your ambulance gonna
make it hard like a volcano
burn it out take your feet against the
table tell them
spots like the flames start to fire
today
[Applause]
i
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah i need you guys to do that too
i know it's a little bit embarrassing
but you got to be confident when you do
that you could even like some some some
people in japan when i went to adult
concerts they also do it like this they
like what they when they get like really
really really like passionate about it
they go like oh yeah
oh yeah oh they're at this little like
oh yeah oh yeah before it um
they like like breathe in with that
good luck
you can do it you can do it
it's a lot of fun once you get into it
um
can we do the wave in the chat i don't
know how we would do that
i guess you can post that emoji there's
an emoji i think of a person uh holding
up their arms
i think
shall we do it
okay but then afterwards i'll leave okay
okay we'll start from this side i mean
you guys don't only have one side so
uh that's that no yeah some of you got
it yup yup that's the one that's the one
all right you ready
three
[Applause]
[Music]
that's a different kind of wave yo one
more little yay
[Music]
you're flashing or what
oh
thank you everyone
thank you it's okay
do you feel
don't have to use your actual body so
you're not exhausted from doing that
nice
couldn't find it so i panicked that's
okay
that's okay
i used mine though oh thank you
thank you guys
i look forward to reading everyone's
super chats
tomorrow because i think you guys
probably wrote a lot about dokomi as
well i want to hear everyone's thoughts
about it thank you for the support thank
you for being part of kfb
i was really happy to speak to some of
you and know that you guys are all such
sweet cutie pies really kind really
supportive really caring
i love you
on to many many more
months and many many more events
let's freaking go
um
bye-bye and in germany we say
yeah yeah yeah yeah that's it
au vida
yay
bye bye
i love you
yeah
bye bye
time to
say goodbye
[Music]
do
you