[Music]
thank you
assistant
[Music]
thank you
Christmas
[Music]
Tuesday
foreign
[Music]
assistant
thank you
foreign
[Music]
yeah I have it pulled up I have
everybody's pulled up oh let's go
Diablo
[Music]
assets that you have as well looks good
thank you I'm a fancy sorceress yay
very nice
it's very pretty
La sorceress nice who who's everybody
what is everybody playing as good
question go around go around Ring Around
the Rosie yeah okay
my character's name is Morp uh morph is
uh she thinks she's a skeleton she's
just really weird she's a necromancer
um very skinny and strange and toxin
third person more talks like this
morphing to aim it more Bluffs pretty
lady because it's pretty lady let's
let's go to
Keandre keonder
hey Andre
don't I look pretty because I put
um the I use the trends more good
whatever it's called
and I put the specific cloves on top of
other cloves that don't look so pretty
so now I look super pretty
um
looks cute but Kelly I'm so glad that
you're joining us a necromancer let's go
yeah I like playing his Necromancer but
now I'm realizing you guys can't see the
skeletons which makes me really really
upset actually warp is sad you can't see
her skeletons really don't they show up
maybe when we leave town maybe I hope
not sure I'm sure they do okay who else
does we have Kyla right next to me as
well
I'm a druid I don't know how to play the
grid but let's just let's go
looks like you're carrying just like a
brick from building a house on your back
yeah what is that a break painting
actually wait you might be building the
house with Cali right because Cali has a
really normal pickaxe on your back I do
more blacks pickaxe
you look like crony
you're so good yeah I've changed I
changed my outfit oh
wow
that's very nice what's Chrome you
playing what is that I am playing as a
bro
okay wait Rogue you have you have two
swords or what
uh I have like a bow and oh I guess I
have two stores yeah oh my God
I can't I can't go that fast how do you
go that fast in in circle
I'm playing on a controller oh okay oh
that makes sense more plays on PS5 oh
wow
oh okay so I'm I'm a sorceress I chose
the the special thing is the day do you
guys know what I try to reference in my
name
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
he no
[Applause]
no Kendrick Lamar
Kinder Egg
no yeah no no because you know I saw uh
I was first trying to recreate myself
but it didn't work so well and while I
was creating the character I realized oh
she's looking kind of like Game of
Thrones character Miss Andrea
sorry Melisandre so I combined Kiara and
Melisandre and I'm the hot red sorceress
yeah
it looks fiery I like I see oh this is
pretty lady hashtag
purple
[Music]
oh yeah macaroni has blue
macaroni and then what was red and Kyla
is kind of green I guess if you look at
the hammer but for now brown is also
good you'll surely get greener
ogre color
yo I haven't played in a couple days but
uh my current goal is the campaign quest
for level 10 the tarnished luster and I
thought we would do that unless you have
any other ideas
it's okay I'll just follow and it won't
follow us okay so follow me and fight
fight for fight by my side yes
this is more skeletons let's combine our
panel
yeah wait there should be game audio
what the [\h__\h] oh yeah okay but you hear
the other ones but no uh game audio one
second
[Music]
check Sun check everything's fine right
sounds
good all good okay all good all good
nice nice thank you thank you how about
now
is it too loud or a song
there's your music okay take off my
helmet so you can see I'm scared we're
ready oh you can go to the wall
you can go to the Wardrobe to like hide
your cab instead of like oh really
I'm here
I want to go to the Wardrobe together
everybody yeah let's go girl's gonna
dress up I love dressing I don't have
anything
okay I'll just wait I'm reading the
skills right now it's okay just ignore
me it's okay robe oh cool okay is it
safe to show
um the the group screen where I invited
everybody
it's okay it should be fun you'll be
fine look at this
we're looking so cool Kelly looks like
she she needs sleep
a plain Druid you need help can we
let's see I'm trying to so unequipped
look but that doesn't mean that it's
unequipped correct
uh yeah it's not it's nice
I forgot how it works crony you help her
uh so you got a wardrobe
and then you can just like uh go to the
Head section and then
it just says unequipped look
oh okay cool
and you just choose that yeah yeah
cool I'm ready to go okay what did you
change
yeah yes because I want to look like a
skeleton more wants to look like
skeletons oh yeah I feel like baldness
looks so good in Diablo you know right
freaking stick
[Music]
no cap
maybe you can reflect light on your
forehead and find like a new skill to
attack with with the light oh nice idea
yeah use my head as a mirror you use
morp's head as a mirror yes
solar flare
okay which direction do we go it's like
down in the east
can I track this okay good it goes uh
I'm going this way now
we're gonna kill a bunch of guys let's
go love killing love killing people
with the ladies murder with the ladies
ooh murder sleepover
there's no accent here
hello damn it we're going in a circle
okay
girl slide out in the circle
[Music]
anything let's go ladies
where are we going
to uh what's it called actually you can
paint it though uh
[Music]
pin it for you guys now yeah how do I
pin it just just right click right click
on the map
oh we can follow I did oh yes
there's Seafood
do we share items or does like everybody
get their own drops
no I think we get our own yeah
that's what chat told me yep yep yep
okie dokie I just wanted to make sure
yeah
I'm not ready
I'm already kind of like
struggling to see where everybody is
because now I thought this person
belongs to us
oh Rando it is random hey more says you
are not invited to this party
you are not popular
where the cool Mean Girls yeah cool like
cool me
cool Mean Girls let's go
and no others no Outsiders allowed
I think Max is okay we're super quickish
of like how many you can have in the
group yep
damn bossley we're the Mean Girls of
Diablo
you can't sit with us they're not no no
our characters are bad girls yeah yeah
yeah yes we are you cannot go to hell
with us no no exactly you can't you'll
go to heaven and have fun there yeah
what do you mean girls Super Evil ladies
but also not really evil but just kind
of mean not mean is good oh we have
there's even yeah even you guys want to
go even even let's go
let's go
more fish here
something yeah okay
it's so loud morphs than skeletons
chat is it not too loud for you
feels so loud to me it's always the
battle of
volume
yeah I don't like that
okay I'll change it in a second a little
bit
I feel like I'm taking away everybody's
like
item drops but but hold on
[Applause]
that was just a quest
I thought that was a level two I got
excited wait maybe it was I'm level six
now okay new ability yeah I forgot orb
increased light
okay not sure
yeah
yeah okay
oh that's what it is okay never mind
pick up gold hold on twice is too loud
hold on hold on okay I also will change
volume Goblin where's this villager have
on them
[Music]
better better for my mental stability
Diablo game right
yeah I've never played diabolo before
how is it so yeah do you like it I love
it
understand it might be addicted to it
yeah I'll probably end up doing a 12
hour stream this week
[Music]
it's too fun
a little too addicting
once you're in the Diablo
um whatever you're not getting out
there's no way back yes
I try to stop playing the game because I
had to go do a recording and I was like
all right time to stop and then I spent
like five minutes trying to stop the
playing the game and I couldn't stop
playing
that's what Diablo did to you yeah
bolo
are we already inside no okay that's
quick
we're all playing on tier one right yeah
I am worldview one okay I am too
probably kind of already privately plays
the other one right
yes he's about right okay so you already
finished the whole game or
uh the the main campaign yeah oh
how long did it took you to finish the
main campaign
well I kind of forgot how how long was
it guys I don't know can you help me
Kyla has no feeling of time anymore wait
what do you mean by tearing yeah
extreme tree stream they say three
streams
yeah three stream how long
yeah they say 40 to 50. okay
um
the heck
well
you okay
you good all good all good I'm just
cleaning up
cool
as I said we're steamrolling the server
and they're not surprised people are
explosion
we're in here in your list now yeah
I have to go up here for the quest do
you okay I have to go there too or is it
just me
no I think it's
um
[Music]
you and that nuisance of a child both oh
are we going into the mines
nights with missing I'm gonna steamroll
it
can you guys see your mirror yes uh
okay did you see the conversation of the
NPC or yes okay okay
well that's probably not necessary
oh I think I skipped it
oh no problem okay I marked the location
on the map so
ladies I should activate the the
Waypoint oh yes that would be hard
[Music]
thank you amazing
hello
hello hello
Ebola time
we're just playing some diabolo Diablo
diabolo
it's you girl Diablo in Spanish what
what is it in Spanish
yeah oh yeah sounds like it yeah
yeah just just some trivia that every
well maybe not everybody knew you didn't
know that did you hear I'm I feel like I
heard it before yeah it just makes sense
yeah oh we have Diablo Pizza I think in
in
which is like really spicy
for like Diablo hot sauce yeah I feel
like I've heard of that before oh yeah
yeah they're really really the really
hot hot sauce that sends you literally
to
hell
because you could almost die that's
Diablo hot sauce right oh that sounds
fun
it's in Captain skeletons thank you
all right I have to pick up all the gold
now clean up clean up okay
skill point maybe this whatever the one
tablet
right here okay
strangers
can you not use your skip why can I
Ranger more business stranger
oh Morp is nice lady
nice skeleton
warp is nice skeleton lady
I have to give more information
[Music]
I'll take the flame Shield
let's see okay I'm reading I'm reading
um
reading skills I don't know um oh yeah
you're playing
I also don't know what I'm doing with
the skills
I never know what to do what's your
secret mean lady
[Laughter]
shut up just Joe
should we do right now
Necromancer is kind of cool I love
necklace is really nice yeah the
character is kind of cool
but somehow the what is that
all of the scale is gonna confuse me
wait I have to talk to them
oh you talk already I'm talking now but
I think us being in the group messed up
the the cutscene oh
how much of the game have you played uh
well I guess I already played this part
so I don't need to see it I played and
the beta I played like
um
wait how much did I play end of act one
get some work done yeah is this your
first time playing the main game
uh uh I played uh last week or so one
time
um but before me and coroni played
Diablo 2 resurrected right yeah
and then they say that one's really good
like this one and then at uh when I was
a child my mom used to play Diablo one
and two I suppose and I was watching her
and sometimes trying to game uh myself
but I was always too scared of
everything and I like cookies never gets
past the first little boss so
I was just like wandering around always
and now the time I'm playing it properly
I mentioned on stream I feel like I
understand why you like it because it's
not too scary for you because I know you
don't like scary games well maybe now
it's not too scary but but it definitely
was yeah although I saw something and I
think that we're maybe still gonna see I
don't know I'm confused what happens
when but like the blood ritual stuff and
all that that
is scary even now fun
oh I love that yeah it was scary too
everything's scary
Define scary what is scary
how much scary is scary everything is
scary no
life is scary life is scary true yeah
life is scary yeah so die
oh
bro
what's going on
there's just a lot going on that's fine
work cleans the battlefield I'm excited
for boss fights I want to see how
quickly we can kill a boss
I took an arrow to my heart
wow you took an arrow to veneer yeah
why why I have no no Mana no Mana
Mana
oh no Mana
will
more bugles sorry sir are you playing
like five years
so Sarah is better apparently according
to some people but you know I'm a
phoenix I gotta be a fire saucerer yeah
I wouldn't believe it if you were an ice
sorcerer
where is great yeah yeah I feel like in
most other games that I played like
MMORPGs where you have the choice
between Fire and Ice Mage or Source or
whatever usually the ice one is always
like super weak
to go
right like ice ice is more like for
status effects and that's why people go
for it but fire is just like more
physical I think like yeah well not
physical it just deals more damage in my
opinion
well think about it if you freeze
someone like you can just they can just
get on
someone they're like that's like a piece
of their body that's gone
yeah but I think it's good if it's
diablo balances it's so well that you
can play Ice and still do good damage
that's good
door I appreciate that maybe I sometimes
some other time
but not this time
I also wanted to play a dream
I was playing I was considering playing
a druid in the beta but everybody was
saying that Druid was like super weak
yeah super difficult I don't know did
they not did they change anything in the
balancing since Kinda Yeah okay it's not
weak anymore like it's the build
it depends on the build I think okay
yeah
Kelly you know it's cute you have five
skeletons right yeah and I just stayed
behind a little bit one of your
skeletons stayed behind with me
what a gentleman to be thank you Debbie
for staying with Wawa what a sweetheart
gosh that's that's the dead beats for
you making sure nobody gets left behind
so sweet just so that I'm not everything
and scared in the dark
oh
except the fight's coming Jesus
is it too weak we need stronger
opponents I know we're kind of we are
really steamrolling yeah
whoa there we go we look really cool
okay now we're cooking we look really
cool though
kill him
wow I'm fast
yeah we could go to tier World tier two
if we wanted to I think we might need we
probably should at this point
can we do it while uh chat can we do it
while we're in the middle of the game
maybe we need to finish the quest first
we need to get to the finish some quests
like complete some quests to add to the
here too yes okay but it's not that hard
if like from one to two okay
I think I'm already on tier two
yeah
wait then wouldn't we not be allowed to
play with each other though
I'm so confused about that
IDK
whoa whoa no whoa whoa what's that skele
dude thing
yeah if we play with others we following
the the host world so if it's like like
Pier One yeah okay so I won't have to
change it okay why am I running don't
run away
[Music]
is still deep inside of you saying no
too scary it's okay
you play
well I guess I could sell this
yeah my point here two weeks and just go
back to Cleopatra yeah oh wanna want to
do it now probably we can just open the
portal oh okay finish the mission first
no we can do it in the middle of the
dungeon too
I mean we can do that
okay
okay whatever you guys want to do this
is gonna be like a more XP too right
true enough yeah so we better do it now
how do I get out of the
uh dungeon map
uh do we just teleport out or
we just need to press T oh God it's been
a while okay
here we go did we leave someone behind
so everybody teleporting to kill the
Shad okay
no girls left behind no no ladies all
right now let's let's go to a higher
higher level
how to change
uh you need to go to the wait the statue
uh
the world tears tattoo
wait is the is the green one you yup yup
yup the green one
um
what's your statue
[Music]
uh statue I I've never visited this
statue statue come out okay
oh
okay let's sell things I also need to
sell
um I need to scrap my things anyway yeah
[Music]
anymore
it's not letting me
huh
it will not let me press confirm
what happened with the Discord can you
guys hear me yeah yeah
uh
hello we hear you
can you hear us
hello
yep we can okay
only the party leader can switch here's
this chat yeah only the host apparently
ah
oh they hear you yeah I hear you
okay yeah let me just restart
chat chat chat
where's the Statue what statue what's
that I don't see a statue
go north
okay wait yellow check mark up north
yeah North
is this this one but she pinned it oh
she penned it okay yeah over there
yeah I just went up there I couldn't
change anything no so you have to do it
okay veteran because I can't do anything
one this will be uh enemies are more
challenging monsters give up to 20
increased experience and they drop 15
more gold
money everyone has all active portals
it terminates are reporters we have to
walk back to the
um dungeon
it's fine Ryan because of Any active
nightmare okay
no no no no no nightmare sounds fun I I
don't know you have to vote for it could
be worse than my real nightmares
we're losing about 50 50. yeah I'm
trying to click to respond
what are you scared Kelly do you not
want to do it no I do no please here
again
hold this to respond let me see ah I see
except more prison Necromancer and she's
scared of dying
well if you were scared
no more points to be skeleton it makes
no sense with Mark's lore no
okay uh it has been changed but I guess
we gotta wait for Kyla what's what's
happening internet Maybe
yeah I think restarting
okay all good last morph runs in circles
wait I have a skill that's called glass
can and I've heard this word before on
the internet yeah a glass can it means
that you know your damage is like real
good but you're gonna die real quickly
I see so is it someone who speaks a lot
but no action
no no no no actually like they deal a
lot of damage but they should not get
attacked or else they're gonna die
almost
yeah that's why it's a glass Cannon
because it'll shatter pretty easily okay
yeah so think of like a Pokemon that has
like 50 Health but like they have a
super strong attack yeah like you said
Gengar Gengar for example Shadow Ball
Gengar gets hit really really hard
should I love Gengar though because the
speed is like real good yeah
now getting our rules just not in those
luck or should I improve this Chad help
me help me chat help me Destiny binder
pick Hydra okay Hydra yeah Hydra summon
a three-headed Hydra for 10 seconds each
head spits fire at the enemies what the
[\h__\h] I can summon the fire dragon
let's go nice that sounds amazing
exciting I want to try it I'm Gonna
Leave the city for a moment
oh Kyle I can't connect to Discord
the [\h__\h] what's going on with what
we just gave our time I'd say okay
we can kind of stray outside while
waiting okay not completely going on a
mission
because mean girls don't leave other
Mean Girls behind
exactly is that how it works yeah is
that how it works in the movie yes it is
let me see oh Kiwa was awesome yeah
that's how that's how the plot goes
right
they learn the power of friendship yeah
and like we watch very different movies
forever
foreign
adorable
oh I can respond them elsewhere
the silent chest do we need a key for
that I want this silence chest yeah I
can't open it sadly but I want to open
it can we buy a can chat oh you know it
I'm sure you know it oh Kyla
okay oh welcome back hi Kyla
I changed back the connection
glad to see her all right okay I think
someone need to invite me back
party
[Music]
yeah let's go QR let's get them
hey
oh I'm going to die no no no no no no
rattle them boys
everyone dead
including your skeletons yeah I'm just
cleaning up the battlefield real quick
okay okay I brought him what the [\h__\h]
morph is clean freak
well there's some level 48 dudes here
that's a strong guy oh what are you
doing in Newberry huh
noobs only
I only knew people
nice little gold for his pockets
[Applause]
Tyler let us know when you're ready
it's okay it's okay
you guys want to check out the Stellar
while we're at it yeah that sounds fun
what's there
I have no idea stop oh okay I'm down
let's go
what what's that for sure it's like a
mini dungeon was that an okay yeah I
like uh yes invite me now Kyla or
oh no no no no it's okay I'm I'm still
um trying to fix the bottom line okay
take your time yeah
yeah
it's fine
true
yeah yeah so it's okay it's okay uh
you've seen it all you've experienced it
all
indeed stay strong they just got bad or
wet I don't even know what happened
there's no problem logging in oh no yeah
oh that's it
goodies this looks nice these all look
super good yeah wow this is it now nice
loot ladies was a small cell
um okay leaving the cellar
okay
like a wine cellar right Carrara
I don't drink wine what what's that wine
cellar comment yeah yeah he said he had
a seller you said you had to sell her
I'm just asking Hey where's beside her
head
where's the cider Brewery
that's what I want to know where's the
cider Brewery
I just want to know where
where the mini drankies at if I had a
wine cellar I'd only put iced tea there
I think
I think I'm in oh really okay
yay
I'll do it look good
maybe we can invite unless you're not in
the game yet what I'm in game
maybe it takes a moment oh wait now
invited
independent okay
yay
[Music]
uh try to catch up with us it's okay
it's okay I'll just teleport okay we're
having a party right now
I'm not ready
these guys are nothing they're chumps
so like we're kind of steamrolling yeah
yeah yeah we're still doing pretty good
I'm glad we changed tears
yeah it's good now it's more like a
little bit more
chat a little bit um
I I didn't totally just almost yeah
we're fighting stronger enemies
it does feel like it yeah but I already
gotta level up so the EXP is flowing
I'm close to Loveland I'm excited for
hard bosses yeah yeah I wanna do the the
act one boss but I I guess we probably
won't get there today
[Music]
I tried to look for Monsters I can't
find it works just following you guys
okay follow follow Kyla we're gonna run
back to the um
here I see Kyla oh yeah let's go
that was awesome
yay let's go oh so you guys finished the
what is that the the story the first
story The Dungeon one no no we were
doing like a seller like a random little
okay okay okay
there is an event
okay here we are we can go to the new
skeletons I'll get some movies
we need to wait for a moment it will
spawn here I think okay I'm gonna change
my skirmishers okay oh it's this thing
it's the defense skellies
inspect the ancient Obelisk oh here we
go
let's go
bring it downstairs Corpses
yeah
go Little Dragons go
okay
do we have to stand on this plate so as
long as we can stand still
do you have to keep standing on it until
it's as long as you can it's already
it's already done it's already done oh
it's already done yeah they're like um
orange circle until it's gone
and then
oh okay
yay
[Applause]
I want to see
some some stats on who does the most
damage me too do we get to see that no I
don't think so no
what I want to see more wants to see if
she's actually helping
you have the power of five skeletons I'm
sure you're helping I guess so that's
true Shield skellies
my Defenders
[Music]
so Kyla which which uh uh classes did
you already play
uh uh I played uh sorceress and
Barbarian before
sorcers and barbarians oh
huh
magic sounds fun we've still got some
different classes to go
yeah true yeah I'm using magic seems fun
in this game in particular
I just personally and in games like this
I just always like to keep a distance
from the enemy so I'm usually like some
kind of Mage class
or or a Healer I'm usually a Healer I
feel like you'd do good with Necromancer
too because Necromancer has a lot of far
away stuff yeah yeah yeah yeah
I I like Nick romance my my sorcerer
it was like a tank sorcerer
I think all of the Demons
but instead of a necromancer I would
like to be a nickel Manta and someone
cats
big scary canvas and eat you up
they have they have two forms they can
be big scary cats or they can be small
kitty cats that you can pet
that sounds amazing right yeah I know
right
forget the skeleton deadbeats I want I
want skeleton cats
or they could just be regular casts
that's fine too
okay like careful it's fine I'm calling
my holy [\h__\h]
yeah hell oh okay you're back up okay
yeah
they coming
non-flexing
flexing
not just a casual Flex it's all right we
forgive you yeah it's okay
for forgiving me casually arrives in a
Mustang
this way
okay
[Music]
okay now we are going to at all where do
you have you have wolves now I see the
the ghosts of the Wolves I'm calling my
wolves oh that's cute
The Necromancer isn't the only one that
can summon some friends to help nice
yeah that's so true the wolves are super
cute though
I can
you know I'm thinking about it now when
I was um
trying to choose classes for this one
[Music]
it was like
yeah but like I thought the Wolves were
just for a show like in the character
selection because they didn't mention
anything about somebody moves
just an image but okay hmm maybe next
time good to be true eh maybe next time
there are like 10 slots yeah yeah I mean
that's the reason that you can keep
playing Diablo again and again right so
you just need to complete the main
campaign first and then after that you
can play the Druid after that yeah yeah
let's try different characters
true Maybe
I should go back
No Going Back
left or right left okay
we're back in the mine yeah
I think we'll blast through it again
yeah hopefully because yeah good feeling
have to do everything again but we
didn't get so far anyway that's all
right it was just exp it was a warm-up
yeah preview
yeah
arms away
oh crony something's spinning around
it's almost like a chronicopter
[Laughter]
too perfect yeah
I just like spinning
[Music]
wings
I think we really need more mops
this is like
too little for us no this is planning no
no no no this is
I want the bitrate to suffer
oh it's too bad Kyle I can only do World
tier two I'm so sorry the best I can do
it's it's not your fault
I'm just saying no
Kyla is too bored she already played
everything this is boring this is
beneaper
this is boring
this is fun
it's not fun for her it's nothing and
the worst time in the world right now
you can tell yeah
exactly
no guys
she's just hanging out we're just
pulling your leg you're fine yeah it's
just hanging with the noobs
you seem a little too uh Pro but I guess
you know we can include you
okay you can hang out in our Noob Squad
that's fine yeah
I'm the part of the noobs oh we're back
here unless we became the mean with a
horse
I mean My Level is the lowest and the
noob yeah I'm the most Noob yeah
full blade
bring in the bars let's go boys
okay yeah I'm so excited I love these
fights I want the floor covered in
viscera for me to clean up
ah
is that an evil laugh yes
but more like style even left okay which
with that guy which is not so evil after
all oh nice yeah what the [\h__\h]
I got okay
you killed the boss too fast
it's mine that was only a mini bar
it's not the big big boss not yet yeah
you've gonna
um uh play with the same character in
your like other streams or are you do
you have separate characters
uh I I have a necromancer oh okay oh
cool yeah
what about you is this your uh I was
gonna just play with this character
um and then if if the group ever like
feels like not playing anymore then I'll
just continue playing this character on
my own why that was what I was gonna do
sure because I I cannot see us like
finishing the whole game together I
doubt that we can make time so often and
yeah
especially because I want to play
a lot of times where not everybody is
available so I'll probably beat the game
on my own as well
I'll be available every time by the way
of course
we weren't referring to you we knew
already
when is she ever not available
great customer service
yeah I mean if you want to play anytime
this
okay okay
I will support your addiction even
though I shouldn't wow
yeah I mean I will still going back to
my main character so if like let's say
you guys have already like reached um
tier three or maybe I can just play my
main okay yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
Kyla with your like potential to play so
many games for so many hours I feel like
I'm surprised you're not or are you are
you playing Zelda tears of the Kingdom
oh that's the reason like I mean I need
to choose between the Zelda and the
Diablo yeah yeah because I know that if
I I just cannot yeah later
I think for some games that I cannot
have the time to play I'll just watch
others to play and okay you can watch me
play
but I'm almost done I'm almost done
though with the game
members playing Zelda too
[Laughter]
oh yeah I saw you were almost done yeah
but I'm trying to stall now because the
game is so good I don't want to finish
it yet we were really grinding on it for
a while there yeah like nine hour
streams but that's nothing for Kyla from
for Kyla that's nine hour stream is like
a three hour stream or something oh
silence Kiara silence
come on now I'll give you that both of
you guys are insane people trapped
without the Hoist what are you saying
you're also the one that do like a lot
of streams
you guys all do long streams yeah yeah
the way I saw her mama they all grind in
our own ways I guess
you're all guilty all right well guilty
as charged is that how you say it yeah
yeah yeah yeah
I don't know streaming it doesn't feel
like a chore to me so I mean I don't
know it's just kind of fun I don't
really notice it
not anymore at least how do we get down
there
this way we need to go around a ladder
well ladder
sugoi
so technology
technologically
a
sugoi oh
they should look at Germany and use
Germany technology
put an elevator in this weird ass
dungeon
something happening are we opening the
door no I don't think so I think we just
need to go this way
oh you'll think we're going out no no no
no no paper
[Music]
Quest complete no reward received you
have completed this Quest already okay
well no reward received
sadness I mean I've already completed
the quest wait wait we are going out
you got the wrong way oh
I have to talk to the dude
oh gosh those days I made the same
mistake before they also did the same
mistake that makes me a little
yeah wait do we have to do it again
no no no we just have to go all the way
back
that's like just a shortcut
all righty always talk to the NPCs
really we got it I don't need NPCs I got
my girls oh oh only one person had to
talk to
yeah ah there we go the scene completed
by the crownster oh we are we are
opening the door Orange
[Music]
okay no
oh everybody's dead sweet there's one
that's alive
talks a lot though do you have any money
yeah
over where
it's good time so much who did this
search don't worry I made sure
oh
yeah he's super dead now jump everybody
jump jump oh well not super dead enough
girls are you coming over
ah
um
but yeah
okay let's go it's okay I already saw
the star of the story if you guys want
to see it it's in my Beta stream chat if
you're curious about the story yeah
oh yeah
mommy yeah
they're all watching I see a mother yeah
we all know Lilith is hot okay we get it
are we are we watching the cutscene
I mean I skipped it oh okay
press Skip and then you guys gonna be
skipped oh no no it's not it's not oh
really yeah there's a symbol that shows
that someone's watching okay next time
maybe I'll watch
Mean Girls play together don't you even
worry about that yeah Mean Girls sleigh
crony
yes I wanted to ask you something
yes would you maybe consider
um sharing some of that cake with me
it's not fair desperate need I am in
desperate need
s
okay I just got fixed what might but
it's still like nothing compared to your
cake and that's just not fair I want the
cake too yeah
I mean it's it's you can't help what
you're born with
yeah I mean I can't deny it I can't I
was gonna say it's not that good but you
know it is pretty it is pretty good
question for you to sit on and stream
for long hours
oh wait I was gonna try to kill Tyler
but she was an animal yeah Kyla just
turned into a bear
really why did I miss that
showing your skills to me you gotta look
closely
uh okay so so no cake for me is that
what you're saying
no I think I think you should ask again
for them to like buff your buff your
cake I feel like the buff that I got uh
was the first and the last one there
will not be any more Buffs
what
such is my desk
that's not fair
make up for it with um my dance moves
yeah
yeah you could probably get another like
you know outfit
where there is more cake butt pads
in the new outfit but be like oh I don't
want to be able to see the butt pads or
notice that they're butt pads but there
are butt pads in the skirt or whatever
yeah Brenda the shorts
well uh as far as I know they wouldn't
change like you know the butt size just
because there's a new outfit
but but you could still ask for the pads
though yeah
I can't really say no because those are
real things yeah well I know Kpop Idols
use it yeah exactly okay so maybe it's a
tribute
suitcase the final butt pad yeah it's
just for it's just for protection you
know when I get down on the floor you
know now I need some butt pads to
protect my butt I already I already
insured my butt for uh one million
dollars but you know even the insurance
it's just not not enough we gotta see it
has a use do we need to climb down I
think we need to climb down
anyone talk about the talk with the
whatever sign is that like in the corner
of the room corner it's like I wait now
I see now I see a quest mark thingy oh
there it is okay okay okay
nice thank you more yeah Morp says no
problem
place to trap nope
million dollar booty million dollar
booty
crony did you know
that your mommy is next on my list
I was going after all the whole moms
what do you mean what do you mean what
well you know
baby popular with whole moms but the
thing is that your mom is kind of
special to me because she's a hello
project otaku just like me
so many YouTubers
[Music]
yeah so you're going after my mom yeah
no
oh no
no my mom not my mom
she she will maybe adopt me you know
because she she she's into Idol so I'm
into Idols I'm sure she wants a daughter
like me you can have a sister
is my game glitched you guys are Smith
now you're just all done in the back huh
what happened no you guys are Frozen at
the gate
all right hand attack enemies
oh you gave it your game froze probably
you cannot move
I mean I can move no you're standing
still I don't think you're having like a
um a network
issue a DC maybe uh
yeah if I leave the party and come back
do I do I have to start over it's a good
question
I mean it's okay
um there's gonna be like a portal that
you can teleport to us later on
okay yeah no worries oh okay
um
progress is based on party leader well
that's good news
nice okay don't worry I'm gonna get out
of here
um
no one can have more than one parent
right
i i i oh
Morp is request yes
why are you girls dying
what oh no it's because of like if we go
further and it's not in the range it's
gonna be like oh I can't see your HP
dance
oh of course why would Kyle and I
ah
Invincible Kyla
where is okay we can't we still at the
door okay
we just need to go around I gotta run
all the way back
yeah where are you now all the way back
kind of far away I'm a little further to
oh no nothing changed
yeah let me see
um let me try again to just leave okay
did you maybe just restart the game
completely
yeah
I restart the game
okay let's wait here let's not go too
far in case she has to walk all the way
no no no
can be like teleport to us okay if you
say so
yeah yeah yeah
luck is not good tonight
yes that's what matters that's the fun
part you know about collabing
like
the club is endearing yeah
now let's let's morph back into party
yeah
I'm in yay the party campaign state does
not match with the party leaders you'll
be making progress in the party leaders
campaign okay now to teleport to you
guys you need to go to the
um the Waypoint there there's gonna be
like four portals just hop into us
okay teleport to oh crony yep okay
macaroni okay
yes ladies let's go
let's go speaking of macaroni
last time I was in America I had my
first ever macaroni and cheese
what'd you think
yeah I knew you'd like it yeah it was so
good but the portion was so big I could
I only eat like half of it I swear it
was huge I tried my best
it's better to share
yeah American portion yeah what the [\h__\h]
American portion please they are too big
I feel like it's better to make it a
shared plate yeah but it was so good I
want to try making it at home
um yeah it's it's pretty it's fairly
easy to do is home cooking
um
don't really know how
mac and cheese tastes like
what I thought everybody over there eats
mac and cheese all the time maybe
maybe not me or maybe not
I'm gonna ship you a bunch of instantly
I'm gonna ship you a ton of instant
Kraft mac and cheese are the instant
ones good too
blocked again
yeah they're decent it's not as good as
like The Gourmet stuff like stuff you
might get at like a restaurant that's
for sure
what the [\h__\h] still pretty tasty I mean
I think it depends on the person
and not in excess of course oh my gosh
let go of me
hellbinder oh
that guy's annoying
um
I got
um Kiara's birthday present it came in
today
I saw something on the Internet and I
thought you'd really like it what
yeah you're getting me a birthday what
yes Mr little thing I hope to ship it to
you make it in time for your birthday
but uh I don't know maybe you'll never
use them but I thought I don't know you
can give it to me in in Japan I'll be
there too oh
here is like yeah I don't know what just
happened I I don't I don't know what the
[\h__\h] happened
yeah she's not here what happened I was
trying to kill an enemy and went in the
same spot where I was putting my mouse
at suddenly something appeared and I
accidentally clicked yes oh no but like
it was the leader what was that anyway
here let me maybe we can invite you back
the later now is crony
yeah you're the leader now oh no you're
joining uh you're about to be
transferred to the party okay transfer
now did I miss something
you're all fine can I can I delegate my
post to you just just leave the party
just leave the party
just leave the party just leave the
party uh right click okay yeah wait I
got a walk to you girl and now and now
it's gonna be me okay I'm leaving the
party no no
no I'll be alone no you know fine I'll
be the party leader that's fine I'll be
the party leader everybody else come
back that's okay I'm inviting the others
back into
okay I'll be the party leader on my
powerful PS5
[Music]
I can host
okay I I need to catch up on you girls
why am I so far oh boy
okay I don't see anyone
are you guys gonna teleport to me maybe
wait yeah
I'm confused take up teleport to town
first the [\h__\h]
okay
yeah let's watch together
oh
it's gonna be easier okay
why did that window
hold hands all right I'll wait for you
guys
okay coming
what was that thing that popped up on my
screen anyway
did you see it
let's go
yeah
sometimes like the leader will do
something or like a character will do
something and then if you decline
it's like join in it'll kick you from
the party oh
I declined a
oh okay some cutscenes what
I don't know
crony dead or is it just not here oh I'm
still here I was gonna say no way no way
I couldn't protect her
I couldn't be there for her
time yes RIP and tear decomposed the
flesh
you can't just kill me off like that
I'm still in the game let's go
I I can still hear her voice
ouch
it's because I am here no no way
[Applause]
oh my goodness
I'm not God boy I'm not gonna fall for
it
I should have teleported what have I
done you can still do it
I still have the choice
[Music]
you're gonna revive everyone
oh no dear oh dear oh bother
oh joy oh you're almost here
I am almost here and I'm gonna die no
you don't want this you're not gonna die
Pro tips don't die
yeah just drink all the potions
I'll come to pick you up
Mean Girls don't leave each other behind
strange
yeah it brought a whole party I thought
you guys would like the experience
points
oh hell yeah
hi
oh I see them
are you taking care of them yeah of
course what kind of what kind of party
host would we be now now we can go
your Uber is here croony
getting the Uber
oh whoa thank you oh and the losers
we're going shopping
no
no no no
uh uh up somebody went up
green is Kayla
finishing the dungeon
Crashers crapping me
no
gotta clean the battlefield gotta clean
the battlefield I can't do that oh a
succubus cool tornadoes
they look sick
Uber
[Music]
okay okay
[Laughter]
help
I feel years coming off of my existence
every time you say that
oh yes
woo
poisoning there's even so many bodies
around guys I have to clean them all up
thank you they've had enough of me chat
already I I guess next time I'll play
alone no no no no no no
no don't do that
no alone
you see in the end all these all these
terms you know where I'm learning them
where well through chat whole live and
through everything I'm doing that's
connected with whole life you know
my education is thanks to all of you my
condolences
[Laughter]
oh yeah
ouch oh there was some nope some advice
I mean don't worry you can leave the
corpses they're useful for other skill
abilities
oh like what necromancer advice I don't
really understand
I mean I don't really see another use
for them is the thing but if I if I do
see a use for them then I can understand
I just kind of like to leave a queen
Battlefield oh wait okay I understand
now because I I I I know that skill the
corpse explosion skill is absolutely
insane you will love it oh that one's
pretty handy I like that one if you've
seen that yet if you get to it in the
skill tree you choose it and then
whenever you run around and you press
the scale all the corpses all the dead
enemies around you will like explode and
do AOE damage yeah it'll be like
fireworks yeah I love that that sounds
amazing God I love necromancer
yeah okay
ouch
this dungeon is very very long
we're making good progress though yeah I
think of course if we finish this it's
already quite an accomplishment
light
my dragons are so cute I hope I get some
fan art with my dragons
you're so cute your little Hydra heads
yeah oh
[Music]
and Cali with her skeletons and chroni
with her wolves and and and Kyla as as
oh Kyla with her
and then crony with her chronicopter
souls or whatever that is
it actually wolves might be a better
idea
nah probably doesn't need any companions
I I think I like companions I I think I
like the idea of companions
I can be your companions though yeah we
are your companions you want to be my
wolf
wow are you ready for mobs
maybe not like that what do you mean not
like that what do you think I said
yeah
I'm drawing it right now
better just kill all of this mobs then
think about that
it's okay
yeah they're definitely taking a lot
more time to kill which I appreciate
yeah I think it feels better idea that
we changed yeah I didn't want to do it
alone but as a party
um I am confident yeah yeah
it's a [\h__\h] chaos though [\h__\h]
chaotic I love it
[Applause]
yay next go next go next
the next we're too strong the boss might
be a bit hard enough might actually kill
a couple of you well looking forward
guys let's go I can't wait
and if you die from the boss like where
do you respond
great question no idea but hey not
knowing is part of the fun yeah right
as the ritual started already here or
what I hear voices dead priest
oh no she's just talking next to me okay
yeah she's just a little freaky
it's kind of like she's showing a little
bit she's destroying fan art I have your
back lady
we want to watch us catching this one's
pretty cool oh oopsies I kind of skipped
it already
[Laughter]
where is everyone oh there they are a
lot more aren't you guys moving I'm
watching hey why aren't you guys moving
oh because you're watching it okay it's
fine I got it
enjoy the casino hold on the fort I've
done this battle before see stop okay
okay you're fighting someone's yes
Mother stop you fighting alive
I'm good don't worry about it I got my
skeletons
she awakened me magpies I saw a magpie
blood ritual the other day on YouTube
okay I thought you were just gonna say I
saw a magpie and I was gonna say oh I'll
make my blood pressure oh
reactions
they were crying when one was like dead
and all the magpies were gathering
around and going like
it's weird warning oh yeah oh hi are you
now we're fighting now
what what's uh who are we fighting
we are fighting the mother
ow yeah she's really pissed right now
okay wait I I'm never gonna watch
costumes again
if I'm missing all the action no no no I
wouldn't have skipped it if I had known
that there was gonna be
do we fight the health spawns and all
that or her yeah probably a good idea
she's immune right so you have to fight
gotta kill her her demons
all right
whoopsie
okay come on get him oh
thank you
she's
strong come on get the hell spawn I got
that okay that's one down
let's go
oh sorry I got potions
potions for days let's go
yum yum oh
you want some of this you want some of
this you want some let's go did not mean
to do that like these oh yeah these are
some big boys
all right let's get a little tough I
like it yeah this is fun yeah
oh God I should focus on one enemy
skeletons where are you at what was that
yeah that's usually a good idea
oh the pit Lord is pretty scary Oh Mamma
Mia hey here I go again and then you
ball
who is a spicy meatball
come on
[Music]
do we have to kill enemies in order to
make them spawn oh here's one yep
somebody not too close gonna start
singing original song The Pit Lord
really likes me he will not leave me
alone
distractions
oh
[Applause]
nice one team that was pretty cool that
was rough I don't know about you girls
but my HP was struggling
yeah let me see what it was fun
we're protecting me
as I was protecting you
are we are we skipping
I don't know I was like I have no idea
I'm not skipping it because I feel bad
yeah
foreign
why there
The Horizon hit a vault there oh finding
it was her life's work as Australian
people say bravar
ES
no
[Music]
I need time
okay I'm done watching
okay okay okay I'm done all right okay
me too
[Music]
oh it's complete well now we've got a
cheeseburgers
we need to go back home we can just
teleport right
yeah okay
we need to go back
all right a little walk in the park
let's get going
make sure to walk in either one line or
hold your partner's hand
s
and yes man like some ducks okay
[Music]
oh hi oh yeah we forgot some enemies
more enemies more exp very nice
I'm just gonna take the loot
Goblin
yeah I'm Lou Goblin
I can't help but
no I'm a loot Goblin just just I am in
general
Gathering Gathering things
I get it
refiner no
okay
um
waste and this is where we accidentally
left before
yup where is it
okay we need to go there to find near
Rail
oh that dead beats down
down you go
is this like the I don't know like the
the deadbeats that try to sign up for a
job at Cali's place but like failed
so they get mad yeah they Rebel Revenge
anger Beats where did Carla go
it's okay just come here
Kayla said we must hold hands we're
walking in line you know my hands are
just that long
dude are you like Luffy or something
yeah
they're just flexible and that long
okay amazing I forgive
but not again lady not again later beans
I like that name
and our Trader Beats
foreign
ER beats sounds like a merchant name
Trader Joe's
or something
Trader Beats from the Trader Joe's
bus in 10 minutes I don't know if we can
join the world boss
okay yeah it's just getting no need
I'm Invincible oh nice
do you guys want to join the world boss
hell yeah yeah level 35 plus
we can take them we can take them no no
yeah we can
try it's it's there it's like but does
it scale of the map does it scale to us
no it's like level 35 hell yeah I'll do
this four of us if you combine all our
levels it's way over 35.
um
you will never kill it in time
okay oh is it a timed thing never mind
if it's time then forget it five minutes
and 10 minutes we need to just go as
fast as possible to there but actually I
can do it you guys really want to do it
I can just
really no because I can I can go with my
horse and then you guys can tell for
there oh if you want to try no no no no
no it's okay
one time when we're higher level we'll
do it yeah and then it makes more sense
yeah One Direction okay
then we can do it confidently
why are you so enlightened what happened
oh I touched a shrine
oh nice I didn't see one I was enchanted
I was blessed with like a momentary
boost
yeah yeah
there's several of those and they all
have like different effects oh I see
here's one artillery Shrine
um
to attack faster and summon holy arrows
holy arrows
that sounds fun
we need to find the neural yeah my
arrows
check out my arrows I'm sure she's
around somewhere
yes
in this game it gives me light Skyrim
vibes
yes music is good I can shoot I don't
know Nero standing somewhere I found her
before somewhere here but it's been too
long I don't remember
um
oh there's a chest here nice
though chest oh I want chesto
oh no the trees
the trees I don't want to hurt the trees
the trees are good people
trees aren't people Kiara they're good
people they're not they are beautiful
they're good trees but they're not
people Kiara is what I'm saying
wake up
they have a song they have a soul I know
it's been a long time wandering these
woods but you gotta stop mistaking trees
for people
but I mean
the trees that we know it's not moving
so maybe it can be people oh oh yeah
yeah thank you
all right ladies whatever keeps you sane
okay
oh this way there we go I found it
yeah it wasn't a person it was a stone
darkened Holt
hello welcome oh snowy
it's very cozy I like it I love snowing
we're getting closer to Santa Claus's
home with every step
I want Christmas to come already
please let's enjoy the summer a little
bit no I hate summer summer sucks Summer
sucks I agree
oh whoa
[Music]
what's the cheapest cell value I wonder
if I've been good or naughty this year
I'd say good
maybe your chat can answer that
well they don't know me they don't know
me like who
does someone know you better who's gonna
be the judge of whether or not I know me
I think I've been pretty good and if
Santa's not gonna give me anything
that's fine because I'm just gonna get
my own gift that's a very good way of
thinking about it it sounded very salty
no that's not salty yeah what do you
mean
I I couldn't understand it I can
definitely like I don't need Santa's
help to get me what I want I can just
get it myself it's a real girl boss
attitude let's go yeah thank you
no problem girl
why are we fighting Phantoms again oh
It's a Spooky Forest
why why are we going back and forth
there's a leader here but none of us
know who it is
I was just looking at my inventory it's
fall I want to sell some stuff yeah my
inventory is full too actually yeah
we can teleport to the city and come
back here right yeah we could do that
okay
[Music]
kill shad
teleport break at least it's not as bad
as in like Diablo 2 where you had to go
and sell your [\h__\h] after five minutes of
fighting all the time always inventory
full it ah it was so
but typical Diablo it was typical though
it was like the charm Point somehow
yeah
diabolo hey bolo okay let's Salvage all
of them
oh I got some really nice new items
actually dang are you selling or are you
um salvaging
salvaging okay both
it's really gonna benefit my main
account so
um
okay
[Music]
all right um junk common
junk junk
can I not just sell these guys because
these like I don't need the the looks of
these
I'm gonna go to my wardrobe because
that's the most important part
I should actually carry it where where
it is
um
is this
[Music]
this one I'll wear
why not they sell hot yeah that's what I
was thinking
and this do I have a stash in this game
yet because I have a satire
of course yeah okay is it by the
Wardrobe
yep okay
oh
[Music]
mustache
drew it
hmm
's important
fashion is pretty important
what's this
wow oh this one is so cool so expensive
how does somebody have
um
70 000 gold from
from
oh
Kyla probably has a lot I have 107. I
can I can give you some no way no ways
like you're giving me a light truck
so kind
it's okay I just saw something in the
store that's like freaking expensive I
don't need it I don't need it no
my my chat tells me not to buy things
yeah yeah just yeah because you can just
uh pick them up
apply look
you still won the gold no
no okay okay I am done uh doing my
things
okay
which which uh what am I which
teleportation thingy am I using of it
we can use any hours
this is the Winding Way one
yeah okay
okay
me too
no Moe's not streaming my PV today
why is I figured I figure three is
enough yeah I figure three is enough
yeah because it's not like we have
vastly different povs yeah that's fine
yeah oh heavy scythe
that seems like it could be good oh
brutal heavy Scythe yes for the Grim
Reaper
it must be brutal yeah
awful
very nice beautiful
oh well there's a scary Red portal here
oh we should go in that's like fire
firing
oh the dog's speaking to us
they're a cute little wolf you big wolf
I guess the big wolf saying
actually meow meow meow
I don't know how you guys know about the
lore but it's looks like my Fisto
Fisto oh
bloodied wolf
this wolf saved me in the mountains
I had a horse once why are you helping
me are you watching the cutscene I'm
watching
oh yeah
oh this seems kind of like I anti
anti-hero character
cute He's fluffy
yes cute
wait can you pet the dog that is the
important question with games these days
I'd like to know it
is if no petting then [\h__\h] game
[Laughter]
okay I have a question Kiara did yeah
did I ever actually ask you to step on
my back or to just crack my back because
I don't remember asking you to step on
my bike no you you did you did remember
in the studio you laid down with your
face with your face on the ground uh
when we did the pretty uh the collab
debut thing yeah yeah yeah yeah you're
laying on the ground and you were like
can you step on my back and crack it
the way that I ask people to crack my
back is I breathe in and then I ask you
to push down as I breathe out but you're
supposed to use both your hands oh yeah
I was I was too weak oh didn't you crack
your back before Kelly yeah yeah we've
cracked each other's backs but with our
yeah
successfully damn yeah
what the [\h__\h]
is it back cracking time
sorry I was just so absorbed in the back
cracking conversation
I mean I I understand though I would
also like to get my back cracked but
that that the way you do it Cali just
scares me I don't want to hurt you
Ah that's okay I mean whenever people
give me massages they kind of do a
similar thing so yeah but they know how
to do it and I I could possibly kill you
when I do it I don't want that no
because you know like you know crack the
neck
um I think it should be fine unless you
want them to rest forever
[Music]
I don't know I don't remember you
standing on my back because I would have
remembered that because whenever I go to
get massages they say can I step on your
back and I say no you can't oh well no I
did not I did not step on your back yeah
oh but no you cannot do that
you wanted me to crack you back though
you were on the ground I remember that
you definitely used your hands
possibly
my noodle arms yes you don't know how it
feels like I've never gone any massage
what
what you should go it's so good
let's get addicted to that because what
I don't know is let's say that you know
like once you try it and then you're
gonna get yeah you can never go back you
all you will always want to get get a
massage once you did it once that's good
for you especially if you stream a lot
yeah you know yeah
I think so too probably like massage you
and be like holy Hector back is so stiff
what is wrong with you they look like a
tree
don't you feel back pain ever Kyla not
not really
wow what kind of chair do you have yeah
yeah it's very nice right which one
which one can we like is
brenwood yeah yeah
yeah I have a Herman Miller too me too
really nice like um normal gaming chair
though oh but those are not they're
they're supposed to be not that good
right
oh those hurts
yeah I mean people say like the office
chair is better yeah like long hours
right wait wait for if you stream like
10 hours do you sit straight like
properly the whole time
not really not really most of the time I
lay down
yeah I lay down yeah but I mean you lay
down my fears know about that like I I
really lay down
and then like usually my voice
somehow change a bit into like very very
common that's the time when I lay down
yeah I can lay down game oh you're
reclining yeah
yeah that's one good thing about gaming
chairs is that you can completely lie
down
when there's sleep while doing that
[\h__\h]
yeah yeah I saw something on Amazon
there was like there was like a bed like
a gaming chair bed and like it's like a
desk set up so that it's like a desk on
top of a bed so you wake up game and go
to sleep oh I know about that
uh-huh yeah I don't think I've seen that
one
no that doesn't sound amazing you'll be
bedridden for the rest of your life
starting what foyer
oh okay
I think I'm frozen again really oh no
everybody's we're jogging in place
skeletons included yeah well maybe it's
because of the Cross play you know ah
maybe could be which is really too bad
but let's see I'll just leave
it's okay
oh Kiara is the host again
look at this fancy beautiful Circle I
feel like if I trapped in this mirror
it's gonna like tell me who's the
prettiest of them all
yeah we all know the answer
well
in this game I mean I have my hot lady I
mean look at her she's I mean
I mean this is true but yeah okay
outside the game do you want to say
anything no what what are you saying I
didn't say anything who is the prettiest
of them all crony I don't know I don't
know I just think that's a no-brainer
yeah
it's you crony
it's rare what a surprise wow
[Music]
you would never anger me yet
you're too pretty for that
I'm
[Music]
my face is turning red on yo
what you doing this is
wow you're like Chopper
yeah oh no I'm not ready yet I have to
kill it it's an enemy no I can't kill
myself
[Music]
wow
how many wolves can you summon
or no
oh I added her head to my hydras
I got four now
that's kind of cool I think four is the
max though I'm pretty sure oh really
yeah okay
do rose only have the Shadow Ball
floating around yeah right anything else
what do they even do nothing cool
they just reduce damage
uh that's
getting received
I'm sure you have something better maybe
in the future
you know I kind of doubt that let me
take a quick look Wibble is that
question towards me or towards crony of
you set your first enchantment no why am
I stuck at this dark screen it's okay
I have nothing I only set up traps I
have no companion what is this screen
I've never seen it before press yes
what do I do with this
to unlock complete sorcerer Legacy
Legacy what
um
you have to do quests to unlock
enchantments
you need to finish your priority Quest
oh it's too early
let's see I restart my PS5 oh it's oh
[Music]
okay
I'll see eventually
from Level fishing
oh I have a quest that came in when I
turned number 15. well that was within
today so I couldn't have done it
which questo
where do I see my quest again
and press J J why is it not Q
because Q is potion right ah right true
yeah
[Music]
so it is
ah priority Quest oh sorcerer the legacy
of the Maggie this one you guys snitch
off collab I really want to do off
collab what do you want to do what do
you want to do in an off collab
let's go
let's go I'll bring I'll bring a
typically German one and maybe everybody
can bring a board game from their own
culture or whatever game of life
though we need to get perms
yeah yeah okay
that's a good idea oh my God wait a
second
um
connecting to diabolo for services I
think I might get in
that's okay chill do you know this um
like it's similar to Jenga do you know
this game where you have like a lot of
really thin wooden sticks and then you
let them fall on the table so they're
like all like a like they fall down like
a mess and you have to like yeah pick
them out like in Jenga without making
the other ones move I think yeah yeah
yeah Mikado
I've played that that's a fun one yeah
Mikado
let me join your party I think they had
some colors on them too and depending on
the color it even gave more points or
you had to get the ones I don't I don't
remember the rules anymore old memory
unlocked yeah very nostalgic
very nostalgic
children's games you're back in the
party yes
[Music]
oh I'm very far from you guys
here
they all go to hold on let me go to
kyovic wait hold on no no no they
appeared right as I went away
yay I'll go find you guys
I wonder if all necromancers are doomed
to be patanko wait wait now crony stream
death what
Cronus what is happening she's not
talking to us so her internet died man
what a night
it's a weird night I'm the only one so
far who didn't have any kind of issues
yet
there she goes there she goes
she'll be back sometime
but it has been it has been two hours
through it has been two hours too yeah
yeah I was gonna say crony sleepy from
from morning when we sleepy from night
time yeah next time we can play when
it's like morning for me and then it's
better times for you girls I think
except for well Kyla said it's any time
anytime's good for her so it was always
good to go anytime
anytime anytime so maybe next time 8 AM
for me or different time zones here
right yeah
yeah but we just we'll just uh go in a
circle everybody suffers sometimes such
as Diablo suffering
fun but I like
I like it though it's fun next time it
can be me
oh wake up I'll wake up I I I as I often
uh need to fix my sleep schedule anyway
me and the bones don't say things what
time is morning for you guys like
you wake up quite early actually oh no
oh you mean when I wake up that's
different that's a different story
so what time is it normally like
11 12.
yeah what about you
I had pants it really depends yeah I
wake up
um whenever I need to yeah you don't
sleep much do you
I already tried this conversation with
her tiara
that's more by the way I don't think we
can play next week because I don't have
time next week maybe the week after
yeah okay it's okay
yeah we'll see how it works out
yeah I don't know what happened crony
where at least I at least want to say
goodbye to her not just leave it like
this it's too fast and I'll say goodbye
we need to know what happened at least
right
agreed isn't the concert next next well
that's just one day
that's not gonna block my whole wink off
let's see what was that
yeah but
when he's traveling quite a bit come
over here and Stand By Me and and and uh
can we and if we stand in a triangle
maybe we can and pour some blood on the
ground maybe we can summon crony okay
okay that's a great idea
all right I'm not ready yet granny
I feel like you're not putting in enough
passion into the summoning
my Summit
I feel like I'm alone in here you know
I'm just like witchcraft thing and I
don't know
any text thing
he sent us a message oh she did yeah
open Discord Do You Wanna Say Goodbye
NBC
um it's been two hours anyway so
you know
just wanna wanna
um
a little peace out should the need arise
yeah
and I I want to say bye bye the crony
somebody worked at least yeah
it was fun though we did that one big
dungeon so that was pretty good I feel
good about it
um this is oh
oh okay
something has been I guess she got she
got sick of waiting for her
[Music]
and I'm forced into a cutscene she's
gonna open I don't know if we leave
right I don't think we can continue it
later on from oh
yeah
hello
[Laughter]
[Music]
it
happens to the best of us yeah
sorry about that okay no worries
um
switched internet recently and I think
that's the problem I talked to them
looks like I need to talk to them again
people
yeah it takes too much energy where do
we go what the [\h__\h] well no I don't want
to force anyone to stay but if it's true
what Kyla says then I would probably
finish it at least with Kyla
mm-hmm
wow we are halfway hmm
halfway but I mean I don't know um
are you planning to do like a solo no
like no okay not really okay
um
and then we just need to spit around
this then okay we can't spit around this
yeah midrand is good or maybe weaker we
can just split
like one go to the left one go to the
right ah okay yeah yeah where is this
I'll go right bye bye
hey just make sure you don't die
if I'll help as much as I can but if I
DC again that's probably curtains for
for more for tonight
okay okay okay yeah but this is kind of
your being alone
um
I need to come and help out my skeletons
can help you
hi thank you yeah
the Mean Girls are finally splitting up
oh no
no they shouldn't you never split the
party
rule number one of ccrpg crony is here
and spirits
mental mental supports
no oh my God I'm out of potions
okay
[Music]
pulled me over to him
hurry up skeletons what am I paying you
for yeah
they gotta get to work what the [\h__\h]
Cali
I know right they're just not pulling
their their weight
holy [\h__\h] I'm out of pushes again
um
here we go
nice
let's go
Connie if you do you think you like be
back you don't have to force yourself
but
if it takes too long don't worry about
it
oh it's just uh
yeah they
Mother of God
are you on your phone
yeah they they told me to uh just you
know stick around for 10 minutes but I'm
pretty sure it'll the dream will be done
in 10 minutes so oh no
I should not have switched service what
was I thinking
ah
why did I switched
with different Vibes yeah the bus is
here so if you guys aren't yeah ah we're
almost there we're almost there
it's okay it's okay it's okay it will
take some time I thought you said the
boss
yes
[Music]
no more Leroy
this I was I never ever had to use it in
the proper context before I'm very
satisfied but now you finally did did
you girls know where that's from is it I
know you know I know yeah I know the
reference
World of War cool
Leroy Dragon
I know that means because I played World
of Warcraft when that Meme was happening
foreign
I will call you now Leroy Kaila
or Kaila jokes
yeah it's better
Kyla Jenkins
I'm just gonna slowly decompose you and
have my skeletons hit you with their
Shields
carols of Lilith Harold is is the name
in German
what's that I think it's a name in
general yeah
yeah
so who's Harold
hello
is there any meaning of Harold I feel
like a dorky name I'm sorry there might
be some Heralds in Chad
that was rude the name connects with the
office worker I think
ah sounds so serious
air hosting
it's
the name of a smart person which is why
I said kind of kind of dorky it's so
weird how certain names just have this
like image
[Music]
you know real smart
you know what some names you feel like
they only fit adults but then how do the
like they were children before children
yeah but did it feel weird when they
were when they were children kind of
crazy to think about it like I can't
really imagine a child
but an adult how lawyers yeah yeah I can
imagine like a child Daryl Daryl Daryl
yeah Daryl
I could never I just can't imagine a
child named Daryl I hear the name Daryl
and I think of a guy in like a business
suit I'll just waiting coffee with like
in the break room hey Daryl what's up
with Kayla how's the workload going on
you know just the usual filling out
forms it's cool Daryl hey you know what
I'll talk to you later
maybe because I I've never like met
anyone before in Austria who's who's got
that name
oh
nothing
are you girls like gonna
teleport out or what no yeah
teleport out use that teleport huh but
there's still like yeah there's still
the campaign quest in inside
no but I oh yeah
why why why so far guys are like why why
you guys are so far
are we talk taking like different
portals maybe I don't know I don't take
any portal
um
that works too I didn't see a portal
they're a blue portal um outside that
room and blind
[Music]
it's okay I'm always Blended
it was next to the boss and Theory
by rathma anyway that's my first
Necromancer cool that guy's cool that's
my leader
oh
let's be a spell in this book we can use
to bring my I mean we can skip this I
think because at this point we skipped
so much story that we have no idea
what's going on but yeah listen to it in
my other stream solo no worries I'm
still
far ahead of this
okay
it's done yeah
yeah it's done Quest is done
okay let's go we can just teleport back
Yay good job ladies wow
[Music]
there's a giga chat here
whoa Giga Chad what's going on
actually
somehow I feel like that somebody who is
a fan
oh oh wow I didn't see I had such a cool
weapon that I picked up
sad
well that was really fun guys thanks for
inviting me to play it was a pleasure
play again sometime
hell yeah but no no
um no pressure that we always have to be
for but it would be nice
I wanna play so next time crony I
already said it next time we can do it
the evening time for you
and then
the morning for me we'll figure it out
daytime can we we'll get there yeah
afternoonish
inviting me too no no problem I think
I'll read some super chats actually
because it was kind of a short stream so
yeah I think me too yeah oh so fun do
you want them together
do you want to read each other's super
chats and read yours you read mine
[Laughter]
[Music]
see you next time when we sleep good
night everyone yay
okay hi guys
yeah it was kind of short because you
know
um
different times girls busy girls tired
this and that but I still got some time
for you we can go to my room follow me
follow me
it was fun yeah playing together is fun
more challenging or but also at the same
time more easy
it's interesting wait a second
where am I where am I
or am I
here am I look at my tools by the way I
didn't I didn't talk about it I didn't
mention it because you know four people
in the Discord I feel like uh cannot
talk about kilo things but look blue
made me some assets I guess right now
they kind of look like they're like not
really on my body you kind of look at it
like this hahaha
but look cute it's a golden chicken ball
with like the red ruby gem eyes
and a fancy stick and the the headpiece
you know Melisandre has this on her neck
but I haven't done my forehead because
the Sorceress has always something on
your forehead right yeah thank you blue
for making it thank you
okay let me fix the chat why will you
not appear you little [\h__\h]
there we go
let me close the game
[Music]
exit
there we go
[Music]
I'm glad you stayed with us yeah I don't
know it's been short and I couldn't read
super chats yesterday either so uh and
tomorrow is the Monday off so why not
read a little bit today normally
normally you know after collabs I don't
do it but this time I think we can do it
um
what
did they announce Nintendo the right for
a [\h__\h] hell but it's tomorrow okay
um
I want to kind of do a lot along what
time is it for me I just heard a rumor
you know that it will be this week but
the day just announced today that
they're doing it tomorrow oh it's the
last minute
ah
4 P.M for me
that's a good time Nintendo directs are
always at a good time for me why
4pm isn't even
such a good time in Japan that's like 10
p.m or so 11 P.M
that's pretty late for Japan considering
that Nintendo is in Japan
why is it always so good for me
America is morning time I guess
um
[Music]
you can do a subject reading after that
possible stream you mean the Nintendo
Direct now if I stream on my day off on
my one
they uh
it's kind of two on my one day off uh
I've it's been a while because I
streamed over the weekend I streamed
yesterday I swim today but if I stream
tomorrow then it's gotta be short I'm
gonna cut it immediately after the 40
minutes but I do want to do a watch
alone
I feel very tempted hasn't been a while
since the last Nintendo Direct
so what
is that chance to announce the Pokemon
game or is it too early
and Pokemon game for like winter time
because they do one like every year
right
would they do a Pokemon Direct for that
I don't know too early
maybe a DLC
info
um
too early what will they it better be
worth it
I better be worth it no day off when kfp
um
Pikmin 4 but hasn't picked one four
being announced Metroid
they must announce at least one
completely new thing right that people
didn't hear before that's the unwritten
rule right
that otherwise they wouldn't do a
Nintendo Direct would they
you would think
okay
[Music]
Star Fox
I don't know if they will do that
okay what BTM do I have
um
here questionable super chats bgm
oh you don't hear it
I like this one
down down there we go
[Music]
I have to record something after the
stream
um that has deadline today
but besides that oh I recorded
um the song cover that I want to upload
on Sunday I recorded yesterday and the
mixing is almost done so Sunday is
looking pretty safe right now just
letting you know
Sunday will be a song cover
Ed
yeah kind of pretty quick mixer and it's
pretty simple
song so yeah
[Music]
um oh and I had a meeting about
my
album slash EP today earlier today
that's going well too
um
discussing things this and that
how did it go went well
very well but there's many things to be
taken into consideration when making
something like that
[Music]
oh yeah I I tweeted something about an
emotori song
yeah well you know I want I want a lot
of variety in my
in the album I mean as much as I can
with the amount of songs
you will see you will see
for me I feel like there's a
for if you liked
any of my previous songs then there will
be something for you
in the album too
I think
[Music]
and unravel type screen uh you will have
to listen to it when it releases I
suppose
get me for blood on the EP I was legit
considering asking but I assume I would
have to buy the rights to it and all
that
so
so now
unleash the screamo smile rabbit scream
was good right I was surprised myself I
was just like I think it was so good
because I gave no [\h__\h]
in that moment I was just having fun
with Mama
and I don't know I was just messing
around I was jumping around I didn't
even sing properly because I had no no
stamina I was just jumping and laughing
and then the arrival scream came
sang my song yeah yeah
similar to Four Blood would also be
great similar to four blood
no I don't think there's anything
similar to Four Blood right now
[Music]
five blood
anyway
uh I'll keep the rest of my tangents for
the next
longest dream
um but yeah yesterday I had two
two collabos did you guys see they were
both not on my channel
so in case you missed it I had one
collab on IMS artist Mommy
uh um
on her Channel because I was teaching
her German because she's coming to
Germany to docomi
um
I wish I could show her around
but I can't you know because I won't be
there and then yeah I was on Nina Sanji
channel
uh again playing in the same group as
last time
how did that collab happen did you you
know you knew her already
he dm'd me on Twitter
and I mean I was following her I follow
I think most of the artists mamas
and she told me she was going to Germany
and asked me if I want to collab with
her teach her some German I was like of
course
oh that sounds fun more mommies more
mommies in my bag
all the mommies
next day
I have a connection with her already
it's a special connection that she
doesn't have with her own daughter
because she's like a huge fan of hello
project the idol agency and I'm not
really following them now but I used to
be really seriously into
the agency's groups back in the day so I
know what she's talking about when she
talks about it
[Music]
HP otaku outfit by a lot oh but I don't
think I can
um
get a
[Music]
uh other mammals
to work from from me like that it's
normally not really you know
[Music]
because they're they're already
someone's Mommy so I can't steal them
[Music]
um
oh anyway you know how I
okay next maybe not GTA next maybe I
take more time with GTA because
[Music]
uh um
maybe Final Fantasy 16 next
it's
[Music]
I could not believe my eyes yeah
and what I saw today
um
expect
Ian's to play F of 16.
yeah I I I
I'm about to end to otk and I'm about to
go on a little trip to Japan
so not immediately unfortunately but
probably that's better that way anyway
um we'll play in July
we'll start in July you don't want to
get spoiled then go get started now play
now it'll be my first ever
Final Fantasy
um besides the Evermore pretty which
doesn't count in my opinion
no not the MMO
[Music]
I guess I'll play on PS5 I suppose
but they said there's a chihuahua in
there right there's a phoenix right
right right people who kept on telling
me I saw it I think in the trailer
oh it's exclusive okay no problem I have
a PS5 hey
[Music]
but yeah um I was very surprised but
very grateful I were able to play it
um
for now it's this game only though it
seems like it
no need to brag
about my PS5 no I don't have five feet
so I only have one PS5 yeah I stream the
rise
did I wait no no I didn't I played on
PS4 right the whole time because the PS5
arrived too late so I started on PS4
right right right
I Sprint something from my PS5 before
something else
it was so weird because Bandai and uncle
gave me the PS5
uh in the hopes that I would um use it
to stream because of a rise
freaking chats
but then I couldn't because it arrived
too late and I already wanted to start
because it will run so yeah straight was
PS5
[Music]
well now now we'll use it to uh
stream a game from a rival company I
don't know how does um I was thinking
actually the other day it's like Bandai
Namco and Square Enix and all these
companies do they like see each other
officially as like rivals or as friends
I wonder
[Music]
finally fixed her fax machine
we don't use facts though
thank God
[Music]
oh they do have collapse Ryan I think so
too
um
just wondering if it's like you know
like with idle companies like hello
project and and it could be 48
it could be if they like like that you
know
[Music]
well well so you'll have to wait a
little bit but that's good for anybody
who wants to play ff16 get going get
started because
yeah why I will pick it up because I was
waiting before long time to get the
chance to play an F of game on stream
wait the game is not out yet
oh
I'm planning this out already
wait when is it coming out two days oh
that's so soon
Friday Friday
but no worries I I won't play it for a
while
[Music]
huh
what
[Music]
Channel sent me a cryptic message
today
[Music]
did I request
what
[Music]
which GTA will you play after that well
the poll that I did for Members Only
uh San Andreas was winning so I'll
probably go with that second was GTA 4.
no I didn't get bonked no no no nothing
nothing I just didn't understand what
she meant
yeah I've seen I've seen some people say
that GTA 4 would be like
um maybe I don't know better as a
streaming game or easier for me to play
or so on
and and most people are just voting San
Andreas because it's like I guess iconic
and and memorable and all that
but it is difficult
um
classic was pretty alternative four
would be better yeah see and I really
under as a streamer I appreciate that
feedback and that reasoning and thus I
am
still open to considering
playing GTA 4 over San Andreas
okay a lot of people agree with that too
yeah a scuffed gameplay
thank you
they're both on sale whoa
basically a rage game
that works best for your boss thank you
probably better in that case YouTube
[Music]
thankfully stories aren't tied yeah
yeah no I know mixed reception so
discount
well I don't know it will still be fun
right either either way it will be fun
but possibly GTA 4 would be less ranged
inducing
[Music]
I don't know I just miss playing GTA 5
and I'm just fine let's playing
something that has the vibe of GTA 5
which I suppose all GTA games have so
[Music]
would be more more my style would be
familiar to you more okay but then I
kind of prefer that you know
for now for now
but I wonder if we can play
uh I think I can have two Series going
on at once
can play GTA for
with ff16 on the side so then we also
have like you know variation
[Music]
I mean there's seven days in the week
I could
yeah I could
[Music]
but we have to finish tootk first
I would say well now now I have a good
reason to not stall anymore
now there's something that's pushing me
um
and the thing is even if I wanted to
play ff16 right away I can't I'm going
to Japan I'm like really busy
[Music]
really busy I I you know for newly
releasing games
it hurts me to not play it on the day of
release
because that's when the hype is the
biggest I have to think like a streamer
you know
but I uh wait two days today is Tuesday
I could
probably switch something out but I have
to ask a little bit in advance too
so I I could probably
do episode 16 maybe on Saturday for
example but even that I don't know
yeah I don't know I'll just no I'll just
I'll wait I'll wait I'll wait
wait
you really seem to care about the hype
and the metal streamer tactics yeah
that's true but I mean you know it's a
game I want to play anyway so might as
well play on release date but one of
your Minecraft plans my Minecraft plans
are um there's a new biome so I'm gonna
go find it on the end server
and and farm it
Farm the materials and if it's really
far
then maybe I'll try to create a rail to
the biome
[Music]
I saw already I couldn't resist I
already saw like some clip of Mikko Sam
by finding the the cherry blossom by Omi
and so I saw a lot of um the items and
so on already
[Music]
and it looks so nice
but here's my schedule there's some
mistakes there but we're already past
that point
um yeah so I have a day off in Minecraft
by only exploration new animals too oh I
did not see I think I heard of one but
I'm always excited when there's new
biomies because I you know I love
Explorer exploring the most
for members only I was thinking watching
a movie because I'm stressed out and we
already played the game last time
oh yeah I guess tomorrow yeah Nintendo
Direct I will
probably do a really short stream yeah
it's my plan
I have a hair appointment tomorrow
actually right I booked myself a hair
appointment it's pretty early actually
I could be I probably would be finished
before
but I'm not 100 sure
oh my God girl get your hair done that's
right like I'm I didn't want to go to
Japan and show my senpai's my ugly ass
Roots you can't see it right now but
I've got some really ugly ass Roots yeah
disgusting
I'm getting my hair done yeah
[Music]
so okay I'll see how the appointment
goes because I honestly don't know
uh
what exactly
I want to get done what I wanted to look
like tomorrow I'll just ask the
hairdresser what she thinks she can do
and what will work and then she can give
me a time estimate and then I can update
you guys if I'm doing uh uh Nintendo
watch along or not
um
while I'm still there just take the day
off I can tweet you
hmm I don't know I don't know I'll think
about it I'll think about it
[Music]
yeah
I'll think about it
depends maybe maybe if there's like 20
home life members who are doing a watch
along
then I won't do it
[Music]
um yeah remember it's only movie I'm not
100 sure yet just wait please
we can talk about it on Minecraft day
and then yeah sell a tltk that stream
I kind of still want to not finish the
game
I could but
I don't I don't want to force myself to
finish it yet because there's still so
much to do so we'll just be um doing
side things you know extra stuff yeah
and then
[Music]
um
then
then soon soon we'll finish it yeah
[Music]
little chicken is having the keyboard
have it yes
[Music]
yeah I will
um yeah maybe like a little bit of story
like one hour of story Maybe
so that next time
we won't be too stressed
but I don't want to go too far
you guys gotta tell me
like don't go too far otherwise you
don't have enough story for next time
because next time we'll do a story
focused stream unended okay
that you guys have to help me balance it
um
also
ah
she won't hear this I'm sure but let's
say happy birthday
just accidentally opened Clips Studio
paint no
[Music]
good one
thank you
[Music]
happy birthday
just like your shoes
[Music]
happy birthday
to you
she like the salmon
[Music]
and she like her gently rice
[Applause]
[Music]
happy birthday to you
that sweet angel voice
and that's funny humor
you are the best
happy birthday to you hey
my birthday is
[Laughter]
congratulations
[Music]
it's the guba birthday and after Cuba
birthday
is our birthday
let's go
yeah
Wawa birthday is soon no Collins oh yeah
I asked her
because I wanted to like uh be awake in
case she does
Collins she said no not this time
so but she oh she put up her frame okay
okay I wonder what she'll be doing
I do not know
that's fair yeah don't have to do it all
the time every time for each
special occasion yeah frame frame I
don't know I say frame like
I think it's like because in Japanese
they say waku
it's like a I saw people say it in
English to the
um
in Japanese they say they opened a Baku
which is like actually also a word for
a picture frame yeah
and then you know for me it's like
somehow entered my brain wow open the
frame or stream reservation frame is
shorter than the stream reservation you
know
[Music]
why won't you weren't you being a Fatal
Frame wait for Halloween 2023 okay
Fatal Frame can only be played during
Halloween time don't you know
no
you play Lord of the Rings Magic the
Gathering cool
that sounds fun you mean IRL you played
at IRL right
[Music]
I'm gonna turn down the bgm number
it's the rules I don't write the rules I
just follow them
okay I've been reading this
oh where where where where am I
where
am I
where am I
okay
[Music]
Zelda which Zelda
let me see what looks familiar to me
[Music]
uh oh yeah the Minecraft ones I've
finished
okay so it's
um
part 7 of Zelda
[Music]
uh
foreign
this one
[Music]
foreign
music's starting who's
birthday is it
Let's Go Happy Birthday to someone it
must be someone in the chat every day
it's someone's birthday that was
probably someone's birthday
it must be a chicken
who is quite the cutest
no someone there has birthdays it must
be you I know it happy birthday happy
birthday to that one chicken happy
birthday to that one chicken
congratulations
[Music]
you worked so hard
for me every day
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday to you you're older now
happy birthday happy birthday
[Music]
if you want
I'll just this one
give you a kiss on your head
[Music]
you want you want
okay come here
continue
[Music]
so whose birthday was it let's get this
out of my VLC playlist I don't want to
sing any more birthday songs
I
wish my normal birthday songs
mine really
it's always someone's birthday yeah
someone Jimmy's
maybe maybe it was the the valve's
birthday but guys the valve is not a
check I know I know it looks like
chicken but no no no no no no no
you guys reactions were so cute
but one thing I don't understand you
guys were like if if not friends then
why French shaved that was obviously not
friend-shaped it was just friend colored
pink chickens think
[Music]
well that was so cute it made my day
um
oh guys
so I'm going to Japan right
now I'm kind of like
thinking I don't have much time
during this trip as it's a short trip
so don't expect like
streams or collabs every day
but I'd like to do at least two of
collabs
[Music]
um
I just don't really have an idea but
like you know when we were talking about
it during Diablo I was wondering
actually that might be a good off collab
idea playing Jenga and Mikado so
I just wonder about if I need to really
get permissions for that
um and then
I think I have uh I wanted to I think an
off collab unarchived karaoke with a
certain person
an archive because I feel like I'm kind
of sick of the songs that we can sing
[Music]
during our craft and I did that before
anyway recently
so yeah but then the other thing
um I'll even do it maybe even with the
same person but I feel like I should try
to
go out of my way and
meet someone new
who have I not of collab with her with
yet um
a lot of
a lot of 6th gen
[Music]
who should I
I know I know I was thinking about pick
one up but I'm like
I feel like if I go to pekora and ask
for collab I need to come up with a
really good idea
honestly wait the idea with Jenga and
Mikado and all those games kind of fits
because she a baby she a baby and we
play baby game
it kind of fits
let me ask
[Music]
do you think I need to get
special
purpose for
game like Jenga
please say no please say no
please say no
yeah I think she has high expectations
and you know if if I I want to ask her
but if I do I already have to have a
good idea in my mind I think
but don't worry I already know when I'm
going to Japan next
after this upcoming trip
and it's a ridiculously soon after
it's actually ridiculous
just for a really really like for for
thing for one day I have to do something
for one day
[Music]
and I'll be back probably
you know after this first trip
I'll be home maybe for two weeks or so
I haven't haven't gotten a flight ticket
or anything yet so I don't know exactly
I'll be back for two weeks
then go to Japan to do one thing
reply back because that's like just
ridiculous so maybe I'll stay for I
don't know three four nights Maybe
and then I fly back
and then then I fly to with rmt to the
UK
yeah
[Music]
and then I think
foreign
[Music]
but all the trips are really short I'm
keeping them short
they didn't do a normal one they cooked
they cooked
that was
that was an idea and they have a lot of
history a lot of collabs and all that
together I kind of don't have that much
of a natural
just stable connection with her you know
so I feel like it's more difficult for
me to
ask it's okay it's okay it's okay
it's okay
um
I actually kind of like the idea of
playing Django of Laplace
I like the idea
[Music]
you guys think Hasbro will be a bro to
me
and and give me perms
Hasbro but yeah bro
it would have to be pretty fast though
this is Mikado also from Hasbro what's
what's Mikado from
Google
[Music]
um
is perfect from Hasbro right but Mikado
I think a lot of companies make Mikado
no
[Music]
um
it doesn't doesn't say it belongs to
something specific oh
and even if it does
a ton of wooden chopsticks
paint some colors on it
and use that
okay wait
[Music]
Mikado's a pickup six game originating
in Europe see so this I was I was
thinking it's it's from us
what did you know Mikado was originally
called Morocco
yeah and it's our European Pocky brand
yeah I love mommycano so much more
[Music]
I'm young
playing with a set of same length sticks
which can measure between 17 and 20
centimeters in 1956 it was brought from
Hungary to the United States and named
Pickup Sticks what a shitty name
this term is not very specific in
respect to existing stick game oh
hey that's two things uh traditional
game doesn't need it probably
may have been avoided because it was a
brand name of a game producer the game
is named for the highest scoring
the game is named for the highest
scoring stick Mikado emperor of Japan
I don't understand this sentence
rules see I forgot the rules okay there
are points yes there are points
41 sticks coated with different values
that have a total of 170 points and are
around 15 centimeters long
they're bundled and taken in one hand is
there anyone who doesn't know this game
that touches the table and work round
the release creates a circular jumble
now the players take turns in which one
stick after another should be taken up
without moving or touching on this it's
basically like Django the takeaway could
be by hand possibly through pressing on
the sticks tip or if one has already I
don't mean really
heard of it though never heard about it
never actually created one
picked up a special oh wait if one has
already picked up a special stick the
Mikado stick
[Music]
or the Mandarin stick it could be used
as a helper ah oh yeah oh yeah I
remember this somehow
there's certain sticks that can help you
pick up other sticks you can like push
them away flip them
um
yeah when somebody does a mistake the
turn ends
and the last taken stick is not counted
the next player bundles and drops the
sticks again oh I thought you just leave
them the way they are
after several Ransom only five the one
with the highest score
the total of the values of the six
picked up is the winner
a player is allowed to stand up but not
leave their own place a bad throw could
be rerun and the rules should be kept
strict in respect to moving sticks to
enjoy the game
oh
okay okay
wait so
um
wait wait wait wait do you guys know if
Labrador ever did a hand cam stream
because I feel like some members are
maybe kind of objected to it but if
someone's done it before
and she would probably do it again
[Music]
um
don't know
Plus
where's my Plus on this keyboard
LaPlace
um
what do I look for
what channel verse shadow box
ah unboxing unboxing
I can't find it now but if you guys say
she did it then
good
[Music]
you could also fingerprint now that's
not possible because we need to wear
gloves
[Music]
can you guys think of another game like
Mikado that's like not really that's
like traditional not really belongs to
one specific company
that we could also play
additionally
Maybe
chess
nah
wait that's kind of fun
[Laughter]
oh
true
[Music]
I like that idea
I like that yeah maybe maybe Mikado and
and dominoes and if I can get perms in
time then uh Jenga
[Music]
wait a second
is this just me I feel like
Louis has a short up where she plays
Jenga with the whole X logo on it so
maybe if I find unbranded Jenga blocks I
think Jenna is listening to the stream
right now so maybe maybe
maybe if I find unbranded Jenga Vlog
cycling
or or if I just cover whatever logo is
on it
the stickers
so you don't know
where it's from
because more than one company makes
Jenga do they I don't know do they maybe
they just call it something else
Google
Jenga is a game of physical skill
created by British board game designer
marketed by a Hasbro
of brand Jenga yeah I think that could
work there's like off-brand Uno too
right like so there's off brand for
every game
[Music]
okay I think I think we can figure
something out
for a stream like this
hey off collab
little games with hands
[Music]
oh
that's one
[Music]
that has no logos
maybe I can find one on Amazon
off brand wait I have tummy horde
[Music]
I have Tommy Hornets
um
[Music]
one more goal
one more goal why I'm gonna be right
back
you chickens have a conversation with
yourselves
[Music]
foreign
thank you
okay
[Music]
surprise
what do you mean Union meetings there
are no Union meetings in Japan in kfp
hi
I I need to move the fan somewhere else
yeah I'm okay
I'm okay
[Music]
now there is one no there cannot be
okay guys it's time for super chats
for real for real Pepsi language
don't be shook when you don't see my
membership Mark you have to place me in
the usual room I found out why I never
received any membership gifts in any
channels what turns out my YouTube is on
the brand account even though it is
under the same Gmail I use when I
transferred it to my Google content took
away my ability to use membership emojis
to [\h__\h] next I found uh all the
memberships that I paid till this month
month to be expired at many different
dates that's way earlier I reached out
to Google for help and they're
investigating the matter FBI the
transfer function is an official
function in Google underbrand accounts
by the way a heads up of what might
happen for anyone that might want to
attempt this too
oh oh I feel like a lost soul in the
empty YouTube void now what
even carefusion of them have a screen of
kiwama on it she cannot fight
I don't feel so good it's okay no Mike
where are you where are you where are
you
where are you
see they're emoting for you
a remote thing for you
but there you are you're out let's go
so wait back to normal or what
you can use emote
of chicken on fire
no problemo
freedom freedom
that was short
I mean
a little trip to the usual room doesn't
hurt no one okay
okay already resolved
and hold on I'm happy thank you for the
super tattoos
now praise and love to you boss for your
contribution to connect the world up
thank you
two weeks now seemed like such a long
time until it will finally be performed
on stage a minor detail I really loved
about the MB is seeing you being paired
up with the moon yeah
um actually
think originally I was paired up with
someone else I think
but um so my line was I think in the
first verse
I think but I asked if I could change it
just because
um
not because of the person I was uh
paired up with I don't even remember who
it was
but because I wanted to sing a different
line just like different Melody
um
the other upside was that I could sing
with Mommy together I guess again
yeah
[Music]
it's just a coincidence though really I
mean I think it was it was definitely on
purpose that they tried to pair up
always like a myth with a council risk
member
that was on purpose
in case you haven't noticed have you
guys noticed
there's always like first myth member
then councilors then they sing together
then miss member then counselors stand
they sing together then the chorus then
myth member then counselors then they
sing together Etc
um
that was on purpose yeah some of you
guys didn't notice
it it was uh on purpose
because they wanted to you know do a
tattoo thing
yeah I mean of course you don't have to
pay that much attention while listening
you can just listen with brain empty
mode yeah yeah no problem
the more you know I should sing it alone
sometime
hmm I wonder if I could sing it alone
but I do I know it when I when I tried
singing uh bright party though
I thought I could and then turns out I I
wasn't quite able to after all is there
an official instrumental on YouTube
uh connect the world
[Music]
yes
oh my God
well we have to test it out now
lyrics please
Google
I don't have stress to finish my Super
Chat reading today guys it was a short
stream and um
[Music]
connect the world
lyrics
oh that's a different song here I love
English
I think I can do it
let's try
I [\h__\h] yeah this song starts right from
the get-go I hate it when songs do this
this thing
um
[Music]
let's go live preaching the distance
across the sea endlessly you don't hear
the music
[Laughter]
Wow Let's Go Again
tell me if it's off Rhythm
brand new style meeting
[Music]
meetings
ah
[Music]
um waking from my dreams swept up into
the stream I make a wish and wait for my
cue how will we connect in this new
frontier we're turning through frapping
in the scene where no one's ever been
with vibrant colors bursting like stars
[Music]
each new debut brings America to life
Charlene we've gotta take that chance
that's right
right now we're ready to change the game
let's see my ringtone case creating a
new place where we can shine day by day
five coming stories
get ready to cross the waste
let's go live
follow me
[Music]
a way to clear each towering trial
sharing all our hopes we can conquer
anything
we'll link our hearts and research
across the globe knowing no matter where
we are no matter how
we can besides
[Music]
share our futures that we can see making
them reality take my hand and reach for
the screen all we need are glittering
dreams our hearts and souls all
fulfilled in the world
we're ready to seize the day traversing
the pathways
to everywhere step by step Gathering
stories
[Music]
joyfully follow me
we'll carry on starting now
[Music]
oh
yeah oh
that's so fun that's so fun oh my God
it's so high bye let's go
I love that ending part and the of
course the shiniest one is that story
reference with the ending
[Music]
I love that
can't wait to see live right
um I've heard if you guys are going to
the concert and you want to be you know
not just standing there not knowing what
to do I've heard fans created a fan
chant but
[Music]
um
should I show you how I would naturally
how I would probably
um do it
I haven't tried it before but
I think it comes pretty naturally
I'm gonna give it a try
okay
I'll see what I can do but but feel free
to take the Phantom as a reference they
probably whatever I do they probably
would do it very similar
let me try we're ready to agree during
this phase oh I wish I had hands right
now during this phase you know what you
do in the very beginning before the big
uh you know the big
Rhythm and instrumental start
ketchup a move called ketcha where you
you can either clap or do it without the
clap but you reach your hand slowly
towards the front I don't know how to
explain ketchup
what's the better way to it's like
you're you're twirling your hand inwards
and extending your arms uh towards the
front and when you do that the twirl of
your hands and and they're like pointing
forward you know what I mean
all right I guess it would be maybe also
carrying light sticks so don't think too
much about the hands but just basically
um yeah hand close arms close to body
and then with the Rhythm
you go I've done it probably in my egg
otage moves before in my egg yeah yeah
and Guiana did it before pretty sure
I'm a visual learner
um
[Music]
so maybe a video then
um
oh I love that one
good idea
um
maybe this one shows it
I wonder if I could do like really
quickly
with like mokopi or something like that
because I'm getting Moco P2
um do like a little bit scarf like not
100 best quality 3D but before the
concert I might be able to do
a quick
um
okay so for the movement for whatever
for now I guess forget it but we start
with ketchup
ketchup ketchup
but you can also go
you're ready
[Music]
a slower ketchup and then here we go
take the light stick I guess
[Music]
hey hey
here we're trying Iris maybe like that
[Music]
man
that one's difficult
when when
[Music]
that Rhythm should be afterwards but I
don't know where else to put kaijan
[Music]
sometimes even in Idol songs you you
skip some parts and don't say anything
because it doesn't fit but you could you
could do
[Music]
or or you could do
that works
okay
[Music]
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi
hello
[Music]
Iris
you do a similar movement like with the
ketchup when you do that
[Music]
oh yeah okay we can continue here with
Amazon
yeah
um
[Applause]
you just gotta remember who sings you
know
and here
you could just either clap but I mean
your hands are probably carrying them
into the intertwines the light sticks so
just I guess just shake them and if you
have no light sticks you just clap clap
clap
if you can you know we have a lot of
yays in the background so
[Music]
where are they
all day one day oh yay that was the day
yay here I think it's always after the
day by day step by step yay there's
always a yay there Panini you already
know what to do yeah
[Music]
there we go
we're going again
three two one yay there we go
[Music]
and Now instrumental
um
that's too short I don't think we can
hi hi nah nah don't worry about it too
short
[Music]
ah wait this one's like the Kelly one
this this one's the same as the county
one because it's too long
[Music]
time
maybe just normal clap
[Music]
s
you mean do you mean
[Music]
and not every part in content I agree
because like a lot of beginners begin
the utakusa there
okay if you want to do it you can but no
no Force
[Music]
maybe double clap
[Applause]
back
that's nice too
[Music]
kind of ends quickly back to shaking yay
oh clap clap clap whichever you want
[Music]
yay
where I would do a ketchup
[Music]
wow you don't have to do the clap but it
makes you catch up too much more
Exquisite and divine
[Music]
yeah
maybe that's how I might do it yeah
I think that's um like a lot of it it
may sound in the beginning like oh my
God she's doing so much but
honestly a lot of us just like listening
to the Rhythm and doing like it
accordingly it's just very normally very
you know when you hear an instrumental
like this uh
like this and uh it's very it just comes
natural you know I think you can if
anything you can at least do this one
oh it's intuitive yeah whenever you hear
an instrumental like that where no one's
singing you just go but if it's like a
really calm one you do like slow ketchup
move where you you're trying to reach
the artist on stage you know
some people will even turn around
and and bend their whole bag and head
backwards and do the catch up backwards
sometimes I would do that too
but if you want if you guys are up with
some of the Holo fans or the Halloween
fans who go there up for learning it I
could
probably find some time to do a quick
mocha Bean
video the shaft tattoo yeah yeah I kind
of like that
yeah there's a lot of funny ways to do
ketchup yeah it comes natural right
foreign
[Music]
okay I think you know actually a while
ago I already like talked to staff like
oh
I want to
do like a guide video like that
um and they were like totally for it but
you know time passed so much and and we
just we just couldn't do it do we need a
towel for connect I mean
you don't need it you can implement it
for example you could during the course
um Twisted Twilight like you do with
high Challenger
you could
but you guys are just asking it because
it was so much fun and hard challenge
all right I know it was you only have a
towel oh you don't have a light stick
and you're going to the concert
I mean you don't have to have the
official light stick you know that right
you can easily buy a cheap one
um even the like like a king blade-ish
kind of light stick or or the ones that
you break
and then they light up for a while
are you doing it from home well then
then all of this doesn't matter so much
but yeah
um
oh
yeah if you didn't manage to get a
a Leicester from the merchandise you can
just get a different one I
uh when I used to go to Iowa concerts
having their own like light stick wasn't
the thing yet at least not for J-pop
Idols so everybody just had some random
King blade or the ones that you break
the throwaway ones
eh
I don't think you can bring unofficial
light stick no way
no way do they really say that
yeah
I saw it ax they're gonna be selling
some extra merchandise that's another
another
um uh chance but I don't think
I mean maybe I'm wrong but that's the
first time I ever heard of such a thing
um
yeah I don't don't believe that that
might be a one guy thing
I haven't heard about that
I don't know
ah no go ahead use your gen free
anniversary concert last year go ahead
please do I think it's cool actually
because like you can
um what I would do at idle concerts back
in the day I would wear
um like merchandise like birthday uh
T-shirts from my Oshi from like five
years ago
to flex that I have an old t-shirt
to flex said hey I've been around for
this long you know
you can Flex with this kind of stuff
yeah
but let me
let me ask
[Music]
um
okay I asked
management if they want to do it
um it'll be a little bit last minute but
we can make it happen
oh I haven't done all thank you since
I'm at the concert you're scared no why
are you scared it's so much [\h__\h] fun
I wish I was in the audience I would go
crazy
Tom is just that besides connect the
world you don't know what's gonna be
performed right so good luck with that
unfortunately I cannot tell you
I can't tell you anything else
sadly so you will just have to
do your thing you can Vibe however you
want and maybe you can take some
inspiration from connect the world you
know learn some things you learn from
there you can maybe apply to other
songs just one thing whenever you hear
an instrumental that's going hard and uh
there's no one singing just go oh yeah
you know please
that's that's the one thing you can
always do in every song
yeah
please do it it will it will like it
will be so much fun and it will be so
hype it will it will it will create so
much so much wow fun atmosphere in the
in the in the concert hall
um oh yeah I I between the light stick
thing too so if you want to do even more
fun things participate in the light
stick project you know
um
we're gonna make sense where I respond
to exist just in case yeah that's that's
what I did for my original songs before
um
so yeah maybe um watch those again
can you hear the audience on the concert
I think so
guys are loud enough
yeah
you just gotta be loud
okay back to Super chats questionable
super chats
[Music]
oh do you chant there is one I think but
I haven't done it on my channel yet yeah
[Music]
yeah because
they are
time limited or you mean because of the
reasons we'll get you kicked if you
bring kuchaku yeah yeah don't don't go
crazy on like making a freaking fan out
of light sticks some people do that
that might be what they mean with
you know
no modified
light six or whatever
it's as beautiful as they are and as fun
as they are
[Music]
okay sorry
um I'm disgusting
no torches no no no no no no no no I
will use uh yeah
no no no no don't don't glue them all
together and make weird builds like in
Zelda 30k freaking qtk brain rocks
okay okay
Flappy boy
it was you it was you who sent me on a
one hour tangent you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
I even sang because of you
Flappy boy where are you at you little
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God now it's your fault it's your
fault yeah
[Music]
tangent record
about that might have gone longer before
you take no responsibility you should
you 100 should you you knew I was gonna
tangent when you sent this super chat
um
you knew it you felt it
come on you know me too good too well
you should know it
so here's a kiss
[Music]
on the beautiful pink stickers
for the pinky all the main Channel
content this week was great I love the
Paul review video that was hilarious and
the new Envy yeah last week there was a
lot of uh stuff going on in terms of
main Channel content
um
I'm glad you guys enjoyed it thank you
very much
[Music]
for the support and thank you for
watching it even when it's not on my own
channel always keep an eye out open or
two eyes open
to see where is Wawa when not on her own
channel you know
[Music]
um
concert song was beautiful it's nice to
see you all together alas also
congratulations on good small supporting
the concert good smile also was recently
announced to be a sponsor
same thing yeah
[Music]
thank you very much
many many sponsors but kfp no sponsor
no no no no no no no no no no no kfp
we're gonna keep our money to ourselves
is that how sponsors work normally
sponsors give the people they sponsor
money right
KFC keeps their own money by keeping it
in a way we're sponsoring in a way yeah
yeah we are I guess a lot of kfp bought
tickets so we're not sponsoring it to
summer
so can they put up the kfp logo on the
sponsor
foreign
this concert is sponsored by these
sponsors that you see on the screen
thank you
but not Chrono Banger me
do I sound like crony right now I don't
know
[Music]
it's one you always
and then the animes
that's what it means yeah yeah
[Music]
this anime is sponsored by these
sponsors
um
[Music]
yeah that was the one we were talking
about chickens a lot yeah yeah you you
you want to know more uh uh Google is
your friend Uncle Google go to Uncle
Google Uncle Google is also chicken
Uncle Google knows it all
Landsberg function
and I came on
no one's bag
okay
what's up thanks for the pinky
kong candy corn wow
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
wasn't it the English last time now
we're Japanese
there
Nintendo
room
go to usual room
[Music]
you must calm down
foreign
wasn't in Japanese last time too really
oh God
you like the PGM really I got it from
audio stuff
memory Pittman's Duncanville weasel
thank you
sure
blood donation poster boys
hi
oh
one of the organizers of the Holy and
light pen light project we have many
talented kfb members on the team they
predicted you would find out immediately
just like to say thanks for the support
you're welcome
welcome
yeah I'm glad I can help
I am all in what it's about making the
concert more fun so
yeah I hope it succeeds both this and a
little bit of fan chanting even if it's
not perfect would be nice to have some
[Music]
um
and
mk59
thanks for two pinkies
I've been running out of new things to
say but I want to say thanks for again
for all you do we're almost at three
years now and wherever it's live gang or
vodking your streams still help keep a
smile on my face on rap days what better
way to cheer up than watching a cute
bird girl sing or stream a game she
likes playing or a hand spreading
infectious Joy with her reactions random
tangents and jokes
hope we'll have fun for a long time I
hope so too well one more where did this
come from though so so suddenly we're
not even at three years yet but yeah
we're getting very close to it
yeah
damn we're at the end of now almost end
of June
no just random fun thank you very much
thank you
well you'll have to think of some more
things to say when it's actual
anniversary then and my birthday
yeah damn three years is so long like
for a V2 but I feel like it's so long
because like the industry hasn't been
around for that long
so
huge
huge long time frame
yeah even I mean okay there were some
early ones but but then back then I know
YouTuber retubing was not such a big
thing yet
it was like he's in the eye
[Music]
slowly it was slowly
evolving
[Music]
and then you know
I feel like you know it really didn't
get really started
until like a little bit later on
[Music]
only a handful of big EnV to his older
than new girls
yeah oh
we're definitely one of the oldest ones
I don't even know who was really like
the tubing not just with a picture but
like with an actual
YouTube YouTuber Avatar before us in
English
I don't even know
I remember I was already doing it
[Music]
oh I mean okay yeah okay there were a
few surely
yeah yeah but we came very very soon
very in the beginning
[Music]
who was the first en
YouTuber really that that would be
and we need proof we need proof though
can't just worry about names there
[Music]
not annoying orange no no no that's such
a stretch We're Not Gonna as much as I
love The Annoying Orange We're not gonna
give them that title
of the first ever
YouTuber English speaking YouTuber no um
it takes the boxes now it doesn't
no no no
[Music]
thank you Jake
knows
an Unwritten words
for the pinky you heard the lady also
this whole have Just Dance perms
I would love to see you Nene and Whip
too less than a month before I'm Pride
let's go uh I don't know do we I don't
think so because of all the copyrighted
songs right
um although I don't know
[Music]
I would like to do it though if we could
Watch Me Whip
and wants me in yeah
once we watch me
[Music]
this is a Momo
foreign
[Music]
it's really difficult
[Laughter]
I don't normally go by her yeah
I don't normally call her by her last
name hmm
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
but that's the whole thing like it was
this is the whole thing you know it's
like a an enemy to get her last name
wrong
yes
yes Mama
oh random shambles
yeah
I don't know it's so confusing I can't
help it
no this is the mama no Suzanne yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
I would laugh so hard oh man
I got nasty or Nasi Taka
I I would appreciate it because that's
so funny
laughs
no why not Akira
recently I feel some head pain and I
feel like I'm transforming into Akira so
if you're gonna switch around those
Katakana you might as well turn it into
Akira
[Music]
we need some bunks in the chat
let me switch out of hyper chat
[Music]
um mm-hmm
bad chicken
[Music]
did I miss someone
I think we're good for now
I have an eye on you I have an eye on
your chickens
I got you
on my radar
[Music]
okay
little thanks for two wonderful years I
will be one of your chickens as long as
you are our Phoenix yay congratulations
on your Revival that means two years
right damn
that is long time thank you for being
here for so long and never giving up on
me thank you thank you soon
until three years let's go together hand
in feather
[Music]
revive yet yes you did I see it
wow wow such beautiful chickens man
we have so many
two-year chickens
already
I feel like we probably have more
two-year chickens than
no okay maybe not that's an exaggeration
probably not in total but maybe in the
chat in the chat right now we probably
have more two-year chickens than eggs
and no blank this is not me asking you
to gift more eggs so that we have more
eggs than
then uh
revived to survived chickens just making
an observation no you shouldn't leave no
no no no just just saying that you know
we have many many
chickens who stayed for a long time you
know
well very very loyal
and very lovey-dovey ah Miss fish thank
you
no but I want to say that overall we got
a lot of eggs they might not be here
right now but overall we definitely have
a lot of eggs and thank you even if
you're not revived yet you're getting
there right you're not gonna leave me
before you revive you can't just end it
as a bucket
to reach the final stage
[Music]
stuck in the bucket
you stayed gray for a year oh no well
now you're green all is good ah blank
well husar is coming
I am ocean you guys thank you we're
getting more eggs let's go
thank you I was really just making an
observation though
but once I started the observation I
knew I knew I knew
become a thing many eggs
[Music]
[Laughter]
what did you hear guys did you hear
something that was Discord cutting off I
swear it's eggs eggs and eggs I was just
excitedly saying eggs thank you for the
memberships okay stop now thank you stop
thank you
thank you thank you stop stop stop
thank you stop
I appreciate it thank you
thank you
thank you they're still the chat is
still trying to apply memberships to the
ones that blank gifted
the other ones are not even oh there we
go now now we're reaching it mm-hmm
thank you guys thank you
thank you
wow wow chat is confusing thank you ah
members welcome welcome
to the kfb
welcome
I will try not to drop you hmm I will
try I cannot promise but I'll try not to
trap you
welcome welcome Yokoso
welcome
okay I will read super chess now okay
guys
no promise um
sometimes you drop an egg and there's
not much you can do about it
hmm
[Music]
you're so round and so
so smooth it's kind of I don't know
it's bound to happen
[Music]
thank you guys uh thank you a 30 months
damn pretty pretty
30.
whoa wait are you here since the
beginning
[Music]
12 12 24 plus 6.
two and a half years of membership
[Music]
ah the 42 is the beginning
pretty much the beginning
[Music]
we have the highest bidder of 32
well 29 is pretty good too 29 is pretty
good yeah
[Music]
oh 42. oh my god oh we have a lot of
high bidders
thank you do I hear 40 free no no no
very free okay
get me moves don't don't stick
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
where was that
um Pride School in the camera
spanking time thanks for the recipe
is spoiled we should have eaten her
before
the [\h__\h] spankenheim
what is this treacherous message you
normally not that treacherous
what the [\h__\h]
that was a joke right it was a joke
that was a really bad joke
[Music]
I'm a phoenix you don't eat Phoenix
you should know better
the board gang is like Oh yay long such
a long Diablo collab let's go yeah no
yeah oh we are at four hours in one
minute so
that means
half of the stream is super chats and me
singing and talking
um yeah
so what
[Music]
um
why not keep on opening today
hmm
here we go would you mind saying some
voices like stop go left right without
any video here we go
should I say it very passionately or
just normal
motion
should I turn off my fan is it is it too
much noise
say like a shout but cute okay
is that fan
problem
ah
say I hear it a little bit no okay okay
it's just embarrassing us like
everybody's watching me when I'm in the
studio recording a song
well not so many people normally
um
stop or
stop
no don't use that one
okay
oh
go
and awkward so awkward
left
right
okay
is that good is it good
keep on my GPS
we good we need anything else
I know I know I know
wait I deleted my bgm completely what
the [\h__\h] wait wait where did you go
here you go
it's good because we're waiting to end
[Music]
so you're welcome Leonidas king of
sparta.com
[Music]
foreign
I could quickly read the other ones too
you're not much
to make up for reading so little super
chats and tangent things so much
oh yeah yeah
There You Go
part eight quickly
the first Junction Jacob 47 now
attention blank face for the pinkies
um
[Music]
had a new Champion's tunic made for link
but the great fairies require parts of
Zelda's Dragon to upgrade it oh
that's kind of
um
[Music]
Sky Silverwing Sky Duncan thank you
hey well again your dream is coming true
is it poetic or is it just [\h__\h] sad
foreign
[Music]
I'm proud to be one I'm happy to be part
of your community and I'm happy to have
been here this long keep up the hard
work and I'll continue to support my
favorite birthday let's go
oh
wow
wow wow wow thank you for staying with
me forever and ever and ever and
I never I never I never and ever and
ever and ever and ever and ever forever
forever
I never
and longer than that and ever
[Music]
yeah thank you thank you thank you
guys in my community too so thank you
for being part of it thank you for
supporting me thank you for letting me
be your OC you're the best chicken
chicken
recipe
[Music]
I told you I would be fast
and now I'm called up except for today's
superchatos
yeah
except for two days but days are not in
hollandizer yet
and now I go
now we're gonna do other thing
AKA cooking
I will go cook and tomorrow actually I
purposefully booked my hair appointment
kind of early-ish
so I hope I can sleep early
ah [\h__\h] thanks for reminding me ah I
forgot about that thank you
yeah I need to I have to
[Music]
um
very very necessary
[Music]
um
no how does she know
this is rolling around on the carpet
I'll go pet her now
um so I'll see you guys uh either do
they ask tomorrow
or maybe tomorrow but I don't know
um
somehow you guys gave me the feeling
that
it won't be that hype unless they
announced that the snowboarding game is
finally
being
yeah updated onto the Nintendo 64.
uh the thingy then it would be [\h__\h]
hype but besides that hmm
I don't know what else could get me so
excited
um
that's realistic you guys think Metro
Prime 4 isn't coming
that would be hype announcement yeah
but I don't believe it
hmm
yeah she understands my language
probably
she left the room again she was probably
like oh I guess she's not ending no I am
though I am though
yeah okay guys maybe no maybe no
Nintendo all right maybe we're good
without
I'll watch it though
probably
um
and I'll see you next in Minecraft
[Music]
thank you for the fun guys
foreign
[Music]
setting Hearts emotions
thank you
[Music]
foreign
movies back
[Music]
Mommy
I'll be right with you
[Music]