he
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
a
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
centuries ago in a small tucked away
Kingdom ruled a royal family the family
was known for rich land blossoming mint
and cocoa bean
supplies the Crown Prince was set to
marry the neighboring and much more
powerful Kingdom's daughter however
there was one Open Secret throughout the
kingdom The Prince and his maid were in
relations everyone in the palace knew
but kept the information away from the
princess for they knew she could have a
temper until one night the princess
dropped by without warning and caught
the
prince while the the princess set the
kingdom of blaze in a jealous Rampage
the Valiant Prince stood by his lover
and fought for their right to
love or so you would
think instead the prince buckled under
the first sign of trouble and
immediately threw his maid away to save
his skin and while burning at the steak
the maid uttered a curse upon the land
and wow
D I can't believe I'm having to study
today of all days I really shouldn't
have procrastinated this history report
but when my o she said she's going to be
making a big announcement I can't miss
it I'm so excited oh it could be a new
song or a new outfit I can't even focus
on this book I just hope it starts
soon oh my God oh my God oh spaghetti CH
spaghetti CH spaghetti ch
is this thing
on marinara and cheese a perfect one to
me I'm a May when a wrapper on your fork
and eat on up a meal even a College St
can make I'm spaghetti spaghetti
everybody with my lovely group of girls
anything is possible but now it's my
turn to follow a different recipe and
that's why I am announcing my
graduations from kit dreamers
graduation
huh
graduation no way no way no way this
can't be happening
SPH no this is just a bad
dream spaghetti spaghetti CH spaghetti
CH spaghetti CH spaghetti CH
spaghetti spaghetti
[Music]
my
huh huh what's going
on oh my God am I dead wait why did the
budget get so bad oh God do we run out
of money what about my family who was my
family who am I I don't know anything I
don't even know how to tie my shoes oh
God oh God what do ghost even do do I
say boo do I say oh
God what's
this get a
job excuse me get a job oh my God they
are audacity like come on can't a girl
catch a break here I just died like I
know I asked water ghost do but like I
didn't mean like I need an answer right
now like give me a break come on I don't
even know I don't even know where I am I
don't even know anything what's 2 plus
two who even who even knows like this is
this is ridiculous just can I just have
a
moment oh my gosh
G yay y thank you oh yeah I mean I just
got here why not relax a little bit and
play a little bit of video games
hi yeah and uh think I better get out of
this weird Forest I don't know why I'm
here but um I think the computer just
set on fire so uh let's just find the
nearest town and uh set up shop
[Music]
smash
trick or treat
[Music]
spooky Mar
big
[Music]
energy
fry um
hello hello yeah I'm talking to you
hello excuse me
um hello yes uh it is me could you lower
the game real quick oh yeah you know I'm
just trying to have a conversation with
you and all that bun stuff yep yep hello
oh hello hi yeah could you put your game
down you do know you're like paying per
hour for this table
right
myness but there there you guys are
okay yeah
hello um hi uh yes
so uh now that I have your attention
um yes I know you have been waiting to
see the wizard and it is finally your
chance to
see the
wizard so yes um I hope you are prepared
to see the wizard and um uh yes but
before you see the wizard uh I
unfortunately I I will have to blindfold
you the wizard is very private okay um
the wizard has his ways so um you know
I'm just going to have to blindfold you
real quick I hope that's okay and um yes
uh just give me one moment um one moment
please okay okay yeah the wizard yeah I
know you have been waiting very
patiently the wizard is a very very busy
wizard okay so I know you've been
waiting
I don't know I don't actually know how
long you've been sitting here um but the
wizard is now available so um just give
me one moment okay let's blind foldy you
okay okay um give me one second I'm
blind you're blindfolded right you can't
see anything can't see anything okay um
just give me one second uh you might
hear some noises you might feel feel me
touching you um don't freak out or
anything please thank you
okay okay um just one second I'm setting
up okay um all right I
believe we're just about done uh wizard
are you are you oh great and powerful
wizard are you prepared to see your next
uh subject what what do you call um yes
okay the wizard we'll see you now
[Music]
I am the
wizard I know lost souls you have come
to see me seeking
wisdom from my brain and Beyond
it is
I the
[Music]
wizard yes look upon my
orb it works very
well yes I am the
Wizard and I know you are a troubled
soul mhm you've come to the right place
seeking
guidance yes I understand you're
wanting maybe answers
that life can't give you but the
afterlife may have what you
seek you see my orb it is how I talk
with the
spirits and how I make really funny
faces when I'm by
myself yes
now
wait um hold on I
must use my third eye which is also very
real to look into the orb okay
everybody are you ready to uh I don't
know is this a
seance
um you know my Wizarding ways have no
okay hold on let me turn off this mic my
Wizarding ways have no explanation
okay you may feel and experience things
that
you may have never experienced
before
yes um and um I know we talked about
like
the like the upfront fee
um you know but
uh um anything that happens there's like
a spirit summoning fee per
minute and um what else do I have here I
have a a third eye fee um for how long I
have to use my third eye which is
basically the entire time and then I
have um you took up you you you took up
a seat so uh we have a chair fee okay
we'll just go over it like afterwards
you know it's all good don't worry about
it what do you require wizard Visa
Mastercard oh we accept all sorts of
payments um so yeah are you
ready to gaze into the
Beyond I must see you say
yes I must see you say yes
my body is ready yes yes
[Music]
yes I made a
connection I've made a connection
oh wait wait something's actually coming
wait something's coming through for real
wait this is maybe the first time this
has ever no this is not the f I mean
this is my Powers at
work now what is that that you see
it oh
oh W this spirit is uh doing dancing
something what the hell is he doing oh
yes these magical powers look how
spherical my orb is it's kind of
impressive isn't it how how round it
is the feet of a spirit have you ever
seen a spirit before say no because
you've never seen magic quite like this
this is real these are my real powers of
my third eye and my magic hat that's
from
a place called Club
Penguin
round
who
[Music]
whoa oh good this this Spirit has not
only just shoes but also socks good good
good to know oh my
goodness I have to use the this the
spirit's going kind of crazy I have to
use my mouth to simulate sound
effects I don't think the socks are
edible I don't think so oh my we even
have a
knee oh my gosh a knee a spiritual
knee wow you could say even a ni noik
knee oh my goodness another
knee won't stop you from trying you can
definitely try you can definitely
attempt oh yes indeed
mhm oh oh oh oh when I
dance the spirit also dances how
peculiar oh my
goodness oh my gosh that's fighting
[Music]
woo no way wait oh my goodness
wa what the that looks UNS
sanitary unsanitary Spirit clean up
after your food how dare you just let it
drip all over you that's
disgusting there's just chocolate I hope
that's chocolate there's spiritual ghost
chocolate all over this leg now that
might be
edible not quite
sure that might be edible but what about
this wait a second I just noticed
something you know this spirit is kind
of copying my
style except I have a frilly band and
the spirit has a a different band um
okay copy we can't both we wearing the
same outfits that's so embarrassing
somebody has to change somebody has to
change okay
[Music]
H
okay so embarrassing for
real
H okay Spirit what else do you got what
else do you have here
[Music]
Spirit oh and also oh the thigh is
really
close don't go licking it now but even
you know ribbons on the back and the
such the spirit's really giving us a
fashion
show not close
enough yeah that's even the spirit
agrees disgusting Behavior this is a
spirit guys this is no longer living you
can't simp for a ghost
okay once we know once we fully form
this
ghost's
form we can ask it any question about
the
universe we can ask it anything that we
want to know the spirit is all powerful
and all knowing because I summon
them
oh wait a second this really is what
this ghost is really still in my
style except this also has like a little
little kind of locket looking I don't
even know what to describe that as H I
think the ghost is is maybe perhaps the
ghost is familiar with my game and is
cosplaying the great and powerful wizard
and that must be the case a buckle yeah
Buckle thanks guys it's a buckle yeah oh
the skirt is so poofy just like mine no
we can dance
together oh yeah oh break it down ghost
break it down break it down go oh my God
wo the ghost is going crazy W I got to
match their energy oh my God wo woo oh
my
goodness who is
this look at this
Dapper squishy moochi Mochi looking fell
he's quite cute wouldn't you say oh I
think the ghost agrees yeah he kind of
looks like my guy but a little more I
can't tell sleepy something's
something's a little
different they're like they're like
brothers but this is the chill brother
it M's the anxiety
brother very squishy yeah very oh my
goodness he's like really dancing up in
there he I think he likes the
PGM a cooler brother
the cooler brother
truly no oh the ghost is continuing to
move
hey ghost show us your face I command
Thee I command the ghost so we can know
your secrets I summoned you here and so
I will have you say I will have you
spill the tea
not yet ready I
think but it seems here we have maybe
halfway or I guess more than halfway
it's half of it's the
waste it is the
waste interesting the cute little little
buttons there huh I wish mine had
buttons a lucky you huh lucky you with
your buttons oh okay maybe the wizard
will sew some on later I don't know
um I'm a very busy wizard I guess I
suppose what's this too oh the arms are
are up why why are oh my arms are also
up why are our arms like
that why are our arms like that well of
course I do it to make the ghost feel
comfortable I'm not a ghost I'm a
wizard but this is a ghost and this is
how ghosts are are except it's really
deor because
it's because it's in a orb okay guys my
crystal ball is maybe maybe deforming
things a little bit in fact I believe
it's deforming this part quite a
bit wow wow whoa wow Spirit what are you
what are you showing off to us oh my
goodness spirit I think things may
appear larger in the orb then they
appear
wait oh things may hold on things in the
orb may appear larger
than then they
[Laughter]
are I
think oh who
oh oh oh my goodness yes things are I
don't
know things are I'm a wizard I know
actually we will know though once the
ghost
shows their face now
ghost show thy
face
ghost oh we're close I can see the neck
and also another Buckle around the
ribbon how
cute oh
ghost no I command thee come back
ghost uh hold on you guys need to pay
more for my third eye to work
better did we summon another ghost
perhaps did we summon a different
ghost what is
this I'm
gazing into my crystal
ball oh it's getting bigger it's getting
bigger oh my God what is this creature
what did what we would have we summoned
oh my goodness oh
oh my God it's it's disgusting what is
this oh my God oh my it's bald wait a
second every time I talk it also
talks creature but it's bald so it's
definitely not me it's definitely not me
cuz it's bald
[Music]
ah the creature has hair the
creature this this creature is is is
disguising itself as me how could this
be everything I do it
mimics what is going on what is
happening why did my bgm stop um H what
what huh oh oh
oh you guys you guys I don't think this
is an ordinary creature I think this is
my ghost oh guys I have a confession I'm
a
hack I'm not a real wizard at all this
is a hat from Club Penguin I'm not a
real wizard I never wanted this oper I
never I didn't want this job oh my God
I'm going to leave town I'm never going
to show my face again here oh oh I think
I think I think my establishment is
about to
explode um I think we but I mean I mean
I got to get out of here
[Music]
I forgot to turn the filter
off um it is
I the great spirit that was
trapped
inside the
orb and I have been
released oh I also forgot to turn the
filters off
there we
go
W I have been
free yes that wizard was a hack and um
now I'm here
too B the ultimate ghost man
[Music]
ha um this isn't
like you could saw the
outfit so I guess I'll just oh gosh I'm
so
nervous I'm
[Music]
nervous okay well I'll I'll
I'll I'll talk a bit and then I have
some cu okay as was my first order of
being the Great Ghost
manid to to to so oh
gosh why are you nervous I don't know I
just it's so new oh my gosh I I'm like
because I I've been waiting since this
was announced I've been waiting a whole
month and now it's finally here and it's
kind of like one of those things where
it's like am I am I allowed to show this
because because for this whole time it's
been like a a quote unquote
secret oh
gosh okay I'm going to rip the bandaid
off I'm going to rip it I'm going to rip
it off I'm going to rip it off
I'm wait hold on let me my be I just
noticed the B Jam's a little
quiet okay okay cuz I have things I got
to talk about before the karaoke
so
[Music]
okay oh
gosh
um hey
um um I'm playing it cool I'm playing it
cool don't worry
[Music]
uh
hi oh oh wait I just noticed something
hold on uh oh no
oh okay I'll have to fix that
later I accidentally deleted something
on my
obious so uh
[Music]
um
hi stop don't look at
me um
stop oh gosh I'm
so I'm so nervous oh my
god oh gosh I'm so nervous
thank you guys thank
you uh
welcome to the almighty
powerful mint
my here I'll zoom out a little bit um so
you guys could see little bit
[Music]
more more wow wait maybe I should get
rid of the
desk it feels
naked feels
naken um uh hello hello hello hello
hello hello hello hello hello
[Laughter]
hello oh so welcome to my um
meal and um I guess I should show you
guys some things oh hold on let me zoom
in
[Music]
here suddenly
Zoom suddenly zoom
zoom yeah and
um uh
H I don't know what to do I don't know
what to say you honestly I didn't even
plan up to to now
so I didn't even plan up to here the
smug is
strong I know I can be so smug but I
guess I can show you some of my other
Expressions oh my gosh wait I'm doing
the vtuber thing oh my gosh I'm doing
the vtuber
thing okay okay okay
okay so um uh the oh did I include this
hold
on I forgot something but that's okay I
I'll I'll I'll include it
um when I get to there yeah because
there's some stuff that uh we didn't
have time to to finish before the debut
so they'll be coming a little bit
later
um
so the pointy ears are new oh my
gosh you guys are kind of insane because
I was like you know what yeah I I'm a
ghost I can have pointy ears if I want
and then suddenly all this fan art of me
with pointy ears started happening and I
was
like what did I
leak I was like H how did you guys how
did you guys know I can't have any
secrets it's so
unfair are you guys me oh maybe when I
possessed you guys some of my
thoughts went into
your
uhoh so I have some Expressions that
I'll show you and stuff
so um okay uh some I want to save for
later so I'll show you guys just kind of
oh um so I can
also have my arms
down oh yeah here's
me
[Music]
hello hello hello can I take your
order hello hello hello hello can I take
your order or I can have them uh of
course this is more natural for me
honestly hands
real so yipp yippe and don't leave
because after I show you all this stuff
we'll do the karaoke and I have some
special guest so um if you want to watch
the karaoke and stuff I know that's like
people leave once the reveal
happens but um show the
hands want to see my
hands you can see it without the
orb my skirt is so flowy it's very
[Music]
ghosty cuz I'm a
ghost oh one of my favorite things
though look at this look at the sparkles
on my
on the little Buckle isn't it so
cute little sparkles on the
[Music]
Buckle um okay um so I can I can um
yeah oh my gosh I don't how do vtubers
do this I'm
scared and um let's see uh I can also
someone said smug earlier huh well
[Music]
uh
okay okay I'm freak
Phantom I've literally seen your
[Music]
tweets I've seen your
tweets
[Laughter]
unfortunately now caught in
4k L woman me you not
me
yeah this is me side eying you
[Music]
[Laughter]
so I can be extra smug
now and um uh for for when I'm always
panic mode which is
no this one I had before
too oh
how I always feel very panicked
so yes
um yeah this is this is literally me
right now at this very
moment oh and um oh uh I have I
[Music]
have I think some of you guys like this
kind of expression oh
uhhuh and then if I do this
too now I'm extra
disappointed oh all of my spiritual
energy has been drained from my
ectoplasm
body I'm taking emotional
damage literally at this very moment oh
it
hurts ah
[Music]
yeah and
um let's see oh I can oh this one's kind
of fun so this is when you guys are
waiting for my stream to
start
hold
[Music]
hold oh
is she going to start on time is she
going to
start oh my God we have we have just 1
minute left and the vtubers are
[Music]
here I'm losing my
mind why' my tongue come out
out but I like to combine it with
d oh my gosh this is the best thing
ever this is me whenever I play Metal
Gear
[Music]
Solid oh my gosh Solid Snake
pleas actually no BL
again you guys look at my
ears when I
[Music]
blush oh
gosh yeah my ears get red
now it's kind of embarrassing
no it's kind of embarrassing
[Music]
though stop looking at my
ears you
freak stop looking at my ears you
freak so yeah this is my blushy blush
blush blush which you'll never
receive um and uh let's see
um oh wait my arms back
up and
um uh I have a couple more couple more I
want to save a few of them for later
maybe um let's
see
uh uh oh here okay and
then you guys
you guys when you're so mean to
me stop being so mean
[Music]
to No Bully No Bully No Bully okay
okay no bully No Bully
but of course I can also um be sad and
oh like could sad sad but you know I'm
happy sad I'm like this kind of how I
feel like right now I just feel very
um
emotional very
grateful
yeah oh my gosh you guys my 3.0
finally
happened and I mostly had no mostly no
scuff I
think
[Music]
maybe and then oh of course I
have my tongue I can't be a ghost
without my tongue
[Laughter]
yeah I
can
yeah so the uh the eye and the tongue
emote will
change um uh it looks a little I think
it actually looks a lot less like
panties but I didn't test it in the um
in the emot thing so I guess we guess
we'll find out
um so now you're probably just like oh
my gosh oh everything is so new and
shiny and la la la la la uh who created
all this awesome stuff you had so many
things that happened uh today right
before you appeared as you are
now so I'll go over my credits and then
we'll get into the karaoke so oh
okay I think I have time I think I'll be
okay is that oh wait I have some other
stuff
too um this one's kind of interesting
because I didn't expect it but these
will be for my emo song hours during
karaoke maybe watch my
[Music]
hair tonight will be the night that I
will fall for you
[Laughter]
my hair
grew
who W crazy crazy crazy and that also
brings me to um another hair related
thing uh that these were not done in
time unfortunately um but like I said it
will happen
um sometimes soonish I think
soonish uh but we I have uh two
hairstyles two more hairstyles that uh
um wait do that work hold
on okay there we go okay um that uh will
be joining
me the first one is
twin
Tails wow wow oh my gosh so Kawaii twin
Tails twin actual real twin Tails oh my
gosh I'm going to look like a real like
a real mid I mean I am a real mid but
wow yeah and then the next
[Music]
will
be oh oh it looks the same so far oh oh
it looks the same so far oh
oh
oo long
hair
[Music]
woo so um sorry that they couldn't be
done for today but um
please uh look forward to them when I
can include them uh uh when whenever
that
is so I know it's so long and elegant oh
my goodness oh my gosh
yeah but for now you're stuck with
[Music]
me for now you're stuck with plain Jane
Mento um okay so uh was that everything
oh no I did have sorry I forgot some
other
[Music]
faces I forgot this one um for when you
guys are
particularly um when you guys are
particularly deserving of of jail time
probably
[Music]
death
penalty Jail jail jail jail jail jail
jail jail go to jail do not pass go do
not collect
$200 Jail jail jail jail
[Music]
jail neckl
mint I could be like a clock
[Music]
was weird Okay um be good
now be
good okay credits
time credits credits credits I'm going
to scooch up right next to you guys I'm
going to bring my desk back because it's
quite lonely without it
and
um and
[Music]
credits uh okay hold on pause okay T
first and foremost I want to do a
special thank you to of uh to of course
uh itaya for helping finalize my 2.0
design because you know uh even what I
have now uh how I look now is with help
from Maya
um and so uh I of course want to oh oh
oh oh yeah thank her there we go and
then of course to 1.0 and 2.0 Mama K M
so thank
[Music]
you
so yeah of course
um even though I have two Mama um and
everything uh of course I'm so grateful
for KJR Mama for bringing me to life
well after
life to begin with
so thank
you thank you thank
you yeah and um for credits for like the
main stream
stuff what that oh oh oh sorry I meant
to say oh see uh this is what this is
what Maya helped me with so up in the
top left corner is kind of what I drew
and then Maya really fleshed it out and
helped me with picking a bunch of
hairstyles and things like that so is
how I became to be in this like
this and look at this she did all this
even the reference sheet that I have now
she did for free and everything she's so
so sweet thank you Maya than
thank thank you yeah yeah and she had
all these little hairstyles drawn out
for me and everything I was like oh my
goodness she she put so much effort into
it I was really grateful all those years
ago yeah yeah and let's see
[Music]
next was it obvious
was it
that um my
mama oh my gosh I can finally say this I
am
mama I am mama is my new
[Music]
mama
yeah and and she made me so cute
what do you guys
think do you guys do you guys um how are
we feeling huh how are we how are we
feeling do you guys like
[Music]
it cute cute yeah
yeah yeah thank you guys for all the
super chats and everything by the way I
really appreciate it sorry that I
haven't been able to really read them
and thank you guys but yeah thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
and then my papa is silia which um oh my
goodness Celia is just so cracked and uh
thank you
selia um for making me move and being so
so attentive to things like oh my gosh
one of my favorite things about like
look at this look at my ribbons when I
move they're so
puffy right they're so like they look 3D
when I I remember when I first sent a
picture of me to matara she was like oh
your 3D is getting started I was like
girl no this is 2D I'm not 3D yet it's
crazy right like they's so she did such
a and like the little sparkles like on
the Buckle and everything oh my gosh
selia I is
amazing so so
amazing so um you might recognize silia
also uh is Liu's Um Papa and doi's Papa
so now we're all like
sisters um I
I love new
[Music]
Aly yeah everybody say hello to a yummy
mama why do why did you send that
no I had to fight her to send more money
honestly um and then um crunchy helped
Celia with setting up the project file
so thank you for that crunchy and for
the opening animation oh my god did you
guys see the new opening
animation um that's by artist yodok on
uh Twitter and uh it's so cute oh my
gosh I kind of like gave them a list of
things that I was like oh maybe you
could include this or maybe this but you
don't have to include everything it's
okay and then they included everything
and they they went all out it was I was
so
happy when I got it show it again oh
yeah I will show it again one
second uh
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
yay yeah so thank you yod and then the
opening music that you heard is by
mitan
mitan if you don't recognize that name
mitan is a one of the main composers for
a little mobile game that I like called
Blue
archive yeah
ha so um
actually I uh I'm so grateful now that I
went to to Anime Expo because when I was
there one thing I really wanted to do is
I was like I'm going to introduced
myself to MIT kosan because I want to
work with him so I was able to give him
my card and then when I was getting this
started I was just like you know what
I'm going to shoot my shot and see if if
maybe he'll do my my intro music and he
said he said oh you know I I haven't
been taking like personal like you know
uh not non-corporate requests lately but
I got your card at Anime Expo and I
liked your style and I saw you're a fan
of blue archives so I I will work with
you yeah because I networked at because
I networked at anime
XO I got to work with
so
[Music]
yes and the song is so catchy it's so
great and um I think it was funny
because some people um my last uh my
last opening intro video had like
welcome to maid world and stuff like
that but the song
actually uh titled by me kosan is hello
Ghost World so we're still ghosting
worlding
yeah
so we're still technically welcoming or
going to a ghost world a
world yeah so I was really happy about
that and um you haven't seen it yet but
the ending animation is by mushroom and
I really love mushrooms um uh pixel art
so you'll see that at the end of the
stream and the bgm that you're hearing
now and the ending bgm is by June which
if you watched mint mataro summer
special you might recognize that name
because he did a lot of editing a lot he
did all the editing for us
so yeah actually it's cute because I
wanted like a song that tied in with the
uh
like I wanted two songs that were the
same but not so this is like a kind of
like a toned down version of the ending
song so they're they're like if this is
like I called it the Twilight
version yeah yeah yeah and then I feel
like I never got to do a proper like
introduction of the cafe background but
it's by Marie which she also did another
background a new one that you will be
seeing soon in fact in like a few
minutes in like a few minutes yeah lower
five version yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
exactly and then um the chat CSS is by
Jason so thank you thank you thank you
um it's so cute you guys are little
ghosties yeah another
mhm and then uh there's more credits
because I had that lure video at the
very beginning uh thank you seven star
studio thank you guys Leah esper a app
and V thank you everybody for working
with me on my L video I kind of like
threw them a
script and threw them the idea that I
wanted and oh my gosh the coolest thing
was like they created that like POV and
it was like a real like 360 World it was
the coolest thing ever I was just like
wow oh my gosh and so um yeah I was like
uh uh and and then they brought
spaghetti Chan to life my
OSI I hope you guys liked it I came up
with the whole
script um maybe
that For Better or For Worse
probably For Better or For Worse
probably should
[Music]
be spaghetti Chan really graduating or
was that just a bit no she gra she she
did graduate yeah spaghetti Chan she
graduated spaghetti
CH so
sad I'm over
it kitchen dreamers is is the best Idol
group or made made idle group
ever Marin and cheese A Perfect Blend of
me
oh rest in
spaghetti rest in
spaghetti and so yeah thank you seven
star studio for such a oh and oh my gosh
I didn't ask if I could uh if I could
share it but before so I won't but the
drawings like in the in the
um like in the sketch part of the video
of the lore video was all like hand done
and then she like with pencil and stuff
and then she scanned it and so it's just
uh uh it's it was like very authentic
it's very you know I was like I kind of
want like a story book looking vibe
yeah thank you seven star studio you
guys are amazing thank
you my I wanted something really you
know I'm not really like a lore video
type
person I wanted something just kind of
more silly and goofy than anything
so hopefully that kind of came across
hopefully and then last um another thing
you guys might have
seen yes um wait hold on I actually
actually hold on let me pause the music
cuz I think I still have it up um
oh I do still have it up actually we're
about to run out of time in the
game
um this is the actual
game that you will be able to play after
stream
yeah so um I basically went to Joi and I
was just like I
um I okay there was this one game I used
to play all the time on Cartoon Network
it was like called trickortreat beat or
[Music]
something and so um I really wanted
something it always put me really much
into the Halloween mood and so I really
wanted something just like that uh and
so we came up with M Phantom freak or
treat yeah so this will be available
after the stream for you to play um the
freaking watch I made this the little
overlay I made it
myself um and uh and uh uh there's four
levels that you can play um there's lots
of vtubers in there and lots of vtuber
references um I asked uh bunch of like
my Indie friends and and people that I
was just like whoever and there's some
other corpos in there as well so um
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah uh go and find them all
and collect all the treats and at the
end there's a
priz
so yeah there's I wanted to honestly
include more people but um there was a i
time time was not on the
side but I tried to include a good
amount of people um and uh the team was
absolutely
crazy oh and all the music is also
custom um so if anybody wants to stream
this playing it um I don't know why if
you want to I don't know if you want to
but you totally can uh because the music
is all commission from
me so or ra rather I commissioned it for
other people and um yeah
so and
um oh whoops
oh my gosh I forgot to credit that wait
no guys I'm so sorry no oh my gosh I'm
such a failure I forgot to put the music
credits and the game credits I'm so
sorry
no oh I'm so so sorry but it's it's on
the ichio so it's definitely there um
but yeah uh Joi did like a lot of the
programming um he had a friend also
helped but he's like doesn't have a
Twitter or anything he's just some guy
so sorry escalo you have salary Toya
salary men as your picture and then L
did the art Electra also help with the
animation and oo is the illustrator for
the P it's a very cute picture I think
you guys will like it and then for the
music um this this song was done by
Fingers um which uh
[Music]
I feel so awful right
now fingers on Twitter as well with a
with a with a one fingers does a lot of
um like metal gear yeah fingers from the
coima frequency yes yes yes yes so
um uh he uh he uh created this and it
sounds just absolutely exactly what I
wanted very like old school you know
show their Twitter oh you know what I
can do that hold
on hold on I can just do that wait
Twitter I can go to
Twitter uh
wait uh oh no I don't want to look at I
don't want to look at there it is
okay wait what what about this show it's
probably fine
okay oh it's really it's really small
fingers fingers I oh my gosh it's really
small hold
on there you
go fingers on
Twitter like that and then of the other
song which hold
on oh everything is all messed up now
this is so scuffed hold on I'm going to
refresh and see what song we
get the anticipation
oh
oh it's
silent oh oh oh because I didn't click
on
it oh because I didn't
click
oops my bad um this is by Daryl so
uh it looks off-centered cuz it is
this is its own
thing this is this is its own thing you
guys uh hold on let me get the let me
get the Daryl's
um
[Music]
so oh why is this oh there we go at
Starlight Daryl thank you Daryl for the
other V which you might recognize um
Daryl uh helped with the um with uh my
original intro music so um thank you so
much yeah yeah
yeah so yeah um that's the game again it
will be available after um after stream
I still got to I got to make it
public um so yeah
okay um I think I'm ready now
for karaoke are you guys ready for
karaoke guys ready for karaoke and if
you find any bugs just like tag me or
something I don't know put it in the
hashtag so that I can see and then we'll
try and fix it yeah okay give me a
second I'm going to go back to my
loading screen so I can set up okay give
me one second give me one second
[Music]
H uh oh I forgot something hold on
okay now I'm
ready now I'm ready oh okay I'm just
going to sing a song um
to warm up and then I'll bring in my
guests okay oh wait I didn't bring up
anything first a I'm not going to do a
lot of songs I have a karaoke
tomorrow so um look at this you guys
we're finally using the stage in my main
Cafe
woo we can finally use the stage in my
made Cafe um I can get a little bit
bigger I guess I can get closer
look I'm looking down on all of
you there was a stage yes there was
always a stage it was in the back corner
of course every mid Cafe is going to
have a stage well not everyone
but most I
suppose
yeah yeah yeah okay um I'm going to sing
something
Halloween cuz I won't sing it tomorrow
this might be a little weird for the
mood actually no it's not weird for the
mood oh wait well it's not the Halloween
song I changed my
mind uh okay
um uh uh one
second one second I want I don't want to
take too long
because I um
I've plan on I didn't want this to be
over two
hours so okay think this hold on let me
double
check I think this is
okay okay
okay I sing
[Music]
what a
thrill with darkness and silence through
the
[Music]
night what a
thrill I'm searching and I'll melt into
you what a fear in my
heart but you're so Supreme
I give my
life not for Honor but for
[Music]
you in my
time there'll be no one
else I my voice oh God
CME it's the way I fly to
you I'm
still in a
dream snake
[Music]
[Applause]
eer somay you go through the
rain and somay you Fe on a tree
frck soord deal the trial to to
survive for the
day we see new
life I give my life not for Honor but
for
[Music]
you in my
time there be no one
else sorry
K is the way I fly to
you I'm
still in a
dream snaking
[Music]
up I'm
still in a
dream SN it
[Music]
[Applause]
up
it come on
now come on now you really thought I had
like no Metal Gear related toggle really
at all you thought I had nothing at all
you just like you were like oh I guess
she just didn't want anything come on I
have ey
patch that's that's boss VTO to
you yay Snake Eater okay tonight I
brought together a group of GES that um
for most of them except like
one that I um
I have always wanted to sing with um I
just kind of for some of them I've been
talking with them a little bit more
lately um and uh so I know some people
might be like whoa what I didn't even
know you talked with that person yeah um
we do sometime I don't always talk about
who I'm talking with in my
DMs
um but uh yeah I got stuff going off
I've been reaching out of my comfort
zone a little bit and I'm really really
grateful because all these all these
lovely ladies were all of them are so
busy and so I um am really really
grateful that they all took time to join
me for for this
and um even though they're just they're
just so nice some of them were just like
oh my gosh it's my honor and I'm like no
it's my honor
to sing with you my voice is really not
doing so well today but um uh this is
all just for fun so
um uh hopefully I can sing with more
people in the future I would thought I
was just like oh my gosh I want to sing
with so many people but I also like I
said I don't want this to be super duper
long um so it might kind of be not a
speedrun but uh just kind of let's sing
some songs with some Duets and uh yeah
um so I'm going to scoots over
and I'm going to introduce the first
person which probably no one is
surprised
about um oh wait hold on uh oh my
tower hi everybody matara kjo here and
this is my favorite song in Citadel
space she will not get that reference I
don't get that
reference I'm a little bit nervous I'm
not going to lie but here we go I'm
nervous too I love you man
man why you calling me so
late it's kind of hard to talk right
now crying is
everything
okay I got a whisper cuz I can't be too
loud I sing while
belting well my girls in the Next Room
sometimes I wish she was
you we never what are these
lyrics I haven't listened to these it's
good to hear your say my name it sounds
so
sweet coming from the Lips of an Angel
hearing those words it makes me
weak and
never want to say
goodbye but girl you make it hard to be
faithful with the Lips of an
Angel embarassed by all
the what you that's my
alarming me t
[Music]
and yes I dreamt of you too but they
were more like
[Music]
nightmares do you know you're talking to
me will it start a
fight no I don't think she has a
clue well my girls in the Next Room
sometimes I wish she was you I guess we
never really moved
on it's really good to hear your voice
saying my name is down so
sweet coming from the Lips of an Angel
hearing those words it makes me
weak and I never want to say
goodbye but girl you make it hard to be
faithful with the lips
[Music]
of oh I was wrong sorry mat so nervous
to see this I told myself I was going to
sing all soft but instead I felt it the
whole song yeah felt it girl my
best you got to you got to speak up
love I love you so much I'm so happy
here with us
[Music]
everybody emotional emotional emotional
okay good toar your voice say my name it
sounds so
sweet coming from the Lips of an Angel
hearing those words it makes me
weak and I never want to say
goodbye but you make it hard to be
faithful with the Lips of an
[Music]
Angel I don't know how song
goes with the Lips of an
[Music]
Angel
thanks honey you calling
me so
late I love you mint I love you whisp I
W call I almost called you guys Momo get
out of here don't call them M I love you
mint big
kisses have an amazing rest of your day
and enjoy this wonderful day filled with
Spooks and celebration byebye byebye and
remember I am matara con and you can bug
me anytime bye honey get out of
here she's such a
yapper thank you my to thank you thank
you oh my goodness that girl uh she
actually like filmed that I think the
day she was starting her subathon so I
was like I was like umwa unless you
decide to record it during your sub on
can I get it today she was like
[Music]
yeah like I said everyone is so busy and
I felt so bad bugging people I was I
felt so bad but um I'm really happy that
um so many people decided to join in the
next one is probably not a surprise
either but this is a song I have never
sung before um also I don't know if it's
obvious but I've never listened to these
videos before if the audio is too loud
or too quiet just just let me know um I
kind of wanted to keep them a uh
surprise uh for oh
shoot oh shoot I
um I think I'll be okay this one might
be a little scuffed but that's okay
that's okay
Okie doie Okie doie Okie doie oh uh let
me put the notifications up above there
we go Okie doie Okie doie thank you guys
for all the gift and memberships thank
you guys for all the uh super chats
thank you Okie DOI okay okay no no sorry
Doki is
not you guys I'm going to have a literal
concert with DOI
okay if you want to hear me and DOI sing
you got to come to our concert I
couldn't spoil it here God
can't spoil it here you got to come to
the
concert shees all right our next person
t
k this is Tak from H life English
hey my favorite little ghost
made Let's sing together to celebrate
today a hella project song a morning
musim song Let's Go
let's
[Music]
go oh oh this is my
fore
[Music]
[Applause]
fore
fore fore
[Music]
fore
my
[Music]
heart foree
I'm going you
myi she smells so good k
[Music]
he loves you he loves
you he needs
it
[Music]
w foree
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my
gosh oh my God than
[Applause]
you thank you
[Music]
helloing oh oh wait that's her
oops
yay thank you so much for having me that
was fun singing
together thank you and have a beautiful
time for the rest of the
[Music]
stream thank you K thank you thank you
that was toky s by morning
M um maybe I should have written the set
list my bad sorry I'm nervous I'm really
oh my gosh oh thank you thank you thank
you oh my gosh thank
you
oh uh uh sorry I'm really nervous and
now I had oh my gosh f i was watching
your I was watching you right before I
started thank you for
rating you're so cute in 3D oh my gosh
and you're dancing skeletons and
everything um I'm a I'm a big fan of
FAA wow I'm really honored oh my my gosh
thank you thank you guys thank you so
much
um and uh
yeah um so uh I have uh four more
people oh gosh I'm shaking I'm shaking
the next person is some another uh
another uh vtuber with an amazing
amazing voice again I'm very honored
especially because she's also so
busy um it's funny because uh I actually
have two Chapel rone
songs in this and um I mean I don't know
if anybody's curious but um but uh I
mean this is my debut of course it's
archived so
um yeah the next person is um someone I
also really look up to and I think is a
great streamer Mousie
hello she's so
[Music]
small it's
fine it's cool you can say that we are
nothing but you know the truth and guess
I'm the
fool with the arms are like an angel
through the car sun
roof I don't want to call it off but you
don't want to call it love only want to
be the one that I call baby you can kiss
aund boys and bars another shot try to
stop the feeling you can say it's just
the way you are make the new excuse
another stupid reason
B good luck good luck B you to stop the
world just to stop the feeling good luck
bab good luck well good luck bab good
luck you have to stop the world just to
stop the
feeling well who
cares it's a sexually explicit Kind of
Love Affair and I
cry it's not fair I just need a little
Lov and I just need need a little
air think I'm going to call it off even
if you call it love I just want to love
someone who calls me baby you can kiss
100 boys in bars another shot try to
stop the feeling you can say it's just
the way you are make a new excuse
another stupid reason Good Luck Good
Luck Good Luck Good Luck
you have to stop the world just to stop
the feeling good luck bab luck good luck
bab you'd have to stop the world just to
stop the
[Music]
feeling and when you wake up next to him
in the middle of the night with your
head in your hands you're nothing more
than his wife and when you think think
about me all of those years ago you're
standing face to face with I told you so
you know I hate to say that I told you
so you know I hate to say but I Told You
So
kiss
boys
another
St say Just the Way You Are
another stupid reason Good Luck Good
Luck Good Luck Good Luck you'd have to
stop the world just to stop the feeling
good luck bab good luck B good luck bab
good luck you have to stop the world
just to stop the feeling you have to
stop the world just to stop the feeling
you have to stop the world just to stop
the feeling you have to stop the
world just to stop the
feeling thank you
Mousie thank
you oh my God so cute okay I love you
bye bye
[Music]
byebye oh my gosh I love her Halloween
outfit so cute yay that was good luck
babe what iron Mouse thank you thank you
thank
you U oh wait I think I put both of the
Chapel Road songs next to each other I
didn't mean to oh no I didn't no I
didn't oh my gosh this next one though
I'm really nervous about because um I
practiced it but honestly I chose this
song with my own selfish reasoning
because I thought that this uh singer I
thought that she could do a really
really great job with it and I felt bad
because she didn't know the song and
then I I was like wait we can change it
I know you're busy and um uh she was
like no I'll learn it and I just she's
just the sweetest sweetest person ever
I'd like to welcome to the
stage
pleas oh let me get smaller
[Music]
I I just woke up from a
dream where you and I had to say
goodbye and I don't know what it all
means but since I survived I
realized wherever you go that's where
I'll follow
[Music]
nobody's promise
tomor I'm love you every it's the last
night like the last night if the world
was ending I'd want to be next to
[Music]
you if the party was over and our time
on Earth was
[Applause]
through i' one hold you just for a
while and
die with a
smile if the world was ending I'd want
to be next to
you
L lost in the words that we scream
I don't even want to do this
anymore cuz you already know what you
mean to me and our love's the only War
worth fighting
for wherever you go that's where I'll
follow nobody's promise
tomorrow so I'm love you every night
like it's the last night like it's the
last night if the World
Wasing i' want to be next to
you wait what's my heart rate if the
party was over and all time on Earth
was I'd want to hold you just for a
while
and with the
smile if the world was ending I i' want
to be next to you oh gosh I completely
forgot you guys I'm so star next to
you she just sounds so good next to
[Music]
you right next to
you
yeah m m 3
HS and chat HS and chat HS and
chat let's go the world was ending I'd
want to be next to
you if the party was over and our time
on Earth was
through I'd want to hold you just for a
while
and
die with the
smile if the world was ending I'd want
to be next to
you if the world was ending I'd want to
be next to
[Music]
you I'd want to be next to you
oh my gosh thank you thank you so much
for having me on your special day thank
you so much it means the world to me uh
to sing with you I want to be next to
you I want to be next to M Min thank you
so much have a great rest of your stream
yes oh my gosh thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank you F
bye there she
goes oh my gosh the cutest the the
beautifullest the oh oh my gosh I'm so
sorry I kind of you guys are for real
was just so I I chose that song from my
own selfish desires I was just like she
will kill this song and hopefully she
sings it again in karaoke oh my gosh
she's so I know I'm like
totally um debuffing myself because I'm
I chose like the most incredible singers
ever but it's really just because I
wanted to hear them
sing it's really just my old selfish I
wanted to hear these beautiful people
sing in my ears
so it's I'm the winner even if I sound
so bad next to
them oh the next person is also just the
most incredible singer ever
and someone I've been talking to uh uh
more
recently um and you know everybody oh my
gosh everybody has just been so kind
[Music]
and and uh hold on my YouTube froze
again I just uh just um having so many
uh so
many uh hopefully I cannot do a revenge
of that song I I'll ask I'll ask
Elizabeth if I can use her vocals again
or something I don't know but just just
uh um all the support the amount of
support that you guys have all shown me
and so many other YouTubers
and um all my friends too so sorry oh
gosh
so sorry I'm really Star Struck and uh
uh just nervous so I sound like dooky
well we'll do Revenge tomorrow
okay okay next one is with the beautiful
The Talented everybody loves her U I
love her maybe the most no I'm just
kidding I don't think so I think the
jailb bird's
probably love for the most please oh
hold on I'm going to take another sippy
let's go
Nissa hi
Darlings this is H live English Advent
devilish Diva the one the only narissa
Raven here today to sing H to go by
Chapel rone with one the only the
impeccable adorable ghost girl made mint
happy Halloween everyone and enjoy the
show
5 6 5 6
[Music]
78 I could be the one or your new
Addiction it's all in my head but I want
nonfiction I don't want the world but
I'll take this City who can blame a girl
call me hot not pretty baby do you like
this I made it so you dance with me it's
like
de when you're doing it with me doing it
with me h o t t o g o snap and CLA and
touch your toes raise your hands down
body Roll dance it out you're hot to go
h o t t o g o snaping clapping oh I I
said hurts part on accident sorry
Anda h o t t o g o you can take me H to
go h o t t o g o you can take me hard to
go I woke up alone staring at my ceiling
I try not to care but it hurts my
feelings you don't have to stare come
here get with it no one's touched me
there in a damn hot minute baby don't
you like this speed I'm made it so you
sleep with me it's like 199
deg when you're doing it with me doing
it with me h o t t o g o you deserve
your toes body roll Dan it out you're
hot to go h o t t o o snapping clapping
touch your toes raise your hands don't
body roll h o t t o g o h o t t o g o
you can take me hard to go h o t t o g o
you can take me hard to go what's it
take to get your number what's it take
to bring you home hurry up it's time for
supper order up I'm hot to go what's it
take to get your number hurry up I'm SC
and cold hurry up it's time for supper
hurry up it's time to h o t t o g o you
can take me home to go h o o o you can
take me hard to go h o t t o g o you can
take me hard to go h o t o o you can
take me hard to
go it's hot in here is anyone else
hot yeah I'm hot girl coming home with
me yeah okay it's hot oh my God I'll
call the
cab thanks for having me happy Halloween
happy
Halloween she
goes I love her so much oh my gosh
narissa ravencraft everybody oh my gosh
thank
you I'm so sorry I said over over your
one part Nisa I was just too excited I
was just too excited to sing with
you
yeah okay I have one last person that
I'd like to sing with which um actually
uh I um a lot of people were like who is
this and um I want to say
uh um last night
ra DMD me and she was just like M I'm
looking forward to your 3.0 and I was
like but also I'm so sorry I chose that
that that Oshi Mark to throw people off
the scent but it was because it's
someone cat related but I didn't want to
use their ooshi
Mark and so I was like I'm so sorry if
people were confused but I would
love if if you ever want to sing one day
I would be so honored um to sing with a
big cat yeah I want to sing with so many
people like I said I wanted to sing with
so many more people I wanted to sing
with um it's funny I chose V show Joo
and Hollow live but I wanted to sing
with Indies as well and just so many
people I wanted to sing with lots of um
lots of friends and um um but like I
said uh there's lots of people in the
video game the video game why did I say
it like that in the game that um that I
made with the team so um you can check
them out and there and too and
everything and why is everybody saying
germa
stop stop you're ruining my wholesome
moment
stop video
game The Last Song is with um with
someone very special to me of course and
um oh hold
on let me make sure I have the right l
lyrics um but uh yeah uh someone very
special to me and of course who else
would that be
except my
mama iy mama why you guys say Mr Beast
coima stop you're ring my stop not
spaghetti y y oh my gosh okay
iami Mama this is the last song of the
night everybody um so uh thank you for
coming out oh stick around though
because I want you to see my ending
screen too it's cute okay all
right
oh hello hi everyone I'm iami I'm
illustrator and bber and me to
you
y happy I singing together yeah
do my
best
[Music]
y I am a
dreamer he's so
[Music]
power
foree for
[Music]
[Applause]
the
[Music]
mic I am a
dreamer power
[Music]
fore
spee foree
[Music]
[Applause]
W it's going to be your
world push push push push
[Music]
push push push
push I love
[Laughter]
you bye-bye
yummy Mama
everybody oh I got really emotional
during
that I got really emotional during that
so I have one last song that I would
like to sing um it's a Halloween song
it's not very long um but thank you guys
again for uh for the um 3.0 debut and
everything and thank you guys I really
really appreciate everybody being here
and um and all the support and
sh Mas thank you okie dokie I don't want
the mash it's not the mash this is this
is a little more wholesome okay like I
said it's a Halloween song I mean unless
you want the mash I'll give you the
mash
okay last song and then I will see you
tomorrow for karaoke we'll do the match
tomorrow no we do not want it you sure
are you
[Music]
sure I don't know I see a lot of
yeses okay last song is wholesome okay
guys it's wholesome it's wholesome
wholesome Vibes wholesome
Vibes wholesome Vibes wholesome Vibes
for my wholesome debut
okay okay okay okay this one is from a
uh actually I I was watching they did a
concert because the show has been around
for 10 years and they did a concert for
it recently like just like a couple days
ago and I was watching it and I was like
oh my gosh I was crying it was so
beautiful and it's from a show that I
love very very much called Over the
Garden Wall that I watch every Halloween
so I will sing into the
unknown I'm really sorry if there was
like volume stuff too I'm really sorry
if there was volume stuff with everybody
I was trying to adjust while singing
[Music]
[Applause]
l through the
Mist by The Milk Light of
moon all that was lost is
revealed are long bygone burdens Mir
echo of the
spring but where have we
come and where shall we end
if dreams can't come true then why not
pretend how the Gentle
Wind beckons through the
leaves as
autumn
colors
fall dancing in a
swirl of golden
Memories the
loveliest
Li of
[Music]
all yay okay you guys convinced
me you guys convinced me
[Music]
oh shoot where's my lyrics
uh-oh wait where's my
lyrics oh wait where's my lyrics oh
[Music]
no wait hold
on I'm going to start over
was edging to a g late last night when
my eyes beheld a Skippy sight where the
sigma rler began to rise and violently
MOG the Costco guys the here is the BS
and
gas he put the fries
in he give of a smash or
F he rised up all the gas from the back
rooms in the Ohio streets where the wolf
inside me last and least the gooners all
J to grow their
ches give tips for me cuz I'm a Luke's
Max
Pro here is a all the G Mash gave them a
smash or a B the mash they put the fries
in the bag they did the mash he rised up
all the gas the streamers were all doing
the gritty
baby groc just red up Liz liy the
rizzler brought big
Justice Aiden Ross and
Kai there was no pops inside everyone
began to Mu Patrick b b on Ax playing 1
2 three buckle my shoe blue tie kid was
on a sigma grind I don't know Dr some
prime he rised the allall of gas
give them a smash or a
pass they put the fries in the
bag he was the fall again pausing his
stream Min Phantom did laugh seems like
doky bird was about to C looked around
to see if there was enough movement and
said did you guys know the low taper
meme is still massive Mas here is the B
the G Monster Mash gave them a smash or
pass they put the fries in the
B he RIS up all the gas everyone loves
skib he's the ultimate gigachad and my
brain Rob bash is the hit of the land
for you the beta this bash was meant to
the funniest meme ever made is
H the Monster
Mash then you can Mash
he put the fries in the
bag he R up all the
gas oh yes good oh oh easy matara you
syssy Ohio o c
good good
o
good easy matara easy
matara yeah
[Music]
good thank you guys bye-bye
thank you oh thank you um I oh I um I uh
sorry I can't think anymore I will have
um uh the game up I'll post about on
Twitter I'll try to remember Blue Sky I
can't remember more than one thing but
now play the game and happy Halloween
[Music]
oh
n