I'm actually one of the worst people for
for like speech advice cuz I I when I
was younger my Drama teacher would
always tell me off of saying my T is
wrong I would say it like f oh wait my T
is too but like voice in yours probably
but that makes you more British maybe
really yeah well I mean I'm British so
you know kind of works out not sure if
that really
applies okay well technically I didn't
live in the UK for a very long time so
my my my you can't get rid of the
britishness you can't you can take the
girl out of Britain but you can't take
the British out of the girl but saying
that most of my friends in Japan were
Americans so I had to say things like
pants instead of well that'll be on the
test
pants no he don't say pants wait what
that sounds British
though well I guess it would be
Underpants