[Music]
[
Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Applause] [Music]
[Music] Lovely maa Aiteru Atteru
haiee my name 5 festival summer color
[Applause]
na  Midnight sister, this is the one who is being filmed.
Ah, other than that, today, I'll explain it in Japanese.
A festival and Carre-chan of collaboration is not happening.
Umi collaboration is happening.
English reason and open web ice cream make-up  Wish Wedding
Specialty Chige Name
yeah
Good Yokose Well, there were various circumstances
First of all, I knew about the talk of collaborating normally and I was planning to do it in the studio of the Hosohoro live It was said
that Kengo is busy  So it became difficult, and I
didn't want to go to Ara-chan's house, so I bought a store. That's
right, I won, I won, I want to win. Smoker is kind, Ara-chan bought me a chair,
but when  Who told Ara-chan's landlord that it
was a tour? I know, I'm
a little old. I
moved to a new house a while ago.  Year is
pretty old, isn't it? A ghost appears, isn't it?
Everyone loves it. The name I chose is ghost. I'm a
psychic, I've been relying on sondes for a while now. I've
been hearing sounds in the ceiling,
and I've been taming it many times.
I had a professional come to make the monsters and ghosts disappear, but they
came about four times. But in the end, it
seemed they couldn't do anything about it. So, I'll tell you the reason why Cross-chan is so cute.  I
thought, "What is it?"
If you just enter the ceiling in between,
it's a cute scene from under the place, see my, I gave up, but I can't stop thinking about it.  The
old lady is getting wet and paving the way.
Uba is also good, but it's okay to have it in the entrance. It's the fourth one, Calamita, but the
caster has a name, but the guide color is,
let's have the wind of the stock climb up from the ground.  I
called him Yabeton
and he was like, "Oh no, I'm a kid, but I'm a kid,
so ...
Thank you very much. I received it and said, "I'm
going to go back to the distribution site."
But,
wait a minute, I'll have my senior come up with the next one.
That steamship is a bit blue, but I don't think it
's bad.  The flow is not coming, and I'm embarrassed about my free time. I
don't have a washer, but now Kei-chan is here.
Ah, it's a lightning rod, isn't it? No, I'm
carrying it, so I'm facing the sound of the street.  I wonder if Matsui will be the center
or not, but I'm really worried about it, but when I read it in about two birds, I thought, "
Someone is serious about Senpai, it's like a
beautiful house is good, but it's good."  It's a scene that will definitely be conveyed, so k distribution
Dog, that's in a hurry, it's about time for the opposite sex, I'm
asking for the nature of the mouse, so it's cute,
no, no,
but still, no, well, I'm not coming, you thought,
and in the end today  I came to the festival house.
And I heard that Nezu is a nice place.
Yesterday during the
live broadcast, the listeners were also there. It's the Year of the Rat,
so I thought I'd get a chap even though I was live, so I went to see the live broadcast and I was consulting with them all the time, so it's fine. What is
that Jaeger?  It's not that it's dirty or anything, but it seems like there's a bastard living there who's been there for a long time.
If the town election commission thinks the house is dirty, I'll have to worry about my legs and back. I haven't cleaned it up yet because it was a last-minute event.  It
's really beautiful. The landmines are very small and the houses are also very small.
What can I say? I've been on LINE for a while now, so I'm glad you called me.
Let's eat at the seat today. I
can't eat it. Yes, I bought 4 servings. It
's 8 servings.  8 pieces already,
how many can you eat now
? No matter how easy it is, it's the ideal period to be in the top
11, eat 13 pieces.
Yes, that's true, it's true. I covered both
lies. No, I can tell you the level of skill on the road.  Ahhhh,
after that, Koyama-kun
That's a lie, isn't it? A woman is a Daimler, I have a guitar, I have a sister, I have a technique, I get a lot of attention every day, but I don't have a deck, I eat a lot, I might be able to say that, so let's
go right away.
I think it would be good to use a hat to line up,
but I think it's good to take off your hat. I think there are quite a few people
in English-speaking countries who are doing research.
Today  I'd better explain what I'm going to do. Oh, that's one 2 h. Senior is amazing. Spe 12 squeeze.
Red v Faren convenience. Add 3 of them. It's no good.
In fact, the cemetery is also s pen. Kathleen seems to be.
Open your eyes to the spabo. Come on,
cast.  To my place
[music]
usas large
deira nodera sonho typed in between
monthly Perth Gohara shop two barbara bike thing tweet case
finish type
No, training in airwaves, Dobe-san, yay, good texture, Fukunichi Pass defense, nomachii-
chan by nature, second, I
learned about the name of the little flower that goes to the moon, I
'm gathering, well, the
taste is just right, ah English  Is the stock price samba
Come on, I want to participate Aaaa English is lighter than English, isn't it? It's a
great device, isn't it
? Haa nu 3 nu Aaaa capital punishment & star OK
Igorie ok
Aaaa eating chicken jp Let's put it
next  Facing each other, shaking the greedy kyu, small
area unter
dele banao,
prissy tube, if you don't have the ears of a rapper, I don't
say high, how do you
say itadakimasu, nu,
west st, Germany bound, yeah, ok, it's Mars chicken  But there isn't, I
walked all the way to the sweets shop.
Uh waaaah,
ua
voodoo,
good. Uh
huh, by the
way, there is, it won't be cannibalism.
Yeah, Armage's face
is a phoenix.
It's like this,
isn't it? Well,
it's not that strong. I don't want you to
do anything. It's
not a battle, it's not a chicken, so it's okay to take pictures and eat them.
Please be safe. What's strange? For example, even if you give a little bit of chicken to Promonte, you'll eat it. I think you'll eat it. I'll give it to you. I think you'll eat it. I'll say thank you.
No, it's not that. Well, let's all be happy. Fujii, no, it's
better not to eat the relocation. The
Phoenix that gave birth to me is something
like that. I don't think I
'll do it. I have a lot of babies in my belly. Of course I don't need shoes.  I'll
die, but if I'm eaten, I'll go
again. If I don't change my clothes, if it rains,
please don't eat me. I won't be resurrected in my stomach.
Oh, right, I'm coming to Minami this year.  It would be better if the dyed hair was dyed by my acquaintances or my
children.
That's how many dead people there are. They
can't be eaten. I don't know
what to do. But even if I'm eaten, I'll go back. I'll talk to Pee-chan and see. It's a
good position. So, I'm more likely to be a good person than the mayor of Chofu.  That means it's stronger,
isn't it?
Utosora
Dahlia No Did you
hear that Matsui is hitting these last three days? Yes, it
's not a good deal on YouTube,
but it's F1.  If you go to Japan, where there are no black people in the second bullet
and you can say "Boobu Tehecha Unyon", this account exists.
How many weapons were there in the stable video?
Well, since it's a phoenix, it's surprising that the 6-hour issue has been
revived and resurrected.  I made a new debut stream. I
made my debut the day before yesterday. I went to the foot and
started to revive. I'm going to go through the cutter for the first time with the barrel type kai. It's fun, but please don't die. I'm debuting on YouTube.  It's the second time. No
one cares anymore.
Bring it on, go home, I stopped it for ten minutes,
Matsumiya-san, if you use Nerima, you've given birth to a video like that,
yeah, I don't know, yeah, you're saying some pretty bad things,
there's no cheer,
Sakauchi-yo channel  Zou-un,
yo, it's nice, but I think it's pretty well-controlled and has a good image, but I've
never been published in the sake tea club,
and the monetization bread has been stripped away and everyone is a supporter of the Chichibu system.  There
was no ASMR or anything like that, but the festival is
pure, right? The government is not a money-maker, that kind of thing. I
promised to make a pledge with the town senior.
Whatever I say, everyone is right, Matsui is also very pure and I feel safe.  I guess that's
true. I'd rather go to Ina-ya. There's
no wave. I don't know
if they'll let me go to the hangar war. I don't want to go. I can't
forgive you.  It's
okay because the patty has sauce.  I'm
sure Japanese viewers don't know that.
Clyder
: Yes, there are a lot of
different prefectures. There are a lot of different sauces. The total number is for experiments.
Yes, so I moved away from Japan. I
don't know if you can eat that much without sauce.  I'm eating it,
so I'm satisfied. But I don't think it's that amazing.
How many kinds are there? It depends
on the place. Digger.
10 kinds are interesting and
many. It's a total number of nests. If you eat them together, the people will eat them.
I mean, when I was a member earlier, I said that this store is not so popular. It's
amazing. It's so cute, grandpa.  Pooh
700,000 people can do it, yeah, let's
go, I want to go, yeah, 5th place,
thank you, Maruyama sheet, English,
yeah, I think I'll try English, our, I think I can start using it,
impressions, born on the 8th, for example,
clock, yeah, mu or
Ni  It's a deck mouse made of Rakuway blankets.
Mahahaha, I
know that I know that I'm a bar shower type, you
know, well, I still don't have many anchor tabs in the snow, I
remember that wire, yeah,
lots of u 4 up,
nakon uh, the largest version  I wonder
if it will be overly sensitive, what is it now? It's really really English, uuh,
even if you do something bad and give birth, you wo
n't be barred at all,
no, it's not a job down, you gave birth, you're a
cute princess,
2 Air's Maru Guard, if you go in Japanese, it's more and more  It seems like sex is coming out, but I'm not sure
about the number of followers, so I'm going to a party
, aran
ok, I'm not sure about the waste, but I'm going to a 1 b sleeper debut, and I'm going to
Hawaii, which is said to be scary, so let's go there, don't you think?  I
'll say it, 5 minutes after eating the third one, it's
so big, if you cut it, please fly half of this small area in the area,
Rubber, oh,
Aug, do Cal,
well, there is a queer theory, hmm  Umm,
I was having fun, but wow,
where is the malice? Umm, the main store is too busy.
Eh, there's no need to hurry so please eat slowly. If you
eat quickly, you can eat a lot.
Umm, in life, you don't get full right away. What?  I'm not
full. I don't know what to do. I'm
not a guitar player. I'm eating only the left front part. I
wanted to eat ramen after that. It's
amazing. It's
amazing. I'm just a pro. I'm so excited.
Well, I ate four chickens and two
7-minute biscuits,
and one chocolate biscuit, and
when I was about to eat a cup noodle for the pennant, my
friend stopped me. Can you fly with a
liver? Amazing, I
can't eat it.
How much do you eat when you eat the most in that way
? No, but I've never eaten face-to-face. I think I've never eaten alone. I've left a lot of leftovers on my device. Yes, but I'm hungry, yes,
that one person is not there, so I'm eating that
much.  But it's different.
Well, for example, in America, well, I'm not focusing on the eyes, but well, it's
really big because you can eat it, isn't it? It's a dragon, isn't it? It seems
that American-sized cola drinks are also really
big, so in Japan, there are dog-sized ones.  But,
hehe ...
-2
Yes, the town is set, no,
I'm sorry, I'm going to sign a club, so if there's a
media person, it's fine now, right
? It's fine, but the
town world is fine, huh, what's that? I
don't know  No, I see. Well,
if you're reborn, you're not counting from age 0. If
you want to say what you want, it's
small. Please, Arne, it's three days before.
Bach.
So, my third son was born on the third day and he's a baby.  It's
not easy to understand with a baby, everyone, what are you doing?
Wa cute,
pink ring game,
milk, drink breast milk, once you learn, ah, breast,
breast,
what are breasts?  That's what I'm saying, um,
Tano, the
difference
is, well, it's cute, I mean, I'm
embarrassed to give fruit, but I
can't eat it in the area because I'm nervous about it, so I just
put rice eating on the wireless network, and the
speed is twice as fast.  Hey,
the festival is me, it's delicious,
but even without any sauce, it tastes the same, well, hmm, I
don't remember the door, yeah,
Kenta, it's not in the mouth, so I'll remember it and drink it, I wonder what the punchline is,
but I'm not watching
[Music] It
's not like Goon has a weak taste, or anything. In Japan, even if you put it together, they don't call it water. [Music] That's not the case, but I've never had it. I've heard of it being turned.  Everyone's role is someone else's. Internet scars.
Hmm.
Hey hey, I'm
safe. Hey, I'm
surprised you haven't eaten Unzen yet.
Well, this is the first time I've had a proper conversation with the Self-Defense Forces,
so I want to talk. So cute. I'm thinking of singing a song today. Umm,
what was it again? How do I search for that?
What will you do?
If you don't do this, it won't come out. It's full of stuff, so
it's 4 pre-la until it grows. If you make Ichi Nanae, it's
this. Idol last, idol rusk. You
can meet 6 random items.
This duet is going to
go with this, but there are
two more. The two guides just came out.
Well, is this okay? Eh, Shimo-
kun, I'll eat what I like. I'll
eat a lot of food at the festival machine. Come on,
today  We were going to sing a song together,
so I think the wind is cute. Let's do it together,
senpai. I
want to know the inflammation of the children in that house.
Where  The
overall impression is that no one is more than one. So,
this is what came out, right?
Mr.'s a. I
wonder if he'll come out here. So, can we
go from above? Yes.
Who is it now?
Just about that.  That girl is our Marnie.
Mr. Niki had a replacement for the earth-facing line. My
sister and Neu-cutter and
Calliope-chan were the ones who finished it.
But the rap was really 9 minutes. I
wondered what kind of girl she was, so I looked into it.  The moment I heard the rap by Tete,
I knew he was a bundle of talent. I don't know what it was,
but I don't understand his weak rap and I don't understand English that well, but I was still blown away. He's so
cool.  That's why she's my wife. She's
really strong,
with pink hair, but she's a bit of an older sister type. I
thought she was cute and mature, but she's not that cool.
But, I think...  Yeah,
this is the best Bible for the inside. It's a
race. I know it's a cleaning. The
city council is Minorin, the best government, and so on. It's the same as the end.
Hmm
, rar
Well, that's right, isn't it? It
's everyone's moon.
Wait, I
think this is the cleaning staff. For example,
Haru-chan says it's for appearances, so I
think that's proof.
Ah, when you get to know her, she's pure,
no, Grenadier.  It's a neat and clean name, but when you get to know it, you're a customer who saves water. That's how long you should wait. It's
not good, is it? There are some
people who are not good.
Even in the base game, it's more about living than Hatayama-chan. I
have the image of Kiba Taiko saying it a lot.  Nehataru-chan, well, I'm sure you're
saying that Tone is the worst here, but I don't really understand what everyone else is saying. But we're
not the first one.  Hey, what's up with Ana-chan? She's kind of a
clumsy image. Thank you. I'm
not going to hit her. I think only Ponko Abusa is good.
I guess if you give birth to Arou, you'll get that message.
There are differences in the sex selection, but it's
okay to do it without it. Pepe, do your best, you can't do your best. Bye-bye.  What is Yokoi Balloon?
I think it's amazing that she's such a mother. Yes, I
have to tell her that I was already married to Enzyme Love on your day. I definitely didn't go to Space Listan. I
mean, Roy is here, but it's okay.  I'll definitely tell you when it happens. You're going to do it, right? Don't say it's
okay. I
invited the sweater to my house and didn't tell him about it. That's so
rude. It looks like we're going to fight, so I'm a good kid.
Deep,
various things, Mengqiarzu.  I think I probably wouldn't have been found out if I hadn't said anything. I'm
sure I'd be able to get away with it. I wrote "Are-kaa-san" when I was a kid and I'm also looking at Twitter and stuff, but I'm really not good at it. I'm
not good at taking baths.  It's
not like the usual "your illustrations are good" kind of thing. It's a
different material. It's much
more like "let's have some tea" than the Janeno that I asked to bring it.
Dandy is actually praising it.  But I don't know how many times I've been in the kitchen.  I
think you can make a living from just one illustration,
so I guess it's fine. But, well, it's
amazing, and I'm feeling a new antidote. I'm
watching the stream too.  I know that you can speak Japanese quite well. Oh
yeah, but when I make a direct comment, you definitely reply in Japanese. Let's
try it.
[Music]
Canoe, I
don't like flats.  I really like the word "big" but I also
like it. It's good, it's good, I wonder what the boobs are like. I like
big or small breasts. I love Aso's size. Seriously.
So I started selling stuff with that old man, and I love it. I
can't even tell Ina-chan's breasts, but I
love Kamen Rider. Size doesn't matter, you can see the goodness of the girl, so it
's a good example.  I
know it's real leather but it's tangled
Amelia-san, at the beginning, you often put on a coat, you know, you know, before that current, you were
talking about Kanemoto Haro, but
when you were at the Court Hotel, you
were like, Boober, I'm
hiding, you know, it's true, it's also  I don't know if I even
said that, but I was surprised by the reception. After talking for four minutes, I thought, "Ame-chan is like that too." I was
hiding it as "Fufufufufufufufufufufufufufufufufufu" and then I thought, "I see, it's cute, but..."  Nyan, I've
been looking at my boobs since my grandfather came, so I'm not going to look at them anymore. I'm going to
shake them, swaying them,
ana
rar,
natural Yurakami, I'm going to shake them, I'm going to
say something, brother, eh, I'm going to feel
like a boo boo, Pekoros, annu, bug,
nyo  Her face is so
cute, I
wonder what it is, it feels like I'm looking at a pet, I'm not late, that town is nice, I don't know, but
still, I can't help but
look at her, I
wonder what it's like, she's so cute, I almost want to  I
really like the song, Mitake. She's good at it and
she's cute. And she's
so tiny. When are they all lined up? Wow,
look at that! It's so
cute!  Well, everyone is cute, but I can't swim, you know?
Why don't you say there's a swim ring? So you're going north from Atlantis, okay? I'm
out of luck, but somehow I managed to get 99 sen
Saipoon 9000 yen recently.  I'm not so sure, but I'm older
than you. What's that?
Mommy,
thank you for bringing luck to women. I don't
remember it. It's a shark, so the qualifying round is the lowest punishment.
That's right. The reason is that it's autumn. Let's guess,
your y is 8th place.
Ryo-chan was a piece of crap.
Ah, please
tell me about the Aion cosplay that happened before you met.
Ah, I don't know what Matsuki is, but I
like the way he looks. The Chon2 Matsuri Baron family scanned it and it was orange.  mosquito
First of all, I thought it was cute. The
interior design is so cute.
I did,
so it's a and it's the first one, so go and see it, I had it at home, I
have it in Iran, Nanao City, it was a bit messy at one point, it's cannibalism, it's like
studying,
it's in the sky  It's a fun broadcast,
but when I'm feeling down I
want to watch it. It makes me want to cheer up, so it's really
cute.
So, having 1 yen is a good deal.
This is the deputy chief of the department. I've
come back to life, and I've
done a lot of different jobs up until now. It's
been a sweet life, and I've
ended up doing the same thing over and over again.
When I was thinking about what to do at the shrine this time, I
decided to
focus on the first
fool's meal.  r Hey, the best thing in the world is the upper and lower sides. 6 items and items came. pivo
Why did you write it down? My mother likes cheeks, but I'm not sure.
That pex bar is not taken.  Anti-
gold crispy chicken inside
U burger and then Yahoo and No. burger too
Ah, part 1 area, I think the child is in it
Petit Yamasu, next to it, lick it, there's no air leak or stick in it
Well, it's not delicious, but I guess that's true, isn't it delicious? There's piano beef. A-bee
minutes.
Yes, there are various Maeda, Kassin, and various safe pots. There are
21 muddy items.  Surf anytime,
that's it, but
there's also the straight fist, but
please don't understand the question of fighting,
there's no cat, the part is always on the chain, it's like a hood,
[Music],
well, first of all, it looks like a hood  No, if you're wondering why I have this knowledge, then what is it?
Seriously, everyone is
like, "Ahhh, it's interesting."
Manya e 4 e I love it and it's late, eh, it's cute, isn't it
?
nc The cute Nakasha with the ceremony is
Sueo Senpai's Machisen and Koyabu Saru, yeah, I told my city hall, it's
like an 8-year senior and a real live  People who say they fell in love are pretty painful, pets, that's right, I fell
in love with it when I found out about it in a good spot,
so if you ask Ryu, he'll say no, I
think he knew about it,
Band-Aid, yes, that's
right, there's a forward going, so it's
Band-Aid Girl
Ah, it's not that it was good, but it's fine
. So I want you to know, it was necessary. I do
n't need a tsun brancher, do you? I
like English, really? I'm not good at back and stuff, Vanguard, after all.  I've
never been to Tancandy, but
if you recommend it, I'd like to try using the bar. Represented by daizu.
Everyone, even men, are using it.
5e anchor band.
5tei ok. It's
good to move.  Nice cat, Chaoa Tauka
Ah, this is a kitten, Ato fish
udon. Hmm, ah,
but I can't read kanji.
Ah, I can read it. Lotus is, of course, returning the disk with a bullet.
That's right.
Japanese is no problem.
Then it's good to play with a flock.
Which one?  Either way is
fine, either way, it seems like it's no good, so if it's the first half of this kind of blazing kisai komachi, then I'm a shell, so what about
something? ok, something like champuru,
it's cute,
then I'll go, I said I did it now, so it's big and small,
Okia
Mommy says "Let's
go then"
Listen
[Music] I
understand hypnosis, huh?
10, that's the key, right
?
[Music]
I'm an
old man with stomach cancer,
licking that embarrassing thing  Even if there is, it is
strong
yeah
[music]
ni
monkey nua I'm
waiting
yeah yeah
[music]
me
haaaa
[music]
ran
That's what it's like to
continue to the ocean
ono
yoaaaaa n
een
yeah yeah
[music]
he
nenuo
[music]
ni
[music] I
want to eat Iki
ni
[music]
alena
me
[music]
[applause]
nani
[music]
No, you
say it
[music] I
want to see money
ani
Ikumi
[music]
Elsera life
4 ni
survive
me You're
annoying
me
[music]
hane
me
yeah
[music]
Aaaaaah
[applause]
ran
[music]
rar
Finger fence etc. It
was good 4 Anyu Reina It was really good but the first 23 flowing is too fast before that
From the middle, it's 6 Gotsui no Uchigu
[music] It
was good yeah yeah yeah  It's
not the same as before, as expected, the song is so good, I can drink Incheon, after all, I'm a
rocking Liger, I
don't like it, so hurry up Joel
Care is in the way, so it's cute. Give me some
fast food.
Take it to a certain area. It's a replacement for a piece.
Hi, Cutter is already good.
Fishing is a little more like Christie. It's about the front of the line. The
best thing is crispy pain.  I'm going to send it to the mainland and miss the spin-off. Hmm, it's like it's
crispy, isn't it? It's good to go against it. Let
's eat a mountain. I want to sing something else. I've been
thinking about it for a long time.  Yes, it calms me down, my brain is like a fireworks display, but it
's not here, it's like a fireworks display, I
know it, I know it, but that's Yonezu 3 part, I don't know, male patcho, I do
n't know how to move, can I expose the mysterious enemy, can I
sing with the sound?  No, I don't know the nobility, so I've
seen that movie. I
went to see it alone at night,
but how was it? The
music was good and
I played the game.  2-
armed turn  It
was number 5. The song was really good, even with the complex sounds.
Darkness. Which one is better? Ordinary beauty. That's okay. You
can't see it. 1-1.
What is this about Hyahotepura? Honest.  Why does the house smell so honest? I can't lie.
url Haha,
yes, I can see it in the 18th of the 2nd row. I got it.
Hold on a bit more. I'm in the car here. Please. Ah,
there's fishing gear.
Which mother is next
?
If you say so, well, I'm going to come.
Next is a good one for the skin. I
think I'll leave it to the main male.
It's a good song. I
was able to catch the wind here.  It's
better to divide the family into parts.
Please don't come.
Aguila,
right? The
intention is rising. Sing well.
None.
Hawaii, how are you?
Wow, Vienna darts!
Poke hugs  Teminyauiko time
Oh wow, I want to sing the 9th song with my daddy. Sing it with a clean feeling. Okay, I'll do my best in politics too. I think I
put it out.
[Music]
Hmm, I just looked around that day. I
still remember it.
[Music]
On the boat.
The words I carved into
your heart, the
waves of the sea, my
feet
running past you,
Ahhhh,
Iuuuah,
ni, It's
just sunset, and the
number of nights we held hands has passed, somehow,  The
child's pyon is
waaay,
after that, you'll be the same 7,
so why is it possible for a woman to do it,
but it's a
machine that moves one by one, just like the waves and the
anxiety that often follows.
[Music]
me
Drink  Nua
Kase
Yarie Duckett Man
Hey Hey
[Music]
Ah ah ah
dan Chair Hunting Style
yeah
[Music]
Emo Hey Hey Mym There was a
cute fireworks I saw on this day on the road
Ah,
that day actually  I
still remember the beach we went to
[Music]
Ahhhhhh, it was
two seasons ago,
your castle
[Music]
se
Humble
[Music] There's
no high-speed rail,
this
was a shame
[Music]
[Applause]
ni
[Music]
ni tana ni ni
ne
[Music]
Ahh ...
Music]
Well, how can I make people applaud? I've already decided to give it to them,
but I can still applaud. So, there's a lot of beautiful weather. If
singing along with Leprechaun's "All Losers" was really his goal for April, then  The festival is also
held
on the 10th, and then the other members will
be there individually. It's twenty-one and twenty-two, so that house is fun.  I have a few
Ah, so, my senior's town, Zlata, bene, Hmm, so that
's why, I'm nervous about not listening, I'm going to clean up, c, something, a, what should I do, what should I do, I'm with River-san, but I'm
already nervous, so I might be shaking from the rehearsal  No, I'll do
my best, Gamba 4 liters, Kiyoe-chan too, is the same, ism is free, isn't it? I want to sing it, let's do our best, each other Aldi, yes, time is running out, Magenpan, yes, next time, please, Cant-chan
Game Ah,
that Tiara-chan's house is now a place where he is very slightly Casper, an
idol who wants to meet someone, or a character who is dancing, so it's highly likely that there is no character, and
then someone holds a stick and you continue  So
[Music]
Kahn, it stands out, then, it's changing, it's Casper's family, I do
n't know if it doesn't exist, I hope not, do you have kids, then I
hope you don't, pray,
So this time, I want to bother you with the fact that it was cut off. Is there any announcement
or something?
Thank you for wearing it today.
Tomorrow, yeah, that hole episode will be a sad song comeback, won't it
? I'm not sure about the English songs, but I'm nostalgic about them. I still don't know what to do with those lame songs. I'm looking forward to it.  I have a channel, so
please
subscribe to it. It's not like I can say it in English.
But I can't say it. It's not like I can say it. It's like I'm
going to be buried.  Hmm,
Jan
Goo, Kiyan-chan, if
you're me, I'm not Abe, I'm not a pa, ah,
subscribe to the channel, ah, ah, Ayana-chan's house, I'm
not doing it,
me,
he, it's
a room, ah, I
put a knife in it, but it
's a role, this sound is good  Well, my father ate it with me too. It's
cute, so let's finish today.
Injection,
to the swamp, and
other treasures. I'll do some buying and selling at the end. I'll
blow it.
Yohaisen by Aa ...
Ahhhhhhh
[music]
Hmm 9
[Music]
Chong