thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you foreign
[Music]
foreign
laughs
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I know I'm not moving that's not working
either
also I I know we're Machu Picchu Machu
picu is we all know that
that was just me testing something
I just really quickly wanted to switch
locations Hello Kitty
it
so I mean if nothing's moving
like
how is it now
when are you hearing me
are you
what's going on
you're not really reacting to me
oh is is the lag really bad
when are you seeing this
on it
what
holding for what
oh
wow that was
that was like two minutes until you
heard my kikiriki
oh
foreign
that sucks oh
two two minutes I can't even get help
from you then and I will need a lot of
help
I say A you say b a
audio is coming up I don't know what the
[\h__\h] that is that has nothing to do with
anything else
uh
yeah okay and
this is
the best nobody still love me
there's still no bee
Ten Years Later
no V
uh okay
um that is way worse than I expected
I've streamed from hotels before
in Hokkaido in Seoul in other places
yeah that bee was like two minutes late
no joke
[Laughter]
you're from the future are you though
are you though
no buffering yeah but this is terrible
this game I would need your help to play
this
tocio
that's way worse than I thought it would
be that really [\h__\h] sucks
um
uh well
I will try to find
a solution
ever stream at other people's place or
maybe someone has a useful good
um pocket Wi-Fi
drop it to 480p
this means I won't wouldn't be really
able to stream the valkyrie connect
thing I mean that's a sponsored stream
I'm not gonna stream a sponsors dream
with 360p
uh
[Music]
uh I can I have a I have a pocket Wi-Fi
but
I don't think it will be really better
because I'm right now I'm even connected
to a cable
um Lan cable
um
I can I can try
we can try I'm gonna try to wait
um
let me try just I need to get it oh [\h__\h]
oh
I didn't charge it though but it's still
looking good
in terms of battery
it just kind of sucks that you guys are
not able to really communicate
um okay so I didn't log in on my
um laptop before
so I gotta put in the password
okay
um
okay laptop is connected let me try
although it doesn't really matter on my
camera I guess because
probably not gonna move anyway
wait but then I have to
say AUC oh I say A you say b a b
I say A you say b a b
oh
oh wait that was really fast let's go
it's the present
switching to the
pocket Wi-Fi at least fixed our lag for
now how is uh is it like buffering
okay let's go to my loading screen and
see how bad I mean for you Jill Geo
guesser is not gonna really be relying
on that but let's let's see the bit
right do we want to see the bit right
let's see
foreign
[Music]
you know this and other games I was
planning to play like slay the spire
I don't think I really need like a good
bit right right
okay let me try maybe with the with the
pocket Wi-Fi maybe I can
connect the
my movement to the Mata you wanna I
wanna see myself moving don't you want
to see me move too you like to move it
move it you want to move it move it well
this is but this is why I was you know
thinking so far ahead
[Music]
you know when I said that when I was
still in Austria
um
I said that I I just in case that my
internet is gonna be [\h__\h] and my at the
place where I stay
um
plugum is still very much there by the
way
um that's why I was trying to plan as
many collabs as possible
I was trying to get one going for today
but
um spontaneously but nothing nothing
worked
and maybe tomorrow
um
is the medicine helping oh I left it I
left it by accident
um by Denmark's place
okay
but I mean I don't cough anymore I have
no cough attacks it's just uh
what no are you is it because the
connection is gone or is it because I
forgot the medicine
hello
what why are you guys like oh no oof
the message okay okay did we not have
like any like stops yet in
let me hide this
no
[Music]
no no
um
okay smooth no like for now okay okay
now give me a second I'm gonna
experiment you know this is the first
stream from this hotel so
we're gonna have some experiments yo
but life today
[Music]
um
mmm
[Music]
you're losing me what do you mean you're
losing me
don't lose me
don't lose me I say hey you say b a
let me hear you say okay okay that's
still pretty good
okay okay
um okay if it doesn't work like this I
have
I have my secret recipe
oh the password one one one one
um
[Music]
yeah that really doesn't seem like it
wants to work
should we
I feel like some people need to refresh
because some people are still saying B
Lee
refresh refresh
we're fresh
I think we have to give up on the life
to do
so
it's just gonna be
that which I don't like it I don't like
it I don't like doing it this way
it's lame
um
but for today okay because I want to
play this game now I prepared it I
bought a subscription
um
I'm sorry guys you never know like
beforehand how good is the
soundproofing and the internet gonna be
well now we know it's [\h__\h] although you
know it's just unstable because when I
did a
um
when I did a test
uh earlier today like in the noon it was
like
um
I think it was like at least 50 upload
well
upload download somewhere around that
that was actually a bit a lot better
than when I streamed at General's place
hmm okay anyway oh well oh
okay
yeah it is prime time but still
okay well all right then
all right then
and I have my two skirts
shall we move OBS back here good luck
guessing
I I will need your help
okay
um
uh uh
like I test I looked for where it shows
where it would show
a location but
I didn't see anything anyway
um
shall we start
which one is which one do I try if I
just want to be randomly placed
somewhere in Europe
because there's a European Union
official map but wait no I'm not in
Europe let's do a specific country
uh like let's say
let's start with Japan but are those
like fixed locations or are they random
locations
if I play this official Japan map isn't
it just like
well-known places rope
oh it is random
like in the middle of nowhere okay okay
okay
I want to do that
okay okay
what's the difference between single
player and challenge
this challenge where you you can't move
around or
see my random semi semi-random
a timer ah
oh well okay
let's go Japan Japan
uh doco
oh that looks like it could be kind of
in the North
uh South sorry I mean south I mean
because of I don't know maybe not let's
go let's walk a little bit
it's loading kind of slow but
the vegetation to me looks like could be
self but
I don't know
I have to find like a
a clue
oh
no no no no no no no no no
is this is this
is this somewhere where I would know it
okay so
the weather looks bad is the weather
ever bad in Okinawa oh
a resort
what that that's
that's definitely well first of all
along the coast
and second of all
it might really be self
wait is this really a random location
or
nakama Port fun
Waterfall oh
oh
should I just keep on walking
oh it's not blurring yeah I mean it
always needs a lot of the moment it
needs a moment
it needs a moment to
find the pixels locations IP addresses
I've got some clothes oh I do I know I
don't know oh I see the front of the car
what a nice job huh
should we just
no no
no
[Music]
um
where where
[Music]
I mean I would have to like go really
really close to find those clues that we
just heard
but I'm thinking
it's definitely Okinawa
okay at least the kyushi area
maybe I just go for like kagoshima
really
saw one of this these islands
here let's go here
well it is an island
I mean if it if they put you on one of
these random Islands
[\h__\h]
how would I know
okay okay oh
we're at least not so much
countrysideish anymore
right
oh yeah this is oh
that cute real look you real estate
I thought oh like it was just for trains
good all right so are we
are in Kanto then
well because like trains in Kanto
kind of like in Tokyo
uh hello
used up my bandwidth oh [\h__\h] yeah I do
think I have a maximum bandwidth
are we back
I was wondering why it's not loading
there you go we're back we're back for
how long
we're doing this now guys there's no no
going back now on it
but
I
guess are you still hearing me
uh
let's go back let's go back
oh oh oh I see we're in The Matrix
one step further we're in the void on
the back we're in the boy
mmm yummy
Internet please oh maybe we can ask her
where the [\h__\h] am I
the [\h__\h] am I
um
she does she says Ah no no English
oh sure I'm sorry for bothering you
let's go this way I think that that one
is cursed
foreign
okay let's just
um
I guess because I'm not getting anywhere
but since it's older cue
and this is already knowledge that other
people maybe don't have
so I'm just gonna say it's somewhere in
Tokyo
um
I wouldn't know if the otaku real
estates are outside of Tokyo too but
let's just say
oh is that what they mean area well I
mean we all know I'm in Tokyo
oh did I click on that
yeah
ah no I just clicked something
I guess I just clicked something
I'm confused
[Music]
yes I think we're fine in terms of that
or I'd guess
oh I mean I was right with my guess that
she would be within the boundaries
of okay but wait that's uh that's
Kanagawa though I I did say though
towards Canada remember that remember
that sport smart
no it's so bad I got 4 000 points for
that 4 000.
oh
nice flowers we're on the countryside
there's a big bridge over there
okay
but I promises I guess a normal not
really famous bridge although it looks
kind of cool
oh [\h__\h]
oh
[\h__\h] bridge I love that joke so much
foreign
I mean
it's it's summer so it looks nice
anywhere in summer in Japan
let's check out that bridge and see if
there's any big street signs
okay
stop
[Music]
um
that doesn't tell me anything that's
just about like random [\h__\h]
um curve
wait wait wait wait
what does it say there
on his truck
is the truck still there when I move
over there
truck ah the truck is there
I want to read like the company name or
so
we shut the street are we ah there it is
oh there it is there's a is a truck
going backwards or am I going but I
guess I'm going backwards
oh
no
truck
no this this area ain't telling me
anything
I want to see the truck
I want to read that
that that's the kanji for North but the
rest I can't read because it's too
blurry
um
should I go this way
traffic sign oh yeah I didn't really
nothing so far I didn't really see
anything that would help
uh maybe after this one we can look we
could go
can I not go any further that side
hmm
what
what how do these buttons work
where am I going
it
is that where it cuts off
click on the road instead of the arrow
ah okay okay okay
that was their eyes are red oh
the seasons changed
is that a graveyard
welcome
and I still can't go any further with
the mouse though
oh now the arrows work again okay
where the [\h__\h]
ing
it's really a graveyard oh it is oh
spooky
that's that's spooky
Kawaii quite
haunted man
I got Issa guide
hey
I think it's also summer again
all right which side also can I now
can I now look at some street oh no
nothing nothing yet let's go this way
is that my grave no I don't have a grave
because you know the fingers that is one
cost
that I will never have in my life
because I I will not
I will not perish
look at the sign on
uh oh
well that kind of helps although that
could still be really really far away
but Sendai
Sendai I know
but the three four six is not how many
kilometers it is right it's just um the
road
okay
well then let's uh go by that send I
should be like above Tokyo
so I hear yeah yeah yeah maybe we can
even find the street like uh three four
six Highway
uh-huh
ah free oh there it is oh see it is
pretty far but you know it's also pretty
long so it could be
anywhere ah but the three four six goes
on the coastline by a coastline and I
don't think we've really seen
uh
of course there's just not seen a river
right there's a river there so where
does the where does the 346 go over a
river to the Mata I lost it is that the
hey I'm playing it I'm playing it guys I
think I'll do voice in America okay
there it is and here's a here's a river
um but there's surely on the rivers that
it goes over too but do we just want to
go for like this one
foreign
from my bro and my mom because like
every time when I visited
um my mom in the past years when my
brother was also there those two were
always playing
um they were always playing
this game together and they're like so
good at it and so I saw them looking for
like the name of the streets like the
numbers of the streets and then finding
the highways on the map and then yeah so
this is a strategy I learned from them
okay let's see
of course I mean it could have been
anywhere on that long Highway
but that's hella good
that's really good
28 kilometers is nothing
yeah oh
huh
we're we're not even on the street
s
this
responds here in places like this we're
on foot
I mean we're kind of in the mountains I
would say
in a shrine but there's a million
shrines
foreign
[Music]
I think I lost connection
um
I think I will as it ain't you saying B
oh foreign
maybe we're back now because OBS told me
we're offline and then we're online
oh I think we're back okay hey you say B
B
hello you hurt my windows that was
obvious
oh hi B my heart I suddenly lose you
without any warning and suddenly you're
gone
um it's not good for my heart and my
mental health
hmm
hello
Guru Guru again
okay