[Music]
me
do
[Music]
you
do
[Music]
oh that was a lot of excitement
i am so excited today i was listening to
a lot of mozart
ooh mozart
yes
you like
sorry
oh yeah i do like mozart mozart is such
a genius oh thank you he's my bff
oh wow
but
i mean
the last
the f and bff
i'm not sure since he's
pregnant
he's been dead for a while not probably
yes yes he's been dead for a while
but yeah we used to be friends i i i was
marie antoinette in one of my previous
lives
oh wow yes
no wonder your party outfit's so fancy
oh thank you thank you yes well
um
nice to
meet you cronie
yeah
nice to meet you it's our
collab one on one
oh yeah
you look like me you look like me
hey
it's like that one spider meme i don't
know you weren't why do you have more
armor than me why is your skirt black is
this like what happens when you play
online and you play the same character
character and they look a little bit
different
wait because i don't have um what are
you wearing oh i'm wearing my my red
skirt you're wearing a black skirt
and hands do you
what's your what's your armor i'm
wearing studded leather
oh
uh wait what was that
what was the enhancing button again
inventory
pressing all the buttons i want the
enhanced button
yeah we're wearing the same we just have
different colors of our bottoms
i think this is so that we can just like
so that we don't look too similar
let's look at mine mine was always like
this
really
really yeah oh i think it's because of
our boots
ah oh maybe
let me take off my boots
no wearing chain boots
my boots don't change ah cause okay your
uh mine don't change my looks but your
looks are changed by your body
the mystery has been cleared up
well well well these super strong super
talented
amazon girls are going to slay some
disgusting monsters outside there in the
world we're probably not gonna
get that far but i just thought it would
be cool to play diablo together because
crony started playing it too right
where's your where's your sense of
optimism we could get far
no we're not gonna get far but that's
okay
um
have you already
taken like accepted the quest the first
quest from
here
the first radiments lair act two the
first one the first crowd yes oh you
have it but you didn't start it yet
right
no then we shall do it together
we gotta go into the sewers
sewers okay are you using
mainly the bow or mainly the spare
[Music]
uh mainly the bow me too
i tried to last time i played it i tried
to switch
uh but i i don't know i don't think i
did a good job at switching
i think w switch yeah yeah but it's just
like i can't think of it i keep on
attacking them on close combat with my
bow
so let's be shitty yeah i heard you're
not very good at the game that's good
[Laughter]
but you know the the point is to have
fun yeah um yes yes yes
i'm already doing it with you you're in
this dude
yeah yeah but
you're dead
what
it's a girl or is that mine shouldn't be
no no girl is mine her name is anna
yours is a dude
yeah his name is
niraj mirage
yeah maybe maybe anna and
love can be a couple
oh already that's a that's a quick
shipping that's sailing okay
um
about yeah before we go are you like do
you have like potions and stuff you good
is your inventory empty we gotta
probably sell a million things i hate i
hate the fact that oh i heard that you
had issues with like the inventory
because of also because of your ocd
it's just just a teensy little bit
i can understand though it's so where
are you going it's so triggering do you
want to sell things
it's like in the middle
selling places in the middle here and
buying i'm trying to look for a stash
because that's where i usually
here here here
yes okay
you have some fancy things in your stash
are you hiding diamonds in this stash as
well crony
i saw you hiding diamonds in the
minecraft stash what do you what do you
mean i don't i
and then you you didn't want chats to
see for what reason
oh
just you know
i guess wouldn't they be like amazed
that you have a lot of diamonds why why
why are you ashamed crony
it's it's not about being ashamed it's
more like uh
you know it might give
people bad ideas of chats like oh you
know they have uh crony has this and
this kind of
thing so you think they're gonna tell
someone else and that person's gonna
steal from you no way
potentially no who would you fake the
girls
i
mean did take some stuff from me but she
didn't she didn't know it was my stuff
she thought it was automatically
generated but i think by now she knows
she knows your boxes are your boxes no
it's gonna steal from you you're
paranoid crony
just a little teensy bit i mean after
after what happened with um
oh irish
um
oh oh irish stole from you for real
sauce
no iris i i hope not but
follow me by the way you talk
right yes i can't multitask um
where do i find um the potion oh you
want to buy potions uh
perhaps i didn't does deckard no
pickard
potions lysander
what do you have trade he has potions oh
yes
iris explode everything says chet
did iris let you make your things go
boom
i can't remember off the top of my head
yeah you of course you can't remember
you're just not
i'm sure you know exactly what happened
you remember
hey let's not sort the details you're an
interesting type of person crony i need
to get to know you more
you're mysterious
yes thank you um but my sense of
direction is very horrible
whoa
thank you
i think the sewers is it is it the the
this this place here oh sue it's level
one yes i actually when i played the
the alpha the closed alpha from this
game
um i went past this point i already did
the sewers
in the alpha but um that's pretty much
all as far as i got off just the suit
was in a little bit more
okay
okay let's do this
let's do this
let's find what do we what are we doing
uh find rather man's lair in the ah yeah
that's a hammer i think it's a hammer
i need to fight i usually just go around
hoping that
[Music]
i'll find something at the end of it
no we have to put iron we have to fight
someone who has the hammer i think he
stole it or so
where'd you go oh there you are i am the
one that looks like you
sisters where are the enemies
where are they peaceful you need to make
a party what let's stand still crony
crony
we need to make a party
can i make a party
we need press p ah
except oh now we're in a party oh so now
we share exp a lot
and oh i guess quest items oh [\h__\h]
oh man i'm i'm poisoned
oh you radioactive
radio ragnan
oh my goodness no panic no panic yeah
you're shooting in the middle of the
enemies maybe do some more
kiting i saw your fight against uh
what's what's her name um anderium yeah
i thought it was pretty damn good
i take the dummy really it was just sad
that such a great job at kiting like i i
wasn't able to do the kite thing that
well yeah [\h__\h]
you're gonna be my kite bunny cronie
hide those enemies take that damage yeah
why is
not fighting [\h__\h] can you fight hello
yeah i have the same problem with
another girl named um
i'm pleased are you collecting i'm
trying i'm pleased i can't grand charm
okay
how do we share items there should be
like a random um
like item goes into random person's
inventory
thingy really there's not as i'm saying
it there should be as in we need it
because otherwise i'm going to pick up
better everything like the greedy [\h__\h]
i am
what's a squish
eh eh first to pick it up to get it okay
well crony um
first who sees it
gets it finders keepers i see okay
just fair
you want to go there oh you want to go
there
because i think that place is blocked
off
calmly
over here i'm thinking i'm bad shy
are you kidding me
i'm sorry
how do you play
the apple together when when you can't
decide when when you play with greedy
people when it's like cooperative
competitive games
okay i'll give you more things because
you're kohai now i i need to take care
of you
crystal sword
oh that looks fancy
get out
i need mana i hate going back to the
town
to sell items so much so
at least now we have two inventories
until oh god i'm poisoned
all of this is bringing back bad
memories it's okay
oh yeah and dario was poisoning too yeah
how long did it take a shrine for you
oh yay
how long it took me to kill on dario
yeah uh chet how long did it take me oh
my god there's a lot of enemies
cats tell me
i do not remember it's been so long
wait did you play it didn't you play it
two months ago or so
it feels like five months ago
five months there's a triad crony and
the wolfman you take that i have to i
don't have space
oh no i'm overburdened again
don't lie didn't take me an hour what
are you talking about you did it really
fast i i rc what does that mean i
i-i-r-c
if i recall correctly oh
wow i can't take the rest
okay don't take the trident
yeah
but we should probably go to the city in
a moment
that city first try did i first try
i think like in the alpha
i had some troubles
uh
but then when i did it again after the
alpha i did it first try maybe
oh wow
yeah but that doesn't mean anything it
was a horrible fight
no wait just kidding no i think it was
actually really not that bad now that i
try to think back
i was probably not that bad
have you played the original before uh
when i was like
nine years old or so my mommy she's a
gamer and she loves diablo too she could
probably totally um lead us for the
whole game and play the like she how do
you say it as she could um
she could carry us yeah and put so i saw
him playing and then sometimes i would
play around i wouldn't get very far but
my mommy was playing it so i would play
a little bit but most of the game was
really scary so i couldn't play very
much
which might be scary i could never get
past the
the what was the name
what was this
oh my god what was the name of the
the first that i never could get past
the first the one in the graveyard uh
chad help me graveyard blood raven yeah
you remember the first
boss that you have to kill
oh
yeah the one in the graveyard
i could never get past that one so
i was quite the chicken gold gold gold
[Laughter]
seem very excited about the gold
teamwork crony teamwork
teamwork i don't know
no but let's go
should we go back should we go back is
your inventory full yet
it is full yeah mine too kind of
yeah i should kill these
skeletons yes you kill i collect items
oh what
i'm so close
i think we're doing great so far
yeah this is a lot better than whatever
my playthrough was it's more fun playing
together than playing alone
yeah there's a lot more action yeah
it's more fun this is not enough i i i
know that diablo 2
is kind of like
like online play
is what it's known for well people
really enjoy about it but i never played
it online until now
yeah um i played the other one
whoa
you can take the little oh it's
it's damaged
i take the gold you take the damage
level
okay i'm so sorry
i can't stop i'm a bird i like shiny
things i can't help this
oh you can take it and it's damaged guns
are you able to use my portal oh yeah
you were yeah
let's sell some stuff
i get to save scrolls nice yeah the next
one you're gonna open okay
so let's see i was identified first
i want this and i already have something
and then i sold it
oh that's pretty cool i got it
you know the problem with us being the
same class is that if we get bows and
stuff that are good then we got a fight
over it but no we don't have to find the
word i already collected it so it's mine
did you get a good one i got a better
one than my current one yeah
damn i got a golden um arrow that is uh
two hand damage five to twelve my
current one is
two to nine
and it got enhanced damage maximum
damage one two three fire damage poison
damage fire resist
do you want my old one
no i think i'm
good but you know what i'm selling yours
two to nine
no
i think mine's a little better
but i can sell it
[Applause]
oh something
else ah you must wait a short time to
trade with that player but why
go oh
diamond
thank you you're welcome i am i'm in
your dev oh i could just drop it on the
ground since we're the only ones in the
game true you have to accept the the
trade by the way oh
check
okay
thank you for cleaning up my inventory
that was all i really wanted
hello
thank you i'm so hashtag blessed
going well so far
using cronie to get more items
just you wait
yeah i'm gonna be salty if you get a
great item that i want them
okay ready to go back where was the
portal
down here yeah
oops well
seems uh you're not gonna hold back on
getting all your items so no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no i'm
ah here's zoomer level three come down
here
i'm i'm gonna go
i went down to the zoo level three
oh i think the portal resets uh when you
enter the portal
are you not here with me
no
what
what i i i need to oh so we can both go
to the portal to go back to the city but
we cannot both go back here's another
one i opened one but where is it for you
oh there you are okay what the hell
that's so weird so
maybe it doesn't close as long as you
don't
ah
okay i need to go after you if i call if
i open the portal then i also need to be
the last one to enter it
okay
well we got that solved understandable
die
a murder
that's the good stuff
it's a shame that they're all skeletons
why
because they're monsters they just kind
of burst open and die and there's that
satisfaction
oh my interesting thoughts mine
i can't i like how you take down your
smoothie oh
interesting thought
i'm so sorry i don't know how to hold
back
oh bailey's nest
oh yeah let's go i found the rain
crowney
you found a ring i already took it
i see
oh
oh my god i'm so sorry
why am i hurt why am i hurt because i'm
the phoenix and you shouldn't get too
close i guess oh wait i think we have
arrived because the quest love updated
oh god oh god oh god no don't die
quickly
oh god
oh i'm not ready
not ready for what
uh just oh god
just everything
did your dude die
you go oh oh you're already fighting
them oh god no you're not where'd you go
oh i'm killing you i'm killing the boss
where did you go
what
oh mirage come on man rather man
brother man you're going down only where
are you
where are you where are you
where'd you go where did you go
why are you over there why are you
somewhere else
here i'm keeping the teleport i didn't
have i'm keeping him alive for you
i don't know how much longer i can take
oh god oh no i have to kill him
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
wow he was right there it was just
around the corner and then you went in
the opposite direction i think
my mouth has been avenged oh there's a
long bow but it's blue you can take that
what's happening he didn't really uh
drop any good bows what is that what are
the books of skills
you take one i take one
okay book of skill
uh
return to atmosphere we did we did it
oh look at this
oh wow fancy you take some gold too um
yum
what's that
what is that
exploding arrow what is that don't you
want to take it
oh i have no more space i mean i can get
rid of that
wait where is the
hey shouldn't you take a scroll as well
because i already took one
oh i mean i did oh really oh okay that's
the case wait did you get the book as
well
did you get a book yeah if you right
click it then you can learn a skill for
free
yeah i got exploding error oh that's
what you mean ah
okay what should i get i already have
exploding arrow i think
yes yes all right
i know what is the quest item oh that's
the quest item that's the horizontal
scroll yeah our quest already updated uh
what should i go for
what should i use we should ah cronie
never ignore the passive and magic scope
they tell me yes yes
[Music]
you have a chance to dodge enemy
missiles when attacking or standing
still
um
i already have exploding arrow i'm free
i can't case
wait i can't take anything
because i'm overburdened again
i mean i can't take anything
it's okay we could just open up a portal
okay
i'll make a portal okay
yeah yeah
we already did the first thing crony
yeah
so easy indeed atma is here
gratitude i have spoken on your behalf
with the rest of the town's people thank
you
merchants have agreed to show their
gratitude by offering their wares and
services at lower rates
i want wares and services for freedom
please you'll find him in front of the
palace i mean
that's expecting too much out of these
people huh i'm the phoenix empress okay
yeah baby
they don't care about classes here
they're just more like i need money i
don't care if you're like thing or
oh it's completed i guess now we dump it
we lost
the decker kane
[Music]
those same majors also crafted fearsome
horadric staves
what do i see what do i hear crony
doesn't read lord by the way oh you
never read the text that they tell you
i read fast
i'll listen to their beautiful voice
collect both parts of a horadrix there's
so much stealing
oh all i see
right now are horadric this
that it's it's because
perhaps because you're with your senpai
who makes you nervous you can't focus
rogic this haradric that what what
uh okay
um
we were so quick we can already do
another one uh the horadric staff
searched the halls of the dead under the
dry hills for the cube searched a maggot
lair under the fire oasis for the shaft
search the claw viper temple for the
headpiece this is the one that i was
trying to do
until last until the very last moment
when the uh closed alpha was happening
but about to close down i think this was
the one i was doing
i was in the maggot lair i think but i
had i was
we're gonna have a pain uh in the ass
looking for this place in the first
place because i remember i was looking
for like an hour to find it
oh joy
oh pretty rain
cold resist is it gonna be cold where
we're going
maybe i should save up on this skill
hello
which one
i have one skill choice yeah
i have three in explosion
so is it good yeah it's very good we can
let everything explode together
hell yeah
yeah
yes
then
it changed
again to put things into the
hot
hot bar
[Music]
oh uh you need to drag the items in
first like in the first slot and then
you can just shift click
ah
also at first i have to fill these up oh
man yeah yeah i really don't like how
that works it's such a pain especially
when you're in the middle of a boss
fight and you run out of the items there
right you gotta fill it up while you're
fighting that's what you were doing with
under yellow i saw that
such a pain
and then i dropped my bow by accident
that was fun oh no
all right
uh
i guess let's let's go wherever the exit
i guess let's go here find something
what are we looking for
i'm not even sure what are we looking
for it's three different adventures
three different places
you took that
no no good for you you take what you see
what you can get wow
yeah that's why we need electro thingy
um
yeah just try to not get killed crony
just don't die got it yes
oh wow
oh
is the btm too loud by the way guys
how's the volume i didn't even ask you
guys yet
fashion
no more felting
oh no
don't look at it for too long it's okay
okay uh balance seems fine it's fine
okay oh good
oh good
wow
what do you call this uh it's a it's a
oh [\h__\h] ow
when when you got a
uh
something something world
eats eaten something
what do you call that
there are so many electric stuff i'm so
confused
a dog eat dog world yes doggy dog world
that's oh doggy dog that's what i wanted
to say
why does he suddenly bullet hell
right
oh i just you took that gold okay okay
i mean i mean there's so much gold
around here
okay what is head
there's a dungeon no it's nothing it's
decoration just getting ahead of itself
oh
anyway the dry hills are
that's where we get the cube that we're
looking for so we're in the right
direction
um
how long has it been welcome to holo
talk with cronie um how long has it been
thank you for it
since you joined a whole life
[Music]
three to four months now oh
so short it feels longer than that
time does fly
just
you lose track
light healing
i'm gonna take everything
this is a very um doggy dog
uh panicky hollow talk
how did you like the
the holo myth outfit sam
the your elephants
yo you like them so nice it's so nice
and the way you guys prepare for it
like some of the speculations um with
the art
like the outfit
was pretty accurate
kind of surprising
for especially for gouda i think most
were super accurate
um
and also inna's
yes
she has
i think
because of like the type of streams that
she does a lot of fellow artists um
became her fans and then
whenever she does like outfit
predictions
all these super high level super cool
talented artists give it a try
and they just provide the best best art
ever it's fascinating
all
right was just standing in there yeah
you're stepping up your game i say i see
thank you
i feel like i took it i'm not sure
where's this calm down stupid birds
disgusting dinosaur birds
darn
don't mind me what that was the matter
of them
they're just
walking around
like a
weird little thing
there we go that was easy
anyway i actually the topic that i
wanted to
um
kind of go for was
if crony
were to get a new outfit
let's say a casual outfit because i
think that's the first thing you guys
need a casual one
uh what would you want it to look like
roughly like do you want something like
really
realistic like a knit uh sweater and the
cute good that's like
the i don't know um
a checkered pattern or whatever i don't
know what what would you imagine you
would want to go for
i wanna i want to imagine you in those
clothes
casual outfit
if it's casual probably
like just regular
jacket like a dream jacket
oh denim girl
you know casual i like those i want to
see you in denims yo
oh like you're already extremely skinny
but you win skinny jeans damn
imagine her in skinny jeans
hall of the dead is this where i need to
go
yes this is where we need to go nice oh
rod break going in oh
what oh
there we go [\h__\h] i'm poisoned
okay so crony on
skinny jeans that's something i want to
see too
you have any other
outfits in mind though yes
um
one thing now that we have casual and
now that we also have a elegant party
dress
i do kind of want uh
to make everyone's dreams come true uh
since i am from austria
i want to have a diandel our traditional
we have it
i'll
i want to have a candle are they just
gonna endlessly get out of there
yeah but i think it's gonna take a long
time until
i am able to present that to everyone
um
yo that would be so cool to see
yes channels are so cute i think they're
losing
one of the
most attractive traditional clothings a
country has
in this world pretty sure there's no
bias involved at all perhaps there is
but
but i mean
are you not gonna agree with me yeah
either i agree like
it is
it's really nice the colors and all that
it's just it really pushes your bubba
holy moly your your milk jugs would
overflow when you wear it oh my god
yes you're made flew literally made for
dindle oh fan art please guys please
wait already know it's all good
let's
yeah i mean i'm sorry for saying milk
just i have to think of noise senpai
because you know oh yeah she's a milk
queen with the
with the cow
extras that she has for her casual
outfit i'm not i'm not just pulling this
completely out of my butt
she has she has cow accessories for her
casual outfit okay this this is
is true yes it is did you see that she
actually did get a an outfit inspired
after a
german gender
can you see oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah that looked kind of like really
nice yes but it is uh like i think it
goes a little bit more in the japanese
um
stylized jandal
like i would want to be
more
accurate accurate
if i do it since i am from there
i want it to be very accurate i think
noise was also a little more like
fantasy themed
since she's from hollow life fantasy
yeah yeah yeah yeah
really different
what was different like notably
different from the usual the the
patterns used and and some of the shapes
for her dress are just not accurate um
but that's okay like i'm not saying like
this is not okay or so
uh yeah it's just more towards like a
cosplay um
cosplay of a dandel rather than a real
dandel
ah it's like a
like a
like a dandel inspired outfit yes
oh that was anna
anna get out of the poison
that's okay
probably dead oh oh she's still alive
that's unexpected yeah
you didn't hire him back
did he die and then
oh yeah
oh yeah he died wait now i found the
proper word pop cultural dandel yes i
guess so that's probably a good way to
describe it oh pop culture
[Music]
yes yes
you would look cute in one too
crony
i can't answer anymore you as well
of course chain gloves chain gloves
um soon we should perhaps
go to
uh
where's the door
go back to the city soon and the map
says there's a door oh
oh there it is
nice
oh my goodness
looks cute in most things yeah that is
true
but everyone would i want to see you in
a white knit sweater and then a skinny
blue jeans
okay
in the same tone of voice
i think it would look really nice help
where are you
no don't take that don't take that don't
take that i'm trying to organize it
[Laughter]
i took it let's go back into the city
oh why didn't he yeah i can't come back
alive
oh well we should go to the city and you
should hire back your assistant
i i guess i should he's up there
at the top i'll show you where
yes
900 are you kidding me yeah it's
expensive i'm gonna keep him alive
should i lend you some money my dear
kohai
oh no it's okay i am
rich and hard okay
so i think i have money
who who's gonna heal me okay
uh how much money do you have uh uh i
have 20 000
money
oh
and
i'm loaded
shiny things yes
yes but i i don't see them uh all the
like the sapphires and diamonds and all
that i keep them
for whenever i will ever need them i'm
not selling them
a ruby
wow
wow okay
i do not need the stamina potion so get
that out of the way
[Music]
okay
sorry i'm organizing yes oh no problem
me too
understandable
i don't want crownie to go crazy here oh
cronie could you
next time you play minecraft if you want
uh i was looking for someone to organize
my my my chests in minecraft oh
really you do that for fun don't you
yeah is it is it really messy
um
it's young it could definitely use use
some organizing
[Music]
please okay oh my mom by the way is also
extremely
experienced when it comes to minecraft
and i think she would um be super
excited when if she would see your
bunker
yeah oh yeah i love minecraft
yeah yeah yeah she seems to be
a gamer
she is a gamer yes
okay are we ready to go back you should
go for the portal first
uh already the this this one this one
i think is it
what is this
this
hall of fame is level three yes okay
here we are back again
oh my oh [\h__\h] oh
right into it
what a pleasant time
the exploding arrow is amazing are you
using it did you switch it
yeah okay
good
oh here's a dude that's reviving them
don't you dare no reviving nana only
phoenix can do
you know cronie when when you were first
announced and i saw that you were
well timed
um i thought that
you know we had some connection because
i'm the eternal phoenix but then
everyone grouped you with ammet and i
was like
oh
no
i guess it's the first spot that yeah
you should be scripted with amen and not
me but i also have a time thing going on
but you know you can be part of it too
really can we be time buddies you amen
me
heck yeah
that's gonna be so much more
lore
lord lord oh god
before the stream by the way everyone
cronie shared with me that she took a
nap in her car she was sounding really
really tired the moment she
joined the vc but i have to officially
announce she was on time
and uh
it was all good my worries they they're
wait we're going i think the wrong way
there were there was no need for worries
she was on time um
i just heard some rumors that crony is
usually not on time which is ironic
because she has time
but all good
i'm happy
you're okay their habitation is worse
than you really are i think
there have been only two incidents that
i can recall oh oh
but i don't exactly remember what it was
now but it was there was two i think
it's also kind of brave from you to
kind of admit it or like i guess you
have no choice if people already out you
but
but like in myths when people oversleep
we're kind of we try to hide it we don't
even most of the time we don't even say
that someone overslept
oh god
kill him first
[Music]
are you dead yeah
wait yummy
can you open the portal
before oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah so that i can go back
because we don't have a portal
oh god i see no portal i know i see a
portal
nice
i spawned right in the middle of
everybody i need another portal all
right maybe that one is still open no no
there's still a portal okay
please survive please just run away
i'm trying
um
it would be cool if you like could kite
the enemies away you know
i'm trying
uh wait where's my other there's one of
my bunnies
okay uh
where's my other body i did it
where's my other body i could see it
here right okay
oh no did you kill them all
is that my body where's my body much
easy eight thousand eight hundred gold
is that where is that where's the rest
of my money crony
uh right here
we got that we got the queen side in the
cube by the way
didn't i have twenty thousand where is
the i have only nine thousand now
crony oh crony no i no no no
i only shouldn't have picked up
never i only had
that death took its toll apparently
that's true it did say something like
that what they took ten thousands gold
from me
yo that's a little too much
ah that's i become that's why you need
to put your money in your stupid stash
all the time
i forgot about that
cali come on you didn't have to do that
please mama mia
oh no oh come on okay but we out of here
go girl new hills go
but it's okay you have like not okay
money
you still have twenty thousand right
no that one's in my inventory i lost ten
thousand but i have money in my stash i
realized i have 50 000 in my stash so
kusa
that's that's a lot
yeah nothing
i think you need to worry about it then
20 000. you have questions
we already finished the second thing
crown you think you're doing so well
this is fun roderick staff this is more
fun
than i thought it would be
when the cube opens place
was announced with into a socketed long
sword oh praying to the cube and the
sphere you guys were the cube right
into one oh it came again
[Music]
the
there was so much leading up to you
guys's debut
so much lore and where is it now crony
where is the lore huh
the lord
is in our hearts if you
if you try you'll find it
it's there somewhere
oh wait the cube
the cube oh the cube
the cube is extra inventory crony
eh
yes oh
we should put our books in there i was
told before i remember uh put your books
in there
was there something you couldn't put in
there what was it chat let's put it in
charm
oh i mean you should put in stuff yeah
like charms i guess that you always need
but
wait does it work like if you have it in
the in the cube it still applies or do
you need the charm directly in the
inventory chat
technically it's an inventory right
oh charms are not active in there oh
okay
charms won't work okay
okay but but we can put the the huge ass
books in there and i guess maybe some
extra potions perhaps
well finally i mean that's still
something more inventory space yo
transpo no transmuting
i always wanted this
more space but i think that's do you
ever get even more space than this track
because this is still not enough
this is not enough
it's also kind of this girl i need my
my helper
should i get a different helper the one
that you have
yeah you should it's actually much
stronger i suppose
with better sense of direction oh
really
what do i i'd like to think so yeah we
need some tanks because we suck at
tanking
um
act two better mercenary
should i just get
the most expensive one wahid level 15.
well they have different skills
i'll i'll go with
wahid
[Music]
i guess
put everything in here
welcome to the team what
now we have two front liners actually
where's yours
did yours die too you gotta get yours
back too i think
oh man why does he keep dying every
single time cause you don't protect him
enough
now he should have just tried to not die
more
like
well you know he's a mercenary he's
supposed to take care of himself why do
i have to take care of him true oh
damn i gotta give him armor
do i have armor or this maybe
how do i how do i check their gear again
oh you can we've all give them that
i'll put that together oh yes
i'll put that together i don't have a
weapon for him
[Music]
where's the weapon that i gave to the
other lady
do i have to buy a weapon for him
yeah
welcome to my shop what do you have
nothing i'll just
uh
i could give him my spare
oh yes
javel with spare spare it's not java
okay whatever i'll wait until something
drops
uh
there's no trouble buy something she
won't wear who is selling the um armor
stuff here
this dude
hello
you can combine gems and cubes
absolutely apparently yeah
can we fix these
jewels maybe
maybe tell me if you managed to do it
top left combined same gems
okay three to one gem okay
so
three two one gently fine
yeah
so if i transmute
what happens good evening
oh god i'm really scared what if i'm
doing something wrong by clicking on
this ah
don't worry
oh there are these all uh are is a
trident or a bardish also okay for this
dude
take okay you gotta take all the items
though okay
yeah i knew there was some
something weird
had a bad feeling
okay
so you can
get all the chipped jewels
to combine it into one gem apparently so
let's see but i don't have any armor to
sock it into anyway what did you get
i got a flawed diamond
it doesn't have to be the same type of
like for example three amethysts
or three diamonds or so
did you
put the three like three of the same
oh yeah i put three of the same uh
uh like chipped diamonds
okay let me put my ammo around the
button i'm going to put this together
what fancy bling bling
how do i make it into a flawless diamond
then
no need you're already a flawless
diamond crooney
creature what i know
of course you know
you're
you're just
eternal beauty oh thank you i admire
your confidence crony
i know
wow
you
you and your charisma cronies
it's fascinating i can learn so much
from you
why you're perfect oh my goodness full
rejuvenation potion okay so if you have
um if you combine three rejuvenation
potions you can make it into a full
rejuvenation that heals 100 life in mana
oh
you're not bad
not bad i will never use it
probably
are you also the type when you play rpgs
where maybe especially in the beginning
like healing potions and all that is
kind of rare you just end up never using
it
because you feel like you don't want to
waste it you want to keep it yeah you
really need it
yep that is yeah yes are you are you
like that very much so
yes ah yes fellow hoarder yes very nice
yes yes but i hoard without ocd so my
hoarding is messy
[Laughter]
uh can you combine stamina stamina
potions or any other health potions
because that would be easy oh there you
go you want to clean your thing and by
combining literally everything
do that on your off time let's go
explore cronie
you're right yes i am right
hey i like that confidence let's go
now we didn't find any waypoints so i
guess we gotta walk again but the
question is chet
by your experience should we walk into
the same direction again is the next
place we're looking for usually like
past that or should we go in a
completely different direction because
we need the we need the maggot layer now
is that same direction okay where are
you cooney
oh i'm organizing don't mind me um
okay i'm crowley no no more organizing
chronicles
crony bad coin
i need to control you ocd crummy
kiana is in control come with me it's
just so therapeutic where's your where's
your helper you got it okay okay good
for your therapeutic yes yes
entering drawings here if you find a
waypoint let me know
okey-dokey
what level are you
uh where do i see it
oh wait i found the portal oh the
waypoint
yeah the way where are you
never mind this is a well
just messing with you
ah i would not see you on the map by the
way where i i found that probably what
that's what you find
we're crowning crony doka
oh there you are i thought you will ran
back to organize your inventory again
secretly
okay i could no no no no
is this satisfying when you step on
these scorpions try it
this one's alive
i
can't i can't stop there we go yeah that
is
uh satisfying and disgusting
so you like crashing bugs
cronie
are you
if you have a bug or a spider in your
apartment or so are you the tab to try
to kill it or you just have to try to
set it free or you just have to ignore
it completely
i just ignore it completely oh
are you not scared of any type of bugs
uh i am scared of all of them
but you just ignore them because you're
scared you don't want them to get too
close
yeah and i don't i don't want to kill
ants i don't want to kill
except fruit flies
they can die you wouldn't even kill an
ant i'll get too cute i i i i i
too slow cronies
what's going on here
oh
[Music]
hey
why do we gotta fight we're not fighting
we're doing teamwork
we're taking care of one another making
sure that everyone gets some treasures
yes yes yeah yeah yeah of course
we're
doing fine yes
i wonder which direction we should go
[Music]
i don't want to look for hours again for
this stupid maggot lair i really didn't
like that one it was you kind of i hope
you're not claustrophobic as well
i'm not okay good i mean in game it's
fine because the next place makes you
feel claustrophobic
oh
oh oh by the way if you still have
exploding arrow on you maybe should
maybe think about switching it every now
and then because exploding arrow takes
up so much mana
oh i turned off accidentally show your
allison map oh
how do i turn it back on
do you guys know uh push f11 and f12
really
oh what's f12 ah thank you chad
what's up chad knows everything i do oh
crystal swords but it's gray
wait great are gray ones useless
no maybe not
like ray is just the ones that are on
no
are green ones useless maybe they are
gray is good though it's socketed oh
you're right
thank you
okay come with me cronie that was a dead
end
let's go back
oh maybe this way
[Applause]
so gray is either ethereal or
yeah yeah
that could be true it's been a while so
i forgot completely oh there's a there's
a saber cat
sample cat with disabled face
just flat crony
oh they might drop something good yeah
there's a yellow golden enemy
i took the club i gave you so much time
to take here's the sapphire sapphire go
crony go cronies have fire
it's a flawed sapphire but it's sapphire
oh my goodness it's beautiful
oh nice
and we're gonna have a flawless sapphire
it's gonna be great
i was just chat i was just i was just i
was just um
having fun i knew there was nothing
good dropping anyway so i was just
messing around
you know
yeah really really oh i just did like
panic clicking
[Music]
i ran out of arrows oh no here take the
take this club is danny
rose
are you good crying
yeah yeah i know i'm good i'm good
her staff was really good to have
oh
impossible crony help i have no arrow
[Music]
yeah
i keep a backup just in case i see that
as a peace offering i can't
a peace offering yes
charge wait why why am i other
there we go
okay
oh
that was a quick level up
[Applause]
you got a level up nice oh yeah you
asked me for what level i am i am
i am
i am level i am
i am level
16.
and activate it
how do i check what level i am
with c
c
o
i see
yeah we didn't find the sewers level 2
waypoint for some reason we didn't
explore well enough
shame on us
i don't wait it goes upwards there i
think that's the way to go what
man this is
is that what we're calling
yes yes fire race is maggot lair in the
far far away oh
i've seen these dudes in bug's life
oh it's true
wait is bug slime the one
uh
with
was it it was it ass
no
yeah
with the blue ants
it's not a-n-t-z
not the
not the ugly version it's the cuter
pixar version oh yeah yeah yeah yeah i
think
i think i watched it when i was younger
anything good dropping crony
oh no not really honestly
you disgusting ill
why that sand maggot looked disgusting
oh that's a sand maggot oh it lays eggs
you you you you you
nice and amazing
thank you
we needed to know that
what's that what's that
oh they come out of the ground
oh
isn't that nice what okay wait uh shall
we
how's your inventory looking right now
kind of
full but i think i can manage what about
you
a little bit longer
a little longer is good
nice okay get this done
you went that way okay
what's that
weird pink
black hole what
found lots of money
you came too late crony
why why
it's okay as your manager says you
should get an analog clock did you tell
your viewers that your manager told you
that
impossible no
i can't
cronie told me before the stream that
her
manager told her the clock to get an
analog clock
yeah
that's about right
maybe i can't believe
someone will give it to you
maybe hey actually that would be a
pretty good gift
i think i ran out of arrows again okay i
think it's time there's a waypoint here
yo
oh
okay but i gotta go back i'm gonna open
the portal
oh i
wait 23
15.
defense
nice
oh
you're so good i'm impossible i can't
help you i can't help you
okay javelin
i can't carry anymore
okay
okay now really got a goal
really gotta go
yeah we really should go right up we go
oh let me just take that okay
okay uh uh a portal
impossible oh well i guess we can just
use the waypoint
uh to loot goley
let's sell some of our beautiful
belongings
and i feel like we're getting closer to
the maggot place
stay awhile this is true stay a while
and listen
what scroll of town nope
oh narash's then
what
oh no my buddy's dead again
no again
yeah it's whatever did you give him some
armor to protect himself
i did and then he died
he just went off and died i don't know
why he just decided to say oh you know
what i can't i can't and then he died
weakling
we don't need weakness right he's in our
team
hey
you understand you get it
just keep him dead
ow
never revive him again
i'm good to go
uh where was he
[Music]
i'm back at the way point uh you're here
too oh
yeah
did you um
did you not pick that up on purpose
which one the blue cap and the javelin
and the chain oh
yeah
yeah why not
i i don't have room for it how about you
use this waypoint to go back and sell
some stuff
wow what a genius idea what i just did
i'll sell this stuff for you then
i'm gonna thank you and
and that money's gonna go to me right
yes
you're gonna give the money to me right
yeah i can give you the items
whoa chain boots of balance wow you
actually maybe something no actually i
know wait wait wait
i
realized yeah i haven't switched out my
boots in a while you can have this i
mean
azure heavy boots
mine are better
[Laughter]
i cannot i can't believe you've done
this
what
what it's a dog eats dog world get used
to it
gotta get used to cronies learn from
your senpai how to stay alive in this
world
in this traveling
world yeah you can have that if you need
[Music]
why do i have this
what do i
uh
why do i have these gloves i thought i
had something better what i'm so
confused mine are really shitty too i
only have white level gloves with
defense free and that's it
that's really crappy
whoa
they're so expensive though yeah we'll
find something eventually
yeah yeah okay
i guess i should revive my dude yes
well i'll look for the maggot layer
where's the mango
yeah it just dies so quickly
[Music]
that's weird mine doesn't die so quickly
what could it be what could the reason
be
you you
can your teammate also equip a shield or
uh
no because he must wear like a spare or
something some item like a two-handed
item uh-huh
it's locked
can you just take it from yours
there's a key in here there and then
there and then put it here and then all
right this was a thing this was a thing
this is a thing
oh organizing why why am i like this i
just don't want to open you up again
no no i got it don't worry
just kiana mommy kiana i have to pick
you up again cronin
okay give give me i'm almost done
yesterday if you say so i will wait how
good is your japanese cronie
not very josu des
but your your
uh uh korean is incredible please teach
me sensei
[Music]
my korean is just
it's not that great but i i'll trust you
can you um can you give me like uh like
i have this i have this to go french
sentence whenever i say people think i
actually speak french uh it's
about moss as well and it means do you
want to sleep tonight with me
um oh my god
i got it from no i got it from a song
okay i got it from lady marmalade
and i was wondering if you could give me
like a really sexy korean sentence that
if i say it uh
people will think i speak korean for
real
oh no
um
i think there's an equivalent
uh
phrase in korean for
netflix and [\h__\h]
oh
what is it maybe what would you like to
do netflix and chill with me tonight yes
yes good stuff i need that yes yes in
korean please
i think my pronunciation is off can you
say it again no no
it's pretty good it's um
are you actually asking if we want to
eat uh ramen
yeah like you know it's
kind of like wanna come over to my house
and have some ramen
you say it differently than it is in
japanese though the korean pronunciation
is kind of different
yeah
in japanese is ramen
in korean it's
l
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
out of curiosity then do you have um
something that you can teach me in
german
not yet first i have to tell you
something crony you're first of all
going completely in the wrong direction
please go to the right side north or
like i guess gosh darn it i've been
walking in circles all this time i'm so
bad with multitasking
[Music]
[Laughter]
no it means like just just take it out
from the bridge
what
wait wait no before that how do i go up
oh that's how you do it
okay
from google
[Music]
there's parts of it i i taught myself
through duolingo and parts of it uh
costume i just learned from from google
google translate
oh my gosh is that the most proper word
for boobies custom
uh
yes yes okay question mark
great i wanted you to teach me korean
anyway so finally i'm getting my lesson
yeah yeah
because i am uh i am
guiding i don't know what i'm saying
i i i i don't know
[Music]
why are you saying impossible
oh did you run out of arrows too
no no no i used the wrong bow
uh wait you were short you wanted to
learn something in german was that what
you were saying yeah yeah
cronie how much german do you actually
speak
uh guten morgen got that morgan
no
oh
she said to me before the stream she did
use the word tricep i was very excited
because we do have that as an icon as a
member's eye what what you want me to
not ruin you say so image you don't have
a say so image crony do you no
no don't be so mellow dramatic crony
it's over
it's over i am
guys
okay
thank you
why
i never have enough lana
who is doing this damage oh god
i would like to shut up
oh my god
and then how do i what is this
how do i
did you take the thing that i wanted to
say no it's okay
i gotta
use it
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's nothing it's nothing it's nothing
important it's nothing good
right so you want to learn and learn
german uh you said guten morgen but i
still don't know how much you actually
speak or understand
none at all is that it guten morgen and
scheisse
my crystal sword
what what what do you mean crystal sword
hmm
do you have the do you have flowers
oh yeah okay yeah
let's give you a measurement oh come
here i'll give you the crystal sword you
take it no no no no no it's okay i don't
need anything
come here
i don't need it i don't
[Music]
we need to find that other quest item um
until that i cannot rest i cannot sleep
wait
oh my god what are we gonna do about all
this
stupid electro damage
uh just keep healing yes yes yes mommy
why
oh sand megan oh there's eel
but yes
um what else do i know
oh yes yes yes
and guten knocked oh
knocked yes
yeah crony is good when she is knocked
um what
you pronounce the word nakht in a way
that it means naked
[Laughter]
mamma mia
oh
what the shame
[Music]
um okay so
do you want to learn
a sentence like the one you talked you
taught taught me
yes okay um
[Music]
um
what could i teach you i guess this was
a dead end
um
yes it was
[Music]
is there see i don't have many good
german pickup phrases
[Music]
i'll just
i'll just say
um
this to
[Music]
that's just kind of
charming isn't it
in my name shrank 45
why
it's pretty long
let me
give you a second where'd you go oh my
gosh why why did why did it turn
it's so dark
it's because they're the night slingers
i was just trying to find i went to the
paper to write it down
i don't know maybe it's one enemy
because the moment i stepped in here
they started making it dark i can't
carry anymore maybe
on it maybe this is just the area i
guess
ah we jumped right to the next quest oh
we skipped this is a different quest
okay
about the strange darkness now let's get
out of here
come with me
okay okay
excited goodbye
oh
is it not gonna get brighter anymore oh
yeah
okay we need to go to the city and ask
drognon
yeah
[Music]
i wanna go to the maga layer where the
hell is it
maybe maybe the upper have we looked at
the upper area
up area yeah
there's nothing there i guess we gotta
go down
again
maybe we missed something in the
bottom area
where is the mega oh do you think it's
that pink one over there pink pink
yeah in the in the center area
like follow follow me i just follow you
also except that you have to speak the
german
[Applause]
i i gotta write it down because there's
no way that i'll be able to give you a
shorter one
oh
that's it
okay
how about
ha ha ha ha
ha ha
um
uh okay a shorter one was
uh
yeah okay
lassonz
jorge zontal
tango tansen
holy
holy what horizontal horizontal
it's easily translated into english to
let us dance tango horizontally
really
wait when is that usually used
i thought we're doing like flirty flirty
sentences
but why tango horizontally
oh
[Laughter]
someone in my chat wrote that he
suggested it
my suggestion was way more innocent i
was saying
uh at home i in my drawer i have a i
have a a drawer drawer
free empty for you because i'm asking
you to move in you know
yeah in my closet i have a drawer empty
for you
i was saying that and then they were
like this is too long
okay yeah
uh well okay let's i'll try to memorize
the other one
oh you two say so for the horizontally
tangled dancing
okay i mean
no it's just dancing it's this is
dancing yeah it's so bad
okay okay the other one my suggestion
was um
um
what was it again uh
no was that what i was how was i saying
it okay different one different one
let's let's make it but that's not good
enough it's often caffeine with me
that's not good enough
caffeine coffee
[Music]
uh
the chat is only telling me long
sentences it's too difficult for cronini
uh
oh
[Music]
let's do
this
[Music]
let's uh let's go to portal portal god
damn it
can we can we go to town we need to see
that i can sell my yeah yes are you in
here
where are you i'm here next to you oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh we can celebrate
london with me i'll thank god i'll think
of a good german sentence
while we're selling ah
could you open it
i can't yes i can
bless i think you have to bring the book
back into your inventory every time
how about um
oh why is it so dark
well yeah because they're not we have
reactivated the quest it's gonna stay
like this until
we fix it
let's start the drug now
i've been researching this lengthy
eclipse and i believe it to be the work
of claude
work of club
beneath the desert sands and you may
find the source of this code where's the
blacksmith here
hmm
black smith i saw the blacksmith
somewhere
wait you want something repaired
um repairs i'll leave my website
right next to decker's kane is is farah
she repairs stuff
i will do it too
[Music]
what is this javelin oh
javelin
went to 15 7 to 20.
is my old one still better chat
because it has more blue effects
okay
what am i
right i'm doing i'm putting this
oh i like that one
uh slow dangle i like that one that has
made me say so enough for a crony
i'm afraid
are you sure
yeah it's kind of long though
uh
betty better getting better off getting
a second bone arrow no no okay
um
so
uh
yes
it's been from ariatsi
can you describe the absolutely
here that
if you have an accident on the street
they're gonna take your car and stuff
so yeah you're saying i am from the ada
sea
it's been from adeyazi
capping
[Music]
did you see did you see that message no
how do i type a message
can each dishwasher up slipping
up
can easily hold up slipping up flipping
up slapping
that's cute when you say that
very cute
very cute indeed ich bin
[Music]
service may i tell you home tonight
oh that's smooth
can you say it in one go
uh it's been
[Music]
slumping
cute
yes you can yes please do
i am all yours
yay
new phrases
are you ready to go back to our maggot
lair and destroy everything in our sight
yeah
okay why are you trying to try me give
me you dude you clicked me
really it said agree oh
no wait i could just open another one
no need to be so dramatic impossible why
can't i just open it like that here come
here with me
okay let's go
let's go i'll give you some
i'll give you some of my scrolls
no no no no no i have more than enough i
think
we're fine but
but you can
you can give me some of the beautiful
shiny items that are gonna be dropping
left right huh that i cannot i'm
you're already doing it though
we're gonna speed around this place
oh wow
it eats stamina
[Music]
why are you not shooting
oh my boat oh i don't have any arrows oh
oh i have some extra but not very many
let's see if we can find some
drops ow
i i dropped some did you take them yeah
i think you did yeah
thank you
32 not many yes we'll find more
actually
i think even before crony debuted i
asked her
if she could
if we would do a stream where she would
teach me
oh here's arrows if she would teach me
uh korean
it still hasn't happened when are we
gonna do that cronini
whenever you're really good
are you are you up for it are you
do you think you're a good teacher
am i a good teacher
not exactly i don't really know
what to teach you to be exact
is there any specific topic that you
would like to learn
uh
[Music]
i mean i already tried teaching myself
some basics for duolingo but it's been a
while and i kind of forgot already i
think it i was trying to teach myself
the the signs the um
uh
like how to write korean
but
chad agreed that duolingo was doing an
absolutely horrible job of teaching it
like
you know how they're like built
like you can combine
small pieces into another letter right
uh-huh
and duolingo just didn't explain that
part at all
so oh
it took me a while to realize that and i
was just trying to remember what they
look like and what they mean by
um
like associating them with uh what were
their turtle turtles what are they
called again
turtle turtle rangers no not true what
are they called
cartoons ninja turtles
oh
teenage mutant ninja turtles if you turn
them around the korean signs they look
like ninja turtles to me
yeah
that's the only thing i was able to
associate them with so if you could just
teach me some more basics
that i would really appreciate
communication basics
you don't even have you don't have to
teach me the the writing i guess that's
probably better to learn
on on their own
right uh-huh
you're fluent right
i'm
baby can you do some
korean asmr for me
i don't like asmr but if it's you
speaking korean i think everyone gets uh
like tingly feelings
oh you wand
do you want this you want
well a token
it's crappy though
i know
and i have better
things to pick up
why
no that's okay i already have some
good stuff i found something
uh
i found something
uh legendary
when you weren't looking i think
why'd you pick it up when i wasn't
looking huh cause you were somewhere
else i think
i wanna know we could share this
beautiful moment together we cannot
share this item however it's unshareable
next legendary item is yours
oh
no no no no i don't know what i'm doing
place is so disgusting
when you play together in diablo i think
i was previously told that like the more
players are in the game the more
um easier no the other way around
oh they adjust the strength of the
enemies apparently is it true
chad
because they feel
i guess they feel about as strong as
they would be
when
uh i would be fighting them alone yeah
it's true 33 percent more hp
apparently yo this this place is so
disgusting i can't even walk on it
my i think my buddy died again
no crawl me your body's so weak fire him
fire
ow
so strong
which way should we go crony
i can't why can't i there we go
going this way
i have no idea what i'm doing
whenever i try to rack up skill points
and i try to
allocate them
what i'm doing why are you dead
because i'm dead should have put my
money into the stash again please open
portal please
yeah
they're so strong what the [\h__\h]
oh my god
i don't know
man
zero i have zero money wait you just
don't die okay stay alive stay safe i
need to sell some stuff
oh
can you oh buddy don't die don't die
don't die i need i need some money to
hire my friend again
hello
uh
[Music]
wow they are very durable
oh oh
yes
oh god uh
okay that's one day
oh god i'm no don't die did you open the
portal i'm cornered yes i did okay
just stay alive a little longer
good morning wow that's very caring and
i'm so passionate
i'm on my way
[Music]
crony
i'm coming
where is you where is you
impossible oh wait i only i don't have
my i don't have any weapons oh god my
body is all the way over there
is everyone down here wait
i can't pick it up i can't pick it up
why can't you pick it up there's the
enemy waiting here for me okay good
okay now okay
you wanted to take
a lot of money i need to get some more
money
oh oh man can't marry anymore
oh man
oh man um oh man
oh man where do i uh get out um
oh man a claymore beautiful
there's an anime clown claymore yo we
got so many items here we need to go to
the city again right away
yeah i can open
the portal okay
whoever sells their stuff fastest can go
back and no we're interested wait wait
i'm not going to eat it
you are not allowed to ocd your items
for too long because you have to go back
quickly
bye
wow wow if pharaoh wow should i keep
this for some reason
well actually i'll wait for you because
the portal closes oh okay you can have
the rest that's there
no no it's okay that's not a very fair
competition i'd like to check it because
i already took so much stuff
really oh i'm coming
okay
[Laughter]
crony
i mean i had a different portal but it's
like all the way in the beginning so
crony
okay here you go
here you go she says
yeah yeah it's it's there now
okay
but it's all gone now
no it's not no it's not crony
are you bullying your senpai
no what have i done to deserve that
you said you picked them so you did it
you did it because so you wanted to
quickly uh i see i see nothing is left
here i understand
okay you can come now
come on cronie huh come on
why let's move on i want to finish this
dungeon
come on chronic come back
uh nothing's gonna happen come here come
here
no not not yet oh let me just sell some
of my stuff oh you have something to
sell oh
and
so you continue to contribute so much to
this game and
yes
that's not sarcasm right okay no not
really i don't know maybe it is maybe
oh for some reason i thought that was
the end of it no unfortunately not
i think this is still way bigger
this place i remember i spent quite some
time here i was rushing through it but i
couldn't
find anything
you now have the opportunity to say
hello to my mom to meet my mom because
she's watching the stream pretty sure
oh
hello
uh mama rony
why are you putting your own name on my
mommy
are we planning to marry or what's going
on or are you planning to to
are you planning to marry my mom i i'm
i'm sorry
mama around
isn't that how you call your own mommy
mixing up some things you're crony also
you're in the way my mom is time mom
what's the magic word
please
oh yes
does your mom watch your stream
oh god i hope not
does she know what you're doing
uh
yeah i think so
oh did you tell her or did she find
out i feel like she would be able to
tell considering how
i scream
oh
oh you grandma you you're living in the
same
place yeah yeah oh wait how do i get
through oh no you got to move smartly
what
yeah it's kind of buggy here what the
hell
and what yes what the [\h__\h] honey what
how do i
totally die oh my ah
now i'm in front of you but yeah i can't
move either oh
hello maybe we can egg is on the ground
but ah
but i can't
kill it
true maybe with the javelin yes okay
oh for some reason the javelin hits
where is where is waheed by the way he's
alive but he's not coming either
will he like teleport to me chad because
i see him bugging around
oh there there he goes
don't you dare kill me
didn't put my money back into the bank
again uh oh man
which direction do we go crony
uh
anyway we'll catch you together
okay over here okay
crony says so
oh nice choice oh
nice if we went a different direction we
would have probably wandered around for
one longer
oh yeah oh my god
i lost my train of thought but oh god
hello
but she's not japanese so you don't
really need to add any honorifics
oh god mistleton
miss mama tori
yeah
wow
11 000 money again never give me money
in my inventory oh my god i can't even
get my dude back okay um can you make a
portal please
yeah thank you
[Music]
okay that's okay
what happened and they keep on hitting
me crony
why would they do that how dare they
[Music]
where is my body
on the
did you take my money that i dropped no
what oh
i think
the few monies that i had left
how much did you have
i don't know they took eleven thousand
so
it's okay it probably wasn't much
death to start look look def takes my
money and leaves me her bloody scythe
thank you kelly she legit she gave me
this this was the item i picked up
aside okay
so you lost 11 000 right yeah no but def
took it you you don't have it probably
you don't have
if something was dropped from me it was
probably way less
because you literally pay the game
like
how many percent
of your own money chad is there a
specific
specific percentage
i don't could you recall this much gold
no
well i died oh i did twice didn't i so
you probably oh yeah once once i got a
little bit of my money back but no it's
something that's right
oh my god
crony donations
thanks for the super chat cronie thanks
for the red super chat
thank you
now move please
can i send you another
yes if you want
i hope i will not lose it by dying again
what's wrong why are you giving me more
money
why
so when you again i can keep the rest
i'm kidding i don't understand the logic
but okay
thank you for the pink super chat cronie
i would feel less
taking your money i mean why anyway
monsters monsters yes
wow she's so generous thank you for
support supporting my cause
thank you always we both have no helpers
so let's see if we can even survive this
from now on
i'm a bit worried
i'll stay behind a little bit more
but it's a little bit difficult you got
to open those doors from close and then
and then they attack you immediately and
then perform you and then you die yeah
oh my god
what is going on
no mana
level up
mana is fully restored oh this is a okay
this is a gold enemy
holy [\h__\h]
feeling potion healing potion thank you
thank you oh god
did it drop something good for you
oh no
damn yeah i also only dropped a blue one
for me
yes
for not a
this is for you because that's something
uh the same thing good that you picked
it up
i
had that
uh
i got that previously the same item i
think
which one the rune yeah good for you
good for you cronie i saw you later
it didn't even took you half a second to
pick it up
now i feel a little bad considering
you're like oh you can take it it's like
you call me a place i don't want to die
alone
why not
i'm kidding okay
um
this and this
oh yeah i need to wait i need to do
stats wait a second maybe i need um
what was i stating on chat probably dex
huh
but i feel like i need more vitality
i'll stat a little bit here 14 stat
points remaining
why don't we have so many stat points
put it all into vine okay let's go
let's go i'm stronger now crony
hey
i'll protect you
[Applause]
oh my together
immortal oh my god yes
no we don't need to be together i'm
already immortal
you too
oh yeah
but together we're even stronger
yeah how old are you now i'm like
infinite years old i have also no h not
really
hey
yay for vague ages
in hollow life english
that's the beauty of it ain't it
yeah okay we we got that
done
how many levels are there here in this
dungeon chat do you know
gonna die yes
me too
oh my god oh what coincidence
there's three oh we're already in the
third one okay it shouldn't be much
longer
saber unless you how do you feel about
have you ever played or watched fate
crony
i've tried playing face grand order oh
my goodness
i think that might be the bus can we
like yeah um i have no mana uh let's go
back to the city for one moment yes nice
you read my mind crony
that is the bus
let's get ready for it's probably not
that strong but uh
yeah
let's put the money into the stash
oh but a little bit let's bring our
buddies
uh
well cost like what 1 500.
and then
um
greetings thank you for healing
honestly crony
i
felt like
this
um collab with you might be my
last time playing
this game on stream but
somehow this is a surprisingly good
collab game so i kind of want to do more
yeah i want to i want to play more of it
even though i died so many times
it's a nice challenge kind of grows on
you and
i would i would like it if we can collab
more too you know
okay
but wait i need to i need to buy some
or maybe i have some in my inventory i
need some mana
thingies
it has none okay
well yeah but yeah i need i need the
korean knowledge because i have you
probably too but you know how hololive
has had a recent
influx of korean viewers and they're so
sweet
i just want to be able to
give them some content
mm-hmm
let's let's uh learn some curry and
shall we
teach me teach me
[Music]
yes that one yes important knowledge
no you can forget that one
i'm ready to go
really i just finished organizing what
uh coincidence what a coincidence we're
in sync
i
give me a second
no where are you going dude dude come
here he wanted to fight the bus stop
kiting the bus dude i'm waiting for
cronie
oh are you already back yeah
but i'm not doing anything i'm just
waiting
okay give i'll be there in a quick
second wait no i'm i'm going there again
too i need to store some more money
apparently i sold
more and they know okay
white white white what what oh crony is
at her stash what a surprise
where else would she be
it's where you belong in front of your
chest just like in minecraft
all right let's go
wait
my potions
my
potions yes
who has it pharah oh another portal
interesting case that is a good idea let
me open it like here
why do i have this
who had the potions um there's two
different ones that have the potions in
the middle there should be at least one
that sells potions in the middle area
close to the
a little bit like left to the stash oh
lysander okay
[Music]
nice okay
should be fine now i think i am ready
let's no
let's make them burn
yeah we will make them burn in about 10
seconds
yes let's go
let's go
that is a lot of
maybe explosion arrow
better
yeah
[Music]
disgusting
oh i'm gonna die i'm gonna die
how deep are you in this [\h__\h]
oh we killed the big one already
oh that's kind of underwhelming
oh
[Laughter]
those are quest items i think oh
i got almost nothing from this but okay
okay you got so like most of the time i
was picking up other things so it's good
it's just funny how you took everything
you learned from the greatest from
takanashi kiwala
thank you you thank you learned a lot i
think through this journey and i'm so
proud of how we have developed our
friendship today here i made a portal
over here we can go back
okay i'll take this then
here white item to sell
yeah staff of kings oh wait is that the
what is it what did it say we need
search for the maggot layer and for the
shaft shaft
it did you pick up a shaft
type of
staff of kings
yeah is that the that's not the quest
item is
ah it it is the staff well that's
confusing it says search for the shaft
and we got
the claw viper no this wait what
maggot layer on the floor races for the
chef but the chat the chest the chat
says that the staff is the quest item so
it's okay it's a typo
where's
roderick staff
uh the quest text got mixed up in diablo
2 resurrected okay
then we got everything we need no
problem
okay we got everything let's go
i think
we it's already pretty late uh over here
so i think we should leave it at that
but who is the quest person again oh no
we're not done with the quest yet so we
can't give it back oh what oh but wait
he has something to say
yes the shaft of queen kings yes the
shaft you have discovered the shaft
portion of a herodrick staff
portion oh cube to unite the shaft with
its headpiece oh
oh
oh yes the herodricks this what stuff he
wants us to unite the cube with the
headpiece what
yeah don't worry about it she's
ah we can't do it now we need the
headpiece okay so we got the cube and
then we have the shaft and then uh later
on we would get the headpiece to combine
those two
well that was fun
yeah yay
patch party
i hope i wasn't um
too
um too
dominating today
oh no no i learned a lot i me too i
learned that you have to pick up items
as soon as possible yes yes
before the other one picks it up that's
the easy rule pick it up before someone
else does it's a dog eat dog world
yeah it's a doggy dog world is the main
takeaway yeah that was just my way of
teaching you that it's tough out there
youtubers there's like millions of
youtubers now you gotta you know step up
your game to stay relevant in this tough
world yeah
yes yes this is a
real wise knowledge from a philosophical
phoenix
i can't store
she's not even listening she's occupied
with her own no no no no no no i'm only
right i'm watching funny i'm walking
it's very dangerous out there
and we gotta look out for each other
so yeah i've been paying attention
you're taking notes
nice it's it's it's all good yeah cronie
is busy that's what what the chat says
crony is busy you lost way the shorts
thank you
thank you for always looking out
thank you crown crownie
i thank you actually uh
i think the first one from here random
knowledge the first one from council to
message me was crony
before the debut like the first one once
once we were in the same discord
remember first one was crony
yeah
um
[Music]
yes yes crony was very interested in
this phoenix lady
right i mean i was interested in
everyone but yes yes of course yes he
was like
i'm a huge fan of you just kidding that
was not how it was
that was not how it was almost close
close to you
kiana
can i have an autograph that's no no
that's also not it nope
yeah but that was i was happy to to see
you in my dms please slide into my dms
uh anytime please
really yes
okay i'll try my best when i'm awake
that is probably always the opposite
time of when i'm awake but yeah let's go
yeah
one day our paths will cross like like
this
i believe in it i'm looking forward to
that day crony please teach me korean
sometime soon and let's let's continue
diablo sometime in january
if you want yeah yeah yes yes that would
be cool because it was so much fun we
should at least finish like
um
i would say i mean not the whole act
maybe because that's that's tough but we
should finish the the staff quest and
maybe the tainted sun quest so that gets
so that the sun comes back
sometimes
we're a great team
we are a great team
maybe
i could save up the
hmm
if i do play diablo oh are you planning
to play more
if i play more
how far do you think i should go i feel
like i'm not going to go far without
you
well i mean if you want to play some
more alone on your channel you you're
welcome to go as far as you want but but
you can also always call me over uh if
if you feel like you know playing
together once more fun i'll i'll make
time for you anytime uh yep yep
oh oh oh okay oh okay that's okay
but you don't have to i mean if you if
you feel like
oh
yeah
yeah anyway
sister so we gotta do some caffeine
sister collapse you know
did you guys know we do have the same
rigor so we can uh move
the most in how left can you go
you can't go even i think you're even
more movable than i am because kathy
rigged you after me
and how how left can you actually go
that's not you can go further i know you
can go further
this is
the limit no i saw you going further
before
how far oh crony i wanted to before we
end this i wanted to give you a senpai
advice
uh-huh
i feel like
uh you should
make yourself bigger on streams and on
thumbnails
okay yes
i think you make your face too small
always
my face
yeah i mean is there a reason for that
you make yourself too small
and it wants you to be bigger so that it
catches the eye better how beautiful you
are
well you know i'm just
i feel like
if people see my full glory it might be
a bit too much for them but
you know what i'll i'll take your advice
i'll try to become be make myself
big
that'll be a very good place yes you'll
go big or go home yes thank you
okay crony shall we end it yeah i think
we have to
don't forget to save i think diablo
always saves when you exit okay
yeah save and exit yeah
we made a lot of progress thank you
everybody for watching our diablo 2
resurrected collab
thank you everybody hope you enjoyed it
and check out cronie's channel it's in
the description
give her a sub
like how you look at me
oh be sure to like and subscribe and be
sure to hit that bell no no i wasn't
really asking for that but that's good
yes yes go go go promotion girl yeah
hit that like and subscribe follow us on
twitter as well
yeah
be sure to ring that bell button
ding ding ding ding ding
ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding ding ding okay crony um
i have a sentence for you
[Music]
manager
oh my god
where do you learn these
google is my teacher
google should not be doing this
you're such a you're such a shy dog
aren't you
no
what
you get so flustered so quickly that's
so easy to
well you know my answer to that is um
[Music]
wait i heard that before
what does that mean i heard that before
does that mean it means i'll think about
it we'll have a great sleepover
it means you'll think about it
yeah we'll have a great sleepover
oh great yes sleep over here yeah
sleepover
okay okay okay okay yes okay i'll be the
one to wake you up crony because no one
else does
sounds like a solid idea yeah okay and
have a great evening everybody oh by the
way cronie i have a uh ending greeting
on my channel maybe you want to stay
together with me do you have an ending
greeting
uh it is chris me
ah wow you really ah that you increased
me
you sound like a like a
swiss person almost
we say german in the end
alf
yeah
okay
thanks guys
[Music]
okay
i switched the screen
[Music]
do
you