[Music]
d
for
[Music]
ch
for
[Music]
ch
the
[Music]
for
d
[Music]
w
okay found it we're here we're
back
yay for first time do it hello everybody
it's narissa Raven CFT the number one
kfp in the
house sorry I don't know I was playing
with the with the mixer thingy because
it's annoying me and
yeah let me put this here
um chat how you
doing welcome to the stream hello is the
is is our audio okay now voice is a bit
low well okay I know can I can this R
yes okay
ah yeah M okay this is maximum unless I
mean I can still like know here how
about
this it doesn't go much further I'm sure
it's fine it's fine it's fine we're just
going to yeah the game is pretty low
anyway so uh you guys have to hire hide
hey hi make it higher on your side up
your volume
mhm the loading screen music sorry it
was so loud I realized I didn't realize
cuz my headphones were so quiet they so
cute
[Music]
yeah hi walk oh my God baby she fought
the is her name but
no I'm petting chunky
wonky aren't you jealous sorry no I'm
happy I'm delighted you I mean them oh
yeah yeah oh guys before we okay maybe
this endless intro maybe we should stop
it like cuz I wanted to talk a little
bit before we get started okay um so
maybe they can like be quiet be quiet
game and so noisa is in my home we're
flying to this island this one
really mhm very soon yeah is pretty much
this island almost um it's got the same
kind of beautiful blue
ocean yeah pretty much same same same uh
soon that is the goal but why is chunky
W still
here cuz she likes me I'm confused
normally she she just goes away when I
see but she's maybe curious cuz you're
here oh really you want to come here for
real let's see come here it's okay she
was like about to go on your chair maybe
we should just like act as if we don't
know what she's doing we don't notice
her I don't
see I don't see chunky wony so uh yeah
is here we've been planning this for a
while so you guys should know and yeah
we're going to play this game before we
go on vacation we're going to go on
vacation
in the game although they they have a
snow resort we don't have that cute Fox
um we did go to a movie today we did
what was
it you want me to say do you want them
to guess we saw the new Hunger Games
movie the new Hunger Games movie the UN
the the title was the prequel yeah do
you know the title was so long something
versus snake I don't know the ballad Ah
that's what I wanted to say the ballot
of uh the of of the song bird or the
bird and the snakes yeah yeah yeah and
that is the second point that I was
saying trying to tell you Lissa but I
forgot what about yeah BAL of song Buton
Nam what reminds me of Game of Thrones
is the long the needlessly long titles
not not even needlessly long but like
song of ice and fire is literally one of
gamer fr's titles Dance with Dragons
Yeah Song of Ice and Fire Ballad of song
birds and snakes I
mean I mean you're right you're right
seems inspired and Peter dlet being in
there yeah that just made it worse yeah
was it a good
movie I have to bring
up I have to tangent about it before we
get started guys so this will be
um spoiler
heavy yeah spoiler warning
for new Hunger Games movie I'm sorry I
have to we have to so first of all
narissa didn't watch the previous movies
even though I told her I didn't have
time I was thinking you wouldn't have
that but you said oh it's fine I'll
watch it I'll watch it you know I I
thought they'd have on the plane so I
was like you know during my long flight
I'll watch it you should not assume that
you should bring it on your own they had
everything else but not
that yes chunky wonky has entered the
table and is planning to sit
down oh my God oh my God I think she
thinks I'm not streaming I'm just having
a conversation with a friend oh my God
which I kind of am we distracted her oh
she's curious about the toilet
sound well well well so but it's okay
because it's a prequel so it didn't
matter that you didn't watch it I
thought maybe it would matter a bit but
it didn't really
matter so we uh arrived and the thing is
there was a huge line cuz they were
underst staffed there was like how long
was this line it's a 15 minute wait for
food like for popcorn crazy line and we
we were already kind of late cuz like
normally there's not such a huge line
and and and you can just come in like
pretty late cuz they do they do like 10
minutes of ads yeah so I was like
whatever we'll be fine but we arrived at
like the beginning when the when the
movie not really the movie but the when
the ads would start is when we arrived I
think and we're like what the is
this lying yeah the and yeah I
talked to the to the ticket guy I was
like how long are they
can we make this whatever but narissa
didn't mind so much right so you waited
yeah that was sweet you you waited and I
waited for a while on the line when I
entered actually the movie already
started oh no yeah I already missed some
parts and I'm curious what I missed so I
think I'm I was probably missing and you
too M some key context yeah maybe like
an introduction of the main character of
his evil supposedly evil father I didn't
even know that his Dad was supposed to
be evil until later in the morning
because I missed that yeah same like
when his sister mentions it okay so
basically guys The Hunger Games prequel
is basically honestly it's like the same
concept it's just how The Hunger Games
became the show that they were in
the main
movies but at this point they already
had like 10 Hunger Games I think it was
the 10th anniversary said but they were
like we're probably going to end them
they're like they're not really doing
much yeah but then the main character
the villain he he was like okay they
have apparently like some kind of school
where uh they some some rich kids from
the capital who are not in the district
they learn how to be evil I guess how to
be I imagine they're learning to be the
next like leaders of the capital so
they're also being taught to
theoretically dehumanize the people in
the districts right yeah so they got to
be
the they were the mentors to the
tributes to the tributes yes so when I
entered it was basically like a little
bit of family story and then they
immediately went to the like the tribute
uh announcement mhm nobody volunteered
of course not who would volunteer well
cat cat catniss but she's not smart so
yeah so um I was kind of nervous cuz I
kept on looking behind me if you were
entering if if you were okay cuz the
door I was sure was heavy and you were
entering alone with like two popcorns
two
drinks yeah you guys volunteer oh no oh
a tribute for what for you what do you
apparently I don't guys know for catnip
catnip instead of catniss wouldn't that
be great yeah okay so I want to talk
about um it was pretty OB is obvious
from the get-go right that those two
main characters were going to have like
a love story yeah well the thing that
was interesting to me is again spoilers
they didn't frame him necessarily it
felt like as a villain he seemed really
nice yeah he he was the nicest out of
all of them mhm all of the mentors like
it seemed like he was going to be the
person who like came from this evil
background but then started to change
throughout but it was not so I mean it
was it was like that for a long time
until he then like yeah he I felt like
help her I thought he became
irredeemable when he was like we need to
make it more of a spect spectacle so
people will want to watch and donate
money cuz you can say oh well he was
trying to save her he was but he made it
so much worse by doing that but I think
at the same time he was just trying to
kiss the ass of the bosses and all that
and just get their get in their favor
mhm but yeah he should like cuz the
whole point of it was that his sister
also says so she's like you're not evil
you're not like your father uh D but
just just you know believe in that but
like the whole point of the movie is
that yeah he was always evil he was
trying to be good but he was always evil
and that's how it also ends it's like oh
oh he was so evil at the end he's so
up at the end but that was a
funny moment with the main actress
that I really wanted to share with you
guys I will not spoil the whole scene
but the main actress she's like his
tribute right he's the mentor she's the
tribute um and she's a singer she's a
really good singer so in order to get
the like attention and popularity from
the audience she sings yeah um and then
there's this one point in time where she
sings and a certain animal like is
supposed to like attack her but she's
singing and it's it looks like because
she's singing they're not attacking her
and I I leaned over to neris I was like
like she's a Disney princess yeah and
then a few minutes after that I was like
wait a second wait wait a second isn't
she the actress that's yeah like
literally uh becoming Snow White in a
Disney movie I was like is it really I
have to check after the movie is over
but this is really bothering REM did I
just say something that made so much
sense it was real like she is actually a
Disney princess you won you won she's
Snow White yeah no wonder I mean she
sings so good and they casted her in
both movies to sing basically
yeah yeah so this and then uh oh oh I
wanted one more thing that really really
really shook head for me and wonder if
they did it on
purpose anybody here who even saw the
movie guys yeah I didn't even see it yet
a lot of you guys don't know what we're
talking about but listen if you watch
the movie tell me if you felt the same
way also if you watch Game of Thrones no
no
no whatever I'll still ask you or I'll
still tell you CU at least probably a
lot of you saw Game of Thrones mhm um so
there's Peter T Peter dinglas is in this
right and he plays also pretty important
role mhm he's you would think he's evil
but the this whole time he's like taking
morphium to stay evil yeah well he's
trying he's trying to stop it basically
so he's he's like the foil to the main
character because he's like you do
realize you're making this so much worse
I'm going to do everything in my power
to make sure you see no benefit for
making this
worse but then yeah you you continue
he's he's morphe him yeah I don't know
like I guess I don't know it keeps him
like happy or hyper I don't know I
figured it was cuz he's not happy about
what he's doing yeah yeah so he if you
don't know who Peter dingl is he's he's
tyan Ty tyan Tyrion thank you in Game of
fron tyan Lannister or you might
remember him from Elf
oh really he was yeah oh I don't know
that movie he was in
what sh she's shook what laner so so he
he's like evil right and and the funny
thing is the main characters last name
is snow and at the end there's a moment
where snow the main character is alone
in the room with uh Peter dinglish yeah
yeah and they're like having like a
final talk basically that feels like oh
end of the movie
mhm and snow his last name is snow
character's last name
snow he says to
Peter cuz he's like boasting that he
just like won everything that he did it
rubs it in his face what did he say snow
always lands on top snow always lands on
top he say he says that to Peter
Dinklage and I found that funny and then
Peter Dinklage he rolls his
eyes and kind of like Huffs and puffs
after that and I'm like hm did they do
that on Purp purpose oh you know nothing
and John Snow yeah is that on purpose
guys what do you think it feels on
purpose it felt wrong to have Peter
Dinklage in a movie where the main
character's last name is Snow Yeah so
the nose I was like are you kidding it's
so on the
nose like they want some connections to
Game of Thrones M and they both have
long titles yeah yeah see these kind of
like it's just look what if what if was
Ghost written by George RR Martin I
don't think he has the time or
motivation for that I mean he writes a
lot of stuff you just won't finish the
next book anyway yeah yeah so I thought
that was really interesting the movie
was good right we were really shocked a
lot of the times in the cinema we were
both shocked and looked at each other in
shock mhm and then we held hands at the
end yeah I was surprised I was like Ki
wants to hold my hand oh my God cuz I
had a feeling that something was
happening but it wasn't happening I
thought at the end like she was like she
maybe told his sister that he's there
cuz she was hoping to meet him right I
thought you would tell him tell her his
sister that he's there to meet him and
then run away together so that they're
all happy together like as a bait yeah
so I thought that was happening and
instead of him shooting her in that
moment I thought he shot the sister and
and then he'll see it and he'll be like
no what did I do but that didn't happen
well I just still think it's so crazy
cuz they're like basically they're
saying she went missing at the end and
you could presume that she just kept
going and just left after that but it
seemed like he shot her he you know I
don't think she died they would have
showed the dead body I think I don't
know or it's like ending but now I'm
curious I want a prequel of the prequel
because I want to know about his dad and
like the family and how the H cuz like I
would think that this would show us how
The Hunger Games were created cuz it
came from a war and all that but no the
prequel of The Hunger Games it's just
the Hunger Games again yeah which I mean
it was fun and all 10 anniversary yeah
it was the 10th anniversary now I need a
prequel of the prequel cuz I want to
know about the creation of all of this I
mean I'm just glad that the main
character was hot cuz it it made he was
goodlooking yeah he was quite a
good-look guy so but I'm just so mad cuz
I was like wait he just keeps messing up
he just keeps fumbling the bag over and
over again pry smart though I mean but
also yeah he got caught and um
but I I do think it was good that it had
such an ending yeah cuz like a lot of
movies especially in the main Hunger
Games
movies there's a HP happy ending yeah
where we see
the the the ones that are suffering are
in the end wi winning yeah but here the
evil wins which leads into Hunger Games
in the end kind needs it's great yeah it
needed to be like this was great he's a
boy failure is he a boy failure uh I he
seemed like a boy success to me oh
somebody actually knows what we're
talking about it was more ambiguous in
the book on what happened ah to Lucy gra
compared oh really it was more ambigous
I mean I felt like it was ambiguous too
because Peter Dinklage was just like
they say the mayor might have killed her
who knows though and that's what's going
to tear you apart and I was like H true
oh my God there's one person who knows
what we're talking about do you want to
get into a call with us on Discord and
no stop hung games was 75 years old by
cat in this time it was pretty old yeah
they've been doing it for a while I need
to know where where Mr snow went in the
future I need to know where he is he's
probably dead but like hunger game
timeline yeah but he definitely was like
working on The Hunger Games yeah to make
it the thing that it was in The Hunger
Games actual movie so yeah sorry I
needed to nerd out about that cuz it was
really good yeah yeah how did you like
um not Superior what's the what's what's
the word for not Superior um inferior
inferior infer how did you like our
inferior popcorn oh it was fine didn't
have butter right okay look most places
in the in the US don't have great
popcorn either oh okay I I just you know
she kept on talking about her buttered
popcorn I wanted to try that too I just
have really good popcorn at home oh man
oh man I I'll show it to you sometime
you can come visit me don't know
know wow fly all the way to Austria for
a girl she won't even come be your
parents can you believe it
well no
bother yeah okay so guys we're going to
play this game uh I have still more
things I want to talk about but let's
for now I mean let's just play this game
we W even talking for like 30 minutes
yeah s oh we should probably I mean I
don't know do you want to play for OBS
or you want to play for this this it
will it will become bigger I think um
eventually uh okay this is couch Co-op
only which is perfect for us is this
loud enough guys or too
quiet oh why is it not reacting oh cuz
I'm oh okay I'll give you the man okay
cool yeah um I love this game so much
really nobody I don't think anybody in
Holo has ever played it before because
it's couch Co-op only and I don't think
people even knew about it so thank you
for the recommendation perfect yeah it's
a bit low really a lot of people are
saying it's good sounds fine okay then I
guess uh multiplayer solo Horizon yeah
Horizon what horizontal I can't read
sorry Horizon I thought that was some
weird I thought I was saying it wrong
no this whatever doesn't matter yes that
no the bloop bloop cuz I guess bloop
owns the game I don't know if that
matters oh yeah this have time
oh wow that this is this the graphics
the anime Graphics look so old oh my God
that me it already does look like you
doesn't
it father mother mommy Grandpa
Grandma
perfect oh that's perfect oh
cute orange hair is that me yeah oh
you're making me count I'll I'll change
controllers with you too that's okay can
I even oh yeah can so
static yeah I'm K's Korean
fan what is this oh
oh oh can I increase the Bona and the bo
the booty I don't think this game has a
focus on that I guess
so look at me walking so happily so cute
I'm like oh going on vacation let's
go oh and yours choose from the
I oh you can do it now oh can you oh
yeah just go with whatever well I guess
I'm you now yay oh you can control it y
y I am going to rub the belly of chunky
W cuz she's still here and offering me
her belly can you find someone that
looks like you oh who that that freaked
me
out oh oh she's
angry well they look they look really
interesting
very
interesting I'm surprised they don't let
you just do the selection yourself cuz
clearly that one looks so that one looks
like oh scares
mea I think this is the most
accurate she has Angry Eyebrows oh now
she's happy oh yeah yeah she's excited
too let's
go let's
go we're going to go on the
cash
wa oh my God we can do anything here
seems like it how are we Landing now we
jumping out of the plane yes we
are oh my God W where are the other two
people
[Music]
Marine who are we going to see those two
in the males I wonder probably not
probably not that much but fishies we'll
see fishies beautiful fishies maybe no
Dolphins but
[Music]
fish y n has a a beautiful new Kimo yeah
yeah yeah okay shut up
intro kawi Island Ka sorry CH you can
stay instead of kaai it's kawi that
sounds like I think be like Hawaii oh
chunky wonky better her leave she's like
I'm leaving Mom okay SAA SAA SAA SAA
ooh Sunshine Beach Mystic jungle
wow okay Rocky Ridge Cove oh oh that
looks like a Mario carart Track oh my
god look the m64 one uh I don't
know she talk looking she's n Crossing
do you want to read it welcome to kawi
Island home to four Ling Resorts Marine
City snow and mountain mountain all
sorts of fun activities are at your
fingertips here just go out and have a
blast finding them let's go oops allow
me to introduce myself I'm Lily one of
the resort guides pleasure to meet you
if you're ready let's go look for
activities she
did first we have to go to the Marine
Resort we have Marine Bites available so
that you can ride around on the water
let's try one out now water bik
W oh who who what right wo that was
sudden okay let's go walk and then
swim just fell into that h s l Sr look
jump oh wait
ah you stop using oh jump oh my God
you're so fast wait for me oh I'm
getting a a blue one uh use was what
that one okay oh no
oh okay we did the first mission o Pizza
we don't actually get to ride them we
just have to get to them I see that was
a full tutorial of all the things we'll
need in the game good now that that's
out of the way it's time to find an
activity to try yay the first activity
I'd like to introduce is Marine bike
races oh this activity takes place on
Eternal Beach which is just past Mary
Bay I'll mark it on the map so you don't
get lost these names they are something
once you reach it talk to someone with a
yellow icon have fun we will oh God
those those Marine bikes I've tried them
in real life have you wait what was
accelerate what the is the camera
doing wait what's the why is my what's
my what's huh huh what's my camera
what's my
cam what Happ what ah
can how do you accelerate sorry what
this I missed it ah this this button
okay you waiting for me right where are
you I'm going to the Red Dot on the map
oh it's motion
controls am I the red or the blue I'm
the red you're the blue God damn
it go go go faster you have to wait for
me I struggled really
hard woo yeah yeah so when it comes to
these like bumps in the water they're so
wobbly I hate that my friend my rmt she
would go like so so
carelessly
what carelessly uh over them and I'm
like I'm falling down please go
slower just wouldn't go slower well
you're would you go slow or would you go
fast like that um I would go slow if we
were actually together yay why wouldn't
I wait for you I'd be too scared no I
mean like if you're both on the same one
oh I mean if you were scared I'd so down
would you not be scared I'm not really
scared of that kind of stuff okay I used
to ride on
motorcycles mot not me but like other
people oh okay motorcycles are kind of
different like this is way more like you
you you're slipping off and feeling like
you're about to fall into the water fun
like have you haven't you ever gone
tubing tubing no yeah tubing I I get
knocked off on my ass I tubing I
oh my God okay read no you're you're
this guy oh I followed in my funest
footsteps becoming a Marine biker and no
one could ever beat me they call me the
Marine que oh is this a lady after all I
I guess I thought it was a boy oh I
can't press the
button I'm guessing Okay She's she's a
hot lady I can see it now in her eyes
I'm guessing you're looking to
participate in the Marine bike races I
hope you've got some real SK to show me
no I don't I don't all right then let's
get this thing started can think you can
blow me away with your skills I can't
wait to see let's e my
show okay this is basically just what we
just did okay but against her yeah okay
press
okay let's go
ikim I hope that at least you can beat
her beat her beat her beat beat her I
hope you can beat her too what do you
meano
[Laughter]
your okay wow me and the NPC should be
pretty
right wait where are we going oh it's
like Mario Kart but in the
water I'm ahead of you huh yeah
oh yeah hug the curves hug the curves
you want to hug the curves
oh something's there I'm
F good
work well now that the camera isn't
up oh there's five rounds or five goals
I don't know uhoh uh oh they want me to
jump over that huh all right oh that
worked
wo wow you see me styling do you see are
you looking at my wet butt I am that's
why I'm staying behind you actually I
could easily pull a front in front
go and now it says one of the five wait
what now oh that's oh it was my
placement
okay the the NPC isn't even on the third
one yeah right what the hell maybe she
wasn't
racing I think she was I saw her wow she
sucks I wonder if we can do this in the
mes if I can go slow if I can decide
myself I would like to do do it yeah
I'll let you drive we can both maybe
rent one or we can change we can like
switch like like you can drive for like
a while than me on the same one
yay yay do you want to do it again no
let's try a different one
okay kawi are you excited what are you
excited most for in the males I don't
even know what's there except for for
water oh we can get massages we can go
SN I'm excited for massages yes and
snorkeling do you like snorkeling I've
never been it was also my first time in
the males to snorkel it's so wow it's so
addicting like oh we would go like every
day we would put on the the goggles and
like a little snorkel thing and you
can't dive deep right cuz you need to be
above I mean some people I think still
go deeper yeah but I wanted to be able
to breathe yeah so and we were like wow
looking around we only had like a pretty
small spot where all the fishies
gathered but there were so many
different colored fishes all over it was
like everywhere and then I puked into
the
ocean excuse me I did puke into the
ocean what was wrong with you SI because
you know our our little apartment was on
top of the water so after we were done
snuggling on one day we decided instead
of walking back on the hot hot um
pavement uh of it was it was out of wood
but still uh how about we just swim back
and you know maybe there's some more
fishies
so we we snorkled and swam to the house
which was like maybe
uh
10 10 minute swim swarm but I got really
sick for some reason and I was like wait
I'm getting sick wait I'm getting sick
she was in front of me and I kept on
saying I think I think I'm I think I'm
getting sick I think I'm getting sick
and eventually it really threw up and I
think wa wasn't looking cuz she was
really far ahead thank God she was far
away yeah I was like stay away I'm
throwing up I'd hold your hair out of
the way for you thank you it was the
ocean we're going to swim in later it
was really disgusting but I think the
fish enjoyed it it was really probably
nutrient yeah they're like
M yeah the waves and me swimming so much
and the heat I think all of it normally
I don't get sick just by swimming I
actually get really sick if it's too hot
if I overheat in my stomach especially
it's like fil and I get hot I'll throw
up too so I understand I actually I won
mind I think I know I know why it was
because I was accidentally through
snoring eating so much of the salt water
I I I remember now yeah I was like I was
I was I was gulping gulping uh down all
the salt water cuz like when you snorkel
if you're not good at it like you you
just accidentally get salt water in
there I every time I've been in the
ocean I glug down on accident I'm like
someone called it your Chum be
careful be careful I'm scared right all
right lady well you've still got ways to
go you
got wao she's salty yeah but they say
practice makes perfect if you want to
get better come back again what is she
saying bloop Kiana way to go just set a
new record I can't wait to see what you
can pull up next next bounce bounce
bounce yay yay oh one out of 10
activities 19 left before you reached 20
oh yes I am 19 years
old what 19 what no 19 19 years I'm one
year
old I I don't know if this has to do
with your age I think it does I don't I
think it does I don't think so I think
okay you congratulations you got a stamp
I bet you didn't see that coming stamp
rally here at kawi Island we put
together a special promotion to help
people find the best activities to
participate in we call it the kai stamp
Dash oh my God it is a stamp rally the
stamp you just got as part of it the
rules are simple I recommend activities
for you one at a time and you have all
you have to do is try them out I can't
read I'll mark your map with each
activity I recommend so be sure to take
a look okay special gear is also
available at each resort to help you
find the activities you're looking for
here at the Marine Resort we offer
Marine bikes and ATVs so be sure to try
them out ATVs I don't know what that is
every time you participate in a new
activity you get a stamp you'll get
spectacular prizes in return so good
luck oh my God I want to collect the
stamps we're going to have to uh do we
understand it yes yeah perfect then let
the Kaa stamp Dash begin quad bikes ah
oh that's sick quad bikes I don't think
they have them on our Island
but yeah one more thing I'm going pause
to see the stamp
menu oh up or down oh what we can get a
dog that's how it looks
okay what you every they want you to
come back every day to see their
different stuff what we
can oh my God okay are you what are you
doing are you too hot now yeah H oh
my got again I'll take the Corgi that's
a corgi right on the right so okay this
is not a race I think we're just going
to the next
activity let's
go this is so exciting like we're
already there it will be it's like kind
of surreal it is it's Al it's also
surreal that you're here next to me
isn't it I it is very weird how did you
feel the moment you saw me very confused
um I was like oh my God I just never
thought this day would happen you know I
I said this before I was fully convinced
you were not going to like me because I
like I was fully convinced I was going
to like you so I was like oh she's
probably going to be like oh God this
weirdo she's like my o she say I'm her
ooshi you they'll know what you're
talking about for real because you're
like I love
you we're gonna do
skying ow what the
wait let me get off of that can I get
off of that wait how do I get off of
that again oh oh oh oh they reset me
what are you doing I don't know I'm lost
I'll start this activity for us yeah
I'll try please I'm counting on you
dancing meeting at skydiving if you miss
out then you're going to miss out ooh
what are you
doing there are all kinds of activities
at this Restort but none of them are as
exciting as
skydiving oops I forgot to introduce
myself too like all the other NPCs here
I'm actually the skydiving pilot and
I'll be heading out on a never flight
any minute the skydivers are flying with
make incredible formations in the sky
while falling seeing them in action is
amazing sick so what do you say are you
ready to jump into the Great Blue Yonder
there's nothing to be scared of you just
need guts do you have guts or nuts do
you have some nuts dud you have the
balls to do this
no well I do and that's good enough I
have more nuts I have enough nuts for
all all three of us okay I'm glad you
got the nuts I wasn't aware please read
oh oh we line this is so fun oh my God
it's like a Mari I think that's a Mario
Party game like pretty much M rotating
and all tilting up and down I'm scared
press
okay it's you on it oh I have to go down
yeah you talked okay you started the
conversation guess I I
did air in a group okay okay
okay my okay I'm like so distracted we
should do like a a like we should do in
the mivs we should just do a talking
stream why we F focus on talking about
all of this cuz I'm so distracted
yeah like my first impression of you if
I even remember that
okay tget 500 points all right where are
the formations Beyonce wants us to get
into
formation I did
[Laughter]
it well that's fun oh W she did a
flip oh oh wait where am I oh wait I'm
going there
oh yeah we don't even have to do
anything like in terms of really
actually going into that position it
just automatically aligns US ah
please get slip up the tongue what did
they say what did they say I don't know
huh what did you
say then that's were on purpose
so where you going where are you going
you're going to die hold on to us I'm
trying
[Applause]
yo don't worry about it okay oh oh it's
so easy I think they're just making
things
up why am I so
bad oh my got to die you're
going to
die oh my
God flap harder you need to become you
need to this is training for w look at
that being
Ted they're holding your legs e e don't
touch me this is training for becoming
Hol Birds yes practicing our flight
skills damn all right all right next one
next
one you so bad it's just like flailing
around so good I tried my best it's so
good I'm trying so hard our formation
still I feel like this is a this must be
an official sport right oh oh wait I'm
also oh there we
go is this an official sport like like
you know in water there's this sport
where they do like cute
formations like almost like ballet in
the water this is like this but in the
sky it is oh of course it is well
narissa will not be joining that that
Sports
me Sky that's so
cool yes I was talking about
synchronized swimming yeah okay where
are we going next maybe there is maybe
you're lucky and the formation lands
directly on you oh oh that's it
yeah clear
clear
W amazing oh a replay of I don't think
we need to watch that again oh I want to
watch it oh are you
sure that one was still pretty fast but
you're
like like a I don't know like a fish out
of the
water oh
yeah I'm looking at your
crotch I see wow I didn't know you were
so lud K cam re word oh you're always
the last
where's she going where is she going
there she
is I think we're kicking you out of the
sky formation team understandable have a
nice day why do we get the same amount
of porns because we did we I didn't miss
any still don't be mean don't be mean I
quit can't work with this team
wow that was fun though that was funny
mhm
why are you laughing like that so funny
yo you've got the skydiving Buck now and
I'm pretty proud of myself for
introducing you to the sport looks like
Ro from Pokemon yeah his hair is so
spiky mhm uh r k that's one amazing
record keep it up except for youa like
maybe you should do something
else he said that no he didn't he said
that I can read the screen yeah he said
that it came out it came out of his
speech
bubble wasn't me yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah what's next that looks like
volleyball a little bit you get a
volleyball I thought you were trying to
tell me something okay she poked me now
for the the next activity is you you're
not going to read that no why is it too
cringe for you
yes beach volleyball matches take place
at the beach volleyball court at
sunshine Beach have fun
yay oh oh ah we can choose the ATV oh or
we can walk or Swim I don't know how far
it is I don't know what an ATV the
ATV it's the the quad
bike I guess same
controls oh
vissa I'm leaving you
behind or maybe not actually who oh the
controls oh this is Mario
Kart
90x
oh oh
wait we have to go around there oh
no did you just flatten the guy in
you kill someone I would never be
careful with that bike it can be really
dangerous oh maybe we should have used a
Pro Controller but I only have one so I
decided we're going to do oh I brought
one oh we stopped moving
interesting wait wait I have
arrived app is being weird
oh oh it's like doing an update thing
maybe again I don't know it's being
weird kicked me out there we go I'm
moving a we want to do we want to give
him a male voice how's your male
voice oh she's yawning I'm too boring
for her no hey L that last race was
amazing ATV sure are complex machines
looks like you're an ATV fan what do you
say want to go for a rhin hoom me you'll
have a blast trust me yeah great
it's settled get ready to ride with the
wind on your ATV so dope man so dope R
oh we're doing ATV race what what about
the I don't know it l us here
right
oh what's doing well I kicked you out of
one you're back oh
stretching finish relapse um I'm good
with the with the boat but not with this
I think it's the same controls yeah but
this one's feels more
wobbly we'll see we'll
see yeah I'm last place I agree can we
jump too I guess we
can maybe not desirable wow why are
there so good I have to hug the
curves okay oh I a you you my
curves okay here we go
I'm first this is why I'm not
participating in the Mario Kart oh
because I would win my God because I
would
win so I wasn't
looking yo the motion controls are so
sensitive for
real all right all right all right I'm
trying to destroy the competition yeah
do it do
it yeah destroy them yeah in a liter
[Music]
sense yeah yeah I'm doing
good there is he's looking at my
B it's
okay oh
okay I'm second currently and
you're you've got a good oh
nice that looks safe to
me just keep it
up splash splash splash
splash so was this game made for kids
then I would say it's like a family game
yeah if anything not for kids alone oh
oh it's okay it's okay I'm still right
behind you and I'm still in second
somehow oh final lap oh my
God the game could still go any which
way what's it going to be Ki this a good
game though like oh my God why did I not
know about this until now yeah it's cute
now we're off collab
game family Wii game oh is it originally
on from the Wii ooh was it
ported M definitely baby game what
no this is not a baby game it's a fun
game you're my baby game Mario Kart like
yeah you my baby game
mhm I feel like there's no one even
behind me where did they go they they're
somewhere there but they have no chance
at this
point okay Never Say Never K
winning yay oh under three minutes
nice
that's a weak I'm so sorry one
more
[Music]
Yun let good it started pretty bad but
we did well oh he is actually on there
okay so they do race us getting the
person we raced for the other one both
both of us beat them and they still were
like you've got a ways to go yeah what
the hell was that about how annoying how
rude mhm right he's f he can at least
like say something yeah no but I will
not have respect see you later anyway
see you later good job listen there's
lots of other stages for racing ATVs so
come back again for some more fun Blum
Kiara congrats on setting a new record
let's see if it if you can break it
again no um we totally skipped
volleyball wa wasn't on our M it's not
my fault I think you started the the
wrong game but it's okay cuz we can play
any of them congrats on getting three
stamps in exchange I'll show you to the
information
center at each resort act as a home base
friendly staff will gladly help you with
outfits traveling to other Resorts and
the school school who wants to go to an
island to go to school feel free to talk
to them
anytime information center is always
starting point one at each Resort if
you're not sure where you are just check
the map in the pause menu okay uh yeah
it's probably close by cuz
yeah I'll just walk there okay it's
probably right there where we're
supposed to go
yeah I I'll let you
leave don't what are you
doing don't don't drive on me into me
sorry I spent a month in Grace for
school one week was okay well that's
pretty I mean yeah it's a dope place to
be wait a second narissa look at this
you see those houses yeah exactly yeah
what it looked like for us I found
volleyball yeah I know but this is also
Bo it is we had like this kind of path
and then I'm sorry we couldn't stay in
one like that this time it's okay I'm
like pretty you know happy anyway M very
happy
yeah oh this is
nice somewhere there somewhere out
there's my
puke I think fish have eaten it I think
it's been converted you don't have to
worry anymore about your Chum oh man but
then a fish
maybe a fish that ate my puke someone
ate it
maybe maybe someone ate it or that fish
made more babies and they all carrying
my
DNA yeah yeah
yeah yeah
I wish your eyebrows would really
reflect your real eyebrows cuz she's
doubting what I'm saying I
think look at her she's mean wow fish
yeah she has the same
hair um S A set and Spike I'm in a
Groove today so are you up around the
beach volleyball it's great playing with
the sand between your toes and winding
your
hair what's the hold up you've got to at
least give it a shot the courts on yours
now take the ball and let's do this
let's ball let's do this let's ball
Queen oh oh no I'm going to be bad at
this me to serve receive set and
spiking
easy um what was
it for Steve SP no what was that it
depends if we're on the same team oh
okay you only you got to tell me when if
you're on the
same
oh are we
oh but what if I just never surf cuz
you're not telling me cuz I have the
ball I could just never serve so hitting
it is this one okay if you want to spike
so when you're up here
spiking are you serious I don't know I
only know German terms for when you play
volleyball is it like the no so this is
just a regular thing when you're spiking
it's when you're close to the thing and
you hit it down so that's going to be
you're going to jump first and then
you're just going to hit the regular HP
button look at my tricks jump is going
to be this so you're going to jump this
okay
oh okay now you're going to beat
me
wa what the
you little
what she's laughing at
[Laughter]
me you did you wi you try your best my
teammate is oh did backwards let's
go oh fail fail no they even go there
automatically oh let's go didn't expect
that huh didn't expect you got one point
you got one point we're got we're going
to get more
more you tried to assassinate
her that was right in her
face bro
bro let's go we're winning let's go
stranger I fell
over yo she's strong y our computers are
both like carrying like we are not doing
but these
computers
oh
no
nice Bring It On hey
hey I did
[Music]
that why is mine not so powerful when I
do
that no do it go what
oh M it just means you didn't do it
right but that's okay I didn't do mine
right
either she's going in and I'm going in
too is it maybe the timing I wonder yeah
I think it has something to do with the
timing as well as your actual
positioning towards the
net whoa that the the the the game
didn't even plan for that yeah for real
I just did something else oh I was
did something else oh I stopped moving
again the computer didn't wait I'm sorry
[Applause]
no I'm sorry teammate it's okay I'll fix
it speaking of teammates Amma has her
birthday stream coming up in a few hours
oo yeah and I'm going to call in I'll be
awake it's like 2 after 2:00 a.m. for me
but we'll we'll we'll be awake it'll be
fun we were long awake yesterday too
yeah I I I might be asleep no meow I
heard a
meow this is better than wi Sports no
maybe not I don't know it's pretty good
it's pretty on it's Beach be so yeah
it's
awesome going to we should play beach
volleyball in the mold but I don't know
only us two might be a little bit lame
yeah but I did buy a little a little
blow up water ball that we can play with
in the water and like shoot at each
other guys by the way I don't know if
there's any artists in the chat right
now but um I uh requesting publicly
hereby asking you politely does anybody
want to draw Kia wha on the beach or in
the water or in swimsuits fan art please
for our thumbnails yeah I need need it
thumnail creation cuz we can't just use
our kimonos
yeah sadly I don't have a bikini outfit
not yet not yet she's there all right so
[Music]
artist mizi
mizi you just oh oh oh what's happening
what
happened yeah
yeah what kind of swimsuit oh what kind
of swimsuit would you like to be drawn
in I actually usually wear one pieces
mhm mhm but um I actually bought a ton
of two pieces just for you oh for me so
I'm wearing them so you can see me cuz I
know that's what you want you distracted
me you little you were thinking
about me in a two-piece that sounds like
a you
problem it won't be a problem it will be
a
delight
exactly okay so are they like are they
are they girly or are they sexy they're
more girly I'd
say you thought you could get me with
that
now I'm like not good at spiking in this
w
eyes it's a TI for
now
oh
dramatic mold ended cancel it's too late
I'm in Austria you can't cancel
it
[Laughter]
very very chaotic oh my god do it do it
girl yeah deu Deuces Deuce isn't that
kind of a word for
poop I don't know like I think I heard
this before dropping a deuce or
something what I think I heard that
before you okay guys chat what do you
say I
don't
they locked me out they locked me out no
more Kiwa the
why would they do that yeah just
okay I'm serving so you can just log in
thank you get back in it's okay I think
I'm coming back back to life okay go
ahead oh oh oh you get in the last hit
ah I knocked you
over you made me stump I'm going to
break my leg
no
oh oh what the is that what the
what was that
wa hey hey hey
ah
hey we're sweating I'm sweating I'm
turning into a sweaty
game I mean I I I would say not me
sweating but the characters are probably
sweating is it done no game
set and
[Music]
match I could have won cute dance cute
dance too bad I don't know I don't know
about that but I'll give you this win
cuz I won against you in the races only
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah so it's
understandable it was close though close
so close good match good match yeah I
think it's just you know stop moving
again mhm oh why is it so
stupid why is it so stupid
today I'm not
sure oh are you starting to get the hang
of running on Sand you only just started
so take your time come back and play
again it does kind of mean as hell why'
you say that what you only just getting
used to running on the
sand yeah takes some time to get used to
I mean I didn't take it like that yeah
um oh oh St let's
go oh what's next D diving ooh maybe
why oh it's just not doing anything why
is it broken why are you broken is it
like updating again or what the hell
oopsie uh go ahead and read it BL Kiara
congrats on getting four
stamps it's just restarting it a million
times uh-huh
you can now access the city Resort just
visit the information center and the
snap will help you they
skateboard oo now for Kaa stamp Dash the
next activity I'd recommend
is scuba diving yes let's go scuba oh oh
so I don't know it's okay let's go I
think she made her Point yeah you're
right should
we walk swim I'm I'm good to walk and
swim why did it stop again why you
broken oh wow oh which way oh oh it's
pretty far oopsie but we can still
change to a boat or so if we want over
there there's one I wonder if you can
ride the same one this is basically
Hunger Games this is the hung G why
don't we just talk to the people we're
close to you have to win competition to
be allowed to enter the city yeah I
guess it is The Hunger Games this guy
looks like he's doing something
no we have to we have to go go to the
scho diamond I'll never get there go in
my boat or find a different one wait
here I have a boat can you can you go
on no wa wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait yeah yeah jump onto it
yeah I think like a hit box it doesn't
work okay go
oh go go go I can start it and then uh
you'll be teleported there
[Music]
fine where is it
somewhere oh no that's uh
wait is it that thing over there no this
is something with the boats and then
that is a speech
bubble oh you might reach after all
I have no idea where I
am look on the
map is that like a a purple waterfall
what am I looking at that maybe is where
we sco ah wait I found it ah yeah what
nice
job hello I have arrived I would like to
scuba scuba
scuba ding ding
please I'm going as fast as I these
characters can walk on water like ninja
no it's like really shallow
usually all right you read welcome to
scuba
diving hi scuba diving allows you to see
all sorts of colorful sea creatures and
explore the wonders of an underwater
world can we find gooy B in the water
hopefully are you interested in trying
your hand or fin this scuba diving
activity wow I guarantee you all sorts
of treasures await
you swimming but how is it a game how
can we win I find the sea turtles within
5 minutes oh okay well all right all
right practice reading
Kiana how do we win on the
screen oh you can't say that to
me oh those are the same fishes that I
saw before the blue
ones why am I only
aend I don't think it's oh weren't the
buttons supposed to do something yeah so
yeah you hit a button to
find okay what is this camera it turns
out there's I think
six I see okay the camera I think
doesn't do anything
oh the SE Turtles can we hold on to them
no but we need to find six ah wait
ah ah where did it go where did it go
where did it
go wait is our are we not against each
other we're like no no no we're a team
oh wait I found I see one but it's
already been found I think that's why
it's making the music right oh
oh
see Turtle do we have a turtle vtu in
whole life no we should though it's
about time they can be extra slow for
everything they do oh okay I see the
last
one okay on my way to
it this is nice yeah this is getting me
really excited for the m i can't open my
eyes
underwater Oh that's okay me NE we got
like goggles like that yay
y ooh I used to open my eyes under under
even sea water when I was younger but I
don't want to do it anymore not even
under pool water yeah I same it just
hurts it's not pleasant yeah it burns it
burns oh actually I have my own swimming
glasses thingies oh yeah yeah goggles oh
goggles yeah small ones for
swimming but it didn't really help me in
my swimming uh Advent Venture cuz I was
trying to swim regularly and then the
problem is like the best way of swimming
that really helps your back is this
style mhm how's it what's it
called I don't know what why don't you
know I don't know I'm doing it IRL guys
they a crawl but yeah for that one you
kind of like keep your head under water
and then when you up you breathe and
then you breathe out and you breathe but
I can't do that I tried my friend even
tried to teach me but I couldn't do it I
can't do it either the timing was so
difficult the Rhythm mhm yeah so instead
I just uh swim like this mhm freestyle
it's nice no not freestyle I don't know
what the I doggy paddle doggy paddle oh
dog you doggy
paddle for real yeah doggy P what you
doggy P yeah why are you making fun of
me she doggy P I don't know I can't
swim I mean
we I think we both agreed on us both not
being good
swimmers but you doggy paneling blows my
mind I well for real you go like this in
the water
yeah she's laughing at me that is like
you're
doggle well I'll be your dog in the M
what if I lift you over the water you
still going to Doggy P like a dogle in
the Aira I'm drowning please oh looking
forward to that
mhm oh wait was she saying something H
nothing
important let's go to the next activity
okay hope it doesn't make us talk to her
every new
activity I think it will it's always a
different person okay no her oh her next
one she recommend
[Music]
is you can only do it at cocon island
cocon island in order to get there talk
to one of the cocon staff located on the
sunshine Beach pier have fun okay how we
going to go Marine bike mhm okay Mar say
bye thank you for letting me your
bike oh it's wait it's right
here it's like right over there and
D how do we get off again I don't even
know how did you get off I don't even
know you're already no we're meeting in
scuba diving
no oh how did you cancel that I don't
know oh meeting at COC yeah that that
was correct right welcome let's go
surfing oh my God she's such a surfing G
I love it welcome come here whenever you
want to transfer to cocona Island the
surface Paradise let's head out wo oh oh
you have to yeah
oh no we
up she thinks we're like really
indecisive this way right oh that's what
she sounds like right this way guess she
has a really low voice but I want to say
she has a high voice
right Hi how are you doing very much
that
Vibe American California how you you
doing how you doing baby how you doing
you know I'm trying to sound like um the
guy from friends I have never seen Joey
how are you
doing yeah P Joe my camera stopped
working
again it's okay oh oh my I'm assuming
you can't uh surf me neither it's a
dream what are you doing did you
completely give give up oh no you're
actually going there I thought we were
already about to do it no we got to meet
the guy to go surfing we already have
the surfing boards yeah to get around
faster have you have you never seen
friends that's what I
said you know Home Improvement we
watched before kind of lowkey watched it
we napped while watching Home
Improvement yeah but you don't know
friends no friends it must be known by
especially it but I just I don't I've
never seen
it wow
okay how do we do this while Airborne SL
or Sr for horizontal spin trick vertical
spin trick any direction shake that
seems easier we don't have to press any
buttons we just shake it right or I
guess okay wait nail some tricks no it's
going to be like with me in 1080
snowboarding I st moving again
unbelievable it is very very very bad
cute oh
cute oh it crashed great and let's share
it with the
developer okay pull off tricks uh what
only me I think we're going to go on
wait I don't know what how the this
it ended I didn't serve I pressed the
button though me too late
what
okay what sick
trick
why you saing who penalty why oh cuz you
failed thing
is what's happening oh it's going to eat
you up be
careful
oh oh
oh why am I getting proud I think it's
to Landing The Landing
maybe but I don't know if it's as strict
as 1080 snowboarding at least you got
some points I
think whoa why didn't they not let me
surf oh my God that's wa this must be an
incredible feeling to be engulfed in the
water
terrified
yeah I don't understand what's going on
yeah yeah turn twist yeah do it do some
cool stuff
[Music]
e cool sick Tony
haw well on the water oh I have to like
wait for it to like shoot me up I'm very
confused let it flow naturally wo wo yo
yo and she drowned in the end the end is
the end of her surf a career oh wait can
we do it again I didn't get to
serve you we do it one more time yes you
don't need to read what they said wait
did it just say zero points for you
though it gave us both d rank and for a
for a moment I thought I I saw zero
points that's
okay did I see that right both had check
the Vault later yeah
welcome don't talk to
me water water gun battle that's so fun
damn it I should have bought water
guns for trip they might have some okay
do you want to talk to him again
yeah come on let me do it I won't fail
this time I
promise why is he telling us his laugh
story again I don't know like bro we are
not
interested okay good luck wait let me
read this again
oh oh so many
things
surfing is a sport where you ride waves
while standing on the surf floor try to
surf for as long as you can pull off
cool trcks a wave of a gentle slope a
large wave of a tube shaped
part good for tight turns and high jumps
good for getting Oh Long yeah we have
the short board okay what about the
tricks score
TR oh grading riding grading graded by
riding Time air tricks stumble penalties
mhm
Coco Co what there's coconuts that we
can
collect oh wait here paddling when
you're floating in the sea press to
paddle surf when it appears I did that
it's gone immediately let's do it again
don't worry while standing on a surf for
tilt the joycon in the direction you
want to
turn while standing on a surfboard hold
down s l and tilt the joyon in the
direction you want to turn turn more
sharply with a normal turn I will forget
this while standing on the surfboard
press Sr to jump off the wave into the
air s r to jump off the wave did you do
that the more air power left hand go you
have stored up the higher you can jump
into the air keep running waves to store
up your air power if you get too far
inside of waves tube you may get
overcome by it to avoid this flick the
joycon matching on the onc screen propt
to escape from the CH uhhuh a air jump
okay whatever I'll be fine
yeah St St oh uh I guess just the normal
one okay
[Music]
okay let's go surfing we'll be the sexy
surf babes
[Music]
he okay oh we start from here did we do
that before
no we're doing it the same time
now I thought you couldn't do
that is this is this a surfable wave I
don't think
so no we got to get out there okay why
are you so far behind cuz I'm confused
this is a surfable
wave okay I'm
surfing oh and
then
[Applause]
we oh I actually landed properly but
this is not really surfable yeah we got
to go further back
yeah unrealistic
why what's wrong with this are you going
to surve on
that I'll go over I think oh maybe I
maybe I should try to get as many of
these as
[Music]
possible oh yeah cuz there's a timer y
B okay this is my this is my wave okay
get
it a
I am being so
small all right land at that baby
yeah oh it was already pretty small but
when we made it
work surf surf surf surf surf surf and
turf
Baby Surf and Turf e okay let's go next
wave go go girl go go no time to
waste oh we both sto moving
interesting
oh no what's going on no girl what
are you
doing there we
go ah no why did you already give it up
ah one more
minute yeah we're very FOC a big nasty
wave this is this is
nasty
okay
uh yeah oh oh I made it okay that worked
I didn't want to go too
hard oh I need more more Air
energy
oh no I want to go this side
no
no I think you're going to win this I
don't know what is your score I don't
know I think W wait we're about the
same
oh I want the big nasty wave
o there's no time oh
ah ah i
[Music]
w were you throwing no no she says no we
had no tasty waves they were all baby
ones rank two yeah before I think it
really said zero maybe because you never
landed one of those I did though you're
so mean the game said penalty penalty
penalty yeah but now we kind of rocked
it yeah
mying
yay quit surfing are you sure yeah are
we quitting
forever no you're done with it yeah
let's go to the next activity
next next next I think it's like right
next to us than
okay bye oh no oh we oh did we say we're
surfing again no this just our GE to
walk around okay oh okay oh see over
here oh what's
this running with a surfboard the
challenge oh it sends us
back
oh ah hey why did they bring us here for
one to Surf I guess cuz the other place
there's too many like boats and stuff in
the way to Surf I guess maybe just
dropping conversation that you do wi
serving even though it was 10 years ago
once I would probably do that when when
to wind surfing once in my life 10 years
ago get to know somebody they asked me
what so what did you do k um son I do
wind
surfing you d i I would love to say that
I would love to be able to say that I
would also love to say to you oh played
with k for one hour w we get points for
that wa
nice I would love to say the following
because it is true um while I do rock
climbing rock wall climbing I guess it's
called
bouldering right I don't know yeah it
was um I I totally still do it it
totally wasn't just on my how do I get
off again just in my childhood no I can
do tricks just here randomly
yeah of course of course you
can
sick wait can you start some activity
cuz I don't know how to get off of I
don't know how you keep on doing that
how do you get off of it a there you go
I'm running over people you're going to
want to get over here quick and stop me
ah yeah I did I did do
um
paragliding um
yeah I did actually in 2023 I parag
glided I remember pretty
sick it looked very fun it was a lot of
it was very nerve-wracking but a lot of
fun like very very M adrenaline inducing
are you an adrenaline Dunkey no not at
all like this was like I wouldn't do
like bunny jumping for example for me
paragliding was my
compromise I see are you going to do
that here what what is she
offering oh ah you found the right one
water a gun battle there we go she
almost puked there too yeah pretty
normal to get sick stop puking I didn't
puke why do you puke him held it
back wow he one go B on the best I just
wish he would come play once in a while
my dad but he went out to buy milk um
yeah not I'm not talking about my little
brother he's always whining about the
water so he went to have a snowball
fighting instead yeah we totally have
snow up here forget about him I'm ready
for another round you better watch your
back up there oh okay okay it's a
free-for all with water gun Splash
everyone and complete compete for points
shoot build
pressure okay
okay fun yeah this is The Hunger Games
let's go what the The Hunger Games
you're going to kill me with the water
gun I will attempt to do so bash my
skull
in oh Mystic jungle
oh are we not going out of the red line
maybe I believe
so bring it
on oh are we playing against each
[Music]
other how do you turn like
that please
a oh oh the camera why is it why doesn't
why doesn't it motion control in this
case what she she rolls on the ground oh
oh are you are you killing someone Nissa
I'm
trying I got him oh I need I need
pressure yeah yeah yeah
yeah let he Al again like reloading or
maybe they recharge
no are you trying to shoot
me don't shoot
there I will shoot you back ah reload
reload see your shirt get wet reload
reload he so he revived that little
bastard I know they keep
Reviving there hey I was attacking the
guy behind
you I knocked him off yay I got a point
for that yeah
I show you okay 100% water pressure now
let's get
Nissa why are you all coming after
me we are not a
team no
no why are they only coming after
me don't worry I'm taking this this one
down
yeah ah he's running away like a little
like a little no there's a
help let's double double team double tag
yeah yeah yeah yeah ah
ah
yay oh nice wait that shouldn't help you
cuz if you end up stealing the kill
we're playing together what do you mean
but you get the
Kill
ah Ah that's my kill yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah oh Oh She Wants
Revenge how can she do that they didn't
teach us how to roll on the ground how
to to dodge oh
you you're going for me you're going for
me why is she defending
you FPS Arc I don't know this is really
comparable oh yeah I had one more kill
than you good work good job we dominated
yeah I there are only seven treasure
chests scattered around the resort you
found zero wow thanks
like yeah wow wow that's nice of you the
yearly FPS is now done yeah I'm done
checked it off my list yes he was happy
he had someone to play with I guess yeah
ooh
at ATS at ATV ATV uh
jumping game let's go
welcome tricks wild Hills okay oh FPS
not FPS
TPS whatever same thing basically I wish
it would give us the stuff that's like
close yeah or just teleport us but she
wants us to look
around they going to they're going to
throw me
no no no I was reset let me give me get
me off of there get me off of there oh
ooh Who will find it first oh this boat
you will find it first I'm so
lost oh purple area what is this I'm
going to get this ATB bike do
it
oh it's cute it's
purple what a cute bike how do you drive
again oh yeah I probably know how to
drive because next up we're having a
challenge where we
drive o up the mountain Mountain where's
the snow by the way did they say they
have snow and skiing but I don't really
I'm not on the mood for skiing I'm here
to enjoy the beach at the sunshine
mhm I wonder oh I found you I wonder if
this is the right the
right move there stop ride me oh who is
that I don't know this is the ride p
uh uh wobbly wobbly no
wobbly oh I think I'm getting closer to
it you're just running now
yeah you gave up I did but this is
basically practice right now I'm weak I
found a frog a frog yeah that was a frog
it's up
there we'll never reach it oh you
found it
mhm
sug wow Lissa taking charge finding all
the games for us to
play okay I'll take charge in the moldes
don't worry yeah you better you take
charge in the game I take charge IRL
mhm oh are you loving the resort so far
there are tons of Co activities to try
but Nar is wicked as a ATV tricks
activity Wicked here I'll set the goal
for you just bam it and everyone will be
like waa you're the best what the
if you're uper you totally got an enter
give it a shot okay nail a bunch of
tricks in one jump okay okay it's the
same thing as surfing it seems like but
with the bite M yeah
okay bring it on it's all about
technique going roack up a wicked trick
combo a
combo combo w why you always you always
look so tired
narissa maybe go to bed de Soldier maybe
it's time to go to bed and heal your jet
leg you won't let me get any
sleep how is
that yo I got way more than you yeah
how what did I do
wrong try again okay let's look at
no you could looked at what you did
wrong we should do it again you look so
angry try again it literally said try
what did you say did you choose crit or
try again I don't
know we try again yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah o go go go again go again
scoot that's a
scoot stop talking to
me
that's is goodest workout goodest
workout goodest
workout come on orange hair
lady oh
oops this is so cute I like this
game
yooo
yooo new resort unlocked it did we oh is
that where the snow stuff is Maybe
maybe huh I didn't even notice that pop
up in the game we just we just got rid
of all the messages
mhm you're got to be doing this IR real
soon I don't know about the ATVs but
[Music]
yeah
how did you not go straight into the
goal oh wait this say try again wait can
we go back up and do it again no
right now I wasn't so good
either why you trying to find uh we
could go back yeah
ah they should just let us do it again
wait wait wait wait
wait now you're mad too try again I mean
okay yeah what are we doing
wrong yeah how come I didn't get to jump
so high again let's
go where are the turns waa woo okay
okay mine was accepted my my score what
are you doing what is she doing let me
look at this I I want to see what you're
doing I will judge it cuz I feel like
you were doing some
turns oh you were low way lower than me
I
think I said quite a
few
I I'm not sure why I was hired this I
didn't land
properly L one more
time one more time one more time you'll
get it this time yeah get him go get him
don't crash don't do tricks too close to
the landing I
[Music]
guess easy I don't know I still didn't
get a i 73 I got a new
record okay what happened you're such a
show off yeah let's let's show it off
let's show it off
oh action camera oh oh look how high I
just went out of frame yeah but that
looks good you at least landed I got two
yeah wonder how I'm not getting so
high hi high high the
time next activity yeah we got one more
left on this Resort okay are you sure
yeah that was
fun oh oh I wonder what outfits they
have though apparently a outfit oh well
me it's on the ocean later later space
taxi to the sky I so people know the
song read something tells me that you
still want to pull off tricks well
whenever you up to it just give me a
holler I mean I totally would well BL
that's a new record that totally blows
my mind go thank
you she likes me cuz I'm sick as as
who wouldn't like
[Music]
youu uh oh uh we're going to the Red Dot
can we make it
oh sorry
sorry oh oh oh ow oh the controls are so
weird I wish I could just not do motion
controls yeah you made it that is a
crazy joke that's what I was trying to
do too was get over this mountain and
just jump off it this this GTA I am way
better at driving in GTA than
this I wish this had GTA
controls did you ever play GTA before
Noe I mean I did once a long time ago oh
which one I don't
know GTA 2 GTA three I have no idea I
hate to tell you this I don't remember
anything oh I'm about to die
oh I found something we didn't do before
I don't know this not the one that we
it's Bunch jumping it's not the one that
they're showing us though we do Bunch
jumping if you want oh oh oh my God I'll
save you I think I literally just
died oh but you're doing tricks and I
don't know what you're
doing welcome of it's incredible oceans
jungles and beaches a walk through the
Marine Resort is nothing short of
stunning so why not jump off of a cliff
and just
die yeah so let's go bungee jumping that
totally sounds like a good idea not
dangerous at all not dangerous at
all start activity oh we're not going to
be are are they going to show us how to
do it or do we just jump I think we just
jump okay let's go it's sponge jumping
what what else is there to it you just
jump oh we jump from the Pirate Rock
everything's pirate themed oh I don't
want to jump from this rock a record for
what pull The Brak to stop close to the
ground what's the break
button that's a button I pressed this
one but I pressed all of them in a
circle really fast none of them stopped
me God damn it but this is like a this
is like a reaction yeah let's try again
try again we we'll figure out the stop
Buton no maybe it's what je is
maybe did we die no no we just I don't
know we just
touch we test and see what the button is
yeah
okay I literally just pressed every
single button and none of them stopped
it I didn't do this though maybe I did I
feel like I felt a a small tiny Rumble
maybe if you don't do it before that it
doesn't count
count yes yeah maybe it will tell
us teach us please how to
play this
one oh a flipping okay there we go a
it's no button this is motion okay here
we go here we go here we
go my boss keeps dying in bunch of jump
no don't worry I don't know what happen
do you actually have to do something in
bu jumping I don't know right it just
happens I think so so I don't know why
this is
us okay here we
go
bunie and H
oh we definitely flipped it both of us
at the same time even well but I felt a
rumble again so maybe we were really one
more time one more time oh I'm
sorry
no what do I I doing
wrong maybe
more we give it a
go maybe
earlier oh it worked
a oh you went way closer to the round oh
cuz I thought I should do it when it
rumbled mhm but I I'll okay seems like
that's not necessary all right oh one
more one more one more okay we finally
figured it out I don't know what was
wrong with the previous one I think
we're just doing it too late that that
first time okay one our hair strands
already touched it your horns especially
mhm
no
what let's go let's run let's run I'm
heading up no I want to do it again this
is
unbelievable one more
time what I was even saying now early
trying to throw you off but it didn't
work in the end we just lifted it at the
same same this is a game of chicken
chicken only one of us in this room is
technically a
chicken oh I definitely want you got it
I went I went too late but I still
couldn't get it like you did with feet
off the ground isn't that a
song Something feet off the ground I
think so some rap song isn't it well
well well we quit this activity and we
go to another one yeah we try to find
the next one for real this time a do we
get we got a stamp did we get a stamp do
we get a stamp I don't
know cuz I want to see it fill
up good job so was that enough
excitement for you just watch and got my
blood pumping come back
anytime yeah nice
flex and go
next six six feet under the C maybe I
was thinking of the Celly song is that
is that all the feed
songs that there are you're just going
to walk again
no a m Maybe be this way
oh I saw a crab o should we collect
shells I would love to do that I
actually really like collecting shells
when I I wonder if they have good ones
though hopefully cuz I I found so many
um what are they called the ones where
there's something inside oh yeah live
animals no live crabs yeah what are they
called in English you guys know hermit
crabs hermit crabs yes we found so many
hermit
crabs but basically I didn't see any
shells cuz the beach was like so clean
M by the way guys do you guys remember I
think I talked about it on stream that I
was going to buy Hawaii shirts for me
and Lissa when she ended my apartment I
greeted her I made her close her eyes
and then I said open when I leted her in
front of the
t-shirts and t-shirts yeah Hawaii shirt
s so we both have now like matching
Hawaii shirts in different
colors and we're going to wear them
matching it's so tacky we are cute
though we're allowed to be tacky
cute that's part of being adorable did
you get matching cargo shorts too no ew
I would never wear cargo shorts yeah
like men okay whatever but I don't want
to wear cargo shorts I don't think they
would look cute on me I think they could
look cute maybe also maybe there's cargo
shorts specifically tailored for
ladies then maybe we could rock it but I
don't trust in my cargo shorts
skills you got to complete the look I
don't need cargo shorts to complete the
look no we can have a different look and
that will be just naked underneath yeah
yeah yeah yeah just yeah yeah naked no
no oh we're doing bike trcks didn't we
no these are on the Marine bike okay uh
of the
spr shake the same thing or okay or or
or
or I'm going to kick my ass again no no
I don't know about
that I'll try though I'll try to kick
your ass you'll be successful you don't
even have to try woohoo let's
[Music]
go yeah I can't surf well but maybe this
let's see let's see it what are you
looking at Nissa what are you looking at
are you having problems with the camera
yeah yay Landing
Nails
[Music]
hey
yay what are what are the glowing things
is should I go through
down what are they oh woo I got a
Bonus I imagine if you go through them
yeah points they give points
yeah oh oh did I not nail that
Landing what
happened I don't know what the supposed
the the the the the good oh dear almost
collided the
desired route route route would
be
and let see okay how you doing over
there oh you're doing better than me
Nissa oo water
bites I sound a little bit like you when
I do that because that sounds like how
you
sing wa nice but we both
[Applause]
clear she kissed
she's like no no no no it's just your
hand it's
okay yeah I'm kissing your ooshi how how
are you guys going to survive that kfb
they they get kisses from me anyway if
they send red super chats okay I see
okay okay okay okay understood it wasn't
so bad yeah shut up she said said we
could be better could shut up we have
one more but that's like three things oh
it's a marathon or so like a triathon
Tria and the next activity is Tria
you're right to sign up have
fun and again it will probably be like
five kilometers
away oh do
[Music]
this oh oh it's somewh there okay that's
okay we're on the water bikes Fri and
chimpin there's nothing for you guys to
cry
about cry me
okay Queen Prim R slay you know the song
right I do but not not anything other
than just that
part really what about this
[Music]
one I don't know what you're singing
that's the same song I think
oh we going to do K in in in males and
see what songs we both know why you
always reach the the destination first
you just have to I you beat me just
because I'm running oh no I I think I'm
going to get reset
though
uh they reset me so far what is this
what is
this a game that resets me really far
holy look at that that's more
exciting whale I
guess whale sighted well SED let's go
okay I'll talk to
him
yeah I froze again it's so cold here
doing that to you it's just so
cold read this I tore up the asphalt
when I competed in Triathlon he T my
younger days Dam he must sick my aching
back is
stealing understandable my granddaughter
always says that I shouldn't be pushing
myself at my age but nothing stops my
love for triathlons oh God he's been oh
oh my God I'm going to keep competing in
triath lons till everybody realizes how
great they are now show me what you
got okay run ride and drive your way to
the Finish Line in this free gear
race start off on a mar Marine bike jump
off at the beach run to the ATVs then
finish it off with a climactic ATV race
okay can we remember the order though
will they tell us cuz I'll forget thank
you for the red ch huh who is this there
an egg there's no name and no profile
picture they just wanted a kiss what
does that
mean egg what about me we to send the
red super
chance oh my God so wait uh run ride
Drive yeah isn't riding and driving the
same
thing Shut Up and Drive Drive okay let's
go Rihanna Rihanna is talking to me
she's saying shut up and drive while
stop thinking about
it excuse me do you like Rihanna sounds
I do oh my god do like I want to hear
have you ever in your karoke life sing a
Ariana song on stream no please sing
Ariana Grande I haven't checked the
perms for it anft is
okay an it's okay it's okay trust me bro
you trusted you trusted me with this
game
today trust me I know cuz I looked up
dist sturby on Jazz rack and it was not
possible and I was so I sure I sang it
before well I know sometimes they change
cuz one time I was checking and I I saw
that there we definitely had perms for
some of the Tenacious D songs you
probably don't know what that is that's
okay no I know it's the car thing right
no the EUR beat no it Tenacious D or
think of Initial D Tenacious D is like a
a Jack Black it's not really a parody
band are we getting off or what is this
I don't I'm not sure I think did they
get off f it yeah they got off they're
running oh God how do we run get off
okay
uh uh good question this is how we
lose
yeah do we shake no I don't think I she
skipping where I
shake
ah this is not fair
are they running faster than you or
I don't know what's happening wait I
don't see oh they're like right where
you are maybe they didn't run so fast
maybe that was run yeah yeah no no it is
it is normal okay I'm I'm so behind
at least you first I'll try my best at
the
triathlon gas gas gas gas step on the
gas oh but yeah we had perms for the
songs is what I was saying but then when
the karaoke time actually came
I checked again just to make sure it
changed yeah and I was so sad oh my God
what the hell I know right they so
disappointing but I really want to sing
you sing you hear you sing Ariana song I
would like to sing Ariana Grande because
I love her honestly you're like your
name should be narissa
Grande cuz you're you're pretty tall I
am pretty tall and your singing
voice is amazing did you remember to
make to do tricks maybe no maybe I'll
get extra points for the tricks that I
pulled oh no I don't think so it's
a race but you win in my heart cuz
even if you come in last I don't want to
be last you're first to me I don't want
to be last it was because I was so
confused about where to get off it's
okay I was confused to we should do it
again
okay one last try off
okay and whoever wins to that will win
the stream today yeah yeah oh my God the
old guy got second or third he's so
crazy oh wow yeah he's still like super
got you still got it but I beat him on
my first try so he can't be that
good oh we got all the stems yes maybe
now they're going to be like go to
different Resort something special have
you tried playing over an activity when
you already got a stamp yes we have done
that oh there's other dorts so they're
like go to the other ones yeah but I'm
like no no this is good for today okay
I'm
FR you guys like the the opening it was
so cute it's made by cow carrot he it's
his fault don't blame
me he did this for you guys to suffer
and I enjoyed
it I could make a to to this
track would
be I love CH you do how car you
Legend you blame me why usual room okay
here we
go and we're s we're sabotaging each
other get out of my way no you you get
out of my way oh nice curves W nice
curves
sexy I hate this I keep getting stuck
behind like an NPC and they don't move
they just like somehow manage to stay
perfectly in right that's how it felt
when I was bumping into
you okay okay okay got to lose some
speed here
probably
oh maybe not and get off get off get off
get off get
off you why' you you you you didn't
remember you had to get off over there
yeah no narissa it's okay it's okay it's
okay I love you oh so I'm happy if you
win it's fine I'm skippity dipping
skippity
dip okay let me
off oh I forgot got the jump button
but I'm I'm I'm I'm really far ahead
this time You' got last time you were
first maybe this I'm I'll be first
yeah
[Music]
and y' I outran them hurry up I'm
hurrying you got to you got to bring it
home for us I will bring it home show us
how strong kiisa
is
we are always winning always are chicken
Sil
winning go go
go we are winning our own kind of Mario
Kart
tournament okay I'm finally on the
bike maybe you can still get four no oh
no looking at the map really far behind
and I'll even do tricks nice look at you
oh I think I heard them
cheer yay you're just so
good oh oh yeah yeah the
curbs they catching up just go just go
straight W just go
straight party party
people how's it going
Nissa slowly but surely I will arve
never give up we both get first place
like this this nice yeah see yeah it's
perfect I accidentally get first place
and now I accidentally get fifth place
and you get first place intentionally
intentionally I you saying the last one
was intentionally fifth place no it was
definitely not yeah that was learning
learning learning
[Music]
curve oh I'm dancing look did you go
look at her
go that was great that was great and
there's I can't believe there's more to
this game but I guess I mean it was 40
EUR so yeah there better be there better
be a lot more so if there's a whole like
this is all Beach F right and ocean F
what if the other Resort is all snow
themed there must be and then I could
play this before like a skiing vacation
in the
future lots of opportunities wow hey how
many resorts are there how many games
are there I think they said there's
three or four for swords cheap no that
was expensive guys wait one person said
like oh that's cheap it's not cheap yeah
most other people are saying it's
expensive there you go yeah yeah but I
mean if it has like five Resorts then
it's definitely like oh it has four
Resorts okay that's pretty good four
Resorts 40 games oh wow one EUR per
game yeah that's not bad that's not too
bad okay
um before we go I think people would be
happy if we like tangent a little bit
more okay just a little bit I don't know
I don't know but like can these bikes
shut up no yes they did maybe a little
bit of music um you talk about what
we're doing after this what are we doing
after this eating schnitzel oh
yeah I ordered schnit okay it I
keep on stopping to move I don't care
anymore I ordered schnit yesterday
nura didn't eat it she ate the cake okay
wait it's not that I didn't want to eat
theit but we'd already eaten so I wanted
some like not foodie food I needed
something sweet so we had also gotten C
we had already eaten we didn't really I
did okay you guys got to understand I
was flying in the air and while I was on
the plane they gave me food and well we
were at the airport kiata made me buy
food I oh yeah but it's it was like
because I was kind of and I I didn't
force you I was happy to try it because
it was Austrian austan favorite yes so
uh I want to explain what I gave her
like oh um I was hungry I only had like
a banana and a kiwi I just wanted a
second breakfast yeah so I asked if she
would be okay with eating this weird ass
sandwich it wasn't weird it was good
it's called Le C and all my German
speakers will understand Le C from your
point point of view what was it it it
seemed like it wasn't but it looked like
if there was like a ham like a loaf like
a bread loaf but of ham and then they
cut it in like a really really thick
thing and then they put pickles on it
with like really busen bread
busting bread right a bread green so
good it's called sem sem yeah it was
delicious um I was scared because I was
like oh really thick cut of like ham M
uh it wasn't ham I don't know
but like I was like oh no I'm really
nervous I don't usually like I usually
like my meat cut really thin but the
meat I don't know how to describe it it
was like
not even though it was cut really thick
it it it wasn't as thick as it looked
basically I'm going to put a picture up
I mean it wasn't as thick as this but I
think this is a joke it it can happen
this can happen funny this is a
leaso um but I was is like maybe half
this size yeah um and it's in the semmer
um and the inside the meat I was just
Googling it um yeah what is it
uh uh liver cheese roll it's not really
liver cheese roll um wait I think there
should be if we WR it here
uh lab
K sea I can't
write wait I'll find a proper English
explanation here Leba in Austria and the
swan Bavarian and franconian parts of
Germany leakas in blah blah blah blah
and is a specially specialty food found
in the south of Germany and Austria
similar to this it didn't explain all
it's similar to baloney and you know
that is what I thought of when I first
took a bite out of it it doesn't taste
exactly like balone but it's really
similar in the fact that it's really
really easy to eat that's baloney that
sounds like
B it consists of beef pork and bacon all
of it and it's made by grinding the
ingredients very finely and then baking
it as a loaf in a bread pan until it has
a crunchy brown crust variations may be
made using other kinds of meat such as
horse meat or turkey also they yeah
sometimes they put in cheese or or Chili
Peppers Etc to spice it up and I would
add like usually they have like choices
of things to put in like ketchup or or
uh mustard but I usually put in uh
pickles or um feroni so what the
was feroni for sake is it not
just pepperoni no cuz that's apparently
salami Chili Pepper but like not the
spicy ones mild mild chili peppers mild
jalapenos I'm talking about pepperoni
pepperoni that are like uh like the
pickles in vinegar like this look up
pepperon
pepperoni that's probably that I guess
ponini sounds like
it I mean they're differently shaped but
they seem like they taste the same yeah
yeah similar maybe yeah um so we had
that and I was really curious what
narissa was going to think about it cuz
for austrians and Germans I think it's
like a like a guilty pleasure food like
a nice snack to have like at school or
or um in between work and your break and
cuz it's warm
yeah it was so good you like it yeah I I
I was telling because the bread gets a
little moist but you know when usually
that's only because of the condiments
condiments that we put in but usually
when bread starts to get wet I get
really grossed out and I like throw that
part away because you know it's moist
this bread even when it was wet I was
like
m still so
tasty so it was very it was a very
interesting experience I liked it do do
I think I'd get it again maybe with a
thinner cut of meat yeah you can ask and
I want I want more toppings more yes
more they only it was at the airport
they didn't have much Choice yeah but um
yeah was good it was very tasty and then
we continued well I uh we had like my
stream my lethal company collab and then
later on your stream so I thought we
don't really have much time it's like
kind of stressful to go to a restaurant
and and I just want to like have you
arrive so instead we just ordered in m
uh and I ordered
us uh a famous from the OG I I I ordered
us the Saha cake and a schnitzel ve
schnitzel that is the most expensive
schnitzel you can get in Austria um with
a nice salad the salad was so good it
was
busting um and the schnit you didn't eat
yet so you don't know yet what it's like
I'm going to eat it right after we end
the stream it comes with some parsley
potatoes I love I love buttered parsley
potatoes yeah yeah sake tell me about
your you liking the Saha cake it was
really different from American cake
because American cake is usually the
Cake part is really sweet too like uh
this this cake wasn't particularly sweet
but that's not a negative I think it's
sweet but I guess you have different
standard yeah yeah it's it's sweet but
not like overly sweet this is what we
ate there was jam between the top layer
right and uh so the the chocolate was
really thick on top Jam is here here it
was so nice it was like a very nice mix
of like the cake wasn't too sweet so the
sweetness came from the it's not
frosting but I don't know what to call
it the frosting and the jam really added
to it and like really kind of were
really really sweet so it was kind of
like a really nice equal
balance yeah it was tasty it's it's our
Austrian cake our famous Austrian cake
that comes from a hotel that is named
Saka hotel and they made the Saka cake
and it's so good but like eating one
piece is perfect sometimes I eat more
than one piece and I'm like W wo
it's too much it's like the the
chocolate is so rich tasting and so
thick it can easily get too much can I
but one piece is perfect can I tell them
about
McDonald's yeah kiata ruined my life
today cuz you said you like ice cream
okay yeah yeah yeah first things first
yeah so she said why don't we go to
McDonald's to which I was like just to
get ice cream I said that just to get
ice cream yeah and I was like are you
kidding and I was like okay I I guess I
it then occurred to me that McDonald's
it probably has different things than it
does in America here I got very excited
I was like oh hell yeah mhm um they
definitely had things I was really
interested in in the menu but they had
you know how we have the maafe we have
maafe mhm and it's and it's literally
just like the coffee though that's just
what they call their coffee they
actually have like tons of dessert
options yeah it's an actual Cafe and I'm
surprised you really don't have I have
never ever seen anything like that maybe
in like California or something do you
guys in America nowhere have a Mech Cafe
yeah not not just not just
the mech Cafe is Australian yeah not
just apple pie like they have like ay
ones like that actual like cake cake it
was
crazy and like they had a donut they had
like two different Donuts they have like
10 different cakes they have Donuts they
have ice cream they have I don't know
all kinds of coffees and teas and they
have a lot of cool stuff they have
cookies they have everything they did
Rebrand yeah I'm really mad oh New York
has a ma Cafe that's more Cafe like they
have cakes and they did rebr a few years
back where that was added well they need
to add it everywhere else too I is a
demand I thought it I mean especially in
America so McDonald's heavy I complained
because you know uh America is where we
McDonald's comes from so why on Earth
does Austria get the best McDonald
Brazil has
[Music]
mea they won't they open one near
Chicago oh oh never seen in Canada maybe
in big like I would think in bigger
cities they would have it but I think in
Austria even in smaller cities or in the
middle of the highway they have
it jeez yeah it's like pretty a pretty
common um combination now I guess cuz it
it was so popular but I think it would
be popular in Ino I'll cry about it
Toronto has it uh Czech has it of course
of course Europe has it all over I think
I heard American McDonald's is actually
the worst one yeah no it is I went to
Japan and I ate McDonald's and it was
way better and now I just went here and
ate McDonald's and it was also theor
McDonald's I love it took you by
surprise it didn't take me by surprise
but I just might be a Starbucks
non-computing I don't think so because
there's other coffee shops that do very
similar things that's weird maybe it's a
branding thing or so but yeah and then
they had they had some other burgers
that are like Austria only I guess but
we ended up just getting some chicken St
Stripes yeah except that like they don't
have that in America we just have the
Nuggets just the nuggets but we have
nuggets and a lot of other like chicken
stps like you were at KFC I guess and we
found out that we like the same dipping
sauce sweet and sour yeah did it taste
the same as okay cuz like sweet and sour
surprisingly it did doesn't exist uh
like this in the McDonald's in Japan I
was shocked they don't even like really
do sa I really I feel like the flavor
would be popular there they barely even
do sauces most of them eat like the the
fries with no sauce because they have
like Shaka Shaka yeah yeah they have
like some stuff that when they shake it
and done before they don't dip it most
of the time and then when I asked for
for dips like they were like dip well
yeah I guess we have like uh ketchup and
like I think they had Mayo maybe Mayo
but no sweet and sour so weird shocking
but yeah I do like eating fries without
sauce sometimes yeah admittedly I prefer
to dip fries and Mayo mixed with mustard
I don't like ketchup oh you got to ask
for sauce I I I I she did I did what do
you mean she did yeah so we enjoyed the
the strips just a few because we didn't
want to overeat and we ate cakes we
ordered two cakes we brought them back
home uh you had black forest cake and I
just had a berry cream cake my favorite
that is so simple M yeah and now we're
going to have the you're going to have
the rest of the Schnitzel cuz they even
if it's for one person they somehow make
uh enough for two people and I'm going
to eat remains of a burger that I made
the day before
yesterday like I made a burger nice yeah
I I don't know I mean the Patty I
already grilled it beforehand so it's
just still be good yeah yeah yeah so
basically our day today was we we slept
in cuz we stayed up so late mhm yeah we
woke up at like 1:00 p.m. then uh we we
tried to get breakfast and then I
realized oh oh it's a holiday today all
shops are closed yay we're literally
already were outside and like oh it's
closed what day is it what it's Saturday
it should be open but no it's a holiday
then I was like whatever I want quason
so we went to the gas station we got
quasa I let her uh cuzz you said you
were even with qu you were like I don't
know how to eat this like I don't know
how you eat it yeah I mean usually we
just either eat the croissant or
like or you like make a a sandwich out
of it with like ham cheese I prefer to
have my quas
sweet yeah I see why after this morning
and you even I first said chocolate
spread or jam and you went for chocolate
but you even did it like me right you
added butter too yeah I love you for
that I love butter oh so one layer of
butter one layer of chocolate spread and
we enjoyed our Quon yeah she laughed at
me though because I cut mine in half and
she was uh rubbing on the chocolate
spread after every bite and she's like
good luck cutting it in half and then I
did it
easily making fun of me even the gas
station CLE was good though right yeah
no it was like surprisingly I feel like
it was pretty comfortable if not better
than the ones you get at Costco but
that's only because the ones at Costco
are already really soft yeah yeah yeah a
different kind of Cl mhm yeah and oh she
tried milit which is one of my favorite
snacks since I was a
child loved eating it at school
too German people will understand but
maybe not even German it might have it
all over Europe This is is basically
just some bis biscuit uh uh chocolate
yeah biscuit and in in between milk
cream a really fluffy milk cream is so
good it's so good it's so
goated and I bought it and you tried it
you you like it yeah it's pretty simple
though it was interesting cuz I don't
know why it looks like an ice cream
sandwich it does so I was expecting it
to be the same texture but it's not it's
really it's like a really really really
thin layer of cake haven't had that in
years do they have this in America at
all I've never seen it before prob not
right the the it kind of looks similar
to kinder in terms of packaging but I've
never seen it it's not Kinder guys no no
oh
yeah they probably have it in Italy I
think it's from Italy penguin yeah
there's a rival snack to this one and
it's like either your P Kinder Pingu
group or like it's Tak thingy or your
mil group and I'm miss the group I like
the other one too but this is I see for
me it's the best or MOX that one is n
not really so popular it's popular but
can't compete so we had that and then
yeah after like chilling a bit uh and
eating breakfast we like started getting
ready I made my thumbnail really quickly
but then narissa was like aana don't we
have to go and I'm like no don't worry
my time management is
perfect but I was right though we should
have arrived earlier so we didn't have
to miss the beginning of the movie well
if they weren't understaffed we would
have been fine it was a coincidence so
we went to the movie then and Larissa
got into the movie b late cuz she was
such an angel to get the popcorn and the
drinks for us both while I was already
going in I already missed a little bit
though I want to watch it again and see
what I miss yeah and then we watched the
movie and it was really nice and then uh
oh then we um on the way back uh I
showed her something
tsty yes a beautiful
beautiful cathedral MH mhm we listened a
little bit to a a guy doing stuff yeah
saying amen
amen
[Music]
amen don't question why I can go into a
church when I'm a demon don't ask we can
of course we can so many people go in
there not being the right religion it's
okay yeah but I'm
like I'm activ oh you think they would
like I'm actively the baddy would they
like sense it and try to like they'd
have to exercise me they'd be like
Phoenix girl that thing with you we need
she needs to be sent back to where she
came from oh is a phoenix allowed is a
phoenix
holy I don't know but you're not you're
not demonic so yeah yeah okay I didn't
oh sorry I dragged you in there it's
okay they didn't notice me oh and I Tau
Nissa how to do public transport she can
buy her own ticket
now
suoy and and and yeah then we went to
the McDonald's uh yeah after the
cathedral we got the little snack and
now we're here and we oh before we
streamed we I was trying to take a nap
while watching Home Improvement and
Nissa joined me in the bed we were
cuddling with junky
wonky and now then then we streamed and
now we're here this is where we are now
yeah and yesterday yeah yesterday you
had the snack and then we streamed and
this and that and you were bonding with
my cats uh-huh they didn't want to sleep
with me though yeah because they were
sleeping on my bed
they're not going to go for you if
they're but I'm so warm I'm so warm when
you were streaming and I was taking it
nap mhm I was like maybe they'll come in
and investigate they didn't no you
should have slept in my bed it's just
like I think the bed the guest just
doesn't even have enough space sleeping
in my oshie's
bed I can't that's too
ludd well yeah I think it's just not
enough space otherwise they may have
they may have joined you mhm has never
pick yes you sat on the bean bag right
yeah you sank into it immediately my ass
crushed it the famous bean bag mhm yeah
uh what else was there something else I
don't I think that's good we don't need
to give them any more PR
information we can hear about it later
yes well I'll think of more oh I have
[Music]
more I'll keep it I'll keep it for uh
that's the stream or so in the moment
I'm will Expos you I will expose you
what did I do you
know you know what you did I will expose
you chicken brains bird brains no don't
tell them I'm so stupid if you want to
hear what she's panicking about make
sure to watch all our of our Mal streams
yes or maybe don't maybe don't don't
come no do it don't we'll be like um you
know like probably doing like one stream
Wawa Channel One stream wi Channel and
so on so make sure to subscribe to both
of us in case you haven't do not miss
out on any of the fun mhm and oh yeah
once again please fan art if you can
yeah give us some swimsuits please
swimsuit
yeah and yeah we'll see you guys uh soon
we're excited
yes
vacation go
vacation and don't forget I'm is going
to stream birthday stream why don't you
redirect into it even though she's not
live yet yeah I will I will it's kind of
too early but I will anyway I mean I
feel like redirecting so early makes no
sense but I mean you could see if anyone
else is life I'll I'll check but I guess
it's it's the my birthday the fault that
matters it's a birthday yeah Happ a
birthday happy birthday so um yeah wish
her a happy birthday guys else or else
and in Germany we saying I'll the same
I'll the oh and I put a different uh
hashtag in the title um I was thinking
throughout this whole mold's Adventure
you guys can because we we'll be
collabing a lot you guys can use that uh
hashtag when we collab um but I think we
might actually or I don't know no wants
to do it but I was planning on doing at
least one solo member stream probably
during the trip as well cuzz I know you
guys are going to miss me when I'm going
to go my break right after so don't
worry I'll I'll do one solo stream too
okay I'll think about it if I do
one okay
I'll bye bye
byebye she's jealous again yeah B
thank you for the super chats guys I I
don't know when I can read them maybe
maybe at the end of one of never one of
these streams maybe I can actually read
them yeah we'll be having a lot of time
in the mold yeah yeah yeah okay byebye
byebye oh ah
here oh wrong
[Music]
wrong
hey guys
listen do you want to tell them what
that is oh
hands
wait we have to end the bgm oh my
[Laughter]
God you know how when you stick your own
hands together uh and the the air pocket
or something does something funny we did
it with our hands together hand
collaboration hand collab okay byebye
[Music]
byebye