[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
ah
no no no no no no no i'm not sleepy
no no no no kick it
keep
[Music]
does that sound sleepy to you
kick it again
i'm not sleepy i'm not tired no no no no
no no no
i was just uh
having a
stressful time before the stream
i think
within
wow within one hour
i
got groceries but
i got them delivered
okay so i got the groceries and i put
them into the fridge and uh i i did uh
turn on the laundry
wow but but also um while waiting for
the groceries i was um
doing something with my plant
uh i have this i have i have a plant
that's like on top of a shelf and has
like really long long leaves right and
because up there i i don't i can't like
i can't see
what it looks like from the top right so
um i just take my long geese kane um um
watering
can
that's probably not it um oh it is
watering can really
but we'll do a starting tweet in a
second um why don't we can't and i and i
just pour it without looking like what's
happening up there right but but but but
then today i was like you know i have a
little bit of time and i feel like doing
it so because there were so many dying
leaves on that plant i took it down um
to
also bring it closer to the sun
and and take off the dying leaves okay
so
i take it down and i see what the [\h__\h]
this plant is drowning my mom's gonna
kill me i saw the plant was drowning in
water like
i was like
did i
i didn't give you that much water but
uh like it was literally swimming
swimming
to the top of the
of the of the pot so it's actually a
surprise it didn't flow over yet
come
thank you
so i
uh first of all i poured all of that
water out
even though i just watered it but i was
like this cannot be good
um yeah
i was waterboarding the flat literally
just like a yakuza i just uh take out my
aggressions on plants because i can't do
it
with humans
so um
so so i i i poured out all the water and
then i took off all the little like dead
uh leaves and
dead roots and all that uh they were
like tangled with the others and
um
you know
i feel like generally with a plant from
what i've seen
uh
it starts
dying from
from the from the
from the bottom
from like the end of the of the leaf but
in in my plant's case probably because
it was drowning in water it was the
other way around like the end of a long
long long thingy like it's like it's a
plant that's like like one string and
then lots of tiny leaves on it right
so half of it the end of it
uh was happy and beautiful but the other
the the beginning of it you know that
comes out of the soil um a lot of those
where uh dead and brown and dry
but but i i'm a plant beginner okay and
i think logically like if there if the
plant looks dry shouldn't i add more
water and this is where my mom's gonna
dm me immediately although she doesn't
watch my yakuza stream so maybe she's
not watching right now but she's gonna
be like yeah you're so stupid no
i'm gonna take all your plants away and
you're not allowed to have any plants
anymore
um
[Laughter]
yeah um
uh so uh
apparently that was not the case so um
all of those half dead ones i also took
all of them out and now my plant looks
like
it had a
huge hair loss
like someone who's half bald uh
nothing against the half bald people
mata kaminohanasi
yeah
um but that was fun that was kind of
therapeutic almost it was actually fun
uh i hope i hope that now that i
deport all of that water
um that is gonna be okay but i have
another plant where i also have a
problem like this is a small plant okay
just a small like little pot with some
small plants okay and um small leaves um
but like it covers the whole soil so you
don't see the soil
and um
i
i [\h__\h] that up that plant also really
fast there is only one plant in my
apartment that no matter what i do i
cannot [\h__\h] it up but this little small
plant i seem to have [\h__\h] up as well
because
going by my logic of
you know the plant seems dry how about i
put some water into it it doesn't seem
to have worked like the the leaves
they're not no brown leaves but all of
the leaves are dry as [\h__\h]
like
it's like completely dried out
and the soil
is kind of molding a little bit
and now we got a new plant the other day
and it's also molding the soil is also
building
that probably means i
i am watering them too much i don't even
water them that much
ah
they need less less no i don't think so
they probably don't even get enough sun
but um if anything uh
get new soil
i should probably just ask my mom but
she's gonna like write me a whole
[\h__\h] essay if i ask her
she's gonna she's gonna come by and take
away all my plans again she did that
last time she took one of my dying plans
home and i was like but not that one
that one was so beautiful and yes it was
beautiful but it wasn't anymore
she cut off
every single leaf
even the good-looking ones she cut off
every single leaf and she was like kiana
i'm taking this plant home it's
confiscated you won't get it probably
until autumn
and i'm like great
you you'll fix it until autumn then i'll
get it over winter where there's barely
any sun so it's gonna die again
fertilize i've been using fertilizer
i don't know maybe my fertilizer is [\h__\h]
but i've been using it quite a lot
it doesn't seem to work
uh so yeah i've been having some
problems with my plants
and um
so i did that and then
uh
then i i brought down my trash
and i also picked up a parcel or from my
neighbor
uh that my neighbor was keeping and
uh what else did i do
uh uh i i
what's what's and kyle can in english um
[Music]
come on chat you can help me
huh that's kind of what a fertilizer is
wait what is a fertilizer what's what
did i say what's a fertilizer
no no no this one is not [\h__\h]
that way i don't think so
what do i know um
uh
wait so what's encouraging do you call
safai they call kapha decal the call
supply or something like that i did that
with my with my water cooker and then i
um took uh uh i i i cleaned my my
kitchen and uh so i did all of these
things and more in one hour i also had a
low-key breakfast
and
um yeah i played with my cats i even
played with my cats for like seven
minutes
i did so much in one hour
yeah the plans took me the longest
because i also had to clean up a lot of
the [\h__\h] that
fell on the floor
uh
calcium not a hotel yes yes yeah that's
actually impressive thank you speed run
speed run of uh errands and [\h__\h] uh
before the stream in one hour
plants can be real fake of pickles
sometimes yeah i can't manage to keep
them alive for next time
me too
i have to keep on buying new plants now
this is my newest plant as i said the
soil is like a little bit moldy right
now but not so bad yet i have to figure
out why it's molding um but the leaves
still look beautiful it's only a matter
of time until that plant is gonna die
too
maybe i should just my mom said so too i
should just buy like the one plant that
never dies in my apartment and and it's
absolutely like
glowing
it's getting bigger and bigger holy [\h__\h]
i should buy several ones of that one
and only have one type of plant in my
whole apartment i should plaster the
whole apartment with that one planned
and people gonna come into my apartment
and be like you're really really like
that plant don't you and i'll be like
yeah that's why i got
50 50 samples of that plan that's that's
exactly why just because i like
only this specific plant this is the
only plant i like
not because this is the only one i can
keep alive no this is just the only
plant i like
uh succulents i think uh
i think i wanted to get them but i think
the problem was
some of them were toxic
i'm not sure maybe not maybe that was a
different plant
but i mean for my cats you know i have
to
i have a small selection of what plants
i can get into my apartment
um a lot of them a lot of the popular
ones a lot of the ones you guys are
thinking of are probably toxic for cats
um
yeah mm-hmm
and for uh for cacti i'm like
worried that my cats will run into them
so yeah
those thank
all right sorry that was a little bit of
chitchat i kind of um i haven't talked
to you guys for a while because i had a
day off and i had a karaoke and i had a
stream on mumbai's channel so i was like
hello hello hello i was sitting alone in
my apartment in the corner and i was
starting to talk to myself and i was i
was yelling at the wall hello
anybody here oh yeah i haven't tweeted
let's let's do like the whole thing the
whole chevy bang
uh
hello
mario
streaming now
[Music]
um
uh who are we
who who are we gonna
uh who where where are we now kirill is
this gonna be video episode i think so
i think
so
right
here you
last
splurge
let go
[Music]
url
and then sooner or later we'll be good
to go
you know i hate youtube studio like once
i start to stream and i tab out
um
every time i tap back in it's like
kind of like broken not responding
and i even close the tab and open a new
one and go into youtube studio that's
faster than just waiting
waiting for it to come back to me
i think it's the [\h__\h] resources i
need hyper chat but for youtube studio
like hyper hyper studio
please
can someone code that for me
[Music]
a more efficient
youtube studio please
have you heard about japan relaxing
work-related travel restrictions to many
countries including australian
haven't they been saying that for the
past six months
so my hopes are
dead
um
i don't i i highly doubt that it's gonna
happen uh before
my birthday
uh so
no hopes for that yeah but this sounds
for real [\h__\h]
now it's actually
who said that
japan travels opening starting on the
eighth
but even then even if that were so now
the problem is that like uh we can't
just suddenly go there like next week we
all have some plans and [\h__\h] and um i go
to the maldives uh
in
next month and uh in june i'm [\h__\h]
busy with dokomi and planning for my
birthday and [\h__\h] um uh preparing for my
birthday like and i don't know about the
other girls but they have [\h__\h] to do too
right kelly is going somewhere um
yeah callie is going somewhere uh
i don't know about gura ahmed ina but
yeah
yeah i mean i would
i would try besides small dips besides
the maldives i can somehow
besides mold dips and dough me i can
somehow make it happen but
you know that's that's the problem like
still even if they open up right now
it's not like you can immediately go
and there's still other things that need
to be planned like where are we going to
stay
uh is the studio even available for us
for like several days in a row
um
is everything ready to really do a 3dw
immediately and
yeah flight tickets
uh also does really everybody have a
vex
you know
and uh oh do we need a quarantine if we
need a quarantine we need another week
extra
blah blah blah
stuff like that
um
i i have it yes i do
uh
i think i got um
you know what i don't care about about
it anymore because like other members
have been talking to about about it too
japan members literally make streams
about oh hey i went to my vaccination
this is how it was so i don't give a
[\h__\h] anymore i had my booster in
december um
so i don't know when the next one's
gonna be
um
but yeah
i was trying to be uh you know
sensitive about it uh
i think all of all of ian was trying to
be sensitive about it but
but then yeah
who gives a [\h__\h] at this point so
i'm like i'm really really hyped today
right now oh my god
so
um i mean
it will be a little bit difficult to go
to all kinds of countries like the
maldives and japan without one so
um
it would be quite troublesome
without it
yeah
[Music]
people have been more open about it now
yeah yeah yeah
uh um so i guess should we play
i did the tweet i did the tweet um
[Music]
meow
woke me up
at 9 00 a.m because junkers threw up on
my on my carpet
um
and i was gonna ignore it until i wake
up properly but then it was so stinky
that um i got rid of it immediately
uh
poor poor chunky
um
chunky wonky
uh chunkers what did you i don't know
sonkers always gets the usual she only
eats kibbles and sometimes she gets her
snack but not so often
and when i say snack i mean a cat snack
not a human snack
any weapons today
oh well there's a cactus in the
in the thumbnail should i do cactus
that face it's like an oovoo face
apply
color key
wow
um
the pixel look very itchy don't touch
them it's a cactus it's gonna hurt you
[Music]
ghost cactus
all right beautiful
that works
it's like i'm holding an ice cream or
something it's an ice cream cactus ice
cream
ah
this is how my cats are gonna be like
they're gonna try to lick the cactus
[\h__\h] hurts [\h__\h]
why did you buy a [\h__\h] cactus that
looks so delicious but it hurts our
tongue okay wow why are you doing this
oh my nose is it
it's itching my nose
hmm
[Music]
um maybe the other way around does that
help us
no no it's still like right in my face
but uh
ah let me try to
let me try to do something on photoshop
i want to turn it around like if it's
too low then you don't see the hand it's
just a random cactus here
but if it's too high it's in my face
it's been half an hour
i'm opening photoshop
your winzip has run out no [\h__\h] sure
look
it just ran out today guys
it just ran out today i'm i'm gonna take
care of it don't worry about it
um
so
ideally
i would want to turn it a little bit to
the outside right
like
like maybe like so
maybe like so
okay
export as pag
cactus
okay
this is better
it's better this is better
it's better
but we'll still flip it
um
transform
horizontal there we go
get rid of the other one there we go
here we go also this is my last newest
weapon i think uh again so oh guys we
still have probably two more episodes if
anyone wants to make a weapon
uh
yeah
[Music]
well i think maybe there was one okay
ours to know
oh yeah there were some books
but
i don't read books so
uh what happened
for me
[Music]
what did we not have yet we already had
so many things
[Music]
did i have a water gun before like one
of those bazookas you know with the
water tanks in the back
i don't think i had that before
and i could use that in summer as well
i think
i feel like we might not have had that
motorcycle yeah go yakuza style
[Music]
uh
a t-shirt
that's
cool but without an animation it's hard
to show that there's a t-shirt inside no
uh
a trash can
well that's so huge oh
i should hide myself underneath a trash
can
but i move so much so you barely will
see my eyes most of the time
olympic torch
ah did i have an olympic torch before
a boomerang oh
i don't
i think boomerang is indeed something we
didn't have yet maybe
what's a tanto squirt
a huge chicken leg
i literally have that in my standard
outfit
or do you mean a raw one maybe i should
get an air fryer
just just have an airfryer in my hand no
no don't do that don't do that one
um
oh
you know that that guy who pours the the
meme guy the
handsome guy who pours salt over meat
maybe a salt hand
you know like the way he does it
sprinkling salt
yeah
sophie oh it was called salt bae oh
um
that could be good that should be fairly
easy
i think
comically large fork are you a are you
working in the clown business
that sounds something what a clown would
say
comically large fork
okay we should start playing
we're gonna start with the agasuji and
we've done
um
whatever uh previously in
yakuza previously in the story of kanto
makiri
i'm going to
start making tea on the side
wait i don't hear
i don't hear some wait
you guys didn't hear sound either but
why did i know why you guys in here so
why did i not hear sound um
oh why did i not hear sound
why did i not shh speaker oh [\h__\h]
elgato sound capture why is it always
elgato sound capture
i always change it
okay i think that
no i don't hear it
this is the recap this is why i am doing
this
for you guys
[Music]
it always goes back to elgato sound
capture i told you guys this before this
is so stupid
in windows when i change the output to
something it always goes back to odd uh
to elgato sound capture even when it's
not connected that's the weird thing
even when i disconnect it uh
what the actual heck
but i guess in this case uh
my god the sound capture shouldn't be
disconnected
[Music]
what
how do you
[Music]
thank you windows
um
it's so funny like i go into
windows uh like uh
manage
audio
thingies right it's in germany for me
and then there's speaker elgato sound
capture and i i
literally click deactivate it disappears
for a millisecond and then immediately
comes back
it is
it is absolutely absolutely triggering
me
oh wait i have a different idea uh here
this one and then
i think this is how i fixed it last time
um
you go here and uh
oh no oh no you know what yeah no no
this was not the fix just restarting the
[\h__\h] uh application
okay
that was it
there we go
this should work
um
[Music]
foreign
what
everybody wants to though everybody
i wish i was this this popular
crime and punishment
oh yeah
am i going to get punished
for a crime
in that style for a while
my tea is
happening are you guys comfy
eight hours before majima reached the
chameleon grove
room
america good
wonderful
having a good day today's a good day
today's a good day
oh happy day you happy day
foreign
m
um
foreign
all right video store
sarah's supposed to call us at cal
videos in shofukucho west i should go
check it out
go to a video shop
okay no i don't want to go to your
stupid izakaya
i don't have time for that all right oh
look we have 76 million let's use it on
my abilities
before we do anything else
i don't like using beast but i should
upgrade a little bit i don't know
maybe health a hundred million oh no
thank you uh
reduces the rate and
okay
it costs so much money
what can we do here
two million early increases
yes
reduces the rate that the heat goes
drops
sounds good to me when you have beats on
a dance floor oh let's go that is so
true
that is indeed very true
can we get some more cheap ones
um
improves the evasiveness of your
quickstart
uh is there something cheap here
two million
[Music]
two million here
yes
reduce the damage to take on thrown by
[Music]
we still have 30 million so we can buy
something big oh
we could wait this is brawler and then
there was rush which one do i use the
most
i've been using
rush and brawler the most
both maybe
somewhat balanced put up your guard
again right after an enemy breaks
through it this ability can only be used
when calm on the first heat bar
um
l1 will attack
no i don't do that though
we don't do that here
kind of
man
[Music]
but i have to use that i have to
activate that one eventually because
otherwise i won't be able to go to the
other ones
um catch an enemy off guard with a
straight punch to the body r1
then back on l and press y
ah triangle what back on l what does
that mean take a step back or what
[Music]
a sense of oh a sense of crushing well
wait that's a that's a
fancy
heat move right evade an enemy's attack
just before it lands
causing them to shatter their fist
against the wall behind you strangle
with a wall behind you when when an
enemy attacks
the very moment they're attacking me
that seems like very difficult to get
the timing ever
that one's fun
is that
is that easy to activate i mean
pretty forgiving
and i have to be against the wall
easier than you think it will be useful
for big slow boys
does it have to be activated
right but just it says just before
when
like when once i get damaged it's
already too late right
um
[Music]
i kind of do it by accident sometimes oh
really
it's not frame perfect or anything okay
what was this what is this one
excuse me guys sorry i have to take the
phoenix spirit once uh first because
what
your heat question will slowly ransom
one time when you win it however it will
only fill up to the second part
not a little
okay
it doesn't sound so
like it's not an attack but
okay
i'm getting
okay there goes my money
okay
um
okay so now we go to uh shofukucho west
which is
uh over there okay
ah kitty okidio kiryuki
such a
tough life for your living
a bit too loud on my side is it okay for
you guys
right now it's generally quiet anyway
it's supposed to be
supposed to be generally quiet
is the game losing a lot of frames yeah
i don't know is it
can't tell at the moment okay i'm gonna
i'm gonna um
make it a bit more quiet but what about
items okay items look okay
looks good stream is fine okay
donkey
sorry guys you gotta move when i'm
when i'm running into you you gotta move
it's not that hard
it's uh did you guys ever eat a fish
like that the the blowy the blow up fish
of the spikes the cactus fish
blowfish
have a fish
yes puffer fish yes
you blow up fish
never had it before either i mean people
if people eat it that's probably sushi
but
i don't eat sushi
oh
girls
[Music]
hi
there's a naked guy in here what the
[\h__\h]
cuties
okay
he's very well informed
yeah haven't we seen that naked guy
before oh well we have more important
things to do right now
oh are we getting a cutscene
this is just normal i'm not sure
that's just normal
i don't want to know what you watch on
that big screen
[Music]
foreign
thank you for watching
marriages are not nothing weird over
there especially earlier not even even
now even nowadays
but foreign
translation
[Music]
foreign
mm-hmm
so i won't know what they're talking
about
he's just been listening to lonely
island
uh i don't know
i would've thought he'd offer to wait by
the phone not not that i'm complaining
about little free time may as well enjoy
a taste of osaka until the call comes in
okay
okay i don't understand why
why are you
okay we're just gonna run around i guess
yeah
does it seem like we have a specific
goal
maybe we meet majima what if we go to
what if we go to
the ground
why the hell was that again here
wait what
hop left
oh this one
and
uh people told me about you know aren't
you not going to sega so maybe i should
go to sega today
so what if i can i enter the girl
oh oh sorry i thought you were like the
the guy i don't want to see but you're
the guy i do want to see because you
have money
warm-up time
he has a nut
[Music]
mommy how much
four
million i guess that's what where the
game wanted me to go
so this is the ground impressive i don't
think there's any place this big up in
cameroon joe
oh no this is more side quest because he
doesn't have a voice over
here for the ground bunny
no it doesn't look like they're open now
anyway oh is it too early
we're open come evening what we open
come evening
when the evening comes you mean be sure
to come on back and see us then though
all right
probably don't have that much time
now okay let's go to sega
listen to your karaoke while playing
tabletop sim game with friends and
overlapping made a great background
music i would thinking marina sounds
from aloha oh by the way about the
rebroadcast
um
i might
have forgotten about putting it in on
the weekend
but
uh
we'll have it next week
i just forgot
[Applause]
i play the card game
how to run
how to play do i have to drive is this
gas gas gas
insert credit accelerate okay change
gears break okay x's stop
circle is go
smooth steering move cursor
steer move cursor
break oh you can also use l2 r2
okay okay okay
insert okay here you go
uh
oh i can select the music
oh i don't
know get ready
[Music]
can i go even faster though
i want to go even faster
i'm about to take off i'm an airplane
[Music]
oh
camera please
[Music]
the police can't get me i'm too fast
yeah
oh
crabs
palm trees where those houses
sorry for making so much noise at your
doorstep
oh
oh oh decisions decisions game what do
you mean game over
[Music]
horse map
wait what
change gear what the [\h__\h] even is
changing gear what does that mean
i don't know what that even means i
don't know how to drive a car
how do you oh
oh you mean i'm bending smackson and um
the gun
[Laughter]
what was the button for changing gear
though
[Music]
music magical sound shell what was the
button for changing here did you see
r1 l1 r1 or square okay get ready
but when do i know that i need it
[Music]
when do i know that i need it also
when you reach max speed
when do i how do i see what is my max
speed
now it's low right
[Music]
almost 200 kilometers per hour
i'll never get a driving license at this
rate
[Music]
this is so i'm okay right today
is that good or bad change now okay
[Music]
wow
guys
[Music]
i killed some houses that's okay
how did i not lose yet with that
okay okay
[Music]
i want to get out of here
no i want to get out of here
[Music]
no
get ready
[Music]
although i have
what
switch screen
break
that's bad
no more
no more it was fun but
i don't understand i don't understand
how to car
um what is this game can i play now we
can play maybe this one
space harrier
space harrier sounds like
let's hurry
okay okay
or harrier shoot is that
uh
rapid fire is that reverse switch
shoot rapid fire what does reverse
switch even mean
okay
[Music]
press option
what's this what is this game
[Music]
whoa
is fun because
i just have to button smash
[Laughter]
where was you when kiwawa was killed
what did that just say
meow it's movie
nice movie
sorry i'm busy right next movie
trees
[Applause]
i don't really feel a dis difference
from uh rapid fire and normal fire but
okay i'm rapid firing now can i oh can i
run out of oh my god what coco's empire
[Laughter]
what
[Music]
you're doing great
am i really doing great you sure about
that
oh my god oh my god it's coco sometimes
babies
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
oh they're coming they're coming for me
babies
those faces
this is just like everyday life yeah
yeah
i know how it feels
many more battle scenes oh [\h__\h] what i
was reading the text
okay i mean that's pretty good for
my first try
[Laughter]
ho
nice high score thank you top score
let's go only a pro like me can't do
that
i played this on yakuza 7 what i don't
remember that
oh it's not playable
i can do you feel catcher
wait i want the i want the burp i
remember that was i remember those birds
[Music]
um not really interested in anything
about the birds oh yeah okay
i want uh one of those birds with a hat
but there's a lot of other stuff in here
too
um
damaged
[Music]
ah
yeah
not enough
a little bit more to the right and a
little bit more to the back ah
[Music]
i can ask the store owner to change
prices what
oh and i went a little bit too far i
think
oh yeah there's elise's i stopped early
i stopped too early
i don't want that thing in the front by
the way i don't need it thank you
[Music]
hmm
then
well
oda is taking care of the phone so i'm
just hanging out in osaka having a great
time this might be okay
[Music]
but maybe now it's easier to catch
i had it
insert coin
okay
now it might be easier to grab
[Music]
on the belly on the belly on the belly
get a good grab
no that's no nah yeah i knew it
oh it's
it's floating in the air right now
we have to save the burpies
[Music]
okay okay it's okay to go a bit further
yeah yeah here is good here is actually
pretty good
grab it very real good
squeeze
yes carefully
this game is [\h__\h] rigged
[Music]
in later island gator i first tried the
ufo catcher
oh come on
oh this is [\h__\h] rigged
this is [\h__\h] rigged
that was a big oof
come on
poke the belly and do it
ah
[\h__\h] bastard on the side it's gonna
get me in trouble
[Music]
they're moving
you can see that
[Music]
uh no
no no no no no
[Music]
it's playing with the dinosaur
it's gonna get eaten in the middle
right in the middle between
them it's dangerous
[Music]
lizard oh
looks like a dinosaur
no
[Music]
can you help me
please enjoy yourself i'm not enjoying
myself can you help me with that machine
there in real life in game game centers
like that
if you if you say sumimasen then they
help you
especially if you're a cute girl
[Music]
why can i change it
oh the prices can i thought you meant
the money that it costs to actually
play with it oh
they're changing the prices and not the
prices
huh
now that makes way more sense
are you waiting thank you
[Music]
it's all birds
it's a [\h__\h] bird army
i want the big one over here
there's a big one there's actually two
big ones
they look so cute they have a hat man
they are burps with hats
and the orange ones kind of made me look
a little bit like a chicken if you're
are they having a birth conference yeah
friends from this glass person i'm
trying to
maybe i should just take the whole glass
prison with me the whole youth will
catch you
i mean it would be a nice um decoration
at home
yes yes
you can literally not grab these things
[Music]
calmly calmly
[Laughter]
what can i do with that
oh my god oh my god oh my god i'm so
happy look
jumbo
[Music]
what do i do with this
i guess nothing it's just personal
satisfaction
[Music]
this means you all are free to go
you're welcome
you're welcome oh
oh
wow good timing i guess what that wants
me
oh that wants me
hold up
oh dog
you don't need to be so direct about it
okay
wow but mutual feelings here let's go
maybe i can
give him the the bird and
and he'll fall in love with me or
something like that
no i should put it into
i should put it into a safe place
there you go
uh come
what am i fighting
or what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh wait there's an object let me try to
use that
[Music]
there it goes
my wife is so bad at this right now
[Music]
i forgot how to fight oh he lets it go
no don't let it go
[Music]
i [\h__\h] hate breaker style
i hate it i'm getting bullied
wait no
stop doing them
i mean be stand-up breaker let's just
change already
i'm trying to activate heat blues but
nothing's popping up
and there goes my teeth
okay
let's do this properly now
uh
[Music]
i didn't see that coming
don't kill the tree the tree did nothing
something bad
[Music]
this is one of my worst fights in
history
i'm still just warming up okay
i have good times and i have bad times
we're going
down here
mama you're talking
who are you
oh
well i'm here
while i'm here i'm gonna fill up my
inventory
with some medicines
[Music]
um did you guys watch the collab with
lume yesterday on her channel it was
really fun
i thought we would like be able to do
more uh
like get further in the game but
uh
within two hours we already
it already felt like we we did so much
so i figured we should just split it up
into
more streams then
gives us more reason to collaborate so
why the hell not yeah
yeah love me some homo birds yeah yeah
yeah and after that actually
we chatted
endlessly for like two hours after the
stream
until mermaid had to go
yeah
god damn it this guy
hello he doesn't even want to talk to me
he's just
happily looking at everything
we talked about all kinds of things but
we don't want did we talk about
some pretty related things
and
some other things that are your secrets
and about her visiting me
of course he got the call while i was
gone
[Music]
think of a single job i've gotten from
tajimana that i would call pretty
i should probably assume that trend will
continue
[Music]
oh
um there we go
okay
plus we'll head straight back to tokyo
once the deal is done
i should do everything i want to also go
first
up
we just went to sega
i can come back later
okay
no i think we're good jumbo addicted
no sad question
okay
i heard you wanted
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
m
[Music]
what are you doing
what's going on
it's okay
they just uh
jumped on top of a cardboard box and it
fell over but that's okay that's okay
they're having fun
it's just loud makes me worry
okay we go pick up makoto now
but that's okay
but that's where
we were with majima
subaki
she wasn't here when we weren't here
with module wait is this the same
timeline or it's just after here
eight hours this is earlier
this is a few hours before we were there
with much but i'm not a hotel because
when we went there it was uh evening
time right night time
oh i like that
soon those floors on floors on the
ground those chairs on the ground you
call zaisu
the crotch looks weird guy oh god the
guy in the back looks also weird
hell nice to meet you
oh my god
[Music]
okay if you're not gonna take my card
that's so rude i'll just put it on the
table
she looks fine
[Music]
that's why she didn't know she was the
owner
um
foreign
she probably doesn't even she would
probably just give it away for a hundred
bucks even
she doesn't even understand the
value of it and even if she did she
probably wouldn't give a [\h__\h] it's just
like what the [\h__\h] man i don't want to
be involved in this [\h__\h]
um
you do what you want with that
well
something's going to happen something's
going to happen something's going to
happen
actually
oh
did he abuse her
when she was she wasn't wait i'm not
getting this wrong right she wasn't um
was it korea or china when she was
abused
uh
yeah she was trafficked um
[Music]
does he not recognize here i do what
maybe he does he just doesn't
doesn't show it
[Music]
is he just acting
he knows what's up he knows what's up
welcome to
well that's the real
crazy thing here
oh hello
no what the [\h__\h] what the actual
[Applause]
oh
of course we have guns
[Music]
oh what am i going to shoot from it
she's like oh god
is that different shoots or is that just
the same shoot what's heat eye like a
heat attack
oh god reload i don't know how to use
guns
[Music]
ah heat eye is slow-mo okay cool oh god
a heat eye slows down the action using
it depletes
the heat at gosh
shown under your hp bar
refills over time
reload advance withdraw into the car to
reload hold x to stay in the car uh-huh
while inside he will not get hit but the
car will take damage oh fun
it's getting well with the cars hp wait
can i heal the car
if i take medicine can i even take
medicine
okay they're barely shooting at me
[Applause]
why are they not shooting at me
reload reload real real
okay i think am i is it okay
okay okay manageable it's manageable
i mean i say while shooting
all the wrong places but but it's pretty
steady pretty stable
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] that dad like this huge
[\h__\h] sniper gun
of course of course why would it be any
of anything else
but that's so stupid from the point of
view of video though because if you
think about it
if you think about it
they're shooting him with real guns and
[\h__\h] and he's still like oh i'm just
gonna not kill people uh because that's
the smart thing to do
right
come on kitty at this point
it's like shooting someone with a water
gun when they're shooting at you with
the sniper i don't know man it sounds
[\h__\h] stupid oh
sheesh
oh no oh no no no no
it's a bazooka another diver
what the [\h__\h] are
now you so fast
oh god
how long is this gonna go down
okay
[Music]
oh yeah i have slo-mo i forgot about it
is it continuing
is that even necessary
oh what what what what [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
am i shooting the bullets
what's up
okay oh god oh god
are you [\h__\h] with me now
no way i can catch those
[Music]
mom come on come on
it's made out of plastic man
pretty impressive
[Music]
damn
i think we did it
we did it
this looks like outlast
oh sorry dude man
that poor guy
does not kill no
no
[Laughter]
why would he he's an angel
oh where are we nagoya
we can't be in tokyo already
why would you hit her she didn't do [\h__\h]
take your hands
um
[Music]
liar
money
[Music]
literally a minute ago i was looking at
her and thinking wouldn't it be so cool
if she had like a weapon hidden in her
stick and there she goes
yes
you have to push a button okay
foreign
thank you
why'd you portray me i thought we were
in love
with
so they both have it right because we
saw it on taji banana
and we were like
but he has it too
[Music]
m
foreign
and we love them
you
foreign
he has a different aura
um
but aren't you portraying him now
the [\h__\h]
foreign
wait so it says
no way
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
he wouldn't be forgiven
for trafficking her before they met
um
[Music]
or
let's
he's gonna die
[Music]
well i hope he will believe
all of this
but okay
[Music]
that's sad i liked him
oh man
[Music]
well what i thought
we still have to fight them don't we
oh
all right i'm totally gonna mama started
um
[Music]
i dropped it
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait let's do um no
uh
[\h__\h] what am i doing
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
one more time please one more time
try again
doodly doo
that's how you start this
[Music]
nice
oh
[Music]
uh this one is hard even though the
start was good what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
it's just just temporarily just
temporarily
just temporarily
thanks i didn't even know there wasn't i
forgot about the existence of the easy
mode
[Music]
you're in the [\h__\h] way
get out of the way
okay good good good
thank god thank you easy mode for
existing
oh there's only two people left okay we
can switch style
damn holy [\h__\h] is so much easier
it's like a different world man
it's a [\h__\h] different world
oh oh we're not done excuse me
[Music]
no i didn't have to work maybe maybe in
normal mode but not in easy mode
[Music]
that works too
when i grab them i forgot
you still alive
[Music]
items like that
slows me down so
much
okay
[Music]
is
i missed it
oh no
but wait there's more are we still in
baby by the way i wonder i think
[Music]
so cool
wait let me eat some bento
okay
[Music]
why didn't you never wait for me
there we go
everything is so [\h__\h] far away man
oh you little [\h__\h]
get up get up get up get up
whoa
you're telling me dad doesn't kill him
that is really really really really
brutal
i literally heard his snap neck cracking
but not like i crack my neck no no no
the floor kill yes yes
that is the excuse
[Music]
[\h__\h] off you [\h__\h] slicing machine
go slice some pepperoni or something
is a propane is that propane
wait
i don't even know what propane is to be
honest
uh
what do we have
now let's use this small one
yes yes yes
tap it
beautiful
finally some variety right
that was not baby mode i think by the
way that felt more like
the
usual
i think it was just that one one quick
find
yeah
nope
you're never gonna get those stains out
of those white pants
sorry i want it to be funny but this is
so sad you're gonna make it funny
somehow
[Music]
you think he's gonna talk after you put
a bullet into his heart
[Music]
foreign
[\h__\h]
it's the [\h__\h] love hotel
it's a [\h__\h] love hotel
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
maybe
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
hey
uh
we're doing it
we're going to come to
oh
wow that's a lot of money
chapter
13 completed
and we're getting another one with kiryu
so don't worry no cliffhanger
we're getting another one
safe oh thank god really that that easy
mode really saved my butt
hallelujah if it wasn't for that i
totally forgot that that even was an
option
because we never have been offered that
before for the whole game until now
and and then
at a stupid part like that that's it's
not even a boss fight it was just like
stupid stupid badass sassy bakas
annoying the [\h__\h] out of me
hmm
oh we're here
west park
oh
fountain is pretty nice
we have arrived
and now i got a girl with me
better be nice to her
sounds like uh
something will go wrong
hello
[Music]
dress her up
make her look
away
okay thank you
is not responding guess heading to
little asia is the quickest way to find
out
guys can i
i'm sorry but i need
i need a little bit of a
organization in my brain i want to um
discuss the timeline of makoto
really quickly please don't judge me but
okay so she
she was raised in china right because uh
her mom is chinese and her dad is
japanese or the other way around no it
was the other way around um but okay she
was raised in china right um because
she was like
her mom was a war orphan okay i get this
i get this
yeah her mom was japanese that's why she
was a
orphan
exactly
so she was raised and she had a brother
that she was aware of who was five years
older i get that till and then uh the
brother
left china when he was 15 and she was 10
to go to japan
uh
because
i forgot the reason why
um
and then
after a while a couple of years later or
so they found out that there was
uh
that they had someone in japan so they
could go back to japan too
right
oh because he just joined the mafia and
he didn't enjoy china i guess no okay
because they got bullied exactly okay
okay so then they join later how many
years later is this
that makoto comes to japan as well
yeah they have a grandfather how how
much later is this
10 years eight years yeah because then
there's two years
where she gets abducted right so they
come to they come to japan
and
shortly after probably her mom uh
commits suicide
uh so she's alone she doesn't find her
brother anymore i guess for some reason
uh
and then i guess shortly after at this
point she's
she's 18 maybe
uh
she gets abducted
and brought to the korean mafia
by oda
which is right before oda meets tanji
banana right
yeah uh then for two years she's like
there
uh
with the korean mafia outside of japan
right
but then she
wait how does she make her way back to
japan
do we know this already okay
ah it's the korean mafia in japan oh
okay okay okay okay
oh she stayed in japanese just
eventually got rescued by lee
right right right right right right
right
he saved her and was hiding her
uh and all this whole time
uh
in those two years where she was gone is
where they the all the other people
started trying to get the lot
right
um and she doesn't didn't know about it
because first of all she wasn't around
and second of all she didn't even know
that that
her grandfather
owned
the lot
right
i did i just needed to i knew most of
the facts i just need to line it up in
my brain
so
so now
the
uh
the the guy who kind of rescued her is
dead
and um
people
found her
and
big mess and
now we're here
oh oh
okay
okay we understand
i think
uh
yeah okay
this is the most you're ever gonna see
the game hey hey
oh okay okay
okay i understand i understand i
understand i think i understand
i understand i understand go to little
asia okay now what is the matter with
our guy
hachi banana
because i guess we oh we should use the
money while we have it 129 million
uh
wait this is
uh yeah uh what do we invest in
damn
this is 30 million
but i never use it right what else does
what does come after that quick stop
blow
the little bird of low after performing
a quick step
[Music]
body counter l1 to guard see that would
be another guard attack
pull up your guard another card yeah
most of this is guarding from there on i
guess so maybe i don't need to feel too
bad about
maybe ditching it
[Music]
ah the locked ones i need to talk well
i'm not even at that point yet so i
think we're okay but
um
well let's just
when in doubt boost his health maybe a
hundred
[\h__\h] hundred
or increase the power of your regular
attacks and heat actions do i want more
damage on more hp right now
[Music]
more health wouldn't hurt
um
more power more damage
more health
health okay
okay okay
and there goes the money
if i had a little bit more i could buy
something for 30 million
uh oh and the pager says what
uh oh yeah that's old okay
all right uh where's the
exit
baby mode is now off
yes
okay
always let me shake down bleach and then
beat him afterwards a little trick
travels your money wow
[Music]
well we have yet to even beat him
normally so
i tried before
but
it didn't work so well
excuse me
oh yeah little angel was was here for
here
how's my health doing okay
oh hello
in every plant store
you just decide
which cactus becomes your smacktis
the one that looks the most dangerous
oh hello so what happened with him
ah
are you okay
oh
um help you catch up on everything that
happened while we were sleeping
thank you guys thank you members
foreign
wait so he
also was aware this whole time
that the owner was his sister
so maybe for him it wasn't so
even so much about getting
to find the owner of the lot because he
just needed a lot but it wasn't maybe
more about just finding his sister
could that be
huh
oh well that's
that is so wholesome
that's
it's all right don't worry man i like
being left in the dark
so it's just how it is with rpgs
oh yeah that's a big twist
do you nanny
[Music]
oh so it was like this
and this and this
is
oh he's dressed up
[Music]
yeah you should have stayed over your
family
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
i read sentences like
nani
foreign
m
well i have a question about the logic
here some people were trying to kill
makoto right
but
even if t if they were to kill her
wouldn't a lot then legally just go to
touch banana
maybe they didn't know that they thought
they would be freedom
free for everyone to take or something
it would probably be auctioned off or
something
but how do they how would they know that
she didn't write a will oh because maybe
they know that she didn't know that she
even owns a lot
uh
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
um
you
oh
[Music]
is
of course it is
[Music]
and i need baby mode again cause they're
trying to cling on to him do i have to
protect him
oh please no
please i [\h__\h] hate the protecting
missions all of them
no yeah please no monty
convent no no no no please not oh he's
fighting with me is he fighting with me
he looks like he's about to fight oh
he's fighting with me
yeah okay okay okay then we fine
then we're good
i'm impressed i'm impressed
[Music]
some help
kind of proud
[Music]
oh by the way guys did you see
on my day off on monday it was finally
finally finally announced big surprise
that i'll be the guest at dokomi again
on saturday which is such a coincidence
because that's my favorite day
how did they know
what a coincidence man i totally didn't
know myself until
you know just just monday i didn't know
i was gonna be a
what's up guest a surprise man
ah they're so good at surprises
um iris will be also guest this time
she'll be new she'll be uh entertaining
you guys on sunday
iris
will
not
come to germany so it's not an off guy
or anything like that we're not gonna
be able to meet in real life just to
clear that one up
i think
gemma is still coming though but iris is
just gonna do it from home
[Music]
i know some some of you guys might have
thought oh iris cyrus will come to
germany no no no um basically all the
things that i'm doing there are also all
things that i could do from home and
ferry but you know me
i love dokomi i love dusseldorf and i'm
i live close by so for me it's not much
of a commitment so i want to go
when i can
gemma might bring me some some stuff
again
yeah um
it would appear they were the only ones
for now
why is there no voicing but they know
you've been hiding here more will be
coming indeed we should leave for the
back it is this way okay
yeah ah the suit only if it's already
there uh when she makes her way to
germany yes yes i
i said that might be faster than using a
postal service but even if like
at this point um
i'm not relying on the suit for my
birthday i'm just gonna book a studio
foreign
he shot me right in my heart how do i
even survive that what
he looks [\h__\h] up
like a villain in like a spider-man
movie or something like that
i don't know where the [\h__\h] of my heart
is
[Laughter]
hmm
please don't kill us
[Music]
foreign
that sounds very sold out the
user
foreign
what you think that's gonna
eh
what are you gonna do with that
what you're not gonna
touch banana you know if you die
your sister is gonna be very very
[\h__\h] sad
what you're gonna do with that little
piece of
crap
[Music]
sound is good
come on drink those energy drinks
speaking of i have cherry coke in the
fridge
it's a really rare sight
i don't think i've seen a cherry coke in
austria
in the past one year
well i found one
yeah i want to get that out of the
fridge later
[Music]
mm-hmm
can i get it now
[Laughter]
now that i think about it
[Music]
okay
looking out
now it's nice and cool
oh you wanna listen to this
uh
can't find
cherry coke
oh
wait i think that's my first time maybe
drinking cherry coke i think i had
vanilla coke before a million years ago
because that tastes very new to me
very good yum yum yum
yum yum yum
hmm
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
um
he creeped me out since the very first
time we met him
he's he's a good guy
[Music]
and he he didn't quite deserve this kind
of fate
i should check on makoto not like i can
do much to away from touchy panyanya
anyway
check out makoto okay
i have a bad feeling what about you guys
it's a flag it's a flag of
something
some some people
probably trying to
hurt her
the moment we the moment we step into
that
park
why did we leave her that's so stupid
she's she's so important right now we
leave her there that actually that is so
stupid
i mean we can't unfortunately we cannot
uh clone ourselves and and be at two
places at once but it would have been
kind of necessary do i hear a helicopter
no
maybe it was air conditioning
but where the [\h__\h] am i going
this place
ah
it's
it's gonna take a while
it's gonna take quite some time let's
fight
[Music]
foreign
no no no no no
we're not in some kind of fight club
okay
[Music]
foreign
um
yeah he does have a big mouth
oh
[Music]
oh all
on your marriage
oh his eyebrows are so angry
how do they how do they do that it's
magic
fish
there's a bit more abs though nishiki
have you been slacking your workout hmm
were you so sad that you were not with
your bro that you couldn't do workout
naked man let's go
[Music]
let's go
people in the back can you you should be
careful
step back i know it looks like a
freaking amazing show
but
take a few steps back oh my god
[Music]
um
don't
[Music]
okay that was that was kind of simple
though i expected a bit more
oh his knees
hey we're we're real
real badass men here okay we're talking
to talk now
this is how growth okay
you little [\h__\h]
sorry i was just too immersed into the
character right now
[Music]
today but i think it's just that i'm
better with majima like oreo
[Music]
come on
ah
oh wait oh i feel like he was waiting
for me to like help him
oh yeah i have some kind of counter but
will take me
a couple tries to really make that work
don't worry
we're gonna get them anyway
we're a dream team now
[Music]
beautiful beautiful
beautiful
ah cherry
oh
you don't want to ruin the suit but then
why does he wear it for all the other
fights
some fights that are even way more
intense than this one
explain that logic to me guys
you're gonna find every fight with me
now what about this one
probably not
because manly
okay you have something i have something
to do
[Music]
didn't know that would happen
i'm trying to activate some heat here
but it's not happening
[Music]
i was trying to pick up the knife oh i
have it i haven't i haven't
oh holy [\h__\h]
you tell me he never kills anybody
really
really are you sure about that
wait no that's a pickup
item wow
oh activating all the heat all the heat
the knife kilter
doesn't work like that in court
that is not gonna hold up i think
is there should i say by the way there's
nothing
close by
[Music]
one cute squirrel
hello um i hope you treated my girl
nicely otherwise
i will set this whole park on fire
yeah but this is just the beginning of
his story
if you think this is amazing then take a
look at all the other games that have
been released with kiryu yo
i haven't even played yet
thanks dude
but i'm sure he
m
already married to kaiju i wonder if
he's aware of that
foreign
a corpse to her hmm
[Music]
back and forth and back and forth
foreign
oh i was trying to
give them some time to talk you know
i'm trying not to interrupt them you
know i feel like when if i
went to the this one earlier then they
would have stopped talking and not
continued it i'm so nice i'm so
considerate
yeah
oh i hope so too i gave them like all
all of my change and i was like
you're gonna feed the doggo well right
and i talked a little bit even though
the guy was a little bit scary
but but the dog was man
the dog goes
um
yes i read the air
is considered yes yes yes yes
and we started to kill doko he had those
double eyes was looking at me
it was under a blanket
because it was kind of rainy outside
i um to rescue all animals in the whole
world
how can i do it how do you do it
no no i didn't pet the dog i wanted to
but i felt like i don't know
dogs living on the street i'm not sure
if that's safe
i don't know could be but i don't know
i legit don't know so it's better to not
touch maybe
charity stream oh yeah yeah yeah
uh
i think sometime this year
uh we're gonna do
a charity stream i think so um
yes
like last time last time i asked
gemma about it i was like gemma i want
to do i want to do charity uh
and she was like okay um
[Music]
let's plan something
but it takes apparently a long time to
plan something like that so
i don't know when it's going to happen
yeah amma did it like uh a long time ago
and she has still not put out the
rewards
it's almost been a year right
[Music]
um
hi canada hello
i'm intense to forget yeah
i i get it though like there's some
things that i just forget for days and
then then after some point so much time
has passed
that you kind of feel like bad about it
and it's so hard to like
confront yourself and others with it
you just want to ignore the fact that
you have not done it for so long right
it gets worse and worse the more time
passes but at some point when enough
time has passed you just you just
can't
you just want to ignore the fact that
you have to do it because it's already
so uncomfortable
um
i get that
i know that i've had it before but yeah
um
okay
there is no elephant
mimika
[Music]
hi
that would be dope that would hopefully
make it somewhat easier too
and when someone's fighting with me they
don't have a hp bar
either right so that's pretty [\h__\h]
overpowered
that is so of a part
you'll fight this at least 58 more times
after this
no i refuse
all right uh or over there
do i have money i have 66 million okay
um
i can get two two skills 230 million
skills
oh yeah we wanted to get this one ah
the wall behind me thingy
[Music]
i didn't get it yet
no i'm gonna take uh oh i can't take
that one
ah
what about this one
invasiveness
i feel like
the thing is with a
rash style
that i am often just too
slow to activate the heat moves
and with something like this that is
already so
um
like a
huge timing thing i feel like
it's not gonna
now it's gonna happen but okay
i'm gonna get it anyway
um maybe something here as well because
we've been neglecting it
iron guts perform a resist guard when a
heat causes at the third bar to stay
standing even when hit by a knife or gun
attacks hmm
now
i think i'm gonna go with uh
i'm gonna go with this one
heat moves are like collectibles yeah it
feels a little bit like that
you don't need every goddamn heat move
even if it looks cool
um
yeah i'm fine with what we have now
okay
[Music]
i'm talking again
oh do i have to okay i can save there
[Music]
wait i can't get into the burger place
it was not an option it was an illusion
of an option
should i buy it should i buy more
medicine
maybe i should maybe i should maybe i
should maybe i should
where the [\h__\h] is the medicine place
thingy
pharmacy
yeah
that's good enough
no need okay but i would i do want to
eat this place barbecue korean barbecue
okay i'll keep going
let's get some korean barbecue nishiki
you and me together
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
i have korean barbecue
last year
uh
at dokomi
because all the [\h__\h] japanese
restaurants were
filled up to the brim uh no reservations
nothing possible my favorite restaurant
was closed so we went to korean bbq
yeah is that all i can order
oh i can only order one thing that's so
lame
um
[Music]
thanks dude
really yummy made some memories with
nishiki before we get
go to another
we game
yes
it's my subconscious when i look at
these two
my subconscious speaking
freudian splits
[Music]
between two guys
all right do i have something in my item
box
i want to go to the item box
i hear audio crackling i'm gonna fix it
in a second just let me out of here
oh my god just how many times do i have
to
oh this is
canceling to save is even more annoying
than saving
oh good no i'm not all good this is so
stupid
i canceled five times i just have
boonchat in there okay
okay
going to little asia
why are you even questioning
them why i'm holding a cactus huh
you guys should know me by now
i
have a weapon in my hand when i play
yakuza it's that simple
crescendo
[Music]
again
but okay at least it's a bit
new because we have nishiki with us
oh i don't want to see how they're
retreating tonsi but no no
[Music]
oh
poor guy
[Music]
no i thought they would
stop
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay are you okay
why are you saying that
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
m
hmm
[Music]
some of them
yo he's gonna get a [\h__\h] concussion
are you insane
i'm gonna forget
where makoto
is good job good job
holy [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] hammer on his head
yep
okay let's go
let's go
so gay
is
[Music]
wait are we finding one on one or two
versus one one one seems more honorable
nah i didn't it
should i take care of the small ones
first maybe
[Music]
already off to a great start guys
what is it with my poise i have like
zero [\h__\h] toys
okay okay okay okay um um um um do i
have an object here somewhere
oh yes uh no wrong
yeah
i am always focusing like my my fingers
literally 24 7
on ah today
on on hour one i swear to god oh there
we go finally something cool
[Music]
you guys have any other heat skill or
only that one
oh what the
[\h__\h] down
okay
okay i think we cleaned up
i think we can now focus on him
[Music]
being bullied like that huh
oh good job i unfortunately cannot help
you with a heat move but
this way
[Music]
get up why you keep on falling down huh
how cool
[Music]
hey
while we're fighting maybe i have some
time to talk um
you may have seen that for dokomi
they were hinting at something that
currently is maybe in the works a
surprise for you guys from google me
and i'm so excited about it
um
i i i don't know when i can tell you the
deeds but
there's there's a hint on dokomi twitter
so
that
i want to use the heaps
um
yes
that is maybe
[Music]
the
the thing that i'm most excited about
for dokomi this year
and um
one thing that
i hope you guys
can
the ones the people who are coming to
the convention in person specifically
one thing that i
i want to make clear
um is that my performance is not going
to be in 3d because
[Music]
for several reasons
it's more like the decision of dokomi
rather than my own decision
i would have loved to offer you a cool
3d performance
but yeah it's not possible i'm sorry
about that
i wanted to
now that i have pretty i wanted to
show you guys a cool
worthwhile performance because so many
people are also coming from
um
from outside of germany
um i feel like a live today concert is
just at this point it's just [\h__\h] cut
out okay somehow
but in order to somehow make up for it a
little bit i
am preparing at least like something
small
something else
to
to try to make it more interesting
yeah
cheers
and i think i might do
a stream beforehand where
i tell you guys how to touch me how to
how to hype up my songs at least
she's
so fast
[Music]
am i supposed to be surprised
am i supposed to be surprised not
who is so high again
excuse me
oh i [\h__\h] told you you shouldn't die
you're old and makoto has left you
[\h__\h] that's not worth it dying for
them
[Music]
looks
was it the hammer to the head
was it that [\h__\h] bad
oh man
oh
he's still alive
are you trying to find excuses for your
for your
okay
um
i don't care what he's saying right now
you're so pissed
you have in your mouth
it's your fault my man died
makoto has no one left except
i know he was trying to free him but
still he was in the group it was his
people they were torturing him
it was his
second
uh i was learning english
it was his
thing
uh
responsibility um
it's the yakuza way man
the highest one in the group so is there
their responsibility
i understand that you guys understand
that too
i told you we'll be bringing his [\h__\h]
corpse to my door
oh
huh
[Music]
uh
it
[Music]
is
hmm
[Music]
stupid [\h__\h] playstation saving system
foreign
oh
hmm
i'm gonna
i'm just gonna um blow my nose and give
chunkers and smoothie
one pet okay
and then i'm gonna be back
uh
hello
hmm
[Music]
soft
yeah
[Music]
okay
refresh
smoothie was sleeping in my laundry
basket
and chunkers just came out of nowhere
so majima resigned himself to working
alongside both sagala and nishitana
nishitani to find her
yes
oh
at least cause it's still alive i'm not
happy about that i hated that mother
since the very first moment scattered
like chapter 15.
um
i keep on saying askiness but it was was
it 17 or 18 chapters
[Music]
17.
[Applause]
i didn't expect to finish it this week
but at this pace
i don't want to go too long today
because um i need to read super chats
[Music]
but i guess we can play
a little bit more
maybe one chapter
[Music]
one one chapter
until this is the 15th right so
until the 16th chapter
okay
yeah maybe some side stuff
yeah i figured the ending might drag
itself out a little bit so we're gonna
do one more chapter today and the next
time
i have more than enough time to play
until the end it's okay
[Music]
is
um
m
[Music]
foreign
google
okay i thought i thought when you guys
said that
could be him
yeah yeah okay
well he looks like a terrible person
okay
and i was asking too
[Music]
yeah he only appeared briefly but he
made quite the impression
with his body
[Music]
um
i wonder what we're gonna find
nice your olympics trip got canceled oh
i'm also gonna try for four festivals oh
whenever that happens
oh thank you there's so many people
coming from overseas and that's why i
feel kind of bad like i'm only there for
one day right and i have a meet and
greet which is really special and all
and a concert but the concert is just
live today so i feel kind of bad man
[Music]
but please so you guys need to make sure
to make the most out of it okay so uh
hang out in dusseldorf you guys know i
went there a while ago on a food trip so
you can go to the same places where i
went okay and and check out check out
the uh what dusseldorf has to offer and
and go on sunday as well when iris is
performing to make it a bit more
worthwhile and and check out the
surprise that
wow that that the document is preparing
right now that i can't say anything
about
okay okay and and and enjoy enjoy please
because i i can only offer you one fun
day and and oh yeah meet up with the
other kf people because that's always
fun that will make your experience more
fun and worthwhile okay okay
yeah
where did this come from i just yeah
what do you mean where does it come from
i just feel like um
there's so many people are coming from
overseas or outside of germany
and even inside of germany
i
i want i just want you guys to have a
good experience okay i don't feel like
it was not worth it also
i'm not gonna write you a travel guide i
already did a travel guide stream for
you guys basically
just watch my
you know my whole essay about the food
trip all the restaurants i went to i
told you every detail huh
yeah
i told you every detail
and besides that you can just team up
with the other cave people and then
figure out what what fun thing to do one
thing i can tell you um there's a
there's a japanese hotel
um
what was the name nikkei hotel no what
was that
uh in that big japanese street and they
have a karaoke there uh that does i
wanted to go there with rmt
when we were there but
um
it wasn't really worth it for two people
it's pretty expensive for just two
people
uh
at the nico nico hotel yeah yeah
japanese business hotel they have like a
japanese style karaoke room i think it's
probably probably pretty old i've never
been there
um but if you guys go in the group of kf
people then it's probably worth it and
you're gonna have more fun
but make sure
one thing you gotta
take care of is
reserving restaurants way ahead of time
the ones you want to go to
it would already make sense to book them
now if you know where you want to go to
and yeah the karaoke as well if you want
to go there you should
you should reserve it early enough
because otherwise
you're gonna have to end up eating food
uh at a burger place mcdonald's or
whatever
yeah but if you're in dusseldorf then
you should take the chance to get some
good yummy japanese food there because
they have incredible japanese
restaurants as you know
yeah yeah don't make the mistake of not
making a reservation
dokomi fills up the city
with a [\h__\h] ton of weeps that all want
to go to the japanese restaurants if you
don't care for japanese food then okay
then you're good then you don't have to
make any reservations
um but if you do wanna eat some japanese
food then
without a restoration you're not gonna
find anything and also the hotels hotels
and airbnbs book them early enough
book them now if you're planning to go
don't um don't wait too long to book
something
because now that the tickets are being
sold again
um they added tickets
now that that's happening a lot of a lot
more people are gonna a lot more germans
who know the area better than you
are gonna book
all the hotels and airbnbs up
i do recommend airbnb though by the way
in germany
if you can't find a a good hotel it's
worth it checking some airbnbs all right
all right it's pretty
cheap too so
yeah yeah yeah
okay champion district
i just i just want you guys to have a
good time while you're there okay
because i i feel bad i can't offer you
more than just one day
um
yeah
just have some fun okay
otherwise i'm gonna be sad
okay
there's so many enemies in the side what
the hell
what
why is there a police car there wait um
should i wait we're in tokyo right now
right with majima
so
he also has no side quests here
thank you guys
you're also going to come to google me
employee number
[Music]
um
get out
i mean like in previous streams we did
it so now i just want to do one more
chapter so that we have less to do next
time
i am maxima and i'm instantly much
better at fighting
what is that weapon though that that guy
has
so
what do you call that kind of sword in
english
holy [\h__\h] like did you get that in a
costume shop
are you trying to be a pirate or
shimmy
oh it's a chinese sword
i've seen similar shapes
used in
by different people too though
ah but that makes more sense okay
uh where is where is where is here
uh this little side street again
any of tattoo bananas guys still
clicking around here um
probably not
a but there's a
there's a
[Music]
a restaurant or a bar here on it this
one
this one
oh look inside
you look like you're
first glance you look like you were
wearing some kind of santa cosplay
let's order something what do you have
only alcohol
i can't get drunk in this game can i i
don't know we've never tried drinking
alcohol before in this game
[Music]
can i get drunk
yes i can is that bad or good
i can get very drunk oh wow we were
really straight edge until now
oh
oh the most expensive place
one of japan's top single malt whiskies
with a cute glass
it's become such a status symbol that
whiskey aficionados the world over half
heard of it
they used carefully selected
prefecturally matured molds to get that
great smooth flavor it's highly rated
well what not a little sip combine
you bought the tocomi ticket in november
oh
seven days
you might be able to get out of that if
you get uh
waxed and tested i think but i'm not
sure
it might also still change until june
who knows
um
oh yeah besides the the concert i'm also
doing that that panel again i think it's
like the
last year one as well
where i was talking with the organizers
on stage
uh in kind of the beginning of the day
hello
because i saw that way more people
are
um
coming then last year because this time
there's tickets actually
um i asked
to have um
two meet-and-greets instead of just one
i'll be spending more time with you guys
just because i want to get as many as
you guys
as possible
through the meeting race okay
now
we're working on it it should work i
think it will be fine
no promises yet but
it's just
it should be fine it's more like
whether or not i want to do it and i do
want to do it
i do want to do it
yeah i want as many people as possible
to get a chance yeah uh last year we had
the whole
you know you gotta buy a birthday
merchandise thing um this year we don't
know
yet hundred percent how it's gonna be
decided
but we will update you guys with the
details
once once we know for sure how long am i
what am i looking for here
you don't see any tasty banana people
that obvious little place
for presents yeah it should be fine
again
just no food you know
but
hello
i'm here
but besides food
it should be
no problem uh but please don't
no no things are too big because i mean
last time i had to ship them anyway
the things that i've received
had to shift them um
it didn't fit into my luggage anyway um
it's probably gonna be the same way
again
but maybe not a one meter and be plushy
okay
an air fryer no i'm really i'm really i
think i'm really gonna get an air fryer
um it's already in my amazon
uh
cart
it's already in there i'm just i'm just
trying to
justify it
in my brain because
some people told me that
if i have a proper oven
it doesn't make 100 sense to get one i
mean it's easier maybe and fun and
faster and all that but
if i have an oven then
you know
where the [\h__\h] am i supposed to go
for real now
for real
i've been running around here i think
i've been in every side street
i don't get it
i can leave oh okay
huh
yeah i had an overwhelming amount of
people
telling me how good an airfryer is
so
i i am pretty convinced and i watched
some videos
uh a few ones of what you can do
with an air fryer
i am pretty convinced and
i was watching this one channel
this one cooking channel
and found the same airfryer that he was
using on my amazon
it's a pretty pretty damn good one
but not even that expensive
i think it was like 100 20 114 or
something like that 120 i think so
it's not it's not that expensive but i
feel like it's going to take up quite
some space and how how often am i
actually going to use it i wonder
but but you know because previously i i
complained about um me wanting to fry
meat more often but i don't want to
use up so much
um
[Music]
i really have to use one of my healing
items i don't want to use that so much
oil right so for that
if i had that and i just had to like
spray the inside with a tiny amount of
oil i feel like i would fry things way
more often
yeah
and can you imagine
when i have some of the girls over
and we do a airfryer
cooking stream
i could make like chicken wings and and
fried chicken and all that and we just
like eat it
and chitchat
wouldn't that be wonderful
i feel like that would be wonderful
i'm leaving now because nothing was in
there but they told me to go to the
champion district and i'm going outside
and still nothing happens i don't
understand what what what what do they
want from me
i went into
one bar do i need to go into the other
bar
oh i don't know
you may know
oh no
um excuse me where the [\h__\h] am i
supposed to go
are you
talking
how did i not find him
if they would hit us up sure but not
really in the position to hit up other
companies and be like can you respond
yeah i don't know i think some people do
that but i
i don't
i don't know i i feel that's awkward
um
right so okay
now you want me to leave again
really broad shoulders be proud of it
okay wonderful
that took me way longer than it needed
no
i can pay with exposure
i had that before in a place where i
worked like some influencer emailed my
workplace and was like can you guys give
me for free
instagram
i was in charge of the emails at that
time
i was like yo i have more
i have more followers and i work here
[Music]
you guys are so lame
oh i missed you
i missed these endless
endless
batting bites
just feels so satisfying
[Music]
i was also thinking
oh maybe if my mom needs one to to buy
an air fryer for my mom
where she lives right now she has a
pretty tiny kitchen
and
and her oven is
like
also very small
so i thought it might be helpful but
i'm not sure if she needs one
i might i may ask her
yeah the question is is if she would use
it i don't think
oh you called us just in here she does
struggle with her kitchen currently
though that's
what
thank you thank you
no
is that poison
shimano oh wow
you i wouldn't want to eat that but that
looks uh really delicious for people who
like seafood
[Music]
yeah that is blowfish right
you
[Music]
i prefer not
um
[Music]
this is so awkward
oh
what that's just mean
[Music]
why did you not just tell me to
protect her and hide her why did you
wait what what speaks against just
telling me directly what to do
wait why wha wha why why why wha
he says that now okay okay okay
i would have done that too because it's
an order and a more nice order like i
would have been delighted to do that
[Music]
i just
foreign
[Music]
mickey mouse ears in one angle okay if i
if we get the same angle again i'm gonna
stop
you know
because of those doors door
you've seen memes of that truly
[Music]
oh
anyway
i was going to say the same thing
doesn't want anything to do with this
time
[Music]
foreign
let's be real majima
say it
okay
um
[Music]
is not happy though
does he not believe it or he doesn't
seem very happy about it
[Music]
but but shimano seemed pretty genuine
just now
like me getting to keep the girl
oh yeah yeah okay he's pissed for being
played around with i mean that's
understandable
really
have a huge hitbox
[Laughter]
okay i'm getting mad
[Music]
is this music
we just let it all happen to us
oh man
well now he looks even more like a clown
funny
[Music]
oh man
you're so depressed and sad
oh my school opening about it won't get
me anywhere i gotta find her
yeah
i'll start with this nishikiyama at the
kazama family office make him tell me
what he does
okay
i keep on hearing them mario laugh in
the background
here but
and now it's
[Music]
fun now i heard it again you guys not
hear it
you guys don't hear it it sounds like
him when he's like on fire and uh when
his butt is on fire and he flies up in
the air you know what i mean
you know what i mean
i'm losing it i'm not losing it
believe me
every time i pass the [\h__\h] touch
ankle in this game i hear it
should we eat somewhere else because
apparently we already ate all of this
even though i'm really
into gluten right now
[Music]
all the burgers too wait that's not it
how could i have eaten them all when i
can't even enter
uh sumimasen
dako
i haven't eaten here before i think wait
only drink manu
where's the food
i go to gindako for the food man
gohan gohan
the food oh
okay
i mean after choosing a drink
okay okay okay that's kind of weird ah
welsh onion
if i had to choose i would actually not
go for the takoyaki even though that's
what the store specializes in just
because i don't like takoyaki
but
we'll get some good takoyaki for it oh
you can eat more than one nice
good takoyaki
enjoy
[Music]
yum yum
okay we have by the way a lot of money
so we should use it um
[Music]
slugger hmm
full advantage of the baseball bats
design oh okay
triangle after
i break the guard on an on an enemy
and hold on
triangle off the circle
i wonder if i'll ever get that to happen
reduces the rate that the heat gloss
drops over time okay
it's like an execution
he's just playing baseball don't worry
about him
[Music]
sure why not
there's a
um there's a there's a
chain a tonkatsu chain in japan
uh
not quite a restaurant it's more like a
takeaway
that i went to very often and had my
point cart fill up several times
it's called
it's a japanese word for cactus probably
because tonkatsu
resembles a cactus because of the
spikiness of the
of the crunchy outside breading
maybe maybe
yeah and it just
reminded me because someone said oh you
have a saboten in your hand yes yes i do
it was my favorite place to get uh
tonkatsu at
r2
a jumping flourish r2 i'm never gonna do
that
i'm never gonna do that
that's a big threat
i can say yes
[Music]
okay uh 10 million
anything for 2 million left
no
did i look in here
uh what uh 50 50
okay i think there's no more
no more two millions
no no
okay
uh where are we going where where are we
going where are we going down here
tenkaichi street though oh i miss japan
i miss japan
ah
i really hope what you guys what you
guys said was true i hope so
but you guys that it
applies to
work
to people who go for work only
right
business
but that's still gonna be limited though
no like how many entries per day how
many visas are giving away and all that
gives me hope again but i don't wanna
my hope has been destroyed so many times
in the past 1.5 years
that
oh no i don't i want to think about it
uh are we okay
am i okay
i'll be fine worst case will turn on
baby mood
let's go
we'll hope for you thank you
thank you
[Music]
um
like little aggressive dogs
[Music]
this is
the moment you step into the door you
should just
to not waste all of our times
immediately fight
because always ending up like that
um
[Music]
0.5 second reaction time oh dear yeah
i'm not gonna hit that
oh we're going to a nice area to fight
okay do not destroy the office all right
all right fine with me
mmm
[Music]
foreign
how is he an [\h__\h] now and there's a
nice bartender
how hard he goes on did they brainwash
him it's like the opposite of what
happens
goes from calm to crazy and this guy
goes from crazy to calm did they like
switch souls or something
all right all right all right all right
all right
no no no let's make him dizzy first
my strategy
i'm scared to i'm scared to hit him uh
because if i stop he's gonna attack me
immediately there we go here we go i
found an opening
all right all right all right all right
gonna be careful here let me be careful
oh
[Music]
all right you come here
i'm back here
oh it's too easy
it's too easy
[Music]
[Applause]
the way he runs is looking funny to me
good morning hello
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
oh there goes my rainbow
[Music]
is in control
is he gonna do it again
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
that's some damage that's added some
damage
where was that where was it
[Music]
oh god
um
maybe i should go to speed
what i'm doing
okay
nice
nice that was important
getting at least one of those in there
and then hit and then hit and get away
nice come back
nice easy
i didn't get the the cutie but i think i
sold it pretty well
and anytime
[Music]
um
and this is how he decided that yakuza
is not for him and he's become
becoming a bartender
oh wow he's really mad if he wants to
take someone's eye just like he
suffers
hi
uh
over there
okay
um
i feel like
you might be surprised by something
there
as always
thank you laser boss thank you
[Music]
wow
oh should i buy more items before i go
there
although i kind of don't see
um
another huge fight happening right away
again
well we better go
if it was up here
all right
always be prepared
always be prepared guys for the waste
we always expect
the worst
and
here we are
there was a company but we're not going
to company because they're only selling
[\h__\h] did i show you mercy
all right we're filled up again
filled to the brim
alrighty
um
oh yeah by the way uh i wanted to say
something
i was talking about visiting me right so
that's actually um
overlaps with someone else who's wanting
to visit me and then
on this on a separate
date
there's also
gonna be
some other girls
visiting me but
they haven't mentioned it yet so i'm not
gonna savor i think i think
i'm gonna keep that a surprise for
a little bit longer
so i'm gonna have a lot of visitors yeah
a lot of visitors
yeah callie did say as well that she
wants to come over so her visit is
actually also
overlapping with someone so
yes
yeah
many
of collabs ahead of us it will be during
a time where i'll be generally very busy
so
uh
combining that with off of collabs i
feel like uh it might be
um
more more collabs than solo streams for
a while but
uh
we're gonna make some fun nice memories
make the best out of it
and i'm gonna prepare my apartment for
it too
maybe uh
get that table that i wanted to get
a dining table
oh nishiki's here too
they're perfect
[Music]
i'm just nervous about it though
how do you think
[Music]
up
foreign
[Music]
foreign i'm getting hungry oh i have a
donut here
can i donut you guys listen
to
[Music]
um
foreign
go get it
um
wait a second
[Music]
mm-hmm
it's a good timing because some people
are apparently not able to watch the
stream
[Music]
um
all right thank you for watching
oh good donut holy [\h__\h]
oh no can we go inside i feel bad for
the lady that we're like making a mess
in here
that
alcohol looks expensive
[Music]
are you taunting me
wait what was that what was that that
was something new
[Music]
it's better after refresh okay everybody
refresh
you destroyed
[Music]
sorry
i need that actually i actually do need
that
[Music]
there was oh
hit left
that one is funnier when i missed
now i'll take that free
stamina anytime oh yeah
those two are so sweet yeah
they should marry you
is it that easy for him why not for me
ah
[Music]
um
ran away
oh i didn't see it
oh yeah i'm learning that now yeah thank
you
hi okay
my guess is
that the moment
where
she was holding
her brother
and we're not gonna look at the reaction
from the chat but my guess is that she
regained her sight at that moment
because her consciousness wanted to see
her brother one last time
and then uh she didn't tell them though
and then ran away
because now that she's not blind she can
actually run away yeah
that's my
what's my guess
she's somewhere here in town if i don't
find her soon she'll get snatched again
find makuto
uh
great the map is not helping me
okay fine i'll do it myself
yes i'll do it myself
i should save here
steve
a chicken fairy no it's a phoenix theory
i'm gonna beat your ass if you say
chicken one more time
by the way for the art stream i was
thinking
um
of combining it
with a q a marshmallow stream
so remind me tomorrow
to open up marshmallows
i thought that
could be nice because it gives us some
talking topics and we haven't done a
marshmallow in a million years but i
don't like i've seen that like
marshmallows
the last time i did it it didn't get
yeah
people weren't so interested in it
anymore as they were back in the day so
i think combining it with something
makes more sense and you guys get to ask
some questions
where am i supposed to go
did they give us a hint
no
if i just had some clue i don't do i
have a do i have to think personally
why could she have gone
to the empty lot maybe no
eh
no no she ran away from the park
they they went with they said they went
with her to the park and then she ran
away but she might be somewhere in the
area yeah yeah
all right let's go there
i know
foreign
lost her at the park yeah
go there
there's some men in black there
[Music]
yeah she wasn't sightseeing where where
would she want to go she would probably
just want to go off to sell the lot
immediately she just
you know that sign it always makes me
think they're just giving me um
tissues
but okay i'll keep an eye open
[Applause]
oh
no
oh no
sorry about that guys
yeah you you could maybe tell me
something
what
i hear she was blind to you
no you gave me no clue
oh they already recovered man that's
fast
did i go inside the park
and there's so
many enemies around
all these cute ladies
is there another way to get inside no
refresh now it's better nice
no i don't need your help yet
yet
no i just thought you guys
[Music]
yeah it makes sense to i mean
i guess
she would want to see the lot for
herself
can you not
how do you activate that again i forgot
a circle while
i guess it walking square more people
say square
for [\h__\h] sake
[Music]
okay
uh
where is the m2
i
at this is this one no children's park
what
where is it
where
i mean i've been there once in the
beginning of the game i forgot okay i
think it's understandable
we're checking the empty lot now
[Music]
oh wait one more fire
down
here
and then down here
[Music]
you just now realized dad is damn too
luck
oh he has never seen it himself either
huh yeah yeah
i scared i ever done a deutsche stream a
german stream no i have i've done like a
german re-debut
and some
teaching german streams
[Music]
foreign
and wouldn't you be happy about you
should you should say something
[Music]
you should say something
that was fast
foreign
yeah because she can't see him she she
he should say something
maybe she can see now
dear she looks um
sad or made
[Music]
i called it wait was that the same no
that was the first chapter for majima so
we can sneak peek we can pick a sneak
peek a snake
peek the sneak peek do it
i want to no we all want to know [\h__\h]
cliffhangers we don't do that here we
don't do that on my channel
we will find out
if i was right or not
chapter
16 proof of love
because because shimano he was like love
so
yes yes you know
um
i told you okay thank you everybody for
watching today
in theory we got our answers so
[Laughter]
i called it to be honest i i didn't say
it out loud but i was already thinking
it the moment when she was holding him
in her hands i was thinking this would
be probably the
like a moment where it would really make
sense for her to regain her sight
because it was something that was
inflicted to her mentally originally
anyway by her own by her own
brain to protect her and then when she
knows her brother is dying that would be
the perfect moment for her brain to be
like wait [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
aniva
we're gonna we're gonna
um continue this next time
that was the butt right
yeah i get that i get that i was
thinking so anyway it doesn't just
suddenly
suddenly perfectly come back
and the butt doesn't come
[Laughter]
[Music]
my
um
[Music]
my
ah
and she doesn't want to go well
um
[Music]
hmm
get some crap going
where is the lasagna what happened to
the three cheese pizzas huh
stop
stop stop or it will never end
are we real no you're not real you're in
a game makoto
you're just a game character
you're made up out of pixels
i'm realer than you are
i ate those food
yeah
uh
we're not seeing we're gonna see this
the cutscene again i think next time
cause i'm gonna end it without saving
yes
are we real
[Laughter]
no i'm not gonna resume no no
the continuation will be i think on
saturday
i think
and that might be really the last
episode i was actually like last time i
was feeling like
um
we should take it slow and all that but
i i wasn't trying to hurry today it just
happened like everything was going so
fast
so
i think we are ending it on saturday um
i was ready to do another episode next
week but yeah i think we're ending it on
saturday oh yeah yeah yeah
because we're like so close to the end
and
i understand that so many people really
enjoy like the side quests and all that
um
of rpgs
uh especially yakuza games side quests
side games and all that and i mean i've
dived into it a little bit so
i'm not taking any complaints
i'm i'm a streamer and
as a streamer it is
better for me to not drag out games
endlessly
um
and and yeah it's just it works better
for me too because then i can take on
more projects
uh sooner
and
yeah
and i still am enjoying the game a lot
and if you guys really really want to
see the side quests then you should play
it yourself
but it probably means you already played
it yourself yeah but um
i think i think i'm i'm personally
satisfied with what we're getting out of
the game so i don't mind
we've seen some of it and what i've seen
like the mini games like the for example
the the the kiaba
cabaret club i enjoyed that
uh the investments [\h__\h] not really um
some of the side quests were funny but
i'm like so
i'm immersed into the story
and at that time i don't want to be
interrupted by the side quests you know
i'm sorry i i understand
oh the bowling
ah
i do want to do the bowling though
you i told you guys to remind me
that was too late wait was that for
kitio pedio or majima
people keep on telling me about the
bowling
you understand completely thank you
worst case we'll do it yeah after after
finishing in the last episode we can
still go bowling
um
but yeah kill you okay kill you okay
okay okay okay okay
[\h__\h]
hold on
okay
to celebrate we can go bowling after
we're done with the game
uh pocket circuit uh-huh we can do that
too
if if if that's like easily available to
us after we finish the game
we can do all of that
afterwards in the same stream on
saturday i'll take a lot of time for it
i don't mind we'll finish the game we'll
do some extra stuff okay
all right
at least at least the bowling i don't
know like
apparently you guys are saying pocket
circuit maybe not so quite worth it but
bowling yes
um
pocket racing story is like five hours
okay then that's not happening
oh
okay ah
now i am going to go to an intermission
uh to go to an idle meeting and then
we're gonna read super chats okay
so feel free to stay if you want to
uh
if you don't have time anymore thank you
for watching today i'll see you the day
after tomorrow hopefully in my drawing
stream where i'm going to draw kobold
kannado the cutie pie
and i just felt like
it could be cute to
draw hair
i don't i don't want it to be like uh
too long or too crazy i'm gonna try to
keep it simple uh probably tomorrow
since i have some time i might do some
groundwork
um i think i think i have no plans for
tomorrow so i'm just gonna do some
so get some stuff done and so on
um
copa with your dryer yourself will be
cute i wonder uh she saw the schedule so
maybe she'll even come by
in the chat and say hello
yeah
oh yeah i see i have nothing
nothing to do tomorrow i was actually
yesterday
before the
collab i was actually at the doctor's
office
uh
but tomorrow
i have nothing
okay i'll go on an intermission now
productive too yes yes i was i was
pretty productive yesterday too
she wants to handle chicken mama ah she
says that again
i'll have to take this smacktus
and brush her hair gently with it
[Music]
boom
hello
jonker is in my lab
cute
oh don't worry about not knowing enough
german
everybody speaks
decent english in germany
yes
[Music]
it might have a
weird german accent though
or is this a toilet or satori
over there
on the right side
not like me
[Music]
um i demand i demand that all of you
uh where i mean you probably would do
that anyway but all of you must wear
uh kfp
flash
full life english
merchandise
so that i can
successfully dodge you
when i see you on the
[Laughter]
[Music]
street no i wish i could give you a hug
you know that but you know
and also not only that but like during
honestly i would i would be
very happy and very panicked at the same
time seeing you guys in the merchandise
for the concert though and for the meet
and greet
um
i would just be super happy to see you
guys wear it
but even outside of that you're welcome
to wear it to make it clear
who you are
the slippers yeah slippers probably
you should leave at home
mm-hmm
[Music]
is this where we're going
oh
wait is this i didn't
want a [\h__\h] mess
there's only 3d key out here where's my
where's my table
uh on it
where am i
what was this
ah
nice
that stupid layer keeps on coming back
cha cha cha cha cha cha
cha cha cha cha cha
freddie wawa
okay wawa
[Music]
i mean we're all real we're all real
there's a lot of
actually i wonder how many kiwawas are
here on this screen if you count them
one two
three
four five
six probably
seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
uh 14
uh
15 16 17 18
20. can you see that one you can't
really see that one thought we're
counting 21 22 23
at least 23.
what's your proof that you're the real
deal
do you need
do you really need proof what about our
proof of love huh
what about that what happened to dad
was that not enough
anyway let's get some
bgm going oh one of those
oh let's listen to this one
it might be a little bit too calm maybe
a little bit sad but i think
after seeing
all of that go down
i think we all need a
little bit of sadness
some emotions running through our brains
right now
there's two more hidden kiwawa's find
them all
if you say so
what do you mean you're not talking
about some chickens right
what do you mean there's two more
and i mean no the emotes keep on
changing though in the chat
i don't know what you oh wait i didn't
count i didn't count frog chiada
i don't know why that's uh
but i did count
um this picture even though i see
nothing i did count it
[Music]
no i don't see anything else
and now i counted the frog yeah
no i don't know i don't know
the real kiana froggiada
yes i did count the anniversary picture
oh wait no i only counted one of them
the one on the book i didn't count the
one because my tail was covering it i
wasn't counting that one okay well
that's 25.
yeah
if we can't frog and and the picture
behind me that i forgot then we have 25
if we also if we also count this one
and did i count myself yes i did count
myself
25 you were right you were right thank
you
16 moms damn
okay let me try to make another tea by
the way
i still have some hot water in my
thermos
[Music]
wait you don't even hear the bgm i
thought you were hearing it
it's just so hot yes yes very hot
very hot
and
add
a tea bag
[Music]
on the top right that is not me
so rude
that's not me
i need to sneeze
[Music]
i think i need to sneeze
i think oh
when i talk it goes away
isn't this kind of chill
[Music]
i miss you
i miss you so much
[Music]
talking like this
effect on right now
[Music]
yeah i think normally it's like in
japanese
[Music]
foreign
oh
i missed you again i tried to call you
because i missed you again
it seems to be always like this these
days
[Music]
make a video like this
you can't tell me what to do
[Music]
oh thank you thank you for the pink
super chat
there we go
[Music]
i'm not part of your system
uh or even though the keyboard
[Music]
should we just stay at home tonight
i'm gonna make you some
nice
yummy curry
so we don't have to
you don't have to
watch a movie
eat that curry
i still have some some cubes left over
it's been raining all day yeah cause
the sky is so
sad about what happened in yakuza
understandable
what's your what what do you want what
you want as a topping
you have a cheese topping or
sausage topping or
potato
topping
or
what else do we have maybe maybe kimchi
topping
no no pineapple is not really an option
but if you really want it i can throw it
on there
uh
potato no no no potato topping potatoes
[Music]
in the curry
she's stopping sans but that's a very
very popular topic
all right i throw some cheese for you on
to the curry
now i love pineapples
but
not on japanese curry it works well with
a
thai curry though
trust me
a voice pack if i if i did a voice pack
do you guys want another voice pack for
my next birthday
i'm sorry
do you want another voice back
when i could do something else too but
the voice pack is not really my strength
but
yeah really
like this what what would
a voice back like this
what would we call it
lo-fi
but then i think i can't sell
it with like this audio stock music in
the background i would have to
commission a track i think
staying in on the rainy day
why do i have a
when i have a megaphone on though
drive-through can't if we drive forward
oh
there's a there's a [\h__\h] typhoon
outside and you still chose to come to
kfb
thank you
i thought
i thought i would have new customers
without today
oh it's so nice to
see you
you come here
often
well i should know i work here every day
so just kidding was a joke i know
is your car okay i just saw a door
flying away from your car
are you gonna be okay you want to come
inside
i think i think it's safer inside
come on in
maybe drive through the
garage first
every step outside is
dangerous
what's happening i don't know what's
happening
you tell me what's happening i think
what's happening is love
because you come even even when there's
a typhoon you come to see me
it's called love
you may have not ever
felt before
but let me tell you that's what it is
okay shut up now
now this is starting to feel embarrassed
i'm not high on mozart but today was fun
and uh
i got some stuff done
and bleeble blue
and tomorrow is my day off yaha
super chattels where do i have to start
i have to think about the voice respect
though like i'm preparing and like
planning out birthday merch already
um
and
i think i kind of decided on on what
objects
i want to sell
um
but i don't know but like the theme of a
voice pack if i do one
the last yakuza
including the masjiankosa
the unarchived
i'll keep on the rain though by the way
that's something separate but i'll leave
it on if you want it sounds good
even though even if you look outside my
window it's not raining at all
immersion broken forever
maybe we need a upgrade update for the
background to have it be a rainy day
just kidding i already have eden
um
oh
no not not quite yet he didn't start yet
but i'm getting eden to work on another
new thing
so eden's gonna be busy again
eden is like my my savior man
always making me those super nice
beautiful high quality backgrounds i
love them so much
giving me so much variety i really
really appreciate it
yeah
okay i'm still scrolling by the way
oh i'm scrolling so much oh here's
yakuza so wait what do i have to read
yakuza or not
not sure
[Music]
yeah
okay
directly translated the japanese word
for slow
when a website is slow you say heavy in
japanese
oh have fun at work thank you for coming
by thank you
um we don't necessarily have to read all
of them today i just want to get some
some of them behind myself
i can still continue reading them on the
day after tomorrow so yeah no stress no
stress
can i drink my tea already yeah that's
some really strong rain
thundering
crisp breath
yeah it turns out um
i'm i'm voicing kiar field
the new movie that comes out whenever
the [\h__\h] i don't know
um
and uh but the thing is that
i have an announcement to make
very important announcement
m
and always have been
voiced by chris pratt
i know this comes very sudden
and surprising
um you knew it how did you knew
how
well chris pratt uh
does voice a lot of things and cover was
like
okay
i'm sure if he can voice pikachu and
garfield and whatever the [\h__\h] sonic or
i don't know
then we're sure then he can voice that
he can voice uh uh takanashikiyana so
i've been voiced by chris pratt
ever since the very beginning
yes
i figured it doesn't make any sense
anymore to hide it
it is the truth and
i only speak the truth
and i don't want to lie to you guys
anymore it's been on my mind for a long
time and um
i feel like we've gotten so close
guys that i i don't want to lie anymore
and um i feel like we can tell each
other anything
yeah
i'm sorry
but
don't worry chris pratt who is voicing
takanashikiyala is voiced by
kiana
so don't worry
it's all me in the end
no i
got you i totally got you didn't i
it's voice acting inception yes
sorry for messing with you guys and i i
shouldn't play with your feelings like
that sorry about that
double twist
it's like a wrestling move double
twister
okay let's start reading super chats uh
let me put up the thumbnail though
at the name
from that stream
it was all mr casper kitchen
yes so miniature pinscher john comes
anita for the red super taco
thank you
hi today is the last day of march we
were happy to meet a new crocodile
friend yes also dance clothes was fun
yes most important thing is there was
hallo fest yes it was an impressive mom
that will never happen again hope you
all have happy days again next month
thank you
i mean in april
uh there might be two
two sun covers
and
but besides that yeah it might be mostly
a rather normal month for me like from
my side
besides the song covers i don't think
there's much gonna be happening
um
yeah
yeah um and then
i think may may is where things um in
some way pick up again because i'm
excited to go to the maldives but that
means that probably during the maldives
there's not gonna be too much content
either
um
but
i'm also planning on
finally
releasing a new song in may
yes
probably gonna be more like
depending on how long the music video
takes um maybe the end of may but
definitely i will force it to happen
within may i feel like i've been working
on this song
for way longer than other songs because
there were also some things that i was
unsure about and
just had a hard time figuring out
some things
and
working on so many other things at the
same time as well
kind of
just
slowed the process a lot um but i just
want to get it out now
and i'm getting very conscious about how
you guys are gonna like it but
we will see we'll see i just want to get
it out now so that i can already start
working on the next one
yeah i already have ideas
for the next uh song after that so
i want to get this out now um
um the lyrics are finished and
um
i'm gonna be recording
the vocals i think this week
maybe even tomorrow yeah
and um
i
kind of planned out
what the
what what art i need for the music video
and
what the music video is gonna look like
and all that
i planned out some things yesterday
yeah
i've sent my thoughts to the artist
no i'm not leaking what genre it is yet
you will probably
be able to guess it once i announce the
title and show you guys the
thumbnail or whatever
because i feel like that might give it
away
um but for now it is still secret um
but yeah this month will just be
normal mostly normal
i mean when i say normal it will still
be fun because we have song covers
coming out and we have fun collabs this
week we have finally hodotody happening
finally
um
and
i think the week after i'll do monopoly
with uh lena odi and ame
which is funny um a funny coincidence
i put together this group to play
monopoly
um and then
kelly put the same group together to
call in for her 3d stream right for the
um for the guessing game the charades
game i was like
how did she do it she didn't even know
about the monopoly group she didn't know
about it but just by coincidence she put
i think
i don't know why it's just coincidence
it was like kusa this is the same group
that i put together from monopoly funny
uncle winky dink
oh by the way
before
i'm gonna leak some knowledge here
before the
um
before the stream started we did we did
a practice round for charades right um
with everyone together both both groups
and
uh we did one only one sample
so kelly starts moving
and
i i swear she did she started moving and
within
1.5 seconds
i yelled out the answer
but everyone else was quiet
she was doing actually the prompt was
idle
and the funny thing is
for doing
uh idol movement
she actually did also the kikkity kick
yeah so i was like ah i do
so the testing round immediately ended
with me yelling out the answer
immediately because i just i just know
what an idol looks like it looks like me
[Laughter]
that's the best way to
express
what an item looks like and i'm the best
person to guess it because i know what
it looks like
no no during the
stream prompt was then takana sukiya so
then i was like
is this supposed to be idol again or
takana
but i yelled out both just in case
well what does that mean why am i a tank
i'm a i'm an idol not a tank
oh i didn't see that because uh we
didn't see that on our side what they
missed
they misspelled my [\h__\h] name
that's why there was tango nasi
kiana
fan art what i didn't i was like where
did that come from
i didn't understand where that came from
what
[Music]
oh my god
i am impressed
i i am quite impressed that they misroad
my name
because uh
it happened before i think with uh
you know like
other other places like i don't know
some kind of
article or something
but
uh
my own company really my own company
hmm yeah
yeah
impressive okay
i am bamboo
or or maybe it was on purpose and
the actual thing that she was supposed
to do was
impersonate a kia that is a tank become
a tank
that is kiara you know like the fan art
and we actually all failed the task
because i guessed it wrong
and
callie did it wrong and the management
accepted the answer anyway and went ding
she was supposed to yeah act like a tank
like a tank nasi kiyada
yeah an attack that kicks a tank that
kiki kicks
now i finally understand that we cleared
a big
big question mark up in my head
i thought it was something that came out
of nowhere randomly without me even like
creating something like the time where
people started drawing whole life
members as cars you know
like that came out of nowhere too i
think there was no particular reason
nothing that we did in order to make
that happen it's just just suddenly fan
artists
drew us as cars
yeah or myth kids but myth kids was
partially um supported by me personally
oh good i had a hand in that really
i wonder
mama mohammed
maybe maybe i don't know oh uh jacob's
monkey donkey shin looking for the top
donkey shooting kiana's bus cart thank
you
skye dan kishan thank you for the pinky
sorry to travel you attention but want
to tell you that the vod of art and chat
coffee coloring time is still not issued
until now it is only 360p quality to
choose
i
several times um
mentioned that
to management and
supposedly it was brought up to youtube
um but
i don't think youtube gives a [\h__\h] about
it i told them it's not processing
anymore it's gun processing and it had
1080p before
but it suddenly went back to 360p and it
has ever since then not recovered
but
they don't care so it's lost forever
um
i mean i can do i can say it one more
time
i don't think it's gonna
help
um
let me bring it up one more time
before i forget it
how when was that stream how many months
had it been
when was that
let me look it up
over over two months ago
yeah two months ago
uh
has been
at 360 p only since
two months even
though it already finished processing
and had 1080p at
one point
what is
back to
mississippi
which makes your archive
unwashable
mm-hmm
yeah i stream
i don't know why
but the thing is like
i don't know maybe with a chit chat
stream or something or super chat
reading stream like it doesn't matter
but for an art stream um
it's not so nice to have everything look
like super pixely and low resolution
can you download the archive and
re-upload i
but that's like
down re-uploading a stream from two
months ago
um
i
don't like the idea of that
for
several reasons but i do wonder if i
were to download it if
if it would
be in 360p or
in the proper quality that's that is a
good question i didn't try that yet
if i would download it from my youtube
studio not from just some
download youtube service
let me see
here it is
a download
it's 1.2 gigabyte
so that sounds like
although it is an eight hour stream i
don't know 360p eight hours do you guys
think that gets to 1.2 giga
that is very small
oh okay then it's totally ruined
maybe it's ruined forever maybe it can't
be fixed
maybe it's just unfixable
but like the thing is though when i go
into the video
it says here uh
quality of video sd and hd
processing complete
so that's a lie
we've been lied to
usually about one giga per hour oh wow
it's an old stream anyway it doesn't
matter now but there's apparently as you
can see still people
who kind of want to watch it but don't
want to watch it in 360p
there are still people there
and i want to be of their service
i want to help but um
yeah maybe we need to give up on it
maybe
oh well oh well
ah butthead we have a new art stream the
day after tomorrow so even if it doesn't
get fixed
maybe it's time to move on
and say sayonara forever
all right doc joseph thank you for the
rainbow
thank you for the rainbow
no text with it
thank you though thank you for the big
support thank you soon
on a rainy day like this a rainbow is
the most beautiful thing to see
the gamer created
uh pinky unknowns blue superchat is not
avoided but we're going to do what
unknown says and love yeah i i saw it
was out of order you love kiara
no maybe it was on purpose
maybe it was on purpose it's just
stating facts
you
love kiara
jacob 47 out thank you in the game of
criticism
for the red super chat
[Music]
let me read this in radio style
um
i try to sound serious
[Applause]
[Music]
how you doing
continue in a little bit
thank you very much for coming by in the
last yakuza stream are you here today to
haven't seen you
haven't noticed you
oh for just over
[Music]
i might not be able to watch the whole
stream as exams tomorrow i'm kind of
like fighting on two fronts now being
the only one left without having to see
thing in my household oh dear
well you're lucky i guess
in in the wrong
area you should be lucky with your exams
i hope they went well
i'm so glad i don't have to do that kind
of stuff anymore oh my god
i do not envy you but i hope they went
well
um okonomika are you here
are you here how did they go
tell us
you died in the accent what did you get
deceiving during the exam
i hope it wasn't too bad
it was a disaster oh no you know what
might be the reason
the reason might be that you watch too
much kiara
you didn't study enough probably because
you watched too much of my streams
probably
that's probably
probably the issue
but
you know
school
tries to
make you think that mathematics and
oneplus 3 and all that is the important
thing to learn in life but i think
you know a lot of what they teach us we
never use again
later but what we create here in in
this stream
at this very moment
is
is memories that are temporary you know
what mathematics is not temporary it's
forever and even though it is eternal we
don't need it
but this here what we need this is what
we need and this is not this is not
forever so
what's more important i think it's very
obvious now i think it's very obvious
but still go to school and do your exams
enlightening enlightening i know
circuit theory i don't know um maybe you
should just go to a circus and learn
there about circus feelings
just kidding and wait you actually
uh i know never mind never mind thank
you though uh maybe you can redo the
exam or something
fine fighter
advanced calculus that sounds like [\h__\h]
you never need later on unless you
become
a mathematician
but fighter vital okay don't give up
chicken rice thank you shin necklace
ingredient
thank you oh you got the omo cat stuff
nice
[Music]
s
you know what i'm gonna do i'm gonna put
it into my schedule now
i wanted to put it into my schedule
learn
korean
i i put it in my schedule
i will learn korean i'm putting it in my
schedule for two hours okay
and
i'm gonna do this in my schedule as well
maybe record maybe if i want to
maybe record song i could also do it on
sunday i think i have time on sunday
it doesn't really matter when i record
it i have to wait for the music video a
long time anyway it's gonna take
gonna take a while
yes i will learn the hangul
writing system tomorrow tomorrow
yeah oh by the way uh
speaking of korean
uh
yeah let's go tangent i should keep
these tangents for the drawing stream
but oh well we'll have marshmallow um
i
on my day off no not on my day off was
it on my day off it was on saturday
i think not this week's day off but last
week's day off
was saturday i think
um
after i slept
after after the vr collab so it was kind
of the same day
i went to meet um some friends who uh
came to the to the city to visit me
um
[Music]
because i live somewhere else normally
um
and they came and stayed one night uh
not at my place but somewhere else but
uh they
uh they wanted to see me so we went to
have lunch lunch was really yummy
i think i tweeted about it yeah i am
we went to a japanese restaurant but the
reason why i say
speaking of korean is because
those those two
they are a couple um
and i love them they're so sweet they're
hot
they're like
goals and and so sweet together and and
they both love korea too and kpop and
especially the girl um one of my best
friends she's so
into shiny
shiny
a male
k-pop group i think she's more into the
male k-pop well i'm an into the female
k-pop
no not bff someone else another good
friend i have
shiny yes yes and she's a huge fan and
and she loves korean
culture and food and fashion and all
that and she i think she even tries to
cook some korean food at home by herself
and all that so i was thinking
she would probably totally be in to go
to korea together with me so i asked her
but she said no
because she doesn't have
um the like you know she's she's
she's like those normal people who have
certain a certain amount of
uh vacation days in one year and
therefore cannot just say all right
let's go to korea
this year
she would do it next year but not this
year because she's using up her vacation
days already
so i'm very very sad i feel like it
would have been so much fun
oh because
there's actually um
a connection here that i want to tell
you when i came to japan the last time
you know when i stayed for one year
um
those two
actually came with me this was like
literally like a few days before the sea
thing broke out everywhere
um and they they went to japan with me
they stayed like i don't know one two
weeks or so i don't know and then they
left and i stayed because i had a one
year visa
and and we had uh we took the we took a
flight together to japan so that was fun
because that was the first time i
did not fly to japan alone
so i could i could actually lean my head
on someone's shoulder because it was not
a stranger next to me but one of my
friends that was lovely
and then yeah we just enjoyed the the
first few weeks together like we were
tourists or something
and then they left and then you know i
thought i thought they might come back
or or rmt is gonna come by and all that
and i'm not gonna be all alone but no no
no one ever no one ever was able again
to enter the country since then
yeah
but
um
you know i thought it would be cool to
repeat that how we went to japan
together repeat that and go to korea
that would have been nice because she
also
she even though she has never been to
korea before i feel like she would
know what to do and where to go
anyway because she also watches a lot of
korean youtubers
and all that
so i think she would already have a huge
plan of what to do and where to go
she by the way watches
um
my clips
not my streams just clips and she's a
clip launcher
and she listens to my music and knows
that she's really supportive
and actually her her boyfriend
does not watch clips but watches my
streams
actually more than she does
so they're both like so supportive
they're so sweet like
even even before hollow
were
like
the most supportive friends i i've ever
had i think
yeah they would even though we're like
really really close friends they would
like
one one thing they did once is um
there was something that i did um
let's say something like a performance
and um they
they surprised me by showing up
with self-made t-shirts with my [\h__\h]
face on both sides
it was so cute
it was so cute and they they also um
they brought light sticks and [\h__\h]
and and gave it to the others
to hold them
yeah
it was so sweet and like
yo
like
i feel like you know friends are friends
and are nice and all that but it's rare
to have
friends who
like really s
are so
enthusiastically
support you like that
so yeah those are some real homies
really yeah
we have a
long long friendship at this point and i
wouldn't want to
i wouldn't want to live without them
they're great people
[Music]
yeah great friends
are friends that will stay with you
forever
yes
i'm looking forward to being maybe
an honorary
flower maiden one day if they ever have
a wedding i am so ready i'm so ready i'm
gonna support them the way they
supported me until now
i'm gonna i'm gonna come to the wedding
with a t-shirt
uh
with one of their faces on each side
and i'm gonna flow
throw around flowers flower petals in
their faces
[Laughter]
i i ship them so strong
oh
the cutest okay i i need to stop i need
to read super chats holy [\h__\h]
um
the gamer creed donkey shown petsy
duncan
it's not so dangerous for the red super
chad
thank you very much
lurker here breaking out of my timid
shell to share some love you're very
entertaining and i adore your singing
thank you i keep dreaming too too on
loop oh
not having the best birthday but this
life is making it a bit better oh
thank you for everything you do and keep
up the good work thank you i wonder if
you're lurking again right now
thank you i'm sorry i didn't know it was
your birthday because i didn't read the
super chats but happy birthday birthday
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
to you
it's my turn
happy birthday
to you
[Music]
stop working you should come out of your
shell more often okay
thank you very much
and and thank you i'm happy you like my
singing and dreaming too too
i hope you'll also like my next song
cover coming out sometime soon
thank you for the pink uh super stick up
thank you
lurker is lurking now
what song is it going to be i'm not
going to tell you no no it's too early
because of duncan allen plays for fun
duncan manuel torres function
oh
if you go to the single arcade and do
the little girl side quest
i didn't see a little girl's side quest
probably because today today i was like
um with majima in tokyo so there's no
side quest
and we'll kill you i was in osaka so
there was no cyclist but then i
apparently get the mom for the cabaret
and she's gold
[Music]
that would have been nice
maple leaf two five zero one donkey
i blew right by her like not no girl
really i don't even remember that
thank you maple leaf for the red super
chat i've come to the conclusion that
keaton's free fighting styles would be
fire brand balanced
bonk puts the crowbar to use
and rooster heavy kicks
and put this towards your louis vuitton
bag
oh thank you
thank you
maybe i'll maybe i will get one maybe i
will go
thank you very much
here's a little fly kiss for you
[Music]
a brazilian snack box sure um i'm
currently just relying on whatever the
service provides but once that is over
unless they also automatically renew my
subscription i wonder
um
but
if they don't then i might just try to
get my own snack boxes together or look
for a different service
on my own
um
mr casper
messed up brain spike thank you
uh wait i need to translate this one
um
[Music]
another translation
coming
in
hey thank you for the pinky
10 to april has just begun in korea i've
enjoyed with you in march i was happy to
be with you on your 3dw i want to have a
good time with tanjo in april too have a
happy end potential and give and see me
eager you scared me for a moment that
sounded like a goodbye for a little
while like oh april has just begun i
need to go back to school i'm busy if
march was fun
but yeah i won't be around anymore
goodbye i thought that's what you were
gonna say
you scared me there but okay that sounds
like you're staying after all thank you
yoda's cool
i don't know how to say that in korean
but yodo school
but no money no no no no the other way
around yes yes yes yes
i'll pour some more hot water into my
tea
you're sure
it's a trauma
it really is
maple will leave two five zero one thank
thank you for the pinky
hi kenneth it's my birthday today oh
what better way to spend it than
watching one of my favorites playing a
series i love oh wonderful
happy fellaini's birthday to you len
yoshido i hope you celebrated well
congratulations
please stay healthy and happy okay make
the best out of it
thank you soon
um
happy birthday
happy birthday i'm already excited for
my birthday too i want my birthday to be
soon
i i oh actually um was it on monday i
think it was on monday on my day off i
planned
i already because i had to early on i
already planned out my whole birthday
stream
like which songs and which people to
invite and and uh uh
what what kind of
side things i want to do what what what
i need what if i need some items what do
i
have to plan early these kind of things
you guys are invited of course
i as i said we'll have to go to a mocap
studio for it fly somewhere um
yeah but i
i would not want to risk not having a 3d
um
concert
for my birthday this year and i also
want the quality to be good so
um yeah
yeah
i have some mixed feelings about it but
i will do it
for
my own satisfaction and in order to make
you guys happy and proud as well
yeah
i'll leave it at that
it's gonna turn out great i hope so i
hope so
i have some
interesting things planned
i hope it's gonna turn out well
i'm monopoly money
you're monopoly money
thank you
if it's monopoly money then i can only
use it on monopoly
so i'll use it on monopoly soon
i don't think i could make it into japan
by then and even if i could it would all
just be two two last minutes probably
um
these kind of things need to be planned
ahead of time and
um
i would need there to be before my
birthday and that's at this point not
really possible i feel like june is like
june is
impossible for me to go
unless unless i know it really early
enough
not but not really last minute
yeah
you know i
i was i was really hoping to have the
3dw before my birthday
because
once i do a proper 3d birthday stream
you will have seen me
in motion
um
in like from from every angle for a
whole hour
also doing some other stuff besides
performing probably so
at that point it's like
it completely takes away
the meaning and and purpose of a 3d
debut stream
and then
that really
makes me
mad
yeah
um
but i hope that we can somehow still
make it
interesting enough
by
you know
adding things more things
it's just for me it makes no sense and
i'm thinking like if if if i'm gonna
like ruin it with my birthday stream
anyway i could already just do it now by
using my home pretty
for like with my head only like somehow
it just makes no sense anymore nothing
makes sense but
i'm gonna try to hold back a little
while longer
um curlish yes but that's just because
that's how she wanted her for dw to be
um because like that's also something
that we can decide ourselves if we want
our 3d debut to be
focused on singing and performing then
we can put as many songs as we want in a
debut but if we wanted to be
not so much focused on that then we can
do whatever the hell we want with it
um but yeah energy is
uh top notch idol and i
think it's
it just fits her
that she wanted to
make it into a big concert because why
the hell not
she can do it so she should do it
thank you brandon thank you
know
i'll it's it's uh
it's just not ideal
at all
thank you guys thank you
maybe we should just all act
for the 3dw as if it's the first time
you ever see me in freaky
i'm sure you guys can do that right
you're going to be like oh wow
never seen you for me ever before this
is so amazing what a legendary day today
is this will be in the history books
yeah you guys are good at that
i'm counting on you guys um
[Applause]
attention my deepest apology i failed to
remind you by telepathy while in the
doctor office
wait what was it again the evil power in
that room was too strong please accept
my blood as apology now i must go i'm
late for my
appointment
what the [\h__\h]
what are you trying to tell me there
i don't get it is that supposed to be a
joke at the end
i'll get it
ah
uh-huh
um
i did mention that um like uh yesterday
when i was at the doctor it was a
different doctor from the last time so i
told that doctor that i thought that me
and the doctor last time forgot about it
for the referral uh uh and i was asking
that doctor if he could help me with
that but he was like oh no i think you
gotta go back to the other doctor i was
like okay
anyway um by the end of the session it
was like a one hour session
uh i quickly had to leave
because i had um i had a delivery coming
to my apartment
so i had to be there in time and then
the [\h__\h] ubers [\h__\h] me over again
by not coming uh to where i ordered them
to even though it was totally possible
so that wasted some time but then i
still made it in time
and
i swear i came home and one minute later
they rang my doorbell
and
this was actually
a delivery
that i
waited for
one year
ichinenko
yes
it was um a piece of furniture
from kick check no
no it was from a from a normal like
furniture store here and i ordered it
together with some other things and the
other things they arrived pretty quickly
but this one piece of furniture
um i think they were out of stock um
and and there was like a there was a
delivery date originally there that was
like i don't know two months or so later
already but that was in springtime when
i ordered it and um
at the point where it was supposed to
somehow arrive sooner or later they uh
delayed the delivery
until one year later
because
i think probably because of the sea
thing they weren't able to get a new
stock from that piece of furniture i
guess probably i mean what else
besides that i cannot imagine any better
explanation
but it took them so long that i wanted
that piece of furniture for summer
because it was something for my balcony
and then the whole summer i didn't have
it so i was like what the [\h__\h]
so still bad
and yesterday it finally came so i did
not want to miss this delivery
appointment
um
yeah
now i cannot build it unfortunately i
need some help to assemble it
yes you need to go to the usual room for
that one yes
yeah summer is uh close
actually it's already pretty warm here
in april although there's like some days
in april i told you about this last year
remember
we call it april weather
where
one day it can be super sunny and the
next day it can be snowing
it legit already happened so
april is crazy here
but there are some warm days so i am
uh
looking forward to using my new piece of
furniture for that
um
it is insane though it's like what the
[\h__\h] april what the [\h__\h] and literally
the moment april is over it goes back to
normal
oh my god my throat help
doomsday dan danke actually those are
flush jets i'm gonna skip those
maple leaf dungeon for the red super
chat doll
this is why i love kiana streams
casually talking about her soaps and
shoes asking the real questions while
she beats up some thugs that's it
breaking my rule i officially have a
number one favorite you didn't want to
have a number one favorite
and now i am it took you that long
wait what show was i talking about
i was talking about upload right yeah
while we were running through that um
through that weird weird castle thingy
yeah yeah remember
oh
oh that's so i
did i tell you guys i'm
i liked the show but
it had so many like
logic mistakes
like
so many things like even for a
show focused on comedy
there's so many things that just didn't
make sense
even if you don't try to question things
it's just so
so straight up like
that makes no sense like you don't even
have to think about it you just
you're just like that makes no sense
yeah
not yeah plot holes i guess
logic
holes yeah and that kind of pissed me
off a little bit but i did my best to
ignore it
and just deal with it and enjoy the show
but it was so stupid partially
yeah
well thank you may believe though thank
you i am happy to be your number one
mwah
uh how long yeah
two days two days is okay you need to
work
go back to work for the sticky note
service after all
uh
[Music]
the new employee will go to bed now
cheer up for today's show
uh
employee thank you
are you here today probably probably not
kosty
krusty
hello hello
hello hello hello hello hello i don't
think kosty is here
well thank you
i hope to see you again
sometime
i think it's already very late in korea
so it's understandable if you
fell asleep that's okay
but i'll see you
in the drawing stream maybe hopefully
thank you for trying your best to watch
my streams dancing
just some guy with a moustache duncan
the gamer crazy
duck joseph thank you
thank you for the sneeze chats everybody
the gamer great donkey blew down
i need a fruit candy i think a bit
my throat feels weak
that was too high energy today
no dog
now we have this one
if you didn't watch it you should watch
it because it was fun
it was really fun for me to do
yeah did my best to
prepare something funny for april fools
for you guys
you re-watch it several times really
thank you
made me cry in the end oh no oh no
[Music]
yeah it was a little bit emotional
maybe
did you tell the myth girls in your lore
i uh told ina about it um
when we were
uh
when we were preparing for the vr chat
stream
um
because we were there quite early um
setting up
and and me and ina were done and just
chilling and while ame and gouda were
trying to figure out some stuff about
the games that we were planning and all
that
so
actually behind the scenes before the
stream i hugged her several times and
this is so weird but when i hugged her
off screen
it felt so real
even though it was just vr it felt so
real and then i told her what i did in
my april full stream
i am always hanging with inna
hanging out with inya
we kept on
staying together the whole time
[Music]
yeah love inna
mmm but i really gotta
um
give props to good at this time
because she prepared so much she had she
had so many ideas for this
she put it all together very fast and
very reliable
and yeah
and she got us uh
those those uh those switcheroo outfits
and all that
she
she normally
doesn't like
manage so many things at once i think
that that was maybe a challenge for her
and i think she did a great job at it
it came out really nice and fun and we
play some fun games
i think you know um we play a lot of
like real games and all that in our
streams
um but sometimes you know making our own
games like that
it can be really fun too just even if
it's just simple game like twister or
something like that
um
or charades or whatever it is
i feel like that has a lot of charm
as well so
it's just a bit more opinion he has to
prepare
especially within vr
it needs it needs more effort than just
turning on buying a game and turning it
on and slapping it onto obs and go
yeah
but i like what we did there and good i
did great
and i think i looked so good in cali's
clothes it wasn't even my choice it was
just a sign to me and i was like holy
[\h__\h] ah it looks so good
i looked so good oh my god
i was feeling myself in that close yeah
sorry
it was perfection i agree
yeah
um when she came up with the idea
she showed us that fan art to kind of
inspire us i guess um and i didn't think
she would like completely follow
that fan art but she did so that's why i
ended up
in those clothes
very very hot
i really like it i mean you guys also
know the story um from me and kelly
that
before debut we kind of talked about
wanting to switch bodies
uh but of course that's not really
possible was not really an option so
um
it's funny how now i got a chance to
wear cali's clothes and it looks so good
on me
my body language i saw a lot of people
talk about that and posting screenshots
and to be honest i wasn't even trying
that was just me like
in a lazy stance i was just resting
that was my resting stance
um
like you know resting your arm on your
hip like that is just just resting
that was that was just me chilling all
of the
throughout the whole stream i was just
chilling but i most of the time i had a
mirror in the front like um we have like
an invisible mirror uh
in front of us
and and i was looking at myself and i
was like yeah you know what even when i
just chill like this it looks so hot so
i just continued doing it
music died for a moment
yeah so i i know it looked good but i
was just chilling
yeah i'm glad you guys got so many good
screenshots out of that
[Laughter]
looking good
yeah it worked well with that outfit
cause uh it's kind of elegant and and
has maybe like a boss boss [\h__\h]
or wrap
is that is that accurate
is that fitting
yeah yeah yeah you know what i mean
that boss baby buzz [\h__\h]
girl bus
oh yeah oh
yeah girl plus
maybe that's what i wanted to say
okay we're reading super chats again
joseph thank you for the pinky foot
massage funds for keep up
if we're lucky maybe next year we'll get
pretty dancing kibaba oh
oh my dear
you will hear the sound of my bow wounds
as if i was just a skeleton
it will completely cover the music
probably i'm not sure about it
i'm not sure if i can handle that
but who knows
who
knows it sounds funny angie to get a vr
model modeled after a kibaba
actually does sound fun
thank you for the idea dug yourself
what you finished tales of berseria wow
i didn't think you would actually play
it and then actually finish it so fast
really
but the tails of vasaria when i played
it i absolutely
binged it myself
when i played it i remember
it's a joke
it's just a joke well what the [\h__\h] i
was respecting you for it
hey go play bethesda visaria now
i finished tales of berseria in a really
short amount of time too it was just so
addicting
and i had nothing else to do
during that time
i think i had a lot of free time
um
so yeah
yo yo
don't turn my profile picture upside
down huh
is not just a car
did you change it
got it why
i don't see anything i have april fool's
slippery shed
wait are you
i thought so it's harder line because of
the car
but the name didn't sound like
harvard
no no
oh
oh [\h__\h] you okay you made me say in okay
i'm out of here
no
no no no
it's not april fool's anymore it's the
sixth of april for [\h__\h] sake
it's the sixth
[Music]
i'm back on the stand
one year usual room i don't care if
you're already there
if that's the case we're adding one year
hope you're happy hope that was worth it
it's a joke you think that can be an
excuse for anything
you think you can excuse yourself
from anything just by saying it's joke
it's not joke
now that went too far
that went way too far
it's just a prank bro
i will put you in the usual room too
i don't even see him here what a coward
i don't even see harbor line in the chat
anymore
just a coward
show your face
show your goddamn face
before you go to the usual room
where are you huh
where are you
it's just a
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] car wood
[Laughter]
where is he is he here
thank you
are all of these super chats [\h__\h]
april fools
mithra hikari
junction for the pinky okay sure tell us
your tales or feelings i'll stay awhile
and listen um i had i've heard that
somewhere i've been asleep for 500 years
or something like that it's not like i
enjoy hearing the sound of your voice
and endless stories you have to tell her
anything returns to normal that's okay
this is okay sooner is okay
becoming soon that is okay oh i am not
mad about that thank you
he's here
see he is so far into the user room that
my eyes already filter him out of the
chat for me
oh bgm oh
like i don't even see him anymore
i haven't even seen him
so
that's not you
apparently your name is still
something else
i don't see him he's trying to come
flash himself
guards get him
he's just not chatting
uh
felix sal thank you for
four red super chats what the hell thank
you
thank you felix i feel like i haven't
seen you in a while
now i see you heartbroken ah thanks for
happy april fools i normally don't
celebrate this yeah me neither but i
guess it never hurts to tell harmer's
lies and have a few laughs but i promise
you danger no matter what form you take
and how much time passes my burning love
never subsides and in the future before
time and this better not be a joke the
first time ends i'm never gonna sure
sure sure never gonna give you i'm never
gonna let you down never gonna run
around and desert you uh-huh
i'm pretty sure it didn't turn out as
nicely as i wanted but you get my idea
i'm just gonna go back and hide in the
oven now
you did nothing bad
everybody take an example from felix sal
who who whose joke it is
to tell me
how much he loves me even though it's
not even a joke it's just the truth
thank you felix
you're the best thank you
[Music]
thank you for all your love and happy
april fools
oh my god oh
are you
are you um let me polish them
are you expecting me to read this okay
i'm not gonna read this
i can try to translate it
with a pain in the ass
and the pain in the ass you guys are
it's [\h__\h] polish
super jets are a bit rusty let me polish
them it's so funny
you're so funny all of you are so funny
you hear how i'm laughing oh
it's actually pretty sweet what it says
that's that's actually pretty sweet
it's actually pretty pretty sweet
it was funny it was actually funny and
the message behind it is really sweet it
does not hurt my feelings so hokan
you deserve this one
thank you
thunderstorm four one two three four
five pinkies thank you
yeah i have something important i need
to tell you i
you
a prayer chance but you should already
know the missing word is love but
i guess i do but can you repeat it and
and put it together properly and tell me
again
can you tell me again
clearly so i i don't have to
second
guess and doubt it
i want to make sure
i want to make sure that that's really
what you mean
and then it's not just an april fool's
joke
are you here skye
are you here
goku
you didn't need to receive the super
chat i was looking at the chat who to
wait for you
but you're so fast thank you
i love you too
i love you
thank you
and now i am sure
now i believe
thank you for your love
much much love back to you
happy april fools
slowpoke the 3 000 years old
kfp pokemon kf pokemon
oh my god i fell in love with your 3d
model you always make it worth staying
until the end of the stream thank you
for the yakuza stream
in my 3d model that's not slow that's
very recent
why is slowpoke so fast now why is
slowpoke so caught up
oh because it was ah
because i was old and it was like three
thousand years later now again
no no no it's not about being caught up
it was because uh i was in the future
we were all in the future
so slowpoke was still slow considering
where we were at that time point of time
big brain
it took actually he got even slower yeah
because it got it it took him 3 000
years
to react to my 3d
holy [\h__\h]
it's probably because slowpoke is also
getting old actually the profile picture
seems to be an old slowpoke because it
has a white beard
that was pretty slow
ultra slow
so you go come here thank you for the
rest of the chat
attention i want to tell you a secret
i'm not a real kfp joke
you can't fool me suika
also if you give it away so fast yeah
there is absolutely no way to fool me
but even without the joke at the end of
it i would have known
i would have known
thank you
[Music]
for the red super chat
story corner
trevor g thanks for the pinky might be a
wild hench but this old lady seems nice
warm and friendly totally not one to
prey on other much younger burps of
various species and then feed them to
her cats
no she
looks harmless enough
so why not i'll stay around listen
yeah
harmless i am indeed
yes
i am very harmless
um
i i was just uh i was just a nice
grandma who makes cookies for everybody
i was i think i was being super super
sweet
cookies doko good question
i have some pocky with me
now this i cannot read but i know
who it is
is that uh that's a a
a rab a arabic red
navida mehdi
i know what you're doing you're trying
to confuse me but i know the profile
picture so
there's only you who has that profile
picture
so
not even a good try but thank you for
the pinky
you need to try harder what does the
rest say here
grandma chicken can i have some candy
chicken
even after 3 000 years you have no
respect for what i am
wouldn't the proof be that i lived for 3
000 years that i am not
a chicken because which [\h__\h] chicken
can live for three thousand years
must be mistranslation yeah that's true
that's probably what it is
that's probably probably what it is
right right navi a mini right
we just uh had a problem with the
translation there
i uh
i give you the benefit of the doubt
you don't seem to want to defend
yourself
in the chat
okay
i feel like i saw you though let's go
with that okay
why you always call me chicken
guys i'm not
you guys can't read or something i'm a
[\h__\h] phoenix do you think do you
think do you really think
that this is the work of a chicken
huh that makes no sense how could a
chicken
make the
whole stage be on fire huh
how could i set the whole stage on fire
if i was a chicken
that's not a cute chicken no
i don't know
i need to just skip all of the april
fool's super chat you know what i could
read them in 3000 years because these
are for kibaba not for me
these are not even for me
i don't even have to read them they did
not even arrive yet at this point of
time these super chats don't exist
i can just ignore them
thinking logically thinking logically
finally aged a 3 000 year old
i wonder if they will have aged so well
in 3 000 years
okay
see you in 3000 years
no i could really do that i could the
way you troll me guys i could troll you
back
i could be like this could this will be
read by kibaba in three thousand years
i have the right to do that
and it will be your own fault you will
have bamboozled yourself
my paycheck for this stream until the
year 5022
but the problem is that by
5022 cover will be um
deleted by the illuminati so
how am i gonna ever get that paycheck
how
how's that gonna work
i need it to be paid in advance
how
oh don't question it don't don't
question it
um
dominican audition for the pinky i guess
i'm gonna read them anyway
consider it beautiful and forgiving
grandma kiwawa please tell what did you
think of the debut of eighteen's new
kojai ah
um
i only watched like a small snippet of
when she was talking to eichen
so
i
don't really have
any thoughts yet besides
she seemed
like
she sounded and looked like she was out
of some
visual novel or something some animal i
don't know
uh it
i don't know
she doesn't quite have that uh ichan
working behind the scenes vibe
which is interesting
it feels more like one of us like a
talent than like someone like ajan which
is very confusing
[Music]
yeah i have to give it some time i
didn't really have time to um take a
good look at it and and i mean there is
probably maybe some time in the future
gonna be a chance for us to interact
maybe like i did with ajan but at the
moment my my mind is occupied with other
things but congratulations uh
maybe she will take off some work from h
on
a chance workload and that will be great
for it john because i know aetron is
also very busy so
um
if it helps on then that's beautiful
miss opportunity to have her be named
bichon
absolutely
absolutely actually i don't know why
they did not do that
why did they not do that
why does ajan just
have the name ayton and then
she has this whole name like an anime
character
because even the name sounds
hundred percent like a character out of
an anime more than a real person
hmm
why is she not bitchin
huh
seriously go with a theme are we
complaining
no no no
it would make her seem less important
maybe yeah
i guess so maybe
um
yeah she looks like an idol master
character
[Music]
um
do you even understand what i'm saying
slightly
because your name name says i am a real
japanese person and ever since i saw
that name pop up in my chat i was like
kind of doubting it
i don't believe also because your
currency is not
not japanese
x a big x on that one jeff star thank
you for the pinky
thank you for the pink super sticker
actually thank you
miniature pincher
[Music]
will you still love me when i'm no
longer young and beautiful
when i'm still an uber when i'm already
in obasan
come on all of you say yes
how do you know that song
because i'm a fan of idols japanese
idols and that's a classic
yes
before in one archived karaoke i'm
pretty sure
[Music]
da
great songs there and the game agreed
thank you soon against monkey duncan
from fro thank you for the red super
chat there's nothing more cozy than see
than to see umi sit on a wooden chair
listen to her amazing stories while
eating glued huge pizza cookies
they're not glued and to have two
thousand two hundred plus cat blue sorry
cat hair in my beak
that's one of those cat is around us
love you kibaba oh no need to i i wait
for kiwawa
thank you
well you don't want kibama's kisses what
doesn't make not never give up or no
kibaba puts glue in the cookies no
also they're not pizza cookies why would
because they're so big are you saying
because they they were so big the ones
that i made
i need to make more there's it's
available
but i'm too lazy
i'm too lazy man and also they come in
such huge batches that like i can't i
can't eat them all
but i should make them i should make
them for my visitors
from mummy
and the other girls who
have not been and cali and the other
girls who haven't been announced
properly and
i'll keep it a secret
oh
that was the name of the user but it's
kind of a
name that creeps me out
uh cruz duncan evans l dankeshen typhon
mysteries
moody crowd
anton m
shawnee
if i could support kiara to your age
nothing would make me happiness
or you mean more happy right
thank you
for
[Music]
da
songs
[Music]
it's kind of like a good transition
there
it works so well together
[Music]
i love that song
they're both beautiful
aquarium i need to sing that
japanese members like to sing that every
once in a while but i've never sang it
in a karaoke before
i should
i try to remember that for
uh
for
for uh
archived stream sometimes
it's so beautiful
since 5000 million years ago i've been
reading super chats but i tension so
much i can't help it i will never stop
reading these to pretend please someone
stop me or help me i will never end
streaming all day 24 hours yay
but it's okay cause i love you so
i prefer this all thank you
i think the original lyrics are nicer
though
thank you for the red super chat
uh
vine ash
thank you also for a red super chat
oh dear what does all of this mean
uh is this a joke
is this some kind of joke
oh no
no it is a [\h__\h] joke
it is a [\h__\h] joke it started nicely
and then it turned into a rick roll
in a chinese
and chinese recruit
unbelievable
she like the tin chun
have a nice day
i don't think i've been rick rolled in
chinese before
thank you
for
35 years ago it wasn't your fault you
have to let us go
how can you
how can you make up such a sad story
mother-son are you okay
that's too sad
it's too sad
i won't let you go
it's a meme
how
how the [\h__\h] does mother-son know more
memes than i do
mother-son is japanese isn't he
why does he know more memes than i do
but even dan is too sad it's just too
sad
not a boomer that has nothing to do with
that
there's nothing to do with that
the more boomer
i am the more memes i should know
because i've been on the internet longer
than you guys
i'm
so sad
wait no i hate that no i i hate that no
no i i hate even the thought of that no
no no i [\h__\h] hate it no that's so sad
that i no i don't like that that's that
is the wrong
the wrong timeline that's the worst
timeline what the [\h__\h] no that's so sad
netanyahu
then
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you for the pinky now we are here
for university kiara
wait did i say kfp was uh destroyed or
something like that during the stream
uh
what happened what happened in 3000
years i forgot
we were shut down
cafe was closed
i saw two yeah sold off or something
like that
it's not that i forgot it's just because
it hasn't happened yet so
oh
maybe there is no oh tax fraud oh yeah
oh yeah that makes sense that makes a
lot of sense oh big sweet duncan 17.7
dancing
unless this is a joke but happy birthday
birthday
proud that granny doesn't have
her leg on the chair
you'll always be our boss boss we'll
still stick with you no matter how old
and wrinkly we all get in the future oh
[Music]
i am happy to hear that
let's get old together
thank you
we already are getting all together
gradually every day every second isn't
this beautiful
we're getting all together right now
it is true
it is very romantic
one second
thank you
warm spring comes every year but kibaba
is always more beautiful than the spring
however unfortunately today is april
fool's day
what are you trying to tell me that it
was a joke saying that kibaba is more
beautiful than the spring
you're not very clear there i'm gonna
assume that the one sentence doesn't
have anything to do with the other
sentence and you still are trying to
tell me
kibaba is more beautiful than spring
which i agree i thought kibaba looked
really cute
um i love kebab i love how she turned
out i didn't expect her to turn out so
good like i i
i
um
i commissioned
a great artist yes yes young dao very
great artist but
i
i don't i have never seen young dal draw
uh
like a
an old person before so it was kind of
like
i didn't know what to expect
i just hoped that
her style would translate well
to
an old person an old version of me
and it actually translated really well i
think it looks so cute and and and the
vibrant colors it made me look very cute
i think and still very much alive
yeah
i loved it um
worth it
cheese sauce thank you for the pinky we
will follow you forever ki baba boss
thank you for the cookies so yummy
you're welcome my dear i have many many
egg cookies
always for you my sweetest
uh
my swedish pumpkin
pumpkin bear
trying to come up with a cute name that
a grandma would give you
the king in ffff00
[Music]
i'm turning 40 this sunday can i get a
happy birthday and some more cookies and
milk pleases makes me feel like a young
kid again thank you
wait you
you're turning 40
in 3 000 years on the sunday or
or
now this last sunday um
happy belated birthday
happy birthday to you
even in 3 000 years to
40 years is
pretty dope
please don't have a midlife crisis
congratulations
yes
at least you're not
3040 years old
compared to that you're pretty young
[Music]
i mean
it is true
congratulations stay healthy and happy
make the best out of the 40s yeah
some people like madonna
are still putting out banger songs with
a banger body with 60 years so
i feel like
we need to
look like her when we're 60
let's aspire to be like madonna
when we're 60
[Music]
[Applause]
pray
yes we have to pray
[Music]
wasn't that a different song
and it feels like home wasn't that album
wrong song no what was that
[Music]
no that was that song
yeah oh was it i'm confusing some songs
in my brain again help me
help me
oh we're so slow-paced today man
uh
from the future i'm glad to see you
still pretty energetic after many years
i have so many questions to ask but i'll
see them by my own but pardon me i also
have a little personal question to ask
you could i fly like you in the future i
wish i could one day
yes
yes you can already do it now you just
have to get into a plane for example or
a helicopter or i don't know bungee
jumping bungee jumping
bungie jumping chimking bungee chimkin
you should do that sounds really cute a
bunch of jumping
mungy jumping chicken a jump king for
god's sake
bungee jump pink
chicken it's a tongue twister
how about we make a tongue twister uh
the bungee jump
jumping chicken is playing jump king
with a bunch of jumping
rope or so
the bunji dumb
i didn't i can't say it right without
stumbling over my words
the bungee jumping there you go kick
kick kicking
i can't again i'm so slow and i still
can the bounty dumping chicken
wants to play bungee jump no wants to
play jump king
while
on a bunch jumping rope or something
like that
[Laughter]
thank you for still supporting me in
three thousand years
crowd
end padaya than dougal jones
counting chickens
naked chicken
eggs
today i became a grown chicken and i'm
ready to take a post oh
because you have the name sea chicken
maybe i should be head of the navy and
take a charge of navy and war against
takodachis i was late because i was
putting up ramadan decorations bought
later oh did you watch it by now it was
a short one so it shouldn't have been
too difficult
so now you're the kfc chicken
that's cute
that's good
ah imagine chicken in sandwich uniform
in small boats on the ocean
looking at looking for like some
um
uh those those those binoculars or
something like that
and looking on a map looking for a
treasure oh cute very cute
oh very cute
very cute
no he's a sea chicken he's not tuna no
he's a sea chicken a chicken on the seat
yeah dakuma's probably done a sailor
chicken before
cotton thank you pinky
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
so much
how do you always manage to get the last
super chat how
we are done with those
um
did i
catch up or do i have more now than
i used to originally
did i catch up a little bit
can't jump or did i make your knees
i know i still have more
but i want to stop
[Laughter]
uh oh
was a lot i've read a decent amount
let me see
uh
we gained today
a bunch
but i read i read
oh i think i read more than i gained
today yeah
looking looking at the numbers so so why
did i i did catch up a little bit
oh
a little bit
[Laughter]
no i don't want you to change that
no
oh
yeah it's pretty late it's getting late
it's been seven and a half hours
uh i will read more uh after the drawing
stream
if that's okay
um
thank you
thank you everybody for being crazy
supportive thank you as always you sweet
potatoes i love you
thank you and everybody who can super
chat that's fine too thank you as well
for supporting me in other ways just
being here is a big support thank you
very much
and also
thank you so much for everybody who got
a duke of me ticket i'm really excited
to see you at dokomi
um
please make sure to plan
ahead everything properly
and be careful and enjoy and have fun
maybe get together with some other kf
people because there's gonna be a lot
over there we're gonna form an army of
kfp
and i'm gonna be so proud please wear
the merchandise so i think because
dokomi is so big there will be a lot of
people who also don't know me and don't
know me tubers so we have to assert
dominance and show them that real we are
the cool people we are the cool
peeps yeah the upcoming
um
trend no already we're already here but
yeah they need to understand they need
to understand
spread the word please yes
hey
[Music]
wow
hello
this is
uh
i need to cook but i don't wanna
i've made cut bolas two days in a row
thank you for the sticker thank you
i made credibility last night and the
the night before as well
with uh mashed potatoes
and linglenberry jam and it made me
realize
um because like every time i talk about
eating schnitzel with lingonberry jam uh
like americans and and also in in japan
also i think that it was hard to find
but
most in uh [\h__\h] bullets sorry in many
countries lincolnberry jam is not very
common so
it's hard to find but it made me realize
you can
anywhere in any country that has an ikea
you can easily get lingonberry jam in
ikea
it's maybe not the the best lingonberry
jam ever but it's a decent lingonberry
jam
so if you have troubles finding it uh
then you should just go to ikea
yeah
yeah yeah it's a good good idea i think
because they definitely sell it for
their chat boulez
yeah it might be a little bit more at 12
really 12 dollars no way
it was
normal normal price i think here
i didn't notice it being particularly
expensive
really
but also ikea offers
uh
online shipping as well now sometimes
not not for the food though you gotta
check maybe maybe they can send it
why not substitute this with crap
you cannot
you cannot just substitute
lingenberry jam for schnitzel
with cranberry sauce
now that is the most absurd thing ever
and every time i every time
every time people look at schnitzel
pictures and i'm like oh that looks like
cranberry let's eat it with creme no
no
that is not acceptable
and it's not exactly no it tastes
completely different i would never
eat it with cranberries
never
never ever ever ever bless for me
it's a food crime yes
don't do that just get that [\h__\h]
lingenberry jam i told you you will not
regret it it's so yummy with the
schnitzel
well ketchup is really bad too but that
was that's something a german would do
and germans don't quite understand
that you should eat yourself with
lingenberry jam but whatever at least
they don't use cranberries so
they're not even trying they're they're
not even trying okay
but the thing is like that that's like
their german schnitzel when if you go to
germany
and you're in a restaurant that um
uh
serves
austrian style schnitzel then they
actually do usually serve it with
lingberry gel as far as i know um unless
sometimes you have to ask for it maybe
um but they they normally like there's a
little bit of a difference between the
austrian schnitzel and german schnitzels
they just eat it differently yeah
anyway
you made me mad guys
i had such a great mood today and now
you [\h__\h] ruined my mood
just the idea of cranberry
[\h__\h] schnitzel is heresy
i don't know if you pronounce it like
that but my my day is ruined
what's that what's that meme phrase
my day is ruined
what's that called
how do you say that
what's that phrase
and my disappointment is imaginable and
my day is ruined i can never think of
these meme phrases i never remember the
bamboozle one either the one that i've
been quite possibly bamboozled i never
remember that one so i can never be
funny i always forget though and the
sand one as well like [\h__\h] sand gets
everywhere it's coarse and rough and
whatever the [\h__\h] i don't remember
i need to write them down and put it
like as as post-its on my
on my monitor
yeah
ah i'm just i'm just such a
disappointment all right everything what
a horrible day what a horrible day i'm
gonna leave now
thank you guys for watching
and in german we say
auf wiedersehen even though i know
you guys don't want to see me anymore
because i'm such a disappointment and
you guys are disappointing me too with
the thought of putting cranberries on
the schnitzel it's just absolutely
ridiculous i never want to talk to you
ever again no
no
i'm just kidding i can't leave you like
that i love you
okay okay
can we take a video
uh that's i'm going to take a video
upload on twitter say say
that
she'll be done
all of you say every dozen videos
wait why did i have to make these noises
another
i should have muted my microphone
i'll upload that on twitter
okay
bye bye see you
see you
in um day after tomorrow it feels like
i have barely streamed over the past few
days because i was on mummy's channel
yesterday
and then there was two days actually
there was three days nothing on my
channel because the unarchived one was
unarchived then monday was my day off
and then tuesday wasn't even on my
channel so it feels like really really
really quiet i'm sorry about that it was
kind of bad planning normally i like to
fill up the days more smartly but i was
like mommy woman we should maybe do it
on this on your channel this time
just because i feel like
i've been i've been having a lot of
collabs on my channel so
yeah yeah yeah wanna see part two
i don't think we'll do it like
immediately i also think luma is a
little bit busy if i understood
correctly um but maybe in like three
weeks or so we can do part two
yeah it was fun i enjoyed talking to
moomer a lot
after the stream
before she was just absolutely
overwhelmed with
literally every application
not acting the way it should act
yeah the camera
and obs and the game and youtube
everything was acting weird it was like
a curse it was really weird
yeah
is that what we're talking like for two
hours
maybe even two and a half
afterwards
it just went on and on and on and on and
on and on it felt really good
talking and talking
um normally normally i don't
um get to talk so much to
the girls after after collab because
like either really late or one of us is
busy has to do something
and so on
yeah
all right i'm gonna go now
bye bye bye
hey
watch out for the marshmallow
uh question thingies
tomorrow if i don't forget then
it should be there sometime tomorrow bye
bye
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
hmm