[Music]
um
whoa that was perfectly timed actually
hello everyone
hi hello welcome
everyone here to witness the battle yeah
it will be an epic mythical
showdown yeah some something like that
maybe
i think i think it'll be a little
anticlimactic though because i'm not
feeling so great
you're dead i should be scared of you
you you you own me
right i mean in reality yes but not in
video games necessarily
oh you own me in reality no no no when i
say oh
no it's not what you think it is okay
by the way is the audio fine like do you
hear
btm from the game and do you hear cali
and on the other side i guess do you
hear me
oh yeah good point hey kiara do we need
to censor the match id
no because it's already filled up oh i
see it can only be two people okay okay
yep
yay then i guess we're fine nice
i need to adjust you tiny bit okay do
what you gotta do
there we go okay so uh
first of all we obviously uh i mean it's
written here
but it says this stream is sponsored by
shadowberries again bacon thank you
shadowverse
freaking dope game
stream for both of us uh sponsored by
shadowverse thank you so much
what an honor it is it's a big honor
thank you so much
wonderful game really really wonderful
game i love it it's lots of fun
i'm quite hooked myself and actually i
even got my roommate hooked as well
yeah my roommate started playing
shadowverse
um she of course used the download url
in my description so guys if you didn't
download the game from the url if you're
gonna download it at all
yeah you can you can use either one
either one i'm just happy anyone can
play this game it's it's fun it's a good
time despite being not very good at it i
genuinely enjoy it
um well that is actually a good way
to uh lead into some talking points
because this game is
free to play not only on pc since we're
both playing it on pc but you can also
play it of course on your phone
free to play yeah that's right the big
ups to you guys hey shadowverse official
thank you for tuning in
yeah appreciate you letting us play game
super dope kelly
you want to say the next point oh yeah
yeah i just wanted to give give a shout
out to shadowverse what'd it do
um yeah let's see i also uh i just
mentioned this actually i freaking love
the artwork
there's uh super dope amazing anime
style artwork and fully voiced in
english and japanese
man yeah voices are
are you playing uh did you turn the
voices to japanese or english japanese
oh me too me too but i heard uh i heard
the english voices too
in on in the youtube video and they
really
uh sound really well as like well
done as well like they fit the
characters in english as well yeah
they're pretty good
so whatever floats your boat i guess
yeah exactly the whichever whichever one
which would yeah that's right sorry i
was
problem the other thing is which i mean
we talked about this before if you have
seen the other shadow for streams that
we did but
uh well this game it's a card game
obviously and it's very strategic
like you have like eight different
crafts that you can choose
from like eight different leaders uh
like for example i play with haven craft
which is like very it focuses on healing
me back up and all that and doing
countdowns and [\h__\h]
and callie has which one shadowcraft
wait no shadowcraft is
it's all about that necromancy man and
you use really like
like dark characters but then also in
the in
the gameplay you can summon lots of love
never mind i'm not going to tell you my
strategies
my anyway let me just when you should
never remember
i thought you meant uh neck romancy
what i misheard you
sorry my neck romans it's okay it's okay
it's okay no no worries chiari you're
all good
i'm just a romantic type of person you
know yeah i guess so i can see that i
can see that
so yeah what i wanted to say with that
yeah it's a very strategic game
with all kinds of classes that you can
choose from whichever you like the most
whichever fits you
your personality and i think we both
chose
uh personalities that suit each other
quite well
yeah i can see you being heavencraft i
don't know why i thought you'd choose
dragoncraft but i think havencraft suits
you best
it's pretty i like pretty things yeah
yeah that definitely fits you i would
say
and i like being on the safe side you
know being able to heal myself
up a lot makes me or like feel reassured
and safe
oh um next up
let's see i wanted to remind you guys
about the the dope event that's going on
for
three more days until may 2nd it might
actually be
for depending on where you live in the
world but until may 2nd they're still
doing the kaguyasama love is war tie-in
event
you got the characters from kaguyasama
love is war question mark
they appear in shadow verse for a
limited time
so let's see oh as leader cards you can
get chica kaguya and miyuki
and you can purchase them from the
in-game shop yeah and you get a special
daily log in bonus as well
so make sure that you log in get your
daily bonus play games
to receive an exclusive emblem sleeves
and more i i know that this sounds like
very like
like like i'm like i'm giving you away
like a prize or something like that or
like
get 50 off now click subscribe etc buy
my merch check out the
but i'm actually that excited i'm not
excited
yeah there's lots of free stuff yeah not
only the kaguya
um stuff campaign that's going on
but also you get a card pack
tickets between march
13th uh until
i'm not sure when on it but uh yeah
there's a
official release of the 21st card set
and tickets will be available to all
players who have cleared the tutorial
and played shadowverse during the above
a window
from the 30th 30th march
2 so it's until the 2nd of
may i think yeah with kiara you're
telling me
that there's free stuff there's all the
free stuff many card pack tickets you
get like
card packs for free lots of them lots of
them really epic ones here super epic
cards like me if you're lucky and gotcha
nice nice or maybe you just have mama
luck but you still have a fun time like
your boy
so so do it they're free
all you have to do is beat a tutorial
it's so easy yeah
yeah and then there's uh the three
temporary decks as well
you can get a whole deck uh i think was
for
like what one month or like how long can
you use that especially
i actually am using one for today's
match
oh a temporary deck
i did all the gotcha so i could probably
build it by
myself uh but i i you know
to save some time i chose one of the
temporary decks
for today okay
cool you made a deck well
on your own uh yeah so kind of technical
not technically uh i chose a quote
unquote
tournament winning deck but me and the
deadbeats had to really search for all
the required cards so
it was a long it was a long battle of
liquefying the cards that we didn't need
and um and sacrificing some of our souls
but we barely squeaked it out at the end
and we got we got the quote-unquote
tournament winning deck we'll see what
happens
by the way my deck is named staying
forever with kelly
oh why is that
there's a reason it's because they're
even is it because matches are never
going to end because you keep healing
yourself
yeah that is kind of like the the the
thing about
the deck that i chose is sanctuary haven
craft and like
it's based on like dragging out the game
a lot
but it might not really be dragged out
that much i might just
kill you before the 10th round so
okay gotcha i mean generally that's like
the
the what it is famous for i guess that
people told me that that's what it's
famous for it drags out
natural oh god no i really don't like
healing like bosses who heal a lot in
games
i don't like it it's like stay down get
down just die
please die that's when you kind of you
know like how when you
in in games you heal yourself a lot but
when the boss heals themselves you you
get mad but
well yeah we are doing the same things i
don't heal myself a lot of games
always
are we ready for the first match i think
we said everything important
i guess so yeah well i guess we'll just
see what happens
i really don't know what's going to
happen but well chat we will um not be
looking at you guys anymore during the
match but you guys should still hype it
up and be active in the chat
we might watch the archive and if you
guys were too quiet i'm gonna kick your
butt
yeah yeah yeah by the way both kiara and
i are streaming this
so if you want to see the inner workings
for both of us
you can go look at kia's stream and my
stream in two different tabs
yes exactly my
link for cali is in my description
and then the other way around my link
for my stream is in her description
yeah so check it out and uh cheer for us
and um
as yeah we can't read the chat because
otherwise that we could someone might
say just one thing that
alerts us to what the other is going to
do so for that reason we won't look but
yeah you're right kiara i want to go
watch the archive afterward and see what
you guys were saying
um while we were fighting so keep being
hype about it
in the chat do it anyway i'm ready to go
all right okay yeah yeah
let's do it ready the battle of the gods
let's start yeah something like that
huh no more npc fights finally battling
against you
i know right oh man
the skeletons really suit you i know
they're like my dead beats
[Music]
i kind of thought you were even gonna
choose like shadowcraft or bloodcraft
but yeah your bloodcraft's pretty cool
too but i'm not quite the vampire type
so
hmm uh yeah black crab looks like
vampires huh yeah
let's see where i i switched i switched
something out
i'm not gonna switch mine i'm happy with
what i have
a good luck callie thanks good luck to
you my dude i
have high hopes for you but we'll see
what happens
let me read i need to do some reading
again because i forget everything that i
read about instantly
i practiced a lot too and read my cards
a lot but still i've
i need to recheck because there's just
so much text every now and then oh yeah
i feel ya
here let me just move myself a little
bit let me scoot a little bit to the
side for my dead beats
so you guys can see kind of all the
cards i have in my hand there you go
okay so let's see what can i do here do
you see what i'm doing with the ground
or is it only on my side
i think it's only on your side with the
ground
i was i was playing around if you tap on
the ground it goes like boom boom oh the
grass
that's pretty cool
watch both streams deadbeats and kfp
employees yeah
it's about to get hot watch them both
okay um alternate insight
i want to use this i don't know if
you've
noticed but i'm not using the the basic
havencraft leader i actually purchased
on my gotcha stream i purchased a
different leader
and switched them out so that's one
thing you can do there's like
uh eight like eight basic leaders but
you can switch them out with others
yeah i like eat
mm-hmm my mine is by the way from
grandpa fantasy my leader
oh yeah i was gonna say very cute very
cute
i just like my skeletons too much so i
really want to change my leader but very
adorable
i i noticed that that was a grand blue
fantasy looking
like you've seen it in the sound oh i
know this i know this character
yeah she's also from gramble fest yeah i
was gonna say wow so
cute
[Music]
oh yeah
did you choose like cute girls deck
no no no no i made i have this uh
pre-built bat
deck and i just learned to play with it
it does have a few cute kills in it
okay what else are you always seeing
girls right now really
powerful guys okay cool
nice some of some healing boys
i see i see okay um
i like this this little rascal is
scouting fanatic
oh yeah i don't need any of these what
is this last one it's necromancer
someone's skeleton okay
uh hold on hold on uh let's see
helpful um
i really ought to just go ahead and use
something
god i freaking love my skeletons
um you're just going to go ahead and i'm
going to do something else real quick
okay take your time immediately just
kill my daddy
i was going to say that too same oh yes
oh lucky okay okay okay
i'm a bad poker fan they have a bad
poker face
which one do you oh no
okay now that my holy sanctuary is out i
just want to let you know that that is
the card that pretty much like
shapes my deck oh yeah and it will never
leave my side ever that's my amulet
i guess i gotta figure out how to get
rid of it
[Music]
okay next smoke's turn i'll play that
so
[Music]
oh wait i still have oh
oh that's a cool looking dude okay all
good oh good
oh i wait i have one more huh god damn
[Music]
all right
i like the pgm here too it's so epic
hang on i want to move
for our showdown yes indeed i actually
want to move you real quick hold on
i need you to be in the top right corner
because there's text i want to show
people about my cards
and uh you're in the way
i'm kidding it's not your fault it's not
your fault
here we go yes touch me move me whatever
don't you want me to be stop
oh my god all right and i'll still move
the chat real quick
by the way guys we'll play um as many
matches as possible
in two hours yeah so i doubt that it'll
be that many just because
if you were gonna drag out these matches
i don't know man i don't know
it doesn't have to be dragged out it
won't depends on you as well
ooh she's hot i know right beautiful
reminds me of ollie
do you want to damage your random enemy
[Music]
followers
that's nothing
i ended it super early but i couldn't
think of anything good
oh you like him huh oh no you haven't
seen who i'm talking about yet
ah some new clyde i see icing
this is the homie right here i freaking
love this homie anyway
oh that's close those eye characters are
just the best listen
you got a lot of kitty cats i feel i
know she has kids
here's the grudge teller this dude
doesn't he have cat ears too
yeah maybe
skeletons and kitty cats that's your
dick
yeah that's right oh he opened his eyes
he opened his eyes yeah
sorry i love when the closed eye
characters open their eyes
oh my god okay i'm just like
[Music]
actually wait no wait that's not no no
that's not what i want to do
wait wait what the [\h__\h] it didn't bring
him back god damn it
it brought back a different one damaged
my dude like kill him and then bring him
back at full health but that's not what
it did so
oh well um i learned i learned a lesson
that's a unicorn
that's one of the things that my deck
does it comes down and then gives me
something like
a special oh okay
like a magical wish
if i do that then
[Music]
um
more scary skeletons yeah that's right
[Music]
okay it's time to heat myself back up
another necromancer he doesn't really
look like a necromancer okay
the gold mine necromancer
neck road
wow i'm a spooky fish okay you got no
more both points left and i got free
hmm maybe i should just start using my
little points
yeah go for it all right all right
all right are you i am
bro nothing like a fine red wine and
shadow verse in the evening
yes yes yes okay i go
oh that's cute more unicorns
wow you got a lot of wishes my dog
i got only ambulance on the field now
cannot attack you but but
wait for it am i really so
dang out of cards okay i mean
oh yeah you are oh wow i kind of wish i
knew how to draw them
whatever um i don't want to use
unicorn army
i wish i knew how to draw some cards
well you draw one per
turn unless you have some card that
makes you draw
i see i see that makes sense i don't
really want to use this just yet so i'm
going to not use it
uh can i use you my dog is he already on
your turn all right well
oh whale all right i got a lot of wishes
out there
[Music]
and a lot of cards
hmm yeah i've noticed that when i was
practicing with this deck
i have like i have like a
a look luxury with my cards and i always
have like too many good cards on my
hands
wow i actually like sometimes like don't
even know
uh what to do with them anyway i'm
healing
hp a moment ago and now i'm back at 16.
wow yeah
i guess i better use this one
i really don't need to evolve to be
honest probably some people in the chat
are probably roasting me by now for
doing this oh whatever whatever
all that matters is they were having fun
man yes
i feel like i'm doing fine
probably so some things to improve oh
[\h__\h]
no what am i done
i made a big mistake i made a huge
mistake
like like enormous mistakes damage to me
that is something
nobody was a really really big mistake i
made a huge mistake
i didn't know it was gonna do that you
piece of [\h__\h] you dumb freaking
graveyard eyeball
it's fine i might as well reap what i
[\h__\h] say so i deserve
that that's perfect that is perfect
banish that bastard
you don't like it i have no cars
all that matters is you have fun cali
thanks shadow first i did
i did look up for a minute to see your
message
all right well i am having a good time i
will say
i could have evolved them then they
probably might not even be dead by now
my dog
[Music]
okay yeah
oh wow that one's really cool that card
if i don't play it by the 10th turn it
gets automatic
automatically played at the 10th turn
just by being in my deck i don't even
need it in my hand
wow yeah nice anyway
there i go so much for so much for
lasting forever with kelly
i i didn't even need to tell by the doll
yeah i guess not huh nice first match
well-played
[Music]
i shall adjust the score me too let's
see
whoa
thanks guys okay let me take a tiny look
at the chat hello hello hello hello
hello that was interesting
clap clap face got a lot
they say yeah i mean i could i could
tell that much immediately
but you you you got a
good deck as well no you got it from
like some like a co
coat uh deck like a deck code and then
you
like re build that one mm-hmm
yeah well i feel pretty confident about
this next this next match because i made
about two
huge mistakes like game alteringly bad
mistakes but i learned my lesson
so i feel i feel good yeah sometimes it
got me pretty low i was sweating a
little bit when you got me down to nine
or eight hp
so it's not impossible if you play your
cards well i'm sure you have a chance as
well
yeah yeah should we get into the next
match
yeah let's do it let's go i'm
ready
who is she
okay we're in the forest oh we're i'm in
a castle
oh oh you see a different screen
interesting
[Music]
that's why you saw the grass
indeed
[Music]
you really want to be with me huh huh
some kind that i switched out i got the
same card again
nice okay
it's card gathering time
did i actually not evolve a single
card last match i really didn't
uh well yeah end it
i love this ghost very classy ghost
his voice sounded funny he sounds like
really really excited
yeah like you put some kind of like
interesting audio effect like
[Music]
wobble with it yeah
wow the effects on your card when you
evolve them
it's pretty nice yeah i'd say so
it got a lot of stuff going on yep
indeed okay cool i like this
[Music]
yay [\h__\h] again yeah
it's ollie except in a different
different life
i like how she like spawns with like a
rose
i love roses
[Music]
mmm
oh
i need my amulets better get them next
turn
well with this one i could get
[Music]
i know they're perfect for me
okay that's just a scratch yeah
definitely
[Music]
where is where
is there we go nope that's also not it
okay
[Music]
oh my gosh you're very healthy
when you get all those hp for me and uh
but but no problem no need to worry
i'll be fine i'm a phoenix i will rise
why did you [\h__\h] up i confused the
attack and defense i thought
they were switched so i thought that she
had no health too
because because the shield is red but
red is always attacked to me
yeah you know ah was that what you meant
why you confused this
yeah exactly same thing
oh she's she's so cute i know right i
love the little horn so i can't get this
high
oh see
[Music]
kelly would you describe your own eyes
as pink or red
um oh that's a good question red
oh okay like really pinkish red when i
was like
creating you in sims 4 in my stream
now i would have said it's like a dark
duck pink but
others said it's red and i'm like okay
well if you say red then i guess it is
red or fishy yeah maybe i mean i feel
like they're red personally i feel like
they match my um
my pendant and my pendant is red
at least i think so ouch thank you
skullfish
that's the homie right there
okay chill cali chill ah
ghost rider what to do
another smell fish yep i like the skull
fish
ah can i do i have something to banish
[Music]
this bgm gives me search like middle i
guess you're hearing a different one
right now because you're on a different
map but
the music generally gives me like
middle-aged medieval vibes
and i love it because it reminds me of
the times when i went to
medieval festivals with my mom and my
brother
oh yeah we used to go to a lot of them
oh that actually sounds like a really
fun time like a really fun family event
where the [\h__\h] is my sanctuary what the
[\h__\h]
you still have so many cards i'll give
you i'll give you some
i'll give you some hp back i'll give
that to you there you go
oh in change i balanced your
dude the difference between vanishing
and killing your dudes normally
is that when i banish them they cannot
affect
their uh let their um like
last wish uh come to effect
oh i see i see so it doesn't hurt you
i see it anyway i'm gonna play that
and
[Music]
please give me what i'm looking for oh
my gosh
what the [\h__\h] okay okay okay
sure whatever i love it
actually this this match is a little bit
yeah bye because i'm i'm
for once not getting the car that i'm
looking for
and you are uh
we're doing quite well yee okay
i'm getting a bit stressed out
why there's no reason
there's no reason to be stressed ah
okay okay and i need to use my both ones
what the [\h__\h]
i don't need you what the hell okay okay
okay well
um okay no
no don't worry kelly don't worry oh wow
so what do i have
[Music]
we only have two left
ah there we go okay there we go
no more worries now i see
[Music]
i was waiting for that by the way dear
chad i'm not looking at you but it just
wants you to know i was
waiting for that that's a shame
let's see
i really can't do anything huh okay
oh what was that again
anyway finally my sanctuary is here oh
wow
and bye
uh this i'm i heal you with that card
but you were already at
maximum hp so i don't care i see i see
okay four points left you can play
can't play him so i would say play you
[Music]
and restore free hp for me kill someone
from your side because whenever i heal
myself my holy sanctuary does something
special
and i get no i guess we can do that one
too
okay i'll cook and there we go i hear
myself again so my holy sanctuary
summons a tiger
wow that's a dope looking tire yeah
let's see cute tiger [\h__\h] i can't just
fly evolving again what the [\h__\h]
so stupid
oh damn it i probably could have done
something whatever it doesn't matter
i have no cards dude well in the end
kelly we're both still beginners so we
both make
lots of mistakes yeah but i'm like extra
beginner
yeah i don't know how to get more cards
i wish i had more cards
i have no cards
maybe it's because i keep playing all of
them i probably should try and play less
cards
it no i don't think so whatever you can
play and what is smart to play
yeah but i have like none
but i have no followers to use it i
think i only have amulets now
okay yeah i also i have like
lots of amulets on my field so it's like
i can't i barely can play like actual
like
cards that make damage but that's okay
yeah i see you know when in a switcharoo
no i'm a
almost max hp and urination
and i was practicing against an npc i
had uh
them like like summon all those ghosts
as well i was like what
how do you do that
did you just call your deadbeats and
they came yeah that's usually how it
goes
nice oh this thing got rid of the
unicorn oh wow
oh wow i like this one too that's the
end
that's the end baby not yet because i
can't attack you with him yet
um not until the next turn so
what could we do why do i have something
oh there we go oh there we go
dang you're pretty good kiara yeah i
practiced a little bit but the deck
really is just way too strong my deck is
like insane
yeah it is quite good maybe i'll try
playing with a different one i don't
know
i don't know you have one ready right
now yeah i have another one
i mean i have your i have yours as well
your temporary deck but i don't want to
use
that same one um that's you
um this one's not very different but
i'll still try it anyway
okay i'll stay with the same one because
that's the only one i really have
okay next match let's go thanks guys
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you oh thanks
so oh you're still on shadow crowd but
you changed your deck
i really want to try to make it work if
i can
oh yes i just gotta think real hard
hello hello
i don't need this one yet
okay that's fine
you know what i'm gonna run with what i
get i'm gonna run with it
let's see what happens
[Music]
okay oh i'm happy about that let's go
unicorn unicorn unicorn
[Music]
pretty pretty unicorns
again
[Music]
is the deck you're using now a temporary
one uh no it's only a little bit
different than the other one
i think i used a debt code to get it
oh i actually don't know what fanfare is
so i'm looking it up right now if i
understand correctly
it is that you hear when the card is
played from there freaking something
whatever you know what i'm not gonna i'm
not even i'm not gonna split from the
hand
okay i see what was it if you just play
the card like
by playing the card it triggers it okay
that's what i thought like the fun fair
that i have right now it's like
it didn't happen so i'm like i'm
wondering maybe if i
messed up somehow maybe i have to wait
several turns i don't know
i love the the bone fanatic's voice
it's funny
yes cute um
and i'll hold on to these for now
you know um the other day when we played
um
[Music]
the clubhouse games you won a lot yeah
so
i'm glad i'm finally winning something
too yeah
card games are not my specialty though i
do enjoy them
do i want to play huh i guess yeah
because no
[Music]
i don't have any of those
so we're doing
nah we can't we can play here i think
i'll think i'll play her
whoa cool i literally hurt everyone on
the field just now even myself
wow but that's okay
[Music]
okay bye bye john it was nice seeing you
didn't she have last words
was that only
[Music]
oh it's still my turn i see okay i wish
i would have
i wish i would have felt this confident
in school during
math tests yeah
[Laughter]
i feel that numbers aren't my strong
suit either
yeah thank you this is the very number
heavy game
didn't even have to think about that
move
okay the amulets really never go away
huh
what doesn't go away um my my unicorn
ambulance is a countdown amoled it goes
away after four
turns oh i see and then activates itself
oh
and my holy sanctuary doesn't go away uh
at all yeah
okay
[Music]
see you really do get me quite low on hp
every now and then yeah that's a really
strong
card yeah you kind of you kind of need
to
like prepare something like think think
i guess a few turns
in the future and then maybe you could
get me down maybe yeah i don't know what
your deck has
yeah that's that's the thing do you have
some secret weapon
i don't know
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i wanted to evolve that's why i
clicked the wrong
damn it and that was a mistake
i know i can't attack but i want it to
evolve anyway
[Music]
oh hi ghosts yeah hello oh
it's again yeah but they all only have
one attack
yup but they're already
huh with all those clothes huh yeah okay
okay callie
you're making me sweat again
[Music]
bye bye ghosts bye bye bye bye bye bye
that's unfortunate i guess i didn't have
a enough room for my bike
oh well okay so
[Music]
horsey go hoisting now we got one more
left so i guess we do that
oh now we're about the same hp oh it's
getting close here
indeed close battle
um
again the bike guy you have a lot of
those
yup oh what is that car that looks so
pretty what the [\h__\h]
yeah i really like this one oh
he got like someone with an apple
who is he yeah why can't he
why can't they do what i want to do
what is his last words
[Music]
oh that sucks oh
i don't know why i couldn't evolve but
okay
[Music]
ah yeah yes
kelly i'm sorry
why why would you be sad
[Music]
do you feel better with that back than
the previous one um
i think it's exactly the same
[Music]
well let's see i guess i'll just go back
to my tournament winning deck
[Music]
okay sounds good to me
yeah i'll probably just like keep trying
until i at least get one win out of it
because
i'm sure that i can get it you can do it
you can do it believe in yourself
yeah hey take as much time as you need
to read the cards i know it's super
confusing
okay yeah i feel like a lot of times i
just don't understand what they do
yeah um
like very similar cards and a lot of
like dupes as well
oh yeah so maybe that's a bit easier
oh um oh well that's actually a good
starting
hand i'll go with that no changes
this is the fourth match let's go
again i like this dude
meet my unicorn altar and pray to it
okay pay it respect
i thought we should actually wait to use
too early i think let's go with that
[Music]
what were his last words again ah some
in a skeleton oh yes i'm in a dead feet
hey dead beat's lurking now dead beats
look at that
oh wait i'm so so my turn oh yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
don't leave me you always die so early
i mean health is pretty low i mean the
defense is pretty low
[Music]
um
no
okay i'm feeling healthier now
there we go
[Music]
oh is that did it get oh yeah that's
right thank you
i did i'm sorry my brain just doesn't
have a lot of room for anything else so
yeah for a lot of other things
thank you
oh yeah and did you did you hear suicide
senpai trying to learn the song
yeah yeah yeah i heard it was great
really amazing
i'm sorry yeah if you'd like there's a
lot of fast rap but
if you'd like to give it an attempt yeah
learning was already
so difficult yes a tough one
i'm gonna try a different
it's a wolf time
oh you got the yo your favorite boy
again i know
this is definitely my favorite he looks
like
so sweet so nice his smile is so kind
definitely a good a good dude but it
could also be like a kind of expression
that's like
i'm i'm gonna i look nice but i'm gonna
kill you
yeah yeah that's how i mean that's
typically how it goes with with closed
eye boys
that's why i like them so much
[Music]
okay i would say we need another one of
those
and then always have more give me my
freaking sanctuary please
dude dude
[Music]
oh
whoa there's a party on your side a
ghost party unicorn
yeah i'll get more
wow wow that part looks still
i got it okay i got what i wanted
can you calm down my ghost dude i was
just reading about you
turn six where the [\h__\h]
which cards make me there we go
something like that
oh wait maybe i should oops
[Music]
no problem no need to worry
don't really be happy
i've had that song today in my ear the
whole day
[Music]
yeah i know it's like my deadbeats just
like my deadbeats
he dreams about a better future yeah
a better life yeah
but now he's got to go
where's my bike there it is oh you got
my eel back thank you
oh oh [\h__\h] i'm down to ten what did you
do kelly
i was just at 20 hp
[Music]
let me drink some hydration time yeah
me too wine oh
nice
oh it's still my turn i didn't realize
that oh yeah
i'm drinking some kind of disgusting
low-key disgusting
uh i see that is also somewhat good oh
yeah
what there we go okay you
you really have to punch me one more
time before ending that turn huh
yeah i mean it wasn't me it was my
followers that wanted to do it so
playing blame the deadpool okay there
you go
that's a really powerful one yeah it
does
uh free damage to all enemy followers
and
restores freedom defense to myself and
makes me draw a card wow that is really
really powerful
yeah i i like
i like healing myself up i like to keep
that card for whenever you have too much
on the field
yep okay
so now the field is clean again swoop
swoop sweet sweet
yeah i'm here i'm your maid kelly i'll
clean up all those skeletons
in your closet oh
okay if that's what you want to do
i'm not gonna involve you
oh that's a cool looking bike
[Music]
where is where is my freakings
it's just not coming but okay okay
[Music]
um
ah thank you time thinking time
[Music]
eight points eight points
i don't know
but oh wait six
five oh my god yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
now we want each is really powerful
yeah it uh um for stories as much hp
as the card that i banish
has a defense so your card has six
defense so it
restored six uh hp for me oh
wow you see it haven't craft really
annoying
[Music]
okay okay okay chill the game was
already like stressing me out to end my
[Music]
turn
again i like seeing her on the field
yeah she's cool
a little bit of an eye candy yeah i like
her but i really like your leader
luna is so cute she's also already
yeah is that a mouse or a bunny i think
it's a mouse i'm not sure
reaping some souls
oh the unicorn wish came true let's see
[Music]
that is very painful but i feel like
like doing it anyway there we go
oh wow that was painful for me too but
whatever okay
i i i wanted to play it a bit risky
okay
another beautiful she actually looks
actually she looks a bit like you yeah
hang on one second
[Music]
i'll wait forever
hold on a minute uh
hold on a second
uh
the next next turn is 10 turn
0.9 turn
i see i see
what does that do select two shutter
craft levels in your hand keep the first
follow up
way too fast it goes away so fast
oh my god that's way too much text
that's way too much no wonder
no wonder there's like some confusion
i know ah my brain is on fire right now
yep come on
there we go you took some time there to
your [\h__\h] sanctuary why why did you
take so much time
dear lord it was kind of tough without
you
okay okay well
uh i'll wait oh yeah
[Music]
hmm
oh god what are their last words what
are your last words
oh yeah we're both at 6 3 all
cali oh kelly i'm just gonna play it i
have no choice
but now you give me another one of those
huh why can't i
no i never should have evolved anything
god
i should have saved it the whole dang
time yeah that's why i keep on saving it
but i save it for too long i still have
free evil points
oh my gosh uh hold on a second i'm not
sure what's the right thing to do
keep them for special characters or use
them early
i don't know i'm just going to use it
oh yeah he evolves himself doesn't he
yeah oh
damn it if that [\h__\h] thing wasn't uh
that word was enough god damn it
yes oh you were so close oh wait could
have that could that have killed me if i
didn't have a word out at the end of
return destroy six other running phones
even if the enemy
has 70 pence or more do you oh my god oh
my god oh my god
until the difference i don't know it's
not a lot of text
[Laughter]
uh
[Music]
um
okay first of all healing myself back up
and finally getting that defense going
and still four
[Music]
i'll get you out there and then
thank you okay we can evo uh
heal a bit more and just
for fun evolving you
into a pretty plain dagger
wow yeah
okay i can't attack you though yeah when
you evolve you can attack in the first
turn but
only other enemy followers as far as i
understand it not the enemy leader
did my homework yeah
i tried i can tell
i've been really busy toodle because i'm
moving on the weekends
oh that's right yeah you mentioned yeah
and i didn't i didn't even really start
packing but i painted
like my walls in my new apartment oh
that's cool
yeah maybe you can one day visit me
one day sure if you will have me
always
it was it was pretty good callie yeah
you were
are you at that you were you had this
one point where you were
really about to kill me yeah i got
pretty close huh
pretty close maybe maybe next one
i want to try you're gonna use the same
one yeah i want to try it
then we go on to the fifth match
yeah i need to change the score again
let's see thank you chad thank you
thank you yeah it was close at one point
we were both like at six hp that was
really
really scary oh thank you what a great
starting hand
okay
now this looks good
actually one reason i think why it was
so close
last time is because i didn't get my
freaking holy sanctuary
until the end of the game ah yeah that's
a good point once you get that it's all
over
yeah it heals me a lot so you were able
to get me down a lot
um
drank some tea oh it's uh still your
turn oops
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh yeah okay oh wait you're
playing this
yeah playing the same day you're playing
the same deck
okay okay but i know my deck very well
so
yeah this is funny
yeah well you've been you've been
telling me quite a bit about the decks
i'm curious about it
oh okay maybe i shouldn't have told you
so much
oh oh how the how the turntables doesn't
it
i should play you attack uh you would
die
yeah i like my deck i'll keep it
i know what i'm doing yeah
but this is getting interesting
sanctuary haven against sanctuary heaven
[Music]
those unicorns are freaking powerful i
tell you what
um jelly you know what because we're
both playing sanctuary haven now
this might be um like you remember our
super long
uno match yeah that dragged
itself out for 40 minutes yeah
we might be dragging this match out for
40 minutes
yup i look forward to it i anticipate it
yay well now finally the title of my
deck comes
to truth because it says staying with
kelly forever
so yeah
[Music]
but i still feel like i might end up
playing it a bit different than you
um well you definitely would need uh
some kind of warm-up with the deck to
understand the cards
yeah that's true they also have lots of
texts
they all do
okay depending on what you have on your
hand you can literally just
copy every movement yeah
uh you're done
um and let's see
oh yeah i guess so
[Music]
okay i'm really curious about this fight
wow that's cool okay that's an easy one
to do
oh cool i don't really need to do that
let's see i don't need to be
so healthy right now i don't
yeah sometimes sometimes um
even when you're full hp you might still
want to use the card because it has some
other side effect that you want to use
yeah i guess that's true but i'd rather
kind of hold on to it i guess
[Music]
hmm
wow lots of unicorns out here popping
off yeah
yeah it's a freaking tiny unicorn
[Music]
there are like four unicorns up i don't
know why i'm evolving now but
yeah that was kind of late should have
done it at the beginning
whatever need to love more
at least it stays alive maybe maybe
or it keeps me a lot longer
[Music]
or whatever you wear
oh cool
hold on
[Music]
i kind of want that though
i don't want to use this one yet so ah
well you know
[Music]
oh hi hi set yeah i like that one
okay what am i gonna do with that can i
forget
oh my short term memory i tell you what
i know that did something else but i
kind of forgot
[Music]
okay let me heal myself back up
attack you a little bit um
whatever more unicorns unicorns
yeah bye bye
[Music]
y'all
might actually be a good time to use
this
i'm still standing my tiger is still
standing good job holy flame tiger good
job
stay strong tiger
[Music]
okay turn six
yeah you can't move right from the
beginning uh i think after the four
appeal
it lets you start evolving
[Music]
okay good morning mariah
okay oh
this really looks like it's gonna take a
long long
long time oh you got your sanctuary
i do
oh man
[Music]
i think it's
um nadi hodo
okay so what do we do what do we do i
say we banish him
wow that is really op got a lot of
health though that's nice
yeah you're welcome
yeah zero class so let's do it
and four points left
give it that one or we got another one
of those
or actually you know hey i have that one
too oh
but i'm gonna go with that one do at
least a little bit of damage
get the tiger eat steam
eye of the tiger
oh kelly by the way yeah are you
planning on repairing my stairs in
minecraft
oh yeah you got you betcha you betcha
i'll do that
definitely will do that maybe if you
have some
if you ever have some leads you know
because uh some of my llamas
pockets were unleashed as well for some
reason
i have i have no idea they were just
like that listen they were just like
no no they were all leashed but it's the
good thing is that
alpacas usually stay together um even if
they're unleashed
yeah oh well yeah there's a
there's a kind of a safety hazard at kfp
right now
yeah i can tell my people can't go to
work because they all fall into the hole
because chickens are not very smart
so they go up the stairs and then they
just drop into the hole
uh that's really unfortunate i'm quite
sorry to hear that
are you able to retrieve the chickens
from the hole
no they'll die
that's unfortunate yeah
[Music]
i'm quite sorry
okay well i can't attack you right now
unfortunately
i'll keep the last wolf
uh okay wow
wow what is this fight yeah
yeah i'm starting to kind of feel that
too oh wow
battling each and all of the same deck
is
[Music]
just like triggering something all right
when i chose this deck on my stream
everyone was like oh my god
cancer cancer oh really why
yeah because it triggers so hard that it
drags out the game but having two
of the same deck and against each other
is even more
cancer yeah it's pretty is pretty
intense
i should have maybe um prepared one more
dick i thought i thought one was enough
and one more deck would have been fun i
guess to
play around a bit more
maybe if there's next time or for the
tournament who knows maybe i'll get
another deck or
i wonder if you're only allowed to use
one deck in a tournament
oh yeah i think that's a good question
i'm not sure
hmm
also i wonder who our opponents will be
just random people
oh yeah i wonder too well i mean i doubt
they'll be random people i bet that
they'll be people who are very
experienced at the game
[Music]
probably need to have a long talk with
the coach beforehand
i really actually learned the deck
before i get in there
[Music]
get rid of them at least and then
okay i got nine nine points nine points
we play another one
there's just so much about this holy
sanctuary
so much to read well yeah
[Music]
get me that holy water thanks lorena
thank you
okay now now i can finally do some
damage to you
i don't know should i really end the
turn okay okay okay
[Music]
that's the one i told you about that you
don't even need any points for
to play yeah pretty strong
that's right
can i play nerdy too that's so that's so
weird to me
yeah but the thing is it's not stackable
oh then what the [\h__\h] then it's just
like annoying it's just like sitting
there i think
wait i think it's not stoppable so i
don't really maybe it is i don't
maybe it is you know what maybe it is i
don't know
[Music]
i guess it is stackable maybe ah i
always wondered why why i would play
like two holy centuries but i've seen
other people do it
we had to destroy each other now
oh well there's no more salvation on the
field at all that's sad
okay okay
that was pretty crazy
well you damaged yourself too yep
so all right what do we do
um i don't know should i play one of
those as well
i still feel like i have so few cars
[Music]
now there we go okay a little bit of a
heel
and there we go tiger
[Music]
i don't want to keep that card but
can do that one
[Music]
oh yeah let's play this turn oh
eight more points left i guess we'll
play you
and yeah that that's that's it
that's it evolve
for even more power
okay okay okay
here we go now i have two wives
can you get through that wall cali um
i don't know it's required i can break
it
last night one second i need to read
something real quick
yep take your time
[Music]
oh wait actually yeah oh yeah oh yeah
oh oh oh oh oh
okay guys i guess
what happens when you have two sanctuary
i i guess so
um
[Music]
she's healing herself again
okay um i guess that's all i can do
my wall okay this game can be played by
two people
i can see that
it's not over it is not over
play it smart keanu
[Music]
i don't know all those choices seemed
really good
god damn it
down to one what happened whoa i have no
clue dude i think that was um my fun
fault
[Music]
you got six points back again
things are getting really intense
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
well not much i can do now okay
okay well at least i'm back to full
health and i got two tigers
okay we didn't waste it
that was my sanctuary thing okay
wow that was difficult dang
it was like fighting myself
wow do you want to play that again with
the same deck
sure okay
okay that might be the last one how long
did this one take spent like
half an hour but i think it was maybe a
bit less
um i mean it was definitely longer than
the first
three yeah before
yeah all right sanctuary haven versus
sanctuary haven
guys this this this might be the the
last one maybe
yeah probably so who's there i mean now
that kelly
understands the deck quite a bit more i
mean a little bit
what what do you think will happen for
the last one guys
um clap crop thanks guys good game well
played
good job oh oh thank you
thank that holy sanctuary card seems
naughty i don't know what that means but
it
is it is very oh they mean they mean
that it seems ridiculously powerful
um yeah it's what the whole deck is
built around
since then since i mean the name the
name is sanctuary haven
and the card is called haven sanctuary
wait was that it
yeah oh am i mixing things up
[Music]
yeah ra is also super strong and
salvador dal
there's a lot of super strong cards in
this deck
and i guess this will be maybe the last
one let's go kelly
yeah let's go go go go go go
oh cool
[Music]
haven craft versus haven craft second
match
i go second you'll go fast
maybe one
okay i like something different okay
chad bye bye again bye bye
see you in a little bit again
long
put this one down
okay you're starting out with cutie pie
eo yeah very cute
she's so cute i love a twin tail twin
tails are so cute i want
twin tails too
ah hi you bye
oh wow we have the same one yeah
are you really surprised no i'm not it
kind of started out like this in the in
in the other match too both of us were
like oh yeah eo
unicorn
[Music]
repeat the history repeats itself
let me think i don't want to use this
one
i think i might use this one
okay
three points um so much choice
ah yes we can
ah well there we go
like that yeah yeah yeah i'm looking for
something
uh-huh okay i forgot to attack
what the [\h__\h] oh no
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay okay she got the sanctuary out yeah
oh wow you're still alive what the hell
[Music]
okay
sounds good to me
[Music]
i got a word huh okay bye bye eel
oh i feel so sorry for her she's
enjoying being on here and i keep on
like destroying herself yeah we had
about three of
three of her yeah
oh first time you see her evolved okay
okay well that
is your turn me lady okay
how are you already putting the second
one out yeah
you really want to win this one huh i
mean i would like to
hmm i would i want you to win one as
well
but i'm not don't throw the match please
because i won't like it if you throw the
match
please don't oh yeah you won't throw the
it's fine
cat hair in my nose
i don't think i got him last time i
actually barely have experience with him
because i got him so rarely okay
[Music]
i think i know what i'm doing
okay
um oh yeah he's the one that gives you
five maximum defense extra and restores
them
what a good guy
yeah okay let's see um
[Music]
maybe i would
yes we'll try and work on this
[Music]
all right
[\h__\h] should kill him
where is my freaking haven
sanctuary where is it
no need for it
ah ah
okay okay okay
now there we go that's what i like to
[Applause]
see
one second please i'm just surviving to
the music
i want to learn how to do like like one
of those medieval
dances that you see in medieval movies
and game game of
uh chairs yeah
but i can't even dance the waltz can you
dance the waltz callie
can i dance at waltz yeah yeah i mean
i i guess i mean
am i what
what what okay the waltz
you can dance the what okay i learned it
a long time ago but
if we meet again i'll test it out i mean
i learned it a very long
a very long time ago uh if we ever have
a 3d
like a collaboration in 3d bodies let's
dance together but i really want to
dance
it's very simple it's one two three one
two three
yeah but my brain can't i can't wrap my
brain around it i just can't
yeah i mean i mean i guess it's hard for
for some
people like like it's hard for me to
wrap my head around
card games everyone's got what they're
good at
i've been having this issue i'll get
not getting my my sanctuary so you might
win this round
oh i see yeah [\h__\h]
um
let's see i should have used that damn
it
oh well
don't worry this this deck is oh i just
freaking realized
uh okay hold on a second hold on
let's just get this one out there
[Music]
ah i was running out of time it's fine
it doesn't matter
oh damn it
waiting for you long enough there we go
don't really need the heel but okay
yeah i do need the heel
kind of hope this unicorn goes away soon
i want more room
does it does it do what i think it does
yes it does yeah yeah yeah i fully
understand my deck now
i'm happy okay
that was the last effect right
[Music]
okay i'm happy
i'm happy
i know you killed him so fast kelly
he deserved a better life than that yeah
let's see my fluffy companions
[Music]
doesn't matter
okay um
oh
oh wait do i want that one maybe instead
yes yes yes yes
uh-huh
and then try that
now we got some tigers going and
now we want that
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay now i have a word too
now yeah
and i can't attack right okay let's go
let's go kelly let's see
[Music]
to get that stupid unicorn down
i should probably wait on this wait no
all right i'm gonna do it
[Music]
uh
okay
uh oh yeah i guess you can't i can't
evolve that one whoopsie doodle
uh you're wrecking your brain over there
hold on hold on um
i'm just gonna no i don't want another
unicorns are good yeah don't
underestimate their power
i know
oh well
[\h__\h] firelight
[Music]
okay
and one more let's get myself back up to
25 hp
yeah that's what i like to see yeah yeah
double double ward yeah okay okay i
can't i can't
i can turn this around mm-hmm
lots of brain trying to
get get the last pieces of my brain
puzzled together i don't even know what
i'm saying
okay um
concentration
oh let's see
nine
all right here we go
what you gonna do what you gonna do when
kiara comes for you
yay
let's see and do that next time
oh i guess i can't go up to 25. that's
very silly oh well
it doesn't matter oh well
i got some tigers
[Music]
oh
fancy seeing you here huh
oh no nobody
who can who can play the most
ah
now the thing that i understand is if i
do this
does this does this disappear see i
cannot look at the chat so i will never
know the answer
i'll just
but do i really want no
but i mean that doesn't yeah
i want to win this
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
chill chill game okay okay
i'll just hope i'll just help
oh
but now i'm definitely oh
yeah that's okay
[Music]
oh what else can i do i only got one
[\h__\h] card left
okay
[Music]
me too no thank you funny kelly no i
don't
see it
i wonder i will destroy you anyway i
will destroy you
the power of unicorns uh yeah
yep um let's see
uh now i'm done okay
oh my [\h__\h] god there's three
sanctuaries
it's a lot of sanctuary yeah
that is nuts well then i don't even need
that one
uh
i mean sure okay give me that pine
oh but this one doesn't
okay oh my oh my god um
well not much i can do
even though i got some points left but
but i'll i'll let
destiny play this one out okay
may the one with the most rng luck quinn
yeah rng's
[Music]
um
it just looks so ridiculous yeah it does
look pretty crazy
you have a lot of sanctuaries yeah
well it's just not
in the end it doesn't matter i think
but i'll go with him
oh my god oh my god
whoa a lot of automatic things happen
yeah i don't even know what's happening
right now to be honest i have literally
no clue what's going on
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
uh
let's end this no i want to heal
[Music]
this is strong horsey
oh god wait who's gonna win this
i have no idea oh
gosh
[Music]
okay oh my god let's what
ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay okay i feel a bit more protected
but okay
um yup yup i know it now this
really it's it's just like like
if oh god i think yeah
i might die because of wrath
only oh yeah
next turn when you end your turn
ross i think going to kill me
oh really yeah this is like
with the automatic damage now wherever
that happens yeah
okay i won a game
i was i won a game yeah
i won a game i won one game
congratulations yay
i got a game one game yeah
that's all i needed just one
i'm glad you got one
wow celebratory drink
i hope that was not too painful for the
audience i hope you guys had fun
watching that
wow i learned a lot i feel like i
actually learned a lot more about your
deck than
than about the deck that i chose
yeah yeah well
yeah maybe you can
like make an even better shadowcraft
deck
for next time yeah i'll be better for
next time for sure yeah if you practice
with it
and understand your own deck maybe
you'll be fine yeah
i think so i just need to learn how to
do it more but i feel like that play
style is a little more
like suited to me i don't know maybe
i'll try some of the other crafts
the one that you had the haven craft
yeah and you should fry other crafts not
not
only like go for a shadow craft because
it has skeletons and stuff maybe others
have like better effects and play styles
for you yeah
yeah not only the visuals yeah
[Music]
well um so everyone that has
been our little showdown and the
showdown champion
i won five and you won one and
we will both participate i think both
uh in the tournament sometime soon we
will both get actual coaches for that
until now we just
learn it on our own but next time we
will have like experienced coaches who
teach
us how to do things so that you guys
don't have to facepalm
that the whole stream anymore i kind of
like making them facepalm though it's
kind of fun
not gonna last there's some there's
something fun about it i don't know
everyone who thinks they can do it
better download the game from our
description
yep you better download it and prove to
us the obvious truth
yeah also it's it's free so as we said
it's free don't please download it play
it on your own it's a lot of fun
and lots of free stuff you can get and
maybe
if you're lucky you can play against us
someday i don't know how the tournament
really works maybe that's already
decided to participate but maybe someday
i mean
i'm going to be practicing against
randa's uh just to prepare
for the tournament because i won't lose
this time
i won't lose i'm gonna study my cards
well and i'm gonna need to play against
some random other players so
maybe the defeats can do that i don't
know we won't battle against each other
unless we both get to the very last
fight
yeah so i guess we i guess we better get
to the very last fight
yes well any anything you got to say
um hmm nope i had a great time though
that was fun
i was i was super focused but that's
just how i get when i play games like
this i actually really was having a
great time
oh yeah yeah you were very focused yeah
but that's that's what happens to me
when i do like
anything that is like i guess this kind
of game
i suppose i feel like i'm obligated to
focus because if i don't then it'll just
be it'll be a nightmare
if i don't really try to because you
guys know my attention span is is that
of a goldfish
um so yeah but i had a good time
i'm glad me too i'm really really hooked
on the game i want to play more i'm
looking forward to the tournament
and i hope all of you enjoyed today's
stream thank you shadow verse for
sponsoring it yes thank you
verse that was a great time i had a ball
also a personal advertisement please
watch heart challenger and my most
recent uh song cover
in bokudano asiyato which reached 100k
today yes did you see it yet if you
didn't watch it yet
it's an acoustic cover please check it
out thank you
and that's it for today for me i'll see
you guys tomorrow
yeah that's it for me too i have a
members only stream tomorrow so for
those of you that are tier three
see you there and um we're going to be
doing tabletop rpg stuff so look forward
to that
um yeah with that being said i guess i'm
pretty much done
um what am i gonna read i think i'm
gonna read super chats from this
stream at the end of my asmr drawing
stream because you guys seem to like the
asmr
super chats so i will read them at that
time
look forward to it yay softly spoken
super chat writing
indeed yeah it do kind of sound like
that
so look forward to it
[Music]
thank you shadowverse bye-bye everyone
um
[Music]
you