[Music]
be
oh my god
[Music]
hello kitty
thing let me see something
[Music]
how are you everyone
i am today playing uh
something for you called yakuza
like a dragon before i do that i want to
try something
because i just noticed
oh wait oh i should probably change the
language through english
uh wait i hope i do that here
audio
[Music]
now english is fun the audio is english
but the subtitles
why do i change the subtitles
uh audio is apparently
sorry wait wait a second wait a second
one second please
can i ask a question how do i um do that
thing again
where i wait a second
uh
[Music]
how do i give uh uh streamlabs a
priority again
does someone know
i now have to go to the task manager
don't tell me to press alt f4
i know that's not the way to do it
uh right click yeah
[Music]
wait that's not exactly it uh
ah there we go
here one second one second now give this
the highest priority
possible please say it works yeah that
should work okay i think i did it
does that work better i wonder
oh no um
why does it lag so much
we're gonna figure it out but i had uh i
feel like i've
fixed those before
i did it on the task manager oh dear one
second will
for every uh minute that we're not
playing the game we'll extend the stream
don't worry about it
oh by the way is it only my life to be
lagging or is it
once i switch to the game window
is it only me lagging or is it the game
too
i think it's the game too
oh
no we're not playing it in german we're
not gonna play it in german
uh
sorry one second let me write to my mess
the manager
no no no no no no no yakuza in german
wouldn't that be weird
although i think there's uh is there
even a german voiceover i don't think so
we're playing in english today
uh because this stream is sponsored by
sega thank you so
so so much and i'm really honored
to get this opportunity
thank you so much i'm looking forward to
this very much
uh kelly already kelly already played it
what manager says should be better when
the game starts oh
i wonder uh
so yakuza like a dragon came out in
english
today today i hope
everyone already got the game i heard
some people already started playing it
and can't get
can't get their uh hands off of it
well let me wait a second
the language change refrigerator
changing line is from the
title screen so before starting a new
game or continuing with an existing
tile was i not in the title screen
let's go back
sorry german is so natural to me that i
did not really notice
uh do i have to go back
um
we don't want it oops we don't want it
to be in german
ah yep
oops step on but
one second let me end this for one
second
they say i have to go to the title
screen
i'm so sorry once again we'll fix it
what title screen
[Music]
the first way to change the language is
from the title screen so before starting
a new game
or continuing system you will have to
access settings audio language option
where you can choose between english and
java oh yeah it's only english though
after selecting the language of your
preference you will have to confirm that
you understand
you'll return to the time screen that
you may lose data if you
but it is in english
it did say english the audio is english
one moment no problem
no problem
german isn't an object maybe that's a
steam thing
yakuza in german that sounds very
interesting
probably the steam language
because audio language
english
okay i'll try to change it in steam
sorry one more fixing let me try to
change my steam language
to english uh
[Music]
where do i do that quick
uh game properties in steam
oh yeah i found it found it found it
okay change it to english
[Music]
english yakuza here we go
now the subtitles should be english as
well
supposedly
sorry if under the way oh sega
let's see if it lags again too but
apparently when i start the game it
should not
be lagging anymore please don't lag on
me
still fine now real yeah cause i use the
gamepad
oh yeah it's english
yay oh it starts lagging again
one second let's maybe also
[Music]
go down to medium oh
why did it go small why is it smaller
now
i know why
sorry that's a little bit uh
a little bit uh fixing to do
no it's not not is that the right window
size
okay
yeah maybe it's just the main menu
by the way i'm playing with uh xbox
controller
so let's get into it whoa
[Music]
thank you they gave me a little gift oh
see it stopped
no it stopped lagging
v-sync off what's v-sync does that
something
does it have something to do with the
lagging
is that does it have something to do
with the lagging
i don't think i can turn it off now okay
sorry
ah i waited for this day
i know you can't have forgotten my face
do not pretend otherwise iamon was the
name of the courtier you murdered in
suriga
that man was my father wait what's
happening you don't mean
[Music]
one last time let me we started doing
the turn the vsync off
let me turn the v-sync off maybe that
fixes it
god dammit was that too loud by the way
[Music]
stream technical difficulties
oh yeah i'm starting from the beginning
not from chapter five yeah i know cali
started from chapter five
because uh the demo that we received
started there but i got permission to
start from the beginning
i thought it would be maybe a little bit
better also since it seems some people
don't want to get spoilered
don't worry i got you i got you
oops what am i moving here
was that here v-sync oh yeah what is
v-sync
it was fine by the way uh when i played
it before
i tried i tested it out a little bit
oh wait ah
keeps changing my window size
stop changing my window size
that didn't really do it huh
oops no no no keep it on medium
low fps okay
confirm yes please
oh i think oh they fixed it
i think i think it fixed it
yep are we ready now
is it fixed
yay fix fix fix fixed okay okay
never mind everything sorry and thank
you for waiting
we are getting into yakuza like a dragon
here we go all the same feature very
good i always forget saving
legendary first aid kit thank you
i know this is the the eighth game of
the series
and this is my first time playing a
yakuza game very first time
i've always heard of it
but i never played it before should i
make my face smaller
am i covering up too much space
on the seventh wasn't there like zero
how long have i waited one for this two
three four five six seven isn't it eight
i know
you can't have forgotten my face do not
pretend
otherwise eoman was the name of the
courtier you murdered in suriga
that man was my father you don't mean
you're that girl from before i'm not
that girl anymore
i am a vagrant on a quest for vengeance
do you know how many times i've awoken
in the night
having dreams of drawing this make it
bigger
i like this music i think that's shamish
and shamisen music
turn the audio up okay sorry i have to
get up
i'll get out of the window for that
audio
okay it should be
louder now tell me if you still want it
to be louder
still too loud
you actually believe i would ever let
myself be cut down by a mere
it's good i will teach you okay
for i am none other than the fearsome
genji the slasher
the legend nice makeover
both of them look very pretty
[Music]
genji the slasher is none other than i
oh i like this traditional japanese
music
did you see that
father
[Applause]
we're still lagging a little bit huh
still lagging right
only sometimes
[Applause]
bravo brother beautiful that was really
nice acting
game volume still too low really
should i still turn it up
lag fatty volume is okay
really i'll turn it up a tiny bit more
a tiny bit just
just a tiny tiny bit
okie dokie
continuing
or taking of that makeup
you don't need makeup to be beautiful
did you finish cutting that confetti
they cut it themselves no
not yet then what are you sitting around
do you think we're live in the morning
look at you you got the audience to its
feet and suddenly you think you're a
star
this kind of money is nothing is that
your money go to your head
maybe it's just a cutscene you
ungrateful little brat
don't you look at me but there's a lot
of cutscenes so
turn down the texture quality oh as soon
as i treat your mother
get the possibility to change something
i will
hire to make the next cut even deeper
and this time
not even your makeup will hide it yoko
stop it
scary don't you dare try to order me
around toshio
who do you think keeps this whole damn
show running
you is it you
well now she's happy again shall we go
to moto machi tonight
mota mati are you sure i think i've been
there before
maybe who cares the game is by the way
not lagging on my screen
it's only lagging in obs
on my screen everything is smooth
that's a nice necklace yeah
are you okay masami
oh that scarf
don't worry about the confusion how did
that happen
let me give you a hand i should have oh
i put obs in high priority already
i may never be an award-winning actor
but i've always been a masterful
confetti cutter every actor needs a
backup plan
masterful confetti cute what do you say
we hit the town tonight
see the sights of yokohama just the two
of us yokohama's really nice come on
i must say okay and it was a boy
oh
so that's what yakuza do when they're
not doing yakuza stuff
acting
using game capture not window capture
so masami did you say goodbye to all
your friends stop lagging
i don't have any friends he's praying
what's the point
schools every month come on don't be
like that
you know when i was your age my parents
wouldn't even let me go to school
oh why
what's wrong about going to school oh
well what's that why don't we treat
ourselves today
hell yeah how about picking them
and the skin comes out so crispy and
delicious you'll
love it i wonder have i ever eaten
picking ducks expensive
don't you worry about that
won't break the bank
so we're going for food um
i think the fps is fine again
i'm playing on a pc but with an xbox
controller
the best way to play it picking that
tastes like
chicken
could be could be well that's loading
long
fry dog come on
oh that looks delicious
oh and a nice private room
masumi you're going to get full if you
keep eating those you know
remember these appetizers i mean
the main course has yet to take the
stage oh
yeah i know i'm going to the bathroom
before the star
gets here the pika
that's a lot of starters though many
appetizers
oh is that the picking duck
oh he's looking forward to it couldn't
you have gone to toilet before
eating the food
oh toilet private privacy please privacy
privacy i like some privacy please
um i've never been in the mail toilet
before i didn't want to see that
[Laughter]
oh it's gone the gun is gone
is he is he dead dad
no
no no
yeah right in the head
is youtube gonna ban me for this
is this okay to show on youtube
damn oh so that was a flashback
to his childhood
youtube don't ban me please oh he looks
good as a
adult as well
nice room nice office oh
two thousand almost 2000. here we are
the last day of the 20th century
masumi arakawa patriarch of the arakawa
family atojika
all i can think about is what i want for
life
wait what's with this hand why is he
wearing a club
to do collections is it a fake hand
joe captain of the arakawa family
on new year's eve you if there's money
on the streets and there's work to be
done
yakuza don't get holidays in kamurocho
can't be good idea everyday
kfb
oh he's thinking very deeply about lunch
very deeply
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
what chase down the [\h__\h]
okay i'm on it i'm the purple guy
oh let's see if we can get him i'm gonna
get you
don't run away from me come on wait wait
wait wait
what sorry i pressed x not y
i want it don't run away stop running
away
which i'm coming for you
let me catch you come on come on where
are you going come on i got some picking
duck for you
where did you go oh [\h__\h] where did he go
oh i lost him oh god damn it
it's loading
[Laughter]
that was a bad hand i'm not a good
yakuza
it's loading it's loading
looks like i shook him off no
here i am [\h__\h]
lucio pal i know you're not an idiot
why did you think you'd get away what is
that
there's nothing illegal about selling
animal [\h__\h] videos
what believe me it's educational oh i
believe you
the problem is you were calling it
uncensored porn
and selling it to dumb horny kids come
on
remember all the good times we had in
middle school and let's be real
it's not like this is hurting the
yakuza's bottom line
[Music]
kids these days are entitled man they'll
come bitching the arkawa family about
porn scammers on our turf
we can't have that kind of [\h__\h] stating
our good name
so come on wait so yakuza illegal porn
hmm
hey did you forget who you're dealing
with no
of course not just some yakuza's street
trash who's gotta learn when to quit
oh [\h__\h] are we fighting now who are you
fighting
are we going to fight now i heard this
is a turn base
uh fight system
and me choosing commands during valley
will select which actions to take
using the command menu in the bottom
left
wait corner on the screen select the
attack to command to attack with weapon
with the weapon on hand give that a shot
okie dokie got you
attack again before a fallen enemy gets
back up a regular attack
will change into a powerful opportune
strike opportunity strikes will just
dish out the pain so take every chance
you can get
all right i got you attack attack before
you get up come up
oh no now
the red card at the bottom right is your
energy or hp
if cast oh should i move my my face to a
different side of the screen
maybe that uh because you don't see my
what do you mean pc dying isn't it fine
now
yeah i'm gonna eat the onigiri one
second maybe i should move my face to
bottom when i'm left
yes
i guess i guess this is where i gotta go
this is just where i have to be there's
this is for for reasons uh
for streaming uh per streaming purpose
no other reason okay what
uh each you see one how do i why is it
uh
items someone oh
to defend himself until his next turn
this will decrease the damage you take
and protect against both bleeding and
stun
if you know the enemy's next attack will
be a powerful one it might be best to
put your guard up just a thought
okay why does it sometimes show the
keyboard uh
uh options what the hell guard for free
ah i have to hold it
do i still have to hold it here we
that's it for the tutorial oh that's it
that's easy
time to teach usio a lesson aren't there
more um soft and gentle ways to teach
someone a lesson
oh and one last thing if there's ever
anything like a bicycle or a street sign
near an enemy a normal attack will
change into a weapon attack leading one
to use
the nearby object to unleash some
serious hurt all right
uh attack i guess attack good bounce
damn get this take these boys
okay they're broke probably not attack
again
got no time for guiding and he
is defeated
wow we have 500 yen that's nothing
that's nothing sukun
okay we did a level up rank up
nice song victory
we smashed him to the ground oh [\h__\h] you
okay
ichiban kasuga
i am ichiban anakin yeah
you okay yes
oh hell yeah check this out man
that's like nothing
that's that's not go that's not 500 yen
that's uh
50 000 yen with crazy business schemes
back in the day
well some of them must have worked the
cash you got there might hit our quota
today all by itself
what are you talking about we're gonna
give this all back to those kids oh uh
nice through all the work we did to get
it man he's gonna give it back yeah dude
hold up you want me to track down every
single kid this guy
shafted for real yes for real what part
of this is hard to understand
oh
nothing that's very nice of him i didn't
know yakuza were so nice
[\h__\h] yeah look at this real quick
how bad is it
knuckles yeah you've got a good sized
lump there dude
no you idiot i mean my hair i just got
it done
you're worried about your hair
[Music]
they're like me and kelly
[Laughter]
oh i was cute so they're pretty nice
they seem pretty nice they seem like
nice people
his hair looked good indeed yeah yeah
but he shouldn't be worried about his
hair maybe
oh the screen is actually um a little
bit
uh maybe should be a bit more up here
you okay bro
you're always getting pummeled there i
think you like it
no you're calling me a masochist
hell yeah you always let him get some
punches in
even when you could wipe the floor with
him i know how you fight hard when you
wanna
all the music is cool
pretty massive i don't like his
hairstyle though
unless you're training to become a pro
wrestler or something
okay fine you should get a different
hairstyle
i don't like that hairstyle
a hero sure i pretend i'm a hero when i
fight so what
it's time to throw down my brain just
starts thinking in dragon quest terms
dragon questions dan with the dragon
quest what's so great about it
everything birds you see that the the
sign in the back
if even one guy gets a lucky hit and
it's all over for you
you realize that dude how many times has
captain sawashiro told you that i
can't die over something as stupid as
collections that's when it's all over
[Music]
i like this life with our kawasana the
captain
and even your ass that's not gonna do
anything to ruin that
the truth is you never wanna be at rock
bottom again
i don't ever wanna be bottom left again
i feel you
so rock bottom he looks cute though he
has a cute face
his eyes are so cute
wouldn't be the man i am today without
it a cool guy
full of the bravery those games showed
me and what they didn't
our kawasan did that's where you get all
this hero
crap huh maybe i should give this gamer
[\h__\h] a chance
oh try and try i can recommend you some
games first let's give that money back
to the kids who got scammed yeah
well right
give it back to them oh
well time to give those kids some
refunds
thanks hit me up at the sig shop when
you're done
got you bro
recommend mario hey
yo eating old man takeo how the heck are
you
good good hey did you know mama michio
is looking
mama she wanted you to swing by who is
my mommy too you need with me
no clue i'm just the messenger
okay what's she gotten herself into now
we're looking for mamma michio
where's she duty calls
dory calls oh
oh i can walk around the city now
oh i think it shows me on the map the
pink
arrow shows me where i have to go i
guess can i not run
oh i can oh
[Music]
he's handsome good looking guy
i probably wouldn't try to get close to
him sorry
social distancing police here social
distancing
probably wouldn't want to get uh where
is it is it here
wouldn't want to get too close if i saw
him in real life
kinda what was that
hello why why are you on the way move
get out of the way is this where i go
oh loading magic cat
syntax error nice names these guys have
hey there
ichi you kept me waiting
mama have a drink with me will ya
it's new year's eve
wait please don't tell me you were just
looking for a drinking buddy
what you were the only guy i knew who
wouldn't have
anywhere else to be on mama
you're serious i'm out here busting my
ass making collections
oh wow look at you so big and important
at least i'm not drunk hey
i've been drinking since before you were
a twinkle in your
dad's eye and look at me now
still gorgeous oh yeah baby
are you okay we drank a little bit too
much i think
help oh i can choose well let's help her
out let's help
nice lady out there keep telling
yourself that
we want to be a nice guy
is she okay she needs to drink some
water
i don't i i actually never was oh
kindness
i was never drunk before can you believe
it i'm sorry honey
so i don't know what helps appreciate it
i don't know what happens in such a
situation casual guys personality
cuz someone's may improve depending on
his oh that's cool
these traits represent castle as a
person and refining them will earn him
a slew of perks and bonuses such as
unlocking new features or characters to
talk to
oh but do i want to strive to be nice or
is it like can the game
be successful too if i don't if i'm not
nice i wonder but i'm gonna try to be
nice
the following are the six traits of
kasuga's personality passion
confidence charisma kindness intellect
and style
i would say i personally me kiara
i am top notch in all of those
personality traits
try out all different kinds of
activities to make uh casaga the very
best magic oh we want to strive for that
okay no problem i like that
i thought this game would be it was
gonna be really brutal and scary but we
want him to be nice
okay you're back i'm back
why'd you do me like that michio was
just drunk off her ass
you're surprised i haven't seen her
sober in 20 years
her in this town are just going to hell
pick
there's some trouble at shangri-la right
now oh
what happened i don't know the details
but you know how soap lands are wait i
don't know what our show plans maybe a
customer got up at it with one of the
girls
you gotta go check is it what i think it
is
wait are we going to the soap lands can
i take a bath there
is it like uh what is that
okay we don't want to go there right now
i think i don't know
can i take a bath
i feel like i'm kind of stinky after all
these fights
because in in japan they have lots of
public public baths maybe that's what
we're going for hello is this where i go
where i'm going
sol pulando perfect timing we've got a
huge problem
what's wrong the toilet's all clogged up
and we can't find a plunger anywhere
oh a plunger sounds about right that's
thing you use when there's [\h__\h] stuck in
the pipes
are not your handyman excuse me
i suppose it wasn't me who cleaned you
up every time you [\h__\h] yourself
he's about cleaning okay
until fifth grade one time and my
stomach was killing me that day wait
this game is funny
i thought this was a scary game
i like it guess i should get the damn
plunger wait where's the butt
i like how the game tells me where to go
i obviously i i wouldn't be able to
find the way myself so thanks for
helping me out there
let's get a plunger you know we we can't
get
or we can't go out of business oh wait i
can't go there oh what's up
what's up there i have to go from the
other side
okay i already reached the point i guess
it's loading it's this this game
probably runs better on someone with a
better pc
and by the way i am getting a better pc
so before you tell me to get a better pc
i'm doing that
you got to pay your taxes hooligan boss
what does dex new year's eve tax buddy
i mean six and beer have a luxury tax on
them don't they
so good times on new year's cost a
little extra too
why would i pay that to you then
just get out your goddamn wallet
that's the lamest [\h__\h] i've ever heard
yo get out of here you little punks
who they like you i was just cruising by
it's new years can't just let people
chill tonight
sorry but we opened for pieces on the
holidays
so if you want to mess with all pieces
we just have to bust up yours
ooh pretty scary but lowlifes like you
give kamarucho a bad name and i'm not
about
to stand for that
good of you [\h__\h] irs [\h__\h] you let's
kill this guy
i don't think so let's do it
the woman in the background so next goes
to unleash your special attacks these
are
three types of skills
i'm glad you like my voice acting attack
recovery and support on-screen prompts
may appear during attack skills which
offer opportunities to deal extra damage
by pressing x
repeatedly or wait what what what which
other
on-screen prompts may appear during
attack skills which offer opportunities
to deal extra damage by pressing x
really impressing why at the right time
or is this a rhythm game skill skills
cost mental points to activate and your
current
mp can be seen as a green gloss at the
bottom right keep an eye on it okay i'll
try
so what am i using a skill right away
tenacious fist
here we go real fast
excuse me knife that's not fair i'm
battling you with fists
leave me the [\h__\h] alone
press b in time with the enemies attack
to perform a perfect guide and decrease
damage taken you can perform a perfect
guard at any time
castle is standing okay much like the so
this must be with a good timing or so i
wonder
much like the guard command a perfect
guard will also defend against the
bleeding and suddenly
some status effects to strive for
perfection always always striving for
perfection
okay uh wait a second let me get you one
more time
i was too late but he's dead oh
no no oh wait how do i do that no
no oh did i do it right i don't know
get him get him ichiban
yo oh wait do i have to press it more
than one time
one more time come on
maybe more times
damn good job
i have to spam it okie dokie
damn it you dead next time i see you
the innocent poor guy
hi why is he speaking
japanese i thought this was english
voiceover
no sweat buddy but for real kamurochos
more dangerous than usual on new years
everyone's drunk and waving the cash
around it's easy pickings out here
tonight
so be careful okay hi hi hi
i will thank you very much
i guess i better get that damn plunger
from the lady at the cigarette shop
oh yes i should uh read his text with my
own voice i think
okay let's get the plunger now that we
got those [\h__\h]
out of the way we shall find the plunger
whoa chill bro it's loading again
oh toilet plunger it looks like she
doesn't have that
i don't think she has that i mean her
own maybe
if you have one could you run into
shangri-la
just buy one for them they raised you
for crying out loud
a man your age should be sending money
to his family anyway
oh really i can afford that i'm barely
scraping by as is
i thought you were making lots of money
you need to leave that sorry arakawa
family
and join a family with some real push
kid
sure you'd be their gopher for a while
but that'd still be better than how
you're living now
right you're an idiot i swore an
oath to arakawa son and i never
abandoned him
aren't you an obedient little dog hey
i heard something real cute about what
is it what is it you're babysitting
arakawa's kid
ichi the nanny excuse me hey look the
young master is the same age as me
he's not a kid young master
what is this the 18th century besides
i'm not
damn she's not scared of the yakuza huh
he's been in a wheelchair since he was a
toddler you know
she's not scared so he needs a big
strong yakuza at his side
every time he wants some fresh air
surprise surprise hey
i don't know how to say that in english
don't um
don't lick me old woman that's not
that's a dire translation but how do i
say that
back to the licking hello
did you give those high schools i got
his name yep
never seen kids happier to see a yakuza
before
it all worked out see they ain't so bad
dude there's no reason to be happy about
it if we don't score big on our next job
the captain's going to kill us
i know that what is our next job anyway
it's a shakedown
shake what's the shakedown mark borrowed
500k from a loan shark and hasn't paid
sharks and apparently he's immune to
yakuza threats
oh what we thought how can you be immune
to that
well let's go man the dignity of the
arkawa family is riding on us
let's go i hope that's not true
hey by the way captain samushiro said to
pull out all the stops to get this money
back
so we might have to rough them up all
right so where is this clown now
i hear he hangs out public park three a
lot
i'll go on ahead and scope it out meet
me over there okay
all righty i'll see you soon i don't
know why i'm not directly following you
but
time to head to public park free okay
what's a shakedown this is like is it
like uh just like killing everyone
wait map doesn't show me where to go
shark excuse me is it the pink
game gaming thing down there
is it here
can i go in here please
give me i can play
wait is this is this public park free
is this where i was supposed to go
virtual fighter 5 final showdown
virtual fighter that
hello am i supposed to am i supposed to
go here
ah my head is blocking the map god damn
it i'm always blocking something huh
ah now i see the now i see the arrow
oh why is everyone in my way this is why
i don't like crowded places
they're all in my way yo bro hello
oh hanukki hi guy here
sure is look over there oh
he looks innocent let's leave him alone
the loading sorry that's my my bad pc
that dude huh
do you know him forget it let's go
hey there here at sukkasan enjoying a
little break are we
having a smoke while you're moot your
ass still owes a ton of money
mood your ass i'm learning a lot of
great swear words from this game
thank you that other family went easy on
you but we won't
the arakawa family doesn't [\h__\h] around
cool
if you don't want to get hurt get out
your wallet
pay a [\h__\h] pay pay time okay
you think i won't do it he's not saying
anything i can't pay back
that's all there is to it he's so
maybe we should not pick a fight with
him ah don't you remember pal
we used to wrestle when we were kids you
thought it was so
cool to powerbomb other kids as long as
you were the only one big enough to do
it
oh i remember you're soapy ichi
and if this guy's your pal sophie that
must mean
you ended up in the yakuza shocked are
you jealous
i heard you joining me are you jealous
willing to flunk out and come crawling
back here
life's a [\h__\h] huh now who's doing
better you are me
with it somewhere else no can do pal
we gotta deal with it right here cause
we're yakuza
see yakuza orders are mandatory and my
orders are to get your wallet
i guess there's no choice yeah because
he's just gonna give it to you like that
i don't have any money
come on great son let's make this easy
great all you need is your wallet
i don't want to get rough with you you
understand are you not scared of him
he's much bigger than you
you saying that even a grown-up don't
pick fights with people who are
bob power bomb i'm saying i don't want
to see the strongest guy in middle
school
tap out be a shame if that was your pee
i'm scared sounds like sophie ichi needs
to taste the dirt again soapy eat
it so bad wait what does that even mean
tag match any key okay you be the
referee
i want him all to myself uh 101
okay brave jabbering and let's do this
come on
he's huge
he's huge i'm scared we can do it
oh what ex damn
that hammer you don't need a hammer what
the [\h__\h]
tenacious fizz here we go
i don't know how to do it like during
the fight at least
one more time do i have other attacks i
wonder
he's almost dead let's get him no no
no oh i did it i did it okay i think i
get it
and it just has to be the right timing
one more time oh
i'm losing mp
maybe i shouldn't always use the skills
huh
hammer down i feel the stats going on
that was
easier than i thought
pick a bench oh how was i supposed to do
that
okay
we're still pretty but we gotta check if
ichi's hair
is all right check his hair strong
enough
say goodbye to your wallet bye bye
please
beat me up if that's what your boss
wants but don't take it i thought you
don't have money
oh did you say you don't have money to
give me here
he did have the cash [\h__\h] low life
and no intention of paying it back
he needs it for something else probably
what are you doing
audigy why just getting all the junk out
of his wallet first man
huh looks more like money to me
all right great son like i said i only
wanted your wallet
oh huh oh
okay okay let's go why is he so nice
why is he so nice what's up with you
why did you take them off yeah why
eritsuga won't screw us
he'll pay it off we just give him time
okay figure that
then why did you just beat him up
destruction on new year's eve just for
fun
didn't you notice what he was smoking it
was just a nub
man he obviously just picked it up off
the ground
why'd he do that if he had so much cash
because it's new years
he probably wanted to buy his mom a nice
meal uh
you know that doesn't mean it's okay to
be late on his payments
look you know that old candy shop just
past showa street
uh yeah it closed last year right
what about it hiratsuka's mom ran that
shop
really she closed it because she got
sick
real sick i went to see her in the
hospital
and she was thin as a rail but even so
she was happy
because her son was back in kamurocho
taking care of her
why is he so wholesome money hirotsuka
borrowed was
it was all for hospital bills what a
chad
oh what dude
if we go back empty-handed captain said
what shiro's gonna kill him how about we
kill him not going back
empty-handed we were asked to snatch the
dude's wallet
and look that's exactly what we snatched
but there's nothing inside
no that's not what the captain meant
[Music]
the office don't stress me man great
except right now you should be with the
young master
oh yeah sorry i'll be there as fast as i
can
what good is that he still has to wait
for you
why are you always slow
just move your ass and don't take him
anywhere dumb or dangerous
if anything happens to him under your
watch i'd have to kill you a thousand
times
yes i know that sir
i like how he completely changes the
young master when he talks to him
damn it i can't believe i forgot me too
take this now he's scared now he is
scared oh no
i'm not going to be the one to hand this
out oh no it will be we will be you just
let me know when the young master looks
bye-bye
uh i'll kill time until then well did we
give it to him or not
apparently not man let me um is is the
audio really low i saw one comment
saying why is the audio so low
but no one else is saying it is it all
right i hope it's all right
it better be all right
very interesting so is
is every yakuza game like this that the
the main character is just super
nice audio is low
okay why are you telling me that now
why are you telling me that i turned it
up
hello
where do we go are we going to pick up
that sun
or that small i don't know who are we
picking up
sorry sorry sorry
simon you're in the way
hello i'm here do i have to take a taxi
taxi please get in
i need to get the young message
apartment complex uh-huh
oh
this is so funny
i heard that other yakuza games played
for example in shinjuku
hey i think kabukicho where's the young
i'm very sorry but i haven't seen him
today sir
i've been to kabukicho many times but
it's kind of scary there
so i'm glad it's in yokohama i don't
really know that area that well
oh he's not he's a full-grown man i just
expected a child oh yeah i'm late young
man
young master came up while i was doing
this he's an old master
anything else you want to know he's a
hot master
not exactly my taste but
sorry sorry
i like how ichiban i think he's like
just so
like how do you call that suddenly he's
like um
like a little little mouse
did you forget what day it is
birthday right you didn't come without a
gift did you
oh no i brought something it's just i
didn't have much so it's
no is he gonna give her the wallet
whatever
as long as you didn't tell dad about
this you did it
did you of course not
if he asked where we went just tell him
we went shopping
yes sir evil fool he still treats me
like a child yeah it seems so
he's just worried about you you mean a
lot to him
don't talk like you know me sorry
interesting relationship these two have
hmm
well that's very interesting so we're
bringing him to
a secret birthday party or what
thanks for the super chat thank you
thank you i'll read the super chats
maybe at the end of the stream or in a
separate stream i'm not sure
loading loading
oh is it happy birthday time to that i
couldn't read it very well
unloading so long
why why is it what's so funny about that
super chant i want to read it okay there
we go
a bit of black should be it should be
fine soon don't worry about it
don't go in yet
stuck in here for a sec okay what part
okay what are we doing now for
you want something to drink iced tea
i recommend iced tea
i guess it's his birthday happy birthday
to the super jet guy i guess
oh what is that a pen
oh no i guess not
[Music]
it's a specialized performance enhancer
performance enhancement genetic nervous
systems
even someone with my condition will be
able to stand and whoa
just like anybody else oh that kind of
performs only immediate
but it won't last more than a few hours
but how
how did you get something that's crazy
today is my woman's birthday
i can't embarrass her by going in there
like this
that sounds crazy though wow don't you
think it's kind of risky
no it just hasn't been approved for use
in japan
damn does it actually exist no right no
no way that exists
that doesn't exist right that's not a
real thing right none of this sounds
good to me young master
we don't really know what else it might
do to you
there's no way something like that
exists right
i'm gonna drink that don't drink it
[Music]
hello
that liquid didn't even he didn't even
really put
it it didn't go in
oh my god
he's standing up oh my god
so he's gonna be able to do that for a
few hours
damn young master oh my
um like a zombie or something damn
holy [\h__\h] well hopefully something like
this will
will be made in in our world in real
life as well
at some point
hope he's okay though what happens in at
the end does he just fall asleep
welcome honey i'm here
nice ass
oh damn he's standing what
yes it's me [\h__\h] i'm standing i'm
walking
surprised huh
i think this is what you call uh
good evening masato-san
oh my goodness are you all better i
can't believe it
she sounds annoying where's humanosan
um we'll call her as soon as we can as
soon as you can
you better mean now well you see she
just sat down with another customer
she's been very busy today oh she said
she's a host
hostess like uh
cabaret uh hostess what
i just need a minute with him to explain
our situation don't worry
i'll be nice
we don't have much time so um she should
better move her ass over here
is he feeling okay
okay
of course we're gonna be nice we're the
nicest yakuza man
in japan so let's be polite everyone
get your mana straight there's something
wrong sir
hey you where is humanoid
over there she must have left
i believe she got requested by another
guest we're rather busy today
sound really healed uh
it's complicated wow does that mean
you'll be released from
indentured servitude what does that mean
no job ass
i'm not some kind of slave this is an
important job
but isn't masato-san is civilian so why
would you need a yakuza like you
following him around
no one asked you now where's humanosan
oh sorry but you'd probably find her
faster if you looked for her yourself
yo is that how you treat your best
customers you know how many balls we
bought last week on christmas
technically mazuto san ordered them not
you right
oh give me a break fine i'll go look
myself
okay let's look at some hot ass women
hello let's find
human no song where could she be
maybe into the toilet and i'll keep
going here
uh invisible wall it is talk
i don't ever want to talk to thunder but
they look kind of busy
this looks like an expansive fancy place
i like how i keep my lucky bro yeah
that's probably where she is
i mean let me in no okay
wait is that oh
[Music]
well it's not it is there no other room
i can go into
maybe maybe here hello is your real
sound around
no this is you
uh you may go i'm not you may know ah
[Music]
sorry i misunderstood something
hello oh that's it oh that's here
sorry it's so busy today nothing to be
sorry about
if you didn't have customers on your
birthday i'd have to assume everyone
else here was blind
true true makes sense
well he looks familiar um well
um how should i put oh wait isn't that
okay
i'm the young lady's escort for tonight
oh
hey john what are you doing
i believe this club is first come first
served
no need to make things complicated
let's just say we came first and leave
it at that
you understand
my controller just vibrated
what the hell is this i'd ask you the
same
you're the one being unreasonable what
are you going to start with here shut up
trying to look cool or something in
front of this woman
ludo what you some normal ass words
don't
normal you said you'd be civil you're
causing a scene you [\h__\h]
sorry
excuse my companion here he's usually
better behaved
i find that hard to believe this place
doesn't really do the
first come first serve thing oh really
you see
in this industry they can't treat
everything
dude yakuza two i wonder the one who's
sitting down big
get better surface it's supply and
demand that's
all that's so
he doesn't inside he doesn't look like
he could be that's my girl
i see i also she's your girl i think
she's the
uh the girl of everyone in this building
disturbed you would you let me buy you a
drink
i think you're misunderstanding this as
long as you're paying her she's not
actually here no thank you
i don't know it's a different kind of
relationship you know
the drinking type don't get me wrong
eating this to try your luck with
another woman
oh you're paying him now to leave
i couldn't accept that oh go ahead and
take it
let me flex my money why insult me by
refusing
help no thank you my position requires
me to exercise some level of discretion
when accepting gifts
okay where do you get off acting so high
and mighty
i think we're acting high in mighty by
offering him that money in the first
place
i'll give you that what's your name
hello oh
what i suppose you won't stop
bothering me until i show you oh what
what
what are you going to show me your
business card
interesting unfortunately i also have to
be discreet about who receives my
business card wow
are you even allowed out this late
should you be here
no law against it now why don't you take
the lovely lady back to your seat
already
okay thank you wait why why is he
why is he just giving her to us now why
why
you spoil us thank you
aren't you thanking the wrong person
he's right you two should thank the man
who bought them
we're very grateful masatosan
whatever it's fine i mean it is the most
expensive bottle in the house
only natural they'd forget themselves a
bit how often do they get drinks like
that after all
young master i'm sorry about all that
earlier
that guy thinks he's too good to accept
my generosity
generosity he's a cop he's more like a
friend no
does he come here often no this was his
first time
oh so human son what did he get you for
your birthday oh yeah did you get her
anything else stop
just the fact that he's here is enough
for me really
really oh really oh really you two are
so
cute i'm jealous i want a boyfriend like
monster
i don't think he's her boyfriend
he show her yours first
uh sure i i'm not really used to this
kind of thing though so huh
just give it what you got do it just do
it don't let you transfer dreams
sorry i know it's not much oh
he did get something i thought he was
forgetting it
he didn't even have a bag what is that
it's a handkerchief
uh i had a lot of trouble figuring out
what to get you
and you're the young masters woman i
mean piece of
fabric even harder but this
was the most expensive one they had i
promise
[Music]
oh no huh
come on the name ichiban means the best
but i guess there's no accounting for
taste actually this is good yeah he's
like uh he's like a
wingman because he got he gives her a
bad gift so
everything else that he gives her
for my ass mata
will look good in comparison smart move
smart move
well what are you gonna do oh here what
is this
jewelry what could it be what could it
be
must be a ring or a necklace or
okay watch me i don't like watches
but all right that's full of diamonds
huh
no way is this
real i'm not impressed that's my girl
i knew you'd appreciate its worth i'd
sell it just kidding
how much was it about the price of a
condo
you don't ask how much a gift was dump
of course
thank you i don't know how i could ever
repay you
no don't worry about it
i guess my next gift will have to be an
actual condominium
for us okay can i have you at the front
for a moment
you're taking her away from me again
really
can't you read a room kid a ha cookie or
mail itchy
don't start another fight it's the
lady's birthday let her go
she's just in high demand
very popular why is she so popular
what's so special about this woman
excuse me i'll be right back okay hurry
up
i'm paying here i'm paying for you john
he's so nice
well back to drinking you have a captive
audience for all your [\h__\h] stories
oh yeah i'm very interested to talk
let's do something more
intimate intimate things are okay here
what
we'd have to ask you i thought it was
only drinking
sure but i'd still enjoy being your girl
while i could oh everyone's sucking up
to him damn
find yourself your own man
he's taken okay
damn they are first thing
ultra simple nice toilet doors
he's just chilling i didn't want too
many some wingman i
am i know what you saw wait
please wait i'm going home i don't even
want to breathe the same air as that
punk
uh who the hell is he masatosan
he's well he's the
son of a yakuza don't say that's a
police officer
well of course to you he's not a man
he's a big walking wallet
stop this is serious it's starting to
freak me out how much he spends in
drinks
just now he gave me something super
expensive and
said next time it'll be a condo so
you could turn around and sell his
trinkets the next day and if he found
out what do you think he'd do to me
oh are you talking about violence
at the first hint of that i'll throw
them why don't you do that already now
i know you would and you're right should
you police officer
shouldn't you be arresting him it's
walking around
run away all that matters is you says
much about how well you're doing your
job
okay see you later hope you get fired
do your job properly or don't do it at
all
so he heard that
okay wash your hands
very nice bathroom very nice i like the
flowers
nice flower arrangements
how long have you been felt like you saw
a [\h__\h] ghost
oh god
um you okay did you hear that
so did you finish your business
huh what business i'm heading back
use this to pay the bill okay my friend
oh he's not feeling bad anything left
might as well use it to wipe your ass
thank you thank you for the tip thank
[Music]
you
uh is it okay to leave him alone
shouldn't we help him get home
safely and get to his uh
roll uh wheelchair
i'm not sure if we can leave him alone
like that
a bit worried about him
aren't you also worried for him
broken heart no i think he's just
exhausted from that medicine or whatever
he took
oh wow that's a long loading time
almost there almost there
he's crushed
extra long loading time
dun dun dun dun dun dun
so he did hear them but he was not in
the toilet
[Music]
are you done babysitting the young
master yes yep
let's meet up at theater square and walk
to the office okie dokie
he sounds very excited about that
okay let's find our best boy
that looks exactly like kabukicho but i
know it's not kabukicho
going around here in the game is fine
but like in real life i don't really
want to go around this area
kind of scary
but it does look like japan like those
areas in japan
oh loading loading
if you have a better pc it's gonna look
much better than this
uh load please is it gonna there we go
okay if you have a better pc than me
it's going to look better i promise
mashimas oh oh sorry it was there
where are we going here
oh i'm here
the map says i have to go here
got it
is it loading something i wonder oh yeah
it is loading something
let's give it some time
oh hey boy i was waiting for you
i was here before you next time
[Music]
yep hello
what kind of voice should we give him i
can't do so many male voices what
yeah let's go back why not let's go boy
interesting what's gonna happen are we
gonna get school dad
don't scold me i was a good girl porn
peddler
nothing sir anike took care of him today
hi you won't ever pull that [\h__\h] again
without going through us first
okay and how much did you get from him
uh 500 yen i gave the money back to the
high schoolers who bought the videos
it was the fair thing to do and the kids
were grateful to our family
wow i see
can we really be that nice oh yeah
went off without a hitch here's the
guy's wallet just as you requested sir
here is the wallet with nothing inside
have fun
also happy birthday to the super chat
person
ah all the money's there including
interest
we'll read properly in another uh super
chat reading
oh wait what oh he did oh he put that
money inside the uh
is that what you thought i would say
hello excuse me there was nothing in
there from the young masters bank
oh ichi what's the real story oh you
should have maybe taken that off
[\h__\h] there there is no real story
the young master gave that to me i swear
he gave it to you oh [\h__\h]
how did you beg him for it to make quota
no
for scraps won't fix your incompetence
i didn't beg i have too much pride to
pull something like that
oh god i'm scared mama
you have pride when you can't earn for
the family
slap chat
what's that look pretending it didn't
hurt
you don't even know paige not for a
yakuza anyway
a yakuza takes real responsibility
hey no no no no
no no no no no he didn't do anything bad
no
i felt like a small knife that's too big
what
what's wrong you don't know how real
yakuza atone
what are we doing
if you're lucky
good to see you boss oh [\h__\h] yes oh my
god [\h__\h] out
oh my god
yes sir oh my god oh my god
that got me really scared
[Music]
i thought he was going to take my ubi
thanks for coming at the right time
shave my ass back there
you saved my finger can't you at least
try to get along with joe
i'm trying he started to fight
that's because well i'm not much of an
earner
you're more of a kid putting yourself in
his shoes
he's doing his duty as a family
treasurer
sure i know that but it's like we just
have
different visions of what a yakuza
should be
to me it's more about duty and standing
up for people
not money oh is that really what it's
okay to see things differently that's
the strength of the arakawa party
sorry party it's not so different than
those games you like
is it everyone has a certain skill they
bring to the table
some people are like you charging in
head first without a thought
others cover your ass like mitsu and
some are better at cracking the whip
that's joel all of these people keep the
organization
running yeah just like halloween
everyone has their own traits and
strengths all of you are more like sons
than
subjects very nice
speaking of you looked after masato
today
i guess i did yeah yes sir sorry to keep
asking you to help me with something so
personal
how was he he was standing up straight
man
that's good to hear these days
he doesn't even answer my calls i may be
king of the arakawa family
but to my other family it's nothing but
a title
well ichiban why don't we go get our
last meal of the 20th
oh yeah it's new year's eve
should have spent new year's eve in a
more nice way man
like go see some some fireworks or
something
or like i don't know what do you guys
usually do for new year's eve
what do i do what do i usually do
depends on which country i am but this
year i want to do a countdown stream
with you guys although i'm gonna
be the first one getting into new year's
eve and new year
goes out in in the in the land of the
rising sun and most of you are not
so maybe you want to spend new years
with me
how does that sound can do it early calm
down and then i can look back to you and
be like ha
i'm the future beach you are the pesk
try to keep up with me you guys are too
slow
i'm already in 2021 and you're in 2020
lame i would say [\h__\h] lame
sounds good i'll be dissing you all
night
did you see that i guess nobody cares
about pewdie
on new year's that reminds me
you find yourself a girl how about me no
sir
i'm like a reverse chick
chick magnet don't be so quick to throw
in the towel
easy for you to say you probably had
girls all over you at my age
what i won't abide such slack
no i you use the pesters going silver
i see i will not doubt that i believe
you
of course of all the women over the
years
there was only one oh just
one i might have started a family but
you didn't yeah
yes but then you did then you did start
a family now i've never told you the
details have i
why did you say you might have i uh i do
know that she passed away oh that's why
yes
let me start on new year's eve 24 years
ago
flashback time just to grunt in the
hikawa family
but the patriarch asked me if i'd marry
his daughter
she was the young master's mother just
listen
i love someone else her name was akane
what did i was naive he's a very
soothing voice indeed yeah
i thought if i ignored my boss's
daughter she'd get annoyed and dumped me
the whole time i was dating akane in
secret on the side wait wait you were
cheating
remember the moment she told me she was
pregnant
damn that i knew right now the music
what i needed to do i had to step
up as a man problem was
i couldn't find the right moment to tell
the boss about akane and our child
by the time i worked up the courage to
tell him
like and he was almost due oh so i got
down on my hands and knees
and told the boss i already had a girl
oh
he didn't let you off easy i take it oh
is this
oh come on if only it could have been
over and done with them
why are they so rough give an order to
the family
in order to kill akane what what
kill her yes
that's not necessary but he was serious
even though we were a small family we
were very good at making people
disappear
and when we killed the body was never
found oh dear i was waiting for akane
and me
for bringing
i don't think they expected that after
how badly they beat me
at the same time akane was at the
hospital having the baby
i called her and told her to leave as
soon as possible
i knew yakuza were already on their way
to the hospital
so i made a plan
i told her we could meet at this cafe so
we could skip
town cafe helps yes
i waited and waited but she never came
but just as i was about to lose all hope
i got a call
very sad pain pickle
so she gave birth wait is the child she
gave birth to masato
would make sense right
damn why so sad
pink telephone
oh that's after they beat him up huh
where are you i thought they caught you
our baby he's here huh
oh what
i got away but they're not far behind
i i have to keep moving
oh my god where are you i'll come get
a newborn baby we literally born like
minutes ago
i'll come get him as soon as i can oh
[\h__\h] once you're in a safe place
call the manager at cafe alps tell them
where you are
now hurry put the baby in a locker
interesting phrase when taken out of
context
that's her go go hurry the [\h__\h] up
where's the woman damn it's where she go
hurry up and find her
oh god it's also pink [\h__\h]
what's that car
eh how did they know i was there
not me but i yeah feels like it's me
how did they know
how do you know i'm here
oh god
are we fighting in the flashback now are
we gonna fight
even though it's a flashback are you
gonna fight
loading time
forgot which locker yeah but i think
like if you hear you would probably hear
the crying oh we're not fighting
oh okay i guess he won the fight hello
i got away safely somewhat simply
now where is the baby is that is that
how the baby
lost his ability to walk or
okay you hear it okay it's not so clear
but you just heard it cry more baby cry
more this one time you're allowed to cry
as much as you want
do it in the back what's he looking at
so crazy
[Music]
oh my god oh my
my baby
you okay baby
oh it doesn't look very good did it
was it able to breathe it looks like the
the face color looks kind of
oh my lips
no oh my god no no no no
no no no the baby cannot die
stay alive baby
baby looked very dead indeed but should
be fine we should be fine
i rescued our child and ran to a
hospital um
the doctor examined masato and said he
had multiple organ failure
due to low body temperature it was
massaging
that's how you get into a wheelchair i
mean i know there's many ways
five minutes earlier it could have
prevented the complications
because of organ failure he got into a
wheelchair
i mean you got there as soon as you
could you tried everything at least he's
alive
you're burdened with masato's care
because of me
no it's okay it's not a burden it's not
a burden
i never saw akane again after that
what she ran to abortion you but
the hikawa family was already dead
as i was taking masato to the house no
they were taking her away
they killed her no no
no few days later the patriarch and
several of his men
disappeared the hikawa family had ceased
to exist
quiet did you
oh never mind forget it did you kill all
of them
sorry for rambling on and on
but there is something i've always
wanted to tell you
what is it even if only by oath
i consider you ah a son as well
thank you that's so sweet
[Music]
well enough gloomy talk
i want to know what's wrong with his
hand by the way i'm starving because
he's wearing a glove so i wonder if like
one of his uh ubis is cut off
maybe that's why he's wearing a glove
i've seen it before
in a hulu series where
the um they were wearing a glove to hide
their cut of fingers so i guess that's
probably like
how he's trying to hide it but i want to
know this i wonder if we got to know the
story of that as well at some point
yeah that was very sad yeah
from punching the locker
hey what do you think happened with he
broke his hand but wouldn't it be
fixed by now wouldn't it be fine by now
how hard do you have to punch a locker
that it never
ever like works it ever again
damn he crashed his hand with that
i guess i guess he was using that hand
huh
some injuries are permanent oh you think
i was permanent
yeah maybe that's it yeah
oh or he's just hiding trying to hide
scars yeah that makes sense too
well seeing as i'm the king and all
how about we feast on the king of
chinese food
okay look at that
oh gyoza i love you
no no no no no no no
i have a bad memory didn't you
not even edible your your father got
shot eating peking duck
the duck is dried in the sun then
and the skin comes out so crispy and
delicious
you peel off the purple i have a bad
feeling
wrap it in the seasoned dough then your
mouth is
filled with the sweet and spicy
fragrance of the sauce thank you for
that very detailed explanation
that does sound good but has he never
eaten bacon
which is why in ancient china only the
imperial court ate it
is this story gonna repeat itself
chinese food
yep but i wonder if we can find it in
kambocho
you don't know a place here there's
gotta be a place serving it somewhere
he's so hyped up now picking duck
picking duck let's go find him oh thank
you matt for already telling me where it
is
you're following me dude oh he's running
old man chill you don't have to run so
fast well then now i'm running so i
guess you got to keep up
yo what up peeps hey y'all haven't seen
some taking duck around here it goes
like
that it's very delicious i heard so
i'm really [\h__\h] hungry right now
gotta fill my belly with some picking
buckle oh i've been here before i think
hello loading wait where do i go do i
have to
wait the map is a bit confusing to me
right now i think i have to go around
the block
ignore the rendering just ignore that
oopsie ah sorry i have to go here
i gotta go here outside whoops sorry
suma santorimo
i'm hungry me and my boss
me and my almost father
are really hungry oh i reached the point
the destination
oh i've been here before i mean feels
familiar
picking that girl oh
loading
[Music]
it's almost the new year the employees
are probably at home
how can you get so fired up about
tradition
another time i promise yeah
thank you sir that duck got lucky today
but you won't get away from us next time
where are you laughing [\h__\h] up go look
somewhere else have a good
new year's you too
[Laughter]
ichiban mind your own business what have
i told you
nothing sorry
be careful where you laugh outdoors the
only time a yakuza should laugh with his
teeth
is when he's with family or when he's in
deep [\h__\h]
always looks scary and intimidating
reputation is
everything for a yakuza but don't we
want reputation as a nice guy since we
missed our shot at the duck
shall we go to our usual odin place shot
wink sounds good i think it's good yeah
we shouldn't eat picking duck right now
uh on new year's eve that seems like uh
foreshadowing
or like back shadowing because that
would that that's how your father died
so
um i don't know if that's a good idea
to
one day we will eat her one day
so we're going for oden do you guys know
what odin is oden is like a hot
hot soup with some stuff in it you can
get it in convenience stores in the
wintertime
in tokyo in japan i guess
i guess not only in convenience stores
yeah what's wrong ichi
you look like you're about to [\h__\h]
excuse me shut your [\h__\h] mouth you
piece of [\h__\h] [\h__\h] worthless [\h__\h]
don't you stop by to help out at home
every now and then ah
not for a while i guess
you should treasure the place where you
grew up
here is that where we grow the most
normal place for a kid to be
that's where we grow up what no matter
how it happened
home is home one day you won't be able
to go back you know
that's our home oh you must be kidding
me that's our home
23 years ago on january 1st i came into
this world
inside this sleazy soap you were born in
here what no
damn
that's your home wait
oh my god is your mom still working
there or does he have a mom
huh
that's why they call him
don't know who my other dad is probably
some guy who dropped in for a wham bam
thank you ma'am when ben thank you i'll
remember that thank you
welcome
[Music]
thank you man to hold him
oh they like babies huh
[Music]
noodles was raised by this city's
working class folks
wow that must have been uh interesting
childhood
or a tough childhood yeah but he turned
out to be a really nice guy
interesting
very wholesome i guess yes
thank you ma'am
i will remember that hopefully ram bam
thank you man gotta burn that into my
brain ram bam thank you ma'am ram bam
thank you man should i say that to kelly
[Laughter]
better not say that to kelly i feel like
amelia would like
uh to hear that she likes those kind of
jokes
she will understand me
[Music]
not the convenience store society all
those people who raised me are scum
well i suppose that would make me scum
too yeah everyone scum yang
what never you're everything i want to
be
you're like a god wow you really look up
to him do you
so first i'm a king and now
i'm a god yep
what a simp he's simping for him
when i met you i had just graduated
middle school
sorry it's lagging a bit again sorry
reloading again are you getting more
cutscenes
i'm gonna wait after my foster daughter
before those cuts
i dropped out of school and just started
drifting
in the 90s
just picking fights taking people down
for easy money
but karma always catches up
eventually i beat up the wrong guy oh
[\h__\h]
oh do they all wear those pins isn't it
kind of obvious that you're a yakuza
his crew locked me in a yakuza office
and beat the [\h__\h] out of me
[\h__\h] that's not very nice i thought i
was a goner
but i made one last ditch effort to live
and yelled out a name
[Music]
arakawa
what you're a kawa family if you kill me
they'll hunt every last one of you down
in those days the name arakawa the
assassin was like a whispered threat
oh i didn't give a [\h__\h] about yakuza who
they were at the time
but i knew that name so he just randomly
said that
drop them maybe they'd freak out and let
me live
oh you're saying you're our cousin smart
one
a kid like you how are you gonna prove
that huh my plan backfired
big time oh [\h__\h] turned out these guys
were in a huge turf dispute with the
arkham
oh no one of your little brats damn near
beat my boy to death
says his name's ichiban kasika
no way not in the sorry state we put him
in
him back you better send patriarch
arakawa
personally i knew the jig was up
i'd never even met arakawa so obviously
he wasn't gonna come
but then he came maybe we ought to just
kill him on a key wait did he actually
come here
ain't gonna show his face to pick up his
trash is he actually coming
looks like you're [\h__\h] out of luck
there's a random brat that said his name
couldn't go
you guys always go this hard on yourself
that's so nice of
him who's this bad of mine you say
you've got
the little [\h__\h] damn near took our guy
out we can't just hand it back to you
without some compensation
somebody's got to take responsibility
i see
oh that's what i told you he's losing
his finger that's why he got the
gloves just borrow this
[Applause]
he doesn't even care his voice is like
i did not just cut off my finger and
what the [\h__\h]
i he doesn't he doesn't even feel it
you you saved my life and gave his
[\h__\h] thingy
why how can
reputation is everything my face
my name they mean something
sorry what do you think it would have
meant if i
begged them to return to you the whole
arakawa family would have paid for it
i don't know giving a finger is kind of
like begging for it no
he's done i did the only thing that
would preserve
my family's credit couldn't you have
said that's not that dude is not from
our
family you've just said you didn't know
me yeah
i mean that's totally that's totally
probably not indeed
yeah why maybe i wanted to make an
impression
on a kid who knew my name
and at that moment i saw my life's path
ahead of me
i mean i don't see that as a good reason
but okay i'm following this man
well he did save your life
welcome back patriarchal
how many times i gotta say this we got
no cups for punks
never mind the kid joe
i didn't care how often they ignored me
or what they said
i stood outside that office every day ah
cute
in the pouring rain oh man
under the scorching sun
welcome back patriarchal
patriarch you know him
isn't something to aspire to haven't
your parents explain that to you
i don't have parents sir i had a foster
dad but he's dead now oh come on don't
make it sad again
that's so sad come on
[Music]
i like how this is all in like photo
style is very nice to my pc thank you
very forgiving
[Music]
the whole game could be in this so be
beautiful
it'd been 100 days since i'd met
arakawa-san
we could i wouldn't mind continuing
having cutscenes like this
my pc thanks you my pc is very thankful
and grateful thank you very much for
being easy
the same thing for 100 days next slide
yeah come on next slide come on
three months that's very persistent but
i guess he didn't have anything else to
do huh
he didn't go to school right
i it's been two hours streaming time but
not really two hours gaming time so
i'm gonna do like 15 minutes more and
see like it's been
uh cut scenes without a break so i don't
even have a
chance to stop at a good point anyway
right now so i'm gonna do 15 minutes
more
man that odin is always so freaking good
when i want to hear more of the story
more story more story
got the stupid glasses just ridiculous
stupid glasses
those really only worked between 2000
and 2009 huh
because of the two zeros in the middle
stop it
do they even still make them
you came here alone on new year's eve
that means you're looking for
one thing excuse me i'm not looking for
anything shut the [\h__\h] up too good
i'm gonna kick your balls and you're
never gonna be able to move ever again
you piece of [\h__\h]
sometimes it's a scum of society that
has to do the cleaning up
hell yeah let me clean up let me clean
up i wanna do it i wanna do it
a new century's about to start and i
know you don't want to spend the first
week lying in a hospital bed
get out of here before an old man has to
crack some skulls uh-huh
that's right tell them how you say papa
keep out of this
you know who i am [\h__\h] are you you don't
know
what family he's so proud of drunk ass
is away from them
saying that that's cute time to go home
and listen to the new year's bells like
good boys
hold on are you guys yakuza um yes
there's gotta be look he's got the hair
and everything
you're gonna pay for this plus they're
wearing costumes straight out of a mafia
movie costumes
you [\h__\h] better not be making fun of
us i'm
getting a little bit angry right now
leave this to me they do not
it's been a few years since i saw you
fight
hopefully yours oh watch me that
movement though
just wait till you see what i can do
this [\h__\h]
hey thank you cool oh my god
come on let me beat him up
you're gonna be calling for your mommy
after this
check this out let's go
swapped
oh he's a bit stronger because of that
fat he saved from winter
or whatever what what the hell did you
do
stupid prank take this [\h__\h]
i wanted to dodge that i was giving a
normal attack
what a ridiculous spawn going on
weakling coward
you got nothing on me i'm [\h__\h] yakuza
you made fun of me you're paying for
that
pay up [\h__\h]
who is this guy
he's crazy
you okay don't be scared of me don't be
scared of me
oh why are you scared of me i don't
understand the boss
it's fine just forget it they don't
understand
remember yakuza yes
they don't understand i get it now then
i'll see you later ichi you better show
up at the office next year
yeah it's like in a few hours visit for
the world good night boss
you too he's looking cool
he's such a bad he's so in love with a
stupid i
wouldn't mind another drink alone
where are we going for a drink
[Music]
oh god oh god
oh my god it's 2001
[Music]
so nostalgic what did i do in 2001
what did you guys do when when probably
some of you weren't even born
before he disappeared i got the new
year's kiss
and i would have preferred it to be with
someone else you know
you know who i mean but that's okay
that's okay i'll take it i'll take it
new year's kiss with a yakuza guy first
time
there's your first time for everything
[Music]
oh thank you for the new year's eve
super chat
aki master
happy for you
it is 2001 now huh
oh wait did you go for 2001 to 2002 or
2000 to 2001 which one was it
damn so many generations in the chat so
many different ages huh
still loading i would like to again
explain that my pc is
uh not very good so it will work better
wake up
if you have a better pc no
is it really a good idea to have that
pin on your suit so obviously
you fall asleep outdoors you know can i
see your identification
police must know what that means now yes
like your license a violent crime was
committed out here recently
oh that probably was me
got nothing [\h__\h] my wallet's gone
i would say that pin on your chest
identify you shouldn't sleep out here
no you need to file a stolen item report
now
i'm busy so you'll have to go down to
the station
first of all happy new year sorry to
call you first
no problem facebook space oh he's so
cute
you want to go on motivated of the year
no
just come to the office try to be
inconspicuous
he's so cute okay
you got it i'm calling he's such a
fanboy
oh yeah apparently they stole the wallet
but not the phone i mean
why what i mean maybe it was in the on
the side
on the pocket side where he was sleeping
on so
what is this music sounding so
suspicious and dangerous get out of the
way beach
sorry you're a student you should
probably shouldn't be walking down these
streets right now i
i doubt that there's a school around
here i
highly doubt that oh are we going in
there
[Music]
oh you we don't want to look suspicious
what's happening there has been a crap
oh it wasn't
our crime with something else
inconspicuous guess i should take the
backstreet okay
i gotcha backstreets
can i run though does that look
suspicious if i run like that
i think that's kind of suspicious but
okay oopsie
whoops
oh ooh i think i'm
going the right way map says so
i'm here what's going on here
give it some time to load give it some
time to load
i know i know very funny hahaha
there we go
oh well we can't go there oh come on
i'm already there though like
map says it's kind of here
do you have to go from the back
can i go here why do i think
oh hold up oh i was right
don't you forget it oh yeah [\h__\h]
how about you don't forget your place
what's wrong what's wrong
and who the [\h__\h] what did i do now
there's a cocky family cocky
i just never heard of your name before
let's do it
tenacious fist
[Music]
oh
oh it's lagging it's lagging you can do
this anyway
bunk bump to real high
[Music]
i'm getting really good hello oh no oops
i should have maybe used the skill but
okay
he was defeated by that for a week
damn oh okay that was maybe the skill
wasn't necessarily
bunk that's how you do it
that's how you do it don't mess with the
alakawa family and not with this fanboy
like he maybe
looks like a hot ass boy but he's just
simple like he's a real [\h__\h] symp
and since you you're gonna i'm telling
you very strong
when it's about protecting hell was that
about whoever did something for
probably nothing there's no kidding no
joking around beef with a sake going on
oh [\h__\h] that took a while gotta head
into the office
yeah they're broke 320 yen that's like
uh
two dollars or so okay can we go in now
[Music]
we should probably end the stream soon
it's uh
yeah when now i need a good timing knock
knock
who is it
tell me a good answer chat
good morning i don't want to quit though
it's going so it's so interesting
ichi have a seat hi sir would you guys
fight for me like that
why are you cleaning up sure
one more hour i don't think i can do
that
i wish i could
it's so interesting
you know the sake family right i think i
have to
get through this uh cutscene
we're fighting them because of a rumor
that they're connected to the umi
but aren't they only all the way out
yeah this is a sponsored stream and uh
they control it two hours two hours only
that most people realize the dojo clan
has butted heads with them for years
it's a bitter rivalry and what
the sakaki families cooperating with
them
no that's a cookie family
oh apparently like in five minutes the
chapter is uh
over anyway so let's finish the chapter
i confronted them about it i hope that's
okay
but their patriarch pretended not to
know anything
long story short they don't like us much
right now
but at the same time they still report
directly to our main family
so we need to be careful we don't want
to cause the main family any trouble
that said did something happen
two hours ago i got a call from joe
he he showed up
really apparently he just happened to
run into
so you just run into one and shoot him
no other men
it was one on one they talked [\h__\h] to
each other for a bit
then joe pulled his gun
why do i have to go that far no one saw
them
but the police have already that's why
they were all there
it's only a matter of time before they
radar god damn it joe
god damn it if word gets out that our
captain killed someone from a family
above ours
it will be considered mutiny i don't
know the meaning of that
from the dojo clan and our tiny family
why why why
why so bad
because he killed someone from another
but doesn't that happen all the time
between these yakuza families doesn't
isn't that normal
why is the child going crazy with george
you see why i can't let joe get arrested
for this
uh betrayal okay i see thank you
does he are you serious boss what
i mean you want me to say i killed that
dude
i've been waiting for a shot like this
[Music]
to ah to prove you're like to help him
it's my chance to finally repay my debts
let him lock me up for 10 or even 20
years
i'd be happy to do it for you
[Music]
oh
is that the end of the chapter and do
they still lock him up
and then it's over can i save now
apparently it's autosave though whenever
the sign for auto saving shows up
i wonder if i can save uh manually
that's so s oh man i thought he was
gonna say what the [\h__\h]
um i guess okay but he's like yes let me
do it
he's so he's so pure and so sweet and
such a nice guy man
damn
[Music]
no no no i was late to start the game
anyway
so it should still be fine
let's go see happy birthday
happy birthday oh it's my birthday it's
my [\h__\h] birthday
good job surviving another year we made
it to a new century when can i save you
oh yeah
i guess so his birthday is on the first
january
birthday boy what's up with you
are you going to your first trying visit
of the year how about we do camaro again
you do it and have a good time i'm not
going oh [\h__\h] he's going somewhere else
something came up he's gonna turn
himself in something on you
yeah basically new year's barely begun
and he's already working you like a dog
no holidays for the yakuza we work 365
days a year
so you're going to be busy all day he's
going to
be busy for a while how old are you
right now
uh 20 if you really want to twenty
that's so young
so in 10 years you'll be 30. in 20
you'll be 40.
yep that's math dude
see you in 20 years eat well and live
lifetime that's so dramatic but uh he's
pro
totally gonna jailbreak now feeling okay
i mean otherwise how is this game going
to go
i'll call you later all right
simp ichi hell yeah simp the biggest sim
kyodan
how do i get to the main menu by the way
how do i get to it start
no how do i get to the main menu
ah here no that's just the math
what
oh okay um hope it's okay that i
eat uh until the end of the chapter
it's eat the people and then end the
chapter sorry
wait why is one one is uh green and one
is pink
oh i marked that did i mark that here
how do i undo the mark
hey okay
i think it did all the save wait
am i really can i do
okay okay manager says it's okay to
finish the chapter okay okay
gotta end it at a good spot right hey
but i want to play some games in sega
no time for that gotta eat my meat
my dinner boy
hello please load the oh wait what
why what happened what happened here
how did this happen hello
that was not air saver
wait a second how did that happen
thank you manager san
[Music]
wow my pc is really a potato huh
this is the time i have realized my pc
is indeed a potato
i don't know why that showed up i didn't
press anything
anyway no problem
loading beef ball
give me my food have you guys ever eaten
before it's a japanese like a rice bowl
with beef on top of it but that's not
just it that sounds simple right
but it's so much more than that it's so
much more
yummy
i think like overseas and outside of
japan there's them
there's probably some japanese
restaurants who do uh
beef bones as well
no you haven't no what
try to make it yourself i think it's
quite easy to make it yourself
it's pretty damn good sorry the loading
times makes
okay you gotta forgive me that my stream
is a bit longer as well because of the
loading times okay
i get some extra streaming times because
of the extra loading times
but no problem i have permission to
stream a tiny bit longer
oh wow it's loading really long that
must be a huge beef bowl
that's a huge beautiful man
[Music]
i'm sorry sega for having such a shitty
pc
uh but i really enjoy the game i really
do
come on pc a little bit more
put the toppings on the beef bowl come
on put me put some cheese on it or
something
you don't need cheese
come on come on what that's like it
never loaded that long before is it
going to crash
that's the first time it loaded so long
oh my god
[Music]
um
come on perfect time for small talk
okay there's actually not so much time
left i think it's almost done loading
almost done just believe in it just
believe in it as i told you i've been to
the kabukicho
many times and apparently there's a lot
of yakuza around there but i have no
idea like
who is how do you identify a yakuza
there's like a lot of men in suits in
kabukicho but they're mostly like
trying to get customers for their uh
bars and and
and cabaret clubs and so on
so it's kind of hard i would like to
think that they're not really around
i i would like to think it's like an
urban legend or so
come on come on you can do it oh there
we go
i think the game deserves an applause
for working so hard
i can only eat one i can't eat that much
damn
how long have you not eaten food
[Music]
i don't think that's enough for all
those beefals
yeah screw it yo oh you already need one
more
you already paid 20 hours sure coming
right up
another beef bowl
it pays me to say this but you've been
banished from the family effective
last month what why last month
if only he'd been from a family outside
the clan
i could have merely expelled you but
this man
not only was he tojo he reported
directly to the main family
but being banished doesn't that mean i
can never come back
i'll be working on that personally i'll
have them he'll be back i believe in him
you get out of prison
thank you boss oh my god and perhaps
banishment will work in our favor
the court will go easier on you now that
you're just a civilization true that is
true
let them do their worst i can handle a
few years in the can
oh yeah the food in the in the prison
won't be that good huh
thanks for the menu
you gotta save her every last moment
don't you
while eating a beef bowl for sure
i like him he's so positive about
everything
i can learn something from him for my
life
the weight will be worth it he'll come
out there even stronger
let's go ichiban
let's go to prison
hey buddy did you ever find your wallet
no
well if not you might as well find a
theft report inside i'm gonna file
something else but yeah
find the defendant ichiban kasuga guilty
of murder
he is hereby sentenced to 15 years in
prison
chapter one done
i think and loading again
but wow oh we're gonna end it there i
hope i can did that save it probably
saved right i can just
it probably saved it must have saved
do i have to wait for it to load until i
get safe
15 years is indeed a long time but he
said he would even do it for 20 years so
um oh wonderful wonderful
okay um
wait let me save wait a second save how
do i save
a here
okay okay okay okay i saved
wow wow wow
wow that was
so so different from what i expected
but it was a really nice experience
honestly i've heard of this
uh series before
i wasn't very interested in the series
before because i think you guys know
i really like rpgs or like jrpgs
but thanks for the applause thank you
thank you very
much i really like jrpgs and this is a
jrpg apparently
but i usually go for the pretty cute
looking ones and
like this one to be honest it kind of
scared me off the yakuza
just because of the title even and the
general look
of like what i've seen until now but
i i loved it like every second of it the
story was good the graphics i mean if i
had a better pc
would be good the the fighting
system was easy and easy to understand
like everything in the game it was easy
nothing was like confusing i could
follow
it uh nicely you know i often have
problems with other kind of games
with making progress and um yeah but it
was very smooth and like
um it kept on going like it didn't
become boring at all
it kept them getting more and more
interesting and the story really caught
my interest it really caught me but it
also had so much humor in it
and the main character is so uh
he has my sympathies and he's like such
a nice guy
like he might even change my my image of
yakuza completely
although probably i should probably
still be wary of
yakuza but yeah
that was really nice i would actually
love to continue playing this
um and uh possibly on stream if we get
permission i don't know about that but
thank you sega so much for sponsoring
the stream i don't know if you're
watching but
thank you so much for giving me this
opportunity i'm sorry for my shitty pc
but i did my best and i really really
enjoyed the game
it was really awesome i'll get a new pc
send them soon
and enjoy even more the full glory of
this game
but wow that's that was really great
that it really makes sense that this is
such a such a
popular and famous game series thank you
sega
thank you so much now i'm honestly happy
i'm really really happy that we got this
uh
opportunity to play such an amazing game
and uh cali cali played the fifth
chapter so if you guys haven't seen her
stream she also did the stream
on uh uh this game today so if you want
to see more
either buy the game yourself there's no
either actually buy it
and also watch cali stream if you
haven't seen it yet she did it today
fifth chapter
there was some some really cute really
good looking woman
apparently in this uh yakuza game you're
actually
able to uh fight with with female
characters
for the first time if i read that
correctly some i read that somewhere
[Music]
american
and i'm also glad i could start from the
beginning i think um uh
it was a good choice to start from the
beginning also for you guys
because i know many of you didn't really
want to get spoilered and
uh starting with everyone from the
beginning and uh
or not not playing longer than two hours
makes it possible for everyone to just
after the stream
go to steam buy the game and get into it
on your own
right i think everyone was really
excited and really
really happy about this game like that
was really great and like
for someone like me who usually goes for
like the anime style
cute games i was
i was uh how do you say that they got me
like i'm i'm
i'm like a little bit addicted now i
want more
more time
thank you so so much for watching the
stream
uh i'll be taking tomorrow off
uh super chat reading uh i'm not sure
can i do it in the stream
manager uh is it okay if i do the super
chat reading in this stream or should i
should i uh take a different uh
reservation i wonder if it's okay i'm
checking with manager right now
i'm also really sorry about the lagging
uh
although it's weird because only obs was
lagging
uh and not the game itself for me
separate stream okay
okay i'll keep uh with this show this
should be only only the game no super
chat i agree with that
okay then we'll do it um
at the end of the day after tomorrow's
stream
i think what do you guys think about
that
i think that's a good idea
thank you everyone for watching and in
german
we say
[Music]
bye bye thank you so much
bye bye thank you
[Music]
so
you