[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
uh
us me and ina hello hello hello hello
hello hello hello hello
you guys hear us and you guys hear the
music
too
[Music]
wow that's so
is loud loud no no that one's ironic
oh it's okay it's a glassy hole
i i like my my calm inna my chill you
know
that's how i like my inna so spare me i
just woke up
yeah inna just woke up so she might
still be a bit
sleepy but it's okay ina took
a good nap right yes what did you dream
of
you remember gotcha oh well that's not
good
that's not good when gacha invades your
dreams it's too late
like dream of god to rules
i hope oh my god the ancient ones are in
the chat
hotel so
welcome everyone to today's
collaboration actually is the first
uh collaboration on my channel that is
not like the full
the full member collaboration and
welcome welcome welcome
i am takana next to me is ninomaya
inanis we are both from whole life
english as if you didn't know already
and today we are doing an arc nights
related stream
because both of us are
actually really into arc nights and we
both play arc nights for
a long time and especially while inna
genuinely loves gacha games a lot right
yes i do a little too much yeah
for me it's um actually
you could say only arc nights i'm like
really addicted to arc knights only the
other
gotcha games not so much but yeah
ina totally goes crazy she plays all of
them all of them
too many of them so
eventually you guys will probably
possibly
see a stream of us playing arc nights as
well one day
but for today we uh i guess
i thought it would be maybe a good idea
to first discuss
some things about the operators and i i
know that a lot of people in the chat
play the game but there's also a lot who
don't play the game
so we will introduce to you today
our top the bestest of the best
waifus and well i guess also partially
husbandos but yay
my food chili
[Music]
and by the way as i think you see like
on on top
of of the screen there is a
small inna above me and small chiada
above ina you know judo is like
like how quick did you even draw those
yes yes good answer
good answer i was i told ina i was gonna
make a thumbnail
and she offered kindly to draw
something for it so she really quickly
whipped this
out of her drawing program nice they
look so cute
now we have like partner look chibis
so adorable our faces when we when we
roll
yeah no followed by faces of
disappointment
yeah and also
at the right corner of my screen and you
see
a small version of me which looks like
uh like me uh
how i would probably look if i was
inside of arc nights
on the battlefield uh a fan drew this
for me
the credits are in the youtube
description
if you wanna check it out thank you for
drawing that
maybe maybe we'll get one for ina
as well wink wink wink
for future ike night streams it will be
really cute if we both had this uh
sd character i guess you could call it
sd character oh
oh good question if you were a character
in arc nights what class would you
be what would you think is fitting
for you i actually didn't think about
that i think it would be good as a guard
i mean or especially a character very
similar yeah we can go over that indeed
get to her
but she's a supporter right right
i guess you could also be good as a
supporter
but so many classes i think would fit
you
but for my guys i find the best for me
since i have this shield would probably
be defender
because have you seen a guard have you
seen a guard with a shield though
was there a guy with a shield
this is gorgeous literally
no we don't need any more guys we don't
need anymore guys i have too many cards
too many
good nights in our audio a little bit
low
roger uh let me see if i can
up you know i should like make me make
that higher
if i'm already at max i can raise it on
my end too so no no
i raised it now it did i think i think i
raised it
can you talk something i made that
i made the background music a bit
quieter and feel a bit bigger
chiara fast redeployed oh
oh yes it makes sense
because i just revive again and again
and again right
you're right it would be really
interesting a fast redeploy like
defender
yeah it could be like gravel like really
defensive
fast redeploy oh that's a good idea yeah
yeah yeah
good idea funny and of course
oh my god now i have to i have to stop
imagining this because
can you imagine like like me in like
e2 version with like a huge phoenix
behind me
um
that would be so cool and for you oh my
god all those tentacles
i think like for you you already look e2
just by your default
you have to blow my waist dance
asserting my dominance
anyway uh today we are using
some tear maker you can just look it up
arc knight's
waifu tear maker a lot of them come up
then
and this is this list i have to say it's
not 100
updated because bagpipe is not in it
however there's at least one character
that is not supposed to be in there yet
i mean it's kind of weird that she's in
there
and i hope it's
okay i didn't find the perfect i mean
she
she doesn't have uh an effect on the
story she was a
um an operator you could get from a
collaboration i believe it was though
which one was it just pure stream you
mean the collaboration
is it uh w
she's in there i don't know why please
forgive me we're just gonna leave her
out
for now because uh i i don't even
i don't even know anything about her to
be honest
she's cute she looks she looks cute when
i first saw her
i thought it was like a new amias
anything looks similar but she'll be get
started
basically we're going to do this at the
same time and at the end we'll have two
different
lists because uh i guess inna has
tastes than me but
we'll see we'll see we'll see now let's
get started with amia
where would we put aviya
[Applause]
i mean she's near the top she's near the
top yeah i don't know if i consider her
the best i like her i think we have to
first clear
are we gonna sort and judge them
by their skills by their looks or by
both
the full package or by your
preference i guess
uh you can decide your
your what you will call it um
your own categories in your mind i'll
say it but
you won't say it and we'll see i think
we should go by the same by the same
because yeah because i can't explain
some things because they are spoilers
so ah okay then let's go by full package
so by a personality by looks and by
skills
okay then in that case i would put uh
amiyah to a i guess yeah definitely an a
for me
not an ass because she's also very tough
yeah she's not so good as a character as
a
caster i guess so that's why she does
nothing she's still
she still are our best
main girl
now i personally will most likely put
all the main characters
in d ranking or not rank them at all
yeah yeah especially if you still got it
you still got to give them a little
species but 12
f does not deserve anything better than
d
what do you mean he belongs an s what
what i mean
i know you have a really kind heart but
that's like 12 f you really you really
like him that much
but he's i'm pretty sure he's drawn by
only nickelodeon
um
bro what
you you put him in b wow okay your list
is gonna be interesting
mine is gonna be much more obvious i
think haha
now where do we put ten
um as a her personality i'm not a huge
huge huge fan
but she's super strong and her design is
cool i'm gonna put her at a
i mean she's exactly an eraser so
and she has good shorts
good job
yes yes a very a very good design she
does have yes yes yes
uh i think can you um can you scroll
up a tiny bit oh a little bit
yeah it's just a tiny bit more close
a little bit more yeah that's all right
okay
so for me blaze is uh s
yes yeah
uh i also really like uh like the story
around her and uh her looks
and her skills everything her huge
chainsaw are is oh so good
definitely yes yeah no questions
for sora i honestly i really like her
design but i never used her in game
i don't know how to use her i love
everyone from penguin yes
but i've never used you yeah
it's like um i know she's really useful
because she can heal and stuff and she
like dances she's like an idol she
should be in her
life maybe we can make like an exchange
maybe she could be an exchange
exchange student for a whole life
[Music]
please please she's gonna have to go
on a yeah
hey wow i'm gonna put her b
because i just don't use her a for
apple pie's friends
logistics hell yeah then texas i put it
it's just fun to play i for some reason
always
uh before i uh put siege on the field
i would always first put texas there
just because it feels so much better to
activate her skill
you know what i mean also her
her skill is it pairs really well if you
wanna
you know like stun yeah yeah unlock a
yeah mob feels like probably siege i
guess of course is much stronger but
still
texas feels like much more i don't know
fun for me i don't know
[Music]
now why did you put her also an s
you also just love him i told you i'm
biased for thanking those just sex
i i get that i get that now
before i make my decision on exo please
go ahead and place your apple pie
and explain or i guess you don't need to
try it you're gonna make her
you're gonna add an extra
apple oh wait oh oh oh there we go oh no
oh i made a mistake i don't know how
this website works i didn't try this
before
is appleby than s ranking for you
yes interesting of course
is the rank for apple pie and all her
friends
everyone who likes apple pie is above s2
now i think i have to
make a statement here and i hope you
don't hate me for it inna
but i'm not a fan of apple pie
she's she's beef for me
excuse me it's okay i respect your
opinion
but there's there's a reason for that
there's a reason for that please let me
explain everyone don't go crazy don't
don't kill me
so go ahead explain yourself
oh she's super super super good
but my whole life i
the most most of my lifetime i spent
without
exu and i was bonding much more with
other snipers
so such as blue poison so exo
is um i don't know she just came into my
life
so late she's awesome okay super strong
but
didn't re-roll for exo no
no because i i did not re-roll at all i
did not re-roll it up i just went with
what i got
yeah i'm not sure i didn't want to spend
too much time rerolling yeah people hate
me now because i put eggs
okay okay it's okay i can't i mean i
can't tell it's different
i could put her in a for apple pie i
okay okay
she has been uh recently helping me a
lot after all okay okay i'll get i'll
change
it i really do wish the
kfc skins oh yeah global servers
yeah but uh didn't didn't ifray also
have a kfc skin
she does yeah that one looks so good
the ifrit caves actually all of ifrit's
skins look so damn good the barbecue one
oh my god
mm-hmm so good
but will they well maybe maybe we could
we can have kfp
skin wink wink wink
it's basically the same thing
i will i will do my best to bring
the kfc skins into uh
the english server with my power of kfp
i will make an investment with the
investments of my investors and
bring the skins into the en server
i'll do my best yes kfb
kfb kfb
sponsored by kfb oh my god that would be
so funny if it was like
if if you open archdiodes and you buy a
skin and it's like
sponsored by kfb
of course that's not gonna happen but
okay anyway let's move on what about
franco
franco as much as i like her design
i never used her me too and she annoys
me i'm sorry yeah she's also deep for me
you've gone for her c she's kind of cute
actually she deserves a green c she's
kind of cute
she's cute she's cute
for me d is all the men so i'm going to
put her in c
yeah she's super cute her design is cute
yeah
but uh she just spooks me too many times
in gacha
too many times
this time let's go on
um my favorite bitty bitty oh
what i'm gonna have to go with
it's difficult
but you told me something before the
stream that you
only use uh cereal
is that true zarya and korra
go to defenders but why do you do not
own less karma or
like you told me that you just now eat
too toshi
or you're on are you on the way or you
just did it
i just did it oh i'm about to right now
you own this card it's a secret but
i kind of have the game open right now
easing up some saturday
like 12 70 potions that i haven't spent
yet but why did you
choose quora over liz carmen hoshi
that's interesting um i don't know it's
like
i've had quora ever since i've like
started the game so it's kind of like
you know
she's like the comfy pic and she
she was like my go-to
block for you know defender yeah
she's tanky she's eternal you see
i actually got pushy and
really really really early like actually
at the beginning that's why i never used
karora
i know everyone enjoys cora a lot since
she's really strong i get that but i
never used guerra anyway liz karma is
cool and i'm gonna put her in eight
oh my baby i'm not gonna be i'm not
ah yeah silence s
uh you know awesome biased for tank and
logistics
yes it also goes for like oh i
agree everyone in rhinelab goes into
steer
actually i love like all the operators
everyone should be asked here
but like i love you so much she's been
saving my ass with her um
drones yes i love her and i love her
penis
yeah yeah and i was out i was so cute
you know you know how um she gives
feathers to
like people who she cares about you can
see them on their design
like if it has a feather on her zaria
has a
ah what wait i did not know that
you should check it out oh my god i did
not know that
wow that's some deep deep floor you got
there
you know like a little easter egg that
they put out i'm juicing
[Music]
it's like you love the operators and
then you see these like little easter
eggs and you just like you love them
even more
hey i want a feather from silence too
maybe i can
become friends with silence
well i love you silence i love you
[Music]
i don't use her that much yeah but she's
like she is strong
she's like
her designs are so beautiful but because
i don't
use her that much
[Music]
her skin came out on global right ah
oh yeah yeah it came out it did come out
yeah yeah
it was really really nice i liked it she
is
all strong and her design is okay but
i'm thinking of all the other characters
i'm going to put in the higher ranks so
i'm going to put
i don't want to be yeah i don't want to
put too many
in the higher ranks i'm going to be a
bit strict here but i have no problem
with the
guitar at all
oh next is you oh here we are
that's you and obviously you must be
asked here
no i never i never i never use deep
color
never i used to like when i first
started and
i didn't know like i didn't have a
mirror
and then uh maggie
magalan wasn't in the game yet but she's
cute
[Music]
she's cute and she's like basically
me in game literally
quite literally what is she are you in
game
i don't want to put her down low either
dear ea
[Music]
yeah and there's better options to be
honest but
i guess i've seen videos of people using
deep color
pretty well i was like wow she
she can do her job well
but some of the summer characters are
really fun to play around with like
the knots that you've already cleared i
wish i had like
i would uh i wish i could
use them more but i never really like i
always end up using the same team you
know
i never really expected yeah steve
but like using someone characters like
when you're bored
it's like big brain strats yeah i've
seen people
like clear like stages with just her
yeah or or for example also with mcgowan
right
with rocky too next is shishiro botan
senpai's mother
have you seen those memes like uh siege
and silverash
made a baby together and oh yeah it came
out
it does look like it it does but also
actually i saw a fan art of shishido
botan senpai today and to me it looked
like schwartz
she also looks similar to schweinsteiger
there's some uh
similarities there yeah really cute
design
but anyway uh botan by his mother
why do we put her yeah i put her in
a i use her very often
me too me too but i i'm not uh
i like her she's super good but no
that's just not the special something
that
i need a car uh that operator needs to
catch my
attention yeah but she has such good
thighs
[Laughter]
i like her fluffy hair it looks really
cute i don't like her ears i want to
touch the ears
right there
yeah my papa knows archetypes but he
told me he doesn't play archdance
unfortunately but he probably doesn't
have time you know archdiocese is so
time consuming
you gotta play it every day if you're
gonna play orgasms you gotta play it
every day but unfortunately i haven't
really been
playing it every day recently i have
sinned
my sanity keeps on filling itself up
again and again
i'm so ashamed me and my 12 sandy poses
right now
i used to like really play every single
day
from like in the morning and before i go
to sleep but since
uh i joined hello live there's no time
right ina
[Music]
well but maybe maybe we can get back
into it once everything calms down yeah
what about simon yeah
i used to use her a lot but really
yes i still use her a lot on
on uh the chinese servers but
um her her skin that just came out with
the currency
oh that looks good yeah that's a good
skin i love it
but currently she's not
very high up for me because i don't use
her as much there's better
than cartoons yeah yeah me too i put her
in c because um
also because she came so late to me and
i didn't need her anymore
when i got her i already got you know
texas siege
and so on so yeah she never really stood
out to me unfortunately
but i guess she's good she's probably
good
b for bear yeah you're so nice
to these operators my my list is going
to be very top heavy because um are you
gonna put anyone
in d are you gonna put any operator in
these
oh we'll see maybe i'm excited for that
i want to see anything
you don't like maybe
instead of d i should put operators i do
not have
ah but even for operators that i would
not have i i
partially i would still like rank them
pretty high if i like their design
i'm a bit biased so murr
she's cute i actually she was like the
first
um killer unit that i got
me too when i started yeah i relied a
lot
uh on her in the beginning so i'm gonna
put her in me
she's cute she's small she's cute
you'll also be okie dokie i have to say
i used her for such a long time until i
got meteorites
she's awesome she's she's a for me
i will have to agree with you
okay i thought for a second you're going
to disagree with me on this one i
thought
you don't like that that's what i was
going for that would have been shocking
you disliking impossible impossible
i like their artists a lot too so
they're the same one who drew shaw
the rock god yeah
it's really useful if you don't have a
better operator that does the same thing
so i remember she safely bought a lot in
uh
the first and then
[Music]
and now
until i got to better operators she was
like uh i put her like in that single
tile like you know that single tile
where nothing is around it
i put her there and she did her job so
well
good job chelsea ah
do you say hi biscuits hi biscuits right
hi disgusted
how are you disgusting obviously she
deserves a higher rank because i think
she
healed a lot of us for a long time yes
yes
all the all the beginner units they
deserve yeah i put lava there too now
maybe uh uh i like beagle too but
beagle you can already place lava and
beagle island
these two yes i used lava still a lot
like in the beginning me tell me
i'm sorry
it's okay don't feel bad about that she
has a she has a comeback she has a
comeback but i won't say when
but you know what you know beagle uh
beagle and uh fang have the same artist
right
right oh no yes yes i really like that
art style i really like
beagle's design i have to say i really
like it's so cute i like her short hair
with those tiny
uh pigtails and that the way
the the eyes are drawn i really like
that art style so
that's bad but unfortunately i'm not a
big fan
of well
her as a operator on battlefield yeah i
don't i don't use her that much like
like you can get better operators so
much easier
yeah so for example yeah
right unless i'm doing like yeah for
example
unless i'm doing like a challenge run
with like only like three stars
even though i think even then even then
even then i'm sorry bingo you're cutie
good times i still use her from time to
time actually
her her because you know pretty sure her
skin was the uh
the free one oh yeah the was it the
first one was it the first one yeah yeah
yeah the first one
when the server well
okay let's do it together three two one
do we have a delay again again again
three two one
[Music]
is there really a delay okay i count to
three and you count together with me
okay
let's count to three together no i swear
when i hear you is what i'm saying it
it's just discord
there's a deal but that's a huge delay
it's like a how do you call it uh how do
you call that when you sing like a song
and then somebody like jumps in like
but sings the same thing how do you call
those things
that's but that's that's kind of do
i cannot i cannot we did a canon
[Music]
all right oh i mean obviously right
if i asked her where she wanted to be
placed she'll be like
why why were you so
almost trying to resist
i mean my number one sniper is way up
here i've heard her since the very
beginning
so i never really used coco taio ah
wow i still love her that's that's how
how spoiled
you end up when you get extra ti from
the beginning huh
i mean you don't roll for your
you don't reroll for your best wife move
no since the beginning
how about you i didn't rainbow at all i
was lazy i just wanted to be is that
your love
could you say that's true love huh
how much is lazy just a side note um i
did get
actually like really early so i didn't
real
especially on the chinese server oh
wow i got her from the very first draw
and i was like this is true love
wait on which server server on the
chinese server you got her from the
first yeah like damn down
down that's lucky wow
on the english account you have how many
times did you rewire
yes yes good answer
yes all right uh
uh me meet your what let's meet you all
right
yeah yeah always got a mixture mixed up
with media right
with your media right but this one is
media not media right right okay
i don't care about her
i don't care i did use her a bit in the
beginning besides from x2
but i still don't use her enough to be
put in a
yeah but i love i love her i love her
art though
like i love everyone yeah don't you love
all the artwork
i do it pays me to rank them
honestly i'm sorry we have to go through
this together
it's okay okay estelle
um i have estelle but i never used a
style but she looks cool her design is
really interesting honestly i have to
say it stands
out a lot in art nights yeah yeah yeah
she's beautiful do you use her
no i like her design but that's not good
enough for me
i i guess if i had experience with her i
would probably rank her higher but since
i have no idea how she actually
works just another guard there's too
many guards
too many coordinates
i'll say b i'll give her a chance in a
bit after i
finish leveling my main teeth okay i'll
play around with everyone
about teleps's tea applesauce i don't
even have to say
anything obviously s tear
right left hell yeah
yeah such a wife was such a top tier
rifle
oh my god yes and her
she's just such a good healer i usually
always use um salads and syllabuses
together so i always use a single target
uh silent and then aoe healing i use two
lapses
which is my to to go with combination
what about you for healers who do you
always use
sorry i'm glad wait
sorry is your killer okay i guess i
guess
but wait you also said that saria is
like
your defender with kawara she has a lot
to do on your side huh
she has so many jobs sorry it's also
dpst you know
yeah it's just everything
yeah that's dad you don't use balance
or like sometimes sometimes sometimes if
i need
like like long range healing
i bring her i think it's that the best
combination
otherwise zarya sorry it does the job
i love your telopsis another owl can't
have enough oils
yay burps bears
bears are good yes blue poison s-rank
for me
because she was with me from the
beginning actually
she was in my first poll i think
i love it she's an elder and a surname
that's right
you don't use her either sometimes
[Music]
she's so cute she'll be in a yay
the good thing is like she's almost
almost an aoe sniper
okay not wrong i guess she's a double
sniper
because she can hit uh two targets at
once she's really useful
i really really like uh blue poison
she's always
always on in my team always i don't
think there was a day where she was not
on my team
unless i could not doesn't she have
thought damage yeah
is that the right word i think it's
smaller damage
it all blurs together when you play
multiple streamers
arch damage that's what i wanted to say
yeah she does damage
so uh in combination with uh with a
normal sniper
i think it's really good to have like an
arts damage sniper she can like really
help the team with that especially also
if you can't use a caster or something
she she would be useful on the field
anyway let's move on doberman
sorry i don't ever really use her
wow i did not expect you to rank her
down low but okay sam
same as me i'm sorry well it's cause
like
imagine if you are in
you are in rhodes island yeah and then
you have doberman like always
being government yeah yeah she kind of
gets forced onto you
yeah so you stay in the very very very
very very very very beginning
of course because what else could you
use nothing but
yeah i used to not oh yeah
[Laughter]
i'm sorry i wonder if there's anyone who
like really chooses to use dopamine even
though they could have
everything else would you still use
doberman then i wonder if there's such a
person
i'm sorry nobody i'm sorry
i [\h__\h] i forgot the name of the next one
you know it
the flame bringer see i don't i don't
care about
you yeah he's for
he's in g for me um i don't know
i'm gonna put him at
he looks good i have to say he looks
good his design is awesome but i
i i don't in my team no no men
belong in my team except for ash
and even even for him with hesitation
because first of all he makes everything
too easy but you know i'm a lazy
lazy phoenix so i don't mind having it
too easy but
yeah second of all he's a guy but so
that's why i hesitate but i mean
it's so hard to not bring him with you
especially in the later chapters
episodes like uh it's just
he's the only guy i can bring to anyway
i think next one is may was it may
it's may right i think it's me
i think it's me
the chat can confirm
i think yes may okay
i like her design a lot i never used her
but because of her cute
ass design and that
cute smile and that cute gun i'm gonna
put her in b
you're gonna put her in a oh did you use
her yeah
not as much but she reminds me of me
oh i wouldn't have thought of that but
i can sell
if it obviously
is obvious
burn
[Music]
barbecue time
my effort
yeah ifrit is just so much fun to use
when you can use her it's just so much
fun
and i like her personality i like her
design
everything is perfect about her her
extra skins are also
perfect she's funny i like her
her angry face she definitely needs like
a certain map to really shine though
because
of her attack range but do you know
that feeling when you like you open a
new map and you're like
can i use it forever
just put her back in yeah always looking
for a spot for it
i just wanna put her in every map as
much as possible
the effort lane oh yeah i know
however i must say i don't have a such a
good eye for the different lane like
often i don't
realize that unless it's really obvious
but
often it's like oh you can use ifrit
here you should use ifrit here like i
get these advices and i'm like
really yeah i guess i guess i can
i think whatever it was what's it
[Music]
or was it the was it the granny event
where there were like that one map or
it's just like
if it's oh
because there was like a giant line that
you could put her down
i know what you mean yeah i guess it's
the granny event chad says
yes oh that's so nostalgic already i
missed the granny event
but i think i think it just came back on
the cn server right
yes yes is it rotating and granny's skin
is coming out in chinese surface oh yeah
i think i saw it and scotty finally got
a new skin oh my god
oh my god oh my god oh my god scotty
everyone waited for it for so such a
long time anyway
let's move on hoshi to me she was with
me from the beginning she goes to us
[Music]
she belongs with chen and her and her
skin
that is not yet on the yan server
however or
is it is it wait it is oh it is just
released
i guess i definitely bought it
so good looking so
handsome oh yes
ho chi please step on me
she's so cool and she was my first uh
uh six star defender
she was with blue poison she was one of
my first
good operators i think i think both i
got like
in the first couple of polls and yeah
yep yep yep good hoshi
her uh shield is very strong
my shield looks really cool too because
it's a triangle yeah
doritos her and
they can go like
[Laughter]
damn nothing can't
my favorite what about bee hunter i
understand
ah she's cute yeah but i don't really
use her
she also goes to b for bear
then i guess you can already move on to
lapland because we don't have anything
to say about bee hunter
love that oh apple pie
apple she is so useful and
yeah oh wait wait um i might have to
alter this a little bit
wait i wanna add one i wanna add one
it's fixed now
how do i how do i add one
here add add a row above
just add it and then you can edit the
title when you get out of there
i can change the color to this oh wait
this is so confusing
did you add one yeah yeah and then you
just you just like click the
the letter and then change yeshu
and s yes
is yes blue poison is yes if it is yes
lapland is yellow silence is oops
balance is yes
and yes the others can ah who she is yes
the others can stay
yes alrighty
[Music]
uh she is she's cute c for cat
i have to say in the beginning i was
kind of lacking good casters
so i kind of was forced to use haze
because i didn't really have anything
else
and i was really hoping that she would
be a good operator so i
i leveled her a little bit but then i
realized oh
she's apparently she's not that good so
yeah i was really hoping the best for
him because i like her design
but yeah i was disappointed
unfortunately
[Music]
yeah as for me and really she helped me
so much during the first dc
she deserves a spot she's like her skill
is so useful because like she doesn't
die
when you use it so so useful
i used her as a boss a player as well
yeah when you use her at the right time
she can save
everything everything
and her design is beautiful yeah yeah
just your normal design also
really looks awesome and her hair
i guess you could also call that a
chainsaw what she's using
is that a chainsaw i guess so
[Music]
chainsaw looking chainsaw characters are
so
cool like the way they go because that
would like butter
what pizza cutter pizza cutter oh there
it
is it's like it actually has a different
name though it's buzz so
what because it doesn't have a chain
so yeah it is i don't know the
difference
let's just go with a chainsaw has chins
wow well it makes that
rip through things but ah
it's just like that rotating thingy
learn something new
there's something new every day
i don't know i just really like red
yes for me it's yes oh for you too
for you too exactly yes
oh she's she's precious yeah first of
all she's insane she
saves my life so many times
she's like just like my oopsie gotta put
her down
yeah yeah indeed me too and she has a
yeah she's the same voice actor as
another character i really like
another game but oh i think
for me most of you who play uh yeah go
ahead
go ahead go ahead my name
to say she is the same voice actor zooey
from crown blue
anyways ah go ahead
for for me red is like a i used to be so
so many times and for the longest time i
really tried
to not use gravel i just always wanted
to go for red but recently i realized
okay gravel
has even though she has less stars there
are times
when you gotta use gravel and not red
even though no matter how much you love
red there's really times where gravel is
useful
and uh red would not be useful which i
think is really interesting even though
red hat so she's five star right
yes so yeah that is five and gravel is
four oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah so that that's i think is a good
example
for generally for arc nights like uh
you don't need to have a full team of
six stars or whatever
lower tier operators are just as useful
or it can even be more useful partially
as for example
uh in the if you compare red with gravel
there are times where gravel is more
useful and she's a four star you can
easily get gravel
that that's a really a good thing about
actually she comes
yeah she comes really easily with the uh
the recruitment
yeah exactly that you will not have a
hard time getting here
and uh that just proves how arc knights
is totally playable
even if you're not willing to put in
money why am i promoting arc night so
much right now
free promotion this this stream by the
way is not sponsored it was just our
choice because we both love acknowledged
it's not sponsored
okay we gotta make this clear it's
really not sponsored i just really love
art nights
i did too i've been waiting for it since
it was like
um what's it announced back in like 20
years yeah you told me
they're waiting a long time by the way
can i be worth the wait
cask in the chat uh who who is not
playing the game currently
please raise your hand who does not
uh who does not play archetypes because
i think right now there's a lot of
people playing arc nights
me me
i guess there's a bunch i if you like oh
we never really explained what kind of
game this is
it's a tower defense game for the
smartphone
but it's like a really really good tower
defense game there's so much more behind
it it's the best power defense game i've
ever seen
and the only phone game that really
attracts me personally
and uh it also has a dark uh really good
story
deep lore and you you can't really like
read the story for hours and hours not
get sick of it if you like stories you
can also just skip it if you don't like
stories
and anyway there's so many waffles as
you can see it's just a really fun game
and it gets it gets so
difficult it gets so goddamn difficult
you need a lot of principles and it
keeps on getting updated as well
there's a lot of events like there's
basically almost always there's an event
happening so it's really fun you never
get sick of uh you never don't have
content
yeah you're always busy anyway let's
stop promoting
[Laughter]
okay where were we yeah and we have
another mofo mofo character
i forgot the name province
ah probably the biggest tale in art
nights
[Music]
yes keep her away so let's put her in
just kidding just kidding
[Music]
but did you use her before i didn't
not that often i used her before but
as i said i had my apple pie with me
since the beginning
did you see her new skin the skin is so
good
yeah the silver skin yeah it made me
like her much more so actually let's put
her in a
shining oh i must say shining has made
the best transformation in arc nights
with the skin like
oh my god it's like a different person
yes
there's actually a time when i sometime
around the beginning
when i started playing the game i had
shining myself
but i saw someone else play the game
and they were using shining skin and you
know when
you only see the icons when you're on
the battlefield and i saw like
a video of someone playing that was
shining but she
with the skin and i was like who is that
operator i don't know the operator looks
so good even just
i need her yeah and then i was told oh
it's the skin for shining and it's like
it looks so damn good oh my god so
sexy yes those ties oh
yummy thanks
so i'm gonna put her in as tear because
she's hot
she's so hot oh she's not she's hiding
she's hiding those powers under those
i don't know those lumps sorry
but like if you if you have shining and
you don't let her
wear the swimsuit skin then what is
wrong with you i don't think such a
person exists
even oh anyway calm the hell down
people keep telling me i belong to the
bottom left again
why why bottom left i'm cultured yes
cultured
uh everyone is a doctor of culture
okay i have to calm down please go on uh
you know where are you gonna put
no or do you have something to say about
china
no i agree with you i'm shining
[Laughter]
ah nero though i don't use her that much
but i love her design she was
one of the first designs i've seen like
back when i said
i like when i first saw arc knights be
announced in 2017
she caught my attention oh my god and
she got me interested you know what i
just noticed
we still have something special i know
let's hurry up a little bit yeah we
always just spent an hour
oh my god oh dear oh my god
[Music]
i have to say i'm gonna put her in a
because she's cute and i used her a lot
in the beginning until i got zarya
what was her name again what's her name
again
[Music]
it didn't either that much oh our design
is cool
oh by the way guys we can we're probably
gonna stream uh
another hour so it's not like we're
ending right away
hurrying up because we still got a whole
lot to go oh my gosh
cool all right i know where you're gonna
put cool around yeah
my bestie yeah i'm sorry she's probably
really good i'm sorry but i just
never used her so also visually she's
not so appealing to me so
yeah i'm sorry cute with her face
oh yeah yeah she's cute oh yeah i'm
sorry okay
for me i for a long time i tried
to resist using her because
once you get used to using her you can't
go back yeah exactly
exactly now i really enjoy using her so
she's like a battery she's just like all
these points yeah
except when you forget that like her
skill like lets
the mobs pass and you're just like oh
let's press her skill and then like
everything goes past and you're just
like oh no
oh no what have i done yeah
she's really cute really useful and some
in such some situations
especially in the newest stages or
events or whatever
there's it's hard to clear the stages if
you don't have a model
yeah actually
she's cute have i personally her e2r is
so cute
i like her huge flag so for india i have
to say no
i don't love indra what you don't love
india you do love india
i don't have india yeah i also still
don't have her
why honestly i've been trying so hard to
get her even though i don't want her
just to
for the sake of completion but she just
doesn't come
yeah i'm gonna put d as
i nobody has you
and she goes here i don't have to it's
like
if they're if there is
any way an operator is in the gotcha
pool then i can get them but
she's just basically more orangey
yeah than gotcha she's unobtainable
indra is a myth the chat says
uh firewatch yeah
actually i quite like her a lot oh she
has an interesting design i must say
but as an operator
yeah i like her operator too i like when
she goes and then goes
you know what i mean right i know i know
i know
but still next is vulcan right vulcan
she also goes in the i don't know if you
can go actually i don't remember if i
have her i just don't use her
nightmare she's cute i like her
she's soft yeah but i don't really use
her
oh oh the obvious
she's interesting i'd like to use her um
more
because her she's just interesting as a
character
but yeah unfortunately i always end up
going with my two gold casters
so yeah sad skyfire
fire please inferno last year
sorry almost like her that much i didn't
have
air for a really long time at me too
this is so many times
same time and she shares the same voice
actor as
another character yeah
chad knows who i'm talking about
i got her at a point where i already had
every every other heel that exists so
she was absolutely useless to me
but i love her design i love her she's
another sp batter but i don't use her
that much just like uh
but she's like yeah she's like a battery
but i don't use her as much to give her
enough price yeah to be in an e
is a guy but he's very good so i'll give
him
the a rank exception mate for
mr schwing swing the father of shishido
botan senpai
i have to put him in s for shrinking
it's okay
i i understand it feels like um
you're like one rank
nicer to everyone than me know what i
mean
like the the people you put in s rank i
put an a
the people you put in a i put in b kind
of like that
you're more kind towards everyone
cliffhard
[Music]
i'm biased for their family yeah the
rash family
but as i said i don't use them that much
but their designs are all so unique and
beautiful
so ram next for me
is uh probably both a
for me perhaps this is s because she's
so
soft and fluffy and her tail ah and
she's so elegant
i just wish i could use her more because
i i just never have the opportunity to
use her i have her levels
but there's just no opportunity to put
her in my team
i want strategy everywhere
can someone make a youtube channel that
is like about
putting praminix in your team and every
map possible
i wanna like copy that because i'm sure
there probably already is
really probably i mean
game has been around for like over a
year now so i'm sure people
you know nightingale a lot of meme
yeah pretty nice oh decent healer
beautiful beautiful design
i bring her everywhere really
for me my uh i used a nightingale until
i got tea applesauce
because uh tea applesauce for me was
just like a huge upgrade because of the
sp battery but nightingale is of course
super
super good in certain situations you
might want to use nightingale over
her cages are very useful
true actually let me put her in ass rank
now ass
volcano the girl
who deserves a new skin but the flowers
never get one
i want to see a new skin for aya
yeah i think everyone does
ever ever get a new skin ever
i don't know i saw uh some fan-made skin
once and i got bamboozled and i thought
that was like an actual official skin i
was like what finally
but i was wrong
got me there perfume
perfumer was perfume or perfume
perfumer getting confused here yeah i
think it's perfume error
yeah that's my first aoe healer me too
yang i think
for most people is the first aoe mm-hmm
she deserves some credit um
me too a easy f spirit
no
[Music]
no no thank you
i use her sometimes so i'll put her
the thing is i have someone better for
magic
art damage cards so this is useless to
me
yes gabrielle is that how you say it
gabrielle i think so i like her color
palette she's so green
uh she had an event in the the chinese
server pretty
soon which was i i played it i played it
i tried it out
it was good eh didn't she get a little
bit
uh well she has a skin too yeah
yeah but i still don't never used her so
i'm sorry gabriel
she's a soft spot in my heart
i never know how to say his name is it
hella girl holliger
hello hello girl that's how i see it
hello he's
he can be very useful so i put in
silver ash and him are like the only
operators that i'm not gonna put in here
i mean it's also also the same artist as
short
i love their art so i'm biased
very funny what about small tiny vermeel
she's so
she's so tiny and cute but i don't use
her so i'm sorry cute but a loser
i'm always biased with snipers because
i've had
axia since the start so i barely used i
understand that's
here yeah yeah
a soft spot in my heart too yeah because
she's been with us
at the beginning and her desire is
really nice like
her little cape on one side yeah it's so
fashionable
it's really fashionable also i like her
her hat i like hats so i like her hat
too
frost leaf i love frost leaf i love her
design
she's cute yes her personality i like
too
as an operator she's also not bad she's
not bad
i don't use her as much as the others
but i still love her side
okie dokie we are on the same page here
for once
i don't use her that often oh indeed
yeah yeah
but she's cute i like her i used her
until i got
until i got angelina i used istina yeah
i have a
i had angelina pretty early too so
i'll put her with her friends be for
bear she's cute
[Music]
good no definitely ate for me actually
oh
her summer skin is really cute and she
was one of my
earliest thunders that i used quite
often before i got zarya so
it wasn't wasn't she uh a healing
defender
if i remember correctly yeah yeah and
you can get her from the shop i
alright oh that's so lovely
[Music]
those memories
she's really cute i like her hairstyle
and it looks yummy when
all those with that candy in her hair
she's cute and i did use her in the
video
i don't know if you remember but there
was a arc night's video contest
a while ago like fan video contest
there's this one
um one video about
gummy and um i believe it was like a
shout out to
what you'll call it rhythm heaven pretty
sure that was really cute
sorry people are commenting on how
casually i put
courier in the deed here without saying
a word i just put him there
i know he's a super super awesome
vanguard but i had the best vanguards
from the beginning
so i never needed career and he's a guy
so i'm so sorry but i don't care about
courier
his skin is so cute though
mata jacket big fan do you like a
hatterhorn then
ah sorry i don't use it i'm sorry
i'll put them sort of sort of close to
actually
um
okay for the memes i'll put him near his
his friends
you're so kind
you're so kind that's so sweet of you
i told you i love them all like it's
hard to rank them honestly
it's okay i feel you i feel you but i'm
still very strict
er wait do you say c.o.b or glb
which one
until i heard her voice line i was
always so comp
confused about how you say her name
where would you put her she recently
came out on the ian server she's very um
i guess she deserves s-rank yeah she's
pretty damn good
but i have not i don't know much about
her yet since she's so new
yeah nian however is so hot
oh my god oh yes
yes nian oh you put her in apple pie
ranking how did she deserve apple pie
ranking
her voice actor wow that voice actor
really has a lot of um
effect on you huh
she is a really good voice actor and it
fits her character really well and
i use her quite a bit too so see i
always still use saria and hoshi
and if i didn't have hoshi i guess nian
would be my two gold defender
because she can also like for the people
who don't know she can
up everyone's uh block
the block plus one for everyone on the
field when you activate the skill
that is amazing really cool skill
animation too
she is awesome but i just don't use her
2r is like so crying like
oh yeah she's really really really good
i pulled a lot from her i pulled
a lot croissants
i like i don't use her that much
i don't use her that much where sora
i'll put her beside sora so she's not
lonely
sorry i think we don't have to talk
about why sarah
is top tier rifle don't think we have to
talk about this at all
sorry i can't go anywhere without flaria
now i'm interested in what you think
about platinum though because
i personally love platinum
i love platinum her design everything is
good but
as i said i had apple pie
but did you see platinum's new skin on
cn server yeah
she's beautiful it's like like a greek
goddess
or something but she's not apple pie
okay it's okay but she's still beautiful
so she's so beautiful she belongs to you
she's so beautiful and i just like her
personality too she's like really like
the quiet uh serious type
oh melanza our savior our lord and
savior
bill menachem where do you put her
here esther and wow
the only thing that i don't like so much
about her is
she seems bored like she
yeah uh like she's not really but her
skin her skin
is so cute i also don't like her
design that much the new design i really
like the new skin i like a lot but her
main design but she's of course
saving all our asses she's a free star
for the people who don't play the game
she's a free star so she's basically a
free to play unit
but she is such a good guard that
you could like honestly you could go on
so long with her without using five
stars six star whatever
as long as you have melanchol you're
safe
yes
a cardigan no we still have a lot to go
kiara yeah
i i'm gonna go quickly through the next
three so cardigan no cardigan
i forgot the name
these two i don't use that much you're
still so nice to them
b really b okay
i have a soft spot for like the beginner
like for you to play
absolutely ansel that was a different
question oh ansel don't
he deserves a little bit oh really
because i actually used him until
politely
i'm ruthless people tell me i'm ruthless
it's okay
this is just i'm when it comes to my
operators i have a
really strict distinct distinction of
who i like and who i don't care about so
much
yep yep it's very clear in my head i'm
sorry
but now we come to someone very special
oh sorry she has already on the board
you already put her yeah
and she's your favorite right no
second favorite second ah i also really
like mostly ma a lot
she's mama mizuki like her
uh design i like her skill i like her
damage i like her
in-game animation i really like that
effect when she activates her skill and
it goes like
and everyone just falls back and again
and everyone falls back again it's just
so much fun to use that
yeah the clock the clock the blueberry
pie to my apple pie
no all right mandicore
i will rank her pretty high because i'm
a fan of mandacorp
steam oh oh
for me she's even in the in the
yesterday
yeah yeah yes
manticore is better she's
uh unfortunately there's not so many
times where you really
need her except actually the the the
last is
the the first cc the zero
cc was it zero or minus minus one
is there minus one zero and minus one am
i being confused here
but the very very first one that we had
their manticore was really useful but
you know there's really
really not many times where she's
actually useful unfortunately but i wish
i could use her most
useful in some of the maps in chapter 6.
it's called cc beta
i think yeah i used her there with my
strategy i think
a lot of people did everyone use
manticore and
in the first cc i didn't
you didn't hey i'm interested in your
strategy
who did you use i kind of i kind of
brute forced it though
oh i did edit the usual strat with um
f eater what's vector feeder yeah
[Music]
but i i did that too but i added a
manticore to that
i guess you used it with angelina huh
i can imagine there is really uh
not much else you can do
all right let's move on i'm a fan of
meteor right i like me too right
same same thing i use it quite a bit
actually
more than i thought i would yeah but
she's not like
s here she's probably eight
it feels good to use her she has a
really long range aoe sniper
upgrade to shirayuki really really
awesome character i like her design too
so she gets quite the high spot for me
and granny
huge horse granny likes apple pie too
actually
what what granny likes apple pie
well i'm not going to play her she likes
okay the next ones are no and no thank
you and savage
almost no yeah but oxides
yes he hurts you
think about it ina he hurts you
average there's nothing good about
him i like his design
and he's like me material
i'm not a big fan at all
probably see sorry i don't ever yeah
when he when when that banner was going
on
it was like how many lungs can you get
five hundred a thousand i'm trying to
get in yeah
too many jessica oh you're still at
savage
oh where'd you put sandwich i put her in
c
uh yeah i don't use her her design
is amazing but her as an operator
yeah i'll be honest i have no idea what
she does
because that's everything oh she's
another guy she's once again
a guy and we
can have like a bit more than half an
hour i think we're good on time right
now okay
well it should be yeah we should be okay
so next is crap baby jessica
she's so cute i love her skins and i
love that that
that fat huge like suit that she has as
a skin
it's so funny oh yes yes like they're
hiding her completely it's so funny i
love it
i love it s for sad cat yes
and rope
oh her new skin is cute her summer skin
is cute
which is not available on end by the way
she has a halloween one right
yeah i don't use her as much though
sorry sorry it's okay
gravel i have recently found uh my love
for gravel because i have
to admit she is as i said before
better than red in some situations so
yeah
she's pretty good and we're gonna get
the skin soon
oh yeah that would be good she deserves
it
she's a good a good waifu a very good
bible
vanilla i like her design that's about
it yeah i like good design but as i said
i don't
use her that much yeah yeah oh i've
never really used her honestly
don't feel bad about it don't be bad at
me sorry
i kind of actually now i feel sorry
about vanilla
i like her i like her
she can like get higher here f eater
that design easy those huge easy uh
gloves it's such a well designed option
yeah
i love it she's funny as a character too
and she's so useful
uh yeah useful in
in the current cc as well
maybe also in the future ccs i don't
honestly don't know but
[Music]
you have definitely a character that you
should try to get
she she will actually maybe not you can
also use shaw i guess
for most cases quote-unquote
gloves
[Laughter]
she's a panda cute kung fu panda
anyways ma'am mirror i never used mayor
i wish i could i really like your design
so
yeah almost implies
and i love others i forgot i forgot the
name for
the next one what was the name you
remember oh my god
waifu
we're doing a list for her right now
right
how did i not think of it her name is
w-a-a-i space
foo interesting huh is she
your waifu no no actually not at all no
i'm sorry i'm sorry
what about you also a little biased
i love her design her e2 art is
absolutely beautiful
oh i don't even remember it
maybe i never even check it out
afterwards
now now the names are escaping me
completely
[Music]
i thought it was megalith here is it is
it madeleine or magellan
i just call her maggie maggie
do you use her though i never used her i
really like her design
my hands are more than the others for
sure
her design is amazing
and like when i when i see her i can
just imagine her in like a really
really like wide open like snowy field
with her penguins doing her like
research
yeah adorable
just a cutie and she's a penguin and
penguin is apple pie
oh you did put her in apple pie here wow
wow so cute oh
is it great gray is next right great i
put him in d
instantly i told you
i told you i told you
i'm gonna have to put in that seat
because i've never really used it
i'm sorry great but those cute doggle
eyes when they look at you
yeah i mean he's useful in the
infrastructure
and where in the generator
dunnar i never use her but i know i
heard that she's a really good defender
she's a free start
what was she freestyle for i think
freestyle
but she's a really good freestyler
is your three i forget let's ask the
chat a four uh it was four
okay she's a really good four star
defender as far as i know
and i like her design so she's just
gonna
i mean she can be in b but i don't use
her that much
yeah okay
er i love her
so much too so much
she's hot i love her design oh my god
literally hot
it's like really hot i love her design
but i don't use her
so but she has this huge lens right
um it's so cool i like characters with
lenses
i love her artists work but
i don't use her so i'm sorry
i got her i i uh with who was she on the
banner again
broker ah oh really
oh you're gonna put a scouting apple pie
yeah i'm going to put her below that
i lost her i lost her dashes
she's cute good very good guard i love
how she
swings like like she almost turns around
completely it's like who's golfing
she's a good golfer and finally
scotty received a new skin finally
congratulations on your new skin i'm so
proud i'm so happy
yes she deserved it and everyone was
waiting for it so i think everyone
bought it on the cn server at least
i did first thing i did now
i love anastasia i can tell you so much
she's so beautiful i love her artist
eugene she's so pretty
it's actually strong yeah and she's a
bird she's a bird like me
those those feathers around here is i
also have feathers around my ears i love
us dancing
oh my god did you see her your skin is
so elegant so
yeah oh so cute i'm just so happy
let's protect for that yeah
well i'm just so sad that people don't
like
like in the chat people are appreciating
her right now
but generally i feel like people don't
appreciate anesthesia they don't give
her attention and that makes me sad
more more more justice
i i don't use her i
don't i don't like her neither but i
like her design
so she's like a high b oh
no hi b oh an a
a don't use her you're gonna give her an
a but i love her design that much
[Music]
i think i saw her e2 design
it looks really good sure
i think we don't have to talk about
where xiao belongs to
rap god belongs where i've got belongs
that was very awesome i'm glad we agree
on that inna
i'm glad yes i think actually it tastes
good when we look at your
s rank and uh the top apple pie and my
yes rank
they're quite similar actually we have
some similarities there
yeah yeah good taste good thank you to
you too
orchid i like her design but um
she was replaced very quickly by other
players on my side yeah he's got me
next to the guy so goodbye
[Laughter]
but he's good i know he's i know he's
really good yeah yeah
i know he's really useful too but i'm
sorry i have my
you know my rules
[Laughter]
hi wait where's the
[Music]
she's like a baby version of spectre
yeah i don't really use her i'm sorry
yeah
oh she's she's really cute but she gets
a b for being a baby
a catapult
she's okay a good aoe sniper
if when you don't have anything else
she's not bad
and i think she's faced i say i'm a
bias for a sniper oh yeah
very biased so it's hard for me
hard to please me if you're a sniper
i'm putting all the guys in the in the
lowest rank right now you go ahead and
[Music]
i don't really use him i'm sorry
oh the robots though
wait wasn't one of them it wasn't the
the the
the the guard one was a guy
like a voice was a guy right okay
[Laughter]
bye-bye
i have to say uh the the castle one
i do i did use a lot so i appreciate
that one but the other
robot uh i never used that did you ever
use the card
yes i do
really when i need like a bait for
something
and i have extra slot yeah yeah
okay kiara if ace was an operator where
would you put him
oh d all of them are indeed
the only one that was able to escape
this
fate was silver ash and heliger for
being
hot and useful but it's raised
wow i'm sorry we won't spoil it for
people but
my toy
yeah me too there's just you know when
you have lapland
um what else do you want in your life
besides lapland
vinya i love vinya she's so dope i don't
use her
but i wish i could use her i just don't
need her but i wish i could use her
see the one who said fbi opened up
during the
obsidian festival i don't even remember
that
but i'm pretty sure it was her
love her yeah and her skin and she's
actually a good
vanguard she's a good vanguard
so uh oh angelina is next
angelina jolie i think obviously
is a little apple pie for you for me
at s-rank she has been very useful for
me
recently but to estrang
her new skin oh my god please come to
ian now it looks so good
so good that all those belts around her
body should make me want to open them up
big fan over artist as well
that's the good stuff oh i forgot one
guy
[Music]
i forgot one guy
now he is where he belongs to embryo
i don't use her but she she has an
adorable design
dude do you use ambree she's like kelly
she runs
true yeah but she has that she has a
halo and the cali does not have a halo
definitely cali
does not have a halo
this little wait did you put this on the
dude
section oh wait it's a girl of like i
forgot
[Music]
impressed i um
i mean okay can be in c it's okay
i love lace lazy her design
her uh i love her
is good yeah the that look how do you
even call it electric
electric magic stuff
i love her what was she she was like a
kitten right yeah
when when she was on the banner with uh
kyobi
i actually wanted lazy more
than kyovi even though everyone of
course preferred klb but i
designed wise and skill wise and
everything i just i don't know why but i
have
i'm like she's my type she's so my type
she's hot
sorry i'm going so much my lips actually
she's so same kind of oh and now we have
a spoiled
brat uh to judge but i like her
even though she's a spoiled brat i think
she's funny sam
as a character and a character i love
her
but but do you usually use her but she
belongs here with her friends
yeah i think story wise she needs to be
higher
she needs to be at least an s rank she's
funny
she's a good character but uh chemistry
with uh
chen is great i love it one of my
favorites
yeah i like their the way they talk with
each other
and glaucus i actually like glaucos uh
quite a lot wait you speed up skills
oh i already put all the men where they
belong to i'm sorry
i already skipped enough to put him
beside his friends
[Music]
is definitely a or she was a free star
right yes isn't she freestyling nope
before four or five no no she's not five
stars she's not five star
what what five yeah she's funny she's
five star what
what's up really she has like that's
really cool like
why did i think she was free star
are you mistaking her for someone else
no they have similar artists or
something
no yeah
well i'm shook but she's good she's good
that's why i ranked her quite high for
my
standards yeah
and she's
that is like god tear design skill wise
she's amazing she's strong
she's useful and she's hot she's really
really hot
a sexy cat i must say
you my real feelings
um actually the tea lady you're gonna
put her in apple pie
what she's use
excuse me she's only useful for that one
event
i know but but her design is beautiful
like her interactions with shorts is
what
i really like you know
and they are precious and i want to
protect them
[Laughter]
fans gonna hate me for being so ruthless
and just being honest you have all the
dudes down on these
you didn't even keep them please don't
hate me i love arc night so much you
don't even know
but but i'm just really like strict with
who i like and who i don't like
i'm sorry
oh no please don't hate me
[Laughter]
okay it's okay every doctor has their
favorites
great bro wait i still have to go oh
please do you think i really like his
designs and effects
especially his e2 or
brooka he's just
anybody too
now we are at the same spot again nice
and
grateful i liked her story arc but um
actually
i like her design but her attitude in
the story i did not like
mm-hmm i got it yeah
i don't want to spoil but yeah
beautiful yeah probably i see she she's
beautiful but she doesn't leave an
impression
to me actually she left a bad impression
to me with her personality
yeah but i mean it's good i think
honestly it's really good
uh that in the story there's like
characters that are not enemies but you
still like kind of
like they all have their own personality
right
i like how not everyone just has a basic
normal
standard personality but there's like
you really
you really see like the differences in
the characters
and it really plays out in the story
like you see how they interact with each
other
and it really shapes the story so with
grapefruit i must say
she's um not such a nice girl
but that's a girl's asking for bagpipes
but uh
if she was here where would you put her
i would put her
for being so strong i would put her in s
yes she's not she's like almost apple
pie here because she's like granny's
friend
but s here definitely
when when you activate bagpipes skill
it feels like you're just crushing the
whole
stage oh my god it's it feels so strong
this is so much fun it's so much fun oh
my god i feel like you're destroying
everything so nice
and where are we a snow snow what was it
what us
she's so cute she's cute she's so
adorable
and is originally right isn't she
originally from
like uh the same university
or like she is from rhinelab but now
she's in
uh uh not around
norah everyone is in rhyme lapse or not
in rhinelab's kiara yeah did you know
that
but but wasn't she like isn't she like
related yeah victoria
she she came from victoria and uh
it's all too confusing but
she's poor oh yeah that's adorable
being poor is adorable she belongs in
s-rank for me she's so adorable
no yeah she worked eh
okay i'm confused but anyway she's kind
of like a
the new chick she's a new chick she's a
bird
she's adorable i like her
how shy and
she needs more uh confidence because
she's actually a good
operator yes
thanks kiara absolutely your cookie is
missing too oh
yeah is a it's not called i guess
everyone from that banner yeah
everyone from that time but for some
reason there is this
chick called uh pure stream who is not
in
english i will not put her in the
ranking at all because like i don't
yeah i don't know i'll just say i'll
just put it here
where are you gonna i'm curious where
are you gonna put jiren oh wait you
still have a guy
[Laughter]
i'm sorry but
i don't use you that much huh i mean i
even used 12 f
but i don't understand i will never use
him
no problem she's a b she's so small
she's a sleepy one i don't use her that
much but i've used her before
eh never used her ever ever ever
two-star vanguard right
and now here come uh people that you
cannot play
but are in the story for everyone who
doesn't really notice much
well should we rank them anyway oh wait
did you disconnect law actually
disconnected
what happened
her pc died i think
her pc just turned itself off
i think we gotta wait for her we're
almost done
i'll wait for you take
your time we got 11 minutes
yeah she suddenly got i wonder what she
did did you just kick
the the power button or something to
wait does that mean when she comes back
her
her list is resetted maybe maybe chrome
or whatever she uses does a good job and
keeps it like reload ah actually that
might be
actually it might be lost but i have a
screenshot of it here basically
so she can uh tell me where the rest
would have
gone on her side meanwhile while we're
waiting for her i'll finish my list
er i forgot her name what was it but i
like a design
oh no it's gone it's gone it's gone
inna's side is gone
no oh but she'll be back i think she'll
join
in the end to say goodbye at least ah
crown slayer what the hell how did i
forget that
crown slayer i like w i like where's the
w
w for me no spoiler
but w for me is um actually
yes uh cultit
uh you know the interesting thing about
calcite i know she used to be playable
at least on the cn server but then she
was like so good that even if you tried
to fix how good she was
and she was still too good and then she
was completely deleted out of the game
i never got the chance to play her i
wanted to play her
ah wait
goodbye but for now hey
[Music]
she'll just be here she's huge
and by the way inadina drew this
come back oh she's back
[Music]
i really need to fix this oh don't worry
i think your list is gone but
maybe you can join
back to say goodbye
that's what you mean is back here
so yeah i wish i could play khalsa i i
hope i hope that at some point
they nerfed her so much that you can
actually use her
uh i don't see how how it was i don't
understand how it was impossible to
nerf her like they tried and then it was
still too strong and then
they couldn't nerf her anymore how's
that possible how can you not just not
keep on nerfing her
anyway first nova obviously yes i will
not
spoiler you guys but yes
[Music]
i like her design but then again she's
an enemy
i'll put her and vido for awesome design
being hot
eh wait i forgot the name what was the
name again of this chick
on the story manager another potential
just like me is she back i gotta check
this we should join call on phone
oh oh yeah don't need
and wait then i have to i think i have
to quit that
just call me or should i call you
she'll join me on her phone
just to say goodbye oh
one sec i'll finish my list and then
we'll bring her back to say goodbye
um oh there's only these two i don't
actually
uh she's i don't even remember her that
much and you
okay my list is done i'm sorry guys that
i was so strict
it's not like i i completely like hate
these operas for example for him
executor executor i know he's a good
operator i even used him before
but generally i just like my waifus i
just like female characters so much more
i don't know why
i'm sorry don't be mad at me please i
love ignites
don't hate me i'm just i'm just trying
to make a clear distinction between what
i like and what i don't like so much
and but yeah by the way backpipe as i
said would be
would have been in us rank but she was
not in this ranking anyway
but i guess that's the end oh pc turned
on
i think i can make it
my list is done by the way
too bad that [\h__\h] that we couldn't
finish it together
but yeah i hope you all enjoyed
the the sorting of our waifus it was
nice to hear
you guys's opinion as well
now don't forget cc is almost ending
do your daily missions and stuff and
uh uh what was i going to say
what was i going to say
i don't care much for uttaga
it was a fun stream really yay
yeah yeah you and your boing boings who
is bottom
[Music]
welcome back it's okay you never left
because you were
you were always almost give up yeah what
did you do did you just did it just
suddenly like
shut up i think pc club was shocked that
every
every dude operator was rank d so just
decided to visit kelly again
yeah i'm so sorry oh no problem we were
always
already at the end anyway so i'm just
sad that your list got lost
i think oh i can i can look back on it
and recreate
but i have to say it was fun making this
with you i'm glad that we have like uh
quite a lot of similar interests when it
comes to games and stuff
good taste yeah for example we also
bought like final fantasy 14
so maybe in the future we can do more
archives related streams
yes next time we'll actually play the
game
yeah maybe maybe maybe we'll gotta use
our brains um
my one brain cell yes yeah and me and my
birth brain
we're gonna be a good team you know i
think we're gonna
be a fun time but the sad thing is cc is
ending
so it's kind of too late to stream cc
now
our accounts aren't really ready for
that anyway i think
but maybe maybe the next grind quite a
bit
here's my 12 70 potions isn't the next
event
they kind of uh pushed something
forward now uh what was that that uh
rosa event because rosa is coming
rosa oh rose yeah they
i didn't check the official one yet so i
wasn't sure if that was
yeah the earth is event is coming
there wasn't there was supposed to be a
different event first but they decided
to bring ursus already
they teased it on twitter apparently i
really like rosa that's why i'm quite
excited about that
oh yeah i'm up for that rosa's range is
so awesome it's like so
different you know rosa's range can you
like imagine it
you know it every time i see her
i don't think of anything else but a
certain beverage
yeah vodka
a certain sugary drink is what i'm
thinking of
since she's a polar bear
sugary drink yeah
everyone in the chat is saying vodka
dough and now they're saying
yeah really yeah that's what i meant
that's what i meant
why coca-cola
why you don't know the coca-cola fair
and the commercials
it's a white bear right but it doesn't
look like rosa
is that like her colors
or is that only you it might just be me
but that's what i'm saying she just
reminds me of
certain differences but i guess
i see how you could make that connection
though but
i gotta kind of end this stream quickly
so if you want to say something
please do now uh thanks for inviting me
to the club today it was really fun
you're welcome
thank you for coming i'm so happy to
collab with you
yes yes and i'm sorry pc can come off
no problem near the end no problem try
to fix the problem soon
no problem yes i had fun with you
please everyone subscribe to ina's
channel the link is in the subscription
if you're not already subscribed
and yeah aren't you
doing another collab tomorrow ah yes
today well today depending on your time
alright so check out her channel is it
on your channel
or something it's on everyone's channel
actually maybe simultaneous
all right then i guess everyone can
check that out i will also stream
tomorrow uh
for one hour sometime um at an earlier
time than now
anyway thank you very much for watching
at the end we say in german do you know
what we always say in german
you know oh i said i said
it before but oh
together probably there will be a delay
again but let's say it in
in and one two three and then okay
okay one
[Music]
oh my god i gotta teach you german
sometimes because that sounded so
adorable
i'm always down to learn new languages
all right everyone
see you soon hopefully and i hope you
enjoyed the collab
[Music]
bye-bye
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign