[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
yay
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
yeah let's
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
it
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
psycho
oh
[Music]
bye
is it
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go
[Laughter]
[Music]
is
let's go let's go
[Music]
okay
give me the money magically
[Music]
stop it
i'm i'm
[Music]
okay
go
[Applause]
[Music]
nice job
come on
[Music]
let's
go let's go
[Music]
let's go
come on come on let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
um
oh
yeah that's right
hey look senpai do you like
[Music]
oh good taste good good taste
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh god oh god
oh no
[Music]
okay
yes
[Music]
anyone here
yes a food place
do you guys have food food
um tuna yeah mozeriyo
mate i mean yes i have food one second
[Music]
here's zettachan there you go tuna
ah monday why can't i drop it hold on a
sec here i'll give it to you
i'll give you some tuna
here
yeah here you go
it's for you oh
thank you
you're welcome the problem
is
mama ichi
and
[Laughter]
[Music]
kyoko
oh
[Music]
bye
oh
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
party time
nice
[Music]
it's okay don't cry knock tonight there
not good night
[Music]
okay
it's gonna be daijoubu
[Music]
oh
crazy crazy
[Music]
oh
right
me and fubuki senpai drinking and
gambling together
[Music]
[Laughter]
freeze
[Music]
ah
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
this
[Music]
oh
go
is
[Music]
oh
is
give me a present do you need scratch
okay you're gonna need
more okay
[Music]
here let me toss them out to you
here you go present from puberty i'm
just going to return it to her
afterwards
[Music]
foreign
let's go
okay
is that fauna in the cow thing
[Music]
you think it's five i'll put a little in
five
[Music]
come on
[Laughter]
[Music]
here
yes
[Music]
oh
oh my god
please
[Music]
is
yeah i just wanted to shove this horn
directly onto your wolf snouts
[Music]
give me one
um
[Music]
likelihood of winning to be hired
shut the [\h__\h] up
[Laughter]
thanks to gambling and drinking together
[Music]
even if you have some iced tea and
watercolor
um
yes
[Music]
oh my god if i hear another goddamn shot
out of all of you i swear to god
[Laughter]
shut the [\h__\h] up
[Music]
sorry i'm just
lagging
oh
hello are you shooting at the casino can
you stop please
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah that's a good point other people
are streaming i probably shouldn't use
that for excuse me i'm sorry everybody
else's audience i sincerely apologize
that was not very cash money of me i
will
might have that in my inventory
okay
[Music]
oh
one
peace
[Music]
are you talking [\h__\h] about me out here
oh
[Music]
mmm
oh
[Music]
how much did you give me earlier i want
to give it back
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
party right here
[Music]
okay
thank you
we only have a few hours left on this
side
who are you
[Music]
okay there's another one um
right around here oh thanks ahmed sure
i'll use it i'd love some more scrubs oh
yeah
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
how much how many people do we need for
blackjack oh my god
i don't know where i wonder is the
question
okay i can teach you if you want
pranks
here play
multiplayer
[Music]
hold on i'll just invite people we're
trying to play cards if anyone
needs six people six people
here let me see if just me sitting down
okay
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
dance action
love peace
[Music]
[Laughter]
sounds like our problem i'm having fun
gambling here
in the world
always one no always one
girl
what if i say that to her
[Music]
wow
i shall try to protect you too if she
does that
oh thanks appreciate that kiara
but you have some cards to count sheriff
[Music]
[Laughter]
m
[Music]
what does this one do
get down
[Music]
[Applause]
we're
kicking ass today guys
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
no one won that's the cursed instrument
[Music]
machines
[Laughter]
i made it myself
[Music]
yay
um
[Music]
is
another one
[Music]
kindness baby
with different numbers
[Music]
yay
and then it cuts to this
[Music]
do you need some more i can give you
some
only if you don't need that i'm just
still trying to build my tech tree
yeah sure here let me see i can throw
you a couple to keep gambling
i'll give you a hundred tech tree though
i'm almost done with workbench one but
that's it
let's see oh
yeah i live right next to a recycling
plant
[Music]
oh yeah i'll do that next season here
you go
he goes here
yeah i just want you to keep gambling
with us
i just i
immediately got them back anyways
[Music]
there's a recycling machine close by if
you want to try and make scraps
[Music]
but i think i'd rather gamble
especially
i'm sorry mostly girl i wanted to die
[Laughter]
[Music]
my new favorite band yeah
how can this game be so silly but also
so brutally
[Music]
i'll take care of us
are they actually drinking
yeah i'm having some something
to celebrate
[Music]
[Laughter]
i thought she was drinking sake
[Music]
only special nights
it's a special night
[Music]
is
let's go
[Music]
oh i won't lose
i don't want my tummy to stick out i
could drink a lot of beer
[Music]
[\h__\h] off
oh
peace
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
get out
get out of my swamp
shot probably doesn't even know that
you're talking to them
yeah
all right
ass
holes
outside the casino
aka
peace palace
this is a cocktail palace
yeah it is a peace palace right i'm
gonna make my own someday but for now
this is perfect
yes
can you make your own gamble please
global chat though is there a way we can
do not global chat
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
come on give me something else
uh
yeah it's pretty rare for anything
besides one and three
[Music]
palace
i'll make a stage palace
[Music]
except me sometimes but not
not this time you know you can split
your winnings yeah like so you can
choose
everybody
that's a stupid idea
[Music]
but i would
it's okay you don't have to
there's an accident
[Music]
but then i gave away
707 of it so technically it's
i'll be able to pay her off holy
mackerel
i'm so generous
yeah i just want people to gamble with
me
[Music]
means
peace
[Music]
so you cannot convince me to pick
anything besides one of three
um
yes
[Music]
if you want to play cards there is a
table back here with four seats
if you want to play
anything besides
i don't really know
[Music]
i think both of them need a dealer i
don't know what game is here goddammit
[Music]
anymore i think i have to stop myself
okay all right kiara fubuki senpai and i
will just gamble here yeah i ain't
leaving tonight
[Music]
see you later kiara bye-bye be careful
don't lose your horns
is
[Music]
mama
my
[Music]
back to madness let's go let's go let's
go let's go let's go
is
[Music]
three nothing hey magikarp
how does she
thank you
thank you friends
yes red
[Music]
my mama
[Laughter]
it's okay
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
m
um
[Music]
foreign
many
[Music]
gg
oh
[Music]
um
so
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
okay
what's up
foreign
[Music]
new
foreign
who is that who is that
yes
no
[Music]
oh
um
foreign
[Music]
feel
oh
[Music]
you