[Music]
kitty
welcome back nice to see you again
we're back outside to keep you waiting
because yeah cooper was asking me mommy
mommy why are we gonna continue porto
[Laughter]
sorry i was mommy was busy kobo mommy
was in america my mom was in big big
america to record some stuff
busy busy busy it's okay now we have
time
yeah i think we are
currently at chamber number four
excursion finals or whatever that's
pronounced as
um i hope we can finish the game today
but cooper said she can play
maximum three hours
so we will see
we'll see we'll see we'll try our best
okay
yes
uh also do you remember how to play the
game kobo
maybe let's see
uh
perfect perfect
okay i'm orange and i'm big and you're
blue and you're let's go
the color and the size right
right i forgot it was just perfect
nice
nice nice i never expected you to make
it this far glad
to build this new course just for you
why thank you
you two have become extremely close oh
i'm not sure i like that
yes he's jealous
is your glados in english or in
indonesian
english wait girls can say indonesia i
don't know can she
that would be
funny because i don't know she's so
sassy
oh what does this do oh
air gesture whoa
shake moves look at me kobo yeah
what the heck
[Music]
you can try too
oh
[Music]
oh wait oh
there's a portal thingy up there we're
sending you somewhere
out here
oh no
where am i i don't know where i am
[Music]
did you see something to make a portal
over there there's that wall yeah
here
and but where are we going with you and
i'll come with you i'll come with you oh
oh it's okay to come with you mommy up
here mommy i'm here
yeah okay okay
nice oh i'm following you
or just you
there's something here
i can make portal here like in foreign
but
really
then i guess i'll have to die first and
then come through your portal
maybe
but choose the right color
no no no can't can't because there's no
bridge here you will you will
die immediately
oh there's
oh yes
platform here
watching you try
[Music]
not sure what happened there all right
let's try again no problem
or is it maybe the other way around is
it this way does it matter maybe it
doesn't matter
maybe it doesn't even matter
okay this time i go first maybe i have
an idea but i would like some blue here
can you put some blue
i can't
oh you can't see it well come join me
come join me okay
[Music]
i'm over here
[Applause]
cute cute mommy how did i say up there
kobo
up there up there
up there how do i say
uh
[Music]
i forgot what portal
oh
okay
oh nice
okay and now uh yeah
yeah
so we have this
same thing again this is my goal you're
staying okay okay
[Music]
what
hello camera okay door
[Applause]
okay which color did i use i used yellow
so
let me catch you this should work
yeah
damn
mommy very genius genius mommy
wow
[Music]
glitter's talking about also chad do you
remember how to
uh
there was like one key where you could
show somebody something on the screen
not making a portal like signaling
something okay i don't know what's that
f
f is a pink tool f us
[Applause]
[Music]
nice yes pink
who's caring i'm i'm i'm totally
carrying kobo totally so we have a
uh catapult
oh no oh no oh no
no i was the testing subject so that
kobo could be
you said saved
would nice
ah what does the this button do
oh
it opens up there and there's a portal
thingy
and then we have one here
ah
and now we already have an airflow i
know i know i know i'm going there i'm
going to go
and die
why
i don't know why can i go there i want a
good
yeah it's not quite straight uh
can't i can't oh
uh i can't reach there
how about how about now okay
[Music]
hmm maybe higher how about now
i don't know but it goes the other way
it doesn't really help you i guess oh
nice yeah
oh
okay but it just sends you over there i
kind of want the other direction
oh oh wait you're over there oh i'm over
here now mommy i can make portal here
oh
well wait i'll send you some more air
there's there's buttons here let me
press
that's touch
how can i touch it i forgot how to touch
it was it e i think it was e
oh you're right okay haha
oh
i think i guess you can send it over
here somehow
so i can keep the ball on the button i
suppose maybe
ah yes oh i got the ball
oh nice
i wanna if i just keep it
on the button is that what the purpose
is i hope so
okay
um in that case i'll try coming over to
you
oh thank you
thank you
[Music]
a little bit more to the left
okay
go down first mommy
oh i can try to
jump over oh wait oh yeah you're right
where's the
where is it
oh okay i'm here
oh no problem no problem but that ah
that gets rid of the portal yeah okay
okay right right
well how was it again like
here okay um with more over there
wait yes
okay
now we got it
yeah
and
nice
[Music]
i must must be able to shoot them
ah
i see
ah no the ball disappeared
oh the ball also disappeared okay
what oh i think i can uh i can you know
you want from here
oh yeah i can hit the ball from here
you're too short you're too short kobo
yeah too small but at least we can try
no no that won't work koba
we'll make the portal again
oh yeah
you got the small marble
i want to hit the ball
you go to the button first up you will
sit underneath all right yes i thought
it was open ha ha
hmm here we go
yeah
i have
uh i have um
i had yeah the wrong opinion about you
you're not too short you can do it
cobalt yeah but what went wrong so i
when i go over there
the my portal disappears so the airflow
disappears so there must be
a tomato
why is there a laser here and why is
there
that over there
oh but there's even more stuff over here
where
where are you mom
i'm like the the end of the room
yeah but
there's another portal
portal placement over here but
first i need to get to your side
[Music]
um
from where you are currently you can't
uh
you can't reach the
the platf
yeah i can it's so high i'm too short
you can't make a
a portal here right over here
i can't do anything here um
barriers
wait it's so easy it's so easy though
i think it's so easy oh is it
wait
[Music]
i why no is it is it easy maybe it's not
easy
[Music]
oh what if i
oh no that doesn't reach um
i'm thinking thinking hard
yeah we
we have to think with portals kobold
we have to think of portals
i think
wait wait so i flow over there
and then and then what if i ah
no
i'm thinking maybe i can get myself over
to that side and then flow over here
like i wanna i'm gonna go over here
let's uh just try to make portal there
maybe the the test trial
try
this
yeah
what
i'm confused i'll just jump but it'll
just get rid of everything again
ah don't don't don't don't call me uh i
wanna see what's behind uh here
this yeah there's a okay i
uh i can send you there
if are you able to go for the red portal
or can you not reach this one no i think
i can't i can't do anything here
wait wait a minute
uh let me
hang here
and my portal will be gone
and your portal still there
and maybe i can make portal here
i don't know for what but
yeah
that's
the laser
is i think a little bit for later maybe
we have to
get both of us over there
[Music]
lock the laser with the ball
oh the ball
no
wait
um
okay that means that well
once we're up there
right now we need the ball so we can get
up there if we want to go over there we
need a new ball
um so this one will disappear so first i
think both of us could come over there
but uh why don't you make a portal here
to descend to send the ball immediately
you are uh
wait do you want to send the ball away
you can try sending the ball wait do it
um
what's our plan actually i don't
understand
we have to send a boat there
right
or yeah
because it will block the laser
um
wait um how about uh we switch we switch
uh rose
can you make a glue portal here
uh-huh and i'm going to make the problem
here
yeah
like this okay and i see it from your
point of view
and go
on
[Music]
so
we can make a portal like this ah
[Music]
yes
i can make a portal over there from here
so
idea idea
um
yeah do that
uh-huh
and now
i send you the air back got it
uh
wait yeah we have some connection some i
think this is new we have a new
connection here with the airflow
because we can
wait where's your where's your light
blue one over there i see can you try
flying oh i know but wait no the the
things disappear
but do you see it
now we have
the airflow going over here
we need to send the ball to the lesser
right
yeah the laser yeah yeah yeah
oh
okay
um can
you try
fl throwing the ball uh on the catapult
like putting it on the catapult or
flying together with the ball i don't
know
either with the with the ball or without
the balls
now
[Music]
don't disappear yeah let's try the ball
only
i think the ball will disappear through
that you know there's yeah that's right
that's right that's sorry too
so doesn't it
that's your name
[Music]
yeah that's on on purpose let's see
where uh uh this way ah this way it goes
for the yellow one maybe we i have an
idea i have an idea
i have an okay okay okay okay
i think i'm getting closer we have to
send the ball through here
uh so it goes the other way which means
the light
the yellow one it must go it must go um
here
now my red one is in the way
light one light yellow okay
uh
and then i send
it
can you make the blue one there again uh
where the dark
flow
dark blue there
oh here
on on the
maybe on the other side
on the other side dark blue
on the other side oh okay yeah
now the air is going to the laser
so how about
i think we're getting we're getting
closer kobo don't worry i know i know
because now the ball can
flow over there just if we make that
last connection so now it's going for
light blue
white blue
[Music]
can the the ball
the ball
um
i will send you a new ball
okay
and aya can you stand on the button
stay on the button oh yeah
um
oh did it fall down yeah um
and now
um
i have to turn on slow mode
no mode
wait uh can i can i throw the ball
to the
you know
i wonder if it goes that far you can try
i can send you a new ball if it doesn't
work yeah okay
oh
[Laughter]
okay i'll send the ball again
okay
and
how do i say wait a second in indonesian
[Music]
i think i have to make a photo like
can you
open the door again stand on the button
okay
must be a reason why i can reach that so
there should be a portal there maybe
but why
ah
no ah
what is
[Music]
how about
uh can you
put the portal here again the dark blue
one
thank you
[Music]
uh
um
[Music]
do you have an idea
i'm still thinking
uh
man
sorry zero iq here
me too
if you were down there
can you make
a dark blue here
i think
mommy mommy
yeah
mommy mommy mommy mommy i get it uh
baby uh-huh let's try to oh
um
push the button push the button
button yeah try to summon
okay
oh you know it will flow wait now it
will flow now what was that was the
wrong the wrong one
we wanted to
okay
and when it comes back you make the blue
portal there
right
[Music]
do i have to do something different oh
let's see what happens
so it first goes
through the yellow
oh portal
then i will go back the other way to the
aha
ah
i
can put
a different portal there yeah
can i put should i put the yellow one
there
but you still need to
but you still need to go here to make
the portal here
with the portal behind and you can do
that there
huh
well i will test well i think it i think
it will disappear huh oh
well you're sending the air with the
blue for the yellow ah
but then then it will just come back to
me no
bye-bye um but that's so okay oh that's
okay
oh okay i'll send another one
new ball
oh
[Music]
okay
maybe maybe
maybe yeah oops
maybe
oh
yeah
oh it went right over there
okay
interesting
oh
[Music]
this button must be have
a poor pose
yeah because we have an
apple section wow
it looks like there's two bowls now
these two balls yeah balls
wow
do we have two bubbles i think we broke
the game nice hacker mommy boys hackers
yeah we hacked the game nice
and i wonder
there's one one step is missing that's
probably so obvious um
probably so obvious
this this one must be you have a purpose
because we haven't used this button yet
i mean i mean we have to send the ball
over there first to get someone to the
side at least
um
don't do anything
yes okay
don't do anything now it's
now it's floating there
keep it open yeah
um
i make orange portal here
okay
[Music]
me
you know i just woke up maybe maybe i
can say that's the problem
i just woke up before the stream you're
on the last few tests
okay it's okay
75 science collaboration points
what blue she's she's uh saying it's
your fault
my fault yeah
what happened what happened why is it
shaking
earth is chicken
oh okay well we can already uh oh
honestly we're playing with momentum
cobalt do you remember momentum momentum
yeah
or maybe not i'm not sure i mean there's
probably what the hell
what the hell
what the heck
okay well um
i see
ah can you make
first of all let's make portal there
yeah let's make portals everywhere
there's another one like here one here
yeah but uh probably that has to be
someone else from us uh um but yeah you
can jump down there oh and then you can
you're trying jumping
momentum try jumping down there and then
you will fall into the
you get a massage if you jump down there
you get a beautiful comfortable massage
okay i love the message
yeah let's go
ah
oh huh
[Music]
ah how does it feel nice nice back
cracking yes very very crappy not very
nice
okay
instead we'll do we'll do something else
maybe with the air here not no
maybe
here
oh interesting i have an idea if i if
you
uh see if i if i would go up here
and then
uh can can you make a light blue portal
here
uh-huh and then and then
uh
when i'm when i fall down before i land
here you make the dark blue wait wait
the dark blue
okay okay
okay okay okay okay i'm a genius okay
before i fall okay because i will get
rid of this portal yes yes because i
make one here
so when i'm falling yeah you gotta be
fast okay okay
three
two
one
but i need to go here immediately when
i'm at the
ah
yeah i mean i mean we're getting we're
getting closer it's already uh we have
momentum
yeah you need to stand on the button so
we'll try again
try again
yeah
oops zoom i'm redeeming myself chat i'm
redeeming myself
okay okay so
uh
everything is in place uh
is that the right yeah it should be done
oh oh wait oh maybe yeah over there
wait should i make it here or there
make it there
okay okay three one two
can you make the portal while you're
you know what you just um
ah
well it must be while you're while
you're on the button so we have to
change the portals a little bit i think
for example uh you make your light you
make your light blue one no not there uh
can you close that again
okay
make your light blue on here
and your dark blue one already here
maybe
because now
you're standing on the button because
those you can reach this one and this
one you can reach
now i have to think
and when i fall down oh yeah i make
you you
make the port the blue portal
and
[Music]
no no no no no no because because we
still need to make a bottle here
so you can float
you you won't fall so you won't fall
there
okay
but um
um
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay now i can bring
the cube
uh yeah we change the airflow i think or
can i just fall down let me try
i can just fall down oh yeah okay
now i can send
the now i think this the cube needs
momentum too
right we need the blue portal again
where it was originally i think
no no
can we not just uh
keep the cube here
so it keeps it open for us so we can go
there together
supposedly
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
i hope that's enough uh can i wait
let's try i can oh [\h__\h] oh no
i'm stuck
i haven't make a portal
i'm stuck like a fly
yeah fly that's
stuck in this stuck in the spiderweb for
some reason um
wait wait let me let me yeah you know
you shouldn't be here though
you're not stuck anymore
[Applause]
anymore
right
yeah okay wait how did we do it uh uh
okay let me make a portal yeah
yes cube is still there nice
okay what did what happened what
happened what went wrong um
okay let me make the portal first and
then you make the portal below okay make
orange pork okay okay one
two
three
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
or not
that was pretty good way better than the
first one
way faster
nice
kobo nice yes
mommy
[Music]
uh
yes
are you are you happy about one million
subscribers google of course i am
good
keep on continuing making the content
that you're already making and
everything will be wonderful
and one million subscribers sure you can
play portal 2 with no problems because
you're smart right 1 million subscriber
is very smart
believe in that
ah let's see
we have more of this where are we even
going
okay there's another catapult here
oh
on this thing what was that again
oh well what was that again
what is that
i don't know um
i was that
um
[Music]
oh yeah you're just going there again i
guess we need your portals yeah
portal
uh from there i guess you can make the
blue one here when you're back here
[Music]
uh this is nice
swimming
wait did i ask before kobo can you swim
no i can but i can float at this
you could vote
i can survive at least
even though i may not swim
i cannot swim but i can float just maybe
to
now waiting for some help to risk
yeah
surprise that's important yeah yeah at
least something floating to wait for
help in the middle of the ocean yeah
yeah oh
but what does this mean
careful of your
head
[Music]
there must be like a laser coming out of
here later no what is this
i think the laser comes out of there
later so we can send it through here
okay
we will
how about we
[Music]
oh now we lost the airflow
oh no you're gonna die i'm sorry
yeah oh oh oh welcome back airflow it's
nice it's so windy windy
um
there's a laser there
i found the laser oh there now
yeah
oh laser there oh
um
we can make portal like here okay
see a dark blue upper yeah you you see
uh can you see my pov
ah by racing right here
[Music]
yeah yeah
okay
i think we can make something there i
mean
maybe there's a ball or what i don't
know
and we'll try to
get there
oh yeah we need to go oh
uh it's not
a little bit more on that side damn it
damn it
it's more
yeah now we can reach that place
ah what happened
i fell down
oh okay all right now that i'm here and
get rid of myself
don't run into the laser what does this
button do okay i don't know
something
there's a cube coming down from there
[Music]
here to where we are
ah mommy
um yes
um
would you send it um over here over to
us no no no no okay oh
i can make portal
here there yeah yeah yeah
if i send the airflow for you yes that's
that's the way
okay i think
could could work let's see how it falls
doesn't it
i know
um
we can readjust maybe yeah just yeah it
does it did it move oh
[Music]
no so close
no you need to do i have to move mine
yeah move the yellow portal out here
here oh
yeah okay come on let's see
perfect thank you
beautiful
what do you like to do in the summer
in summer
yeah
um
even summer time i don't know
i
i'm just doing as usual
yeah
what about some going out for vacation
or ice cream
i don't know like a hobby in summer uh
i mean
i'm not not something special i'm just
doing as usual
oh
okay
i i tried something but that's not what
we want to do okay
uh you remember the one there the there
yeah
yeah yeah
we have to send it
there was over here was a place where we
can make a portal
so currently we're not using
your blue portals
oh no i want to go here ah oh no
wait
uh
[Music]
i want to go there
uh without changing my current portal
wait no we don't
you leave
yeah uh can you make one uh
one blue portal
over there to set the laser
yeah i can see okay
and
then you can make the light blue one
over here later on
[Music]
but i will ooh
how do i
get over there again uh without changing
like currently currently we have this
and
i think i can't
oh
mommy
um
you need to make for the yellow portal
here please
oh
okay i
will go back for that oh sure sorry
over there
yeah because i cannot go here
okay
okay that was a little bit
too far
here
hear the snare okay
oh wait i could go there too oh we can
just we can just go by the portals here
again we can go together
just here yeah
easy
how hot is it in in the summer in
indonesia
what how hot how hot is it in indonesia
in the
summer um
i don't know about
around i don't know maybe
about 35
celsius
oh my god
and it's very humid right oh we made it
yeah i'm sorry okay yeah
we made it
nice
[Music]
warm up in the first puzzle that's why
it wasn't so good
i think in um
it also gets uh like maybe 30
but maybe
32 degrees maximum or so in the summer
but we don't it's not so humid it's more
dry
so it's not so bad i think indonesia is
more humid you know the air is so humid
well do you really know probably do you
trust me humanoid
what if i told you you human
what is your partner
human
human is when the air is wet
when the air feels like wait wait cooper
did you ever live in indonesia
leave
did you ever go somewhere outside
indonesia
uh maybe outside my city only not
outside okay then you then you only know
the the weather of indonesia right yeah
right ah okay so you don't understand
what's not humid what's like how is it
when there's uh not humid weather
sorry
you only know how it's uh when it's
humid that's that's interesting oh my
god you will be very surprised if you
ever leave indonesia
you will be surprised about you know how
the weather can feel so much the air can
feel so much different
yeah yeah
okay
what is this
river river
are you river
yeah reverse seven reverse reverse
reverse reverse it looks hot though
it's cool it looks hot
oh
what does it do we have to try
for example
like this
you want to go
[Music]
let me go here first
there's a cube over there yeah and now
you you ah
pick me up
yes mommy
go go go go
you have the important mission of
protecting the cube yeah i'm protecting
the cure right now i'll let you
i want you to fall okay
hi
[Music]
something here yeah
oops uh yeah
someone ah wait do we have to
sense the button through there
because it has the the perfect shape for
the cube
maybe we have to send it there and then
it will stick
yes
oh there we go so smart today
yeah
oh yeah oh
yes
[Music]
there we go
please big brain
oh nice oh
we're finished already
[Music]
i trust you
you are my favorite question
a cobble has a big brain oh we we have a
big brain
how to say it uh
in indonesia
whereas
[Music]
we're
uh thank you what was thank you again
[Music]
okay pretty cute
i saw this stream where you called into
ollie's
um call in
olivia olivia excuse me ah yeah yeah you
know i think i always want i want a girl
as my child but but maybe you know maybe
it's not so bad with a boy can you speak
in
your boy book
i want to see how it is you know
it's not it's it's not me it's taboo
yeah yeah temple table can you bring
chapel over here
oh what do you want
to see
mommy do you want to want to say huh hey
everyone i want just just a little bit
of a talk uh you know
have a conversation see if i can take
care of a boy
hi temple
hi
um i'm so happy to have you as my son uh
um what was your favorite thing about
mommy
don't be shy but don't be shy
what's your favorite thing about mummy
uh
about mommy
um
mommy is so kind and
i don't care about kobo the hell with
that kusogaki
i only care about table now let's go
check but we're going to do this
together
so so you know no you want to play with
me instead of cover
[Laughter]
yeah yeah i'm playing with you now okay
go go go
go
make one more portal here maybe
i think i don't know okay wait that
doesn't work that makes no sense
[Music]
sorry mommy sorry
mommy
sorry
i'm sorry that's the first time i ever
heard it like actually makes sense
it's okay
it's okay you know suicide would go
crazy over you right now i i don't know
why many people
are pregnant right now
oh okay
yeah
we'll keep along keep on floating
i'll take care of you i don't know how
where to go from here oh yes chapel
there you go
the perfect
okay now what do you think about your
sister kobold
um
i die again i don't know there's
there's a spike
i i don't know
why did it go down then can we stop it
did it go automatically i don't think so
i i don't think so
go again go and get in temple okay
[Laughter]
ah
i make make portal again okay same
portal
i'll do anything yeah yeah
yeah don't forget that one okay okay
don't die don't die jibble
i'll i'll i'll watch now properly
oh no okay now i understand it just
comes down automatically when you get
closer to it
indeed
[Music]
i didn't do it on purpose okay um
i think i have an idea
yes table
okay you have an idea show me show me
okay oh okay mommy
genius oh my god
ah
ah now you need to let go of that one uh
maybe put it somewhere else like here
oh no i don't know it's fine i i thought
you could just fall down that's all
right oh
there you go temple
yeah
[Applause]
tell me what's over there
i can see actually oh there's a button
yeah there there's
oh
oh nice orange did well it's reversed
are you shut up glasses thank you
you can't stop chipping it was mine
okay okay now oh there's so there's a
reverse button
what else is there mm-hmm
nothing more
it's nothing more okay
okay
ah
can you make a
blue portal here
okay okay i know i'll die though will i
die i will die but maybe for now no just
for now no no you want mommy trust me
and then yeah just just go now you know
you can go now
not yet because you have to stand on the
reverse reverse reverse
no you just need to go here right
here so we can
yeah but you have to stand on the
reverse button
reverse the button
no red button cobble no yes do it do it
simple listen to your mommy okay okay
mommy okay
i'm sorry i'm sorry okay there you go ah
no sense
oh are you okay okay
yeah good boy good boy okay
that's that's perfect
no yes
i mean let me go for it no no you
how about i do this
yeah i'm coming to you because now i go
from my
good portal
do you feel betrayed by blue
am i a good boy
okay but i want i want my daughter back
ah give me michael back good work well
give me my cover back come back bye-bye
bye-bye was nice to meet you
bye mommy i will see you bye-bye
hi
[Applause]
what are you doing with my
[Music]
i think i prefer cobra i like cute
cobble okay
it was nice to meet you though cause
like in in the olivia stream i did not
understand the word because it was only
indonesian but this time i understood
everything i'm happy
okay okay
it's very funny though
yeah table did a whole level and kubo
could take a break meanwhile so now
you're really recharged and really
energetic again right you took a whole
break now
what did you do while while kobo was
gone what did kobo do when jebel was
here
i'm uh
i took a nap
no i'm drinking milk
yeah
okay
okay let's see what do we have here
there's a button here to reverse this
one
there you are huh
we're very spot nine doll yeah
[Music]
make
the thing is when we walk through here
portal gets disappears but
okay
cobalt jump
uh jump okay
let's see where you go oh my god
oh yeah
yeah you landed safely i'm surprised
yeah
what's over there let me see there is
another
okay
give it a try
[Music]
we need to stop you somewhere
i see i see
i need to stop you somewhere
there's another thing here
when you fly are you able to make a
portal here and here while you're flying
oh wait uh huh
[Music]
disappear when you go through that so i
stop you maybe
uh
huh think of it
what's up there anyway
i guess we can't go there
uh
right now at least i think we do the
same thing again
for now
yeah we do the same thing can you repeat
can you just go back i guess you have to
die
i mean or
wait you don't have to die
can you jump into the airflow
oh that's fine that's fine
ah i want you to um go through the
portal
just now uh
yeah to jump to the other side
and then we do the we do the same thing
again with the portals like this
yeah and trust me trust me okay okay
okay and then
[Music]
oh
i guess you have to stay there i think
so it stays open
now yeah stay on the button and now i
think i have to go somewhere we'll make
one here
and we'll try momentum
we have to try momentum i don't
understand what's this for
not eh yeah
because i have to fall through here i
have to catapult my stuff and then fall
there
something like that
okay
okay but where do i want to
go i died maybe no
ah
i'll make one here
let's see what happens when i do
this
[Music]
oh
yes i know you did that blue don't look
so proud oh huh
i couldn't do anything what the heck
she's trying to get us again together
but
[Music]
the portal here and the portal there so
you go up there
ah yes yeah
and you can make the blue one uh um
i guess
nowhere i guess we don't need the blue
one right now let's test
testing testing testing
oh let's go
[Music]
maybe i can i can go there alone
what's what's up there what's up there
oh
i can oh i can make a portal here
and one i can make a few portals myself
yeah
[Music]
uh i could make one here
i brought you some air uh
i can make one here too
maybe with the catapult
i don't think you need the button
anymore i need to go die
yeah
yeah or maybe not but okay i already
died
i agree i'm looking good
entertaining
that was entertaining thank you glados
i'm trying my best here
i'm an entertainer
yeah so
let's see i think i did everything in my
power
uh
i could also still make it here whatever
helps you
here or here
oh yeah they're there yeah yeah also um
oh wait no no okay
um
[Applause]
[Music]
remember
yeah
zoom zoom
okay this place looks a bit bigger oh no
what is this thing oh my god
button
ah that's reverse button i didn't see
[Music]
oh wait reverse reverse reverse come
back
okay come back go boy i i'll i just
can't come back oh okay okay
um
let's go right there let's see
if that was uh i i fell but i'm okay oh
yeah okay oh
oh
i'm not trying to go here but oh no
oh no
oh
oh no oh that's uh yeah your your
portals disappear then
i'll try something else
there's i don't know what is this
maybe i can
eh
oh never mind it would be useful if
you're there we'll figure it out
okay
i think i can send you air
i'll send you air over there now you can
send it through here
i don't know why ah for that there you
go
and now we could even reverse it but
what is it for we will never know this
is four
and there's a lot of
dangerous stuff there kobo be careful
yeah i know
where am i
oh
[Music]
no i still don't understand what's this
i will i want to check it out i'll go
but i guess we need someone to put push
the reverse button
me me me me
that hurts where are you right now oh
yeah i'm here now there you are
um
ah the problem is
[Music]
it's kind of complicated because there's
one beer up there you can see my pov
mommy
yes
yeah cause you're here confusing
no you're here and then you go up here
and go here you know because there's
like
porsches yeah here and then maybe go
here
and then go here
and then go there
so you're inside a maze right now
yeah that's what it looks like
yes
[Music]
um
see it's a bit big
so we have to think hard
do you want me to be the floating test
object this time then
um
uh let me i
think the difficult part is is because
when you float through there
uh you have to try
to keep on balancing of the reverse
button so that i don't get hit by the by
the spikes yeah yeah i know
yeah yeah
okay okay okay uh we start uh
i guess
like
i think i need the dark blue one here
first
i think mm-hmm yeah
okay so i go there again
well i don't
see it oh oh no it's okay okay we
reverse here yeah can we
go up and
[Applause]
i think maybe it was the other portrait
wow
maybe i want to see the other portal uh
okay
that was very brutal how about this one
okay i understand
ah but you need to you know
where them ah up there up there okay
okay uh
[Music]
it went so well it's about timing then
ah
okay uh there is a certain
rhythm okay
i see then you have to control that so
mommy doesn't die okay mommy okay
[Music]
okay
i think i forgot to make a portal
somewhere where is it here okay okay
let's go mommy
okay
wait wait wait wait wait let's see
what timing do i think
okay okay
[Music]
oh no oh no okay let's go
am i blind i don't see another
wall for me to make the do i have to
jump
um i think you can't mind
this
huh
oh i guess
yeah okay
oh is that really where i want to go oh
no i'm scared uh
well i'm not sure where we are right now
it kind of lost track of where we are
[Music]
down here
there's some something you go well can
you go there yeah yeah okay nice
turn so yeah
um um okay okay take it slow take it
slow yeah there's cube right there
i will i will go there and uh i will
destroy them i can take a oh wait never
mind there there's oh okay okay
uh
what happened
what else you can breathe
[Music]
where's the cube now
the cube's here
oh nicer
ah
you can pick it up somewhere there
oh i heard this wait wait um
i cannot can you leave me picking it up
from oh yeah
okay okay um
i'm not sure
or you send it through here
where should i send the
box uh if you make the dark blue wait
let it go back yeah and make the dark
blue portal here i'm not sure how it
will fall we can test it ah
oh yeah
oh now you can let it go
uh a little bit higher yeah
and then you make the red the dark blue
portal somewhere else so it falls down
or the the light blue portal uh whatever
just change the portal so it falls down
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah and now i guess
you come to me but the thing is it's not
always it shouldn't always be reversed
right yeah so
where you should put the box
i i i think i can help somehow by
bringing you here whoa what
where is the exit
where is it here it's here oh
but how how can we get there
oh there's a mommy kiwawa
there's a
there's a a square button there so i
think the boxes need to be there
okay i didn't see that one yet
but how
okay okay maybe i can
i can probably uh
take ah no i have to bring the cube all
the way back with me mommy mommy
oh momentum
[Music]
oh there's another one here
oh
let me try it i think let me try it
because you see there's uh you know here
can i
can i jump
with the box um
yeah
let's see
i am right oh yes
[Music]
mommy
okay beautiful wait can you go back here
oh wait oh oh
okay okay mommy mommy i will pick you up
so how what if i just die
no no it's easier if i just die there's
a portal there right can you make plural
here
oh yeah uh
uh there uh yeah i think maybe oh yes
yes yes ah oh yeah okay
you know
yeah and then reverse reverse yeah
what what
this stupid turret is in the way it's
okay go away
we don't need you we don't want you
oh
where am i
so confusing
no no i'm going back again
um
uh
[Music]
how did you go over there
uh just uh
like yeah fall down yeah
we fall down and boom boom
[Applause]
momentum
mommy
[Applause]
yeah
nice congratulations
easy easy standard section of this
course
before you can go any further yeah i
need you to complete one more question
[Music]
because my viewers say when you die
i am pregnant because i am miss chicken
and gopro means like smashed because in
indonesia there's some uh like a food we
need to find i am
at the end of this it's uh
this is a spicy chicken but the chicken
must be disconnected
like
yeah it's just good so when you die my
viewers say that you're like i am go
prank
yeah
i see
you go die because there's a lot of
laser turrets have fun with them go go
go walk straight cobalt
[Music]
[Laughter]
my viewers are
saying you i am go preg so it's not my
fault what are you doing
okay uh i'm dancing
your style
okay well i let this one slide but oh
look at this mommy's smart we're
protected now nice they can't get us now
unless oh yes
[Music]
when
you know huh
we want some air here here mommy
[Music]
can we jump into it
oh please don't move that where are we
uh we we can go here
oh my gosh
we can make a wall there we just have to
do the same thing again
okay all right okay okay
i have it you have it again this this
may need some trial and error
[Music]
okay so kobo is in charge of air i'm in
charge of the of the shield okay
okay
sorry no problem
scary scary factor boba have you you
haven't played portal alone yet right
yeah i have one
you should
well i can already make it oh
you should because it's a lot of fun
no i think you have to make us fall down
wait i forgot which portal
ah uh okay this portal again
oh we landed we landed we all landed but
where we are there's
okay nice mommy mommy
oh i thought we already finished the
level ah not quite not quite
[Music]
ah
okay i take the shield again
up there we're protected now you take
the air again um
[Music]
it'll tickle a little bit are you
ticklish cobalt oh ticklish
oh no where where oh no no no no
no
i
died i die
i said
it's okay we can do it again
um
on it
yeah okay i have it all under control
[Music]
um yeah you need to
yeah you need to
start the barrier
uh-huh yeah okay
i have it i have it okay let's go thank
you forever
thank you forever
your barrier
right well
i don't know yeah
okay
you have less hp than me
i don't know but i die too
anya
stop that
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh we can jump over here huh
can we oh yeah
we can jump into this airflow is that
what they want us to do it seems so
um
different no no no no
what
what was that
i'll get easy i can i can come to you
probably
where should we go
from there yeah good question oops
where's the exit
oh
i make my portal and i make it here
i have to
open our eyes
very very wide oh no oh my god oh hi
cool
yeah oh
[Music]
did you try playing hoto cure i have one
because it's just not my type of game to
be swim
really oh [\h__\h] yeah
it's a lot of fun
i know but
not
i'm in
i just can't you can play with mommy
i am in the character
yeah there's a there's uh
me you can play me
and you can play good one you can play
everybody i know i know but it's just
not my
my type of game to be shrimp
that's understandable all right
but i would like to play it but not on
the stream
yeah it's just something
um a little problem oh wait you see what
is over there oh yeah
um
that's maybe where we need to come
[Music]
okay let's see
like this
oh and then we jump here
oh yeah
candy
okay i'm safe now oh
oh
okay me too me too
nice and nice
yeah my viewers say that they love you
they love mommy really
yeah no way
yes away
how do i say i love you in indonesian
again i forgot
[Music]
we can support each other yeah
um do we have to go down here
i think so
um
oh no maybe no that's where we came from
that door doesn't open um do we have to
make something here
yes
oh yeah ah the airflow can you make it
here
oh you're right
over there there's a little uh
oh
and keep on swimming swimming keep on
swimming swimming swimming
[Music]
here
oh we just go again to the other side
now i take the air and you but what no i
should always should have kept it
where's them where are you
mommy
i couldn't have taken it from the
previous one because uh it deletes it i
think
if you walk through this it deletes it
so
there
must be
a while somewhere
why is the wall
dangerous
[Music]
careful okay we use the water
oh
[Music]
nice good job they can't see us
can't see us
nice
uh we go
oh maybe we have to
we'll have to make it here
but this is where we start
before yeah see see this robot right
here
oh yeah
down there
what
what's up can i make it
[Music]
yeah you can kill them
oh that way they don't come over here
but i don't like that
and maybe we i only see this one
um
it will take me in the other way
so
we will try cobble
trust me
okay i trust you
we can
oh but iron we go oh no there's
oh i think it's different now
even if we fall down we're starting
somewhere else because we have a
checkpoint
uh yeah yeah yeah uh let's let's just
let go of that
oh please i don't want to die
we will not die don't worry don't worry
oh my god oh my god what's happening we
can go here okay
yeah yeah yeah safe
ah it's a
this cooking insert disc they have a do
you have a disc
where is this insert
this here here mommy look at this good
job
yeah
cobra have you ever touched a cd before
of course
only because you're so young i feel like
nowadays pcs don't even have cd cases
see the uh
cd slots
everything is bought digitally
maybe you haven't touched it
have you ever tried
tapes though cassette tapes sausages
excellent
what
yeah look at this a little [\h__\h] little
[\h__\h]
yeah that that's good job kobold yeah
but now the first words that we'll learn
will be your little [\h__\h] literally
[Music]
nice and freeing
humans we will free the humans
whatever he empowered
oh
mommy mommy something moving here
[Music]
let's go gels we get gels now tails
tails yeah well i don't know what else
but okay and that's another another
fun thing how do we get there though we
have
[Music]
i guess we can try to
finish five if it's as long as four then
we i think mommy mommy
yeah or maybe not because now it's
one hour 40 minutes
how did you get there there i made i
made a portal there and just
mommy brain already very dense
okay
nice mommy
then let's start chapter five
we might need uh
chad's help so we can finish under three
hours please help
what's your favorite flavor of milk or
do you just like the normal plain milk
you like
i drink strawberry because i heard that
strawberry milk will grow your subjects
foreign
i think i prefer chocolate milk because
strawberry milk often tastes so
artificial
yeah okay what is this looks so old it's
so old here oh yeah right because uh
lore
portal lure
um
first of all i walk to the button and
then we press the button
look behind you
behind me what
what is this
what happened
here what do you find now
[Music]
so that's what
the gels
four
yeah
this one makes you boing boing and then
there's another one that makes it really
fast
oh you can ah
yeah i i i stand on there and then you
can jump because otherwise it's too slow
okay
now you go up there and you press the
other button
oh you're right okay we'll bring us oh
[Music]
is it
i guess no oh you're right i know it is
the same button
wait okay oh yeah
maybe
we could make a wall there
red wall oh there's oh oh it is simple
uh
walk through the orange portal yeah
congratulations
this was just the tutorial
though just a simple introduction
there's more gels there's i think there
was three three different gels i think
oh yeah one what was a white gel when
the white gel you can make portals
everywhere where the gel is
uh
[Music]
through the portal friends oh you're
right oh yeah
we can but uh i made it i did it wrong
now it will fall for woo
[Music]
what do we have over there i look on
cobalt pov yeah i'm standing oh there's
a button on the bottom and you know
that there's a button
see
oh
is it safe for me to go to you i don't
know there's maybe
i'm coming
oh
i hope we don't need to chill anymore i
think we need to jail cell but is there
another generator no
there's more space here
huh
[Applause]
something over
there
i see
um
we
probably have to send the gel
uh
somewhere to us because there's there
only seems to be one generator but
maybe we can bring the gel
there's ah this one this one is sauce
we can send them
a minute
[Music]
if i can reach that from here
interesting
no wait i already made that yeah but i
can reach it from here
that means
what can i reach from there
maybe here
um
[Music]
yeah i will make it go away but
um
[Music]
where does it go
uh nowhere
not sure it went somewhere
[Music]
no no
it doesn't go anywhere
nani
um
yeah
if you can see on my pov
yeah i'm watching oh
that went somewhere can you scroll in
that made a whole wobble blue but still
we will do
if we fall through
a hole get some momentum
maybe i don't know
maybe maybe
maybe just make me
i'll come back to you
oh
wait keep that if you thought this way
we can catch the with the wind we can
catch the blue oh you're right hey
uh um
okay i wait uh
oops
now i throw the blue stuff over there
and it will go into the wind wow
now what do we do with that ah now let
it drop let it drop let it drop okay
when it's in the air i'll send it again
and you'll make the portal somewhere
else once it's in the wind yeah now let
it fall
and let it go let it fall
okay we can drop it
on the platform yeah
[Music]
and we do the same thing i guess
somewhere else yeah
okay i'll sand it again
drop it like it's hot
there we go
okay maybe we can also make it drop
where it is right now
can you put the portal again where it
was before okay
and then
[Music]
i wonder if we can make it somehow
if we can bring it over here
by
putting it all through the portal but i
can only make mine over here
i don't think we can
at least
believe yeah we need this
color here too so we could go from
[Music]
what happens if we
oh mommy mommy i can i can i can okay
let's try let's try that's right
that's right let's try okay you said
that i was thinking if the if the color
can bounce off itself probably not maybe
not
maybe not
that's right is it coming
uh where oh no no i did not come
i just pointed at it okay
okay
it's there
eh wait no no no no no i may have to see
my portal is done
ah
oh
no i think
we're on calculation
sorry guys who are asking for super chat
i turned it off because i need to catch
up i have many super chats to read sorry
sorry
indonesia has super chats now nice one
yeah
sorry donations
do do wear a shirt and shoes in no time
move quickly for your test track do not
not forget to not touch the glass
wait for more than 20 minutes touch the
glass
leave your belongings here do not touch
the glass
what glass
ah anyway that's just a little bit of a
piece of floor touch grass yeah
we're so close we're so close we already
got the color on one of them yeah bouncy
platform so we're just going to go here
um
[Music]
oh definitely need one here
ah
huh
yeah i already did that i already did
that
i can't bring it there
[Music]
i go i'll go over to see what we can do
now
[Music]
hold on
momentum
momentum momentum
what happened if i jump down there
where am i crying i don't know where are
you going
wait
nowhere
i think i know i should
die
oh come on
[Music]
if you have
this
oh
[Music]
yes yes
yes helpful
um
what happened if i jump here can i jump
there
[Music]
yeah too far i can't jump
okay
we try again
with the
sanding the gel you you go
make the portal in the same spot as
before
and we'll try to
[Music]
send it through again
use our thinking caps again yeah again
okay let's bring
[Music]
my ascendant
and then
it's the the airflow currently is going
up right
oh ah
i thought okay oh mommy mommy try try
try it try to send it down
okay
okay let's see
we let it fall
mommy yeah
yeah yeah yeah
i was wondering if that worked already
yeah yeah okay now what can i think
oh
oh my god
um
oh no yes let it go and i make a bigger
jump because of momentum ah but not
really
oh
[Music]
okay what do you want to try i want to
try okay
hi
oh
okay
okay here
no it's your turn but
i don't think you can oh yeah oh [\h__\h]
that's right
[Music]
i think i think
we can make portal here so
let's see here mommy
oh oh
i can make porto here but i don't know
what's going on the air will catch me
okay okay
[Music]
yes we used our our brain power together
preparing for human testing again i
checked an old suggestion i go to orange
you go to blue and request
less deadly tests
that's right i don't mind deadly tests
how do they know for sure the tests are
deadly
in phoenix
my
partner in science not partnering in
crime
yes
so we get a new gel now
[Music]
there's a bridge
okay i can make a portal here or oh yeah
[Music]
yes beautiful blue cobra blue yeah blue
purple blue yes
we can send it somewhere maybe and can
we make the bridge the gel to the bridge
yeah
we can test it
but we need to readjust the portal yeah
okay
can you make a portal maybe here
that's okay
we need a blue one here
uh
blue
wait
yeah and then one like there so we can
walk over yeah
wow
[Music]
in my solo run before nothing ever
happened before
putting the color on the port on the
bridge is new to me
fascinating
wow
we learned so much
say
that is new yeah
okay
we
have this
yes oh confusing
where and more color
it's really far
let me let me let me
hang there
okay
again
okay okay
it's coming
[Music]
can you go here
wait can you get
i yeah my bridge disappears when i walk
through this invisible wall
you're right
i
go
back
[Music]
can you make another blue portal there
one here and one where the
word
so we can have some uh
blue stuff on here so i can jump to you
okay you know where
though
oh
okay okay
[Music]
i have to push button oh yeah oh
oh
okay
push button push button and
now would you look at that
to or cue
high five
nice
nice ones
lucky for you too while i can't control
the world outside of the testing process
machine
[Music]
a lot of complicated [\h__\h] all the time
complicated [\h__\h]
um don't don't repeat my swear words
people will be angry that i'm teaching
you swear words in english
i guess you already use that word all
the time
no
no no
i mean not in english
like oh oh my god
oh she made everything blue over here
ah
you can also make stuff blue here
probably oh
sorry kobo where are you now there you
are i don't know
oh first of all make everything cobble
colored yay
yeah oh no
everything everything must be cobble
colored
yeah
it would make everything into a bouncy
house
yeah
you like bouncy houses i like boxy
bouncy i like trampoline
oh
ammo has a trampoline in her room i
tried it i haven't been on a trampoline
besides the on the trampoline yeah i'm
excited she did a 3d
uh trampoline stream before
[Music]
like oh yeah yeah i want to do that too
and how did you get up there yeah
momentum from here and then uh
i come there
jump jump from the
not quite
something was wrong there
jump with the chest first jump with the
oh
i think i did that
oh how did you do it
let me let me
i i watch you okay
[Music]
and then this is not what i did
oh wait
portal must have been somewhere else but
like uh when you did that huh i think
there yeah
that's where it was aha
i was just throwing stuff around i
didn't realize oh no now there's so much
blue stuff everywhere why did i do that
good
[Music]
i can't
can't
um we can't recreate what we already did
um unfortunately
what
oh wait oh
i'm doing it
just try a few times you should get
there sometime
okay i'll try my best
sometimes you just have to brute force
it yeah it's already everything is
already set in place correctly you just
have to
yeah
[Music]
i believe in you
i can't
how did i do it i don't even remember
how i did it
one more angle too straight
[Music]
my angle is too straight
you're right but how
but how oh how turned up
maybe
[Music]
can i make the portals differently
oh
[Music]
you can see a higher jumping point i can
see a higher point
i think the higher chocolate where
i know i can do a lot of
different stuff here
it already worked before i can't
i uh
to my right there's nothing on my right
ah yes
yeah yeah oh there you
[Music]
oh no no
no oh no can you do it again i'm going
to decide
i don't know but let's see
you finally got as i blocked you
no
that's okay
how did you doing
okay mommy mommy
[Music]
[Applause]
i know why that was so difficult
oh no
oh okay another more
we have once again a bridge okay
a button
here
bring
the bridged area
uh uh higher i guess can i make it here
no no but maybe i can go there oh i want
to see oh yeah you can go and then it
doesn't disappear
go check it out cobalt what's up there
oh i see it
i cannot go in
is there
anything else around you yeah yeah there
we go
we can
make the color drop
there uh no maybe just one
oh yeah and the one there okay okay okay
now we will
send the color oh
this is the super mario side jumping
again the wall jumping now send it to
the other one okay yeah
yeah there we go okay okay okay i see i
see let me let me try to hang
oh wow
have you played super mario games before
nope
also not your kind of game
no it's just
because it's really fun though
i want to but i just haven't played it
oh wait i see some stuff here oh
yeah
there's
ah
there's some more
oh
yeah
can i
[Music]
you can make a portal there too that's
good uh
yeah yeah we'll send it for the the
first one that you did
but where oh where do i need to send it
uh uh uh
here for this one
maybe maybe okay
let's try let's try
ah
and i thought it falls out angled over
here
i can
ah
okay
mm-hmm i think we try again the same
thing uh-huh
and it lands on the bridge
and then
we
oh do i want it
maybe i send it again
i think it will bounce off
oh i see i see
oh
oh oh what this is not the intended way
of doing it i think i
i'm stuck
you're stuck joe i'm stuck
can you die now
interesting
humans will die
do you want that in your memory banks
[Music]
it's close close close close
like i can do the wall here i can do the
wall
ah wrong portal i can do the wall here
and here
[Music]
if we
send the blue color there and i just get
stuck if we send it
can we send the blue color from here
okay let's try
get the blue color on this bridge yeah
i'll press the button
i'll go
ah so now i can bounce off and theory
from that and i want the rest of the
color to
can you make one here yeah it should
fall through if i get rid of my
bridge
i'll put it uh
and something maybe you can pull it here
oh okay
oh it's okay now i think oops okay
oh wait but ah no we have to do this one
first and then the bridge because now
the bridge has no more color on it
ah-ha
okay
so close one more time uh over here
please
okay
[Music]
why is there an empty spot here oh no
okay well i'll try
ah but wait let's froze some more color
and let's throw some more color i'm
scared maybe that will fill it up go go
go go more color
okay yeah okay that's better
there was a little spot with no color
okay ah and
ah
only on the bridge we only have to do
the color on the bridge again
should i don't move i just i went a
little sideways yeah but i think it
should work if i try again
oh beautiful perfect
maybe i wonder if it matters which side
i jump to first i'll jump here though uh
yeah no opening no moving no moving yeah
yeah
nice and so much easier
mario games oh man
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
going pretty well so far gladys is
impressed too
nice
koopa what are you gonna eat for dinner
today
[Music]
i don't know
i don't know i uh i ate dinner already
but i'm feeling hungry okay
[Music]
what is that
some water and uh
chicken
i don't know
but it's a
chicken dish but i don't know to explain
yeah
how do i write it i want to google it
[Music]
yes give me something i want some
something move please
i want to eat them all
so send me something
the way you the way you stay somewhere
is cute
[Music]
we have a new gel
yeah
[Music]
it makes you fast oh yeah you're right
oh
which means we want it on this platform
so that we can zoom through
it okay okay nice easy
easy
nice oh beautiful
wow
[Music]
it's
already open you can walk through
behind you
oh
i might go bye bye bye mommy no mommy
what's over there
on me
yeah
i don't know it's a long long way
oh there's a cube dropping down yeah
there's a cube i wonder what's that
come back
yeah you have to catch the cube for one
while you
uh we can go here
only if one stands on it
oh we put the cube on it
oh i see i want to catch it
where are you looking out there
so i i'll i'll push the button
yeah you push button
and i i'm going to catch it i'm going to
do a gamer move
yeah yeah
move okay let's go mommy all
right you test it once so you see when
it falls yeah
there you go see that i will try to
catch that okay but we have to time it
um
i'll count
okay
one three
okay three
two
one
[Music]
shortcut
now you made your path longer though
because you went back up yeah you're
right nice
oh
that's it that's it no not yet of course
not
wow
we're gonna be stomped on again
by the spiky machines on you
mm-hmm ah it's okay because we'll just
zoom through with the orange color yeah
um
the color
which will
go through mmm not all
it's really complicated here they're
even numbered why are they numbers yeah
there's true one the true two
one two
all right i'll try uh to put some color
here first or on it oh no
here
well first we'll just put colors
everywhere that's the way to go oh yeah
oh yeah
we need to go there
and there
yes
yes yes yes yes see now we put some
color
here
what's kobo's favorite color is it blue
of course it's blue
yeah my favorite color is orange what a
surprise what a coincidence what a
coincidence
yeah it's a coincidence
maybe we should also put it in these
rooms
i don't know should we
should we
i'll just do it
oops
[Music]
keep on pushing the wrong button put
some more
put some here
and now put some here
combo you can already think how we're
going to do this
yeah i'm thinking
um
we need to i think that's good
momentum
so
we can go there
yeah yeah i think we already uh
should already be no problem
just gonna
color this one
okay
and this one
and okay i colored everything everything
that's possible
[Music]
oh
my god
hi
you're too small to reach us should i
should i give you my hand so you can
come here no
i'm good
oh yeah ah i think
these walls maybe
we have to
[Music]
uh go
from well one wall to another really
fast yeah but what happened i'm sorry
i'm asleep can you make one blue one
here
oh no wait
yeah maybe yeah can you make try making
a blue one
over there
yes
oh you made it on the other side yeah
i'm
here
i'm here oh
okay
huh
how about this oh that gets pretty fast
nice
see what i'm doing
see how fast i can get
um
i need another portal probably here
but which one which one you uh on it
maybe light blue can you put right
through here um no no no no no no well
maybe
ah wait i'll just make a loop okay
[Music]
um
come here mommy
okay okay you make the purple here like
before
yeah yeah yeah yeah
like this maybe
we can
go there again
uh-huh
[Music]
um
yeah
i think what wasn't there a space for
porto there
yeah
i guess one has to be there what color
did you not use i think light blue
uh-huh we need
do we need more liquid ah
do we need more orange stuff
try try to run now mommy
okay
oh
okay almost at least a little bit more
momentum a little bit
just a tiny bit
ah
how do i get back there
i'll make a portal for you i'll make a
fortnite
[Music]
with a loop so i go
i guess i need a light blue
here
okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
you know this must be kind of difficult
[Music]
okay okay
i don't know yeah
oh
wait
but what's there
huh
uh there was something it was it
happened too fast i already forgot
i think it was the right the right way
we did it the right way we just gotta
whoa okay let's go let's go let's go
[Music]
oh sorry yeah the timing that was the
time and that's okay
okay all right wait uh oh wait uh uh
what if actually
what if i just use my do i need uh a
couple can you make a light blue one
where the yellow one is yeah
ah
i guess
cause chad says we can do it
[Music]
wait oh what color do i need to us
a dark blue
this one's difficult
because it's so fast
hey
[Music]
it's not your fault ah oh oh let's make
it here i guess
mango
thank you
okay
timing just a matter of timing
ow
bunk okay just go straight straight out
out
[Music]
what does this do i have a button here
what's up there oh button okay it's
right too
uh-huh i'm not sure what it does ah
ah we need to both stand on the button
and then this deck mark opens the door
well
uh
i might we might be able to
[Music]
do this while i'm here yeah yeah cause i
can also make portals here
you're right okay
i'll try to help
you can you go for the blue one again
yeah
and then okay okay you go for my portals
this time
you can run you can
[Music]
i'm gonna have to
figure out the timing um
no okay
yeah
[Music]
just trial and error yeah
okay
okay let's go again try it again
yeah
[Music]
let's go mommy
finally yes let's go button
yes
[Music]
wow
this game makes me feel so smart so
pinned up yes me too
it doesn't motivate you i'm not sure
wonder how much more chat do you know
how much more
come on
no
that's okay
do you dream of it or do you never dream
they are sometimes i dream sometimes not
and you know sometimes i got lucy
what i never had that before
but they do make a great test you can
lose it dream um
teach me i don't know
it just happened
yeah
i'm jealous i want to learn that too
oh
wait what did that one do ah cube okay
this button creates a cube over there
yeah oh
uh
huh
huh out there okay it's really big again
what if i
send
sit here mommy oh yeah
oh look where i am now hmm
oh there's a laser too okay we have a
lot of elements oh there's turrets oh no
oh no they're not looking at me
me too
do you see these portals
ah
did you see that one
yeah maybe aya can you make the
the orange gel come through that one i
wonder how far it goes probably not far
enough
[Music]
yes
wow
nice
okay
no maybe you can run
wow
um
okay so okay momentum right there can't
complete these tests we will never free
the humans
but we already have like this highway
highway to hell basically because uh
yeah we die there yeah
there was another platform there that is
uh interesting
uh
no don't go so fast stop stop stop stop
ah let's
let's send it
uh you can't see that one
[Music]
oh
wait
wait a minute
wait can you can you reach that one i
can
oh i didn't realize okay that's good we
probably have to use put it somewhere
where the laser is uh but there's no
platform there so
i'm not sure
how ah we need a bridge was there a
bridge somewhere but there's no bridge
no
no branch
[Music]
i'll learn it
[Applause]
[Music]
the first time i heard it i was already
in love hmm
but i have to learn how to pronounce
how how to pronounce indonesian
is my pronunciation okay
i think i mean it's not don't think
about the pronunciation you'll be good
you'll be good
okay
yeah
[Music]
yeah but it will just uh
yeah
it won't stay where we want it to be
uh well but i do wonder is there like a
a portable oil here or is it a normal
[Music]
yeah
okay
let's start uh by standing
uh maybe we can before the cube can we
send some color through here
yeah just see where it goes maybe it
will push the target the turrets
over
oh hi
so fast here
the cube is here now
yeah
oh yeah
oh oh no oh [\h__\h] oh my god it's so scary
it's so fast
can you make a portal again here and
then we um
oh yeah and then sent the color through
there
oh i see okay
[Music]
oh my god so fast
oh you know when we take the cube
further i think it will disappear yeah
take it through the wall
yeah
keep the cube safe
okay
um
there
[Music]
hard to see where did that
ah
it was
maybe
oh
maybe that's useless but i don't know
i don't know
[Music]
can you make uh
the yeah blue one there
okay okay i'll go uh but can you send
this one a bit more in the middle
is that possible
okay you see i see
it's kind of on the left side maybe it's
better in the middle
and now i try
where do we go okay
[Music]
wow oh no they're gonna kill me oh no oh
no okay i see
something
[Music]
now we can go over to that side though
so that's good um i think we can send
the
cube
somehow
without
but
maybe
because i wonder if the cube lands um
if the cube lands over there
maybe it will reflect everything and
kill the time where it's on yes yes
maybe like this
uh oh no
no it's useless oh
um or like this
[Music]
like this yeah
that's probably not it
wow when it's
when
okay my brain is not usable anymore
ah
what if we then it just flies through
huh
and it just goes through here and then
on it
um
[Music]
we're getting there i don't know are we
getting there
um
[Music]
almost three hours i think this will be
our last last room
let's just finish this chapter
yeah okay okay okay
yeah
but
stop a boat you wanna
give and take out the turrets yeah yeah
yeah that's what i wanna do
but we can't go far enough
i will i will go to the
platform again
when i jump over there
ah
oh i can stand here
[Music]
i think yeah okay i'll make i'll make a
a portal
um
what
wait that was the wrong
one are you still there
yeah
you want to make up
oh no
die again
put a cube on air kiana jump on air huh
you throw the cube
oh
but i think you cannot catch the cube
right
oh damn it i think i need a different
color
ah
from portal to portal on the ground to
hit the laser that hits the turret
portal
to hit the laser and hits the turrets
or tilt the portal which portal this one
[Music]
mommy i can't use
i can send the cue from oh
no yeah okay
you're dying
you want me to catch it there okay okay
when you run from here
yeah so i can uh and then i i send the
cube here
all right let's do that but
i think it's hard i don't know
all right like let's see let's see the
where's the cube
okay there oh okay there goes the cube
but wait
but when i already kept the cube so
where when i got the cube
after after you sense the cube i think
you have to put one portal
the dark blue portal here
after i get the cube
is that
manageable is that too just too fast
let's try i guess
uh it sounds difficult well let's try
but yeah because it's it's about the
timing the light light bulb light blue
light blue dark blue light nothing dark
blue
because i want to then with the cube i
want to jump
through this one
and land where the turrets are
maybe
let's try i'm coming
[Music]
okay okay i think the cube came a little
bit too late it's okay you don't need
yeah
ah
you don't need to die though if at first
you don't succeed
five more times
maybe it will refresh my brain if i die
oh okay then
but don't i need my own pointers
somewhere
[Music]
it feels wrong if i'm not using that one
here's dad
he will bring the people jumping no she
can't
she can the cubicle
oh [\h__\h] okay okay
and
three two one go
[Music]
three two one
i love us
wait wait if you don't need to die come
here come here to the portal
okay okay
uh
[Music]
so i go on one no you send it on one and
i go on zero okay
you when i say one you click the button
okay three two one
[Laughter]
[Music]
there with the cube then it will be uh
perfect
yeah okay so
uh
on one you send the cube
okay should i go even later i think
[Music]
something like that okay
three two
one
okay
oh almost okay okay okay don't go
anywhere come here oh yeah oh no oh
sorry
my phone
no no no no no
all right go but don't worry
don't worry phoenix can die many times
it won't yeah one through anything yeah
um right through it one month
rats from the ashes oh yeah three five
on ice
i'll just fall faster i guess okay maybe
it is about the same timing three two
one
oh no oh no
i'm sorry i'm sorry
ah
we need to get the cube we need to get
the cube
what maybe zero goes
out on those two four billions and
someone to hold the mirror mid air
isn't that what we're trying to do
hmm
huh
when you got the cube i'll send you
to the exit
ah okay wait can you send the cube right
now
right now
where uh just where it is like the same
way the same way as before like uh but
right um i want to see when you push the
button
push it okay now one yeah
okay
push it again
one two three
one
two
three
okay
okay try
uh oh man that's difficult
ah
maybe on zero
huh
zero
uh
i i count
i count um
i count one two
three
and then three you push
and three you push the button and then
and then
i wait
i don't know send it again okay just
destroy this right let's go try an error
okay one
two
[Music]
um
one of the wall before
but i don't understand it sounds so
complicated when you guys write it down
wait i want to see my chat i want to see
my ted now um one of the walls
when the mirror is in mid-air put the
first bottle to the other wall below
wait a minute
oh actually
on the one just a little down beside the
laser and the second one
[Music]
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm talking to my
dad no it's fine this is cute when you
speak indonesian
i'm sorry i just i don't expect you it's
easier to understand are you in
indonesian so don't worry about it
no no it's hard not to
see here
if i if i
if i bring the cube here yeah
yeah
and like like this
nah
it will disappear in the uh
wow yeah it will disappear see it will
disappear
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
huh
[Music]
can you send
the cube uh from
from here to
just just uh just through here so it
comes through here and then i can catch
it when it comes out right let me see
yeah
oh i mean i will i'll jump i will catch
it mid-air
and then i will still fly through there
and you'll just have to make a light
blue portal here
[Music]
wow
okay let's let's go
okay let's see one two
three three
got it
but uh you got it but okay oh
wait
um
uh okay i need to change the portal
really fast
it's kind of hard but okay okay let's
see
[Music]
um wait um
tell me when you're mentally ready
wanda i really can't want to find oh
wait i don't know
i i think i can help too
can i try maybe i have to make a uh
orange portal here when i'm flying and
then i fall from there that's okay i
already got it i already got it i just
need to okay okay
okay let's try one
two
three
okay i guess it deletes it that's right
yeah yeah okay got
[Music]
okay
now
i thought i thought we could easily just
block all the lasers and then destroy
them
uh
two platforms when you go into it
huh
we'll pour the walls below the laser
yeah this this this platform must have
some purples
do i have to fall through there
and
okay let's try it that way
instead of falling from here i fall
through the bottom one yeah yeah yeah
yeah that's what i was gonna say okay
let's go let's go one
two
three
wow
got it
okay
okay oh nice nice
okay one is burnt i just go ah i have to
go again um i think we have to create a
loop or that's okay
i'm sorry
oh okay mommy wait for me okay let's go
here let's go um
okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
one two
three
i could have done all of them
okay
no okay okay mommy mommy mommy mommy
mommy mommy
now you're running again
run two
yeah just run now okay let's go okay
[Music]
oh they're all gone oh yeah they're all
gone
they're all gone no you have to come
here
but okay
you make the portal now
okay
why did you put the other one though one
here one here
no one
one
here and
here yeah okay okay
okay i'm coming mommy
i'm coming
mommy
[Music]
but the other ones we did pretty well so
forgive us please
i'm sure it's not so much left yeah
probably let's finish the test this
chapter
okay
maybe we have more
orange stuff
okay
uh
exit is there there's a little space for
a cube so there must be a cube somewhere
ah yeah from here
kettle cube
oh
cute
[Music]
yeah i see
we have to run
over there to the top
and catch it in the air
okay yeah
if you stand on the on the
uh
thing that makes the platforms go up the
button or push the button
is it time limited yeah it's time to
leave me that
one two okay three four five six seven
seven seven seconds can you
ah okay
three i thought it goes through of
course because there's holes
i was thinking that was gonna happen
okay i'll send the color in other places
for now because that seems a good thing
to do
here
please stand it here
i send it here oh i'll send oh wait let
me okay okay
same thing now again
okay
i don't think it stays on the ah
okay yeah it goes through because
there's holes yeah
what's there
is that where we came from yeah
okay
um
[Music]
yeah and then jump oh but then i think i
have to put some more orange color there
yep
and on both sides i think we shall
uh yeah yeah that looks good that looks
good good enough i think
i know on it you want to try
no running running running okay
okay running
where do i send you oh yeah from here
okay okay okay
yeah
mommy ah
okay well you can land on there if i i
press the button first yep
yeah and then it stays for a while
let me see is it this button
yep okay okay
how long one two
three
it's pretty long okay
well first you start a little thing
okay keep on looping keep on moving
that's why i was able to put the orange
color here too so i can be faster to
reach the button okay
and
i think maybe do i need more color
mommy oh
not
quite why
why why why why why why it can be
reached or
i i think so
or
where they want us to
i need more color all right
okay more color in here
oh probably
there yeah yeah ah yeah that's better
now because there was some color missing
here i couldn't go fast enough
okay
now creating endless cobalt loop once
again okay
[Music]
yes
you gave it to me
that was pretty fast
[Music]
oh did you see my tweet when i tweeted
at you that um if i tweeted that too
a marriage in german
huh e h e you always laugh like
right what you type it out like e h e it
means marriage individuals marriage
yeah the security code but so every time
you laugh you say i am going to
basically marry me kiwawa
really outdoors wait oh i told him i
told him
yeah yeah but you also also love like
when i when i
when i say like mommy kiwawa
[Music]
i mean no that basically just says mommy
marriage it's not marry me if you want
to say marry me and it's uh
if you want to say marry me it's
a bit more difficult
[Music]
but i cannot no no sorry because you are
my child
i wanted to i want to kill the
turret personally
okay
but uh how do we get the cube back oh
you're so cute oh no oh no
[Music]
get wrecked turret yeah sure but cube
double was that the color
it's the orange color where how did you
get the i thought you activated the blue
color
[Music]
you got to find the vault door
how did you get the blue color to drop
there there's a button there on me
yeah for me that made the orange color
drop
ah is it see that made orange come down
oh
you see that it makes orange come down
huh orange
wait i i didn't see stop doing that
all you need to do is
[Music]
maybe we need no more blue
maybe that's all we need yeah the blue
is just dropping
oh
yeah
okay
well can we go
ah
i wanna go
it's so hot i wanna go there
i can only jump like pretty straight i
can't jump forward
i'm starting to think you don't want to
rescue this oh i guess it it all the
dropped yeah
automatically uh
ah
oh okay okay you made it go
[Music]
uh oh
now it's all over that platform but what
so it's it's bouncy now
oh
almost
huh
interesting this close
and you're going to fail me what's
what's wrong with gladys why is she
so
so desperate for attention right now
yeah
i think like there is only one way to go
there right
so we need to spread those oh yeah yeah
yeah wait can you send uh it again uh
wait no if you send it
ah can it bounce off there
i wonder
um no no no no no no okay okay
again please
i will push the button okay
now it comes through there
and we have a lot of orange i don't know
if that's enough though okay um should i
test it no i want to send one more
because there's a
a little bit more a higher another spot
which will make
the um
i'll test it out i'll test it out
oh
and that said kobo oh okay okay okay
that's all there is to that
wasn't that too easy
i think yeah you just can't do the same
thing
all right
easy
okay let's go on
and then jump at the end yeah
[Music]
okay
okay next
oh
what
an oreo
portal here
what's over here
yeah
come from my portal okay
okay
what do we have where are we going
another portal here
where would we be going down there
can we jump there no oh you ah yourself
oh interesting maybe the another blue
one here
um
blue dark dark blue
oh no we have to fall we need to yeah we
can fall
ah wait what's there nothing
um
are we able to reach the dark blue one
from the top
can
we
nah
it's in a weird spot
unless we go back here and then we jump
from here yeah yeah i think we can yeah
okay okay
oh you lost the momentum
yeah
[Music]
i think you have to go all the way back
to make the portal again
okay
[Music]
uh
through
here i think
and now
[Music]
now one more
one more
there
i need to go there first mommy please
pick me up here oh where are you
here
in the portal
oh okay
i think this cold oh damn it this color
okay
okay okay it's okay now
now i'm kind of confused
okay so we can okay
[Music]
i'll cry it's kind of narrow
let's say it's too many potato chips but
okay i made it
no diet necessary okay nice
oh
nice yes
[Music]
big big factor here big big one two
you go right i go left i check out left
side
hmm eh
uh-huh there is a button inside but i
can't get inside
i can't get it
combo this is the last room really yeah
okay
nice um
it's so hard
oh there's an orange
color all the way at the top so i think
we have to
this one we have to bring on this whole
middle platform the one in the center
[Music]
i don't understand how do we get there
leave it to kiwama mommy i look at your
side is it the same i wonder no i think
it's not
hmm
not the same oh yeah it's not the same
oh
oh you can send some color here oh
interesting
[Music]
oh
okay
hmm
that's
weird because of the
if you leave the room then the portals
are gone
oh
there's a
a higher level up there i wonder what's
there
but this is only for zooming
[Music]
you need to go up there
ew it's such a slimy sound here
ah
but how can i get there
[Music]
wait that sign says there's there would
be a cube coming out
or does it want us to
make the cube orange can we make a cube
orange which cube though i guess it's up
there
on the ground look at the ground oh
oh
oh [\h__\h]
okay yeah i wanna try
oh
okay okay okay it's like it's like the
previous one oh
so close no no no no no i think mommy
mommy
yes yes
yeah oh
and then you change the
portal where the yellow one currently is
you put your dark or light though
[Music]
um the problem is when i am in the air
um i like i can't i can't move much more
[Music]
maybe we try
ah
uh-huh uh
i think uh i think i know something
can you try just telling me the same way
again
and then i you have to look around
because there is portal surfaces up
there that i did not see okay and then
yeah
i'll just leave one
i'll just leave mine maybe here okay
okay
[Music]
oh
oh no
ah okay i see
okay
oh here i am
i saw
some important surfaces okay okay okay
i i just put one there and then we can
walk up okay
okay i made it
now we should be able to get up here
oh yeah
what's that cute
hi cube we can't greet you we need the
color we need to go let me let me let me
let me let me okay
oh yeah i see it
okay oh
yes it came to me
nice it's covered in orange jam now
[Music]
where do we want to cube though
can you send some more color
wait where did you ah can you can you
push the button
yeah i can
tell you
[Music]
oops
one more please
okay
how about oh
nice i think i don't know what that is
for yet but it might be useful later
okay
now i was there something to insert the
cube down there
um
[Music]
ah
okay can you send it
i don't know why i did that but can you
send it through like a portal the
dark yeah
what's over there i'll come there too
oh
there's oh
do we have to push this override button
come here try to
see here mommy
hi hi hi
oh
uh
uh-huh
okay
now you come too okay how cute you work
i think we could do it differently too
but this is cute
that's really cute yeah
yeah
what is it hey what is down here
is it
there's nothing here
it's not mom yummy
okay i die oh you died thank you forever
there's just deadly water there
there's nothing else there
nothing nothing there here okay then
we
show
i have to come back to you
yeah
can you put a portal there and then
there or maybe somewhere where i can
break it or maybe here um
i want to come back to you
okay sorry um
[Music]
so what's up here oh
this was where you went before okay why
does the game tell us to go here there's
literally nothing here is this just
gladys trick to kill us maybe perhaps
even though we can just jump
ah
glados you tricked us
yeah nothing here
but wait do we want
several cubes and if we want free cubes
and every cube needs to block one of
these lasers
because i think they're activating
something
this thing here
but we can
we can have more than one cube right
oh
really
yeah okay let's let's put one down here
first
ah it falls down okay but that's
interesting because ah
i see
i think it has something to do with
these platforms maybe you can stand here
and see what changes when i put the cube
uh onto the laser okay
you're right
down and you have to run over to the
other side
snow number two no number two
uh
i i have to do them all kind of like at
the same time almost yeah i'll show you
yeah yeah i see oh yeah
that's
well that's a glitch
[Music]
explain that to me game
now i need a new cube where did i get
the cube from again
wait no i can't go on my own wait wait
wait wait where is the cube on here god
damn it
small indie company is it really an
indie company
okay i'm i can get the new cube i i got
it uh i just need some color on it i
guess otherwise it won't slip wait do we
want it to slip
i think we wanted
i don't know why why why do i die
why why
i want to call
wait before you come up here can you
uh activate the color
oh no
i'm sorry
yeah we want the cube to be covered in
the orange gel again wonderful otherwise
it won't even come down okay
now
yeah we go over
and you check the
the platforms and i go um
okay where was it
[Music]
here
but the cube is safe all good yeah it's
okay
wait we have to run together
nah no way no no no no no you just need
to make a portal there you have to make
a portal you just slip over
ah
okay
wait a minute okay now
thank you and
okay now you go here again
yeah
okay
okay bye-bye
i think it may be better if that's my
portal because you may maybe you need
your portals okay okay okay i'm not sure
i'm just making my portal okay okay
number one okay i will i will i will let
it slip three two one
[Music]
yes yes and push the button or something
here
i mean the timing is of the essence
there but you have to put them over
right
you don't need to you don't need to
to you know to to pass the cube to throw
the cube up come true
yeah just just bring your cube the cube
oh my god bring my cue manually manually
yeah no don't throw the cube
oh no um okay please don't make me
i'll make a portal
oh okay okay you can come up no
maybe you should do the cube
okay
okay we're so cute
we need we need to
to gel the cube first
yes it's
uh
ready
now
okay
okay i'm coming
okay i'll hold the laser one by one
yeah one by one buy one by one okay
let's go okay
so it's me or you
i'll i'll do it i'll do it
okay
i can do it i can do it
okay i'm holding okay first and then now
second second huh
no
yeah
okay second one okay
no cheese
okay
out
reach up wait let me i don't know what
is this okay all right
and then that's it
that's oh you can reach both
perfect
look to the right what happened
what happened i think
yeah we just did some
i think it's in order to open the big
door maybe
so we need we both keep going
we
uh at the same time we have to trigger
the the button
right there
okay that's right yeah
okay
but then that means i have to let loose
off the cube hmm
i have to let loose
yeah from
um
from here i guess and yeah i need to run
oh yeah
yeah okay let's go let's go let's go
mommy
wait let me orientate myself i will go
to the right okay okay i'll go to the
right side okay
for the right uh
this one okay that's where i'll go okay
okay left okay
okay let's come over here
let's go
[Music]
beautiful
is that it do we just jump over did we
just zoom over wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
no no no no no no
uh okay maybe yes okay
let's go um wait let's even your sound
[Music]
we need to override that too or what
what's that but we didn't really check
out the other room at all this one
okay now it's time for that
um
[Music]
okay let me
i'm not you again how do we get rid of
those
[Music]
all right so this one
what's that
this one lets
the color go aha
i make uh
ah
i can't
uh can you make a portal can you see it
from there i guess you can't make a
portal there now i can make porto here
it will disappear so oh wait there's an
airflow
there's an airflow over there
you're alright you see that
so
where
i put the airflow
through now
so
if you
if you can move the
portal here
can you move the airflow to somewhere
else yeah
that should help with something
but something but how can
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i deleted it ah
let me i want to look at it
hi
[Music]
oh
no oh
no no no no
oh
no no no no i wanted some color here i
wanted some color okay not enough hair
let me just drop some color now
for whatever reason we'll figure that
out soon enough
um
[Music]
we have the balance we can do oh no we
can probably bring the air somewhere uh
the air i don't know i don't know what
i'm saying can we do this all mommy
mommy uh like this
oh no oh i almost
can't
ah
oh
what
um
[Music]
yeah i think your idea was very very
good
we will work on that
where will be this um
[Music]
there's no reverse button anywhere huh
reverse would be nice
button or reverse
ah
i want i want the gel to go to that side
too yeah
and
we send
make one portal here
okay and one here
up here
okay and now we let the
color go
and we send it over to the side
ah and now hook to the other side i know
yeah yeah go to the other side and make
uh
a portal [\h__\h] ah
i was thinking
no it's picking right
do um the other way around because i
think i'll i understand
um
we do it the other way around
when you're back
out uh you just put the
your portal
you're putting the one here
[Music]
and one here
yeah and the rest leave it to me you
stay on the button
okay on this button
and
we press
the color
oh [\h__\h] that's too early that was too
early
i press
the button
we wait for it to go through
and then yeah i want to put one here and
one
yep
oh
[Music]
yeah that's what we're gonna do and then
they'll bounce around and they can
control themselves anymore okay so
we sanded again
and this time i just don't want to get
killed
one here
okay and then i drop it
somewhere here
[Music]
now we can safely go to the other side
can we hopefully
yeah oh
[Music]
there is more but wait there's more
oh do we need to
oh does one person wait a minute
[Music]
does one person have to go back and stay
uh
sending the air
still the same way we sent now oh maybe
not maybe not
oh do we need more color
should i go back and send more color
cobble is dead oh that's what she meant
with wait wait
ah
oh there she is
sorry
it's my brother i'm sorry
oh
my altar
yeah yeah ah ah cool
yeah see this one
um
that one maybe helps oh i see
oh
i see so i don't know i don't know how
though
maybe like this
maybe like this one there one there and
then
light blue i don't know
ah
but yeah we send okay
we sent the air
through there you go up
that way first
and then
but that's not lined up perfectly can we
i can can you make the portal here
yellow portal okay
yes
ah okay you did land in it nice
and then i'll make one here
okay
then again
and then oh there's a platform there
yeah
oh there's a button
we can go back now mommy
i will just go jump in here into the
water take a nice bath with lush bath
bombs
yeah we're done
we did it
we don't know yet that's right
i have reached something the other side
oh hello
[Music]
huh camera
camera in the lock try something okay
okay glad i was trying something
try something try something always just
you can using her test subject yeah well
i think there's nothing here gladys your
little [\h__\h]
[Music]
you can't fail
top left
[Music]
oh
i see i see two where are we
we're free
are we
where are we going now
towards freedom where the humans are you
gladys believes us that we're humans
what happened oh here's god it's worth
it
you just look at all those test subjects
yeah oh my god the testing
oh the testing yes let's go glass saved
science
what
sorry global
humans life be their own worries
as long as the robots survive
everything's cool um
okay yeah yeah
oh no
there seems to be still like a dlc but
obviously we're not doing that today but
maybe another time if we wanna get there
oh oh so many errands
is that the credits
is this not a team
we did it we did it we finished it yeah
yeah yeah yeah
but we finished the main game yeah oh
nice
yeah we finished it guys
yeah
it was a little bit too painful
sometimes maybe for the chat sorry that
well which took so long sometimes yeah
i think we grow a few extra brain cells
today brain cells really
yeah
that's a big indie team big yeah big
brain cells christian
wow so these are oh no they're using the
people who worked on the game to test on
them oh no
oh that was you
oh there's me
what is all the turret
so
cute credit actually
yeah i like it it's fun i like the music
people yeah people people
like the crowd you like 8-bit music it's
kind of like that i beat yeah yeah
no not really but
yeah i enjoy it
[Music]
thank you ivan thank you jacob thank you
j vote shake up with okay thank you
james thank you jane thank you jared
thank you jason thank you
thank you day thank you day
deep dave
dave dave yeah
jeff
[Music]
oh
one in portal 2 alone you need to play
it solo because it's really so much fun
and you're so much lore you need to play
it cool
okay baby and you will understand the
meaning of the companion cube
okay i'll i'll play
i'll play portal one maybe
don't worry after you play portal 1 you
will want to play portal 2.
you will want to but you can stop before
the line just give it a try okay give it
a try okay
how how did how does channel enjoy the
the game today
i i think chevrolet is happy to meet you
oh
yeah
what's wrong with that you know i mean i
want to adopt both both chebo and kobo
yeah okay
is olivia table's girlfriend
no are you dating
no not
you should ask her out just uh like a
little brother to olivia that's what
olivia said
yeah
that's sad i'm sure cebu has some
feelings for olivia and then they are
unrequited and and sheba's heart is
broken because olivia only sees channel
as her small brother but gemma has
feelings
[Music]
some others there's more there's more
voices
oh oh oh the voices yeah whitley whitley
[Laughter]
lately my buddy
waited my best friend yeah he come he
only shows up in the solo game oh and
cave johnson too you only heard gladys
but there's more characters in the game
actually i see
oh
okay
british
mother-ish buddy
wesley is british
can you do a british accent kobo
uh
wingardium leviosa
wow
yeah
okay
[Music]
no
[Applause]
oh there it is we finished watching the
credits beautiful
[Music]
my british accent is perfect i don't
know what you're talking about
[Music]
no thank you no more of that
maybe one day
for now i think we're done testing our
brain
it's a dlc
and apparently
um
[Music]
sorry i kept you up so late
no it's okay i know you're
busy so you're
probably tired
and me no oh uh if eternally we can play
more
we can play more but i thought you
wanted to
finish uh after three hours now it's
already four hours cool full of four
hours with mommy flowers nice yeah
as long as i'm with you
yeah
um i'm okay uh for
four hours five hours six hours it's
okay
for some reason awake on friday during
my stream i think it's in the middle of
the night for you but i will try to sing
and mantra
so maybe maybe you can be there well i
think it's gonna be very late for you
when well you can watch tv on friday
friday no saturday saturday night
saturday night saturday night but it's
like i think maybe three a.m or so for
you maybe when friday
yeah but actually yeah then it's sunday
[Music]
something like that
maybe uh otherwise you can watch the
clip i'll do my best
[Music]
saturday what is saturday it's 16
oh oh okay it's okay
oh i'm watching you
for sure not really okay oh i'll sing it
in the beginning then you don't have to
stay up for too long
okay
thank you for today hope you enjoyed
this chat uh
somewhere
at koala action
[Music]
uh
but when there's water in the fire then
there will be no more fire kobold
that's sad
you're right
no
don't extinguish me
no no okay
because you're the phoenix
i'm the
song of water and fire beautiful
greek fire burns in water excuse me well
i'm not a great fire i'm an austrian
fire if anything all right cobalt i wish
you a good night everyone in the chat
good night how did i say good night in
indonesian
[Music]
yeah
and in germany
is german right
yes it's true it's good enough but i
always have an ending greeting that's of
widazin i always say it
so it's goodbye
[Music]
together yes that's two
i write it down so that i don't forget
okay i hope i hope you don't uh you know
i'm sorry if i
do uh i i don't know if i'm annoying
because i
oh
i love you you're not annoying i mean i
mean i like um i don't speak too much
maybe okay it's okay because my my
english is not perfect either so you
speak in english in simple vocabulary i
speak simple easy vocabulary it's
perfect
yeah uh
because sometimes i don't understand my
own gen mates
i don't understand what they're saying
[Laughter]
maybe your english will improve if you
if you
collab with me
um
yeah for sure yeah thank you
thank
[Music]
me to you this collab stream from the
start
thank you so much i'm really happy
and i just i just don't want to
end this
and this is so cool
because we already finished the game so
we can
cope look at my hands yeah i look at
your hair beautiful hand wait i can't do
my wait no i can't do my heart to my dad
i want to do my heart for you yeah
i i give you
i give you my heart
[Music]
give you i give you
everybody
um
i just don't want to
end this here because you know
it can't be so cute
[Music]
we should play like i don't know mario
party with some friends or so i love
mario party or monopoly
oh okay okay
we can play a lot of games
[Music]
thank you
yeah
okay
you have okay switch right do you have a
nintendo switch
[Music]
so
woof
[Music]
do
foreign
[Music]