[Music]
the song is really great
okay okay okay hello hello
hello first how are you I have to
speak German German German German
German German German
I'm missing
the game capture here
Moment
tired
best second channel of a youtuber
ever that's an exaggeration
[music]
today we're playing
through the German beautiful
[music]
it's over the plants
because I don't have any separate layers okay
yeah not that bad not that bad
looks good or
plays well  on  German
oh oh do you link yes
[music] wait a
minute
first water need water
need a little water
detention
that Josh that's Japanese too and
I can't get out of the habit of that I'm
sorry
every time I've put my foot on it
since I hurt myself  not
streamed in English already or GTA was
in between or my foot is fine,
although today I
wore shoes that I haven't worn for a long time
and then I
got a blister,
it hurts, oh dear, oh dear,
we thought, yes, I'll ride with
them  Public transport and then I
somehow walk for 15 minutes because there
seems to be no other way and then
BAM after a few meters I have a
blister on my foot, the one on my
Achilles tendon,
yes, but the one where I hit myself is
n't that bad,
let me tell you  compare the size of
my toes
looks normal yes
looks normal everything was good it was very
painful but it got back
to normal quickly but I hit myself on the wall
so aggressively with such a swing
that I really
thought it was over now I have it
really hurt my toe  broken
because apparently you often break your toes without noticing it
during your lifetime.
You know, I've
already mentioned that, I think
milk fits the bill
[laughter]
yes, and I thought that's what
happened now, but  It wasn't that bad,
I mean maybe I
broke it but no, probably not,
but if it happened like that and you didn't even
notice it
then it could be that the toe
doesn't hurt that much or if you
wouldn't even notice it yourself
I have to break my toes more often in my lifetime
was one and a half
well the little toe yes for me it was
more like the ring finger toe
oh Düsseldorf no you
want to trigger me again
and who did that ah you are you are sick
sister oh what
oha oha I could never do that
I have a video today  I watched
something that was a bit medical and didn't
show any blood or anything,
but it was about a topic
that somehow made me feel sick
but there wasn't any blood at all or it did
n't show anything really blatant, but
I watched it out of interest
because  I the information
but
just thinking about it made my
stomach turn and
then I had to turn it off because I felt
really sick even though
it really wasn't anything bad,
no actually it wasn't anything bad
that had anything to do with injections
yes, because I don't actually have a problem with injections per se
[music]
because, for example, with the
vaccination, yes, that wasn't a problem either.
Thinking about such information is not a problem
for me, but with this topic
I just can't,
yes,
um, well  I would ask you
is so so sweet  It's also that you're
interested in it, but I would ask you
not to push me here on the channel
to collaborate with certain people.
If I
feel like doing something like that, then I'll do it on my
own, don't worry, I'm already
aware of others  Youtubers who speak German
and if I take that into consideration
then I already have the
knowledge
that I need to invite these people,
no problem so yes we
have only just started with the
channel but maybe there will be
a collaboration
yes yes okay well we play that  Here
now for about 2 hours I
have to have a playlist of maybe a run
really what I should play because then
I can make it bigger
it's so small
[music]
so long about to play like I was about
to cancel the stream where are you
I was racking my brain as if
it were such an important decision,
it's not that important now but it doesn't
matter what or but but no I
was racking my brain but I
mix in English sometimes
no complaints yes here my
main base on  TV
English
wrecking my [ __ ] brain not a bad
choice really
music slaps yes
music is really cool
I didn't expect a surprise about
what is love it's a road like
welcome to
[Music]
the only game show where your
biggest dreams come true
[Music]
but will your dreams come true or yours
Nightmares no
no oh no ways the night Emote
let's find out here is our
host
[music]
no that would be cool if I
could do a show like that too,
the wonderful Chihuahua is still coming
[music]
thank you very much, dear audience  and
welcome back to my labyrinth
of endless  in horror our
next participant will die big or
lose everything
we could find out here is
ah I don't know
exactly my love that's how it works here
tell me warrior what inner emptiness has
driven itself to risk endless banishment
at my hand
most expensive why are you playing  you today,
yes, I actually wanted to
win a monster truck and also
become the strongest man in the world,
how inspiring. Well, you know that
we here at Dyson Dungeons say that
luck doesn't make you great, but it
's too late, your opinion too  change
why are they dice click on the
box and go to you okay I do
n't have to do that you can jump on them okay
oh a sword what choose
I didn't choose anything that was
there was nothing in the middle but okay
then I'll go back who
is who is Space Marine who is speaking
man or woman hello player is this
the first person side to
power up the old plasma blaster again
put your die on the sword
oh so
great because you used a 5
you did five damage
ahh okay cool cool  his number is up
click on the end turn button when you're
ready okay I'm ready
Spongebob I'm ready I'm ready
something if the thing reaches zero you have
problems
okay
oh no
that's okay sometimes that happens that's
just
you can reroll up to three times per turn
oh
the war  just a special ability
okay okay fight so the
special ability is three times onions
okay
that's all scripted here
does yes yes
yes we're coming now of course
[music]
I don't want to really break out now
because then everyone will say it's so bad again
click on the end move I think okay
but  fast  on
a
limit break on click on to
use other mint
doubled next action ready in
eight HP
so now I just know how I already
activated or how so this will
now be twelve yes yes
yes
okay wonderful cool
apple doesn't make you healthy again oh apples
I even have that  not eaten I
thought he would pick it up automatically
when he walked past no okay
aha a
maximum of four because that's twice yes okay
what if I got a six I
said what if I got a six really
okay but now we can get it
exactly okay
what's a  Difference if I go
back and forth to the individual fields here  don't
I lose any moves or anything
[music]
oh he's a fiery head
aha oh well I can't use
them now I can't use the battle wagons for you
but it gives me
a selection here this camera it
needs a lot or less yes good  yes
[ __ ] man okay yes then I'll do
this once here and then we have
this in here
now I don't have a good
number again but not in this case oh
fuckingham yes okay that's
fine you're over it
use status effects this fireball
about that  is pretty hot
yes fireball fits well but maybe
not against that one or are you already using it
against me
or yes yes yes yes
I thought because it burns yes
oh what did one of my cubes burn
[applause]
that times two is just sex
then I could use it  don't kill at all
it doesn't just cost two hearts
ahh
[applause]
okay okay we'll do that I would say
[music]
okay well well
I've already forgotten what that means again
so
I should have done the one before, I
should have done it twice now  had
oh
I didn't do well  pre-planned [ __ ] yes
good yes
[applause]
we are little heads
is the learning profession
[music]
you get episode okay good that's what we
needed and to Gerlingen
better
okay yes next what should I
go here so once there
a match burns you
burning dice
but
okay we have to try
that out I would like to see it in action
[music]
number rolled plus one cool
okay there is an exit but I have to
fight against the courtyard
of course I have to fight against the
one at the train station
it works like this  fast  gone
the what
[music]
has to plug it in but let me tell you a
secret it's dying today
the equipment okay
now he's on the screen quite a bit
okay I can even here
maybe it's a good thing we saved each other
because it's over  the
following fight apparently is
n't bad okay so once
I'd like to re-roll it and again
very well
so I'd do that again too [ __ ]
I don't have anything for four it
's okay it's okay wait I want wrath
and then the doubling then the
[  Music]
then okay, he still has it  not done
but it's coming soon or a wait
no no I thought of the skin too now
I just have more dice
what
[music]
thought of the skin then uh 6 + 1 that's
seven twice so 14 like that but he
just doubled the dice for me
yes, great, I can't use the rest
unless I do it and that does
two damage
[music]
[ __ ] man snowflake
and what's up and Charlie these
shitty cubes on oha
okay
okay here mom there twice
the green I still don't understand
oh well if I do that now  If I
were to put two in then I would
get another two dice or less
one I don't need I'm
already done I can then a three
oh so okay yes now I
don't need that anymore or have I misunderstood
[music]
make it rocky his
is also misunderstood, I
thought if one of my dice
burned
then it would make the burning go away
but they didn't explain it well.
I think putting the dice down in shock
triggers what
[music]
sounds like what
is a bastard
[music]
[ __ ] now  I did that wrong
[Music]
because
[ __ ] then I can
put myself in here and now if I do that but
convert the environment,
yes well
[Music]
yes well then I'll open this up with it
and do the treasure here
now I have it again  not
used but I don't know how
why not appoint the prank
[music]
oh no
I have how to do it
okay okay what happens now if
I throw this in here you should
it should be a
sausage what I put a number on it  I
only ever have one die from him
burn
[music]
has to be straight
well wait then I want a two
okay you can
try me out okay he burns once if it
was worth it we don't know
a little bit of damage here and here still
okay
[music]
he too that I but  a little bit painful
when he attacks it right
[music]
and my HP is so low, my HP isn't at all
what's that now
[music]
I can't use these three
but whatever
a little weaker okay here BAM okay
until then I could have sworn
that's it  dying was oh oh goes my
Your o'clock will be with O'clock is it right now at
your place
no
fits no PM
okay home
and now it's supposed to be the lava
where am I here so I can
fight it I can go to a shop
I can fight a marshmello a burning
marshmallow and  I don't
really care about dancing,
I'm going to go to the marshmallow
[music]
tutorial complete first, there's
nothing scripted here anymore or was
n't it at all who knows but well
okay I understand
then we'll put this in here
had it burn once then I'll hit it  in
here
Bürkle that in the hope of getting a 4,
it's still a three but that
's okay,
that's what you would have
done,
what does the snowball and fireball do,
they can do everything
then the mom cinema 3 + 1 would be better to
start three
why  oh well then I would have got a four
then I wouldn't
have had to change it here
[music]
anyway ah yes that's right, [ __ ] is good yes
but
you don't like that, that's okay
I would roll it again now
or would you put it in  toast
give it in
again okay okay okay and
again yes
and now just one
because then at least maybe we'll get
one more exactly exactly
okay okay okay okay
[music]
then we can kill now
is dead
no bad bad
yes the music  It's really loud, actually
there's something quiet like that,
so I'll take that, it
looks more interesting somehow
ah if it's an even number
then I do damage with its
odd number I do it really cool
I want that thing
I have the option of the shield  so
against
the beer what are you doing here you
should be on the sea
so I have one in here
one really new then I'll do that
then I'll do that then I'll do that
then I'll do another one and then
I'll finish it
wonderfully
next
show me  what you can
[music]
are you one reason why I chose oil
because I thought if it's in German
then games are where at least
somehow explanations are like that then
it even brings what it is in
German because then I understand  I
understand it better than in English  It would be easier for me
if I had somehow just
played Mario Kart or something like that then
I wouldn't have been able to take advantage of it at all. I
wanted to use my language but there
's not that much text here. They
make you like the game then you have a
text in cele  Mario cars
of the German anyway here uh one in here
ah yes that's true it doesn't work
wonderfully perfection again
wow that's that's not nice WhatsApp
back
it
that's [ __ ]
what are we doing
okay we don't need it at all
I'll save it because  apparently
in the next few years  Be taken into battle
okay once here
why do I have a hair in my mouth
and I already have that what's the
point of
having that again I then have
an extra option to poke
Jolanda
oh a new adventurer walk in
I'm barely at the dungeon
I have here  a few great things in
stock do you need to wash socks a
potted plant no who needs socks do
I need them because I have some
holes in them I haven't bought any for a long time
okay what do we want do I have anyway
how much money do I only have five
[music]  the
plus two damage a
maximum of three different
[music]
poison is nice if that yes
present
okay I guess that's really cool
can I only go to a shop like that once
ah no I can go back in
okay we just don't have any money  more okay
let's go
[applause]
[music]
larynx okay the characters are
pretty good
I'm going first because it's
lower leveled
we would have bought ourselves in shock
but then we'll make it quick
quick thing out of it
once here
then
that'll now be 16 more damage  do
or
yes
still  a good old one
that was very well rolled I
somehow didn't waste anything I do
n't think that's nice no no no no
no no okay we can
do that again actually
oh he's already dead oh that's quick
you what
boring boring doesn't even really do any
harm  Done
okay, I can strengthen something or
that's how it comes to life.
I've also been able to strengthen cards.
Interesting,
what should I improve here? The best thing
I can do is actually have money for
it. Bye Simone in another one. Oh wait, I actually have to
put this over to my equipment  change so that
I can do that  at all times I thought
it was random
where is the difference there
is no difference here there is no difference
there is really no difference that is
a difference that no longer has to be straight
oh so it's about space
oh so
stuff and carry that means
[  Music]
plus a damage
[Music]
Yes, I don't know how long I would
carry these beginner things with me,
whether I should go for some of the newer
things
[Music]
Yes, but smaller would be cool, yes then
I can take one of those in  without
making any kind of loss, although I
don't really have enough
dice either  I have the most time to really
take advantage of everything
that uses the
maximum of 5 o'clock
twice an hour
and here
[music]
it doesn't have to be a maximum of five anymore
ah I could protect myself very strongly
if I wanted to,
okay but no then first  I do that
there
yes and then another time I make the
sign
I think and then here I now have
space for
the claw
nice nice interesting
nothing
very Inter
okay something new here a cactus look
how cute he is so scared
cute
I'll do it
[Music]
that
's all the numbers  too high so I mean
I have
no like that and then I need
no that's not really good either
[music]
and the dice don't come with me on
the next turn right
or or oh so that's just
what I didn't think of
[music  ]
okay
cactus,
he protects himself completely from me
I suffer three damage if I attack in the
round one for each thorns
three damage yes
I would still attack, I
think
okay
[music]
now I'll just do it
no
[music]
I have an idea  I'll do this and
then  I do that
and then it's
[music]
hey
level 4
[music]
let's go
very good very good what's in here
crystal sword
5 three times damage once program
okay now it doesn't really come to me
much space I'm going to go we don't
need HP we don't have it  Just
ticked off the level,
it's that far, it's somehow
easier than ladies because who knows then
there's a bit more information
so it's quite easy actually
[music]
let's see
nice and yes the 6 is just a bit
wasted then or but
what should you do  I don't have anything else
anymore
[Music]
okay now I'm angry
burning light what are you doing
no it's burning it's burning calls the
fire brigade
1 2 2 what do I think
two dice oh
interesting I know it can't go any higher
yes [ __ ] if I ever oh so in
Germany but  In Austria it's already
122, I think hopefully otherwise
I would have a problem if there was a
fire in my place. Thank God the last
time the whole thing was automatic and
I didn't have to call anyone, it's
okay,
okay then you don't have to
worry
[Music]
We still need six damage okay,
yes, different in Austria but
similar, that's confusing a bit
okay, now we need healing here
and now we can buy it
[Music]
I can I could heal myself but at the
moment it's
ours  our
HP actually isn't that bad but
maybe in the future
before the Future Baby healing
for the future
[music]
in Austria both should
end up at the fire department oh is that so oh
perfect for two A's yes
I don't need that
okay I'll take it  that
at some point we might
need
Sunday
okay where are  we here
kristallina
Yeti and a branch
[music]
also a kristallino
40 HP holy [ __ ] and I'm not
even fully healed oh [ __ ] that could
go wrong then let's see how
strong she is
okay let's start
here oh no that's right  That doesn't work
here
then we roll the dice 1 9
perfect 3 is what I need then there is
that too and
I'll risk it again for more damage
okay now I don't want to risk it anymore,
wait but I could still get angry should I
now  or pick it up I'd rather keep it
when I can do more damage
yeah okay
next
what was that again
air crystal
hollow Christa
not yet
okay I might do anger and then
battle ax
then I have eight times two again 16
[music]
and then here this  are the face
then there is again
and yes
how does it feel hey
you still don't kill okay
[music]
now we don't really have to
rack our brains
[music]
easy easy that's gone
too easy too easy have too much  Lucky
maybe
oh he would have even been weaker
with 20 HP
on
Hartmut weak against fire oh I have a
burn
match yeah okay
numero un
o and here that and that
and that perfect
not to be heard in German that's
strange but it's nice thank you
for me it is  still so strange
[music]
still very strange okay here
again the three
[music]
nice then I'll just do it
no that's a waste oh lol
[music]
worse what okay what are you
even doing leave them here now too
Here's what
you want  an I'm just winning
what are you talking about
a stick magic magic magic now comes
the magic here comes the magic
[laughter]
[music]
yes he lost and me loose
loser
six fire damage a fire die burns
one of my dice that's
somehow not  so clear but you tell
me sure
show
now you come oh [ __ ] ah I should have
put the fire stick in his
everything is okay okay okay yes I
always doubt it well here
and here
[music]
and
okay no problem
[music]
circle people well ah  yes, looks good,
I have to watch all the Marvel films
[music],
are there a lot of Marvel films on Netflix
already or do I have to do some bingo
action here? I've hardly seen any,
I only think I've seen Heroes of the
Galaxy once and  I used to watch
the first Spider-Man film, maybe it was
great, I even did that. Well then
what is your favorite Marvel film what
you favorite Marvel movie guys
ahhh
[music]
love is strange Tor
Captain America Iron Man
giant man Deadpool
if you liked watching Spider-Man  watch
Avengers everyone
[Music]
yeah good
no choice
[ __ ] didn't go so well
a bastard that doesn't exist so of
course I'll kill him now but that
's very close yeah because
okay then I'm not allowed to
attack you because otherwise I could
wait for the [ __ ]  That's actually wait, it's
not that easy because new damage with
two dice
okay that okay okay I can do that
okay okay okay everything's good
everything oh my god
I can improve or shield hit
double a hit with the shield well
I want to improve I think ah yes
my HP costs then are  again full
I take that
and
what happens here more damage
and here it gets smaller
three times damage I think I'll make
the crystal sword smaller
okay do we want to put it in somewhere do
we get more slots or does
it always stay like that
matchstick away good good idea more
Potential yes
should I also replace my sword
who is
good or
why does it say eight it is always 8
why does it say eight
sex harm but why does it say eight
would keep the sword
so I need one
what I need
so I need a six and then
two or  what, oh
or so  no matter how much
it's full of [ __ ] I have to roll more
dice than it does damage
no then only when I improve
maybe then
I'll keep the sword for now
what is that why is the green the
tutorial shop
a trading station here you can
exchange things if  It absolutely has to be
oh but no we need the healing crystal
for the future
no deal there was a TV series
but on German television about it
but there are certainly all over the world
right that's one of those
series
I want to have my i  wanna keep  my healing
what doesn't start here 4 4 ​​5 okay then
let's go this way first I would
sayor
4 5 4 and then to the shop what if they take
us
with the motorcycle
Aurora
Aurora why is Aurora why did I have
such a design
music again  totally popping
okay okay I should
wait a maximum of five when I realize
that you have to do it one, five rows
and before that Zorne
said that I would do it,
I wanted to put it in here but
somehow my my brain was somewhere
what the [ __ ]
well okay
yes  okay
[ __ ] but I would have anyway  no no
it's okay that fits like that yes never mind never mind no
we already had enough of them in
Europe
no no no no no no no we do
n't play GTA here
I would have them too I had Aways one hit
hurt and
the second something else we will never
know
Well, well, brain, you just need brain, that
's the streamer problem,
you're somehow distracted,
he body for the first time
[music]
you just missed one and we
have
a
very German one here, I've
never heard of it before, so I always say advises
even when I speak German
you have
well Berry is such a hat a kind of
food advises in northern Germany
[music]
improve or which poisonous slime
is only poisonous if I also have a 6
dice
I think I want to improve
and we said
I'll do the shield maybe
first or
[music  ]
you know what doesn't know who
is limited then I can do the shield instead of the
sword then I always have the
choice either six damage exactly that
I still have the choice if I
just have sex or I just do shield
I think that does  Meaning
then at least I have the choice, that's
all  OK,
but wait a minute in the playlist, I can see
in advance what they're
going to do in the next turn, but here I don't really see it,
so sometimes I can
maybe guess but or
so when do I know that I have to block,
just out of intuition
here  long
because of that
[music]
do it again okay
he can do that
and I don't know what he rolls okay
aha
[music]
once
12 with three dice so what is
this he has to fill it up with 12 right
and then you get but  only five damage
and he blocks one dice for me
oh well I have to use the singles
if I have them okay but that's
not a lot of damage and that's just
okay interesting okay
in important fights I'll take a look
at it and then I'll see if  I
should block
St
oh awesome
like another five is awesome
yes
the perfect move people
here the perfect move baby
perfect
[music]
yes come
here
[laughter]
[music]
she left me no
anyway that was amazing should I just
talk like that
but you can do it so well  That also
mix um all the whole sentence already here
separate in German and English
is it half full or not
prison Denglisch oh she she he blocked
my one DICE blocked
oh so I can't even use that as a one
I thought he would just
block me that  to change but okay I
can't lose him that's good
a lonely and not that bad it
's not that bad I don't always speak
English oh man you're
stupid [ __ ] okay that's not that good not
that ideal I would like to have one
that
but we have an almost down already
three times two
yes it's already going already it's already
going already
so I had
an important
professional
conversation today my dear people and
[music]
with the professor so yes a formal
conversation
a sun meeting yes in person
and
it's exactly a meeting where you
would sit and
speak to each other very politely
and I was a bit
embarrassed when my German failed like that.
I couldn't find the words in some cases
and in cases where, for
example, I would have plural something in the plural
I should say somehow in the
singular in the singular and  so completely
embarrassing
[music]
[applause]
[laughter]
yes, but I hope you did
n't notice it so much and thought to yourself that
he was completely stupid,
didn't go to school and that's
why it was raining, I thought that was
good timing
Timing
[music]
you should
this [ __ ] gave me something
this [ __ ] [ __ ] cursed it and
that's why it took it away from me
[music]
I saw that it was
just a random like I couldn't have
known or
yes music  is banger
what for  a [ __ ]
that's
unbelievable
I'd love to I could
kill her but it's fine
I could roll the dice again [ __ ]
but it's a shitty number come up if
I roll the dice again then I've
screwed up I can definitely
kill it if I make anger but  is it
the word
[music]
it
's better like that
okay yes
healing great I needed it
here too very
okay go shopping once what's
there so
oh I've seen it before
I've seen it before yes
I've already looked at
it I wanted to  not have
what should  I don't get it
or
fight against Sana here
ah that's gone
[laughter]
the length of the hair the color of the hair the
pink one with the stars perfect everything
perfect
nice to see you here
what's going on
hello first of all I don't know if we
already knew
okay now I want to  We're
always
okay,
I like it,
okay, it's just about acceptable,
yes, ancient
comedian, I don't know if he still
does comedy, but yes,
you can see the boomer in
me again, sad verses,
what did she do there
[music]
only now on the next move would  they
try  To fill it up from 17 onwards, that's
awesome,
she toned it down for me
[Music]
unbelievable but I can handle
it, yes, a
maximum of three, hey, I would like more
damage, what to do with
[Music]
here, there was one left
when it was up  do it,
we almost have it, it's
going down,
it's at 1 p.m. you have to bring it down to
zero
[music]
everything's good, everything's good, it
doesn't get that far,
unfortunately I can't imitate the dentist's voice
well
for art, I'm writing a song
about it orange
I look forward to it  what do you do what
maximum
what on is it then
reset again and again like Slater Spire
level
I thought it could be a
little higher
yummy repeats the next attack
and the 12 means that I have to
clean up with 12 and have to fill it up
until it is at zero or  like
[music]
I don't know if I like that, it
's somehow too much of a hassle for me, I
'd like to have
a result straight away, okay, what are we doing here
[music] ouch ouch ouch ouch I have a
stitch in the side of
my little boy
and I'm also having a heart attack  incoming
heart attack sounds like a fact yes my heart
is a fact
but no it's all good on the right side
it's a stitch in the side it's
pricking so that might be good I
'm not thinking about it too much
just do the
internet
[applause]
myGodGirl Scout who
probably still sells cookies like that  look evil I had
the money in her hand and she
completely ripped people off, it's
Großkarl making big money from
the shitty cookies
I saw I know the Boy Scout
ride when the Boy Scout was there but in
my world where I grew up
I did  never in any way so this is
someone grown up that I
was talking about but I've never heard
of the possibility in my childhood
that I could have joined something like that
or that
somehow one of my
friends at school
was a Boy Scout and I was  I think even
if it had been someone at
school, I think they would
have made fun of it, but we do
n't
really care
I imagine that
there is someone with me  would ring and
kick me and I would probably
even buy it
I want to sell it myself that way
it's really practical actually
okay okay
my house and and
oh yes so chocolate cookies are really awesome
why is there such an intermediate step here
doesn't make any difference let's go
Boss doesn't have one  level
depends on the cookies yes typical
chocolate cookies are really cool it's 12
years old and she's here to win against me
how much HP do you have
[ __ ] wait I have my healing so
no I at least have my shield that
's okay
yes, we can manage it or or but
I should have given myself the healing
instead of pushing, maybe
okay
yes you're right, I already have the song
ready, does that
mean I heard it from last time
or is it always in boss fights that
you have it from the beginning,
that means  15 damage is really
cool oh y
EAH her last time I don't know
why
but she's done
the arms
are okay I'm just throwing dice in her
face
okay let me think for a moment I
would like the four
and then these
of course what  you do
actually [ __ ]
chocolate biscuit well it doesn't look that bad
and then just one at a time and
was good good rolled
bad
yes you're going down now I think my
love
okay here once
here once
but that gives you damage to
the rest
[music]
congratulations yay
yours  first victory is me I am
now understood no but look
that's a good start you've
already won a whole pistol yes
now there are only 35 more and more
difficult episodes left
like please what 35 what more and more difficult
and of course now after each episode  the
Opportunity for cupid
and if the wheel points to a star
then you can leave the dungeon I
would say the dungeon but okay and
get your heart's desire fulfilled
what
if I don't
[music]
oh shitstyle skull
that's always like that
[applause]
where is
it  okay
it would have been very bold
S
[Music]
Channel
there are still a lot of people waiting especially
[applause]
[Music]
he's finished he's not filming anymore yes
[applause]
okay Episode one Warrior Episode 1 is
Warrior once one
next
character
[Music]
after all we have an argument I could
n't do that with solid Spire
okay difficulties
two why is it more difficult I'm
not here to make new friends I
want to win shouldn't it
get easier if the levels
get more difficult
what does the different
title do oh [ __ ]
what  does
your and level lover
can't re-roll the dice
let's try it out
I hope I don't lose then but
I'll do another complete
round if I can
a huge round of applause for the next
hopelessly
hopeful participant he has big
dreams unrealistic wishes and he  has
contractually promised us not to sue us
[music]
here is the one
with the dice you mean
literally I mean everything
literally
then tell me what's for you in
my arena of mischief
okay a spoonful of what
he doesn't hear too much chatter
So God my girlfriend doesn't take this
seriously but I do and I'm going to
win a trillion dollars
and what do you want to do with all the money
everything I want
and luck is with the brave
at least that's what those who do
n't know me yet believe
up to  days weather is [ __ ] today's news
are [ __ ] everything is [ __ ] go back to
bed hide on the your covers and never
wake up ever again good luck
so let's go
let's see
how this goes oh
what
's my attack no what I have
a plastic cannon
Share one  Dice 2
so which two years for that
I get two one's or something oh [ __ ]
but do I still have that because
I have to set it up here I ca
n't do that on one move I would
still have it on the
next turn next time  not
from whole fight though  He still has it
anyway or had two
anyway, yes, well,
so I can't get to the charging point. I
think with so few or so
crappy dice, I'd rather do another
attack.
Parts that
I have one, then I have two individually,
no way
really that's how I'll do it then
win
okay okay here it's better here
we divide it
come on
yes then we load both up
I thought he'd divide it into three
and two it's a coincidence we'll also divide it into
two if I now have
what I have  thought the
five of us went in there twice or
what is it, the four of us  individually extra the
41 with
4 4 damage or something
[music]
oh so okay
7 8 9 10 11 oh 7 8 9 10 11
I have enough to hit him
oh there I go
yes
let's go
[music]
okay he has me too  pretty much
punched in the face
snakes eye magic dice 2 1 what what does
he have with all his ones
I like that well let's
see if that's helpful
so if I do that now  go in here
smells two one what the horse then
I could if that's right now
two more so one extra that
really works
okay
three and that's a maximum okay yes
again at least you can use it again
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
maximum minimum
so it's very different
okay I can get all the ones again
or
[music]
parts are three and do it like that but I do
n't know then I could attack twice with
three it makes sense
but no maybe I want the
files  because otherwise I'll get it
Nowhere, no, but I could
get it in there. What does it still do? It still only
does three damage. It doesn't do much damage. Yes, well, then we'll do it like that and then
we'll do it like that.
Now it's worth it
and then one two three one more damage,
which isn't worth it
okay
no problem
[music]
it's pretty cool so far then
I hardly have to 22
a great too thank you very much
so the thief makes it very interesting I
'm having fun with it
okay a maximum of three
but
what's the headbutt that I
stole an even number and  then
do it like this  a lot of damage like what I
go in
so I share that one then
I get an extra
one has to be straight so I put the
two in
and then
we have a few more in
what was that I can't see it but
I can use it
but I can  see and I
reset parts of it then
the effect
[music]
wait a minute put this in here
ah I can test it
wait a minute
[music]
and what is it then just blocks me
or throws it away if it didn't
work
even
that's just blocking me okay
um
oh so okay it's not exactly
that worked so it was
probably a one or a three
or white maximum 3 food that wasn't
exactly
okay and then I share
[music]
okay
that was an one oh so yeah I could have
seen the damage  can haha ​​I didn't
look okay yes and that's okay
aha there's always something there okay
cool
she's not again let's
try it out
where do I want to try it out
[music]
no I want to but the parts
unless I hit snake magic
[music]
ah too  decide which one at all
game I want to play in the stream and
now you're presenting me with such a
decision that's very difficult for
me
hey you could always throw it in there
if I wanted but first we get
four
then let's try this
worked what was that
like now  Back then it wasn't seen
and then the four in here
and then the two in here and yes okay
cool it was three no it
's cool
[music]
for the accent do you mean I don't have an
accent
I don't have an Advent
but I'm surprised that  I haven't had
an udder come out yet  It's because today
at the appointments where I should have been so polite,
an owler
slipped out of my mouth,
but it doesn't seem to have bothered people that much
and it wasn't,
but I was talking about something,
that was my reaction, so I
said something  so because of
that you know yes or sorry for
the for the yes language
but it didn't bother them
okay so cannon fire we
stole
[music]
if I fill it with eight I do
six damage and for
burn one of his dice okay
then I divide  times the fiver
[ __ ]
wait a minute five
[music]
yes okay
please wait but that doesn't matter okay it
's okay [music] it's okay
maybe it
could have been done better somehow but well
mom mom
yeah I just wanted to use it no matter
that bad
[music]
but I think I do  beat me pretty well
generally pirates had a maximum of five
come at 4 we if I put a four in
I can use it again cool
um and I can also do something twice so
no not double we are at the
VIP four we four ones extra
okay
turnaround  me
Splitting that into a 401 would
actually be quite nice,
yes, okay, and then I'll put it in here,
okay, then it'll be used again,
then I can
[Music],
it can be reused forever
good for that, thank you,
I can do it again, bad luck, okay
It's burning here but wait let me
think about it
at 4 can be used again you
can do it twice now
[music]
oh god
if lythering
the sea is far away yes you're
completely wrong here I hope you've noticed that by now
lead lead
then go back go  back
to the sea WLAN reward poisonnatel or
crowbar reduces all countdowns by
so and so
and poison
three times per round maximum two
makes only one is what should I take then
is okay
I trust you
let's go
now I don't know which I
like better or this  They
're both really cool games,
okay, I like this one. It's
easier for me to think here.
I rely on the chat so much
while I actually
make all the decisions myself here, except
maybe sometimes when I have to
decide between what to buy
in this game I want  Lions
yes that one  Marshmallow, he'll burn us up
soon,
okay, what's this even number? That's how
much damage we'll do and we'll
burn a dice, okay, we
can't roll the dice again, so
we have to be satisfied with the four here
and then we can have a few singles
[Music  ]
share a maximum of two
three times per hour
[music]
and since three I think I'll share once
okay,
yes, I like it,
but that's
good because I'd waste it anyway
then I'd rather just throw it in there
then you get an extra lonely
bit of sharing  or
yes, okay,
why not  why not
very good thank you
thank you thank you I had to tell them
I really like the game I also
maybe it's just a lot of hype
and very loud in general as if you'd like it to be
a little quieter like a
quieter soundtrack
you're nice too but that's just the
way it is  I don't care about the atmosphere of the game
right now, I'm doing it
[music]
at most, here we can't do much
except that it's two parts and then
attack twice here,
yes
poison leaf several rounds if you
keep piling it up, I do
n't quite have it yet
but also observed here  [ __ ], we don't have to
do any damage because it only ever does,
huh, now I have that was from four that
went down to one to three
but only did one damage that
only did one use that in the round
or like so if I have a lot of poison  start
in one go again but just
deduct one and we move on and so on
and so on
so it's worth it um it's already
done
but it loses one there
oh okay okay then I saw it wrong
okay then it's worth it
so now it would do three damage on the next turn
but only go down to two
I understand that correctly
[music]
here it says he loses three health
oh
cool yeah then we don't really have to
do anything more but I'll
still hit it
cool
interesting
to up to forever
only go down to free I will take up  all
this
is you
[music]
pickpocketing is just starting goldah
okay if we know who wants money
to buy more items
don't know if that should be our priority
I haven't been in here
yet
you could maybe upgrade then
come on in
pea pistol 5  okay countdown 5
leather armor  reduces damage
but I have to have everything in my inventory
so in my set or like
a fake doubles a yes that sounds
good that's also so cheap why is it so
cheap
if God buy that already
that's more expensive if you
can use it again but up to  five
charging no,
oh, you know, it's that big, yes you can
make it smaller,
I think it's good and then
I won't waste so much. I
could still go shopping.
I want to have another one.
I don't know
especially before nee let's see
Let's see what else I have later
hello and vacuum cleaner
sweet where am I hello here always
difficult to find myself the
magician hello
with magic take off
okay we even start with bad luck
before now but needs two
and then does five damage burn
how strong  is that
if I split this up now
then I'll hit him in there and well that's
okay wait maybe that wasn't
smart wait I can at least
fill this up
um
yeah
I can stand if I don't want to
I'll do it here
but go again
okay I should have  I'd love to have that  divided
but I can only do bad luck also
[music]
and then yes well let's do it so
I should do the individual ones
[music]
okay he already has a good stack here
oh what's that
I'm also a magician
[music]
who  blocked it for me
okay but I can again I can
use lightning no
and a bit of poison and here the three
not so bad quite good actually
said down nice
yes that's a lot of effects
ah he still has three wars now
two the human being so that's enough  when I
hit him with it flexed and easy
finish hopefully then I'm not doing
anything wrong no I'm not doing anything yet
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and an upgrade would be no
hmm
okay what do we want here that's oh
that would be good
that I don't care actually
I still have space
oh so fake fits  but not in
I could also take pickpocket out
and maybe put it in what does
fashion plus
double a small okay
I'm coming that
oh I should have done German
then I'll do that in German next time
[music]
cleaning
okay
wait a minute that's actually worth it  not in
two  to hit in because there is still
only one available
then it would be the best because to share
I might just get
the ones
or I did I should distribute the film
Baby
wait a minute wait a minute
I'm hungry
he
okay okay I want you to share  now
I'm
doing this and that and that we've
already had a stack
Lucerne didn't appeal to me that much
[music]
but okay it's okay we can
use it next time
we can use it next time
[music]
German why
does it cause harm and that with  the heart
of difference
i guess if he  For example,
would block maybe then it couldn't
block anymore or something like that
oh so no it doesn't come to me oh well
like in Pokémon there is also something like that
oh I didn't check that's
then comes to me okay
okay um
wait a minute  Here the dice are so
high,
so I definitely have to divide something
into which fives or a sex has to
divide
[music]
then I'll do this, maybe
even more ones,
so all I have left is this
and then I can divide it up,
why not  so much is poisonous yes  good
but no I think that's good but
only one of them is
okay difficult
I hate the
modern
yesterday already
[music]
maybe
which double then I
don't see both or like
okay that doesn't work so that's more
more its four
so maybe share
Okay, what was it, how much did it have?
That's still more, oh well, then that's
less than us
one, that was a one,
you know why
are you confusing me? Otherwise
[Music]
I'll do [ __ ] [
Music]
yeah, okay, yeah  Well then it would
n't have any other use
had that was good that I
threw them in first then
no problem and the one five well
I can't do anything with the five
okay then we have the two here
and then here and
then you get one HP because then
we can  three more damage
doesn't work
[music]
okay at least I still love everything good
but interesting opponent
[music]
welcome or that's such a
wolf can see
that's my my hate skill in the
game I'll try
it it worked
two I think  Got from 9 to 11 and
knows at least a little bit of HP
get back
new cube
[music]
Now fill up the box 16
okay now I don't need that
oh actually it has the level up so
I'm full again no
you are my opponent
in the German and
[music]
okay let's see what is the cauldron
get some damage new ones  Dice
so no matter what I throw in
I only do one damage as if it
goes something that I absolutely don't
need I can at least do one damage
with it and get something new
[music]
then let's do that
oh I could
throw the six in here  or and then
make [music].
okay, then do a little bit,
we
[music]
can stand up for money once
we can also
dig in once,
maybe cover it again
if you have more,
yes, Christmas,
okay, I'm happy to be once, because in the
end that's actually filling you
up  I can't make sense of a loss
but I can only use it once
okay but it was good that was
good that was good
wait okay
[music]
it's not that bad the cauldron
it's actually really funny because you're
always like that
we can try out new things,
we do what that and just so much
I then do damage and it freezes
their dice an
odd one it has to be okay
maybe I'll just do it with a 1
no I won't finish I'm if
[music]
what do you two say too good or something
like that and so on again poison why  not
[music]
once
more so there
are fully the pro gamer or you
could almost think that I do this for a
living
playing games
on Google
[applause]
exactly
number eight, wait a minute then
she gets three damage so only five
damage has to do this  Zug
[Music]
is easy  So whatever, it's so cool that's
[music]
at least a little better than nothing
then
I should eat a few of you,
you're chickens or are you
all from the day Anna
can I eat you exactly
[music]
in the chat
the next one  deadly oh
[music]
but will I die now for sure next
time
one health star what should I buy
yes
[music]
no she is very busy translate in the
chat
yes die if I don't maybe
I would if then take the baton
I think but whether I
I don't know if I'm going to use it
[music]
and now  Does it take up so much space
or whatever?
I'll take it and then I'll
think about it because I actually really like my setup right now.
I always find something,
okay,
I'm so hungry.
Clarifications,
sweet, oh cool, I can do it  here even
purely out of necessity
I even needed
it
Michel
lets like that I thought too
let's beginning wait a minute share
[music]
then I would put it in there now
I think
two lonely
ones in here
unfortunately one can against him but well like that
now I'll do another one  a few three oh
wait, actually double
one
and two and three is the question, am I
still using my bad luck against him?
Okay,
by the way, I'm going to
eat something frozen today, but at least I'll make myself
a fresh homemade
salad with a homemade dressing,
but we're out of it  I have
n't caught a frozen sliced ​​meat like that yet actually spaetzle
with paprika sauce pan something like that yes yes
you know something like that I really like something like that
these pans to
warm up in the pan
the litter is mine  Scrap yes wait I
haven't really processed it yet
yes that's bad for me because I
work with a lot of small numbers no
numbers
um okay wait we'll do that in here the
parts we
wow you have to be able to work with it
somehow no um it's in there oh [ __ ] how
shouldn't I
[music]
at all now
okay [ __ ] man it
's better to put it in poison now
than in that one
so well I'll definitely do that
because at least it's straight
and that doesn't do anything for me anywhere else so
I put it in here  I
at least earned money but
double it
okay yes good good
let's fill it up first
no it doesn't work infinitely
what do we have to divide up here
[music]
anyway
he dies anyway
my mouse isn't working right now okay
everything's good everything's good yes I would have some
water on  have to give snake magic
no matter yes because we need healing it has
become a bit more difficult
but very interesting if you
use your head a bit then
it's not a problem so song
reduces damage by two from each
attack
but needs five exactly one 5
nope like that  thief a thief  he doesn't need
iron armor he already has someone a
thief with so have you seen they
usually have leather armor or nothing at all
okay
what do you want
[music]
sorry now I think maybe not
perfect but it's okay the
main thing is that we do damage like that
wait a minute
I should have done that  can oh [ __ ]
yeah okay it's okay should I do that now
four damage yes
a few times there
and
what is that what is he doing there
[music]
dangerous dangerous
five damage locked in cubes twice
you can now
do [music] 13 damage  the next turn, 13
damage  do I survive but you mean
13 damage
I can I can maybe
find something against him
[music]
that
[music] is
n't that bad should I
listen to it again now or just completely the
person
gives
it then he'll do it  four damage,
he still has ten,
yes, we'll definitely get him
next turn down, but now it won't
work, it doesn't matter, it'll be the same thing,
really
[music]
has done both now, I was
n't paying attention at all,
the gold,
yes, I don't need any of that, no  no
no
at least now  should I take the gold
okay yes well bye
still so much no was that just a few
an opponent let's take a look at the shops
here
[music]
um
no I need the lock pick I
use it so much what but what is that
3:0  Damage is caused
no
no you but I just
somehow hurt my thumb but
I don't want that or
daudia okay
thank you for helping
mom dad what do we have here where do we park
two plus one okay somehow
they have to have a lot of equipment here
Things dice he had
something twice next round but I get
once per head
[music]
I would actually be really cool there
but if, for example, I just
no we have to eat out which
situation I would then
throw something in but yes I go with
my
latte and  my lantern with me down
there the stars are shining down there
we're shining my light goes out I'm
going home I've got the rubbish
rababuraboom
goes out I'm going home I've taken
out the rubbish
we made lanterns back in
kindergarten,
really nice lanterns and then they are
actually dark was
walking around with the lanterns
[music]
a real catcher
that was nice I won't do that
anymore
so please share once or
what's the odd one oh yes
take this
okay
[music]
I want it twice the two in the
next round have or are fives
depending on what I want then the other has
double now
maybe
there or wait I could also
get the lonely one here I could now
get more ones and then I could
fill that up with six five and one
gets two singles or  I
Now just double the fiver
and second
[music]
OK, let's do that, I can
put it in
then I'll get it alone,
we'll do it like this, I'll get nothing at all,
nothing underneath,
wait, but I'll get it,
I could get one more stake
back
yes, why not two A's next time
if not whether that was really good
the lantern bath is on November 11th I do
n't even know who the date when it
was always done on November 11th
making lanterns that's a cute idea
I like that one  I like these
craft streams but is it just that it
's a it's a a
Roman Catholic holiday or
a Christian holiday recognize that
the English-speaking people
St Martin on the eleven November device
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[  Music]
inflict new damage or more
because I suck at the next attack
yes what yes what
[Music]
but smart that was halfway smart
suck
if I die ham
[Music]
less English more German  okay, so
I was just about to be okay,
that's a good thing
if he still survives
[music]
yes, here when you have very little HP then
the music changes to a
heart-pounding
lantern festival,
kindergarten that is still important today, that's how you know
it is  you're currently in kindergarten
[laughter]
so he's already getting ready damage
what what do I want to double
I have to see probably in two
parts
but should I double the threesome beforehand but
then it doesn't do anything for me or unless
I put it in here but well
so do that  I definitely do  Case here
but like I did before like I doubled it fully
maybe
hit it twice, wait, but I want to
have one in here or
and then I'll divide it
can regulate a little bit here okay
yeah okay so I should now I'm going to make
an attack  dodge or
actually I should
survive now chilled out
what's happening what's happening
wow had just
dodged damage or something
no okay that's it I dodged the
silence or
did I dodge the silence
okay then everything's fine could
make it will
[music]
everything's good everything  good no stress no  Do
you know all this well, I'm just
somehow so precise and right now
[laughter]
[music]
yes well
back oh what's that showing
means that, for example, a
minimum 3 is no longer a minimum and
I can put in whatever I want  I
want
two ones or another, it's double
improvement
3 + 1
I need your dice but also or
the lonely one I need you I have then
no
oh so that's free okay okay
good
was so close
I have to say that I'll see in the
future  maybe a death on a
bus
[Music]
now cowboy
sweet I would go this way first
weak against fire
spot plus two I could heal myself
if I put a six in I do
n't need any healing right now
but
maybe you still put the six
in because then I'll do sex damage,
wait a minute, right  I just divide
twice I divide once I do
n't need any healing here
[Music]
[ __ ] that's not that good
ah[ __ ]
[Music]
I won't actually get the two back then
oh I didn't know that in that case
okay okay okay
[  Music]
okay
not the best move but
yeah  good, it's back again, good, you're
very happy,
everyone makes green,
you know what, maybe now that we've
received so much damage from the last
opponent, it'll really
be like that all the time, then armor would
n't have been so unbeatable,
oh no, I have  really
lost it oh so because it's here I
got two ones because of
course it goes in yes okay okay
the magician can fire that's actually
perfect that's what we should do
we have to fill it up with 12 okay
[music]
so and then so I think it's quite  well solved
then  can we still get the ones here,
put the individual ones in here,
good, the foursome is now useless
[music]
apart from that
I think it's good
haha ​​we burned two of them
didn't use them at all
but they he
[music]
[applause]
[Music]
okay
then a Gorgon let's go here,
what do we want to improve now
or do we want to save the improvement
in case I can buy something good
but let's see what we have to
use
[Music]
Put parts in three
cubes maybe that's it  even
surprising  well
that
ah that would then no longer be once per
fight but I can get each one
to choose from every round so I would say
either I should keep it
[music]
yes so in the next round I
always get doubled
[music]
or I just want to  Really crazy,
I'll do it, it's really cool,
I can be sure that I'll
use it, well, now let's go
to the snowman first because it's level 4,
I can also heal myself. Baby,
a cube freezes if it's odd, okay,
I  just have  straight things
[music]
I have an idea maybe I have
an idea I have an idea I want to
share it and put individual ones in
a six in the key
snake eyes together but actually
I have to share these too I have a lot
to drive I have nothing  actually
that's [ __ ],
it's pretty [ __ ] for me, wait then
I'd rather double a
no, it's all [ __ ], it's all [ __ ],
[ __ ]
what
but that perhaps makes the
most sense
[music]
[ __ ]
because the viruses are getting me there  well,
should I do
[music]
I still have
well, just give me that then
Lucky this time
he only did a snow wave
okay at least
[music]
we'll share it,
we want one like that, we already
have
one here
and
then  and
want to double we
can still use bad luck
[music]
a strong poisoning he should
definitely go to the hospital
urgently ah [ __ ] okay that's
not so good now because I've got nothing left
but that'll carry over to the next
round or
it'll be fine
As far as I know,
it's not wasted
after all
[music]
should maybe
anyway
yes yes it doesn't matter we are
yes I was just chilling no I
just let it happen like that
I need it urgently
here I can still be 18 no I'm going
first so I don't waste anything
to gargo it's very nice for me  dangerous
in front of you,
I should go to the cowboy first
because I think I would waste an HP
and that's I don't like it
because it's going to be so difficult, that's exactly what
I imagine, but whatever we
just go to something doesn't matter
[music]
at least three three damage  throws
again with a lower value
I get a new die and do
three damage but the new die will
be less than what I put in,
that's so
cool
[music]
what do I want next round
maybe a three of a kind
wow
but only pays one poison made but see you
next round  please build on it,
what did I say,
you're so unfunny
[music]
that's why we have two dice I know I'm
getting new ones all the time with the avalanche
[ __ ] man okay
[music]
what do I want what do I want when we do
it all
[music]
I know there were so many options here
but there are so many options  I don't think it's bad either
so
woah
[Music]
given
en down I would say
[Music]
but wait a minute
do that
[Music]
smart how smart I am because
I didn't take advantage of my bad luck haha
well done yes there is here
I can go home I don't need and
that's an apple and then there's another
apple I think or maybe
not
another lockpick you don't
need a trigger a damage
for every enemy for every for
every bug that's good because I  working with
my
gift stacks
[music]
interesting
so we double all the poison
I put that in myself instead of a
lantern I haven't really used that at all
not that active
I would say
so
nicely organized even
can do that
and yes
cowboy [ __ ] I don't have that much HP,
maybe we should  But maybe get married,
how much is that two gold? Yes,
I need it,
okay surprise.
A level up ball
would be good.
HU, what's the shooting iron? That's new.
His dog is behind his ears and
we shoot and his mother's shoes.
He has two pistols  It
's dangerous to give a cat
two guns  Cats
are already very aggressive
danger cut to two Pistols
are you
let alone two
okay so
[music]
okay I don't have six
okay so put it but then I would
double heal and then share baby
[music]
oh
[Music]
Wait, that's hard, do I want two
more in poison and then the many straight
or how do I put the two in the ones?
No, I don't want that but
for example, I want two maybe in it
and then couples then
[  Music]
so we'll definitely take bad luck  okay
and then put this
in here okay okay then put the two in there okay
but then I'll just do the count and
then we haven't lost anything we've
lost a left so well
[music]
use midnight clean food
this has to be quick here now
[music]
[Music]
yes okay it only ever takes a six
yes okay okay yes maybe he wo
n't get it next time it was very
lucky now
[music]
[music] there
is still more money yes well
[music  ]
I would have a child
no
or
[Music]
I hope at the level up so yes,
well, once I can make a mistake
oh Erika
and a new command and what's here
now we get more of the [ __ ]
24 but
is that
that's already in harmony with the
other one  stuff I use but
24 an upgrade would be good isn't the next
level somehow a boss level
baby
what don't I use that often
maybe I should clean in snakes
because if I really had that much
then I can always put it in the
plague too
then I'd rather fill the pest  also
with that on so queue and hopefully
if I still if
the boss doesn't come straight away and next time the
boss is oh it's expensive
[music]
yes
yes okay then we'll stick with it even if
it's in the theory it's quite
nice
okay, let's see if I survive this oh
FGO character
I don't know how to pronounce it,
it probably has it as a human being
because now it's an ice country
I have a bad feeling
that feeling maybe I'll need a
first aid kit then but 16
hey where am I nice
i feeling
[  Music]
okay, yes, I hope  I hope we do
n't screw this up
okay
I think I think I'm going to die
immune to lockdown and just I have
nothing out of it
except I can use your freeze against
you if you have something like that we'll
see the birds singing after the breath of the wind
But fighting also hurts the
stock market [ __ ]
[music]
I don't have it right now, wait maybe
I'll get a foursome
okay let's start here
a foursome would have been nice
[music]
they're weak on the other hand looks a reason
okay yes well then
okay we've got five
and then straight  I
only have that
can double it  and put one in here
[applause]
at least
and then
[applause]
the 5 are completely wasted now too
[music]
okay
everything
is fine baby the game is very strange I
'm just having fun with it yes
I made a mistake with the
fifth ones
[music]
wait it's full the people here
maybe one of them it has to
be a fiver so only a
fiver goes in yes
that's not no five no five
[music]
no okay cool cool cool cool cool
at least ah yes good then that's it
I would have  the others didn't know okay there
are no fifths
[music]
or I'll try it here
maximum 2
okay that's that's everywhere two and
under one no it could be a six
or a 3 or 4 that's a
sexual 3 or 4 okay and that that
So it was a second one yes that's
a sexual 3 or 4 and we put that
in here
when I should double okay can
share
but before I share
I should share then I
still don't see what it is
double 4
Should I then get a four?  put it in
but maybe I'd rather try it
first
and I'll share one or
try it here once okay that's
not possible so it's over a 2
that's more than a two
should I try it here too
that's more than a three
maybe it's worth it  to share
[applause]
no that's worth it wait it's more
than a three it has to be a 4 5 6
or something like that so
okay
now I have to think a lot
I'll share
I'll put this in here
I think I'll put this in here
and then I share it  Fours
so
there's
[music]
okay
and parts there
okay okay
[music]
now she gets eight damage
you have to do that
no problem there's not much done
tell us about monster human
yes then I'd be unlucky
and put everything down with ones  try
but then
what will happen then wait again carefully
then then then then then first
but should I have one a one
lockpick shain so that I can divide it up again
but should I put in the cheap ones
or I mean that it actually makes
little difference
individually
open the trigger first  first open
like this
[applause]
so now he gets a new
damage and oh they say already dead or
because
that's already
yes okay no
yes wonderful
[music]
cool
successful
[applause]
[music]
and that means it's time for  turn
the wheel turn us out if it points to one
empire then you get your
trillions and it
's always on you where there's no
price at stake version broke like and uh it
's always reset no
always like that
I'm a drumroll
[applause] yeah yeah  no
Worry oh you'll get lucky here again
we'll be back soon with
more episodes when will I get lucky does
n't seem like I've
ever come
[applause]
yes that was so much fun
we can play that again
soon if it does  you guys had fun too
I had fun
yeah going out I like this game like
you
[laughter] again again soon
soon now I'll make myself
something to eat
and we'll see you tomorrow in the member
stream and in Pico Park  all
channel I think  in tomorrow Obi on I
Mission
or
[Music]
History Thumbnails for a monkey have
time
Baby after opperson
Reservation modern August 25
ine
[Music]
To-do lists and extreme
challenges
yes, so you don't know exactly yet
here you can't find out anything else,
wow
baby  cute yes
why thinking
[Music]
a magician a magician would also be cool do
n't know what's next but I'm
very interested
okay then that's it Thank God
I don't have to read superchats here
so now you can I
think I'll wait for the finale  List the
finalist the morning Fortress
[music]
you
it should be
in en everyone
expedales and
[music]
wait okay okay
weather that
talk ahead that was wrong
[music]
on each side that yes to that
[laughter]
and  in German we say a Germany
say goodbye
[music] it was
fun bye goodnight bye
bye bye well I almost wanted to
end in English no no no
[music]