[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
assistant
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
what about noises you heard that eh in
the loading screen
so
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay hi
hold it
Kiki
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
hello Brian well no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
no no no no no no no but
playing
hard casual right um
yeah
um
playing hard casual like a pro
like I don't I could play classic and I
wish I could still change
but I can
yeah
how are you guys doing everybody
um
tell me
yeah me tell me
[Music]
oh
I'm good I'm good I'm I am
perfectly uh healthy I arrived in Japan
I am helping out that was just like
something my friend I just I just woke
up
um
and then
I I cleaned my room a little bit
just in case someone wants to
you know
check by
but
you know
unlike other people
I I do think Ina
um
really did not appreciate the roast by
the way
the uh your room is not clean roast
but you know
[Music]
the truth has to come out hmm
that's the only way
like to to change something about it
hmm
yep it is what it is it is what it is
she took that one personally
a little bit
you need Advanced booking while on no
walk-ins
you should expect walk-ins like I do
when you live in the en house
foreign
[Music]
I really when I when my alarm was
ringing today at 9 30 I was like
engage
mood yeah what emblem crumb with Robin
and emblem Veronica have banana they
will join your group once you complete
the respective divine paralogs ancient
well has been added to the thumbnail you
can use it to exchange items you don't
want for new
you can now use nerd skills in the arena
as well as the ring chamber
oh making things more simple
so
continue
[Music]
wow I saved at 47.47
before apparently
mama
Veronica from the mobile game I wouldn't
know
I really like to get
I forgot what that was
[Music]
me a multiplayer
the one I called cute in the direct oh
[Music]
I
what can this humble liar do for you
divine one huh I'd like to have a talk
that's a liar I understand and I'm
prepared to accept whatever punishment
you have in mind punishment
no
I wanted you to know how grateful I've
been to have you by my side
what well that's how I feel you fight
hard every day to protect our allies
there's absolutely no reason to punish
you in hindsight I think the only reason
you lied is that we don't know each
other very well yet so let's change that
why don't you start by telling me
something about yourself yunaka
but if you don't want to then I won't
pry simple as that
okay before I joined up with you I was
sort of just wandering
looking for my place in the world I left
my old self behind me
I wanted to think I had at least
sound very fond of your old self
oh I like her well enough others though
not so much that's why she had to go but
I like who I am now and honestly I've
been having so much fun since we met
I'm glad to hear that good talking
I think we should do it again sometime
my what do you say you got yourself a
deal
my sound is chopping but do you is it
shopping for you guys do it or is it
just in my ears
choppy as I'm like not that much but a
little bit choppy
no okay
then it's fine
when you said I had changed you were
right I have not for that
um
yes when we met I was wild as they come
my home life was Rocky to say the least
and that left me filled with anger so
each day I would go into town and pick
fights with anyone who got on my nerves
looking back on that time now I see how
pointless it was yet that was the only
way I knew to cope until I met you
though at first of course I assumed you
were as wild as I was
we hit it off right away huh taking out
goons by day riding our wolves by night
yes we were thick as thieves little by
little you helped point my rage in a
more useful Direction at men who cut you
in line
that only happened once I was talking
about all the bandits and thieves we
fought you taught me to take all my
pent-up directionless anger and use it
for good well I'm glad though to be
honest that wasn't really intentional
yes I figured as much even so if I had
never met you that rage might have
swallowed me whole and spit out a lonely
resentful husk I could have wasted my
life feeling bitter about the hand I was
dealt
bam
at this point I would like to share
thank you
to Blue
for making those
assets again as you've seen I look like
her right now oh
cute
right very cute
they look so good
did you need something for me panette
oh no why do you ask you have been
staring at me for some time it's just
that for a princess you seem so how to
put this
composed do I
it seems like a rather ordinary level of
composure to me really but you are not
bursting into song or dancing to and fro
correct
I do not do those things nor are you
running around like a mad wolf or
cramming prime rib down your gullet you
are simply standing around it was so odd
I could not help but stare perhaps you
are merely unaccustomed to the standard
and expected conduct of royalty
oh my God my deepest apology no no need
for that
I should not be looking for a fence in
others Customs it's rather nice to speak
with you actually
enrages me femininity really I enjoy
your company as well good
then if it's all right with you
I'd like it very much if we became
friends of course your highness it would
be my honor it's it's annoying
I don't know
I'm not ready for this
kind of
khaki khaki conversation
as usual always well that's one of my
redeeming qualities
[Music]
in point of fact I have been meaning to
ask you about that why do you insist on
pretending to be cheering all the time
you think I'm acting you think I'm so
talented I could keep it up all the time
I'm flattered
do not Bluff a bluffer I can tell that
this is not your true manner
when I began serving the boss I had to
swap out my own dialect for a more
proper one since then I have had a keen
ear for others false tongue
takes one time doesn't it I can't answer
your question though ah rainbow spoiled
to the mystery who would you harass with
prime questions my hands are tied so be
it forgive me for probing but this
duplicity somehow it does not sit right
with me oh
[Music]
what double rainbow
my God
thank you
it will take a while until I get to your
Super Chat
a long while probably
I hope you're aware of that
thank you though
thank you
um
double that's a okay
I'm like Midway through the
super chats from the Showcase so I mean
it's pretty decent but
hmm
yeah okay
oh so we did that wait there must also
be surely some bombs one okay
he is a golden deer
oh wow is that what music sounds like no
I want my ears to know what they're in
for
[Music]
eign
this will never change thank you
spankenheim
this is from 2023
what do you mean
you think I won't read this until 2024
excuse me
[Music]
I will
2023 just started
a while ago
um I didn't wait there's one more
um so we're gonna play this today for
like I don't know
seven hours
uh probably
and then
huh
and then we're gonna I mean seven hours
including Super Chat reading I would say
so maybe a six hours gameplay one hour
Super Chat reading
because after that
uh dinner time
and
um
oh the new well is that the new one
dinner time and then I prepare for next
stream which is with
goo bags
um exactly
[Music]
um
whatever see dial I guess you can have
something
and the collab reservation have to still
put up the reservation and make a
thumbnail
because I didn't want to make it
yesterday
yeah I know what I'm doing
and I measure
nah I'm sure it's fine
no blind luck here I'm a genius cookies
delicious
she loves this delicious
surely this will help fuel my dance well
he says the whole sentence
Bae if female also gained strength plus
too what if it's female
but I mean love
thank you thank you heart dancia I love
you actually step right up
so I'm gonna give you a gift
um
here pebble
look it says Pebble I found on the
ground s
probably not giving you trash
no no no no no
at least it's not the horse poop yep yep
yep
well shall we start off with something
I'm really upset about
stupid
yesterday
[Music]
uh uh myth together we went for uh
Teppanyaki
which was really fancy it was nice
and
so there were courses
and you could choose the course and I
went for a course that was like around
uh 10 000 yen
okay ten thousand yen
and what you get with that
is like like starters
cool cool starters pretty nice starters
and and eventually you get the meat
and the meat
um there's like the normal meat
um normal basic Teppanyaki meat
not too fancy doesn't cost does not cost
extra write this down okay
and then uh uh it said below
no
below it was like you know you can
upgrade your meat to this or this or
this
three other options
um and it would cost a little bit extra
and the most expensive
extra
would be young
you know I love it oh oh that's new
is this tarot greeting
Magic
yeah I'm not sick I'm just like I don't
know
I'm really not sick though
fortune teller see the hell uses card
Supply is trade only available in the
evening so visit once the sun goes down
do I get like extra if what he reads is
good
extra like stats oh my God
um yeah okay so I was like um
from my experience with Teppanyaki
normally the amount of meat they give
you is
so little
it's so good but it's so little because
it's so good they only give you so
little and then I I remember I would
always crave
way more I always wanted more
[Music]
um
so I thought maybe I should not I should
take the the standard meat but also the
Chateau bouillon
pay some extra foreign
[Music]
you know it said like 4 000 Yen extra
on the menu and I got confused
because it said their Chateau Brio four
thousand
[Music]
and I thought okay so I guess I'm paying
the course money which is like 10 000
Yen plus the four thousand
from The Chateau Brian
and I asked the guy the waiter if that's
possible
[Music]
and he he said well he spoke really fast
let's take it easy he spoke really fast
Crown Prince of Brody oh this might not
go to I don't know
I can learn a lot from you
[Music]
yeah I asked if it's possible he said
it's possible
and then said something blue
he he then offered me something that
would make more like sense in terms of
you know financially
you know
and I don't know he spoke
shorts and I was just like okay
I am Fender so at the end the bill came
and it was
it was twice what I thought I was gonna
pay
that was fun nice good job fogado
it was twice I thought I was gonna pay a
hundred bucks turns out I was gonna pay
200 bucks
and I was I was like asking is this
correct because
in hindsight I think I understand the
final price but on the bill it made no
sense to me
because listen listen
the bill had the course listed for its
price
which if you don't change anything it
will always have the the main the basic
meat in it included
and
yeah that's included in the 10 000 yen
and then
[Music]
however
the bill added
and the listing the basic meat as like 4
000 yen
and the Chateau brino is five thousand
yen
even though this was my question
[Music]
shouldn't uh the basic default meet
be
part of the course anyway why is it
listed separately
and I think even though nobody in the
room was apparently understanding what I
was trying to say I think Dad's question
in theory was correct
but it seems like I guess maybe
they just you know and if you are or if
you order things like separately
just the without the course just the
Chateau Brio apparently it costs you 100
bucks
um
uh but the Chateau Brio they added to my
bill was five thousand and an ex like
the default meet four thousand which
kind of adds up to roughly that
right to the Chateau Brio a la carte uh
one
but you know if they would have just put
the Chateau Brio extra on there
for that final price I wouldn't have
been confused but I was especially
confused because the course was supposed
to include
the the basic meat anyway and yet
on the bill it's listed as course uh uh
a hundred bucks
then the basic meat separately extra
money costing
and the Chateaubriand
you get what I'm saying why I was so
confused about it
I mean the price was also shock but in
hindsight I understand the pricing that
you know I misunderstood that the
Chateaubriand only costs
4400 if you just upgrade your course
I did not expect it to be double that
when uh you order extra
I get that but the way it was listed was
just so confusing I thought they made a
mistake
and I do think that it's it it makes no
sense
in terms of how it was listed Pam
no it was a Teppanyaki well it's still
worth it was good the Chateau Brian was
incredibly good but in hindsight um it
was actually in general way more than in
other Teppanyaki places it felt like way
more meat than another Teppanyaki places
so
I could have just
gone with the Chateaubriand only and and
if I knew it was gonna cost that much I
wouldn't have this is my chance to shine
I wouldn't have oh dear sorry friend I
wouldn't have ordered both if I knew it
would cost us not
it's okay yeah I had twice the amount of
food yeah I mean twice the amount of
meat
compared to everybody else
yeah not yakiniaki yeah yeah
so do you understand why I was confused
because like they're in the room no one
was understanding me
no one
thank you
[Music]
oh thank you thank you
like Inna was trying to explain it to me
but I I I don't think
my points though
it's not what a la carte means yeah yeah
I know I ordered I guess I guess I
ordered uh Chateau Brio as a la carte in
a like extra
but the bill makes no sense
even if the price makes sense
they kind of like took took the price of
an avocado
but split it onto two items on the bill
even though one of them should be in the
course anyway you know what I mean
but yeah he did that to I don't know I
don't know to confuse the out of me
normally like when I
get a bill I don't say like man what is
what is this all about because normally
it all makes sense but this this time I
was like doubting it because the price
man
oh well
uh what else what else we cooked we
thought
um
[Music]
I don't want to polish those stupid damn
Rings
um
chapter 17 is Health yeah I've been
warned about other chapters before and
they were easy peasy lemon squeezy so
our marine Armory
I'm glad to see you
[Music]
a chance have you seen any ghosts nearby
thank you
oh this stuff oh
[Music]
thank you ah
guess what that's not I mean that's just
our outfit though let me take a look I
guess
um this I think only had had accessories
right oh I like that though
not on her though
oh
yeah this one's so cool it looks like I
think I said this was before but it
looks like something that Daenerys
Targaryen would wear
[Music]
ah wait what about the head
yeah what about bunny ears what
this wasn't there like is it not only
for specific people
whatever
drug cars
welcome
eh
YouTube says the stream is not live but
you're watching right
My Stream says it's live I guess there's
like a glitch but you guys are watching
though
I mean it works right if it works it
works
just
oh
are you a big crony fan huh
are you desperately looking for crony
tangents
people aren't getting notified oh
because YouTube says it didn't start yet
oh hell
uh
[Music]
man well I don't care we're live now I'm
not gonna make a new slot I don't care
wait
[Music]
I'm gonna buy I thank you I thank you
distract
just in case I'm gonna buy
I thank you everyone visit
oh thank you
[Music]
do come again
what happened to my mouth I am trying to
look like
her
see
I look just like
her
foreign
oh man she's cute I'm so sorry I don't
use her anymore and guys what one of my
what am I gonna do am I good to go well
I mean surely there's like something
else I could do but I don't wanna
maybe I can upgrade some weapon
I guess I'll go upgrade something
hmm
um
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
L fire
two
uh
[Music]
rest is okay I think
oh wait no win I can upgrade win one
right right we should upgrade it because
like she's using it because of that
thing
but wind itself is kind of weak so we we
want to upgrade should I upgrade to four
or is it a waste
sure it's not it's not that expensive
okay okay
yeah if we can't make it into L wind
because the thing that we have only
works with wind for some reason
um okay swords like who am I using
actively I I like these cute little
icons but
somehow some of them I just I just don't
like immediately realize who they are
it's kind of difficult for my brain like
for example this one who the is
that is that Vander
right
it's not only me
should I upgrade the iron sword I think
she's using it relatively often
maybe oh no let's upgrade the 11th sword
yo oh I can't
oh my iron no more iron
[Music]
oh
worm Slayer no one's using the
wormslayer
Rider's Bane
um
killer ax ah maybe Killer X I can't
okay we'll be back we'll be back I'll be
here
we'll be back
we can convert one simple to 99 iron
where again where was that again was it
here
change
but I want Iron and I give
once 90 Island
maybe one
hmm
weapon shop this is the weapon shop what
do you mean I'm talking to them
[Music]
maybe just a plus one for now
Silva's great silver is rare yeah
oh
okay
I'll be here
but well of course I would think that's
the weapon shop if they're selling
weapons eh okay no they're not selling
weapons they're just upgrading my
weapons okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
was he serious with what he just said
he said I lost the weapon in the garden
would you go get it for me
was he serious with that
take care why does he not mention it
again
like oh oh don't you only get this
special Quest if you
don't mash the buttons
which I did but I still kind of
caught that one
oh the well was
are there
oh wait
here right
[Music]
oh
something French
[Music]
I know that one
it looked like really strong weapons an
accident Lance right
is he gonna give those to me
[Music]
also I want to try out the that thing
foreign
[Music]
any of the Nations I know you should
hold on to these Divine ones there's
something odd about that well
you can drop your unwanted items into
the well when you do they'll disappear
forever forever
come back after at least one battle
however you'll find new items to have
taken their place it always like this
nice ones
like like really good stuff
or is it not always this nice
gotcha
[Music]
why don't they
wait so this comes from an update from a
very recent update or does this come
when you progress in the game because if
it comes from the very recent update I
think many people already finished the
game
and didn't get this at all
it's a free update my God
people finished the game and
did this
release
the Sun
it
pushing though
[Music]
I've had this ready in their pockets a
while ago right
they didn't just come up with this and
like
program it within two days and then free
out the update
there's no new game plus
incentive to play again
it's been like two months since released
exactly like they're there's definitely
people already finished it
even busy people like Cali she says
she's almost done with the game
hahaha
uh the more Valley bottoms you drop the
more likely what you find is an upgrade
in value
um
okay let's Drop It Like It's Hot
drop something in there and then I don't
need
don't need the money that much after all
so that that makes sense like at least
like when you're when you don't need
much more money
like at least this way you can get rid
of things and get like something
else than money for it the one we throw
in
oh look at all I should use this
uh oh I can throw
anything in even non-weapons
damn
[Music]
okay I have this silver ax and this
silver ax
or maybe only one
nah you could have both
no
we're just one
this one
can I like break up the silver ax into
silver somewhere and just get the silver
Lounge
[Music]
steel blade
nah oh that's because that is just
a realistic thing to do
[Music]
that's what they did in in the Colosseum
with the Colosseum in in Rome people
came and took the
materials the valuable materials on the
Colosseum ripped them off many of them
to then reuse them somewhere else melt
them and make them into new things
makes sense
history has proven this
[Music]
I don't know what else guys
I have another silver sword
[Music]
and this Javelin because I'm I'm gonna
give you the javelin plus one
and
um
[Music]
can we get up to five stars
that is the question
here have the Thunder
still not five
I guess what I threw in was kind of
oh you can have the Thunder anyway
I wonder
if it matters
[Music]
if you have trapped up in a while check
back after your next battle for
something new okay nice too we'll be
back I'll be back
okay can we go now can we go fight can
we go do some story
[Music]
um
yeah I'm not bro I know I know it's
gonna give her Channel
plus one
look at that while I was doing it
[Music]
here look look look look look it's
better than the Jabba what's better than
the javelin
a javelin plus one exactly
yes I will do story because last time I
have made no progress with the
story
hmm
two chaplains if you told javelins or
Javelin plus one
yeah yeah let's go the part uh world map
[Music]
but the Parallax no time for that
no time
but I think you know on my on my next
plane ride I will play one or two
paralogs on my own
if I don't sleep for the whole thing
um so please forgive me but
you know I I need to like
help myself make some more progress
outside of the Stream
[Music]
okay uh we were at the northern Fortress
last time and saved a dancer
while we were questioning ourselves
are we human
or are we dancers
begging for the answer
are we human
or are we dancers
and turns out we are human
mostly but also a little bit of a dancer
inside of any of us and I just realized
once we're done here it probably
connects with the other side huh
I love that dance back in the day and
that song ah
[Music]
um
oh he's using Korean now I guess I will
use him for one battle and then I'm
gonna drop him
yeah that's what I'm gonna do
so I'm gonna that's exactly what I'm
gonna do
okay about that about what eh
with emblem core and added to our ranks
each country's rings have been collected
for real
except the ones that we still don't have
back right
all right no more rings in the wild
between us and sombron they've all been
taken okay cool
let's consider the situation there are
five emblems on our side only five nah I
got more than that like violet
Janelle corn meanwhile the Bell dragons
got seven in his grubby claws most of
them are old allies Marth sigurd Celica
Makaya damn leaf and Roy that's another
emblem bring his forces stole from
lethos the Azure twins oh together all
12.
we will need to face the enemy directly
are you proposing we invade illusion
turning to alucia already yeah that's
gotta be complicated we might indeed
call Gondor that aside
invading illusion now would be a mistake
they have a clear Advantage seven
emblems to our five the worst case
scenario is but they could they steal
more of our Rings that's what concerns
me maybe you should hot glue them to
your fingers we can abandon all hope of
defeating the feldragon but the longer
we wait to attack the more likely it is
they'll attack us or hide them in your
brain we strike first one never wants to
be on the wrong end of an ambush we're
not ready to take the offensive
rocking a hard place huh
what
[Music]
pardon the interruption
word from the port of soul
a number of Warships were spotted on the
horizon judging from the crests on their
sails they appear to be illusion vessels
they're attacking the queen them again
[Music]
no Queen them in fact
Kingdom we better take a look for
ourselves
let's head to the Azure Coast it's near
the border and it's got a clear view
[Music]
that group who sang that is called
queendom
smooth sailing at this rate will be the
first ones in firenay
I wonder why zeppy had told us to go
ahead our orders are to kill everyone we
see right with this kind of Head Start
think of the body count we can get we'll
be heroes
seems like Steffi has really taken a
shine to us don't you think mavier I do
not particularly care I have my orders
and I will follow them
this way I can't stand you you never
praise me and you're no fun at all this
was bad at least he's not the boringest
man in the world boring
[Music]
lady Marnie hello NPC number 45
Two Soldiers have deserted the fleet
perhaps they had reservations about the
current strategy
let them be
they took
the ring what explain as a precaution we
kept each ring on a separate ship in the
fleet these soldiers attacked the guard
on Watch and stole the Ring of the Azure
twins warships
we will take Chase as well the ring must
be returned
I thought those two are behaving
themselves lately no longer it seems
do we know where they went nice they
were headed to some by wyvern they're
gonna bring it to Hortensia turn this
ship around take us to the coast of
Seoul now
we were in the lead those two are in
heaps of trouble
[Laughter]
I guess they're switching sides now
we're in some now I think it's safe to
say we lost them
perhaps we should pause for a moment
then
I'm sure your wyvern needs to rest her
wings good idea let's take a breather
and then start looking for Hortensia
we have to make sure she gets the Ring
of the Azure twins
why indeed
it's pretty nice ring
aha there they are aha
I like them no
it's a few minutes rest really is to ask
let's get out of here gold Mary
you want to give Coran come with to you
and I got a great fog effect
foreign
[Music]
a we have to get there before they do
there's a big monster that'd be nice but
look
we've got illusion soldiers on the beach
you wanna attack
I'll give you a good old-fashioned
soulmate welcome
that's not enough troops for an invasion
it looks more like a search party Divine
one there's a wyvern coming this way
spotted us everyone at the ready
Rosado
gold Mary
new friends
Hortensia you're not hurt are you
I was so worried
nice to see you and your retainers back
together again
retainer is such a weird word the Divine
Dragon watch out isn't that what you put
in your mouth from the dentist
put that away Rosado I'm on the Divine
Dragon side now my sister is too
Princess Ivy as well
Ryan held against your will blink three
times
it's not like that I
I question is
as my retainers and my friends
will you join me if this is what you
want then it's what I want to whatever
Banner you're under I will defend it
with all my might
[Music]
Divine One
sorry for drawing my weapon on you
here this is yours no it's mine
the Ring of the Azure twins
stole it from the ship we were on
thank you get going
to talk next week
this is just what we needed
restore calm emblem of the sacred
I'm so sorry
oh
cute
you're flying to Japan I I think I can
return to your side my name is Erica a
great time but you know
um sorry that you didn't make it and so
many others didn't make it either it's
really just a small small number I think
there will be
like you can count
kfb who can go to the
concert or Expo on one hand
probably literally five people
um
that will be I will be other chances
surely
where you guys have a favorite chance
I'm sorry about that it's really sad
hmm
but as I as I said
before I'm sure that the streaming POV
will be really good too as it was last
year
we can do watch along
afterwards of day one two
I raised my sword in hopes that peace
will come to this world at last
I know we can depend on you Erica
now which of you should I give this ring
to
you're both to thank for bringing it
here you
ought to give it to Rosado
Rosado flew us here he was instrumental
in our Escape no
you are too gold Mary but there's no
time to argue is there lend me the ring
and I promise I'll do my part
no
you cannot have the ring
[Music]
you will not take it from me I have to
throw it into the volcano
settled
here you are Rosado
stupid I know
English this is where those are those
ran off to right
by all accounts yes
now we sniff them out
big mistake
wait can I actually take it away from
him
[Music]
oh wait he's and are they currently like
um green units they're not in there yet
okay
okay wait uh yunaka
Hank
[Music]
uh foreign
right Corin I'll protect you
corn
I believe in you come on
I love corn she loves corn we love corn
corn
oh
you're also gonna be in Japan
man someone
[Music]
make it in the laundry
oh man
okay unit selection
what are we what are we dealing with
this
worm I don't know what's strong against
it
um do we have a lot of wyverns no
just one
uh
marnie's heavy armor so we need magic
there's like a couple of heavy armors
here too
yeah so magic for sure maybe two
at least two always oh there wait
there's two flying ones over here
oh yeah
manageable
we're playing for the dragon
[Music]
um
oh
uh wait first let's decide on the units
[Music]
hello
I'm gonna take her with me
uh Magic
whatever you are uh that
that
that okay
got it oh Chris
now we have forgoto
bench the armor
Jade
[Music]
I was gonna give her a chance for whom
oh Chris why would I need two
Emerald people
oh sand already makes you slow and she's
already slow
of course better than fogado
is on the horse
so he can reach those
uh flying ones on the bottom faster and
still catch up with us
but okay
[Music]
orange horse is really bad on stand too
wow somebody else fans
[Music]
of units also have troubles so
you have
made me do something I did not expect I
would be doing
okay in that case
Take This Ring I guess
and
you can have fogado's ring
[Music]
um
Lucina right yeah yeah together
so just so that everybody has a ring
uh oh I guess I'm not bringing Marin
after all I wanted to like you know
switch it up a little bit
okay who who instead of Marin
we could bring Chloe because she's
flying we haven't used Chloe in a while
yeah okay nice
but I think I don't have a
ring a special ring for Chloe
don't worry
Chloe always good yes
and then wormslayer to Puma
uh who can wear it anyway
I just want to look at the weapon
it works in life and rhinos though oh
because engagement abilities shreds
dragons oh okay you mean the new the new
one thank you for 10 memberships
okay if it doesn't work then let's do it
[Music]
yeah you guys have been gifting so many
memberships recently
oh
wow the beach was dry that's a bamboozle
my ankles the tide here seems to rise
and fall at a moment's notice oh try to
keep me on dry land will you oh I'd hate
to be stuck tromping around in the water
oh because you're probably heavy armor
are you
hold on
defeat money and movie yeah Pro tip win
the battle
that's what I'll do
okay nice music again
our last desert map for now probably
yo do we have
one two
three or five
or six seven eight nine ten eleven we
have 12 units yeah
yeah membership gift thing makes
everybody happy
[Music]
so this thing
uh what's good what's what's what's good
what's good this guy right with his
thingy
our side's cuter for sure by the looks
of it yeah it might be tougher
with my power you can punch through even
the heartiest Bose defenses well you may
also call upon my twin brother's
abilities if you like oh
oh
emblem
Erica switches with her twin brother
fleib to adapt to different situations
the sing skill lunar Embrace increases
damage dealt in proportion to the foe's
defense
[Music]
oh
the engage weapon deals bonus damage
against Cavalry and armored weapons
armored foes the initial sacred swims
enables the unit to invoke Erica and
ephraim's skills simultaneously what
with both swords sword and lands making
it easier to break foes and Deals bonus
damage against the corrupted
noise
okay so should we like engage right away
there is a charging spot right over
there
so I guess yes
are they not gonna walk over I guess
they can't reach
[Music]
okay okay
cuteness combined
oh cute
and then
should I just do a Twin Strike
oh
yeah I don't know how much damage I
would have done with the other ones but
I guess not that much
[Music]
oh
nice does this one have an extra HP bar
no
it's not
Grace and skill
race and skill you can't do here it
seems
oh no way you can oh look what not worth
it what the
[Music]
should I send someone down by the way
for these
oh Mobius here should I split
[Music]
yes what you got some calm
I'm going down anyways am I
just wait for the water goes down they
will come to you but don't get tinged
okay
um
ready for anything
you know Miss magic would help
no engaging necessary
but
right rest at the top left there's a
house okay
okay it's gone
I can fight
and I guess all I can do is try to
get across
the water for now but next turn I'm
guessing it's gone
[Music]
my will is firm
lots of waiting in this chapter oh
what's that
whatever you ask while the levels rise
and fall for two turns each
[Music]
so I will tell you a little tangent
remember my PC story
remember when I was like
thinking my PC is broken and I I got RBF
to come over
yeah and then
he just pushed it once and it turned on
so um
the other day
maybe I should have danced someone else
um
I I I I I I me I pushed
the button to turn on my uh lights here
several times
go ahead
and it didn't
it didn't work what's that again area oh
nothing was good
it it it didn't work and I thought oh I
guess so the light bulb or so was just
dead
oh
oh sure it moves in the middle of the
turn
who did I call well um
so I I told janma
my Lions is not working and
it was like which lights and I showed
her a picture and she said okay I will
come by tomorrow
and
and another
en staff
came by all prepared they even brought
like a mop uh in case you know it would
be Dusty when opening the light thingy
and
um so they they come into my place
she's like okay which one which one I
say this one and the Gemma pushes the
light switch
maybe twice
and it turns on
[Music]
and I started screaming
and Gemma is like
as the other stuff is just like confused
and laughing
and and and I'm like no but no I
[Music]
don't I wasn't disbelief
I
I got Gemma to come on on our busy
schedule when she's already sleep
deprived all the way to my place
and oh this is so embarrassing
it was so embarrassing
no
it's gonna attack me on this
foreign
so many Pawn moments
[Music]
yeah it happened more than once
and you know jenma knows the
story
of
my PC and I was I was devastated
God damn it
I was so devastated I felt I felt
humiliated
[Music]
we've all had moments like that are you
sure why am I not moving
apples
guys remind me to buy an Apple before my
collab with Kuda after the stream at the
end of the stream remind me remind me
I will have her do it
in the middle of the Stream
no matter what
why am I not moving down
my app my opinion is dead
give us some time give him some time
no one desires War
it's alive but not really
[Music]
oh I think oh it's it's it this is like
doing something it's crashing
[Music]
oh restarting again oh there we go
why are Mages so overpowered broken in
this game
that's right after that
[Music]
that's so embarrassing in the end you
know they just left
but the other staff of the with the mop
of the cleaning mob was so funny
wanted to you know prove themselves
useful I guess
and on the way out mopped my floor
so that at least something was done
how nice is them this pajama by herself
is
yeah
ah man
I want to kill that bastard
and I guess wait a second wait a second
uh
ah fogado
can't kill him are you sure about that
two
let's try six percent crit chance
I'm still alive
[Music]
oh dance dance I Wanna Dance With
Somebody
with somebody huh
[Music]
it's perfect
wait I'll actually go One Step Up
maybe if we can yes
the 11th sword damn
[Music]
it also another cool thing
why am I saying another the other thing
wasn't really cool
um
[Music]
I got confirmation
uh that my Korean course my private
course is starting
very very soon
and it will be okay
the teacher will even come to my place
so convenient so it's not almond it's
one-on-one but she will come to my place
and it will be many many lessons I think
it will take like like three months or
so at least
um
yeah private course it's about horse
private tutoring yeah I thought it's not
even like that expensive
um
considering the fact that it's private I
found a private course would cost
quite a bit more
oh wait I can kill him
just tap to
pack crummy
yeah I wanted to learn the basics on my
own last year but thanks for looking out
I guess I just don't have the
discipline anymore that I used to have
or like I mean I wouldn't say I had
discipline in terms of for language
learning but just like I don't know it
kind of happened smoothly and naturally
and now
I don't have the time and I don't have
the you know for Japanese I just like
had to have conversations with people
every day and it just worked out but I
don't really have that for Korean
oh
I was like in order to really make this
work I think I need someone to push me
really
and for that I just need to set up
lessons
on a regular basis
no I lost
no
[Music]
no no
no no no
[Music]
I will undo I think
we moved Hortensia at the end
um
in that case how about
the one that killed us was the one on
the horse right
as long as he can't reach me
[Music]
okay I guess Hortensia is staying in the
back and she's just gonna chill
no
it's okay though
and this is okay too yeah she couldn't
attack back
snake
finally she would counter
that's not
yeah she got broken
anyway that's happening soon so I'm
excited
[Music]
I think it will be uh like one and a
half hours per week
it depends on me though like I can
schedule it how I want it
and
on a day or on time that I want it's
really convenient why is everybody
him
[Music]
it was a long sessions yeah
but I think that's good
um to have at least an hour
for it to actually really
be efficient
yo
oh we need to I wonder if that will be
homework
oh that reminds me so yeah um you may
have heard it from Cali but
um Cali
found this place where you can do art
while
um
drinking some stuff
like mocktails and I guess cocktails
and hey
we were like trying to build it with
everybody but schedule wise
it was kind of impossible
wait a second it hurts I understand I
know I know it hurts
so in the end you know we just thought
okay
we can't go with everybody but let's
just go with us too
and they have like so many different
courses to choose from
and we both really wanted to do like an
acrylic pour but they didn't have why is
she stuck there is she like Frozen
we didn't they didn't have like the
acrylic courses available because they
were all sold out
like way before so we just got whatever
was available at the one small time slot
that we had available
damn damn our schedules man
Cali is
uh gone for the weekend
I think
so it had to be before that
the painting was beautiful thank you
[Music]
can you attack from here nice okay thank
you
need help
that was amazing so
[Music]
we were
already gonna be like 15 minutes late
and because we came from like our
rehearsal thingies
we were already gonna be late
um
and then we arrived like 15 minutes late
a bat it was the wrong place
which made us even more like and I was
like
wrong face
which means we'll be even later so
oh man
I think if it was just me I may have
kind of I would have maybe could given
up on it the thing is like you couldn't
even call them to tell them that you're
gonna be late
because
um
they have no phone number available they
say if you have an inquiry email us
there's literally no phone number that
you can contact which is ridiculous like
you must like what if people are late
I wanted to tell them at least
so that you know they would like I know
I wouldn't ask them to wait for us but
just so they know
but we arrived 40 or 45 minutes late
to the class
and that you must understand is in in a
thing that takes two hours in total
almost 50 of the class and I was like
Halloween gonna catch up because like
they they must be so far already and
this is so embarrassing to walk into a
class
like that
it reminds me of of school times where
you know
when you're late I mean it didn't happen
to me not that much like to be really
late that's great
to be really late
um
[Music]
still come to class
if if I was late maybe I would would be
like five minutes later or so but no no
normally I I was even there or I wasn't
there at all in school
because this that's just the most
embarrassing thing to me
[Music]
walking to a classroom late when
everybody is like in the middle of doing
something and then having to be like uh
swimming sorry if I was ever too late I
just ditched class
at that point it's like too embarrassing
oh yeah I need to heal uh wait can
I hear one foot dancing I think I can
now but from a distance all right
I can do it from a distance
um can I do it from here how much is the
distance again
okay it works
you're too kind how did you catch up
well
thing
and you draw this whole line landscape
on on an ocean with a sky and then some
some beach some stuff
so I thought they would be way further
ahead but turns out when we arrived all
they had on their canvas was blue
they had the base of the sky and the
base of the water
and you know I I had Cali going first I
was walking behind her and she walks in
and
I think she just said like
maybe like sumimasen or so and then the
teacher immediately was like
showed us our seats
and
it was just like like whatever like oh
God it's like no problem
if I would have
be the one to talk I would have like
gone like a waterfall I would have been
like oh God I'm so sorry
and then
because you guys don't have a phone
number I wanna tried so hard to explain
everything
man
but
I I couldn't hold back in the end you
know I I did say to the teacher oh I'm
so sorry if we went to the wrong place
[Music]
we couldn't call you guys either
oh man
it was
quite embarrassing
but then we just sat down and like
nobody it seems like nobody cared that
we were late it was all good
and
I was like I gotta
catch up so immediately I take out the
brush I dip it into the blue and I go
like
all over the canvas
um trying my best to catch up
[Music]
and I did catch up within like five
minutes I did what they did in 40
minutes within five minutes
[Music]
the title
yeah yeah like
uh Kelly said this too but
um
I felt very appreciated in this art
class and I was like kind of like unsure
of how to do what I wanted to do and
you know I was watching the teacher a
little bit what he was doing and he was
really chill and he even spoke uh he
liked me fluent English actually
cool so um even good for foreigners if
you guys want to do something in in
Tokyo there's like they have three of
those they have two in Tokyo and one in
Yokohama it's called Art Bar look it up
for all the kfb and
in Tokyo
you can look which classes are available
and it's a lot of fun it's easy
and and a nice chill group activity I
felt really relaxed throughout this
whole thing
just focused so hard on the
on the art
that you know I wasn't really
we weren't really talking nobody in the
room was really talking much okay wait
it looks here
already that's a lot oh wait it feels
like a waste oh wait I can trade because
uh she's right there
[Music]
you can get I can eat pretentious meals
the first time I'm eating a meal
I will do exactly that
let's go
where the market is really good yeah I
think so
and then we're fine
um
you'll see what I'm made of
[Music]
should I attack or should I heal
even if I would attack I wouldn't be
able to kill him unless maybe I have
something that way
yeah I know
unless it has a high crit no I would die
I should just heal right
that's why it's Art Bar yeah
the fort can heal
oh
um I might heal myself anyway but I also
want to charge him you know that's why I
was kind of hoping to just go there
um
I was rather fly so no bonus oh
I want to drink and make art that sounds
cool my art wouldn't look like anything
hey no no I think like even there's a
big big big big beginner
um you know it they they teach you step
by step so I think it will turn out
really pretty and if you especially if
you go for something more abstract then
I don't think you can do much wrong what
we were drawing wasn't abstract so
it's a little bit unforgivable I guess
but
you can only charge I know I know I was
going on this I don't know wait for it
hmm
okay I'm gonna chill here
and take an elixir
yeah so we were painting painting and
you can kind of do like whatever you
want
um with it
a little I'm going for him
[Music]
yeah and I guess I was doing well
because even in between the teacher I
mean the teacher was nice to everybody
and would go by everybody and like
encourage them but I felt like his
encouragement to me was real because
like he would come to my painting and he
would be like whoa
and I'm like
hey
and then when I was done with it uh like
several of the
of the participants
came by my painting and the teacher too
and this even the students wanted a
photo
of my art
yeah I was like this isn't even like
that special
and Kelly said mine was the best in
class I don't know about that there were
some other really good ones hers was
really good too
um
[Music]
I do think
mine turned out good especially for the
fact that I haven't drawn this was the
first time I think that I drew with a
Krill paint on a canvas
so I wasn't 100 sure what I was doing
[Music]
um
but it was fun it was a lot of fun
and so relaxing I want to do it again
we were both really happy with the
experience I want to do it again but I
want to do one of those acrylic pour
thingies because I've been wanting to do
that for years and they do that there
they teach you how to do it
foreign
[Music]
like only
um like traditional art but what we did
was for example
um drawing with like
coal I guess
and
um
what else do we do a lot of charcoal
and studies of like
you know shapes and Shadows on fruit
like that typical like that
um
stuff like that
no digital art
I did eventually take like a digital
course a little bit and we did some
photoshop stuff but not
we didn't draw on Photoshop it was more
like
learning how to use Photoshop in general
for manipulating editing stuff
let me see let me see what I can nah you
know what no no no no
be smart quinoa be smart
okay I'll take care of the lens boy over
there
same for me too
to self-taught with digital art yes
I mean I think
most artists are mostly self-taught of
course there's none self-taught ones too
but like a lot of them are just
self-talk
[Music]
enemies over there
I guess now
no one's like really because of the
water no one's really like threatening
you so I can chill here and take the
elixir
[Music]
yeah yeah
um actually
I told Cali you know when we were
getting to the point where most of the
art was done ready
[Music]
and we were just like thinking oh what
could we add I saw that the the original
from the teacher
had a little person in their art and I
was like Kelly Kelly Kelly you should
draw like yourself low-key like you know
just like from behind black dress with
pink hair
right there that was a suggestion for me
and she did it
the stuff with drawing writing our bread
parade on it
was not my idea though
that girl I swear
I was sweating when she did that
I was sweating
oh my my sound is cutting out so much on
my side oh
Kelly Kelly the risk taker
well it was such a collectivity and then
we were so proud of our
of the things that we did of our
paintings so proud
I'm so happy and she's gonna have it be
um shown up at the Expo so for the ones
that are going to Expo you can probably
see her
piece
at the Art Festival thingy
[Music]
um mine however I asked Kelly if she
could send it to my place
in Austria because I didn't want to
bring it in my luggage
I would be worried about it in there so
she's gonna send to me and I'm gonna
hang it up in my home
yeah
it looks kind of tacky
I guess because like it's just such a
typical
you know us Skye water reflection pink
that's so original
and the sakura tree that I drew was even
more tacky I wanted like
um I wanted
the tree
because like I was looking for something
I didn't want to do the same thing as
the teacher did
I wanted to do something a little bit
more original
I was looking around for inspiration and
I saw some trees and some other
paintings in that room I was like hmm
what if I draw a tree because it should
be pretty easy I could just draw like a
like the black silhouette of the tree
[Music]
I want to go too far because next time
though the water is going to go down and
they're gonna attack me aren't they
I'm gonna send kiwawa to the front and
hope that goes well
it's Beauty and simplicity I don't think
it's saggy really
how close season starts it's already
kind of started
it is so warm here it suddenly got so
warm you can just go out with no
um jacket
so for the ones who have not arrived in
Japan yet you might not need to bring a
jacket
it gets a little
evening maybe but not really at the
moment
[Music]
it's not harder
nice ikanji
[Music]
I'm gonna be taking some damage here
imagine that what if I does she does
this guy have a javelin I wonder
does it
what you idiot
so far into the game when you don't
bring a javelin
need help
oh he can't move at all
[Music]
well
can't help you with that
[Music]
this one probably has a javelin right no
all right I guess we're gonna play
around a little bit here
[Music]
yeah anyway I've been getting along so
well with can we you know we've been
doing a lot of stuff together
we went to did I yeah I would have told
you this past story right we went to a
spot together
ain't that nice ain't that lovely
[Music]
together
I feel like I've bonded really really
greatly with her in this trip
[Music]
we talked about so many things we went
after the Arts and we went to a Mexican
restaurant which you guys already have
been seeing on on Twitter that you can't
believe that is actually good uh Mexican
food so I asked Cali yesterday do you
think that was actually like authentic
and she said it was good but maybe not
like that offensive
apparently that's what you said I don't
know you know because I can't really
compare
what did you have I had a burrito which
was actually way spicier than you know
expected
so I ate like one half and then I gave
the rest to Cali and then we switched
because she had like some cheese nice
turn by the way she had some cheese
um taco rice
uh
uh that was really good so I ate like
half of hers and she ate half of mine
and we had a yummy a yummy salad
and
um
some fries
but the atmosphere of the place was
really cool like I legit I said this
place doesn't feel like Japan
maybe we got a crit
so even if the food wasn't too authentic
the atmosphere was getting there
was there Mexican music uh well I don't
remember the music
but it was kind of set up Loki like a
bar
because there were a lot of counter
seats and actually only High seats
no normal chairs
and
um
gosh this map is boring
oh at least I can finish them off
no mariachi
they were playing like there was a
apparently some baseball match going on
so the TV was on and everybody was
watching that
everybody was so focused on that Japan
was playing against somebody maybe it
was just Japan versus Japan or or
something International I don't know
wait until you get to Mobile in morning
I can't wait I have to go there
was there nachos oh yeah I could have
gotten nachos we didn't though
um
[Music]
ah what is the time with Korea oh
protect everyone oh
who won in the end I didn't pay
attention at all I had my back to the TV
because I don't care about baseball at
all it's base I know baseball is like
incredibly popular in Japan is it the
same in Korea Korea lost real bad
oh no
yeah all the crates man that was nice
great
and where are all the enemies
there's two coming from here it's cool
very popular
okay even had no idea it was big Beyond
from America Korea has their own League
collection pandas doesn't everybody have
their own League I don't know what that
really means is that
oh is that
is that where I have to go ah is that
the house oh wait I just
really likes baseball a lot of uh as
well I loved around the world
it's not that big outside of Japan in
America
it's definitely not big in Austria
I'm almost at the end of the month
is
Mexico restaurants
Japan Korea us and Latin America
[Music]
are you able to talk about the big myth
day trip yet no
I can't I will tell you about it uh
eventually
I promise I wrote everything down
I wrote so many notes down I can't tell
you
okay thank you
[Music]
okay okay
you know you know at rehearsal
I was cracking up so much because
um one of uh
not it
oh it's not a match it's like a
[Music]
let's say a higher up in Ian management
um
I don't know how we got to the topic but
um he was showcasing like um
of other like managers to me
it was
so funny because you know I've been
meeting so many managers and they are
all our managers are so
oh they have something
special about them every single one of
them
they're so like what's the word what's
the word they're so unique
and I wish I wish I could like have you
guys experience this but you wouldn't
even get it you wouldn't get it
explanations at all
but those impersonations were so good
and it was so fun it was just me
um and and and uh I think uh jenma was
there next to me when we were listening
to the impersonations
ever another member showed up or or or
one of the managers I was like listen
listen
again they're so funny they're so funny
so the whole day you know
we were listening to those
impersonations they're so funny
so funny just to explain how how special
give you I'll give you a little taste of
how special
our managers are one of uh although this
person also I guess isn't quite a
manager like direct manager more like a
you know staff person who's in charge of
this and that
um but this person
every time I met this person
he would take out a
a
really pretty
beautiful classic
no not it's this this person's not
Japanese no
a classic beautiful fancy
teapot
this person brings a teapot everywhere
as well as loose tea
laughs
and make himself the most perfect cup of
tea
wherever he goes but the teapot is like
Japanese style teapot
you would think
[Music]
British right well I will not say
anything about that but
it's just so funny because like we would
sit on a table this is like uh waiting
waiting for something to happen and then
yeah a man of class he just takes out
the teapot
starts pouring himself the fancy tea
oh man
nobody else does that
stuff
you know
when some tea whips out teapot
how does it get hot well there's like
everywhere we go there's like hot water
dispensers somehow
ah
charge him
yeah cool cool you right where are we
okay oh my God I charged him well I'm
not quite enraged
oh no no we're good I guess I Gotta Wait
matzo Canino
whole management team the management
team seems full of Personality it they
really are
they're so funny everyone's so funny
um
let me try
can I emblem
oh that doesn't do to him
ah normal attack is better
that also doesn't do
I can only do like half damage if I
wanted to maybe I should call some
doubles though
we need all whole stuff to have a
holograph
IC
you're always going to win Madness
aren't too serious but you're serious
enough yeah
I really like our team they're all
really really nice and supportive and
they try their best
you know of course they have to go
through others so they just do what they
can
they try
oh wait oh that oh no oh no no we
stayed behind I think we all just gonna
stay behind until the other one can
reach maybe or we're gonna try to go
this way okay but apparently he can
reach
can reach
oh no which means he can already
reach us here too though
I already moved everyone
yeah okay I guess I have to call the
doubles I have to
come I know
[Music]
okay
smart
I know someone
next turn might be hectic yeah
oh wait am I already
oh I just realized I'm very left that's
already dumb oh oh okay one double down
wait wait it was
did he just go for the real deal
that much for the real deal not for the
double but fake all the missed
yeah
ivy
potatoes
okay okay here we go here we go take him
down take him down
we're gonna
I guess I'll go from here I know that
all the ones up there might kill me
that's okay I'll take that risk
okay
it's worth it
if this is Wars
here it comes
okay
and we'll finish
maybe with Ivy even
or
[Music]
um
yet
wait can you do something like something
wow
and I get the crits please
[Music]
we are like so close to her
but we can't quite reach
[Music]
I should maybe send someone up to hell
up there
let's see
we can blame the tangents for kiwawa
those are different Chihuahuas though
[Music]
not there she's not there oh can I
maybe he can take on at least one of
them on his own
honey
join me
oh oh
no
he is just a dancer yeah no fighter
no fighting me
[Music]
chicken Russia came around
was that right
I remember like being really confused
that it was actually like such simple
lyrics
[Music]
is it anything wrong
[Laughter]
my house yours is no way that's
like a troll lyric
Bonita
[Laughter]
Ben yeah
she loves dad
oh man everybody's so useless
[Music]
magic it is
it not Magic
oh oh oh oh it's L5 that's the one
ah
no
[Music]
wait what if I engage what happened
I can't find the right
chess piece
of
[Music]
foreign
a lot of damage but whatever whatever
I respect that I respect him
it's okay
oh this person's still alive too
um
oh
[Music]
yo
yo yo
what is that damage
he came here to hunt a couple beads what
are you punks doing here
[Music]
I know she has another bar but
you're nothing
that is incredible
my girl
so good
you know Emma was really sweet yesterday
she
um went out early
to buy so many so many snacks
for both management and on
so
it was actually our life savior
we were rehearsing something and then
there was
for some reason there was no food on
that day
some reason I don't know why this time
no food
you know we were kind of losing our
minds somehow not me but I feel like you
know we were losing concentration in
some of us
and I felt like you know we needed some
food in order to refresh our minds
and
I'm abroad you know so much stuff
he brought like some really yummy fruits
that were covered in a thin layer of
Mochi like strawberries and mango and
melon and white strawberry
so we were sharing those
it's really good
thanks Alma
really really appreciated
I wonder okay I wonder if I can do more
damage if
ah wait hers is a
goddess dance with violet oh
dude
what
let bingo
I can do the same thing again
oh maybe I should have
I can still do that
so everyone around we can you know
attack too right so okay okay okay okay
okay sorry sorry sorry
um in that case wait who was doing that
right
can we ah I can get someone here
and
I can get Tamara to be here
Jenny and I don't know if it makes that
much sense though because someone has to
kill this dude
hope that kind of like takes care of
himself
I guess
okay so like this for example
foreign
okay so we are
we finished up the monster in this turn
and we are
in one turn taking care of Marnie
I mean
[Music]
foreign
was pulling out some more of the snacks
she had already you know
she was planning to eat those with us oh
my still nice
she was trying to eat those with us and
she just pulls it out and I look at her
and she looks at me and she's like
should I not should I not do this can I
do this and I'm like
it's a private room but just you know if
the waiter walks in hide it as fast as
you can but like I I I would personally
not do this but okay she really wanted
to do it she really wanted to share
the desserts that she brought they were
kind of cool she had
um maybe she talked about this because
she was like streaming right
before me or maybe still
she had a like something that looked
like an onigiri but it was a cake
it looks exactly like an onikini snacks
them yeah she's a million snacks and
and then we were already at the dessert
stage
and she wants to share this thing right
but the waiter already took away all the
cutlery and everything except for my
single wooden spoon because I was still
like low-key eating my ice cream
and so she's like uh how do we cut this
and she looks at me again
seriously and I look at her seriously
and I smirk because she smirks at me and
then she just takes my wooden spoon
and she cuts through the onigiri snack
which is not an onigiri
and then she shares it with everybody it
was yummy it was very yummy but it's
like so typical
I I was saying so many times yesterday
this is the on my way this is the on my
way
so sweet though she was like getting so
much stuff for us
so cute
I don't know how she bought so much
stuff alone in Victory
stay on my way yeah the way she was
eating her food this time to
was quite the on my way
[Music]
I don't know what to do
let's just do a fallen star but I can't
kill him
or maybe it was combo
I just gotta get closer sorry
I would step too far
shouldn't make another weird combo to
see
um yes yes she did no obstacle will
stick what she was very happy with it
and seeing her happy with her creations
of dominations
made me very happy too
you know after the meat was over we got
a rice course we could choose between
like garlic rice and something like I
don't know crab rice or so and it comes
with like some
soup stock that you have to pour in is
called
uh you eat a little bit of the rice
first and then you mix in the liquid and
then it becomes like another dish right
so she did that but she also added like
the leftover
like toppings I guess for the Teppanyaki
so salt pepper some kind of sauce like
liquid really uh
um really liquid so it's not like a
thick sauce and uh we had like garlic
uh
crunchy garlic
chips kind of which makes all that in
which it is isn't like it's not weird
toppings so I I can see how it would
work out
yeah yeah she always makes a Watson
concoction it's cute
I'm sorry it takes me so long I want to
make progress today so
all the tangents I've said so far
[Music]
we might not be tangenting much more
after this
give me a crit come on come on
me first
[Music]
okay
crit is a lie
which rate is a lie
okay
oh
my God tortencia's retainers would seek
your forces out
what's gonna happen
ouch but okay just one hit
yeah oh okay
what you healed your friend
you little
double heel
well what else could they do they're
losing all their units
mmm
this is also not so nice
gonna be honest
and they're coming from the back too I
don't know if I want to kill all of them
no I don't I'm not gonna try
immediately
next time I run through houses unit
dressed
hey you mean basically a repeat what I
just did
before
but then it's all over so quickly I need
to still go into the house
yeah I can't kill him too fast
can't
is there something good in the house
wait it's just like saving someone and
what do I get from that again
is it worth it it's worth the detour
recover stuff
am I not faster going this way
should be
you didn't see the house when you played
it
get the bus well I'm gonna at least
attempt
at least I break him
yo what his crazy animations really nice
if I can drag it out one more turn
maybe get some exp here
um corn
quick
torrential attack and flood an area
[Music]
I'm not happy with any of that
Dragon vein and Dodge and
like this maybe
I don't know
[Music]
wait oh
did I just say oh
whatever
it's going to dodge everything
um who do I need to kill
um
which one is
the boss
ah well Sam
is it you
just oh no yeah okay I see it now
[Music]
I don't wanna kill him ran away
so
emblem and gate
oh come on
you must give me the crits
yeah just leave him with like one HP
[Music]
dolls
what does that mean molder him
what are we doing for the collapse and
we're gonna play one two switch
and for every game
whoever loses for each game there's a
batsu
scary scary button
and I want her to break the Apple apart
you were beautiful while you lasted
well I I never said I would cancel an
apple but I guess I could give it a try
if she can't do it but I I am not I
think we're like on the same strength
level roughly
did you miss
I can't believe it
can't
chain guards the double
yeah yeah yeah
I know I know
no I thought that that could not
possibly be her true
because I've been watching that show and
I know that was one of the
um me too from some participants in the
original show and I think she probably
got the
um idea for it
when searching for inspiration for some
lies
uh when she was like watching some
episodes because I I showed them one
episode as like an example
but it wasn't that one yeah Bob Mortimer
was the one who had the same claim
and he would even like show it off
and it worked yeah so I've seen it
I'm here
um
[Music]
sorry brain slow
okay
um yeah
uh what was I saying don't waste my time
oh yeah since I heard it already in the
show I thought that must be her lie
also I can't see her actually doing that
can't imagine
but we'll see I guess you know maybe she
remembered oh oh right I can do this too
when she was watching it for inspiration
probably
and I'm glad everybody enjoyed that show
so much I'm so happy
I'm so happy
I'll help the engage attacks
he'll be fine he'll be fine he's ready
has one more HP bar he'll be fine what's
so good thank you
the assets and everything was really
last minute but thank you blue for
making it so last minute the logo from
Spirit snare I had commissioned like oh
a week before I think
um
and I I booked the studio way beforehand
like I said uh I just wanted to do one
more big off collab
before
leaving
foreign schedule-wise
this week that was the only day
where we could all get together for a
tropical lab like this
and yeah I just wanted to do something
and I already moved them oh
I'm exhausted are you exhausted I'm
sorry we're not quite done yet
but I guess I can't I don't have
anything for you
so you can just chill
I won't even hear you
glad it was able to happen yay
yeah yeah everything went so well
um you know I arrived in the studio a
bit early to prepare everything to set
up everything some OBS and I I had like
you know bgms downloaded just for that
like four different ones
I set up everything I actually on the
day before I put everything in my OBS
here together so you want to see it
this is
this was just my
my little playgrounds to you know test
out what I wanted it to look like
um
because I was uh I had to like set up
everything from scratch there
I didn't use the laptop I used the
company's PC
oh wait I can one hit him
let's see
oh no
hahaha
oh man
oh
man
[Music]
Ivy sweep if she's not the MVP for this
one then I don't even know
okay yeah whatever the house I
guess let's draw for now
but we will meet again
Spirit does
anyway everybody was giving positive
feedback so I'm really happy and worked
out nicely and then all the fandoms were
happy not just camping
and
um everybody got to speak gouda was like
so into it
she was so into it she was like playing
Detective
just questioning everything everybody
she was making reasonable arguments
yeah
I was so happy to see her so into it
um
magical suit to use it permanently okay
we'll send it to the Convoy
yes oh only seven turns
um
[Music]
I'm glad because the last of
collaborated she didn't speak much right
so
I'm glad that this this time she was
like
having fun
and being into it
the illusion soldiers have fled
Marnie and mavi are too now we can head
to firenay
yes right away if those ships made
landfall then my people are in danger
ous drained I was drained too
I was really sleepy too man
[Music]
um
where is it
yeah this guy like to do something
for the group
I want to reuse the format
um
but I don't think I can reuse it too
often
[Music]
oh that's right after that we had a
dance lesson
I can't
I can't do
you think you came here we had a dance
lesson together which was also fun
um but I think before yeah before the
dance lesson we were gonna have some
lunch and
I asked what do you wanna what have you
not eaten yet that you have to eat that
you want to eat
and one of the things she hasn't had
until that point
that
you're another
you are a tiger
and fancy cat
uh oh nice place you can even go up here
she hasn't had Ramen at that point and I
was like you cannot come to Japan for
like
more than a month
and not have Ramen a single time you
have to have Ramen but I know I know why
she didn't have it until now
until that point just because you know
she cut she seems to have the same
problem as me just like me for real for
real she feels kind of uncomfortable to
eat in front of people like that
especially Ramen I guess because you
know
hmm
so I was like okay
I have the perfect solution for that
we will go to ichiram Lemon so you don't
have to feel nervous about eating
because you will be kind of like you
have you have walls around you no one
will watch you eating and you just
you're just doing your own thing and I
will also teach you how I eat the ramen
maybe it will help you
so I may just go to ichiran Damen yeah
they have good ramen they have really
good ramen I mean they only have like
one type but it's a really good one and
and yeah it's the perfect place for
someone who's like insecure or nervous
or introvert or whatever you know to eat
ramen no no all of us
and we all went
I was in the mood for some Ramen too
anyway
ah no she enjoyed it I think she did she
liked the ramen
put that down go now
um
foreign
somewhat concerning 99 is perfect for
anxious eaters 100 agree you can like
remove the wall if you want if you come
with like a friend
you can remove it and then you have like
the counter to yourself with your friend
but yeah we didn't do that I I sat next
to gura
but I just kept the wall up so that she
can just feel safe
yeah
you know exactly what you mean he thinks
nothing of killing people
how to fill out the form because you
have to fill out something to tell them
how you want your Ramen I heard about
those awful things the Divine Dragon
said and how everything else works there
set the place for spicy Ramen it has
normal Ramen I guess you could make it
spicy a little bit
[Music]
but generally it's not spicy no
yeah we were still chatting
I was making sure that
you know everything was going well
that you killed Lumera stole the Rings
if I were you I wouldn't believe a word
of it after hearing who your father was
the Divine Dragon probably said that to
hurt your feelings second breakfast time
I've decided I won't harm him
even if it cost me my life so I'm not
going back to Papa ah I don't want to
destroy this world real girl
kind-hearted a few
if you two really want to help then
after I've cleared up this
misunderstanding will you help me find
my sibling
sibling to say you are Lord Sombra
siblings
you have no brothers or sisters
that's not true we've met
look at this
how beautiful
it looks like a Dragonstone it is a
dragon Stone
a thousand years ago
I was crying and one of my siblings gave
it to me
I remember it well even though I can't
stay with you I'll always be your friend
if you're sad or lonely remember if this
stone is intact that means I'm still
alive as you can see in all this time
it hasn't even cracked
but that means
what does that mean it means my sister
is still alive
and I'm going to find her perhaps with
her help
I can convince Papa to end this horrible
War
Sophia is something wrong they don't
look alike though I'm just so except for
the two colored hair how do we finished
our business in fear in a which isn't
even written I will help find your
sibling thank you
I've been looking on my own this whole
time
you two will be a big help look lady
Vale fear and a on the horizon why don't
you take in the view maybe reflect on
what you'll say to patch things up good
idea
another one of Lord sombron's Children
First Time hearing of it
I don't understand they all perished in
the war a thousand years ago
it's too young to fight
I watched it happen Chris watched as
each and every one of them met their end
unless
no what remember something it's only a
hunch but if I'm right
we may have a problem on our hands good
thing we heard this before she fell
asleep I mean I think it's pretty
obvious what they were hinting after all
once we've gotten to fiorinae and
uncovered the truth
she will never awaken again
kind of a weird way to reveal it to Loki
I feel like they should have revealed it
in the more surprising bam way
um
you know what I mean like if you reveal
it then reveal it
don't just half reveal it because this
kind of killed the surprise
there's the hint not the reveal exactly
that's what I mean like it's a hint but
it's like so obvious
but now it's just kind of awkward
I'm all dead
he's dead
[Music]
yes it's you knock off
okay
I'm eating like a
Danish with some potatoes and mayonnaise
and stuff on it I know it sounds weird
but
it's okay
I want to try this
oh yeah
how
I thought evening it's evening is it not
um
I guess it's just Dawn
[Music]
sorry I'm playing with one hand
I'm done now
um
or milk
are you gonna sell fruits too but
[Music]
thanks
grapes how about that
[Music]
um
Max
oh
[Music]
I cleaned my room
before the Stream
because Ina said
she'll drop she might drop by my fire
alarm stream turns out
she didn't make it
she had to go somewhere else now
okay but at least it's already clean for
Gouda
Chan
now I've been giving her so many names
and the earthquake I I did like I was
like awake uh
half a wank for it
I noticed it yeah but yeah
it wasn't done
such a big one wait wait if it's Max now
can I just ignore him now
where's he Max now I thought he was QP
m
[Music]
hahaha
stay in the middle
thank you
don't want no Riddle
[Music]
time to lose
downtown
[Music]
and
wow
Jesus
dance dance dance
in my hands oh I asked by the way if I
can record something they said no
I miss my chances I don't know when I'll
ever get the chance again to record
something in a proper
fireman
oh yeah yeah
I'll make a list for all the things I
want to record
in case I get access to high quality
recording environment again
hmm
I'm gonna say one thing though
uh
in the rehearsal I noticed
that my upper body
moves
more accurately than doing my showcase
uh
now this rehearsal was not happening
in the same environment
so this is a good thing
um I mean Ahmed we're talking about why
and I know why
think I know why
even even better technology
um so that's pretty damn cool
[Music]
hit press yeah like stuff like like body
rolls and so on it's just oh
that was tiramisu sword there's a
tiramis storm
treat
plane lands cry wait did something wrong
like kind of scroll kick
foreign
what the hell is that
I'm impressed
yeah so that's a good thing I
um didn't have to try so hard anymore to
move my body like at 200 percent in
order to get 100 or like 90 percent
um
of what I wanted to be you know what I
mean
was the meal to your satisfaction Divine
one it was the most accurate yes
thanks so much could you look me in the
eyes please
yeah sure perfect keep on looking right
at me you have such an intense gaze
tell me what you're feeling basically
the more cameras
so much really the better
have I stirred your heart so little let
me ask you again
a whisper in your ear sorry I do not
like ASMR
do not whisper with me today no brought
you any feelings of contentment no oh
very much so I knew it I'm so glad
gonna tell me more about these feelings
well no no I'm so content I couldn't eat
another bite
I'd be really curious to learn your
recipe
my recipe not exactly what I had in mind
I feel like I've heard everything but
she speaks exactly like that
outside of Polo
[Music]
foreign
excuse me princess Hortensia Prince
Alquist what's up you're not usually
much of a talker well I was just uh no
never mind it's not important
no running off after a build up like
that
come on spit it out her hair is still
twitching
what did
I didn't oh yeah
please teach me how to be more confident
wow too loud tone it down back it up and
explain yourself properly you always
have such boundless confidence princess
Hortensia it amazes me I think very
highly of myself
so I hoped you might teach me to be more
like you ah okay yeah makes sense good
luck with bad for you though
Maybe if you were in a prince of brodia
I'd have considered it but you
no way wow of course she tried so hard
to ask you and you're gonna turn him
like that turn him down like that just
invaded illusion more times than I can
count
you have every right to deny me besides
you shouldn't waste your precious time
on someone as worthless as me oh man you
made it worse shocked by my own
impertinence
how embarrassing I'll leave you be oh
hang on a sec I never said that it's all
right please forget I even approached
you like this
I won't Sully your ears with my pitiful
mumbles ever again you have my word
[Music]
I was so sure he'd get mad and snap back
even more soft than I thought I'll have
to try a new approach the next time I
see him
[Music]
does my reservation went through for uh
dinner tonight for us I looked for a
nice place uh another thing that I'm I'm
in good I haven't eaten before
when I found a nice place with private
room
had to rely the relay related and we
like relay the info
it worked yeah
what's wrong princess Hortensia
yeah I get it now you've got a whole
other kind of charm
I do yeah it's like an aura of
sophistication maturity I wish I had you
could be anyone's modification I like
that I want they had Oklahoma already
mastered cuteness yes I need to add to
my repertoire I mean maybe not good
development or of maternal
sophistication as I get older but why
should I have to wait I'm gonna have it
I love it
I guess so I'm glad you agree Chloe
because I demand you accompany me for
observation once I see how it's done
I'll be able to steal I mean learn so
myself she
well
for someone to teach her how to be more
like that person but she will not help
that poor poor alcaris out by teaching
him a little bit of how to be confident
[Music]
but okay
I'm honored if someone as cute as you
thinks I'm sophisticated though
excellent wait really you don't mind
that I just up and demanded this out of
the blue
oh no I don't mind at all it's all part
of your cuteness
that's exactly what I'm talking about he
wanted to how do you do tried
ah
she could have tried differently
but it's okay
look at the boys
see doll
may I ask you about something what would
you like to know Prince Alquist
I've heard that you were once part of a
traveling Caravan is that true yes
that's right Merchants performers
dancers
traveled with them all and many more
really
it's incredible
that's a flattering description
I'm surprised you think so well I've
rarely traveled outside of brodia my
duties as a prince keep me so busy I see
I'm also a bit of an introvert I envy
those who can navigate foreign cultures
with ease the world is full of Wonders
things I've seen
like trying to lower Pokemon's age
creature red but absolutely encouraging
and painting I could tell you a story
see really I would enjoy that very much
of course if I tell you these Tales I
will be obliged to leave out some of the
best bits I can't be responsible for
inspiring a prince to go adventuring
Beyond his Kingdom's walls oh no need to
worry I'm not that brave I was at uh
I caught that one off sorry
okay and we're done with that a little
bonding Maybe
violet
I don't get it Professor I abused your
power
how can you pretend like that never
happened I'm not pretending I just don't
see any reason to chastise someone who
already feels remorse hmm
okay don't give me
all right
uh I think
like if I go to my place I can sleep
until night right
uh wait uh my room
and we'll sleep and then I want to do
that turret thingy
not because I want to hear what happens
at night I actually do not want to hear
time will pass okay until night please
someone's coming in
which creep is it this time it makes me
nervous potentia
I don't know if this is okay
my whole country worships the fell
dragon
I wonder what father would say if he saw
me in this place
and Ivy too
Divine One
what I look gloomy
no at least use a classy word like
melancholy
but don't worry I'll still be there when
you need me
well whatever
[Music]
huh
uh ah this one Farm yard
watermelon quality melancholy
Melancholy I'm feeling kind of melon
Cali right now you know
oh yeah speaking of Callie he was saying
in her stream that
I've been like trying to cheer her up in
terms of like her music things
I guess so like it's it's not that I've
been trying to cheer her up
small like you know
I'm just trying to be reasonable because
like she said some stupid like
I don't know my music
and I'm like
so well your music is doing so well look
look at your album being on high ranking
in Spotify whatever that was and so many
oh so many regular listeners on Spotify
and all that stuff yo yo you should be
like proud this is yourself is doing so
well and then she was like um
stop doing this rapping and I said what
the I mean okay in the end you
should do what you want to do but I do
think you should continue rapping you
shouldn't give up on it completely
because that's what makes you special
that one's making what makes you stand
out and you're doing a great job at it
so have confidence and like just
continue doing it I mean you can mix in
some non-wrapping things in between
shortly but I do not think you should
give up rapping like what the
what the
I just tried to tell her what I think is
smart from a business point of view
and then she said something like you
know
because her recent most favorite song is
uh what was the title
like her her own from her own songs the
one that's kind of like Rocky the one
she did in her showcase I forgot the
title uh
wanted ways it yeah
and I said yeah that one's really good I
really like that one too and she said
she wants to do more like that and I
said oh yeah then you'll be the rocking
rapping Reaper not only the rapping
Ripper but the rocking rapping Reaper
like a pirate
would you like a fortune told yes Ollie
tell me whose Fortune shall I tell hmm
mine may the Stars guide the way
olly would like this Karen were we
afraid they're engaged for himself
thinking of chocolate
[Music]
May the Stars guide the way
the same I see tripped fire from
anything so bad
far from anyone where is someone saw
thinking of Fran they never
ended
[Music]
the premonition card tells of unexpected
consequences someone they've been
thinking about may give them advice
whose Fortune shall I tell
if you get more support points if you do
activities with cartoon and for how long
forever
May the Stars guide the way oh
could be better
time
ah Lindo lands the card of laziness they
feel that even having their Fortune told
is too much work but a certain someone
may help motivate them oh kiwawa
shall I tell
could be better
Gene John the food is so good that it's
easy to eat too much
whose Fortune shall I tell
um yeah I don't think I'll ever be doing
this again
[Music]
yeah
I thought it was like gonna give me like
a stat uh race maybe then I would do it
more often or it would give me more
proper lore
more serious
worries I don't know
tell me more about them
I guess not
all right
binder kind of cute though like the
cards
hmm
yeah yeah the cards are nice
uh Jane is cooking
we have new members let's cook for them
oopsie no
not
compote so it doesn't have been simmered
in sugar water
let's cook these
nuts
[Music]
cooking is a bit like rice it's all
about focused creativity
first this then that
better cook these nuts
I think you'll enjoy this meal
oh presentation that outfit
oh
nearly as good as I would do
[Music]
see rank take this for the road ahead it
may pick you up when you need it thanks
for the snack
okay
[Music]
oh you know
you know when I said on Twitter a while
ago
uh that like some bad things happen or
like some some bad news
both things have kind of
cleared themselves up
so we good but I couldn't tell you about
it sorry guys whenever I have something
that I can tell you about I will tell
you about it
[Music]
um
tried always
tell you guys about what concerns me and
so on
sometimes I can't
but I'm okay
it bothered me for the day but I was
having fun so in the end
all is well
talk to the pool don't just promise okay
yes I have
an old well deep in a forest a single
Sunbeam Illuminating a lone flower In
Bloom you conveyed a perfect balance of
warmth and isolation light and dark just
breathtaking wow exactly
you saw all that right away didn't you
you might not believe how much time I
spent hiking in the woods to find that
view but to hear your experience to know
you understand makes it all worth it
finding beautiful things then sharing
them with friends who would never see
them otherwise
you found a lovely hobby Rosado I can't
wait for your next piece whoa sweet of
you to say but if you're expecting more
I need to race the steaks hey maybe you
could help me there's a spot I want to
get to but it's a tough hike it would
definitely help to have a buddy he has
such a video
great thanks so much
everybody's got a YouTuber voice I guess
hey Google
but why the sudden interest I've been
right when it comes to cuteness I'm
obviously miles ahead of you
excuse me
whisperings and cooking is one of your
many talents so I figure if I really
want to compete with you I should learn
how hard could it be
sorry
still not past the part where you
were you Styles ahead of me and cuteness
really
well we can come back to that another
day the important thing is
and I want you to teach me right
I'm here now the most flattering way to
ask for a favor but since we're friends
all right I'll teach high energy thanks
gold Mary yeah that's not exactly
like it I suppose we'll see
laughs
it does
hmm
very interesting you should definitely
see more of gold memories conversations
oh oh you know I dreamed of kfb like
yesterday
I didn't tell you guys but I dreamed of
you guys I met you guys in my dreams
yeah
we have like a fan meeting
oh you were there chicken support cover
kind of like that
can we give the monster seal to someone
I wonder uh
uh
uh what how uh what
huh
wait what wait ah wait what
uh who can
not S rank
um
lean no right
[Music]
see now
I think cedel can get mustard seal
ironically
cliffhanger
you guys
it was nice seeing you
I think right now only see though
no point in master ceiling scene helps
oh
you're so honest it hurts
maybe not yeah
but Rosado and gold Mary may be when
they become level 10 right
you see us as Champions no you guys
we're not chickens in my dreams you were
people oh they're already promoted what
the do I need monster seals for man
eat them anymore everybody is already
done with that give me more upgrades
oh look at them
[Music]
cute
hello
um
who do we want to push
I don't know
how about
Chihuahua and Hortensia
[Music]
that's exactly how I swim just like
Chihuahua not Hortense you know
hmm
now that it's getting warmer I hope
Austria is gonna get warmer soon too
because I wanna
[Music]
um
I want to go swimming outside
I think we're ready already
for the next oh no wait Arena
one more thing
don't take some time yeah
Austria is probably still pretty
old is someone in here in Austria and
Germany like surrounding countries
[Music]
where my European Peeps are you guys
awake yet
[Music]
anyone awake
somewhat I am safe online
is it cold I don't think you still have
to wear a jacket probably yeah right
oh
she's moving Elwyn
but I do what
what's wrong
still pretty cold Germany needs jacket
snowed last week
oh man
big layers of snow outside North America
yeah yeah well no from Europe yeah
obviously it's very cold
this might end up oh
almost end up in a family
there we go there we go you cut me down
oh could have skipped it oopsie
at least she got her level up that's all
I wanted
okay who else
anyone close oh yeah
[Music]
famed dancer of song hmm I am Boucheron
Royal
whoa
my hard work is rewarding
that was incredible
he gave him no chance
[Music]
he dance dance dance with his hands
hands hands above his head
like Jesus what was it
you just told him because I don't know
I am Chloe
I am pennette Royal Soldier
[Music]
this night has met her match
okay
you got that song stuck in my head all
day
it was stuck in my head too
[Music]
dance dancing I listen to the original
version I just knew about this song for
Wednesday I wouldn't even have known it
otherwise and
when I was looking it up on YouTube the
other day I realized for the first time
that there's a slower version and that
the original is from Lady Gaga and
that's the slow version or like that's
the original version and what we know is
just a Nightcore version why did they
isn't that kind of weird for
such a big Netflix show
to use
a sped up version from a song rather
than the original
I mean it works and it's better than the
original
but that feels so weird for them to
use that
[Music]
very interesting
50 hours
we've cut through 50 hours
of this game
and we will continue with story now
I hope I did everything that I really
needed to do I think so
we connect
oh no we didn't oh
hello
uh I guess we're going up
right probably we would go off
um
[Music]
chloropod oh are we going island in the
middle
[Music]
chasing illusion warships heading to
fareen the Divine dragon's Army arrives
at Flora port
or riding
here we go here we go
here we go
Carlos are piling up I'll take care of
it I'll take care of it
I don't see any illusion soldiers yet
they're like maybe they are we better go
to Flora Port eluding you
that's the port closest to fearne Castle
you might remember it from your first
time here right my first time here
I was so taken in by those beautiful
Rolling Hills
oh no what's wrong
smoke from the Northeast
it's the direction of floor report
oh they must have
no no no no let's go
oh no
did I miss the job yeah apparently you
did should have listened better
Flora
why would they do this
these people aren't soldiers Farmers
live here families don't give in to
despair Alfred
for your Kingdom's sake we have to be
strong there are more illusion warships
off the coast if any more make land
fear and a will crumble we need to fend
off the incoming vessels and then rescue
as many villagers as we can
ah
oh dear what a mess ugh and the smell
from that smoke it's really quite horrid
zephia oh
and the Bale you too she's pissed off
guessing this is your handiwork no
absolutely not we only just got here
I heard you'd be coming to fairly and I
wanted to talk
why do you think we're here because we
saw illusia's Army coming your army
the one that's burning Flora to the
ground yeah
how can you not know what his forces are
doing I'm not sure slangs did you order
this attack is that how you knew where
to go
oh my God
sure it rains the attack but I'm not the
one who gave the order well then who did
what monster told our forces to attack a
town of innocent people why it was you
Combs Up In Smoke people burning to
death crying for help any help at all it
was your design
your command
nanny
alive what did I miss they only had two
HP bars and I took them down a
complication
[Music]
mavier why didn't we just finish them
when we had the chance rest after that
long trip yes I'm a little late but I am
ready and raring to kill everyone in
town like you said
do such a horrible thing
those are innocent people innocent it's
not like you to care about that
oh I get it you switched huh you're the
boring one
switched boring what do you mean someone
explain this to me
all right it was a chore dealing with
you anyway I'll tell you the truth you
should hear this as well Divine One
truth you want to know why you're
clueless why you can't remember ordering
the attack because it was the other lady
veils doing along with every other move
we've made
other Veil Lord sombron desired a fell
child suitable to carry on his legacy
you disobeyed him failed to use your
fell Dragon powers
were a defense
Unworthy of your parentage
thus lord sombron gave me the power to
make a few
adjustments
what adjustments what did you do to her
it was simple really I strengthened your
draconic impulses the teensiest bit
then you thought nothing of killing
humans you embodied Lord zambron's with
killing Lumera stealing the Rings
unleashing the corrupted across Elliots
all you're doing
that's why I kept waking up in places I
didn't recognize yeah
as your Consciousness left the other was
awake carrying out her work think of it
you fighting the corrupted that you had
created
but it was better
the fell dragon's daughter and the
Divine dragon that came from
hilarious isn't it and pathetic
person who killed my mother and stole
our rings
it was Veil but
not there you have it lady Veil I'd say
the misunderstanding has been resolved
Sophia Chris
Marnie mothier
you weren't my friends I'm alone I've
always been alone
I
I feel it's all right please let me help
you how about no
from this point on I no longer have any
need of you
sleep now go on drift off into a dream
oh man no no
time to wake up Lady Veil we do need you
I know how disappointed you would be if
you were to miss the bloodshed
oh uh
thank you for waking me zephia I've been
so looking forward to having some fun
fetch me the Ring of the hero King
yes as you wish
Mars
and my Helms prepare yourselves as well
whatever you desire My Lady
how exciting this is
I hope they have the endurance to at
least resist a little it's no fun if
they just die
right don't you agree
seeing is how I don't share memories
with no pathetic little girl my audience
cutting out when I were friends now and
every word I hope that you can forgive
my rudeness your apology means nothing
to me you're not fail give her back rest
assured that I am there yes in fact I am
veil in her truest form
only one of us deserves the honor of
calling the great Bell Dragon her father
completely
my sound is called the best part the one
the one good voice acting part
I guess I'll watch My Stream afterwards
[Music]
um
that's gone oh that's right why is my
audio gone surprise for you
[Music]
oh come on
come on
oh maybe I restarted
even when I closed it
it's like
kind of gone but
uh
[Music]
come on
also I just realized one thing I gotta
ask Emma something really quick
because I realized when I was playing
one two switch with
Corona
senpai
oh
you know you have to use the small
switch controllers you can't use like
the Pro Controller I think
but
you have to add that little bar onto
your mini controllers
[Music]
that's what we had to do I think you
can't do it without the joycons yeah
and you have to add the bar pick now I
did not bring the bars
I don't even know where they are because
you never use the bars
and I think you need them
the bars don't they add like another L
and R to them so you can use them
sideways
don't need them
foreign
[Music]
has anyone played one two switch before
though
I did not need that this makes it easy
to press
okay
hopefully it works without because I
feel like those are really easy to lose
because you never normally use them
please require you to drop the controls
so the strap helps
yeah
anyway
[Music]
when I get my game back please
oh
there it is I hear the audio again
ivy and you divine Dragon it's been some
time has it not
King hyacinth
mother
you're alive
he's not this is corrupted hyacinth
you really have to kill him looks good
as new hmm not like father's King Morin
I can do much better than that when I
create the corrupted they're just like
themselves but at times that can be a
hindrance
so I made some modifications
unimaginable Princess Ivy earned this
what
why me for stealing the Rings from
destinia Cathedral
ever since then I have longed for
vengeance my God I'm so into it I
intended to give you the Ring of the
lady of the Plains but your daughter
stole it take this instead The Ring Of
The Sage Lord
yes lady Veil
have me fight my own father
no don't worry we could let someone else
do it treat people like this don't you
understand how cruel this is
cruel this is easily the most fun I've
ever had speaking of fun
all of the emblem rings are here six on
your side
six on mine there's no telling who might
win
now then
Let The Killing begin
let's go
[Music]
it feels like
um
quite far in the game now am I wrong
oh my God
what is this place
oh
[Music]
I think I might just send some people up
here first
17 out of 26.
yeah not even counting hairlobes I'm
struggling I didn't prep enough
yeah bye you are struggling
well I struggle too Marty and Roy
some of these monsters oh yeah well that
looks like you could struggle
damage minus 10 unknowns
Hyacinth and length and Zephyr and
sticker
oh give me a second
Vale and Mark
um
um if I send some up here and some down
here first
then I think we could like meet in the
middle or should I just bring everybody
out
everybody seems like too much but
knitting makes me feel scared
splitting is really rough
with all the DLC braces you should
ultimately be fine
45 freaking Maps
they love the top side first
if I kill him do I get the ring
immediately can I use it immediately
I guess it doesn't even matter because
pretty much all of my units have
something no I can't okay that's okay
all of the units I I'm using pretty much
have something
you mean no they look it is I guess I'll
go up with everybody more or less maybe
the bottom row can like go slowly
okay
in terms of unit selection I don't know
I could just go with the same team maybe
without see though
uh
who should I bring
[Music]
hey Brandon dancer
and bring seed hello questions
I guess so you can double a good unit
that I'm bringing I guess yeah
no hey this is over the second fight I'm
bringing him with all right I just same
team I'll keep the same team
um
since we're going up uh let me
from the flying units down
okay
whoa four Flyers
[Music]
pulmonary could use a ring wait do I
have one for her
is there someone I'm not using
[Music]
are you mean just a ring in general
right
oh
this one again speed to extract sounds
good
and uh
[Music]
she has a spare still she uses spares
and swords maybe do I have something
else that's like
interesting for her
[Music]
I feel like
for example we have the steel sword
to me
what's one plus two is that better than
a steel blade plus two
oh still blade 18 11.
75 90 8 10.
higher accuracy
do we have anything else maybe
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
warm Slayer you think this would be
helpful
we we said no right because those don't
work for those big monsters
[Music]
Javelin might help though on her
I only have
everybody they already all have Javelin
stuff blame us how about Dad should I
give her the flame lens
I think she can use it
but is it good a magic lens can strike
close or at range oh
but she doesn't use magic so is that bad
it's a magical unit
okay
um
like Chloe
Chloe would like the flame lens right
now
[Music]
I guess she might not need The Mending
stick because everybody I have like two
other healers already here
let's take this I feel like that makes
sense
it's extremely heavy
it doesn't make her slower
foreign
[Music]
so just by putting it in her inventory
she gets slower
was only when she carries it on her
first hand
[Music]
only if she's using it okay
why not bring it
might come in handy right
I'll bring it
singing down
[Music]
this is apparently a tough battle so
you gotta be prepared
foreign
take that silver dagger I don't know
Maybe
maybe good
take that Elks here
my dog now
um
oh she got the revenge and Jade's meal
okay nice
[Music]
wait can I be no wait no not Ivy uh can
alcrest use the croissant Bowl
and if yes what do we replace it with
because
good
Has anyone used the crystal ball I guess
it's a new thing so probably not
Minnie bow is pointless
short range
but what if someone attacks him like
directly and he can't fight back
it's a joke weapon light and buttery
death upon your enemies
probably better than the Iron Bowl okay
that's what I wanted to hear
a bowl of a sweet scent disappears when
consumed
as an item
[Music]
but I can use it as a weapon too right
so can I choose between eating it or
or fighting with it
[Music]
because it does have stats
it's it's really better
[Music]
emergency yeah that's actually
a preference both for different
occasions
um so he has no space in his in his
inventory for food but just in case he
really needs something he could just eat
his bow
foreign
okay
I think I can go
[Music]
I could put one more thing into his
um
inventory
he's spare and ax
how about hurricanes
can I follow
magical glass
or maybe a one of those no
[Music]
you wanted to a quarter
instant kills fire should we bring it
okay for that oh Hector's bracelet
does Jaden give her the hammer
I already decided on the team though
what's up
wouldn't the arrows be the enemy I guess
not
besides quasa I'm so into a mimir right
now
is it me Mia or is it meal
my favorite words right now
[Music]
puzzle
okay okay okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah ring okay I will I will
onto changing the ring you said
uh what
which ring to who
Hector's string two
[Music]
on Rosado
who does Rosado have right now this one
wait America I'm honored
[Music]
and you can have Hector leave it to me
leave it to me
hi thank you
um
defeat all six enemy Commanders
I gotcha
[Music]
all right
have you listen to places yeah
was interested
she says she likes twice too
and
we watch it a little bit after it
released
put out my I run out of my phone and we
watched it silently together actually
not that sound
she made some comments she really liked
it the video and stuff
it's maybe not the best opening but oh
well
yeah
we're not 100
like caught by it yet it has yet to give
us an ear warmly
but it was good it was good
I had the same thing with previous songs
where I felt like
somehow it's not catching me
but then later on it did
with a lot of K-pop songs I have that
and and Cuba also actually I was so
surprised
because we were talking about Kpop I
asked her if she likes K-pop and she
told me she also really likes new jeans
kids all the time
[Music]
all the touches let's go
foreign
[Music]
partner think whatever you like
oh oh I'm doing rehearsal
and I noticed I mean I only kind of
noticed this before but I told gura
she's the second best dancer in math
she
um has a good feeling for rhythm
and she knows
like you know you can really see the
difference
uh and like someone who knows how to
move their body who has like a feeling
for it
and someone who doesn't
you know it's nothing nothing like
negatively so but it just really it's
easy to see when someone tries to dance
[Music]
really well
so I was praising her about that she
told her you're the second best dancer
in this girl and she was like
yeah
that's good
hmm I was quite proud of her and
whatever what was I gonna do oh yeah oh
yeah
um
she's
still like Kpop Style dancing with me
and I was like what
are you sure
dancing
super cool cute flowers
I said well perms.com
perms are gonna be a problem
and then she said well I guess we just
gotta make our own the stage is mine
song like that for that kind of dancing
would fit
somebody dance unit
[Music]
maybe we'll say the world even
no mistakes I wish I could reach from
there
who's got Lynn right now
did I already move
uh
uh wait where is Lynn which one is Lynn
what the this this one's Lynn
probably reach with bubble but it's it's
hard hard heavy armor so I probably
won't do anyway
that's why my dad's oh yeah I bought my
chair
oh
[Music]
if I dance like this
everybody around him will that well it
wasn't only that engaging skill
where are we headed
oh
no just one oh okay
only the engages baby okay because it
looked like it okay
[Music]
to take this heavy armor guy down with
your magic
king of dancing
I feel like I I didn't want to you know
stare at her but in dance practices I
would like sometimes
take a little peek at her while she's
doing her thing
and you know mostly when I do like dance
practice my face
I just kind of
like keep it neutral dead inside
just saving energy
[Music]
you know not doing anything with my face
but
um she has such cute
expressions in her face when she dances
I wish I could show you but she has like
this cute
smile and like she's really feeling it
she's like imagining
even in the practice she's imagining
that she's like
you know
forming the song in in her mind
[Music]
she has such cute Expressions I'm
telling you
you don't understand
should we stay should I just have some
people stay
I don't think we need to move all of
them up
sedimenting
sweet mental image you're welcome
try doing Expressions while I'm
practicing
[Music]
yeah I don't even try
so
I don't think my face looks interesting
when I okay when I do that
When I Dance
I guess I'm bringing everyone low-key
ah
[Music]
um
no I know this I know oh oh they're
coming oh maybe I'll just
um
leave the others behind and let them
take care of that
oh he's like oh he's also like I'm still
so far but he's coming for me
um foreign
how far can dancer go
so what is that dude anyway what is
effective
he's a he's a mage
oh uh what's effective against Mages
again
punching Sage I don't have a stage
although when my can't he punch
would that actually work like
would he do well
it's Tim
yeah only to break him though
how should I do
what should I do
you know what I have an idea
[Music]
let me find it
grant me straight
do I sleep well
foreign
[Music]
to someone else maybe
he's actually been tanky
okay when in doubt just send kiwawa
first
just kind of sucks that I can't do the
first hit
[Music]
you can go so far
because I left
Shields she'll survived right well if
she doesn't then well
foreign
[Music]
she will die
well I don't wanna go back in time just
yet
that was my first move
Celine should be fine
oh
I wish we could switch
moved let me go there
ah wait wait can I dance
where do I have to stand to be dance
uh okay diagonal to the bush
if I dance myself here then I think I
can go in front of Chihuahua
dance dance
what good fortune
wait what about lemon sword
[Music]
all of this is not good
damn
[Music]
yeah
but now I've come all the way
we brought her there because somebody
said she has good magic resistance
so at least you could you know
take a hit
so does he well okay then she'll just be
a shield I guess for now
foreign
[Music]
I don't know
I don't I don't know
just bad
[Music]
um
Just Gonna Have Some Fun down here
get some work done it's going to
teleport to someone
Unforgivable
to one of my units
well
so shall it be
let him try
Javelin does more
other things I've noticed by the way
did you guys somebody asked
[Music]
um
callium
there's also a quick learner
and she puts like a lot of
extra energy and her own style
into her moves which I think is pretty
cute
she has some some dorkiness
in her moves that's also really cute
and she gets like so into it she gets so
into it
she likes to exaggerate her moves a bit
she has definitely her own style and
like you can see her personality
so much in her movement
[Music]
she lets out all her energy
and then uh well I don't know what to
say about Inon like
you know I'm a of course
you hit me I hit you let's get this pain
party started okay have fun I'm of
course doesn't have so much experience
and email to me
really
[Laughter]
I knew I would disappoint everyone wow
get out of the way for now
I'm sorry
[Music]
um
all flowers eventually will live return
thank you
how can I know who he's gonna teleport
towards so oh look at that window tap
oh sick I will not forget you're pretty
cool it's pretty cool
the only difference is staying out of
range
okay now I'm returning hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi hi hi hi
oh
that I cannot accept
so should I go all the way back to
kiwawa's first move
[Music]
yeah but I don't understand like
eventually I I have to reach him anyway
but
how do I reach him and stay out of his
incredible teleporting range at the same
time
something
well we are already apparently in his
teleporting range
I guess I'll just keep everyone out else
out of it okay let me do the thing down
here again because that worked kind of
nice
[Music]
how exactly did I do it
foreign
okay so I would hope that he would go
for hotels you know maybe I'll put her
to the front of them I'll even put her
into a bush
she's the furthest out there
maybe I'll move everyone else back then
he has to go for her right
right
oh yeah she's not affected by terrain
okay but still
okay
sorry Hortensia
but
this is for the greater good
maybe I didn't have to go that far back
but I'm still in range
my God
waiting goo
[Music]
yeah
I see it don't worry guys
oh yeah stuck in the hell fly I should
do that again yeah
[Music]
oh wait ah
so
I'll dance
great
so she can take one more down
Unforgivable
[Music]
foreign
beautiful
get our crisp out of there too
oh you can't go any further that's okay
wait
another range
go away go away
oh but like
yesterday at rehearsal I was I was like
praising Amir a lot because she tried
really hard
she said that like she didn't have she
felt kind of foggy in her head on that
day
but she did so well anyway
and I got what she means so you know
is that what she means
she did her best and she did really well
and when she got something down that she
always like messed up before
I told her
[Music]
Embrace they're trying to get her her
motivation and her
what's what's the word
you hit me I hit you let's okay
rejoice
[Music]
what's up
now I can attack
stupid
very stupid uh how to
uh
[Music]
Ivy has some good dialogue she can't
reach though
unless I make her dance
I want to use an engage
I can't see though
okay I'll try
it
it doesn't show that it breaks him
because it has to do damage in the first
place
[Laughter]
[Music]
devastating
foreign
[Music]
I'll do the Eternal claw of a high crit
chance for that one I'll take some
damage that's okay
[Music]
oh
Dream well right there was one more
that
oh
easy easy
[Music]
Maybe
cuteness I'm standing in the fire if
he's there
no he's in the thicket
Dobson always follows up foes cannot
follow up
can I do that
[Music]
he will not be able to follow up
what about the other things oh wait that
does a lot of damage wait can't we I
can't switch through it's kind of hard
to see
[Music]
still great ax socilla acts does the
most damage
it's not an attack
why does it show his HP thingy though
[Music]
and kill oh but that only would work if
she doesn't never quit
[Music]
but yeah could do that
okay okay
our foes are strong
[Music]
okay
um
I don't think I'll
never create
thank God
maybe we can still take him down in one
turn with the help of others
let's go with the mirror
a clan
oh yeah we can finish him off with that
oh
my MC is so weak yeah on my way
give me back my ring or I'll bite it off
if I have to
okay
HP string speed luck
sandstorm
that sounds like Bolognese
it's really mad you fired him always had
like the strongest one
[Music]
if I
was that
the conversation was moving to five
space radios
all allies hey are we here
let's go
incredible all right you guys wanna link
follow me
all those enemies
do I have a snatch I don't have a snack
[Music]
uh
uh yup
kind of you
so now we go left
oh
didn't I already move her and attack of
her she's so confused did she get a
second one
she dancing what what's going on yeah I
did it right
it's still engaging huh
can I do something
[Music]
very satisfied
oh
yeah okay left we go
we're in the next one image oh there's
another boss right there
um something's up there ah
I'll stay a little bit lower
just need one turn to move everybody
um does she have a physic too no
Okay so
leave her behind a little bit
for the sake of the Hill
okay she'll catch up
Maybe
[Music]
there's also special directions but it's
not that strong to be honest uh-huh
well I could have repositioned
oh here we go
[Music]
ah
nice nice Dodge
[Music]
what is that what are they wearing
that's Cape they look like a people when
they're running
here goes
just gonna run away
although I mean I still have my engage
thing on
might want to make use of it
you know what I mean
let's get a credit out of this
yeah I think I'll attack them
[Music]
no crits that's okay oh
did I just say I need one more exp for
level up one
or am I like max level or what
what
my God
[Music]
I don't know
game trolling me
guys did you see the new Mario trailer
it's really good
uh should I just finish off the one
that's almost dead
yeah
I am the Divine not yet
so good oh I've got the critical
should have killed the other one
yeah the whole like Mario Kart
the fact that they include like the
Rainbow Road and stuff like that is so
cool
I'm getting excited for it
it'll be released what next month
[Music]
so that's exciting
I kind of want to help up there
[Music]
I'll help that's all the members I will
bring up here
oh wait I can even oh
sh 23 pretend
[Music]
you're gonna go soon of course I have to
you look so high quality they said
they've been working on it for what six
years
oh my God
my God yes
I'm not watching in English yeah I guess
I'm gonna watch it in German because it
will be in our theaters and the language
will probably be German I wonder if
they'll also have um
original
is there original English I guess the
original English they probably have an
English version in the cinemas too maybe
but I guess I'll just go for German
because from what I've heard so far in
the German trailers
the German synchronization is really not
bad I think I prefer Peach's German
voice over the English one
for example
[Music]
um
what was the effect of again someone's
someone's
someone has an effective
was it irica
now I'm curious you can look up German
trailer
against that monster up there
which emblem was the fastest one Erica
[Music]
and difficult to range so I'll guess
I'll just walk around
[Music]
how much damage does
okay not that much in that case but look
at the Kusa
what's up
she'll go that's the most
possible
[Music]
this one sounded good too oh crap I had
no choice but to win nice
and watch along when it's out digitally
I don't know about that but
because how long will it take
until it's out
digital is
okay I kind of want to see it
engagement his
[Music]
when someone one hit that dude so
you can throw a javelin can you throw it
back yes you can
[Music]
foreign
play what I'm doing wait what can I
wasn't I able to reach before
[Music]
because of
reduced moving huh
I thought it was doing something cool
[Music]
it's not admit though that was cool
this works too
[Music]
um
I believe I believe
yo
whatever
Mia
[Music]
no no no no no no no
no no no no no thank you
[Music]
for some reason I thought I would switch
let's try this 76 86
last 26 it's not worth it it's not worth
it
maybe maybe the fog wasn't so good
maybe the Flop wasn't so
I don't even benefit from the Vlog well
that right yeah okay I'm gonna play
some even though you know I'm
pretty I mean I should benefit from the
woods because like look how deep she is
in there
she's obviously covered by the woods
okay
[Music]
I'm not above the tree I'm in the tree
ouch
[Music]
oh
good job see now
oh he goes for clothes
where are we
oh
no
[Music]
yeah nice think whatever you like
oh oh
I'm eating
European talking
sticks
chocolate cookie sticks
[Music]
all right
yeah I brought Mikado to the land of
poke
I'm running out of my European chocolate
by now
I'm running out
keeping it raining Channel 10. what else
sleep now Nice Bridge
Dream well
oh yeah I'm gonna give
everybody
like specific presents too like specific
snap presents
she gave me
chocolate
from Godiva Godiva
which is like
special
collaboration with Animal Crossing
Godiva chocolate
so it has like a metal case
with the Godiva logo
and Animal Crossing characters
haven't tried yet though looks yummy
though
and I think I can reuse them the Box
hmm
this is the good stuff like they got
cool collabs here man
Animal Crossing ma'am
[Music]
it I'll do it
go for it yeah
man guys I'm so happy I'm finally
healthy again
so nicely
took me a while also it seems like
nobody got sick from me
hmm even though you know when I met
uh Cali no I was so sick and some of the
others I was like at the end of
recovering so I was worried that I would
get them sick
but it seems like it was okay I won't
miss a step
[Music]
I really didn't want to be
responsible for getting someone sick
especially not in such an important time
yeah everybody's gonna be careful now
um
I might just use this opportunity to go
back
or should I
no she can only fly as long as she's
engaged
I'll go this way
sorry sidel you might die
um unless do I have a physic
no
well
sorry
[Music]
I'm so nice I'm so nice
it's so nice oh
so nice
okay what do we do here
um
shall we advance to some of them
horizontal almost dead so he definitely
needs some healing
but let's focus on getting those two
little enemies down first
which we can do by
I'll bring her over to the side
ah
[Music]
must be kidding me what
what's your triggering
that's so triggering
[Music]
if I do it with the Killer Bow I might
be able to kill before he hits me back
right
[Music]
maybe maybe maybe
around I'm ready to watch Mama's room
hello
finger okay no crit
[Applause]
I'll apologize later
I could have outrange them
yeah this map this map has been uh
already giving me some trouble so far
teleporting Bamboozled me in the
beginning
okay I'll walk over here just till I get
closer
at least a little bit
okay
I'm sorry you had to see that
I was asking for a hard map
yeah yeah
a 10 or five and Italian coins would you
bring it to Japan and leave it at home
last time I just ended up with more
coins oh that's a problem I'mma has
right now too
too many coins
they're like what I do with all these
coins I said just give it just give it
to henma
just give it to Henman ask for some
paper money
yeah I always gotta make sure that
you're using your coins
but like I think you should bring them
bring them the Japanese money that you
already have and then use it in like
vending machines or fill up your your
suica with it or yeah just use it in the
convenience store or wherever
[Music]
no
I think you should just bring it I still
had like I I still have and I still have
it's a hat and have a lot of leftover
money from when I stayed over or on that
state over but like lived in Japan last
time
um
because you know I had a bank account so
I was trying to get all the money out
but I couldn't make it in time I was
like doing the daily limit for like a
week or so a week and a half
I would go to the ATM every day and get
out as much money as I could
oh that sounds like a weird Flex
well in any way in the end uh
I had to like on the last day
when I had to like
the leaf was like well I still have
money in the bank account
so I went to the counter and I said
please give me all the money and cash
yeah and then I had the stack of cash
and that's what I've been using for my
last trip and this trip
just bring all the cash like
the Yen that I have left over and use it
instead of changing Euros to
uh yeah because like I knew that I
wouldn't come back to Japan for a while
and it was a while but I did not want to
waste any money on changing the yen
back to euro when I knew I would come
back eventually maybe not anytime soon
but eventually and then I saved me some
conversion money smart right I waited
ages though to use that to use that
stash
all my savings from the year in Japan or
that really it was only half year
savings since I joined Polo before that
I was not making any money in Japan
our year was worth way more than Yen
well
now maybe
but back then I don't think the Yen was
that weak
and also my brain is also weak so I
don't think I would have really
understood I even if the Yen was weak in
that moment I thought well
conversion takes money too so why not
just keep it the way it is
um
I hell what do I do here
[Music]
she's meant
um
I wish I could I need one more step to
reach
to use mend
um
[Music]
oh thanks yeah commission and conversion
okay
yeah I I could move them backwards but I
don't want to move them backwards I want
to move them only forward
[Music]
you can move them backwards
do you have a moment no I'm Alex here
[Music]
wait would you not got useful
interesting
[Music]
maybe not that far one step back
Wards engage attack
I think whatever
it will be like that
[Music]
it I have to do it
well I mean I do like the men because it
heals so much
and I don't want to replace anything
else she has in her inventory
wait she has something useless in there
doesn't she
[Music]
no
she she can use all of that
[Music]
gonna die no
no no
she's not gonna die
man is worth keeping up okay oh that's
what I thought
some at least one close range
healing stuff as long as it's a strong
heel I think it's just nice to have and
here you go there we see the man come in
handy right here
I thought I was done for
since I've forever since you started I
don't chat March but I've been looking
since forever thank you
you're welcome to lurk list
if you want
[Music]
in one month apparently we can do that
ocean
oh you were in range oh we can do
that
um
free no 2.5 years
chat subscription
all right let's see
is she gonna engage oh
yes
oh
oh oh
she survived
oh she replaced the fire
interesting cool so I can do that too
once I get that ring
big damage and fire I like that
she's like dying she has one HP
left
ah
we have to heal her
uh I'll get her out of there uh there's
work to do
or maybe should I keep her there
is that a Healer
behind her hell
[Music]
I cannot find all of dragons oh true
true true
Dragon vein right here
should I do it here
you can't spam the fire
I do have to heal you otherwise she's
gonna die
wait think
well yeah I know I know it's gonna be in
a way like I'll I'll I'll get a
disadvantage of it too but this way I
would get rid of all the fire
Maybe
maybe it should be here
another one here
one thing just do
ah fire can never kill
Ed yeah how much do I care about the
fire oh well I'll just get rid of it
fog last
oh
I haven't rewinded much yet I think I'll
rewind
um
[Music]
okay okay
who will get to heal
[Music]
him all these units are kind of
damaged also what's effective against
Mario magic huh
damn it I have to use my at least one
magic unit to heal
okay I will
fire your ass or one of them now focus
on this one
however it's not a certain kill
oh well
[Music]
and then
yeah wait just
because I saw someone engage saying
engaged so far I've seen like
mostly like one Arrow engaged thingied
Lin the rest are all like kind of close
combat is there
is there a magical engaged ring
Sarah
she has holdouts
Sauron oh
[Music]
yeah yeah okay okay
not so many of them
wait hold on so is it like like in
Pokemon like endure
if I would shoot her now
with like Fruity damage would you still
only go down to one
now she would die
[Music]
how do I read it
on air
if unit had 20 HP or more at the start
of combat unit always survives combat
with at least one HP
and it's not worth that I give her
another hit I should focus on the other
ones
wait let's survive does that also count
for when she has two HP bars
like I can only get her first HP bar
down to one
two
but it says under 20 hp at the start of
combat so wouldn't it apply to the whole
battle to the whole combat like this
this one round
I know I know I know it said over
but like she had over 20 in the
beginning of this round
so what I take from that
is even if I bring her under 20 in this
round
she would still
survive
[Music]
at the next hit for example
combat not round
[Music]
oh combat combat means
that one interaction between
two units huh okay
I thought it meant the one turn
okay okay
[Music]
she also doesn't have much but I think
I'll heal you knock out with her and
then her with uh
uh my other favorite chick
now she's kind of standing in the way
for the fireplace
huh
oh wow
but now then she'll take uh
ah whatever
she won't die from the fire it's okay
[Music]
okay
um
we can do something here I want to see
it
how much can you do with engaged
ah yeah that was bad
I don't like that ring
my goodness how awful did you die yes
Grit
and she didn't
get or he missed I don't know
[Music]
I did not expect that
are you able to
do two damage
by any chance
no
it's incredible
incredible
give me an order
can you do two damage
no only if I take 46 damage first what
[Music]
okay okay okay
the killable can do it
but also the Longbow right
may I please um actually you know what I
can stand no
I'll I'll be here
wanna be safe in the ticket
nice
I have no choice but to win an ugly
warped to hit or engage with you knock
off
um instead of getting rid of the fire
Maybe
-10 is quite a lot
I'll just take a look how much it does
[Music]
oh
nothing
okay
I am late one more one more one more
thing
something oh you can hit the the one in
the back quite nicely
yeah magic is it's just always magic
when in doubt use Magic
so unpleasant okay that healer I think
is down
so we're good we're good
here we go
oh
oh yeah maybe risking
[Music]
Celine Dion no she cannot
uh how are we doing up here oh this
one's following whatever
can't waste my time there forever oh
no
oh no he's in range of the monster
ah
[Music]
it's not good
wait wait wait wait wait
I protect
I will protect you
[Music]
depends down range of an orange yeah
I'll get her I'm a bad obviously I
haven't moved here yet
it will ignore kiwawa
don't ignore
do not ignore
well if I'm gonna go back I might as
well
should I go
undo the Rosado thing too
but I like that that he killed someone I
like that
I'll just go
[Music]
oh the reach
kiwawa should survive
you little
why is your reach so big
all right all right
I'll take you on then
it's not a flyer
does she have a longbow
ready for a fight
this is so scuffed
lion
[Music]
he also doesn't have a close combat I
think whatever you like bow either nice
she was not ready for this battle he had
no Longbow no mini bow nothing
okay
wait we're done I'm kind of worried
about Tamara up there but oh
[Music]
that's what you meant
the fight for peace must not end here I
hate to leave but I must withdraw
what do I do
stop at nothing to protect lady
they're just done it what
what a mess
[Music]
oh man
see that
[Music]
no I don't care don't even I don't want
to see you
no
stop nice gold Mary though he survives
everything
[Music]
I shall
under
[Music]
uh
man
[Music]
please give me a crate again please
please please please
how did she cut with two percent before
even
how does she even do that
you have my respect
oops she did it again
what is this game just is bullshitting
you
when it comes to percentage don't
believe anything
[Music]
I don't know if I like what I'm doing
but I have to try something else out
I could dance kiwawa
make her go further
thing
I haven't seen all that because I don't
want him to be in reach
[Music]
I will also give him
nothing
well this time he will dance
[Music]
I moved as far as I could without being
in range and while still being arranged
to dance for kiwawa
so she could also move a bit more
[Music]
panic
someone needs to heal her would she at
least if she got healed would she at
least survive it
if I bring her this far down why would
he go for her
try to kill him
okay
well not like that
come on that
for the mother this is so difficult
those connectors
oh
33 man pretty free
[Music]
Killer X hope for a crit Maybe
yeah maybe worth
come on come on come on
[Music]
oh
my second hit right yeah
still got the damage still but I also
got the kiddos my goodness how awful
okay
that is taken care of
so no
imminent danger down here but there's
also a lot of danger coming from here
and everybody's already pretty damaged
so I took this one down with our first I
think which
Berry is fine in my opinion
but
there's a lot a lot to work on here
what I also did though is that I used
one of them
I think Chloe to heal
you're not gone and I used her to heal
Chloe
[Music]
I guess yeah I'll have yunaka use fog
and then at the end
so that it hopefully gets as many people
as many of my units as possible in a
safe fog environment
[Music]
take these mobs down now
back how far back
[Music]
okay not
everyone is too close not everyone
no this is all this is already too close
if I was here it's already too close
that's where fogalo died
well Chloe can't do magic anyway
so
she will heal
what if I bring inaka here no
[Music]
if I bring her
here use the fog red here
afterwards
[Music]
so difficult I think I have to lose at
least one unit
ah
[Music]
the flying ones almost all of them are
flying and they don't benefit from it
[Music]
I don't know
I feel like this is not going so well
how much more do I have left here
oh
ah
[Music]
I need my units
and I understand why someone else was
saying
they haven't
done this one yet I haven't gotten free
lips
who did I use to kill this one
I used those what what did I use
who did I use
did I even kill him
connect oh well connections
out of order now
I cannot get her into reach to do
anything right
so I might just use her to heal the net
unless I move you're not that close
enough to be healed by
Celine
nunaka needs it a bit more
but then if I move her over there
you know the fog
we also have to be there
unless
[Music]
I bring her this isn't that kind of what
I did before
all right
okay
[Music]
I'll try
you know guys there really
but she can either use the item or use
the fog and I guess in that case the fog
is better
anyone else who can heal oh yeah she can
still be healed by Chloe but that means
I just can't really do much in this turn
besides trying to be defensive
so I would use it here and then move
old Mary in its two
and maybe move Acres first around to do
a final hit
[Music]
what I want oh yeah wait I can do it
from here
that's what I did
with the longbow
[Music]
cause we we need to take money down we
have to
[Music]
it's okay I'll apologize later
no enemies going for her they can't hit
her in the fog
you think so
I would do it here
[Music]
I was certainly gonna get hit yeah
how hard
oh wait Marnie
phil1 HP
oh yeah Ryan
[Music]
I need to go get the 48 treatment again
huh
I know I know I know they don't get help
but you know I need to help the others
wait before I do that
so many things to consider she can't do
anything here because she can't get
close enough
but you can't do much damage to this guy
ever it's not worth it
can you do if you're not gonna
[Music]
um
do anything effective
[Music]
I want to stand right here because
apparently I'm
only out here
what if I Endure with
Rosetta wait Hector no was Hector the
one that endures what the does heck
they do again
emblem engage
but that stands it always falls up close
commercial up
uh
so
would this help
probably not really
[Music]
let he lets Rosado attack first enemies
can fall off
[Music]
I wanna do some damage
what
what honey
[Music]
I wanna do damage
at least some damage
I mean
why not if I'm not gonna get hit back
then why not okay what's gonna happen
stop it nothing
nothing lady fail
[Music]
s
what Chloe is that first
event lucky I'm such a luck
[Music]
we go
and again they go for Ivy but she
survived so much stuff it can stop her
that's so angry she clears up everything
she doesn't stop she doesn't stop she
goes her own way
[Music]
oh
whoa Ivy single-handedly fixed all my
problems
I mean
this woman is the woman of my dreams
[Music]
why don't you have little maybe I don't
know
[Music]
wow
what a turn around
foreign
oh
no Stefania huh
no healing stuff on you
could Warp
why would I work
let me think about that one
my God
okay time to take down Marnie
and all these other suckers why are you
already here
oh
I I I I I I need to
reduce your magic
wait why Duster
I know defense does he have
that magic doesn't do
to him
what
what's his weakness
[Music]
Focus night what can I even do to hurt
him
what
what maybe Erica
I'm sorry you're stuck with me
make an attack
but yeah that's pretty good that's
pretty decent
All Things Considered
but I could one hit this bastard with it
[Music]
he is on a horse
got peanut at him let me try
I think that works well that's pretty
decent too you guys don't know
[Music]
maybe oh
oh no what wait
would be nice if I could break him with
that breaking stick now but she's too
far
maybe oh can I trade it too Celine
Celine goes over breaks him
it's like a like a Olympic torch run
[Music]
wait I can do it from here
the range
that works
yo
wait did I do damage too
but did he already have that no it had
the damage right
so boy
so he can't he can't
can't fight back now
and if I'm lucky I'm gonna get the crit
but she already is uh her percentage is
generally already pretty low here all
right all right all right come on come
on come on come on come on we're
throwing my dice here
oh yeah okay I'm fine fine
at least she hits
better than nothing
[Music]
um
you have to kill Marty we have to kill
money we have to kill morning I can't
kill money I can't I can't kill money I
can't kill money
I can't kill money I can't kill money
um but uh no I can't what it's being a
let me think
What if I
try that from here
leave it with one HP finish her with
some idiot who can't do much damage
anyway
[Music]
oh the skill
was that why
put it
um
damage boost for adjacent units earlier
uh why would I
adjacent right so
but I can't kill her anyway right
[Music]
what if I do one like one small hit
but I'm a Slayer what is armor slip
what does nothing do nothing
[Music]
why doesn't do anything anything
do nothing
I just want like two damage please
I had it right the first time huh
I will
what can corn do
we need to heal you knock up
back up like for real
for real for real
for real for real for real
oh
I could drop her below the 20 with Chloe
tell me what to do
only with Chloe
could do some fun stuff here with Rosado
at least
almost kill the top one
with the spare damn it's very good
no crit chance so
[Music]
foreign
finish of clothing all right what
can I please do some damage please
[Music]
change and then heal your knuckles
yeah so useless
[Music]
Longbow it is
yeah then I don't have to use
flowy for finishing him
[Music]
and
I mean Chloe's HP is also hella low
very concerning
they have put me in a spot
very uncomfortable one
but hey I can give her a big heal
cheers
should I do the tarantula Roar maybe I'm
not here
but
either to the left or from here up
it only floods that two spots in a
straight line right
bottom up
oh wait three lines
maybe we should go step back then
oh I can only do it if I hit directly oh
this flat is straight but the draconic
aura splashes okay let's see let's see
that's awesome decent damage
anyway
oh what does that Dreadful overdue
[Music]
all the time
what did I do
Nerfs are status let's move on to zero
they can't move
okay go
these two oh no all of these four
can't move
[Music]
he does have
uh this does mavia mobile can still move
or does he have a long range weapon he
does have a
huh
well I wanted Jason yeah I want to kill
the one here
but
it's difficult
he has two range because of magic
um
[Music]
Celine
wait
wait I don't know
[Music]
I can't wait for the dancer hi
Tamara by the way
[Music]
oh should have drank in the bowlery
too
ah
at least koala is here now
um
[Music]
and I trade Celine something useful
like a Ponder
but would the Thunder even kill
[Music]
worst case panette does
but one unit for healing the rest of the
Army is good yeah
just use the turn to heal okay
I'll bring her here
oh she has no salt healing items
I have to give it to her
I did monena
[Music]
switch out with
maybe the iron sword
I don't think I've been using that much
what
I mean at the boxing heels too but
[Music]
wait what do we have we have
let's just do again right seven
oh I wish I had something better than
the Wolverine
it does heal
[Music]
I will switch out the iron sword for now
four to five
wait would fortify
heal herself oh wow
that's Hortensia the fourth of five
stuff
uh well maybe next time
well I can still do something from here
oh the alien Hill
too precious it doesn't particulate
anything right now well I guess it is
really precious
oopsie
oh wait I can
kill this guy
and for the next turn they can't move
right oh wait I can't kill him
unless I can
I will never fail yours
[Music]
yes
who's left just my dancer who cannot
dance What You Can Dance for tomorrow
oh nice
of course
nice
okay cool we got through that somehow
oh
Wow Let's Have Some Fun wow wow wow
Chris
I'm sorry you had to see that
nice
so lucky
whatever he's so far behind at this
point
they're my favorite sacrifices have to
be made
two
sneaky little shits
he sounds plenty what
sheesh
she mad
I'm still feeling kind of half dead once
we're done with these three I will heal
everybody before we go up there
um and also probably
around here have to like Focus On
Healing again I don't know
no no time Crystal don't care
[Music]
no time for the QuickTime question yeah
I have no choice but to win
foreign
if I can I shall
so I'm assuming that I'm killing this
dude in this turn so I think I want to
focus on healing connect
Bang
on mobile would have been better oh
I wonder how much damage that would have
done
let me let me just check
okay well low battery
well it's been five and a half hours so
they will survive a little bit longer
right and that's six hours I said I'm
gonna probably
stop anyway and then read to the Jets by
then we this fight should be hopefully
over
and I don't think I charged them
properly
cannot make up my mind
whatever you like
[Music]
Steph use time for dancing instead
but somebody just said now I have no way
that's idle guard okay wait final up
stands
who's who's the dancer
ah this one
okay
[Music]
um
still in it
oh that's also why I want damage
um
help me guys help me make a decision
[Music]
where
has the stream been just been this one
map no we did one before
maybe we even get a crit
iCal politics
oh she helps and she doesn't really know
[Music]
[Laughter]
even hypocrite I did not expect to kill
I am such a lucky
what
on Earth
well
so
I cleaned up oh now I will heal without
getting into the range of that monster
up there
um
wow
yeah the stupid ass Arctic out
so annoying
[Music]
foreign
yeah right I had this reaction before
wait how much possibility 70 that's
pretty high
that's pretty high
oh thank you
I'm just zooming away
um
[Music]
well koala won't get that much damage
from the bow so I'll just leave her here
all right
I would like
not the 45 but
that's a treat
covers an allies HP 20 usages but how
much
is it better than
it can't be better than men
I'll give
potencia and Men
[Music]
tween heel and Men
hmm
but 20 usage
oh wow wow we'll take up the Archer
maybe next turn
wait besides that
um I'm gonna do one more
yeah
wait
more importantly
okay
give me an order
you may as well
use your Alexa
wait did you just heal 5 HP from there
from the quality time
sweet
okay
I think we're good
[Music]
leading up and the would be good
the monster attacks suffer with Terrain
I don't know if I'll do that I don't
know if I can even reach
whatever you need
who was the one
this one I need to reach with irika but
we're so far
this shitty problem again
what do I do about that
what did I do last time
[Music]
no Chris
let the monster come
but bathe with whom
was it hotensia who had a good
resistance
[Music]
I think so
oh or just okay you're gonna call it
dragons
[Music]
here should be good
my MC's and I need them some sad food
okay I will I will give her all the
items I have
[Music]
simple enough
oh yes all of it I will buff her with
everything I can offer a nice level of
holy
oh
can I
hmm I'll move I'll move them a little
bit over there
the only one who's who has to charge
right now is Chihuahua and Tamara right
mirror is in range
yes
okay looks good looks good to me
go
I put rosado in range
um oops
yeah
oh they're coming they're coming oh
they're not yo they're not giving me a
break but at least they're saving me
some
walking
I appreciate that
my computer will handle it better and
you could not deliver it fully anyway
wait I'm at 720P 60fps
I'm streaming in 60 FPS
[Music]
oh wait wait well now I'm because
I haven't charged you in a call
[Music]
oh I am
um
let me see
she would survive
I'll survive I could change Rebecca
[Music]
Annette
voice connect
[Music]
is she dead
huh
well that's been that I didn't recognize
her
[Music]
horses
one one combat not one hit two hits one
combat
amazing
although I am worried about the damage
she will be taking from all of these if
they all end up going for her so I'm I
should send some help
here this is my specialty elfaya
bad morning
Unforgivable
maybe can take down one more no I don't
think so
too far oh
yeah almost
four percent crit chance
possible
wait did I
yeah
and there's no more dancing unless I
choose the the pilot engage me
[Music]
oh but it's AOE dancing right
no I will I will keep the AOE dance for
up here unless I mean there's plenty of
charging too and they're coming down to
me
who's got pilot did I just did I just
use yeah I did
yeah maybe next turn
[Music]
oh Lambo
oh baby
oh sweet apologize later
just realized
when looking at my options I have so
many options
oh this is going smoothly again
beginning with rap cute again until the
middle of the fight
now it's going smoothly
let's see what happens when the last
bosses come over to me no magic level up
come on
oh that's not bad either
how much do I get back twelve
silver sword very very powerful
hmm
no I'll do that
[Music]
it's going nice
what am I sweeping this whole round in
one turn
yes I am
back in the game
you have only suffered one casualty
nice
all right
next line is uh I don't think they'll
even reach me right so
they won't even reach me
charge her ah she is stretching
she can't reach but I'll bring her down
here
um way beside was
actually better
[Music]
okay oh
still a party going on here but no uh
now it's the left one was it the the
right one before
I think so
he Wawa getting those low Bob kills
had to stop you now they're dead the
Archer and Archer's best friend
[Music]
they're on their way
on her way they
so German and why so dreaming
oh panette also needs to charge I will
not lose
[Music]
it's subject meal
okay so we're dealing with two free
why is she waiting there
what does she have to hide
why is she doing that
should I go in already
[Music]
is this Reckless
I don't know
guess we'll find out
still have time returns anyway
honestly go back no
seems quite Reckless
yeah Middle Earth
[Music]
I know only forward exactly until
everyone dies and then I heard food or
rewind
ing by doing
I don't even care if gold Mary dies
I know this is really Reckless I don't
know how
how bulky gold Mary is she's simply
bulky she was taking quite a lot of hits
before wasn't she
was taking some decent hits
let's see let's see
it's too good
no damage from that either so
nothing else okay
yeah good defense
she even gotta level up from that
hmm
red
charging
what could I do
good morning
[Music]
should I go for the bus or for his
friend like I'll go for his friends
[Music]
scared of the friends but I'll go for
the friend
go for boss I have died oh
[Music]
no I want the kill
first
does it have to be the first hit to get
the dialogue
[Music]
for Lucia
no
okay then we have time
quadruple hit damage 22.
sounds fine
I'll Stand the behind feeling
I'm feeling very comfortable right now
I can't see I will have dialogue too
[Music]
okay
staying behind with him too
okay okay okay I'm ready bring it on oh
he goes for Rosado
I remember
look on your face
hatred
oh
[Music]
is dead
oh
nice
he attacked that really nicely yeah oh
oh okay
new toy I'm going to enjoy this fail
versus gold Mary your old friend Mars
to try
but she's a happy yeah
okay okay okay
nice tank
gold Mary's like who's Mark who's like
me for real oh another one
laughs
good job
[Music]
oh she heals
okay
that's it right
[Music]
of course
unfortunately I I can't help here
I'll think about it later
to watch for me
and play high difficulty in my store in
chapter 14. oh
you don't want to be spoiled
I understand you have to play more go go
go go you have to catch up come on
playing in hard difficulty
thanks for the pink Super Chat though
thank you
oh catch up with me come on
come on come on
I will heal Rosado right here
rails shouldn't have even engaged
foolish
it's almost as poor it's like basically
four
um
[Music]
unforgivable first get rid of everything
I can with one hit
I wonder what's effective
she's a sword type
so Lance
let me see let me test to God
yeah not in particular
What if I
packager emblem
what happens if I kill Veil before
everybody before the other bosses it
doesn't end yet
well that's good that's good
that's good I break her too
oh wait he's here I forgot about him
um
[Music]
who who's called my life you got Violet
I mean I might want to attempts here to
dance
for kiwawa
[Music]
I really want to finish the stupid map
now
oh
ah come on
no way
it hurts I know I know
hold on a little longer yo
[Music]
one HP bar down
did she miss
[Music]
Ed called Mary
I even chose a weapon that would have
higher a percentage
I thought it was pretty decent
so that's a Tuffy tough cookie longbow
is it smart to focus everything on
available right now I know much more
skilled
but that worked
here okay let's make it
hero King
imposed by father
emblem Bell dragons are far
the emblem is going wild
this is just like what happened at Seoul
Palace oh this pose is a real challenge
[Music]
um
now let's
I don't think I can like
take the second HP bar down within this
turn
so
[Music]
foreign
I don't have like free people I could
dance for
possibly four if I also move Chloe here
does that sound good and I put a violet
in the middle Hortensia by love in the
middle
[Music]
and four people I would dance for
me you ready for daylight
so
every time
[Music]
tomorrow or today tomorrow
Saturday March 12th 2023 will end Yeah
March 12th
tomorrow
whoa whoa whoa whoa okay
already
but it doesn't uh yeah in Japan it
doesn't apply to me in Europe it does
tomorrow
laughs
[Music]
oh so my time difference to Japan will
be
another hour uh
less once again
which you know sometimes it's good
sometimes it's bad
[Music]
I can literally do no damage to him here
like it's like so useless
I'm only taking damage it's not even
worth dancing for Chloe yeah
I'd rather go up here
she can do this much here
he could do a lot of damage if he's just
in front of her can he do damage there
no
well
once I danced for Chloe
who's calling for heels yeah
but in order to do a meaningful healing
I have to go up here
actually that makes a lot of sense thank
you
because she would have probably died
next turn
oh
yeah that's fine too
I just moved to the spot where I wanted
to go
one down I guess did I
I want to do something
new cuteness come
do something meaningful come on
still great ax does decent damage
I take 10. and I only have 60 67 hit
chance what do you think
no
[Music]
crit 36 on his side damn
go for it I have been lucky so far but I
feel like this will backfire
oh oh
[Music]
I'll take it
after a dance style I heal Rosado
oh he moved him away
I know it wasn't so good but
yeah I will
I will I just hope it makes it until the
end of this fight
uh okay so we have dance
another heel
this is a long turn
all these turns are so long
[Music]
what can we do
oh wait
maybe I can take bill down
oh wait 24 percent
no that's nothing that's not gonna
happen I could break her at least though
[Music]
all right well this hits I didn't look
at the percentage 38 annoying no wait
please
[Music]
don't wanna
foreign
[Music]
what about here
I'll go up because I can break her
[Music]
back
yeah Veil is a bit squishy uh it feels
like she's easier to take down so
um this is the way
[Music]
48.
I don't think there's really a better
option right now though
come on
right my turn okay okay okay
Wawa
what are we gonna do with you
uh
maybe he can focus on her
she'll survive right
I'm here too guys
ah she'll be fine I know what I need to
charge her but everything's so far
hey what's gonna happen who's gonna die
I'm okay with one person dying maybe
maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe I'll think
about it depends on who
the mayor will not die
oh oh
oh
bye-bye never hit him she might be down
unless someone misses
rattle rattle ride
two hits
[Music]
oh oh miss me
I let my guard down
do we accept this
I feel like I can make it without her
Chihuahua just arrived to
um healing the bus is kind of oh no no
oh dear
two
two much use in the state two less rap
oh yeah wait there's one more
um
[Music]
don't have much time though it's almost
over
yeah
um Vale is pretty much done
I don't know can we make it we have one
two three four five six seven
eight nine ten
nine money no
I have plenty of charges but
yeah I'll see how this turn goes we can
still rewind after
it's very time consuming
[Music]
should I take down that horse team no I
need to focus on bail first
[Music]
which one is harder to take down the
soldier right but I do want the Healer
that too
that can damn well do it thanks
feel the soldier
Halo soldier healer Soldier healer
Soldier
[Music]
Rancho Aurora
yeah might be a good idea too
flip a coin healer
dealer it is had no choice but to win it
is annoying
can I do a tarantula of War like all
these free ones who did that again who's
whose thing is that
the unicorns ah you can't reach
that thing
yeah that's that's hers I could uh not
dance for her
in any case
she is not charged
oh
the one over here no
is it worth going to church with kiwawa
now
[Music]
to charge my Pro Controller in case the
other one
[Music]
foreign
controller to my phone charger I don't
know if it will work
when they charge the Pro Controller does
it uh give like a light off
because it didn't
[Music]
hit Hyatt simp you'll get a charge from
it what
you mean charge
oh for my for my
engagement
[Music]
why are they both just zeroing each
other
[Music]
89 89 November well have fun and good
luck are you coming to Japan
thank you Al
so most intense battle do I really even
if I do zero do I still get like a
charge
show damage no damage Miss no damage
oh she's ready
no charge was necessary
I mean no
no manual
charge
we're going to be flashing orange like
okay I don't think it did I don't think
it's charging
I gotta do this
no one really needs healing right now so
I will go full in with Celine
[Music]
all flowers eventually wrote
oh
dangerous position
dangerous position is it not
uh
what you gonna do
oh wait fog
everything here in the end okay okay
okay
[Music]
foreign
but who can do something meaningful
and I like
shoot her in her back
no no no no damage
should I call doubles
elsewhere does do some damage though
I'll call doubles but not here
um
if my double stands in the fire it can't
kill it right just expired Never Kills
[Music]
that would probably be clutch yeah hell
yeah what big brain why did we not think
of this earlier
so now I made up for my free lost units
with four doubles
[Music]
ho
I want to attack
maybe that's the best I can do
24 24.
what
[Music]
that was all my friends good idea
yeah okay
[Music]
yeah there's so many boss units here
I know founder can snipe but generally
yeah no damage
this
is
gonna work out
apologies
okay
we only have two bosses left uh no free
oh
what do I do
oh wait that's that's not that's pretty
good that's pretty good
I don't know 82
I think I'll risk it
[Music]
double should buy us some time you know
wait he yeah he got 46 crap
crap risk it for the biscuit let's
imprint again
no I don't want to watch him quit again
who did you guys use to deal with this
bastard huh
[Music]
I need help
what does corin do
and the floating
but now not now
[Music]
not now
diamond
give someone a help for our next turn
[Music]
can do
should I Dragon vein or should I attack
him for some poison
oh an easy mode they don't
poison
[Music]
this one he only has 40 hit chance on
this one
nice
guy he's poisoned
[Music]
something significant you can do
snow
maybe this
Savvy is going to sweep for the doubles
um
scared you think you can defeat me in my
Knights then by all means try
what if I don't make it I committed to
not rewinding now until but
is that
oh wait
oh that's what she did
okay okay but big brain doubles were big
brain big big brain oh it's so big brain
okay they're gone they're gone now
oh
foreign
[Music]
has to go somewhere else I don't know
how much damage Pinette would even do
but
um
what are we gonna do what are we gonna
do what are you gonna do what are we
gonna do help me help me this is so
tough
focus on Veil
okay yeah she's almost dead we need to
get her down
and then him
um
I'm sweating
thanks for the info
it's like me for real for real
the pilot one
[Music]
maybe maybe we can go first we're gonna
go to poisoned
or we only when I might want to save you
no go this time for fogging
Aaliyah first
uh on who
[Music]
and we want to give someone an HP Bardo
but she does a lot of damage this is it
this should be a like
a combination and we don't get damage
back
84.
better go for the 89 Maybe
Chris okay
hey Kitty
did I only hit once
bad
I will endure
[Music]
let's get special
whatever it wasn't on purpose
[Music]
let's get
oh my voice
19.
97 this one this one
ow
still not so bad
oh
I know I need to focus on veils but I
feel like I can get his HP bar down
oh
[Music]
yeah I can
um
I just did that because I couldn't do
any significant damage to Veil
[Music]
you'll see what I'm made of
no oh
what is this again
oh
not word for turn the last thing
it's allowances
is more dangerous
[Music]
yeah well
okay let me try
better than nothing question mark
it would be nice if I could attack first
of your knuckle but now it's not
possible
[Music]
what's up
oh yeah maybe
[Music]
from here she can't fight back right
from here I think she can
oh no
no no no she only has red beer
75.85
[Music]
I'm just going for high percentage on
hit right now because I'm scared to miss
foreign
[Music]
guys this is really
just have to test out all my options
this is just pretty decent
48.
at least you can't fight back and if it
hits then
it's great
[Music]
should I go back
change the odds
did I change the arms
I have
five more charges
with gold Marinette starts to set up an
80 chance to hit for free damage pull my
next to
cool
next there
63.
this is the best I can do
they're an attack range day combo
okay
there was a break ah
a 40 free it's not gonna happen
it's not gonna happen
hello
[Music]
foreign
so now to do gold Mary first
[Music]
it only does nine damage
I'll break her with really high
possibility
well you say next to bail right not here
right
or
should I just put her here this one
actually I don't know
[Music]
next to Baylor
as long as she's in the range okay
came um probably missed
[Music]
allow me
down to three it's me
[Music]
okay free HP come on
you can take her down too yes 48
what is that all my choices
she looks like a double but I still have
her
as a backup
maybe do her first thing she can still
call doubles
she has a
higher chance of doing it
chain attack is 80. yeah I guess that's
enough okay okay
okay
uh I don't really want to stand in the
fire
can go here
right
it's not possible
how could this happen
I promise you will not survive our next
encounter
ah
two more two more two more
and this one only has one HP bar left
let's focus on the old guy bears
[Music]
um oh yeah I can do a lot of damage
and I only get three back yo yo yo yo I
don't really depleted the the left one
I've not seen you since we were at the
Brody and border
in this life
it need not be I can appeal to Lord
Sombra ask him to welcome you back as
our Ally now
your
not you
I will not cling tearfully to my
father's Shadow but I am grateful for
this
grateful for the chance to thank you
say goodbye
and tell you that as Illusions Queen my
real surprise
I will either you're strong you're done
so much stronger than him
show it to him
ouch
good job though
um so my left controller doesn't work
anymore
[Laughter]
I mean what can I do I can only like try
to charge a bit
go into handheld mode if I go into
handheld mode I can't like stream it to
you guys
no I don't have any extra joycons no no
my Pro con didn't charge let me check
oh my baby inside
oh for sure
brought the cable I might just uh
hello
it's showing me some lights on the
bottom of the controller though
what
okay well if I connect it to the switch
hello we're saved
why is it showing full battery why
wasn't it not reacting when I was trying
to pair it
oh well okay nice broken safe
I was smart enough to bring not only my
joy-cons but my Pro Controller
more luggage but
came in handy
for Amazon's collab and now
what do we do with engaging in should I
do this should I
thank you
it's just weigh my options
I feel like maybe we should keep the
torrential Roar for
um if anything the other chick oh wait
would she not be affected because she's
flying
[Music]
freeze the other bus and
what
I'm not from here I could Praise Him
but that actually won't be that helpful
because
you can just attack from where he is
[Music]
she's my last unit this turn right so
uh
engage but just use an attack don't
engage
um
but when I when I'm engaged I take a
little bit less damage don't I
think
[Music]
oh no it's the same
I guess it depends on the unit
[Music]
stiletto
sound is like chopping off again
oh wait it doesn't matter even if even
with 11 crit chance I'm only doing one
damage so that won't get much higher
I prefer
um
[Music]
well go for this one because there he
only has 70 percent
Hansen will kill ivy if I may I would be
a very dramatic
outcome
my sound is dying
what's pause again
oh
wait he's going for a tennis he's going
for Pinette he broke her but she's good
[Music]
oh
she ah she was she's riding again
he's just zooming for the field
can I just restart my capture
utility real quick
it is annoying
one two three
[Music]
how much damage
checking
oh
[Music]
I wanna risk it
but okay first
I can still do this can you
okay
[Music]
father I've missed you I wanted to see
you so badly oh man I've been so sad
since you died then dear daughter follow
me kill your friends you sound so
reasonable
no
no you won't
I want to live up to my father the wise
king of illusia My real father before
the Feld Dragon ruined him
goodbye father
I'm sad we didn't have more time
together
I love you soon this will all be over
okay
soon you'll be able to rest
no I don't
do it
you freedom from suffering so proud
dragon's throne
Ivy wow
I'm sorry
no
but I love you both no it's forced to
leave
lead to yours
[Music]
don't worry
they will be the perfect leaders
L you're still here and it's spoilering
you
I thought you didn't want the spoilers
ow
lashing fist art
usually don't use this kind of weapon so
all right we have enough units I think
to take on
the last one and I did like
and how much damage that did so
74. I'll try
[Music]
yeah yes
yes yes
I'll just throw everything at her that I
have
oh it's a hardship
s
thank God I'm so relieved oh it is still
her second uh her first I guess HP bar
but I'm still relieved
I'm very relieved
be free yeah
I will never fail
a lot it was looking tough
a lot of times
why
[Music]
why oh
look upon the might of Lord sombron I
see no might left
all the mighty ones
have been defeated
you can't do anything with him
retribution is due
um
[Music]
I wonder if she would come for pregnant
should I I mean why not prepare my great
Avery just in case
[Music]
don't fear for me
set out some bait should wait do they
what was it do they if they see someone
who has less HP would they prefer to go
to them
should I not heal her maybe
[Music]
it's Canter well well she doesn't know
what's coming don't you they tired
weaker okay
here there's many weak units here for
you
like a dragon vein too
would it make that less likely for her
to go here
no but then I might also
use it
line up for her oh yeah yeah
come here you want to use this
um although if I go here she might end
up out of the territory of the cancer of
the override
whatever you do you want
[Music]
okay I'll just wait
I hear you
[Music]
um no I ain't wearing hmm
I will call doubles
here
you might go to the very left one oh no
she will overwrite
that's where she goes
laughs
she's having fun
she's having so much fun
[Music]
who are you fighting
huh
I killed my doubles
oh
my doubles
um
can't reach
the sake
[Music]
what was that camera angle
I love you
she's such cheeky
sleeping
man let me finish you
Queens
can't reach
that's what you get
that's what you get from for going up so
far
I'm gonna try anyway
oh dear I'm not gonna try
I don't know
[Music]
yeah I override one miss and I just
lined up for her
not if I make it into a four people line
because she can't override then
foreign
if I make a four people line she can't
override
okay oh great help oh
[Music]
to me
well then I'll make the no
[Music]
oh
let's make it fun
[Music]
can I even do
on the line
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait I can still leave the line
oh
[Music]
am I so far because maybe I want to
charge her
and she's gonna go to the left side
probably again anyway
[Music]
don't line up
where are we headed
back
[Music]
I want the judge no no he doesn't need
to charge I don't give a I don't
give a where you are it was a break
yeah but probably really no problem
Victoria
hi Dad
did she just kill someone
was that my last double no wait was
there someone there no she didn't kill
anyone
[Music]
a little bit angry
I'm a little bit annoying
just a little bit
a little bit angry
thank you
ah
[Music]
good
I can't unless I go directly at her and
I can't reach
I can't read
it still freezes her
ah whatever
[Music]
so let's go Church
no
I don't know
[Music]
soon
how many times can she do that
anyway why can't she do it all the time
[Music]
I'm just gonna they're gonna just chill
they're like this I'm so mad
it looks here not even worth it
huh
yeah but mending is only
so big
there's a special scale
I forgoto you going for them
no way
I thought it would just go straight down
you little
oh no you didn't and now she's standing
in my okay it's okay it's gone
she had to take down number one with her
I can't believe it
yes you are
quite strong
so mad I'm so mad
like this and yet I did not win
who's had a lot of ups and downs
man
18 10.
[Music]
that was
quite something
[Music]
um
I thought it would have been gold Mary
yeah she did pretty well too
ah sorry it took so long but this is a
long chapter
thanks guys
wow
damn
this must have been one of the most
difficult ones
in the whole game at least it felt
really tough
damn the ring we gave Hyacinth they
snatched it we gotta protect the other
ones let's get them onto the ship
I will take the Ring of the hero King
come my lady we must hurry oh
which mode is she something the matter
safia give me a ring oh she's faking
what are you playing she's faking it
just do it she's making it that's why
you're not showing us her eyes
and they have only one left
please take take this
laughs
why why I know you can't forgive me why
don't you do the things I've done join
us
you must know
I need you to know that
even though our friendship was brief
it meant every everything cheesy and
easiest book
cute though
[Music]
hmm
what the hell you filthy defect
[Music]
s
Phil
when we return I'll see that you never
wake up again come here keep an eye on
those other rings
understood wouldn't you just throw them
all over
the Ring of the Holy Night
so is that cigarette do we get cigarette
back finally and from stickers
I'm glad you two are back as am I
allow me to apologize for failing to
protect you at the Cathedral all this
time within my dimmed consciousness
I feared you and I would never again
meet
I'm Secret
that was my fault not
as you saw
they have been twisting vale's mind and
using her as a pawn with some bronze
movement Limited it is she who carries
out his will I see
should we try to rescue her
first we have to help people of Flora
we can go to illusia after we've put out
the remaining fires and rescued the
survivors with this fight we have eight
rings we're at an advantage to take the
other four yes Victory is in sight
Alfred why don't you go to the castle
tell Queen have what has happened here
yeah leave the bill
thanks everyone
I appreciate it
finally
[Music]
yeah yeah
um
I found out about the fact that you
should give everybody counter
even after we were snatched the ring or
very close to it so I didn't have time
to give everybody counter but now this
will be my mission I think when I
privately do
like one or two parallels I think I'll
do at least two
um I'll try to
give some peeps Canter some
important ones as many as I can
yeah
and you are
that was fun
actually I think we can continue next
week like one stream I should be able to
squeeze in but you know what's next week
I'm so excited
one is today Saturday it's Saturday
right oh in one week I'll be on stage
on a big big stage
seriously it was last time actually
same venue
one of my favorite venues in Japan
um
so
hope you guys are getting excited for
that
it will be so worth it
I'm telling you if you are kfp
I'm telling you streaming tickets for
day one worth it worth it
so worth it
oh let's do a Listen by the way to the
preview uh when is it when is the CD
coming out I don't know but um
preview is at least already out from
mine and mermaids go through cover yes
I am am I ever glad digital tickets
don't sell out yeah thank God
oh you ordered the city thank you
um
what was he stripping is weird I I heard
about this thing I saw you guys on
Twitter some of you complaining about
something weird happening when you put
certain items but not always the same
ones right but like I'm his hat and then
it gets super expensive the shipping
now I don't know like if this like what
you have to do to make this happen but
it seems to be a bug
I did ask the management about it
I asked him can you please fix this
is it specifically with ama's hat
or
is it is it just like kind of random
because I heard someone had the bug
where it added huge like unreasonable
shipping to it and they would just like
refresh several times and then
eventually it fixed itself so just in
case someone is still having problems
with that don't give up immediately it's
not no I don't think it's normal to have
a shipping charge of 150 USD
for like two or three items that should
not happen no matter where you live I
think
yeah yeah yeah this is like kind of
weird thing going on I'm sorry about
that
um
yeah I hope no one did that
like no one accepted it just like that
please do not accept it
that makes sense you know
so it's uh
5 p.m now
[Music]
I have to prepare the other stream
I have to take a little break and I have
to go dinner
[Music]
to go buy an Apple too
I don't know it's a woman and I won't
Bollywood
hmm
[Music]
maybe no superchato
okay while we're falling behind
oh I can make plenty of time for Super
Chat readings in Austria
[Music]
oh tomorrow by the way collab with toy
senpai
I I
um gave her like three ideas we haven't
decided yet
one of them is kind of canceled because
we didn't get perms in time for like
this game
or something like that
[Music]
what would you guys prefer either
okay with jatsu
possibly archived yeah probably archived
or
the idea if somebody gave me this idea
of playing Apex with one hand each but
like I've never even played Apex before
and I I don't think this is a good idea
okay okay okay okay
yeah okay that's okay okay okay okay
we'll go
and where we go that she'll be
disappointed in my hands now
because ever since I last met her my
hands have been like I don't know
looking really weird my fingertips have
been looking weird like I've been like
losing skin on them I think I I don't
know I need to go to skin doctor
dermatologist or stuff
what if she doesn't like my hands
anymore she used to be so fascinated
inside my hands
not anymore
I mean I think they still feel the same
isn't it funny we're both Divine dragons
but your hair is different colors I love
it why thank you Tiki your hair is very
pretty too the green gives you a rather
mystical air
cute
yeah I just won't show her my fingertips
in close up
they still feel the same
also I'm not sure yet if I'm going to
her place or she's coming to my place
because both Works she said
hmm
I'll message her tonight
I think I'll go to her
I'm on my channel and at least here I
have OBS completely set up
she has a cat all right I'm going to her
place
say no more
no more say no more
also I really like seeing whole life
members
um homes
it's interesting to see like what they
decorate their home with
kind of furniture they have says
something about their personality
oh I wonder if she would give me a shirt
I'm wearing this shirt that somebody
said they gave me right now
uh my collection of shirts
[Music]
let me write to her now otherwise I
forget those spaghetto
foreign
uh
[Music]
foreign
yeah
oh okay
[Music]
hmm
okay Mama
[Music]
this
is
mama okay
mama
okay okay I told her I want to meet your
cat
please let me in and we're going to do
[Music]
um
okay don't turn it into the whole talk
no no I won't because there will be a
prep a whole talk eventually
honest about my intentions
no it's not I'm not going there just
because of the cat but I found I think
you know generally also
it's comfortable to have off collapse in
other members places because they
usually have like their things set up
properly for off collabs
[Music]
I wonder if she has a soundproof room
like many others do
but also there's a cat exactly
I forgot what kind of cat does she have
she's posted it before right
look at the cat does she have
yes no I think I saw her before maybe
[Music]
are they short hair are they short hair
munchkin
oh my God
happy munchkin
don't forget the Apple okay Apple I'm
gonna buy Apple then uh no first I make
um thumbnail put up the stream for Cuba
and
then I go by Apple then I go dinner then
yeah okay
okay
safe
it's safe I think I did though but I'll
see it again
at least I already met towards Empire
before for that dinner and when we got
along really well I remember
just about me being so energetic
she was cracking up about how
enthusiastic and passionate I was about
the topics
so yeah she might be laughing a lot at
me tomorrow too
yay
[Music]
let's post cute emojis I generally I
have to force myself to use emojis and
discards
I don't know
I feel like if I don't add emojis it
just it's boring to read it doesn't
motivate you to read
you need to use more emojis
[Music]
because I'm too lazy to use them
the only ones I use all the time is them
are like a couple of Amit ones
the ones with the big eyes and the one
where she's on the floor
and the one sometimes the one where
she's laughing and another one I use a
lot is the the praying one to say thank
you
or please
and the Chihuahua clap one
um
I have a Chihuahua clapping one an
animated one
also when I'm excited I use the the Army
bounce animated one
[Music]
I wish I could have the Chihuahua
clapping one animated on here I wonder
YouTube has been trying to do some
things like twitch like the
um raiding viewers so maybe eventually
they'll add animated
emojis right
I feel like they will
ah they've also been doing like Clips so
like clipping directly
from the VOD
[Music]
so
we'll see you in two years for that now
I feel like they'll do it earlier
one year
I'll give them one year
oh yeah I guess yeah animated super
stickers
[Music]
yeah their chat system their chat is
already so heavy so without hyper chat
the chat just breaks so much
but I wonder if animated emojis will
make it worse
people really need hyper chat then
one thing
before I leave you guys
um before I leave you guys before before
before I leave you guys before I leave
you guys uh before I leave you guys
where is the information that I need
um
[Music]
maybe here
where the hell did they put that info
here okay
I would like
to do some shout outs
[Music]
um not Super Chat reading
I want to give a shout out
[Music]
oh
two gigabyte
which is a company one of the companies
that have been
um you know providing some streaming
stuff for us
and they provided gaming laptop and a
gaming display
gaming display especially
has been really helpful
I did bring an extra
um like portable monitor from home just
in case but I haven't even been using it
because this one's so big and so nice
it's kind of curved even it's my first
time I'm using a curved monitor and I
have not every uh had found any problems
with it
and this way
I can stream properly because streaming
when everyone's traveling when I was
traveling
and I only had one monitor AKA in my
laptop then it was kind of tough because
you know we have many things to look at
like OBS in the chat and and and Discord
maybe on the side and the stream
everything the game everything so yeah
second lab second monitor definitely
necessary
so thank you gigabyte was very very
helpful and convenient thank you
gigabyte the gaming display by the way
was
G27 QC if you're curious and the gaming
laptop was an IA row five I will be
making some tweets about this too
um
[Music]
so besides that I'll also give more
shout outs I've been also using a
keyboard mouse and headset from
thermaltake have you guys heard of
thermal tank
they have a like a line that's called
Argent
so I have the Argent k6 keyboard which
was quite nice it has like RGB lights
actually all of this stuff has RGB
lights now
and Argent at uh M5 Mouse origin H5
headset the headset I really like the
headset
this stream is not sponsored no but I I
you know I gotta give a shout out
somewhere so this is it this is where I
do my shout outs the headset is really
comfortable like I kind of want it maybe
hmm it's like pretty big
I might like it more than my own I'm not
sure though
interested in buying it kind of y'all
it's really nice
comfortable soft not too heavy
covers my ears completely kind of square
I'm gonna take those back home no I
can't
you need a new one anyways oh yeah maybe
think about this one I think really good
is it pink though it's not pink bug
oh wait no this one doesn't have this
this is map RGB but The Mouse and the
the the keyboard has RGB lights maybe
they have some headphones with rgb2 I
don't know
that was from thermal take and also from
seki kagu I've been using their gaming
chair and the gaming desk
and I'm really especially in life the
gaming chat
I've given up on gaming chairs rides at
home I ditched my own four different
ones but this chair is so comfortable
and big and we used it for the watch
along when I was like you know cleaning
back during the one too long comfortably
when we were watching Lord of the Rings
chef's kiss I was sick and I wanted to
watch a movie with you guys and the
chair yo I'm so good at promoting this
stuff and the chair was just my
Lifesaver
to watch a movie comfortably with you
guys for four over four hours per day
[Laughter]
yeah it was so comfortable I wanted to
fall asleep in it hmm
yeah that was uh seki cargo it's in
Japanese
I'll I'll put I'll um put out tweets as
well but I will just I guess put this in
the chat in case you want to look it up
the gaming desk is called Legion
legionesku and the gaming chair is
called Shastina version two
Justina
Justina version 2 V2
uh
is
Legion
what else what else oh and every media
so from every media we were provided an
audio mixer
[Music]
and a microphone
and a capture board
provided yes
uh thank you very much
thank you thank you thank you
we were set up perfectly for everything
in case we didn't want to bring our own
microphone or our own mixer and our own
capture board Etc
yeah
that's it so basically no need to bring
anything in theory unless we wanted
something specific from our usual setup
um
big big big dunction
in
yay
hopefully
uh maybe in the future
if counsel ever comes to Japan
they can use this stuff too maybe it was
really helpful
hmm
mission
okay
good
I'll tell
management I did that
leave a little note on it forever who
for whoever loses it next
you're so good at being nonchalant
that what is that bad what's that mean
clean
oh yeah leaned on you guys with my chair
Helena chat with the chair
um I'm a natural oh yes I am
no but I really appreciate it I mean
I'll be honest I didn't use everything
that was provided but I was using uh
a lot of it um
so big big tank
and so with that
I will leave you guys for now I'll see
you guys later
the day is not over so go rest
and I'll see you later and join me say
I'll be dancing thank you
more Fire Emblem possibly next week
[Music]
foreign