Come on dude, please!
I will give you 10% of the profit!
The new “Special Usual Room” is definitely safe!
Uh...
Alright!
Tell me why I should hire you?
I am a big fan of you!
KIKIRIKE!
Eh...
NEXT!
OMG
Can’t even do a basic KIKKERIKI?
Young chickens these days...
HEY!
YOU!
Why should we hire you?
KIKIRIKII!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
Trying to make fun of me with the Australia meme now?!
This is serious!
NEXT!
What can you do?
KI KI RI KIII!!!
Ohhhhhh!
Nice!
That was divine
Exquisite!
So you say you know many languages?
That’s great!
どこ出身なの？
好きなご飯は？
Wie alt bist du?
Was ist dein Lieblingsfilm?
Ki-
What a disappointment...
NEXT!
YOU!
What can you do?
Ohhhhh!
DAMN!!!
That’s pretty good!
Why do you want to work here?
I...
I just like here...
Hmm?
What’s wrong?
You seem like you're hesitating
Just tell the truth!
We will accept it
Don’t worry
Well...
Actually...
NINOMAE
INA'NIS!!!
UGH!
I knew it !!!
Unbelievable!
You just a spy from Takobell?
Oh... God dammit
Those Takodachis!
NEXT!
Huh?
NEXT !
Are you another useless chicken?
No...
I...
I'm a-
I'm a huge fan of you!
I'm very passionate!
I...
WAIT A MINUTE!
I worked in a fried chicken shop before!
Ohh?
I protested in front of other stores
While holding a standing sign of you!
Hoo!
Aww
Good chicken, alright
That sounds good to me
Congratulations!
You are hired!
We need more chickens like you!
#WOKE #YOLK
You know
YEA!!!
As a KFP employee...
its all about being
Brave!
The act of you holding the sign of me in front of the rivals?
Excellent!
Alright!
So
Can you start right now?
YES SIR!
Here
Eh?
KFP Army!
Listen up!
Ready to attack the branch store of
*Censored*
IKUZOOOO!!!
YEAH!!!
Oi!
Put your backs into it!
And let the money roll in