foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
[Music]
why does Bijou have a way cooler logo on
her thumbnail
where did she get that from ours look
different
the house
hello I just saw her thumbnails got like
a skull with horns in it
[Music]
oh well skill issue true true very true
oh
what's this this doesn't look
good
what's going on
uh okay let's do
[Music]
how you doing
which one is it
we are starting uh uh like 10 minutes in
like first we decided to give us some
time to introduce our characters
um
what the [\h__\h]
uh I can't find the right there's just
two Callies
well okay
this is fine
oh it's a big one though I hear a
shh okay this is fine yeah uh because
then yeah we can show you what we
created Cali is probably still creating
but yeah
um hello
okay
uh yes
um
we're playing ball to skate and I
decided against the cleric but what did
kiwawa create uh well first of all let
me actually show you my guardian first
okay so
if you look at her she looks kind of old
but still like me right first I was
thinking of creating recreating someone
else but now I'm kind of recreating me
but this is uh basically the mommy
of
the character that I created
um I made her as old as possible but uh
it's not old enough in my opinion but
yeah
um
yeah because I I uh Bijou explained to
me that the Guardians like in the demo
maybe were like a like an evil thing but
now they're kind of kind of trying to
help you
um so I thought hmm what should I do
like what would be interesting and then
I decided how about I make like my mommy
like she's trying to help me uh as a
ghost or whatever I don't quite
understand but yeah
um and and and and the cool thing is
that I I decided is because my character
is a half elf so since she's the mommy
she's the full Elf yeah but more or less
Mama Tony I guess yeah
so yeah
um she's the full Elf I guess her dad
was a human yeah
looks like a lot real she's a Wood Elf
and yeah I don't know if you really care
about these things
um
I'm a bit confused because I turned
Unity off at the beginning of the stream
but I still
ended up seeing the genitals but I'm
hoping that you guys won't be able to
see it on stream let's be careful and
now here comes
Liara
with the hot ah Natalie Dormer in Hunger
Games hairstyle let's go first I was
trying to create
um Tiara from the ttrpg
um and I was doing white hair and
everything but then I I saw that all the
other like Bijou and Larissa were kind
of recreating themselves
so I thought okay
maybe I'll just recreate myself as well
then yeah
um but I did stay with the ranger
because I don't know um first I was
saying I'm gonna do cleric BBB but um no
I'm now doing something else because we
came to the conclusion that we're
playing on easy anyway so we don't
really need a uh uh
A Healer probably and then healing is
kind of lame apparently because you
can't do it like all the time blue blood
blue
but you guys tell me do I need to change
the thing here this is like default and
Bijou said it's okay if it's default
but I don't know should I change
something in the ability points
less strength more whiz less
intelligence I can't uh lower
intelligence anymore
ah yeah
can't lower it I think this is like
minimum
yeah I'm going Bo and oh yeah so let me
show you so we're half elf because Mommy
is full Elf I'm a wood half elf
I have movement speed increased by 1.5
I'm the Ranger and I got this true
strike fingering advantage on your next
attack roll I want to say one thing
ahead of time
um
um I I just want to clarify okay
especially in English when I read things
and especially even more so on stream
like there's times where it just doesn't
enter my brain I try to read it again
and again and again and it doesn't
register in my brain so I asked Bijou to
in such situations explain something to
me in words because
um it just won't register you know you
know how that feels sometimes right man
so I'm a bit nervous about that because
I already noticed there's like so much
to read uh yeah I went with the this was
kind of default I think I read all of
them but I thought magebreaker is just
better any like one of the good ones and
Bijou agreed that it might be good
um because when we battle spellcasters
I'll have the upper hand and then peace
favor
when I saw that I can tame animals in uh
in with Ranger I was really excited
because in World of Warcraft I used to
always think that
um what was that class called I don't
know but it would it would have been
cool to have animals and true strike not
good don't take truth eh
which one do I take then
it's not good should I take I was
thinking uh maybe this one instead
but
am I gonna even meet creatures from
other planes of existence that much
Bounty Hunter
yes okay okay then I'll do this one
a lot of people say Bounty Hunter though
um
okay I guess I guess so
uh
make sure last night
you came for an investigation creature
it
investigation
because Bijou and I were talking about
we might we might want to balance are
they unmuted yet almost we might want to
balance you know our
talents and all that
um
and I think she said something about
investigation let me unmute the center
unmute anyway
hello
it's balder's door let's go
oh wait foreign
I have to ask you things yeah actually
this is good maybe you know because when
we were creating characters yesterday
people said it might be good you know to
like balance out everything so that we
are have every like you know uh we cover
everything you know what I mean and then
they told me people they told me uh just
now that I shouldn't go with magebreaker
because true strike sucks
um well they said they kept saying that
to me too but then other people said
that true strike is fixed now and that
they fixed it they've fixed it
yeah what was wrong about true strike uh
I don't know I don't know too much about
I think he knows I think it's hard too
because it's just like everyone always
has their own play style and things that
they like and dislike
um
it's true strike sucks
okay then let me just ask you people one
thing did we say somebody is gonna have
investigation as their thing or uh let's
see if you guys look at your abilities
and look at your proficiencies what do
you have because we should cover our
bases yes
let's do that that's true all right uh
I'll go first I'll go first so I'm
playing a barbarian
um as like my class I'm a huge huge half
orc
um Outlander and my abilities I have
really high strength 17 strength uh
dexterity is pretty good 13.
Constitution is 14. uh stem and physical
endurance of course because I'm big and
girthy uh intelligence nine because I'm
just not very smart uh wisdom wisdom is
pretty good
um
it wouldn't let me put it into other
things so this is how it has to be uh
Charisma is uh is 10
um like it's fine how is [\h__\h] Shrek
smarter than my half elves
don't call her that her name is not
Shrek it's moriope get it straight first
of all
um but yeah I guess I can kind of tank
because I have high Constitution as well
um and then I have plus two bonus to
strength one plus one bonus to
Constitution uh my skills in particular
I've got plus five to Athletics such as
really good
um you know most standards I have a
negative one on Athletics Good Luck
running away
um and then animal handling plus three
oh what's three
um and then Insight plus one medicine
plus one perception plus with survival
plus three good Survivor I'm pretty
intimidating so I've got plus two there
um yeah that's what I'm good at where do
you have all these weird stats I'm so
cool um if you go to abilities and skill
proficiencies and you can hit change and
you can see what you have
oh okay
okay you can handle a lot of weapons too
so Cali what's your strongest points
then in a build in skills skills uh
let's see so the highest my highest role
is Athletics
um
I don't know my Athletics is plus five
okay let's see and then survival plus
three animal handling plus three
okay I'm stronger
um
what was that what was that I got plus
four in those but
alrighty what's your strength uh
uh 12. okay well you can't beat me in
strength so an arm wrestling match
you're gonna suffer anyway continue
onward your turn your turn well I don't
really know if I should change any of
this um you you don't have to so just
read it off okay well right now
[Music]
um
uh stealth is plus five
oh that's good yeah uh another strong
one is animal handling inside both a
plus four perceptionist plus four
survival is plus four
um I don't know what do you want to know
people should I tell you my weak points
too then we can cover those or so
yeah sure
um
I'm weak in history
and religion oh yeah we wanted someone
to cover religion in history huh oh I
have plus one in history I have negative
one oh no I have negative one in history
I have plus one in religion okay okay
okay well we don't have to cover
everything I guess but
um okay and then yeah basically my
question was if it's if it makes sense
to go in uh you know bounty hunter that
gains me Proficiency in investigation do
we have anybody else who has Proficiency
in investigation because of yes then I
won't do it I have a negative one
investigation Okay negative one in
investigation okay so go ahead go for it
okay it will only bring me to plus one
but okay
then then I'll just say with what I have
now uh yeah I think um we'll be fine
what does narissa focus on
uh well I'll read my downsides first
with all the other skills I don't have
so my Athletics is minus one aerobatics
plus two sleight of hand plus four
stealth plus two Arcana plus one history
plus one investigation plus one nature
and religion plus one animal handling
zero inside zero medicine zero
perception survival zero deception plus
five and then invitation and performance
and persuasion all plus five but then
strength is eight dexterity is plus 15.
Constitution is plus thirteen
intelligence is plus 12 so I'm smarter
than all of you wow
[Laughter]
does anybody have deception on a decent
amount because me and there is on zero
I feel like maybe well maybe you could
instead choose to roll persuasion or
intimidation instead of deception yeah
can we choose that plus zero it depends
it'll give you multiple like dialogue
choices and you can choose what you want
to roll on ah okay I have plus five in
my deception too oh okay okay you're the
charismatic one oh wait you have plus
five interception well then there was
something else that I heard was Zero
okay okay cool uh cool do we have
persuade persuasion covered by someone
yes I have plus five persuades okay good
good good same
me and people will do the persuading
yeah we'll do the talking I think both
of us uh scale on Charisma so we will be
the razors and my guys do the talking we
do the killing am I the only stealthy
one well I'll kill two but yeah
yeah it's good to do both oh yeah you're
also healer right Bijou cleric oh you
got cleric anymore I am swapping to
sorcerer I'm only going to be cleric for
about two levels and then I'm swapping
into Source where uh for extreme magical
violence
um I do have heels and narissa should
have heels as well as Bart so we should
be okay okay just have some potions with
well then I really didn't need to be a
Healer okay good good
yeah uh did everybody show everything
off on stream then I think wow and
they're Guardians too I forgot to tell
the mine
the what
my my thing right yeah you haven't
introduced your character yet yeah yeah
ah yeah go go go go yeah okay hi
they forgot about me it's okay no no
never we need you you're important not
cleric
what is it yeah I'm
not cleric
um strength is nine
bad string our Dex is 13 Constitution 13
intelligence eight I'm not very smart or
strong but I have Charisma and that's
all that matters
um and also wisdom is 15. 17 and then my
proficiency
uh I got persuasion plus five
performance plus three intimidation I'm
very intimidating plus three deception
plus three survival plus two perception
plus two minus and plus four inside plus
four and we're handling plus two
religion plus one and then nature
investigation history Arcana all
negative one but I got still flight of
hand acrobatics and yeah
I can't yeah there you go I can't
uh
oh they're telling me to add one
Constitution but I can't
okay yeah you have to take away from
something yeah but the plus is grayed
out even when I have one ability Point
extra I do I wait like this okay
wait what but it still has no no where
was that where did uh where did I go ah
you messed it up
it was I changed it now I don't know
where my bonuses were
we'll find it okay it'll be free take a
picture and put it in the group chat
wait I did have a picture yeah yeah go
go check real quick it's okay thank you
for the reminder
it's okay no need to panic we have no
worries we got your back
but good but they really want me to have
more Constitution
and I can't I thought the constitution
for the group
oh wait no the picture I think was of
something else
[Music]
now I don't know what to do okay hold on
well I think we just have the
recommended because we didn't really set
them right
okay
oh it was okay okay okay
you recommended yeah
okay okay we can start again maybe cool
maybe awesome right so we're all gonna
like RP as our as our characters
but yeah I think we're all just us
except for you oh yeah
that makes it a lot easier
how's everyone's Guardian oh yeah random
one you make your sexy a sexy love
interest I already showed it off but
mine is my mom
yeah wow that's so cute
mine's just a random a random that I
could name
yeah mine is literally just the older
version hello bearded lady
wonderful hello bearded lady let's go
all right are we ready to get started I
guess yes
Venture fourth
okay here we go what's gonna happen do
we get a clue oh
that's right
Pirates of the Caribbean yeah yeah the
Kraken oh uh Davey Jones yeah yeah yeah
baby John yeah Jones
wow he's got alien feet
ah Taco it's Taco Time Taco Time
it's a single escalator in the game
Maybe
[Music]
maybe we're on a big ship yeah we're on
that one's so cool yes I think you may
have missed the first cut scene yeah we
are on that show watch it later
we don't like it there though we were
there against our will okay very evil
that doesn't seem right
we did not choose this life hold on a
second
that rendering is great on that that man
yeah no right really high quality
Graphics oh wow I can see every dust
particle that's grip strength man
oh they're getting captured
I thought they were getting
disintegrated
suffering let's go
well technically they're not dying
they're getting teleported uh oh the the
Mind players the goal with Calvary is
here I want to ride a dragon like that
in this game
[Laughter]
why do they have dragons
they're the targaryens obviously oh my
God they're not blonde though it's fine
let's go I guess oh the other the other
ones weren't blonde right
then yeah yeah
[Music]
all right well cable management
let's blow this Popsicle stand boys
ah run the frosty chat is the audio and
the visual is fine is it lagging or
anything
it's a big old beefy game it's pretty
loud
yeah
so crazy loud nice I think you'll turn
down when we exit the cutscene
um
specifically or to save all everybody
no that's not my character okay
she's always angry all the time yeah
she's kind of cool though kind of bass
but your character still seemed much
more stands out here than that one even
Kelly oh yeah I think so yeah she's a
star moriope is a star she knows it
rally
it was slimy
we will not be joining forces I'm sorry
you're going straight to the camp but it
was nice to see you anyway beautiful
rendered and also whoa excuse me
I like that
boulders
flinched immediately
she looks so good scene everybody missed
them in our head yes when did that
happen just just know there's a worm in
your head because that's very important
oh okay yeah we got wormed yeah
private dialogue off
don't don't check it don't check private
dialogue all right I won't it's off okay
keep it oh there I go
I have the oh I am too
yeah I look great
looking real good here let me oh we're
all together
so let's freaking go
um where are you yeah
playing with like a much
if you guys don't mind I'm very going
I'm going to very quickly turn my
settings to best or extremely good
instead of ultra just a moment please
let me really quickly change the video
to not be ultra how how do we do that
um if you go to settings you got to
press the start button for for me it's
probably and then go to settings
okay
[Music]
who
right yeah yeah
nice sisters
no none of them yeah I get to throw you
later on
the genitals what do you mean because I
turned them off in the beginning of the
game but apparently it's not really
turned off so I need to turn them off
where are the genitals oh go to settings
it's probably in settings be careful
okay okay okay uh maybe I checked it
right I'm unchecking it yeah we're all
scared what about cinematic genitals
is it an accessibility
yeah in gameplay and then scroll down a
little actually you should even see it
without no genitals off yeah dramatic
nudity off share private moments off
yeah none of you guys are getting my
private moments yeah with the hot demon
lady none of mine are checked so I think
we're good you're going for the
maybe I wanted to go for the demon lady
too bad I'm yourself you're so cool
we can fight for her you can have the
bear the bear I thought yeah you can
have the bear
you were so excited about the fair what
are you talking about okay look the
Bear's cool all right don't get me wrong
oh it's just
look
should we turn off dice
is
harmick dice avoids failure streaks
while keeping the results mostly random
no that feels like a good thing to have
on
any crowd say it again
I will just have it all turn it off they
say off yeah off off off okay
wow are we ready wait wait I'm just
trying to turn down some things no
problem me I'm bringing everything down
to like medium and low I mean yeah
you know what medium's good
medium's good actually
it's better than whatever I was playing
on the other computer I don't know how
to do anything by the way what about
narissa
oh same I don't know let's go on beeble
and Cali you will have to like uh tell
us everything sorry yeah
I know a little bit that's about it I
know a little bit too
just a little
um
uh okay wow it's so pretty though pretty
yeah it's very very detailed oh we're
moving I love how you move like you do
in League of Legends I thought that it
was going to be like I gave myself a
controller oh yes you're the league
player where's the karmic dice by the
way
uh I don't know hey Chad where's karmic
dice
I make dies uh here they're also on the
first one gameplay
on so we're turning it off right
yeah they say turn it off okay
I should look for that no we saw is a
league player
yeah I like Lee are you ever gonna play
those kind of games on stream
uh it's kind of hard because they're
more fun you have more people to play
with but some people just don't like
want to try it at all but I feel like
you would be feeling a niche because no
other en I think is playing those that
genre on stream
I'm not good though make it bigger
I might try it I want to do Dota 2 too
too because I haven't but I I'm more
familiar with League than I am DOTA in a
really long time
whoa It's shaking why is it so wide
wow I think I need to change the
solution to not be white and then we can
start and we can start aspect ratio
gotta change the aspect ratio
this is called sphincter I don't like
that
why not I mean we're in a thing
what's wrong with it
all right we've already got some party
conflict yeah let's play the game better
why are you flexing in our faces people
all right uh oh man dies
come on karmic Dice off
off
avoid failure streets okay anyway back
to the game
yes
[Music]
can we just go through it or do we go
through this thing go through the
sphincter
I know it's gross but you have to but oh
okay come up here come up here
well I need to get used to those
controls okay
get on the platform oh yeah you got it
okay so let me try and throw you uh
bagel
bagel okay is that you no someone go
talk to that person right now
Charisma people okay hey get it done and
then I'll loot them afterwards who is he
no he's still alive
barely
he's fine he's
happy yum yums
from this place you'll free us
um
[Music]
those are the yummies
turn the music up uh
this is important what I say
I don't know what would what would your
character say yeah
um
uh yeah hmm maybe the first one looks so
high-res
the high-res brain
I like your face
you look so you look so like disgusted
you see the same cutscene with yourself
oh okay we can we can also
yeah we can suggest things
what are you suggesting you can destroy
the brain no don't destroy the brain
it's good it's good let's ask more
how many memories
okay
oh okay I see guys I'll fix it in a
moment
let's
before we destroy it we have to you know
cover all options yeah what's the plan
yeah what if it jumps out and hurts you
free free the brain it sounds pretty
nice
well my strongest one would be the
dexterity one I think I say or
investigation
[Music]
definitely prized the brain from the
skull bro I will I will do that let's
take a look oh my God
skill checks some dialogue options
require skill check a dice roll at most
meet or exceed a target number your
character skills add a bonus as well
okay okay wow
your first roll good luck
oh it has to be minimum ten right
or if it matches it it's fine too
crippled a strange creature Lord
what am I looking at
uh yeah let's mutilate the brain yeah
what happens if I fail
something bad uh oh no do I does the
brain take over me
wow you're just stupid
you killed him dude
killed him
sorry it was so wobbly
little legs
we got a runner
oh time to destroy it it ran away oh
it's running away but I destroyed a
destroyer
I don't destroy today I know we should
have killed that thing
yeah
I'm sorry no it will follow and haunt us
forever
I'll be back oh we left we left I was
adjusting
where is throw okay I'm here wait
um do you have hey do you have a bagel
do you have improvised melee weapon use
it
on you improvised yeah do you raised
melee weapon yeah
I do improvised melee whip I found it
that's too heavy to pick up
oh only yet yes I can hold on a sec
hold on improvised melee weapon
[Music]
head over oh oh wow
[Applause]
real sorry about that yeah it sucks well
anyway you'll get enraged thrill later
and that's the big eat cool I'm hyped
for that that's the one yeah we're gonna
oh we're gonna use that
yeah that's pretty sick I thought I'd
provide some some background Ambiance
for your guys's fight no please thank
you I like you are playing tiny horned
winged one wait you don't have wings
time
changed my whole uh layout in OBS I'm
ready now
bye
Marissa good luck fighting whatever's
over there ah just kidding
oh man it's gonna be a long journey
let's go okay let's go time battles whoa
what I reach forward want a ball ready
to ready to Bonk them in the head with
my the hammer oh
oh my gosh yes
oh no oh no
no you cannot join our party
excuse me I am much more beautiful yeah
she's so insulting
yeah
Abomination doesn't sound too wrong
oh
we share a brain we share a brain cell
s
you cannot join my party
I'm sorry what is this they all want to
join us yeah you guys we're just we're
just that cool they want to join the
squad party's full yeah squad's full
sorry
real sorry about that
well you got to go to the camp
um I are you making these decisions now
who are you what do you suggest who are
you
who are you who is you uh
what made you think I was a thrall
parasites
unless we are cleansed
basically if we let the thing stay in
our head we turn into one of those
tentacle people oh yeah
so we don't want to do I mean that could
have its upsides too
it must be our priority together okay
Escape you can do that oh the yum yums
getting the the snacks the munchies
okay okay
bye
all right delicious go to the camp and
wait
teach us combat
oh so angry
oh look at that Bloody smile generally
tutorial I kind of get it all right guys
it's hard to fight let's go
I was around you during combat so you
have time to come
huh
is there gonna take a little shot
uh is there any water
yeah there's no order why am I playing
it
why am I playing with you
all right well anyway you could never a
dull moment tell them okay I mean we're
pretty strong right off the bat
really big piece of dirt
nice yeah yummy
and X I don't need that I could sell it
though collect everything sell for big
money
we'll take it
I took it oh right next door again oh we
have to wait for
um I have to end their individual turns
yeah okay
Luke Goblin engage
what okay our tank should shall be in
front of us
I guess I'm also playing as the NPC oh
[\h__\h]
to you
yeah
can't believe they're giving me this
responsibility I got gold yeah
I can't believe that they're leaving all
this nice loot around here what is she
left it for you because we know you you
would want oh wait
ahead so I can get all the water first
he's got so much good stuff hey hey
no what's this restoration
what's this I want to go up there we go
all right let's climb up this nasty
thing yeah
people took all the loot I did that'd be
faster than that but you'd better share
the money from it the revenue yeah we
split the prop put the profit no
why
did you not oh there's a girl in here
oh you do not react okay
the button
I'm sorry I probably should get close to
her face what am I doing
oh what happened what happened we're
killing a guy okay I guess
it'll take us some getting used to team
but that's okay
um I have to add my turn uh nice hit
Bijou it was still alive here oh you
okay
not enough movement
I guess I'll just move forward
I don't think I have any range ranged
attacks all right
unless I could throw
do something to me nice Miss idiot here
we go no I want to do something oh
[Music]
I'm Barbarian
oh oh hell yeah
no I will not help
us now okay the brain you told us not to
kill let's get him
let's go
all right cool I mean that works oh wow
wow I'm so powerful you are you're
pretty strong
already
is there any loot left
see what's over here how about you what
are you holding does not want to see
this room
oh thank you hey I saw you snatched that
before my eyes
Goblin piece of dirt what's this do
I'm gonna go free Shadow heart I'm gonna
push this button
which button uh
oh wait what
oh all right I'm gonna free
what what's happening
everybody needs a ranged weapon there's
a socket in the car inserted
I'm late to everything let's go did you
get her out it will free her I'm freeing
her now
place to handle the console just let her
out let her free
YouTube why don't you take my kids
singing everything else you lose Goblin
oh I'm gonna share
yeah sure
I don't even know the pods are open fine
what are we doing
um
is Shadow heart gonna die
he's rejected me
no it's over did he die
yeah she's super dead
tear it open I'm not giving up this is
all my fault
what are these ass rolls
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] are you
kidding me I'll show you Shadow heart
I'll free you hey no I would have free
Shadow heart I wanna free I won The Rock
ETS
can't use a reaction shocked
already limited it's different from
already in use
iPod can I do it too critical failure I
haven't even had a critical failure in
my game that I'm playing right now
okay so I need to if it fades I can't
free you a sensation
it won't work
only one at a time open yeah only only
one at a time
do you need the key
incredible
Something Beautiful about that wow
I guess rip Shadow heart it was nice
while it lasted
[Music]
oh poor oh what's happening why do we
want this anyway
she's not gonna be a party member anyway
yeah she's super dead oh well I'll place
my head oh she's so dead
I'm still alive you can use that key
that you got to oh you already am you
know how to play this game I guess we
should just move along no I don't know
what
is a romance option well it's not like
we'll never see her again if we don't
free her okay you got this you got this
you got it it's almost like chromatic
dice are off
[Applause]
what I only needed a two and I got 19.
yeah we both got ones well how did you
only get one
[Laughter]
there's four of us am I right ladies
critical success
across your mind we look so good
together sated
iconic Duo come out ladies get out of
the shots
yeah
man no she's pretty good looking I'm so
glad I could free you wow thank goodness
I freed you from the pot the thing I
freed you myself oh all by myself
do you feel that just now dangerous
companies what you need in a fight looks
like there's plenty of fighting it says
Danger
is that a heart beautiful no you're on
your own if you're if you're waving if
you're waving compliment already uh we'd
make three double lady I want a shadow
heart okay you can have Shadow heart
okay I'm taking Shadow heart yeah
you look good yeah
no thank you gotta call dibs don't worry
Marissa there's a very nice vampire dude
no no we will not allow him on the team
he will never be anywhere near any of
you why not he's so you can't tell me
what to do
all right you know what Marissa live
your dreams
Live Your Dreams
yeah we came that way let's go to the
right
monster we have a big party now yucky
vampire out of our camp
aign
but he's yucky
that fiend
okay
you got it then we step on the sphincter
in the butthole the face butthole time I
don't want to I'm ready
we're ready oh yeah yeah we're ready oh
you know it the soul squad's here
the whole squads
hop up the squad oh
oh yeah no
I mean yes
get in here beat him up get in here
I'm here now
we must escape
now
uh so we got it we're on the tentacle
dude side for now gotta get rid of the
devil
s
no who am I right now on Lily kill
everything that we see yeah
and probably do some other stuff bonus
oh yeah I forgot to rage
[Music]
oh my God
so angry
oh that was looting okay who's alive
here
I mean okay we're pretty strong Jesus
yeah we're strong you can try and shoot
let's go oh
that's so dumb that was so dumb I mean
it hit
whoa oh
okay
um
it's on the other side
got a dash
was that good oh there's more there's
more bad guys here can't get there can I
Dash
what if I can Dash
two damage in our Dash back was
resistant and we did two cop damage
what if I want to fight the devil
went up the devil is level eight it has
a hundred HP okay never mind all right
never mind
yeah the commander person it sounds like
quitter speak actually oh moriope kill
everything
[Music]
it's resisting everything I'll wait for
you
wait we have 14 turns remaining by the
way
I see so that's how the rage works so I
should probably use it up beforehand
when I'm about to hit I'm about to
strike my rage ended
loot
uh
that I should be using is that correct
are you guys still shooting at him yeah
yeah I mean you're going for the
transponder bro there's three enemies
because he's super powerful yeah okay
yeah let the tentacle monster men fight
we gotta get those guys but I'm just
very slow I need some assistance
okay let me help
no I'm just very slow
I didn't need your help I'm trying
everyone's dead now the woods
everyone's dead
it was Dash do I have Dash yeah you do
have Dash it's on there it's on your
other side how did I miss it okay
people you're too strong
myself
oh they're still fighting
yeah I just killed everyone here
[Music]
oh oh oh okay I can take it I can take
it oh I'm gonna go for the thing I'm
going for the thing go go for the thing
I have pets already I don't have a
package done
are you surviving on your single player
it's easy in fact I'm playing on normal
mode
however I have not really played much of
the Barbarian class yet
I'm really good at Magic but I'm not
playing Magic this time
can you guys see the cutscene yeah okay
good
yeah big old dragon
that looks painful
wow
be careful
sounds about right
get ready this is the rest of the
campaign
okay I know how to dash now
good I I don't know how to do anything I
wish I had a con same I wish my
controller worked because this is so
confusing that like I have to use my
mouse to move and then to turn the
screen stuff I Like to Move It I have to
use the things we'll get used to it use
q and E to wrote I'm like what
I'll try it
I mean I prefer a controller personally
oh the Goblins I know those guys I know
them now all your other your friends no
no they're not
definitely not I beat the [\h__\h] out of
them
goblins are never good guys in any
medium
yeah
can I say the thing what go for it
people how could you
I saw it in chat before you even said it
[Music]
Darkness will fade away
oh
put it down okay who saved you Hey Big
Ups
who did save us I don't know
oh Magic that was plush
then you are so beautiful
thanks I know you feel gorgeous Bella
the ball
oh what's up sis
we look good what me
oh I see I see boo boo turned back I
mean you can be my sister too if you
want
yuckys check for injuries am I okay
yeah other than the infection you're
more or less intact
iCal given everything you've been
through we have been through for nothing
if you don't find help soon I love the
narrator's voice yeah it's very soon
very ASMR I need a cure what it do bagel
okay unique item okay I know this
oh please teach me where the dash is
um it's on the left side of your bar
it's like a foot with wings
I'm such a dummy
I just don't think I have eyeballs all
right
um is very important and jump is also
very important you will need to jump oh
yeah definitely nowhere the challenge
all right leave it to me
hey
oh what's that oh
it's the it's the cube from that one can
I link it that one scary franchise
Hellraiser tesseract
give me summon Pinhead
oh [\h__\h] dang it that one's very
franchise I don't know the name of it oh
people what were you doing
oh I uh checking to see if you're okay
of course she's in love right away
speaking of
how are we alive I saved you obviously
uh
we made it it doesn't matter
judging by all the corpse history about
I remember the ship
I remember falling
than nothing
damn uh I love the deadbeat inside jokes
where are we
but anything's an improvement on where
we're dang Sheila good
Ness
bad
no bad
oh no stealing clothes let's go together
no it's what you can steal their clothes
as long as you don't steal their
underwear oh
yeah I've imagined with Hangers On
already oh excuse you kill at the camp
that's all you're good for chilling at
the camp just stay at the camp there you
go bye yes
all right ladies let's let's Bust A Move
yeah
oh we leveled oh I'll click on your
character level but you're gonna need to
level up
hold on a sec or excuse me level up
how do I
oh
26. there we go it increases a lot a
spell slot
well danger sense nice and I'm getting
tankier
oh I have to choose the Spells now
okay anyway I still have to read these
to give me a moment I got destructive
wrath okay I'm good I'm gonna choosing
spells man takes a lot of reading oh I'm
gonna go loot these bodies while they're
busy leveling up hmm
[Music]
I think everything everything
is good
oh yeah you're a barbarian who just hit
level up and you're good yeah and then
I'm good to go
you guys have to tell me this is the
mean book
are you a man do you have a man voice I
do but I'm a lady who's you sorry he was
you sister
oh my god when you're so cute and small
yeah and perfectly eatable yeah oh we'll
be doing lots of throwing yes
and then he throws away at us both
Waypoint discovered let's go uh
oh money
I I guess I'll just that's cool well
what did you just find oh this is a warp
point you can work on the map oh yeah
I think this is our first one though so
we can't go anywhere yeah
where's everybody
what the [\h__\h] we're over here
don't you no you never split the party
that doesn't seem like we know
I'm exploring so yeah no fish I found my
little brain guy did you guys take all
the things
you're gonna need help you're gonna need
help here okay
these guys do not mess around
just salt them insult them okay please
they're so close to me it's not worth
checking anything
you guys we can just throw insults at
them yeah my turn I need my turn
oh as far as possible oh okay help me
bonus fashion there's nothing I can do
whoa whoa nice nice
oh that was good
she's fine she's fine she's okay vicious
mockery
yeah we just kind of we just gotta kill
this guy though
uh they said biboo apparently you hit me
yeah you hit me we were in the way
so there is uh friendly a fire in this
game yes there is correct correct
I know
you can run so quick why all right I got
you I'm gonna throw you a potion I can
be used here here I'll heal you here
yeah you're the clearer why do you have
so many attacks
I need help
I need help to equip a bow
do not throw uh we're fine we're fine
someone smacked this thing right
yeah I didn't hear a smack or anything
it was weird
oh god oh
no idea what's going on too late I want
to go up here I Will Follow You Marissa
oh yeah wait no I said come here don't
you wanna be a nice elf man I do I do I
do want to meet a nice elephant come
over here will he join my team and help
me yeah we'll do a lot of things if you
want him to
him that sounds more more than one thing
okay if you really want him to
okay walk walk up the hill Marissa walk
up the hill yeah go go meet him go meet
him you don't meet him go just go talk
to him
I don't see anyone keep going just keep
walking yeah keep going how big will it
be oh I see a man yeah go talk to them
follow me yeah okay
look let's go tune in it's got a brain
thing cornered
you girl
um
what are we doing right now
oh you're listening okay that was so
based of Marissa right there
[Music]
oh good luck
get a wrestling baby
[Music]
it's a show who's boss yes lunch money
yeah
he's playing hard to get struck out
whilst I was trapped in that pot oh [\h__\h]
off man
tell them how it is
hahaha
this is chaotic I like it why does he
think we belong to them
we're obviously good people
we share a brain cell
s
he likes you yeah no
that's why it's how he shows affection
it's the Mind flares where are we
connected us that sounds
[Laughter]
whatever they did whatever they put in
this no he's annoying
let's go
whatever just happened the typical DND
slash world of Darkness vampire
is is he even a vampire yeah
you just gotta gotta learn I'm out of
wine with flowers it looks very much
like one also it reminds me of Victor
Vic Victor Good Old Vic yeah but a
little bit less obnoxious still yeah
true
um
Dorian option
[Music]
are we all beldorians yeah I think it's
better assistant
various ways
yeah I think we are all of us yeah I
think we we all got we all got like
joint from from the city okay
we clearly move in different circles wow
he's like Bernie
in GTA 5 a little bit
can I kick him out I don't want to talk
to him anymore why did you guys make me
do this
no I don't like [\h__\h] men I like evil
men not [\h__\h] men
ah what's the difference
the big difference
[Laughter]
yeah it can't come out
no thanks uh
it won't let me think do what you want
I'm leaving I don't
that's [\h__\h] hilarious is it gonna
make you send him to the camp
I don't know I don't know
it won't let me pick
again
no no it makes a sound but nothing is
happening
uh-huh
click a double
click a triple he's never gonna leave us
alone I'm clicking so much guys help
maybe
vote time
what if we stop listening yeah guys get
me out of here time to save and reload
stop listening X is on the top right
excellent oh
all right bye Marissa my cute friend
oh did you find this Kiara I I summoned
it I have I can summon like five six
different animals I just realized it oh
this is sick this is Froggy one numbers
don't work numbers aren't working you
guys can we knock her out of combat yeah
can you kill me I got you yeah
I'm sorry guys
[Laughter]
oh my God this is so dangerous oh my I'm
safe can I even save and reload is that
even possible
um
I got a different I got a different
option I got different options
okay wait no no I'm stuck again kill me
put her back down put it back down to
survive
no kill me
okay did you get it
no I'm staying in safe distance
oh my God
I mean look look did you at this point
I'm just having a good time having a
good time
save and reload apparently can you all
right let me see I don't know what data
it's gonna show hang on let me you got
it I got your back let me save the game
really quick
oh can I help you
okay
load game safe successful okay
[Music]
going back
did you did you get into a loading
stream or screen yes yeah okay good why
is my game
a bit late to save
dive safe after everyone calls hi
it'll be fun and we're new at this it's
okay
we still have much to learn I'm dead
because you killed me
you'll be fine sorry we can
we can save you oh you're back down okay
oh let me help you up
hello
do we need him for anything no what
about our low HP yeah you guys gonna
heal us oh my God
[Music]
okay
I can't move can I kill him
I I can move my screen but I can't I
can't move
oh oh oh God they're broken
The Matrix
oh do you have an earlier save do you
have I have a quick save I think maybe
go back to that earlier save before we
met this freaking guy yeah and it all
fell apart and everything all right let
me see auto save all right um there's us
on the beach okay we probably will lose
some loot but you can just grab it again
you get it again better than better than
whatever's going on right now yeah
whatever whatever this is thank goodness
for autosave
[Laughter]
[Music]
back here oh I think we have to level
again too yeah that's yeah oh no I'm
good I don't need to take so much time
I can't level oh oh Shadow heart hi oh
we talked to her again hold on let me
I'll let you go faster
you do your thing Bieber okay uh
okay
going to the camp
I don't have the leveling thing guys
yeah I don't either neither do I I think
I already left it's already after we
level it okay I'm not sure because
mine's only at 13 and I thought I was at
like 20 something oh you're right there
we go there we go
just popped
okay
get those levels
Three Hats mom yeah let's save if we
decide to talk to that guy again
beforehand uh yeah since he broke the
game
oh yeah oh you know there are always
other greener pastures like uh maybe
houses you know I bet you'd like houses
this time guys who who
a house in is a great kind soul I think
you'll really like that character and
maybe you can have a romance
[Music]
yeah no why wouldn't you trust me I mean
I feel like he's just a very Charming
character that you'd like that's all
that there is to it there's no surely no
tricks no trickery no anything just give
me different clothes
that's why I wanted to get a stereo
because the stereo has nice clothes too
it does have nice clothes but I don't I
don't want yes I want to steal his
clothing
okay now we're all here for the bathroom
okay
uh can I walk around this
I'm probably gonna have to move around
it
okay
I need to equip something long range
pretty sure I have a short bow your frog
is so cute
can I
eat
everything
it's pretty evil captain like the little
corner of it
Ash is an action
when I dashed no because it's an action
you can't yeah I can at least leave a
Hunter's Mark
nice it'll do more damage if you if you
shoot them just throw axes oh I can
throw axes oh you're so right Chad I
didn't know that because I don't play
Barbarian oh boy
you're good you're good on the way can I
control the Frog
you should be able to yeah it's not the
Frog's turn yet
oh
okay you want a party
page oh yeah
oh
rock your friends
wow loot
give me brain frog only one HP
Nani
oh there's another one up there
Maury smash
triangle
eh my turn I love the Frog's portion
okay wait now it's frog okay now it's
froggy time what can froggy do
some things can froggy attack no not
enough movement okay froggy just follow
oh cute he can be butter you know cannon
fodder or bait yeah I guess so I guess I
can't do anything special ah wait wait A
Touch of a creature can I do this no not
enough movement I guess if I would have
dashed but it's okay
you're good oh you need help you look
okay hp's only half
am I gonna be okay no that's not bad
it's not bad yeah eat the Frog good
shoot the other one girl he has a
hunter's Hunter's Mark on a Hunter's
Mark nice yeah
what
you had to concentrate to keep the
Hunter's Mark active yeah you're good
you're good it's only for me
yay can I do anything else uh and rage
nah there's no reason to end my rage
yeah keep raging keep raging I think
it's over though after this turn
yeah this one
I need healing
um do you have some uh oh there we go
you have a potion maybe oh that was on
that was on the wrong thing it's fine
[Music]
thank you a little bit
oh thanks
Mario fan no smash
and only smash
all right time for you to go kill that
guy we can also yeah
we want to steal his clothes but we need
to save right before we talk to him yeah
I'm not talking to him again this is up
to someone else
you were so cool when you like when you
like got him to the ground and like like
just beat him up that was sick
talk to us
man is my worst nightmare don't worry
okay
so yucky ooh yucky
help yeah you got it it's useless kill
it yourself
what else we got um crossbow you want a
Tango dang pretty boy he got you on the
ground too yeah good luck
push yourself to your feet
Arctic inspiration is that okay
I want to be cool
well let's go
wow yeah success
apparently yeah we're picking locks yeah
he's a stealthy one
[Music]
um
sorry I haven't done anything to you yet
he's kind of kind of a jerk you know big
meanie yeah you're looking
no rizz no rizz
get out of here Dollar Store
yucky man put the knife away and I'll
tell you any everything just
if I do this I'm only eye resting chat
he saw it
all kinds of things it's all right it's
ready to decorate the ground I would
like to after this cutscene rest for a
moment I can heal my HP
apology accepted oh yeah oh you can
press short rest yeah I just need to
yeah apparently everybody too
you got it rest alone
Dash through this guy's dialogue yeah we
just need we don't care we just need him
yeah
go to the camp dummy all right we can
rest we can do a short rest we don't
need to do a long run there you go oh
much better I feel rested
let's go ahead and do a save here
oh yeah good good call yeah
what's popping off in here hello
let's kill it yeah kill it beat him up
you guys talk to them you little [\h__\h]
it's you oh Jesus
kind of based I don't know
right for that yeah that was kind of
Awesome
all right I think we need to go this way
why did you just suddenly die
oh Goblin scimitar
let me
oh The Bijou kill it during the cutscene
I bonked him right in the head that
scene was too good for it
what is that
that looks uh crazy Marissa do you
really want to stand so close to it
yeah yeah punch the center
oh Ellie and erisa was stuck because of
a party boat I don't know what that
means though oh uh I don't know because
every other time when people were voting
it didn't get stuck like that if people
didn't vote so
I think I think the Voting is just like
a suggestion isn't it yeah yeah exactly
I don't think it was a hand give me my
hand there was uh the hands slap it
slap the hair
um
oh
yeah
20s already I'm just saying good well
critical failures on this
Style
gotta help him out I don't have anything
I don't have any strength so
can we quit arms
it doesn't really look like you're
pulling that hard there is some oh wait
who's he oh oh this is what you like
it's a wizard I don't know I want to
know who he is though
you look perfect hello
Mr Magic Man yeah
a bit shocked I'll be nice to him he
doesn't seem like a mean guy what a
pleasure to make your acquaintance
and like his floppy hair in a manner of
speech you're on the noise Lloyd as well
the wizard of water d
ude I assume you too we're on the
receiving end of
unwelcome
worms in our brains
[Music]
it is there yeah
I ship it there is that and The Wizard
what's your wizard I know I just think I
just think Houston's really cool you
know
unfortunately we have no clerics with us
now ah wait we do yeah but so soon to be
something else
hmm
I have one
certainly going to need a Healer I'm a
really dumb cleric though I don't think
you would trust me to like worms out of
your head
I trust you
oh
okay
oh I see you're traveling with plenty of
company already
perhaps I can join you later instead oh
um where you will never leave yeah go to
my Camp stay there forever forever if
you play solo are all these dudes like
joining you yeah yeah if you play solo
they they join up and then you can like
hang out with them and do their like
story quests but we have our own we have
our own Squad we have our own party
which is so much better I wonder how we
get their approval though if they're
never on our team like out in the field
with us oh this way
but you got to get their approval if you
want to raise them up but if they're
always in the camp you can't get their
approval the reason why are you walking
like that
no I don't know
what I she's like I think it's nice back
to normal okay
Camp talks
hello
there's so much to look at
oh there's people here hello
should we kill them
yeah it sounds fun I just saved the game
uh Taman in case wouldn't [\h__\h]
you're real nice to him God hey what's
up it looks like one of my old cats
I am not impressed looks like a raccoon
I summoned a raccoon
oh
really it looks kind of raccoon but it's
supposed to be a cat
attack you like a baby
I have a meow action and what else just
meowing attract the attention of nearby
creatures to draw them closer to you
oh
oh cat cannot move too much
the distraction no one will hurt this
cat
[Laughter]
I heard the cat I will destroy them I
will destroy them
[Applause]
it did attract attention so
understandable yeah
are you kidding me
bye
what was it
was that anything oh God
oh
all right hold on I got you
wow what your nostrils
what's with your nostrils
you in fact my eyes and nostrils wait
why didn't you throw it I tried I was
trying to throw potion at you
sorry oh she dead
we only have Cali at full HP
sorry
what's happening right now
um uh someone's turn oh oh oh God what's
wrong with that person
let me oh oh critical news all right let
me hold on a sec
hmm thank you you're welcome now let me
see if I can anything else I can do I
might go to sleep
[\h__\h] how dare you do that to narissa
so rude can I use a Potion No I mean at
least if I'm knocked out I heal right if
they make me sleep that's how it works
in Games
bad news
I'm gonna try to wake you up okay
okay next time I kill him
I'm not the team baggage am I doing this
right to chat
I'm using
I thought I threw a potion at her dang
it um can I help you wake up
rage
but wait uh to die how much 80 I'm dying
still
don't range to yeah that's not what I
wanted to do
oh yeah
I don't know that it would make me auto
do that
nice damage yeah I finally got to loot
something
I am holding a ranged weapon now
uh oh wait there's still alive okay okay
let's take her down I gotta take them
out
go down beat her up wow
did she do that when we're like like
right in front literally right here wow
she is arranged
it doesn't matter it doesn't matter oh
wow you think I know that thank you
stop taking the gold right before my
eyes hey
food
outside in here Point Blank shot oh oh
are you okay you go to ground
oh hello
oh this is like a dungeon oh Jesus okay
um
oh that is a lot of people okay that's a
lot of dudes yeah that's more than one
okay we got this who are they
oh my God
oh good yeah insult them insult them all
my stuff number stinky
oh oh
tomb Raiders okay I'm gonna try to blast
all of them here we go I'm gonna blast
them okay anyway I start blasting how
many can I get oh okay
yay look at this
I got it I blew up the explosives
apparently I got I got nobody what's
that even worse you did good I tried
your best I did not have good rolls so
it matters
this person
yeah
somebody set the oil on fire do it oh
it's a fireball
you can shoot it
[Music]
oh
I don't have fire
but there's oil on the floor now I don't
know if this really works I also do not
have 505.
How's It Go five Fire Light to fire yeah
as you desire
tasting all that we aspires
never ever have I ever
been a dreamer take the chest with my
lighter oh magnifier you can throw a
torch oh nice oh
they can rage too all right
oh yeah yeah I'm right here of course
they don't aim for the tank
of course they just point blank ignore
the tank
wow
I don't know what that means but I think
you call them stinky stinky
he's smelly dude
what are they doing wait what's that
oh they added more reinforcements yeah
hold on a sec I go here and then
X I do this get them
oh damn you
let me get off this oil
just in case
yeah that maybe would have been nice
wait don't leave me in here
gotta fight them on your own
words
I'm still in Rachel I'll apply Hunter's
Mark on him I'm going to perish I'll
find him next turn
hopefully they will yeah please attack
me
please let me take the damage yes what
do we have our tank for don't attack the
the weak ones
this is not the glass cannons
help
[Laughter]
oh oh wow oh dear
good luck
everybody no spells
ow
it's like they know I'm about to die
wait let me use this on him can I not
he Dash oh it's gonna be fun looting
this place afterwards oh there we go we
definitely will
oh
oh yeah what
[Music]
don't worry Bijou we'll take him down
I bonked him on the head and he took
zero damage
yeah
what's that mean
um whoa you're choosing how to react
yeah you can react sometimes you can
like hit back with a counter spell go go
oh
wow oh I didn't know I could do that
okay
I wanted to throw a hand ax
okay well that's one person
oh yeah
what's a flounder isn't that a fish it's
a fish
it was your father a fish wow
yes
goodbye
to you guys no no no we'll revive you
somehow I'd love to revive you but I do
need to do something about this yeah no
no no you do something I I'm on my way
don't I have a Revival thingy oh yeah it
was a pretty yucky attack right there
uh I'm gonna try to revive her then
if I can the only thing to remember is
when she comes back it'll be at one HP
so gotta make sure to follow up with a
quick heal myself oops
oh I'm in the way
so small though shouldn't you be able to
aim over her head
come on why is it only 42 of me being
able to throw it properly because
because throwing is difficult yeah
throwing's hard can I oh wait is there
anything else I can do like they say
just touch her
yeah just tattoo yeah
it'll give her one HP though so you
gotta heal pretty quick after that or
someone will just knock her out real
fast all right
uh retreat
oh little [\h__\h]
knows what he's doing he's using real
threats wow I mean smart man I should
play like that
um
why have any um
[Music]
if you throw the potion right at her it
would hurt her because it's an attack
roll so you have to throw it right to
the ground next to her is that what
happened to Cali before yeah I think
yeah okay because like the Polish is
made of glass so you're throwing a glass
bottle so that's probably on the ground
when we want to do that thanks for the
help chat we're on the ground
I can't do anything
um I'll except uh perform again yeah
yeah
[Music]
my favorite
do you know Ragnar the red
no we Ragnar the red you gotta learn
Ragnar the red
it's my favorite thing this is this is
all this is this is what you get in does
that even does that do anything oh good
oh really oh
okay it's fine all righty let's see
I'll help I'm helping
thanks
oh dummy nice nice nice Tyler
no I mean thank you
my other weapon was it changed if
[\h__\h] okay you
oh they're still taking it yeah I know
sneak attack ow
[Music]
I think that didn't do that much damage
depressing F wow
yeah I don't know how I feel if someone
called me that uh
pretty pretty rude
owie
okay okay okay
let me add them yeah
nice one yeah okay
okay
let's see yeah
yeah
let's go
um I suggest we all take a long rest yes
ladies.com
[Music]
long rest well I sit like such a lady
no no I don't I just wanted to sit down
oh but we're doing long rest right
hey what were you able to sing
Shadow hot
to say
we look like fry adventurers yeah
it's so good
well everything fuses in our heads
sooner or later they're going to blow
everyone's everyone's backside is
finally crafted in this game even ours
it's gross yeah
we need to find a Healer I want a ghost
why do you want to take off her clothes
so badly maybe we'll get
huh
underwear I doubt that they will fit her
uh just FYI says somebody in chat I
don't know if it's a one guy situation
you can't steal their clothes with four
UPS four Co-op players without killing
them
oh
he breathes so loudly
[Music]
I guess we could just murder him how do
I take his clothes by killing him was
there anything no what's your damn mouth
let me save the game every day
[Laughter]
I'm gonna slap his cheeks around a
little bit yeah
roll initiative
literally
crimes certain actions are frowned upon
by others like I give a [\h__\h] let's go
yeah I killed him oh my God
[Music]
tracks
you're so messed up right outfits
[Music]
take his underwear
oh
this happen with the Looting
you killed some more conversation with
him yeah it was sick
why
I wanted his clothes now I got like
fancy clothes
just undressed them I don't think we
have to kill them no we gotta kill him
if you want their clothes
sadly with four with four players hungry
I'm happy
okay put them on
I did
well
would you like to go to bed yeah sure
yeah let's sleep
you can't you can't resurrect them back
apparently somebody cancel what what
me not me
what is this oh yeah yeah but somebody
cancels again why not your boy I'm
currently choosing camp supplies for a
long rest yeah yeah okay so someone wait
what I think I think Kelly has it
choose it okay okay one or more players
denied the request failed to answer on
top go to bed yes okay yes
okay we'll rest okay
tiny noodles who is trolling shots
oh yeah we can always res around to
Syrian if we need him I don't think
we'll need him but since we're already a
party affordable whatever
I don't think anyone's interested
Force the tab pull out of your mind I'm
not very intelligent so I'll use wisdom
and stuff I'm smarter than all of you
all right well I'll use wisdom I'm Wiser
than you I think that yeah
okay I'll try it too
I'm succeed
you know it's our first meal of the game
success
maybe maybe we want it
yeah um it's a brick but why is this a
mountain watch exactly I mean it's in
character right
here
[Music]
the more you'll pay no understanding
I can't wake up because you guys
wouldn't I get to sleep if I failed this
what what would have done what what did
that even do the fact that I succeeded
and what would it have done if I failed
I don't know no idea
[Music]
someone mentions uh somebody says you
you said you wanted to multi-class yes
apparently we can't on this difficulty
what yeah it says it's disabled on the
difficulty because it's fairly Advanced
oh my God
what should we do
um it's okay I'll just when when can we
change when the re-roll happens I can
re-roll
changing difficulty and menu option I
can change it oh yeah change it to
normal yeah normal we'll be fine well
yeah we'll we'll live we will live I
don't know about that you guys no no no
I've already been on the bridge of dying
a lot of times
it's okay
on the break of dying because we don't
have stuff yet exactly okay uh you can
return that back down to easy
if it's too difficult yeah but then the
multi-class things you know it's just
it's fun just change multi-class then go
back
yeah
so
really do we go back to the Mean Girls
situation is this a Mean Girls situation
I'm looking at right here am I not
beautiful enough for you
hi am I not beautiful enough for
you you're the only one that's kind to
me Liara
oh
oh maybe yeah no you extra Spain you
take like two spaces I do I'm pretty
hey nice but there's always going to be
one girl excluded why is our our posters
so [\h__\h]
all right why don't we sit like that
how do I steal people's clothes without
killing them
you can't are we gonna go back to the
fight yeah we should I'm already here
what how did you go there yeah
hey click on the bed click on the bed
roll
the bed roll
the bad the bad thing ah leave Camp okay
all right
are you trying to end the day
going to bed again
a ladle no I don't need this stuff open
this
oh
yeah I already took all the treasures I
took it look it for me
I'm stuck
where are you stuck oh okay I'm good now
there's been nothing left in here that
we already kill everybody I thought
there was gonna be more there's a
there's a thing over this way hey
why would I need the cutting board
[Music]
you guys are still inside yeah
yeah
I'm on the other side oh stealing all
the money from here
books have HP
can I jump oh
it's just the sturdiness
is there ever something special in here
I did something
did something happen
you do not recognize the language on the
plaque oh
it's all loaded scroll to Magic oh
there's a there's a door I opened over
here
I'm on the way
this one this way this one yeah this one
yeah why are you giggling
why are you giggling hey
where what
are you going through something
like a crib I love so I'm just exploring
some more she's a little thing let's go
it's just money
it's
like nothing of value in there did you
already steal everything in here Bieber
no I oh oh where are you going
oh
[Music]
oh oh
no
the game has passed around and then time
is working down into another okay uh
what's gonna happen
a trap
what's happening
I think we're fine
oh what what's happening for you girls I
mean I ended my turn uh uh I think yeah
I think you have to end your turn
oh oh but there's a button apparently
what button
go back to entrance okay
oh okay that's about what I thought
okay
yeah at least it wasn't hit this time
but maybe now no maybe now it's it's not
as dangerous anymore because it's shot
once you think it's gonna shoot again
oh
oh maybe it'll be fine no it's not safe
it's not over okay okay uh let's leave
yeah yeah there's treasure
yeah oh oh okay
stand in there with your hands on your
hips just fired consumed you
no not until you Karen out of the turn
based mode okay
whoa whoa okay oh
they're like
oh are you guys fighting something uh no
no it's fine it's fine it's fine it's
fine oh uh people does it ever stop
you're dying oh I'm dying yeah you're on
some help over there
okay where's Marissa
um I'm I'm not nearby oh
I just realized
one HP I bet the bottom
oh [\h__\h]
yeah there's a button oh but I mean do
you want to walk into that
I mean it's the thing in the middle you
did is there more look than that because
I I earned it I earned it I went and
grabbed it and survived I earned this
I turned it on
okay we'll go find them
oh
oh I turned it off what's in here go oh
now I will know oh
I found something with 71 health
oh she's dead though
but his tennis balls are still kind of
moving oh no
it's locked oh
man
you're finding I want to see what you
[\h__\h]
is this better than what I have Mario
pay only Fine Dirt
[Laughter]
we're too dumb to understand what's on
the plaque yeah not very smart
clip The Shield
are you guys still down in that uh Place
yeah we didn't finish exploring Lauren
okay still exploring the crib I think
yeah now it seems it's finished
yeah it looks like we've all done well
there's something over here
Scrolls
there's dead people with loot oh cool I
love that
my aesthetic
foreign
oh they have so much money
huh I pressed a secret button uh oh nice
mine mine Mario Mario Pez things maybe
it's a trap again oh oh
what's up I missed you guys oh they
don't look very happy to see their Maury
time where is it I hear oh okay
um there's a person next to me oh yeah
one right next to me too
nowhere
oh
get him deadbeats whose side are you on
boy
all right
oh he almost died
I wonder how tanky these guys are I need
to see their health nice shot
but we can take them
now that beats attacking Bijou now
they're surrounding me
ha ha it wasn't a [\h__\h] that looks so
strong though sheesh I have the same
thing I think all right fine I'll go
help my friends but uh
you loot this area before
before
bedtime you're really angry
on a little solo Journey
yeah yeah I was a looting looting things
on the beach
rattle them boys
first one
you've been frosted
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay
yeah bye
hi dummy I love that spell
um
okay
okay does it work yes okay one HP left
use the other one
back off that beat you don't want this
you don't want any
oh
I'm too lucky
they never hit they always miss
ions
let it all out it's good to let it out
uh let the aggressions out
[\h__\h] off the beat back off
deadbeats have a bad aim yeah
out of things to do I already used my
bonus action I'll live through this
surely
oh yeah yeah it should be fine
uh oh I forgot about him
he has a different Target
no no
[Music]
how many enemies are left
only three
they're all pretty beaten up
yeah yeah we we got this
boom
oh you die he did die
hey
yay
nice
let me
what you gonna do yeah what you gonna do
is there there's one left gun
take them down there's still one dude
behind people who kind of yeah behind me
oh SPM I see him okay
I'm here for backups
they worship some kind of they have
money
oh
all right
Cali is he what's in there
what's this guy big treasure beyond my
wildest imagination oh
huh
this scares me I know this guy
he's got pretty eyelashes oh my God if
we found your Romance
[Laughter]
understand this
the Supreme deadbeat right
right heal that nose what a curious way
we just got a little beaten up
now I have a question for the what is
the worth of a single okay this is a
test from sensei okay um
let me see the multiple choice questions
we've been crawling out of a tomb a
peaceful Undead interesting why aren't
you attacking me attack what's the
reason for your question
no attack Mario
[Applause]
again okay sorry
hold on this is this is on the quiz I'm
trying to remember the real answer is
ogre is having a harsh time answering
the questions if it matters is Mine
mine's on the Mortal oh my God
that depends on a person's Deeds
I am sure thou believest was I right
Sensei there are different ways I can
phrase it
I'm satisfied
money Jesus name
[Laughter]
again no join our team and plays oh oh
he will he will
see each other again
[Music]
I got magic Missile magic Missile
thank you
oh actually
do you want this Amulet of lost voices
it lets you speak with the dead oh yeah
that sounds good with your homies okay
here I'll give you yeah cool
you hold on what is this Soul coin
the coins can power infernal engines
um do you want magic Missile
I'm not gonna use it oh sure I can hold
on to it no wait I don't want it top I
don't want to use it
still the controls they still Escape me
okay sorry I remember how to do this hi
Lisa
hi does this do anything other things to
put on
the light cool armor surely there's a
ring on my finger
Yoo-hoo
girl why are you holding a Starion
something I think you just do
ladder way out
same underwear
all right it's a little weird but
alrighty Alan come to us
wait who has a serious underwear yeah is
wearing it
yeah what
no
yes you are what do you mean I'm wearing
it
we're wearing it I checked your
inventory
oh
yeah what
what I didn't
consciously equip anyone's underwear
you're wearing it
there's a ladder
that will find you guys don't worry
Ollie left
because all half of underwear is the
same okay
is he a half elf
I didn't know that that's a lot less fun
um well oh no vampires
[Music]
but I don't know if anybody did that
all right I'm out I'm on the way
where shall we go next team good
question can you show us here before
yeah
oh so I gotta I gotta do the short rest
huh
as the host
S
no worries okay
okay I'm here now
where are we going I don't know you guys
lead the way okay I'll be going this way
I'll follow me boo okay I've been
together strong average the other strong
don't you know you never split the part
where are we going
um actually no not this one not this way
we've been this way we didn't go up this
way yet
um
does
left or right
this way
wait actually actually wait hold on
there's someone over here
uh anyone can short rest but it's good
to talk about it gotcha
oh there's a b oh it's the it's the girl
it's not yeah
oh wait no that no that's not no uh it's
a different situation
no
oh
and if it escapes how will you
oh hi a guest huh
what do we do in Liara
good luck
get rid of them well
um
[Music]
shoot the Trap down oh
but am I saying this to her
yeah I think you're saying it to to the
the teeth
ah
but I don't really have much persuasion
and deception at all yeah do your best I
could I could try to talk to them
because I have both of those
I'll
I guess I'll try this you're your best
difficulty
over ten come on yeah
get out of here tieflings
we check out that blast tea flings tea
it's German by the way for for deep
links
oh really yeah Isn't that cool they just
make it sound fancy
um
good so we came for a look
yeah I'm in dire need of healing ah no
not really but we'll find out where the
campus we need to help to get to get the
the things I ever had yeah oh okay
uh five okay oh that's not bad totally
doable totally doable yes yeah yeah
foreign
traps even the worms
oh cool they're pretty nice I killed
these dudes no wow yeah
um
[Laughter]
well then you're gonna stay up there
too bad
ah
that's pretty funny
you can just kill her and they even
shoot it unsurprising what if we
accidentally shoot her Release Me
Stone
we throw something at it what does guys
rock how about a panda
the atrocities We are Becoming hold on
bro there's no Hopewell is there I know
oh what did I do
release me and she will share it okay
bro go
now share
you're free I'll feed you at it maybe
next time
I must find a crash you will join me oh
hi that was me
all right uh we'll go our separate ways
uh thank you what's that uh what is a
crush it sounds like a French uh food
training grounds she does oh it's like
they're they're chill Camp when infected
with a gay tadpole we must report to
Augusto for purification ah I'm catching
up okay
all right we'll journey together
it's Warrior all right who's the weakest
Warrior
oh
wait at the camp you're the weakest
Warriors
go back to the camp you you're the
weakest go
we're all very strong ladies yeah
also her armor looks like plastic so
yeah it does yeah it does simply made
okay
the thing oh yeah
yeah the thing they just told us about
before they left oh the the area the
campsite they came from where like he's
dancing up ahead yeah we'll get we will
get there for sure I think oh
something's happening quickly Steve hold
on
oh quick little save
oh oh yeah okay this is I think this is
the right direction
I'm for gorblins
more like gift janky
let us send
the yucky one
yeah when the bad guy is there
Goblin
no dad
a lot of facts let's go oh maybe if you
open the gate sooner yeah
that's a that's a life they lost for no
reason
can we help him
yeah we can let's do it let's fight
well let's go well I love will will
Wilson
[Music]
oh yeah Mr Hero man let's go
hero man oh so far
I can't do anything
we are pretty far back I might
what is this like
what am I dashing I want to Dash
yeah we are pretty far away Dash might
be in order
why does it even start when we're so far
away should I get on the hill or stay
yeah
go on the hill
oh wait no no that's I thought that was
one of us
okay uh
um
you're gonna finish the battle before I
get there
hmm
well good luck theme
good luck
really far
these guys look like they can handle
themselves
yeah
Cali is this why we never split the
party exactly yeah this would be the
reason
oh ow
we're doing a little dance
[\h__\h]
oh I get better accuracy the further I'm
away with bows oh
interesting
yeah I thought I thought that was never
one of us that's why I got so close Okay
um
[Music]
that's true it's a dude horn from back
in the day
the old days the medieval days
wow
wow wow Miss twice
right
I pushed this person all help 40 I will
I will risk it but
[Music]
double your movement speed should have
used that before
good good I'm not gonna use it for this
battle I'm going to save it for future
battles whoa whoa I'm sorry
okay cool cool
nice I don't know how I did that but
so you can push and then also attack
still
try the same thing
[Music]
Chad if he's like down here and I'm up
there
can I shoot him because like
realistically I don't think I could
I mean
The High Ground is an advantage you have
The High Ground I mean like down yeah
yeah oh right there because he wouldn't
be what do you mean do you see what I'm
pointing at
because I below you yeah yeah he is kind
of like you know what I'm pointing at I
mean right below like right it doesn't
matter I was
you aim at him and it says and it says
that like he doesn't say your path is
obstructed and it just gives a regular
like percentage
should be okay
well then
hmm
and now we shoot
yes oh nice nice weekend
and right click to Pink Kelly is almost
in the bed I'm almost there hey that
Dash was helpful
to know
you girls know how to Ping because now I
found out yes
uh I think yeah like that
this is what I meant here oh I see I can
see it on the map is it right click or
left like right click and ALT right
click okay oh okay
yes yes
let's see
this
point
hold on okay go help me
good luck go help
hold on they're really far away yeah
I'll use this I think you can scale down
the mountain mm-hmm or the hill that
we're on
there there she is let's see there I am
yeah
[Music]
um
throwing
uh let's see
piercing shot
let's go
oh good crit iCal oh oh he's mad
works are scary yeah I know I can throw
the knives but I don't feel like I don't
know
he hated that he's mad
[Music]
uh hold on
uh
go Pew peel and pretty strong I guess
throwing would be nice what was that
oh
um
so I know I know the order is wrong why
go down yep because they're so far away
I did not see that
yeah right look at the Rings thought so
they're they're front lining I'm in the
back
oh that person 's dead
yeah we couldn't save them we failed
them
he'll be revived surely
okay
oh I can't do this more accuracy for
being up High
[Music]
um
you stabbed him okay I'll stab this one
then
that was a poke
but good good just sprotted at him
better than nothing
[Music]
I put the mark on
it oh on him huh
um
okay oh oh that's AOE damage Ross yeah
it would appears well thank God I missed
everybody
oh good well now I know that I have AOE
damage on that one
you guys left I think they're pretty
much outnumbered I think we'll
definitely win
yeah
we need to fight more things so we can
level one more time
I want more stuff yeah we're weak oh oh
that guy's dead too and they're dead oh
oh
[Music]
no
okay all I can do is stab so I'm just
gonna keep stabbing
foreign
[Music]
I didn't do anything to him
oh what what happened that was but it
doesn't like you leaving the dead goblin
the goblin is a bad guy I think you may
have accidentally looted one of the dead
people
Julie okay can we run away kill him
uh is he temporarily hostile or permaha
style
I'm sorry we put him to sleep or let me
see I think I think we both did it Bijou
I'm not sure oh I don't know I just
thought the goblin
you guys can turn off you guys can
toggle non-lethal attacks and we need to
fight him I think
yeah there's like a switch so like you
know where you have all your spells and
stuff like go to the first wheel and
it's like at the top wait not available
sure
goodbye okay sorry will sorry
one person toggles it for the entire
time oh oh he's after me knock knock who
did it it might resent you but they
won't be actually hostile main capacity
that's harmed okay good okay
come on be nice pretty
let's go nice one
can we just enter
I'm leaving yeah
don't worry you hit him he'll never be
your friend we just gotta run from him
don't enter they say one person says
don't enter
yeah
charm just means he won't attack you
you're gonna run away and then flee to
Camp aha
oh so you have to run away and get far
enough so it disengages through combat
well we love will I want him on our team
yeah it Will's great he's awesome
be nice
I wouldn't even lose it wasn't even me
he's not up for reasoning
okay just just run oh
I remember I remember that yeah I should
have remembered that was gonna happen
it won't work on him he can't be an
enemy please
there he says I might have to reload if
this goes poorly no no no no we'll just
have to run away for far enough
doesn't like the green people Theresa it
looks like a heart I like it run away
can I disengage now
yum can I can I flee from combat
am I far enough
how do you how you tell if you're far
enough I don't think there is a far
enough
get out of the battle
[Music]
27 meters isn't so much okay well I'm
far enough now okay he's gonna chase me
oh wow me alone
it's fine
and a dream my dreams
I I spam the red button the red button
didn't work
see
right I should be okay flea combat yes
Wii combat flea combat it's not working
right
is it working for you yeah I flee I fled
to Camp how come
from me I'm like are you not far enough
I got pretty far away I'm using well
you're using dashed yeah I'm like super
far I also have fled to combat
yeah his eyes are open just keep keep
running keep running you can flee from
combat and go to Camp if you are far
enough from your enemies and it's it
says it's far enough now it's the
difference oh no they're closed
how many camps are there
this one's pretty
can I buy arrows here
yeah it won't it won't let me press the
button okay I'll keep running I guess
maybe game
this works
oh
a collaboration it's okay I'm still in
combat too so nonetheless
wait oh he's coming after you people are
you pressing the disengage thingy
I am the bottom white red one okay I'm
pressing the bottom white red one but it
I think it's bugged I can say how many
meters you're away from him because for
me it said I need 27 meters
I was out of his range because it didn't
say the 27 meters anymore but now he got
closer so I don't know
but he's chasing me
well they say that he likes you when he
chases you so
look I it doesn't say 27 meters anymore
because I'm far enough but it won't let
me disengage still
I am going to perish going without me
remember me
yeah what you got something to say about
what I'm doing over here no I'm just
kind of concerned
um admiring how do I volunteer without
killing him is that even I think he's
gonna kill me
I can hide okay
that I have a great respect for privacy
for instance especially my own
we can reload if you want we that battle
was easy so
yeah you can just do it again
you want to reload it must be unarmed or
using oh I can maybe I can Bonk him
yeah hold on I'll try to oh okay I'll
try to Bonk him hold on one second yeah
as long as the damage is
what fits away yeah
[Music]
unconscious okay I need to be unarmed so
I need to take off
weapons okay come here I'm gonna Bonk
you
foreign
I'm chilling you you look so beautiful
they're basking in the sunlight but also
partially being covered by the beautiful
leaves above you
thank you the sunlight work Wonders on
you
guys Romancing each other maybe we
should
a little bird dancing over here
well well well you shouldn't have looked
at them
[Applause]
this is your chance you get for being a
dirty loot Goblin oh another chance
oh my God why
why did nobody nobody carry away the
dead body of hysterion you still here no
leave it there it's hilarious
to another camp
[Music]
to bring them back to life well maybe my
skeleton friend can help for a price
um yeah
hey buddy can you help me bring my
friend back to life
I crossed that no Cali
Yankee can you help me change my class
uh resurrect someone
resurrect Bagels
wow
oh
okay we're gonna bring you back oh thank
you
surely he'll forgive you
listen now
really thanks for noticing as if you
have turned bad snout is any better
thank you hello hello there you are are
you back there at the battlefield or
where are you girls now no I'm in I'm in
campus okay okay I'm talking to a lady
might want to rest I have one HP yeah
can we yeah
what should we do we have one short rest
left but maybe we should just sleep we
should just do a long last problem let's
just do a long one oh that [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
foreign
oh oh this oh he's still here yeah huh
we just we just keep bringing his dead
body with us
I guess so that we can one day bury him
which is very respectful exactly that's
what it's all about the respect are we
ending the day
yeah yeah because so just to heal yeah
okay again
[Music]
someone in Camp still wishes to speak to
you go to bed anyway yeah
Marissa if you want to speak to me just
speak to me
I mean I don't know who would want to
talk to me
why can't we
[Music]
if you're too shy you can DM me you know
every day I spend in your DMs yeah
all right good morning everybody
good morning good morning dead person
good morning you guys ready to go back
into the fries
I really hope he isn't still mad at me
well we'll find out won't we hope it's
safe
fingers crossed shall we enter The Grove
there's a lot of blood around here nice
yeah that's that's where I died
this bagel's Blood right there whatever
reason the the living room
is he done
is it safe now
hopefully
yeah
level
ooh do I get to choose a subclass now I
wonder
I think subclass additional rage charge
nice
okay I get to choose a subclass gonna go
Berserker okay need to take a moment to
maybe look at the Spells
do what you gotta do so don't run away
everybody okay no more cleric I'm done
bring a Clarity yeah I think the one I
wanted to do was a college of lore oh
should I go for this one now it's a good
one girls
always wanted me to take this one
um
yes okay
and then so is it even with animal
enemies like the work just now that I
could speak with
or just like random doggos and so on yes
also with the works
oh okay I'm just gonna hit the shop
really quick don't mind me I can now
speak with animals
let's go oh animal Whisperer should be
helpful what is this should I take
Shield or magic oh wait magic Missile
useful I gave you a one magic Missile
scroll so you could test it out well not
now obviously or I'm taking orb
nevermind I'm getting an orb or pretty
good yeah Thunder damage lightning
damage okay ignore okay
do not bear
do not this was already the one I wanted
to be I think
hey
that was what I already did
I think beforehand yeah I remember that
um
let me check it out
master
[Music]
cast speak of animals friends are strong
as is Flash okay long rest
so until we rest I can speak for any
animal are there any animals here I
haven't seen anything
are you animals
I can use Chad I can use frenzy without
using rage first correct
Pals
hmm
do this
oh wait why do I have to press this
again
and can I speak with my own animal
frenzy replaces rage
I see
it's a better rage
look at that little guy
I'm taking this
I am taking your
um
why is it following you
my best friend
all right guys I walked into something
oh she's
she said why are you listening wait what
happened what happened I don't I don't
know
be in here oh I see you're in the hollow
I was gonna talk to the shopkeeper
anyways
yes can I talk to that bear now
can I talk to your crab I'm not wait you
also have to speak with
maybe then I shouldn't have taken speak
of animals
hello
I'm talking with a cow
I have another son
oh the cow didn't want to talk to me
let's freaking
[Music]
I am going to bring in never saw
new good armor oh that's sick all right
I stole your Raven
huh you're Raven's mine
how could you be Savage your Raven likes
me
can't tell them uh you know I I
understand it because I like you too it
is what it is you know
pretty good oh
cute yes you can talk to these uh you
can talk to these cows I'm doing it
right now
because I'm hungry eat my eat my Raven
maybe
oh my God you need Army oh yeah you're
right I don't need armor cause I'm a
barbarian I Gotta Get Naked
oh oh God I forgot uh Callie can you do
me a favor what's up uh when you have
time can you save and reload the game
I'm stuck in combat music probably
because of the whale thing oh
you've got it let's go just a moment
no prob
which is the healing really quick this
creature
oh
ah
what I just rolled a success
everyone
all right let's see
oh
all right quick load
is a cow being mean to you oh sorry had
to quick load the game oh it's okay
could have said something I am very
sorry I should have said I'm quick
loading the game
pardon me
big pardon dude I'm sorry about the
power I have I don't know what's
happening
I'm like I've walked away let's deal
with people there are people like
praying and they were really mean they
did not want to let me in
um
no no one's fighting me I'm just talking
to people
oh good the music's back thank you no
problem
ah wait this one's good
come on give me a good roll they're
gonna eat you cow you better tell me
yeah
yeah 16.
Battlefield blood not resist death
embrace it
it's my job
that's all I have to say besides and
apparently animals in this game are
jerks
I believe it
this this this
um this pig wants a mate
um
[Laughter]
hello I was gonna say looks like Shadow
yeah that's the one I summoned I can
summon two apparently
and another one
there are different choices I can have a
boar I can kick the butter excuse me
let's not kick the bird
s fine I won't kick the bird are we down
in the Grove
honey honey I love these random animals
following us
how'd you guys get down in there they're
kind of guarded away I just walked in
they were like cool awesome is not for
sale
right
must have done something right okay
oh yeah I held to the bird
can I still kick it don't don't hurt the
bird heart fatty be nice with the birds
I think that the Druids won't like that
yeah it might get a little offended
though I'm gonna join this cute from the
bird you pickpocket bikini pocket the
bird
thanks
did you just take it what
happened what's happening
[Laughter]
you did it
realized I thought I would talk to it
but I took it they don't seem to have
noticed
they didn't notice it was you the thing
y'all just lost house
oh gosh
you have started a conflict
yeah oops
yeah that sounds like a good idea maybe
we should just reload the stage
well okay if we kill them we lose the
Bear boo boo but yeah let's reload I'm
so sorry
[Music]
this is wait hold on there's a little a
slight spoiler though which is why I'm
confused in the campaign there's a child
that steals it
oh huh yeah well today it was me
huh
so it was supposed to happen
I mean I think
maybe maybe not it's just a difference
of who does it try to steal it and she
failed
apparently it just tried okay
um let's try this again
um
why are you trying to deceive the cow
now my feet fail before I before I
didn't fail watch me lose my dice roll
this time I already saw the oh yeah I
talked to the bird again
scarier I feel like I'm stuck in a Time
Loop man this is the first time I'm
talking to this cow
so why don't we actually uh doing in
here and then looking for someone
looking for the looking for the Healer
we're looking for Nettie
she said she told me where she is if you
talk to Epis
apocuses
she's right over by me and bee boo by
the pig
I use few words
Polo
YOLO bolo
hmm
I could go this way
can I have your key
little bit of leg
you like
oh
superstition
jump the blood getting to the bottom of
evolo we believe in you
oh I found I found another barn Timber
nice you guys can connect
I'm talking to a Squidward
Musk
[Music]
what
do you think the squirrel lunges at your
foot and bites it oh no
[Laughter]
I must take the thing where I'm strong
at
DJ stole from the bird
I'm gonna kill them
I killed a squirrel because I had
critical success in kicking
ah
well that's so chaotic
what do we do you have any loot
oh my God
I only we only have to kill these two
people okay
you guys are fighting there's only five
above me
five five in my battle
you can't steal things
[Music]
you gotta tell me hey Mori I'm about to
do a really risky action save the game
so shall we reload another time okay
okay
maybe you can do it in the next life one
more quick load time
again then we lose the bear because we
just gotta play for okay well okay if I
if I lose I won't steal the key okay
listen it was the birds why did humans
get
stealing the birds keys I don't
understand nature they love nature
they're Druids no yeah don't steal
anything don't steal [\h__\h] you want to be
friends with these guys we can steal
from the Goblins okay well no it seems
like it seems like they're being kind of
corrupted they're being kind of like
racist to the thieflings and stuff you
know like they're they're yeah they're
bad yeah so I think
is listen to me she's in a room through
the carved door deeper in the Grove yep
so that's what she says
an eye dot touching the bird because I'm
scared okay I'm gonna talk to the bird
yeah again
oh my God I want me to save the game oh
thank God no it's okay
if I fail
I know how you really want to play it
it's fine don't worry about it uh
okay I'm gonna add guidance
I'm gonna go find that barred lady again
she was cute okay it's good I beat the I
beat the ball where is the way you're
not just looking into a mirror
I mean cute fart lady I only know of one
yeah
she's another tiefling Bard well so I'm
kind of curious I think I wonder if she
can join our team
okay save it so I don't have to kill
this bird yeah all right
we're good all good and then yeah I'm
chilling by the stone door what's going
on here where we can find the Healer
inside here wow
hello there buddy oh
stone door yep right over here
once we go inside the healers inside
okay I'm waiting
see
the whole team ready to enter
save the game
I saved the game yes
all right into the stone door
shall we follow
yeah sure that'd be cool I got the
cutscene there's a small child hero no
oh
oh wait it's like a dragon snake
and I will cast out every stranger as a
child I do not
uh what is the girl's actual crime one
of your guards outside said you wanted
to see me here I am
glorio paid no care about this
Idol in thanks
wrath look her up
she remains here all right well that's a
little messed up I do have a moral
compass it's not cool devil
Tila is restless ah she's so mean come
cooker
surely do it
all right um
let's go Mario pay mad all right I got
these added so let's go please work
let's go let's go
yeah
I
can't see her roll
I need something
Let Her Go nice persuasion my Grace has
its limits oh that was really cool
moriope
oh how
yeah house is great I think you guys
will really like Allison
um
so cool chest here I'm not gonna open it
of course because that would be thievery
[Music]
silver
what a pretty dog
with nice goodies in here that I will
not be taking because we're friends
where are you guys I went into that
where you said Nettie was wait I didn't
yeah
I didn't I don't know where that was
either okay I'll leave and then you can
see where my icon is and then just go
there yeah yeah yeah
here I come okay
all right I'm outside so follow where my
icon is
okay
okay wait yeah I see it okay I can get
there you can go back in thank you all
right you're welcome I save game
I save game every two seconds yeah just
take it over the bedroom if I
accidentally seal the idol again
oh did you find the Healer yes
nice oh I'll start a conversation
good woman
oh
[Music]
excuse me and more important than some
bird now whoa everything I can do to
help
it's like so weirdly what a weird bird
um
I'm looking for Nettie need help now
need help
do you know anything about mind players
[Music]
I've got plenty of them
um I have a tadpole in my hand
I wish it was a frog tadpole
um
that'd be kind of gross too though what
other kinds are there it's not like a
frog hopped into my own but does that
means sarcasm
help me
I'll do what I can come but there's four
of us can you help all of us please
let's go follow
this one oh all of this stuff that she
has I can't pick up sad
she'll get mad at me
you should you should have expected to
be a thief
I really should huh
closer look
I stand on his body
crack the Druid find whatever bro he
runs to and report back to me remember
you are only a scout do not engage not
kill anyone simply observe and return I
shall decide what we do next M what who
are you talking to
I was reading a letter on this person's
body
I'm hoping for less grave cured so you
killed him and laid him on the table is
everyone being captured by mind didn't
think it was a common experience
um
was she not answering me
ignoring you giving the other cold
shoulder
she's got a stick it's pointy
at least that's what oh she does have a
stick what are you gonna do with that
hit me with the pointy end these things
still
we have you can use the amulet to speak
with him oh nice idea
oh the bird does look like Shadow
oh God Jesus what are the cats doing
okay
no
tell me oh baby
I need symptoms
oh I have a bug
yeah you see that right
uh I wonder if what I click is actually
though not what it seems to be uh
um I'll just check the first one okay
okay
not that the others know they're victims
of course how do you pick up the
parasite
Halton was desperate to find where all
this was happening
okay uh
she is asking I mean okay
there's no problem
should I go for the first one I think
that yeah I go for the first one okay
yeah they're okay they're safe I checked
on them they just knocked something over
so I'll be straight with you
you're dangerous I'm dangerous
[Applause]
you deserve a chance to save yourself
thank you I'll watch you put the stick
away
oh cool okay she's not gonna Focus
I'm sorry can you say that word again
how did she pronounce it was it wyvern
or wyvern
Library
all right let's go
I swear to me ill swallow it if you feel
any symptoms
I thought you could kill me what about
that branch of yours why coated in a
fatal toxin
you're funny
you said I was gonna kill you she's very
honest though saying that
she likes us now but I had to be sure at
least she's nice versus like the mean
lady outside yeah definitely yeah she's
pretty chill
or not yes
I swear I hope it doesn't come to that
but I mean we can use it on people yeah
we'll be useful later I never once saw a
mind flare infection then suddenly
there's dozens is she Irish a lot of us
Master Houston and I were tracking pick
up a hint whoa what is uh what I like it
what's going on
apparently we can kill cows
all the The Jerk lady yeah what's that
one that set the whole Grove against
itself I don't know
I think we could I think we should kill
her
changing
first
I yeah maybe maybe we get we get house
at first and then we can we can murder
her yeah I mean I I love violence yes I
agree with seven gruesome days later no
we only have seven days
we need to stop sleeping
it's already been like two days right
because
right yeah it doesn't seem it doesn't
seem like we're turning into mind
players is like the is the thing oh I
see we're special so maybe it might be
more than seven days
um
[Music]
hard to say they were special of course
have been converging on an old Temple we
have plot armor we're the main
characters okay perfect we're heading
that way he saw a chance to get him oh
okay let's go find him whatever the
house said okay he didn't make it back
um
let's go and get him
so don't get him to find him but the
place is rotten with goblins it's okay
we can kill the Goblins yeah
technically speaking I mean kill someone
carrying their parasite oh if you can
find house and get him one of us one of
us we can discover what he learned and
perhaps he can save your life okay how's
that sound all right okay no no find
them let's get him it would mean
everything to the groom to me okay
Here Comes Goblin slayers
oh all I can say for sure as they all
went to the old Temple of saloon
Mr halson didn't make it sounds like
there's one Roger okay Temple temples
are full of treasures remember your oath
hi
okay let's go let's go let's go
oh yeah
well before I accidentally steal
something
hold on I'm sorry guys just a moment my
cats are batting something around out
there and I don't want them to be
batting around a tiny thing they might
try to swallow so is it the tadpole okay
is this so should I uh you keep this
because it's single use is this like I
needed to get you a new outfit
yeah it seems like I could use it keep
it
drink it
I can Code 11 with it yeah amazing thing
I have a serious armor too
oh yeah
apparently there's a secret room if we
check behind a bookcase
all right we're all fine I took it I
took it away from them we're good I
don't know how they found a little thing
to play with a new toy let's get out of
here
wait wait apparently there's a secret
thing apparently behind the book behind
one of the bookcases
but all the bookcases are red meaning
like yeah meaning if we touch them we'll
uh we'll get into call back save the
game oh wait
wait perception four
open locks maybe we need to be friends
with them first I don't know
read Stone tab
yeah there's there's apparently a chest
so it'll lead us to her room oh
maybe we can sneak
oh apparently this door can open but
it's red
oh
does it say locked or is it just yeah
and it's also red ah
oh
attitude negative five bagel
what did I do what are you doing I
didn't even do anything though
are you sure
it's readily making people angry can you
do it oh
that's a bigger woof
I'm sorry cute no one no one fought me
though I want to talk to the rat
yeah the rats surely have a lot to say
can I kick this one too oh did you find
it oh I found the servants what about
you
oh
spawned it simply Bears it's teeth
boring
I want to kill the rats
okay
I can't I can't they won't let me
do anything a little cruel
I mean I think you probably can you
probably could kill the rat if you well
I know
I don't think The Druids are like okay
I don't know how to get into it it's
locked oh
oh I heard it click probably need a key
maybe you could pickpocket the key oh
wait how did you guys
walk around oh yeah you go from up here
hi I thought I picked up a thief kit
I mean
it's true
[Music]
same my sleight of hand uh only got six
oh I can roll
yeah yeah I'll try it give it a shot
nice
you succeeded
all right this Goblin it's up to you
I just want to see what's in it I just
want to see what's in him
we're not okay no one saw me so yeah
that was a big secret secret and they
can't just sense that it's on you right
so we're fine
what did you take what was inside uh
let's see there was a ruby there was a
okay I'll read it okay
the Mars Chris crossing the page don't
look scribe so much as slash uh kaga
swamp docs tree meet me alone allodon
okay
hold on wasn't that one of the rats oh
oh we got a quest no we got a quest for
it you know Journal updates
is one of the rats hmm
okay
Fred talk to me
that whisperer
do we follow all of them I don't know I
only heard the last word all of them
that's all I registered in my brain
yeah I remembered one thing and it was
oh maybe God doesn't say anything
is not actually a rat maybe we can make
him say something
shape shift into a right
cool
um
I'm beginning to feel like that's all
right wait
hold on
let me talk to you again all right
watches your movements but yeah speak to
the rat
no okay it really doesn't want to talk
okay
[Music]
swamp or something
yeah I think yeah well let's go okay
we'll talk to the tafeling leader and
they she's like get them out
ah yeah that's right get them out so we
could just like escort the tifflings out
of here but um
you heard what happened to the squirrel
and raise Flora we are the Thunder and
we are the rain we shatter Mankind and
grow new life in its place okay
I'm looking at your outfit people I just
realized can you give me your cleric
outfit
oh can you wear heavy armor I don't know
I don't think you or can you wear medium
armor or is it better and just I just
want I just want to change out of what
I'm wearing now here I'll give you I'll
get oh oops
I'll give you
asterion's clothes here you go okay
I don't know where they'd go my items
perhaps yeah just checking your bag
I thought I did too I don't think I need
to pick them up I don't have it
wait what did I give it to
eh
I I give it to you right
yeah you have it a padded armor okay
okay I was in the wrong I was in the
wrong
uh can I uh live for uh two minutes or
one minute
go for it
we can uh eat some chips too
Cali yeah you're in um underwear yeah uh
so the reason for that is because
um as like a bird as a barbarian yeah
I've read that it's better that you
don't have uh armor oh okay are you sure
about that
I may have been missed what
I may have been LED astray here
um they're basically correct they don't
count as armor okay
your normal clothes don't count as arm
okay well I mean this is bad I mean
it's not bad
well you have you have like a six pack
yeah you know she she works out it's
almost an eight pack you know we'll get
it there though we'll get it
all right is that does that look better
are you happy in New Clothes Marissa
they look good on you yeah yeah I feel
much more comfortable not in the ugly
default clothes
I could I could play a little ditty
they're not what I meant to do
you can have bad Tyrone it's not it's
just the equipment armor you don't need
gotcha
well I can work with that hey nice tune
I like it what the [\h__\h]
did you what was that what was there
what even was there she fell apart
there was nothing in the pot
you could throw the pot
well I just wanted to show it guys
[Applause]
look at that g string okay look mine are
way more decent than yours okay but I
love the time isn't the top so cute like
oh my God it is but put some pants on
please
panties are the ones that that guy was
wearing I doubt it yeah yeah maybe maybe
not yeah
[Music]
why are you so scared it's just a
natural body of a natural person my
underwear is like Warriors underwear in
the cheeks I like yours yours
how do I take my clothes off
you look like you're about to go to
Coachella
[Laughter]
hair the Buns the colorful buns and
those clothes you look like you're ready
to go
it's really likes Coachella
kind of cute that's kind of nice oh wow
and her you will look visual but not at
me
keep it on keep it on no stop
stop crying
together oh my God please give me a jump
scare warning
[Applause]
yeah what is the stream turning into can
we make story progress soon we're
supposed to go beat up
um Banner please of me and Marissa okay
thank you and Cali too in those Club yes
okay I don't think they're unfashionable
yeah you know the cheeks are protected
yeah
they're very strong I need another face
to throw at you guys
okay how do we make progress where what
do we do where do we go oh yeah yeah we
got distracted no not at all very very
distressed no no no no a little bit
that's okay
um now here's what we can do
would you guys like to go to find the
goblin Camp yeah let's go
all right I really want to feel the idol
again you know no no I don't think you
should do that
let's save let's save and test our power
level what's going on here all right
okay
get close so we can all come back
together what what are you
what do you really want to talk to
you okay wait okay
goodness to answer a few questions
pertaining to the Goblins you
encountered at the game I won't grab it
I won't grab it until you guys say
you're ready
but I just want to see if we can take
take the idol you know all righty wait
can you hide subscribe that I'm trying I
mean there's a lot of people around I
think that the site of them is a little
too widespread
you search your mind
successfully required I succeeded in
yesterday let's go unbelievable
uh I'm ready to get steamrolled I don't
call them the same as only LOL
yeah no they they're they're questioning
they're like why are you sneaking around
they're watching
this is a legend
he's a legend and the dragon they had
marching in the rear was it something oh
grass or silver I don't have an idea
okay
oh yeah he's a lore important NPC
legendary figure in DND
okay
uh there was no dragon how do I how do I
play my songs for some reason I only
have the option to do bartic inspiration
and I don't want that I want to do my
actual song playing is there no like
regulars I I think I broke performance
because I don't remember how to get to
my regular performance
would come watch you play your
instrument and then biboo can pickpocket
them from behind oh yeah
someone's here
maybe don't pickpocket him maybe maybe
whatever I can see
okay here let me see if we can distract
these people maybe ah probably not but
yeah
I'll Stand between these ones
we're busy
I think so too but just just we're just
seeing they're doing like their
blessings
I think they're ignoring you
yeah
you're gonna get thrown super hard
[Music]
whatever you mind
ignore me
oh the boy likes it
is
so adorable look at him look at him
dancing he's taking his little what so
cute
she's so adorable I'm done okay saved
are we actually crying why not okay
okay come here and I'm gonna do
something okay okay what are you gonna
do
okay
go get it there's a fallen Cloud go get
it
huh
nice okay wait oh no they noticed anyway
oh God immediately I mean they were
blessing it like two seconds ago
remove The Outsiders
welp I'm
yeah watch his skull get bashed in it
was pretty pretty sick
oh yikes you know that hurt him
oh yeah that's gotta be painful
[Music]
but like oh he's feeling it was his
fault
no yeah you're just blaming the
twinklings for a lot of things
apparently I don't understand
[Music]
oh
it's not very nice
are we battling or are we running
battling of course we wanted to fight
something right shoot the bear
yeah tough it
okay he's gonna try to kill us
[Laughter]
we're gonna fight guys so many people
yeah I don't know man I I don't think
there's a way to win yeah we can try
okay
uh well we could all always just reload
again too if you guys are true I guess
yeah then since our since our plan to
steal the idol didn't work with the with
the smoke cloud
what was that
yeah I don't think you can steal the
Idol without getting everybody upset
sadly
I want it though
oh
attack a creature's eyes and blind it
right about the bear for evil well we
can't
I'm gonna kill the bear
good job shadow oh
Haley's still naked
I mean yeah and webbed you
alrighty let me test my test my bro
I feel like
I feel like Frodo
nice
now Armstrong
can't do the throw bonus action already
used I fly somewhere safer
no probably not
dang
oh that's cool I'll throw them
apparently they kill all the teeth
Flames when you do this so even if you
beat it all the time yeah it's a little
messed up silence
[Music]
I have a good idea if if you guys want
to kill a bunch of stuff we can go to
the goblin temp yeah
wasting our time
I was trying to win a battle we are
going to lose against the Bears did I
draw my ax are you kidding me
gently heated your metal and melted
yourself
Cali a voice of reasons
I I remember where the goblin Camp is by
the way okay make our way over there
yeah I remember nice I follow I have
only ever gotten as far as the goblin
can happen past that I do not know what
happens
okay let's see so let's we gotta exit
the town first I'm following you yeah
just follow follow Mario Pez lead let's
go let's look at Cali's butt while she's
walking up the stairs
let's go let's go oh yeah there's a
shopkeeper by the way if you guys want
to buy items like healing potions
uh up here uh past these cows there's uh
a merchant does he have ice arrows
selling stuff here oh maybe I think I
saw ice arrows really I'm pretty sure
that I saw some in the inventory but you
might want to yeah grab grab some stuff
really quick
why are you selling
no longer need armor
see but I don't think it does have ice
Arrows by the way yeah I think there's
another one on the way as well what
can I sell all these weapons uh guys I'm
sorry what I'm stuck oh wait no I got
out I got out it's fine it's fine oh oh
one at a time yeah one at a time that's
too realistic I know I'm gonna leave and
go this way I'm just gonna open up this
part of my map oh I can actually we can
fast travel there and go there instead
you know when you guys are done shopping
okay I'm just selling stuff okay
oh money how do I get him to give me
money oh give me money
give me all your money
oh um
you can do that
I won't leave
refugees adventurous definitely has a
frost Arrow it is and suddenly we're
overwhelmed
can I
make use of your services is there
anything you need yes at first if you do
the ritual will be coming
first talked about this
doesn't will normally appear around here
you guys just some bits
um doesn't he like show up and he's like
hey and he's like teaching the yeah
he's not here
uh is that very bad
wait I don't know who that is but I'm
down to find whoever oh no no you don't
need car lot
okay I don't think
man that's a shame
the hot demon yeah
[Music]
um
do I need any of this can I I wonder
I wonder if he's where like he killed me
um
Vengeance first
should we go look I'm gonna go check
around where I died
I really hope he doesn't agree on me if
he's there though
maybe we just need to have a chat with
him yeah
oh if you go to Carlock first he will
find you apparently oh okay so we could
we could go find her yeah what's
bartering
kind of
we need to look up first oh he is there
oh I'm scared I'm scared
did we just go talk to him you want to
say the game maybe yeah hello
hello are you okay hold on I wait I have
no money oh I can't even click on him
yeah I can't and I have no single money
how is that possible we're probably gold
I got gold but didn't I did I I feel
like I picked up money before
you remember opening like a chest yeah
several I mean I thought it was gold
oh well I'll sell things
gotta loot more
yeah mostly you can pick up stuff you
can sell all of them
I dug that up that was my treasure thank
you I'm never helping you again
yeah I'll give you I'll give you some of
the loot you wanna
um across the party
how much gold was it money is shared in
the party it looks like yeah
zero okay did people use up all the
groups money oh I didn't I didn't buy
anything it's weird because it doesn't
matter by anything
well it was definitely on zero and now I
I made some money but
I'll try attacking him we don't want him
to aggro is shared apparently so we can
but we don't have she has to send it to
you
it says party gold it's 329. aha
nice so I guess technically we can use
each other's money yeah I mean you guys
need some gold I'll give you some gold
so we have I can just access your
inventory right now I could just take
y'all's stuff right now don't do that I
won't but I could is the thing
too so next time I see oil I can no you
can't make it go boom
yes I can I will I will punt you so far
over the mountain if you steal something
else
we'll put you so far
okay
um
okay and anything else that's worth
buying here
it'd be common drops luckily really
okay
oh yeah I have the amulet I can't talk
to that Dead Guy totally forgot when
you're gonna talk to the Dead Guy
it's cool I'll talk to him later when I
quit this
please I want to look and see if I can
buy anything uh yes uh green green bow
huh
sorry I'm blind uh uh
I'm blind I'm so blind
um
this swing okay okay that's that's okay
cool insufficient gold
uh oh that's expensive I'm never
reaching that money uh
yeah
yeah maybe another time Sylvanas guide
your path oh
they donate gold
attitude that is
I won't leave them behind I wonder if
she'll notice
maybe you never time
oh you do what are you doing here
I did something good go check yeah yeah
what'd you do look in your inventory
and I don't know what's different
look at Cali's inventory I see gold
I don't know how to even look at other
people's planetaries
press tab I love this it's just mine
okay
do you not do not see my message
is there a message I don't see any scrap
of paper
oh it's not reflected
um
man too bad I spelled something for you
in your inventory but I guess it doesn't
oh I see it says hi
yeah yeah it says hi oh futures
no you just care about your stupid
apprenticeship why are you fighting I'm
gonna take your word for it
hi
sorry
what's the idea yeah that's very strange
I mean it's that
she just placed the items in an order
that makes it look like a letter
I see
I'm still in
ah Kelly's playing on Console oh no I'm
using a controller oh it's different
with a controller yeah I'm I'm ready
okay let's go ladies we got some goblins
to kill let's gobble those goblins up
gobble
[Laughter]
need a turkey in person no I think so
yeah you don't want to why not they're
[\h__\h] huge they're terrifying that's
like a body you be boo I'm sure all of
you have seen a turkey for Thanksgiving
before I don't know what I mean like
alive
they make so powerful when I eat one you
know I have some big ones that used to
live near the old my old place
[Music]
I remember seeing some cross the road
once and I was like holy [\h__\h]
can I Dash like now no oh my God
my phone before we go to the goblin
place I want to make a little detour I
remember the whole thing okay all right
there's it's combat though okay we're
ready to fight
let me save yeah I go ah already saved
let's go we gotta go this way oh we
gotta see the dog too hold on yeah the
doggy dog the dog's over here
yeah we were just acknowledging them
we're like they're dead
[Music]
wait wait don't don't loot the body
accidentally okay
[Music]
oh God I hate when animal mouths move
when they're spraying humans yeah
I wish it would just you just hear the
sound
someone candy
I believe
I believe in people power
cute there's death in your scent
yeah
you should go
your friend is injured I think your
friend is [\h__\h] dead
he's with his God now I'm sorry not over
yet
wake up
we have a Revival scroll
Revival fly I have a skeleton yeah here
come with us come with us
I won't leave him oh he's hatching oh is
he Hachiko
now it is Court
his name is scratch
um here
follow my son
never leaves the side office
okay now now he may show up
okay another detour we are going over
here there's combat this is the combat
detour all right let's do it
I'm ready to fight
always ready to fight
me too me too I want more fight
we spend too much time in that City
yeah yeah yeah
we got a goblins soon and then we got
this yeah we can definitely take all
those goblins
I need you to kill the mom and not kill
the child why you guys remember this
yeah yeah yeah yeah kill them kill them
not the kids we can get Hella cash okay
yeah
oh okay yeah that's that's okay she's
really mean
yeah maybe you guys should wait for me
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah it's a minute not
enter without y'all yeah spread out
super far I love the little animals
yeah okay let's go oh okay okay
you can talk to her actually because you
can talk to animals uh okay
oh have a little chat how do I talk
without uh killing uh oh no just walk up
oh okay okay
I didn't mean to speak face oh do you
have animal handling no hmm well time to
get eaten
let's be fine lunch time we were
planning on that anyway so oh please oh
lunch time yum yum yum yum yum yums
yummy
so pretty
how bear
a few times
we have to kill it
oh
nice striking while the iron is hot I
guess
was up in the air like she just don't
care go it's kind of Awesome
you just ascended
[Laughter]
oh oh
[Music]
um
can't go so far so go as far as you can
oh fly to Target position
[Music]
I wonder if I could throw your bird no
Shadow go you probably could you have
enough strength for it
don't forget about the crap
hold on a sec don't worry
um
the baby is coming to defend his mommy
um this is a bonus Ash and then I can
also do a rage attack
oh all right
I feel like you're scarier with
underwear on
um
she's cute
little bleed
oh
these days oh God it's really angry
oh The Voice came out of it
who killed the baby no no the baby's
still alive
I don't know but the baby's still okay
um
crab crab no crab attack crab cannot
attack crap oh maiming pinch I'm like
one step too far away
uh
wow I believe crap Maybe
maybe act as a fate baby
that would have been so epic if the crab
would have gotten the kill
ER okay
and now and now listen to the baby yeah
some people talk to animals preferably
where where was the baby where is it
yeah you can't kill it it's over here
hit save let's save real quick before
one of us accidentally kills it okay
I'll talk to babble did you guys get the
egg yes
single strike will speechless
[Music]
why do we have to leave him here we will
find steel presents yeah he'll come back
to kill us because we killed his mom no
no we we will take him as a pet yeah oh
there's a shrine back here isn't there
yeah yeah look we can't do anything with
it because it's sealed by Magic
I want to go look
I remember correctly
I see a chest yeah sealed by Magic so if
you try and open it
I think me and uh oh yeah we might wanna
you know heal
[Laughter]
ing
oh my god do it do a short rest yes
please oh yeah sure no problem
nice
so it when you try to open the chest is
that when you got damaged yeah
does that happen to everybody who
touches their chest that's the volume
yeah I think so
I want to touch it
I know
read ER dedicated to Saloon imploring
all to accept the moon maiden's blessing
and share in her Bounty just an old
prayer I like her no religion failed
oh no wait I think I have religion
there's a prayer behind the statue
how do you jump again put that note in
front of the chest it's one of the um
actions on the
um the second one in the first row okay
I'm gonna guess over here right here I
took I picked it up I'm gonna send the
prayer to one of you guys to use it
because I could not do it so who has
good religion I have plus one I think
it works
eh
did you get stuff
oh
what
necklace Bloodstone Idol
pendant
cool
okay now we can go kill some goblins
let's go pray words all right goblins
goblin killing time
that one suck yeah
you don't have to pass the check if you
just know what to do yeah that's cool
wow
pretty nice
that's true just an old prayer a dummy
oh I mean I'm not smart I might be dumb
no I'm not stupid
do we have who's the smartest one in the
in the party again me in terms of uh
Dame stats
ha ha
ha I see
oh I see
okay
upstairs goblins yep up here yeah we got
across oh wait yeah that's right oops
across the bridge and then we go that
way yeah I will wait
um
yeah I'm trying to catch up
um any charismatic people wanna lead the
way
hello we're both we're both charismatic
yeah you guys can you know take the
charge away
why did they get
I don't know oh they didn't even give
you a chance to yeah
oh they're up they're on top of it yeah
I am here now this is I did not have to
fight this so I'm not sure how this will
work but we're fighting now get in here
and help us goblins yeah okay well we
want to fight those yes
um not what are the memories they're
they're on They're Up on the Roof yeah
or the house right next to us yeah what
what
um
Alex really don't see them
okay you see really hard
go to the left and in the middle of that
roof ah and then there's also one at the
end if you go down just downward
with the arrow okay well we won't come
back here we are I guess yeah
oh well okay
I guess I can't do anything
ah let's go bird let's go
you're the front door
I love the flying work
oh
hi
can I not
what what does that mean not enough
resources
oh it means you are used in action or
something yeah or your bonus yeah
movement Etc
well if there's another guy
ah
I get some from oh can I get them 65
percent
and then can I fly up on yes I can yes
[Music]
[Applause]
this might have been a mistake
yeah that's all right you can handle
those guys we'll handle these other ones
ah
yeah
oh you missed
nice
[Music]
that would have been so awesome
um
yeah
let's say
[Music]
oh
I'll be fine I know what to do with them
there's one on the other side
um and then there's one inside the house
let's go
you really couldn't take me talking to
him like that yeah I love your insults
insult me please
I could number you're perfect oh there's
another one on this Waypoint discovered
um I need to heal myself at some point
don't die
come on
oh my God is this guy
um I think we can get him oh let me get
a bit closer
maybe then
oh nice nice
yay
take him down take him down
all right
go burp go
no why not rip go here
oh burp getting closer
I wish I didn't have so many archers
okay
if this this person has a ball right so
that means they won't attack me if I
move behind them right I'm not sure okay
the building below
here we go don't miss
that's so awesome
okay
beautiful
so good and I feel myself
just a couple left I think two goblins
left
I'm gonna switch sides now that we got
the Waypoint we can return to Camp as
well if you guys yeah right there
okay
wow your words are very strong if my
words are hurtful
it's my job demon of words
not super song
oh nerissa if you go too far into the
village you'll aggro more people oh okay
I'll stop moving in I thought I needed
to get by the Waypoint to unlock it
yes
okay there's one in the house and then
one by Marissa oh there's one in that
there's one by me
there's one right in front of you
um
oh yeah inside the home
almost forgot about that
I'm fighting fast
that's all right I can survive this you
got it yeah
foreign
are you okay I'm okay I have one HP how
do I how do I get this person
and I like shoot it from the
oh shoot he only had free HP that's why
I didn't do it I'll do it on the next
Target
Cali only one HP what the [\h__\h] yeah
that's okay I'm good not okay I'm good
you're bleeding how do you get in
because I've been tanking damage I guess
it's the adrenaline
oh
yeah I don't know where the other oh
there's one in there
I'm just gonna stick take the killing
shot on Cali what excuse me so you can
get exp from her
oh no I'm not gonna waste a healing
potion when we're literally about to go
rest at the camp
so I'll just chill here
you guys might need the help though
maybe I will pop a potion
take the shot get him
oh
no time for mercy
nice
and I wanted to check out these bodies
oh fire I love your Footprints are
sending me
put that fire arrow
or maybe I should have known a bit
further ahead of me oh
go shadow
[Laughter]
an attempt was made okay
I have endless responses
nice oh we're done we go to the camp
Camp yeah all right we've got this uh
already all right so let's go back to
I'll take us back to the camp go to Camp
yes
um
oh I think you guys got to return on
your own oh
so it's in the scroll wheel the same one
where you like go to your inventory and
stuff
like okay press that and then it's the
bonfire icon you click that
dlss what DLS jet
I'm Gonna Save really quick
just chilling with one HP at the camp
all good it's doing just hanging
living my best life okay end the day
okay
well let's all take a little nap go to
bed
someone on the camp wishes to speak to
you oh um
they always keep wanting to talk to us
why are there too well why are there too
yes why why is it why is there two of
them
homes
what is going on
[Applause]
what let them cook I don't know what's
going on but is this Mirror Image what's
he gonna do with himself make an army
out of himself right oh Shadow heart
wants to talk to me really oh no we
gotta talk to Shadow bird
are you hurt him I'll protect you always
Shadow heart
oh Gail what are you doing here this has
nothing to do with you brother
let him live
oh oopsies I failed oh yeah like me very
much a little freaky you made her mad
how deep is this inventory you can talk
to her separately can't you I wonder
did I aggro her forever
no she's she's fine we should get to
know each other a little more
yes make her like you
um
zero is
a crush you
somebody said don't don't put the silver
and open phone oh I think I'm raising
her up don't let's go maybe I'd like to
get to know you better what if I do
oh I kind of want to watch this
what happened to it what happened to a
Starion I'll show you wait oh wow
whatever she's wearing is very sexy okay
for now I'll leave her beef and I won't
press how do I oh
okay hold on nice you're getting it I'm
I'm doing it I'm doing it
um
okay
okay I'll I'll talk to her again later
when when we have more time to buy yeah
I don't think she wants to talk to me
she doesn't want to be interrogated
right now so I'll leave him alone I
gotta give her space you know yeah
all right ready for sleep
yes let's go eh yes I'm gonna go to bed
sleep sleep sleep let's see a supply
pack we're gonna need to steal more of
these from the goblin yeah
saving her risk for the real prize you
cop me
I don't go
oh he's a good boy who's a good doggy
[Music]
so that's so sad
all right oh he can talk to me
um
never forget him
but I'm glad to have met you
baby
her pets pets you can pet the dog 10 out
of 10 games you can
pet the dog
I mean you're small enough you could use
the the dog as a seed right
the dog
everyone approves when you pet the dog
pet him again
is he ever like say stop that
I wonder
maybe not you know over here
that's nice oh I can only leave now uh
um
well he liked it he did
okay
shall we save another roll full health
yeah good idea save game
um
goblins
whoa whoa there all right I'm in another
another crab
how about this
yo that's so cool that's a big one I
didn't expect it to be so big I did
wasn't expecting a spider
it's just another crab look they look so
similar
of
legs and hands right definitely
yep just Green Green Crack I mean crabs
are just sea bugs just giant spiders
yeah yeah you know you've got a good
point
an armored spider
aren't shrimps the Cockroaches of the
sea or is that crabs
it's not me not crabs excuse me yeah
I didn't mean it I didn't mean it I
didn't mean it I'm sorry
crabs are cute they couldn't be
cockroaches of the sea
yeah just like you yeah
oh you're cute too
narissa at it again just you know oh
yeah play music for me you want my duty
you know what I meant to I can bust a
move too okay oh yeah oh something at
you again please I like that oh look the
NPCs like it oh yeah
they came over everybody's into it it's
like a big party now see everybody likes
me
amazing everyone's gathered around
what what wow
why
I thought Advent was like really
friendly with each other
it's always going on oh my God
guess we gotta sleep one more time
because y'all are injured uh no we can
just load this we can just we can just
rest
[Laughter]
do it
you you hit me first
it literally did one damage
after we just healed mm-hmm
[Music]
by the river
[Laughter]
all right what do we want to do you guys
okay fine fine
but like actual enemies wait did we end
the date we did okay yeah yeah how do we
leave the camp
um so I'll leave well you go first uh
it's the scroll wheel where I don't know
how it is for PC um
click the bonfire again
ah
okay um all right we're the blighted
village which okay this is close to
where we're supposed to go you may
follow me and we'll I know where the
camp is from here wait uh
I pressed the I pressed the uh the the
bed right bonfire no no no no no bonfire
no it's the bonfire so go to the scroll
wheel oh
um where like you have like level up
inventory Etc put your bonfire again
wait I can't click anything right now
it's waiting for other players oh no
yeah cancel can somebody cancel this
oh you just have to wait till the timer
runs out oh okay yeah yeah ah that
bonfire okay different bonfire yeah yeah
three two one the only one with the
scroll wheel I'm using a controller
sorry
leave Camp okay gosh I'm so hungry
okay well
guys I recommend not really messing with
the blighted village right now I don't
want to get to this
handball
you gotta cross this bridge over here
it might be locked yeah gotta cross this
bridge I believe
okay well let's cross it okay Crossing
is there a reason you're letting me go
first
there's a
there's a there's like ogres in in here
yeah or yeah yeah I don't think we can
take them there's yeah they're really
strong and there's three of them but
don't worry they haven't noticed me no
I'm just yeah yeah maybe maybe they're
just doing it yeah let's just keep going
they're just chilling
are you sure we can't kill them
maybe later okay come back later
yeah when we're really strong we can
beat them up
hi honey this is a goblin camp now if
you have high enough rizz you can
persuade them that you're cool okay I
have race hello I have oh good you saved
it okay hello
hi
it's just boxing casually people go
alone first yeah can you convince no
there's like poop on the ground yeah
what did you just call me
okay we don't need to hire those big
ogres we can yeah do it ourselves
I feel like that was a mistake do I have
um
yeah
I have perception oh I have deception
okay
guidance we'll give it a gum looks like
yeah
oh I made it I made it nice
yeah yeah nice nice okay
hmm
okay that's kind of rude
you want to let it there's a party oh
nice razor you can get a nice and safe
now no need to wear our wall colors
how did we get here
absolutely
for the sake of the team
go on you have to do well take one for
the team
all right
um let me see is there anyone close by
I'll just Dash into battle
a lag
feeble let me do the reasoning next time
what so you were gonna put poop on your
face yes
why would you need to when you could
just kill them oh bee boo
we need to make good relations so we
don't have to fight so much why not
why not yeah
oh
[Music]
um
fly as far as you can
go yeah be the bait can speed up archers
okay oh boy
oh
there is a large dark monster up there
that is very frightening
yeah I'm nervous what is that livestock
monster
yeah there's like an icon for it I don't
know what it is it's like a pitch black
spooky thing it took some damage already
behind us
I don't know
oh
there's one monster behind us indeed but
you're spooking me different ones
well sharp-eyed nerd what a name
probably spider
um
the icon didn't load at all no it's
definitely there I see it it's just very
dark
hmm
ah pitch black portraits are from
Monsters
Hello
Goodbye bye-bye
goodbye
classic
oh come over here
nice one spider even though it's so big
I love that dagger
thank you for taking that damage for us
that's a good thing yeah
and damage good good
what lacerate that
oh
that really sucks
no no we're not we are not thriving
I had some better accuracy
oh can I talk to the work
even in the middle of the battle
eh oh no
oh no no person going for the alarm
knock them dead
what's the matter no the one that is
behind us
oh bird is gone too
okay no Shadow is dead there is a no
bird for you anymore
what would you like to have next
I can bring you almost any animal
not kitty cat because I just don't want
to see how that ends ever again
understandable anything else I feel you
[Music]
um
are you gonna kill him yeah okay please
I was about to say Jesus
get him
I'm going again
that's my girl
nice
I can't reach it's my Loop okay there's
still one over there okay I probably
should have walked tried to walk around
wow
you gotta be careful of the daggers it's
fine I'll just add the water uh the
water is electrocuted
huh
my dad uses non-lethal I don't know it's
not why is it not toggled why does it
say non-lethal damage I don't understand
I can't take it off
I have that too
I think no I guess if it's grayed out I
don't have it on or what hit change it
is it grayed out for you
oh
my girl there we go I don't know why it
was like that all right please
[Music]
mediocre loot yeah yay and then I think
I can actually I can bring you back
nice well because I got next return I'll
try and be like kind of bait I guess
this guy hopefully targets me instead of
you
got anything nice on you no
and taking a shot
okay we just got that one left
oh he's going
oh I got you okay you try to run don't
let him leave
or
or oh
that means you've been holding back this
whole time I can't believe I didn't see
that was titled
how can help nice oh team
is that it I think that's it
nice
[Music]
please kill everyone yeah do you need
need a short rest I'm worried about
narissa maybe
get that short rest real quick and I'll
save the game ah
yes
I get this loot oh
popping off over here
I've never I didn't go up there what do
these guys do big wolf I'm scared
what what's happening
I know the goblin the temple is over
there the Temple of look is over there
but then there's these guys what are
they go rats
I'm small
ample time
quickly change some graphic settings oh
yeah what happened oh sorry whoa uh
brain worms
control yourself
Saloon
the Temple of the The Loon
whatever it is it's irresistible
it's delicious
I'm so beautiful
I can't take it
can you speak up I can barely hear her
louder
[Music]
oh
why can't we see them
oh yeah
[Music]
the weapon
for the back stove
oh
sick actually let me turn it up
elsewhere
whoa whoa what is happening to the front
oh it's the tesseract
let's go take me to the underworld
like needles in my face
let's go
[Laughter]
yeah wow ah
I raised volume and also lower I get it
it's a d dyeah
oh voice those visions
uh put the artifact away
just put it away
put it in the old pocket okay uh this is
another situation where I really think
you guys should go I'll stay close
behind in case it turns into a battle
and I need to tank but I think in terms
of Charisma wait wait
[Music]
what
oh he's performing for them
oh even more lag you want to challenge
him to a rap battle
I'd revert it back
chicken chasing
the owl bear
let's go let's let's go guys outshine
that big silly
see they all came over when it was me
I'm gonna crank a brand new move
back up dancer
thank you
okay shall we move on yeah yes I mean
you've really captivated them I don't
know man I know I'm distracting them
wait I found the owl bear
oh yeah
I'll bear cub remember us again I think
it was better before
I can't speak
why was it wait I want I want the owl
bear
his voice absolute
roasted dwarf leg
OS
[Music]
we're just in the camp we're just
chilling
[Music]
slightly where are we going some
exploring before we go into the temple
wait can you can you talk to the people
about the owl bear give them a chat the
game okay
come on
they're only talking about Volo to me
oh it's so cute
oh chicken chasing sounds fun Count Me
In well it disappeared okay are they
gonna burn him is this like a steak
[Music]
oh I hope not oh we gotta get rid of
Volo first if you want to do this
okay we gotta get rid of Volo then okay
do you mean kill
no
uh I think
quit
dialogue is moving pretty quick
[Music]
let's go
yeah very cool Volo tell it how it is
damn those rhymes
the stage
oh come on I'm just telling it how it is
boo you stink
friend of yours
I'm busy here you lying uh-oh he's gonna
fail the deception he's so British
yeah he's a shitty Barn continue our
palette
why is he here
[Music]
oh man
I am Patrol accident
I don't think he's doing very good
he makes up words like I do
nice sorry
it's sorry guys I tapped out uh he's
crazy
there we go oh cage him up okay
nice chicken chasing time
you have tomatoes in the chat for Volo
no extraction time well chat I don't
know if it's normal but it's taking up
38 39 of my CPU and
7500 of my Ram I don't know if that's
normal
oh that's a bit better now I guess okay
I'll place a bet
that's fine that's normal like face is
glitchy now
I saw that too it wasn't always this bad
but now it's fine
wait
[Music]
wait where's the bear going wait
wait he's running oh
what's he doing oh man how did that owl
bear cub even come here
oh was it already here before
Club is a responsible for your pain kill
them yeah persuade them do it yeah yeah
yeah
too okay oh I can't use both okay I'll
use guidance okay yeah
that's a big role fight yeah girl get
the Goblins get them
small small baby very angry hey we're
not involved in that battle right yeah
I think I think it was a stray arrow
that hits you might want to get out of
the way
I mean can we save him oh baby gonna die
[Music]
no
well there's got to be a better way to
save him
[Music]
you can't later apparently but yeah then
we'd have to bring him back to life
oh yeah I can't revive this this little
guy
I don't know how long ago we we had to
save yeah I don't either
when are we supposed to get something
super cool for leaving the mom alive
we're leaving the baby lines
hella money I guess right
um
well shall we go and live with that
guilt yeah
you sure are you sure we're in Savory
silly
hold on a second I'll give it I'll check
it
I'll check it out
all righty let's see uh
last save
load game
um
I have to do the Volo thing again but
that's fine
to be okay through it
save scum I mean yak
yeah we'll definitely tone it down as we
get more of you know the game some
people are saying you could group them
with a performance and then use all the
AOE attacks on them
oh nice that's huge yeah that's a good
idea that's actually really awesome
um
yeah because they're not fighting us I
really don't want them to fight yes you
know you really don't need to I don't
think we should enter the temple
yeah okay
I'm sure he'll find a way out of himself
Albert is worth keeping around chat says
by the way
um I guess we can kind of skip this part
because we've already seen it
put it away all right cool
nice
let's Jump Right In leave out there I'm
gonna Boo this guy off the stage
if you can stealth it you can slip
poisonous tub oh kind of awesome do we
have we do we have the wyvern poison
remember
I'm down to try
uh but we should save before we do this
he's getting rid of this guy first get
off the stage
where is there beer okay I found it I
found it it's right here okay I just
need the poison because I don't have it
um
I think uh same save
it's okay I'm right here
um
this is
the crab looks so cute so what do you do
uh just poison you got to put put it
into the booze tub how do you put it in
I I'm not sure but there's a ton of
goblins around so um maybe what if you
did a performance over right yeah your
performance your performance
let me yeah the remote so they don't
look at you
I got it
well
okay
hey wait another one's coming over so
oh
no wait there's a guy right behind you
guys yeah one is watching you they're
more clean there's bobbing his head he
likes it I didn't do I think we've got a
sharp eye
yeah it's a good thing
oh yeah yeah yeah it's a good thing
yeah it's an extra delicious it makes it
makes it tastier
yeah yeah yeah
okay he's happy with it now uh
okay are you distracting people
they're not paying attention
let me let me try a different song
[Music]
a cake
it's the symbol glows power courses
through you why is he watching you like
that
I mean I would too to be honest maybe
maybe you guys why don't you walk away
from it for a minute and see if they
don't maybe you know walk away and then
you can try yeah nice idea
still watching me
yeah is he you he's like the potion guy
looking at it
oh he ran away
nice
it's hard to be The Bard
yeah yeah yeah
okay let's walk all the way over here
sneak sneak up over here
they're they're taking some booze
how do I
[Music]
um
yeah
he's over there yeah oh now he's gone my
crab made it up but not the wolf
okay what if I oh wait this guy's
leaving this guy's leaving this guy's ah
hiding success okay did you get it no
they're more difficult you're really
thirsty
cool
Cloud I think you can
does this mean that they're not saying
anything that's in here because
okay it's poison it's poison now nice
okay okay it wasn't even in the red
before huh
huh what's happening let's all drink
I'll die
no thanks oh thanks
what's happening what should we toast to
Marissa um
yes
oh are you guys seeing what happens how
come I didn't get a cutscene
um
okay well may I bet each and every one
of you before the sunset that's crazy
tell me tell me what happened okay
oh boy
[Music]
drank up I'm like uh
do the bartending drink
oh cool I'm literally stuck let's see
how this goes oh why do I have to enter
the cutscene yeah it's okay
you got two days make them drink it I
trust you
surely it was a success yeah I know it
was
a drink go do your trick
I wanna see it too that's a banger
drink it up
a drink oh yeah
I didn't do it not me what are you
talking about I literally just like
danced I did a jerky dance over there I
did the stanky leg that's literally all
I did
I should have your arms ripped off
please please work because I need to
roll a 20.
good luck
it's all right
yeah
nothing back off I still think we should
kill him so many of them are still alive
yeah oh wait is
[Music]
no
no I should save the game yeah same
time I'm safe
because that was gangster oh
bear okay save him
oh
yeah
[Music]
we'll definitely see you again yeah now
we save okay now now we saved the game
okay
yeah let's see what awaits Us in here
yeah real quick okay get out of this
leggy area
because it's a lot smoother inside the
temple
hi guys
hey get away
it's the big idea
yeah what's wrong
oh what's your business guys
oh a great question you should figure
out a story
straight
response
I've got an audience with the one to
charge into it you have good deception I
think yeah
a master deceptive
okay
yeah yeah yeah I've got skills
right
well
you ain't the first foreign type I
suppose us woes gonna have to be a bit
more specific though mate
oh oh
what does that mean
s
oh we're here to see oh definitely
wow yeah
audience is right she's in a Pity one
and no mistake but she knows her
business
she's in telling the war Chiefs what's
what oh next ride it's gonna be a beacon
oh yeah
oh all right nice restart the game
oh you know actually I was thinking
maybe we maybe we stopping here for
today oh yeah yeah
we've been going for about five five
well four and a half hours I've been
streaming for five and a half but yeah
so the journey began yeah yeah the
journey began and it's only going to get
crazier we'll tackle the goblin Temple
next time we're gonna try to do this
music Weekly right yeah yeah at least
once a week we really should try it
because we want to beat the camp it we
really want to yeah so let's do it
yeah thanks a lot for more Ballers games
for inviting us yes yeah no problem
it'll be fun
um I'm hyped to see where our journey
takes us from here on out yeah
that was fun um I'm also kind of playing
on my own as well at the same time with
a different character so so maybe next
time you'll see some improved gameplay I
don't know
I think you did pretty good today though
yeah thanks I'm learning the Barbarian
ways you know and yeah look at this
masterpiece character
he's after my own heart I never put
those gloves back on no way confident
you know it better Shredder stuff
um so yeah everybody take care hope you
guys have a lovely day wherever you are
please hope you guys
you guys are uh doing well and have a
lovely day yeah are you all ending the
Stream
uh I'm gonna talk for just a little bit
and then end so yeah yeah I'm Gonna
Leave the call here okay okay
bye bye all right see you later
everybody thanks for tuning in yeah
uh well I do I think I'll go on an
island meeting and then I'll read
superchatos
uh I need to go I don't mean it I'll do
it like do we just leave the game
did she like safe and all that is this
okay to leave
I'm assuming yes
probably
okay
uh gosh it's so hot okay I'll be right
back I'll bring a banana too
because that will help me stay with you
guys
[Music]
BRB stay here guys don't go stay once
you stay a while and listen huh stay
here why don't listen
got it
hey
stay
hey wrong games here the POV looked very
similar
and the style partially
Hey listen no that's very wrong that's
not what I meant
okay BRB
yeah I brought a cold beverage
and uh
uh a banana but my my cup is full with
water damn it
oh
chug chug chug chug
actually
I'm just gonna put it back into the
water jug deeply thank you oh my God
uh I I want to say one thing I'm sorry
like at the end I in the past I don't
know 40 minutes or 30. it was kind of
like struggling to keep up with
what's happening
what we're doing where we are uh and I
felt like very unimmersed suddenly
uh sorry about that it was like not
there
sorry
I I wanna you know it's the first time
I'm playing this I wanna like also uh
take time to listen to things but then
uh sometimes we're like moving on so
fast
um and I don't know it's confusing me
that
people are people are everywhere
maybe I'll play a little bit on my own
to like slowly play the game I'm
definitely very interested in like
slowly playing the game alone now
and absorbing the NPC is alone
um
oh not necessarily as a stream but maybe
but I don't I don't know I think it's
lame to have two two Baldur's Gate
streams on my channel
when we're also starting Final Fantasy
16 on the weekend that's a lot of RPG
you wanted hmm
maybe not like a series but maybe just
like I don't know off I guess
German channel Time
but then most people won't understand
I was thinking a little bit about you
know if if we didn't have four povs I
probably would turn
the game into German
why is there a German language setting
but no Japanese there is German right
so that I can understand more easily
naturally but
a man
I was a bit worried about you know
having to read a lot of skills but
actually it's not as not so as bad as I
thought it would be only at level UPS
really
hmm
yeah
let me go to my office
here
oh you got the hang of the game yeah I
think so two
I would agree with that
I got like nine plus Discord mentions
and some are from my mommy
huh
oh that I thought she would write
something about Baldur's Gate but it's
very unrelated I feel like Baldur's Gate
would be something my mom would like
surprise she's not like giving me balder
skate tips
right that's like totally her Jam
actually
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
did Mama told you see you kick his girl
I'm not sure if she's been watching like
normally she watches any of my streams
unless they're like really not her
type what does she say there's like
maybe Sims or something it's just not
something she wants to watch but
normally like RPG I know Yakuza she said
Yakuza is not her thing
even though it's an RPG
but now she she can't get into Yakuza
it's I think it's too
childish and weird for her
um
I mean
hey
I understand why it maybe froze her off
when not you know really
looking into it I I think I understand
let's see what are we gonna do for bgm
what's this one like
[Music]
RPG I I wrote this one down as magical
RPG music
mom
yeah yeah so it's so far I really I do
like the game
but I'm feeling a little bit lost here
and there also like when I I'm so
confused I I wish the game would like
automatically let make me force me to
listen in on all those conversations
because often I don't even notice that
they're having a conversation with an
NPC or so
and then I'm always late to the
conversation
is there a setting that I can change so
that it makes me open up all the
conversations on automatically but I
guess that won't work because you then
whatever several people have
different conversations at the same time
of NPCs out loud okay
um you'd probably need to play in single
player where there's less chaos and
klept those running around yeah
it felt a bit chaotic
but we can talk about it I think I'll
tell them off screen that maybe we can
next time
wait more for the party
and I'm personally gonna say
whoever kills a mob gets the loot
um
hey you want it lowered even more
still
okay
yeah cause like in Games like World of
Warcraft or so you get to roll right and
and whatever like say if you need it or
so you don't have this here man that's
unfortunate I feel like you we should
although so far I guess there hasn't
been really like like loots that has
been incredibly important to anyone
Maybe
I wonder if there'll be a like really
rare crazy items that everybody wants
[Music]
um yeah the loot didn't seem so
important so it's okay it's okay I just
uh want everybody to you know because
narissa also seems to
fall behind sometimes
um
[Music]
I think it's because both of them played
the game before so they're like you know
very familiar at least with the first
couple of areas
um
yeah I mean there is our the Lost sexy
girls
[Music]
and later on she wandered around too
though probably thinking oh well
oh well might as well at this point
[Music]
um
yeah but gameplay I really like the
gameplay and
I I honestly went into this so blind I
did not expect
uh anything
[Music]
um
didn't you guys oh this is a different
game
when we first talked about Baldur's Gate
weren't you guys like kind of surprised
that I would want to play it I don't
understand why was this about a
different game
maybe it was it was something else
no
so beautiful this is
you know
much prettier than some other games
that I've played and you know how much
visuals are important to me
hmm
hey
duh uh turn based
combat though I when I heard there's
turn based I thought it would be legit
like you know turn based RPGs you know
like single player Timbers RPGs that you
stand like in a line
and then you know everybody chooses what
to do and then bam bam bam bam bam it's
a bit different than that huh
um
[Music]
very interesting
very cool
mommy wrote to me she is watching oh
really guys when was the first balder
skate game released
tell me the date well Google it
Baldur's Skate One
huh
[Music]
Mommy I think you're a little bit off
my mommy said I I played popular skates
where when you weren't even on this
world yet
[Laughter]
uh yeah yeah let's let's go with that um
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah yeah I I wasn't mm-hmm
[Music]
nobody mommy played baldus game one huh
and I see pictures
even then the graphics looked good no
way this is enhanced Edition Baldur's
Gate one enhanced Edition
and but even the unenhanced one looks
good
it looks really good for 19.98.
and maybe I was in a different world
dimension
[Music]
pre-drawn backgrounds
it's pretty
[Music]
that's so cool that this like concept
already existed back then that's
really interesting
[Music]
go for the eyes boo it's the famous BG
quote what
never heard of it
[Music]
mommy says I should try a solo run
because the NPC allies are not loot
goblins
[Music]
and maybe I will you know now now I'm
also starting Final Fantasy
I'll think about it
[Music]
if I have time I'm not sure if I have
time
um
yeah
it's a big time investment yeah how long
is this game
this game length does it already say
[Music]
between 75 and 100 hours
it's gonna take a while for us to finish
as a group hopefully like this time I
think
um we we had to keep it like relatively
short because uh it's like what four or
five a.m for Cali now and she's
she's gonna go somewhere right
maybe an other
um
times where we play together we can have
like longer sessions six seven hours
maybe night would be nice
[Music]
so that way you can actually make
progress
[Music]
um
I got you guys actually oh I can play it
on my steam deck I wonder if it plays
well because then then that's controller
controls huh
[Music]
controller controls
apparently we are ferted in some kfp
really did we did we Zoom so fast bro
and plug in the controller on PC yeah
but I don't know I want um I like the
keyboard controls
[Music]
for the steam deck run bg3 without
exploding it I feel like I read
something about bt3 works on Steam bag
gotta lower it a little bit I guess
[Music]
I it can I play it I play it on it oh
Santa played for an hour or long for an
hour longer than us and we went way
further oh is Zetta playing alone
yeah I mean
[Music]
yeah okay
yeah I mean I think if I played solo I
would probably also take a lot more time
um
[Music]
she spent an hour pickpockets in NPCs
yeah I can see how it could be very easy
to get sidetracked yeah
um
maybe it's good that we're rushing
otherwise we're gonna spend 200 hours on
the game
or like never finish I don't know I
don't guys I
we're gonna try our best to keep this up
as a weekly thing and all that but don't
don't uh I'm not gonna promise that
we're really gonna finish it
because that would be honestly
wow quite quite a challenge
it was such a long game with people in
different time zones
a running collab I don't think that this
has ever happened before in the whole
life English History to actually finish
such a long-running game in a group like
this
[Music]
I don't think we ever
had something like that before
that would be
quite an accomplishment ttrpg even the
ttrpg didn't get 200 hours right
[Music]
um
Diablo dropped instantly I feel so bad I
don't know I don't know it doesn't seem
like
[Music]
um
seems like if we wanted to continue that
I would have to push for it
because yeah nobody else asked about
should we continue this
[Laughter]
uh
yeah Baldur's Gate will be a long long
adventure hopefully but no promise that
we'll get to the ending
[Music]
if we don't get to the ending
then it would be cool
if like there was a function
tell me if there is but if there was a
function to leave like the host like
take your character and put it into a
solo game and continue the story from
then on
I'm guessing no
man
you can get the save file from Cali
[Music]
that'll be a genius future right why
doesn't that exist
um
you can save it and use their characters
would they be played by NPCs
[Music]
or it has to be real people playing it I
want to see more g-string Wawa
oh I'll come from oh oh
busy busy yeah
wait for a solo run
the NPCs you control those two or they
do what they want
[Music]
do they do combat on their own
what's the yes for
you control them nah okay okay okay so
basically you get fancy NPCs then hmm
air so unfair it works no
if we ever are like okay sorry after 50
streams we're like sorry can't I have to
focus on other things now
we could take the save file and continue
in theory
[Music]
okay okay
so that's an option would be nice if it
worked like to drop and drop out yeah
that would be nice really
um
oh well
[Music]
we'll see we'll see how it goes
okay I'm going to read super chats but
where did I leave off
[Music]
let's check I think I know
I think I know yeah I didn't read the
one that has a lot
[Music]
let me check something really quickly
wow
I got logged out of YouTube while I'm
streaming what does that mean
what does that mean
[Music]
s okay
yeah it happens sometimes so
weird
you cannot continue to multiply or save
single reminder
weird a lot of people said I can
[Music]
wow
but now I understand why you guys said
uh we should
oh wait did you guys even say it well I
know I don't understand why some people
said we should do four povs
[Music]
because there is
there is always something going on
something else in everybody's screens
oh God I feel like I prefer if we would
look at the thing same things together
because then we actually understand what
we are reacting to
um
yeah
and I feel awkward you know I have this
problem where I feel awkward when I'm
like I'm doing something that I know the
others are not part of
like commentating on it alone
I feel awkward
[Music]
it's like I'm like uh while their their
viewers also have no idea what I would
be talking about
um
and they'll be like why the [\h__\h] is this
chicken screaming
I don't know what she's talking about
[Music]
anyway
oh look here
[Music]
they'll see the squirrel clipping on his
van did you guys know
about the squirrel possibilities
is that why you told me to do it
man you guys must have explored a lot to
fight that squirrel and do that and know
about it in the first place
good
you must have done a lot of exploring
where's my thumbnail
where did I save that
[Music]
it was brutal oh my God and I even
because of my dexterity got a critical
success if it wasn't critical I wonder
if would if it would have survived
does somebody know
[Music]
you just kick it it dies either way it
would have died on success okay
but is it a different death
like a less bloody death
does that change things
no critical successes don't change
animations well then what does it change
just does it just feel better for me
is that all there is to it
[Music]
just the feeling of having a really good
success
[Music]
oh it automatically succeed regardless
of the DC yeah what does that mean
we have a daisy for you still pass on a
critical success
[Music]
if you need for you to hit and roll a
natural 20
match with the natural 20. you still
succeed
so
[Music]
okay
without the bonuses so like the maximum
I could have possibly with my dice
[Music]
here
wait how do I I must have a lot of
bonuses
to reach
a 30
without the 20 though
what if I have a 19
that's still critical success
then I must have a [\h__\h] ton of bonuses
damn
pretty is like
[Music]
no okay
only 20. okay okay
[Music]
oh is that like it was like turned on
once and I don't know what triggered it
I guess it was maybe me did I press
something
maybe but then everybody told me to turn
it off
is it better maybe in certain situations
to have the
turn based thing on
what exactly is the difference
I'm still trying to understand some
things
[Music]
what what was karmic dice again I forgot
ah
I wasn't that something you guys told us
to turn off
oh it reduces multiple numbers
[Music]
you can turn on avoid traps and commit
crimes a lot easier
[Music]
that's uh the difference yeah I remember
the difference was like
when it was turn based the fire was like
you know not constantly
right I could have walked through it
and then we turned it on and it was like
and it was impossible to walk through
huh
because the fire then also is like turn
based
that's weird
from base mode out of combat
let's let's me take my time of dangerous
situations
hmm
I don't know if I because if I turn it
on it's turned on for everybody right I
don't know if I like should make such
calls
[Music]
it's also better for things like
pickpocketing wait never mind
about this one thing at the end you know
when I kept on turning on the red area
the shift
and you guys told me that if it's
red basically they don't see it they
it's out of their Rage or do they also
not see it whatever is not red they
don't see it so wasn't that beer pot
always out of like I always saw it gray
it was like never red anyway and they
didn't have to go that far from
yeah red is their line of sight
when I looked at it even before they
made that fog or whatever
and it looked like it was
not in the red so would it have been
safe to take it
or is that personal by the way does
everybody like if they would press shift
would they see the same or is it because
somebody just mentioned Bijou has
terrible stealth
they can see if you're not sneaking
password ah
a
the pot seems to hide the vision so I
could have seen it
sound also matters beyond the red Vision
code
they might still hear you aha
[Music]
see to sneak up
maybe that's what never said was doing
at one time sneaking
thank you guys you guys are clearing up
a lot of my confusion
ah and
[Music]
also I'm aware of the the targeting
thing sometimes uh
sometimes rarely I forgot like where I
put it on but mostly I'm aware like I
now I know I put it on the Target and
then I want to shoot people and if it's
dead I put it on the next Target people
[Music]
um
and now also know more distance good and
High Ground good okay
understood understood
[Music]
I will try to find The High Ground when
I can
[Music]
but then when I shoot something that's
far away maybe often there's still my
loot
because they're closer
so I'll tell them
[Music]
bottle of oil yeah yeah I got fire arrow
and bottle of oil
I want to try
combining those kind of things
that's like that's me is like really
ttrpg-ish
[Music]
try to re hey I don't know what the
difference is how do I I don't know
which what what
was I
was like recasting it well I don't know
how to reapply it you'll have to tell me
[Music]
yeah
you'll do poor decisions and die during
fights trying to run to them yeah right
right
[Music]
just blindly looting
and you cast the first time it gets his
own box at the right okay so I uh I I
choose the one that's on the very
furthest right side okay okay I think I
noticed I my brain registered that icon
I just wasn't sure if it's not just the
same
okay wait what did I ask before that I
feel like I asked something before that
[Music]
you can ah no I wanted to say yeah uh
that seems so ttrpg-ish to me like
doing things like you you see oil so you
should uh fire at that and hope for
something cool to happen rather than
attacking the enemy directly
[Music]
I want to try more things like that but
I don't even know like what the
possibilities are in this game
[Music]
like some things don't just not so
obvious to me at all
like I thought it was fascinating how
they even though I was partially not
very much not aware of what was going on
it was fascinating to me how how it
works that narissa would play music and
they would actually go to her and
therefore be kind of distracted I guess
that's so cool
hmm
yeah yeah but I I just don't know how
far are the possibilities how big how
wide
[Music]
um
wow
if you summon a cat and have it meow it
can do the same
oh yeah right didn't we do that once in
combat I made it meow and then they
killed the cat
maybe if it's out of combat instead of
killing the cat they would just pet it
look at it
yeah poor cat it's so fluffy it looks
like
um my old family cat a little bit
that was um my old family cat was kind
of a mixed breed
with like brown and dark brown middle
Brown lighter Browns
and very fluffy and and
it also kind of looks like a like a
raccoon just like that one
like a trash panda
so cute
good memories no
that cat
hated me so much she really disliked me
but
it's because I always tried so hard to
make her like me
sadly
and I was like still very young and you
know like she already hates me I can't
really fix it and but my my
the older I got the more my goal was for
life to one day get my own cats
and then force them to love me and I
have achieved that successfully
yeah
yeah guess first Auntie was a cat
I'm not sure if that was the first one
but yeah she was our family cat for a
long time
and
yeah she would
when I would like walk slowly walk to
her the moment she sees me walking up to
her
she immediately will try to run away and
hide onto under a sofa or a bed but I
was so desperate I would like
get down on the floor and like crawl
under the bed and drag her out because I
really just wanted to hold her and pet
her
oh yeah I I'm I was definitely too
clingy but I was really young and I I
don't know what she hated me so much
[Music]
yeah now these my current cats didn't
follow me everywhere
they're very very freaking clingy
so I can count out is the best way to
make it hit you yeah I know I know I
just I was so sad because like there was
there was like no way to make her like
me
hmm
she always ran away from me even when I
you know walked over really slowly
slowly slowly and was very careful and
gentle
you were a bad cat owner I wasn't the
owner I was a [\h__\h] child
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
even if you had food or snacks oh
no she
just I guess
go for the food but I will I I wasn't
really the one feeding her most of the
time
[Music]
my child used to sneak into my crib to
sleep with me when I was a baby
[Music]
God
I'm so cute I see videos of that like ah
cats cuddling with bad boys and toddlers
that's the cutest thing ever move also
with puppies oh
oh those videos are healing me
[Music]
them like resting on each other ah
man this is too wholesome
you know
thank you
can you use my drinking
oh I I want to use
David fan
[Music]
I want to change this
double demon Fang
[Music]
wanna play tails off game man but but
but we're playing
Final Fantasy we're getting into Final
Fantasy now let's go
okay let's write some super chats so
around the kitchen Studio wrap dancing
for the pinky into it again thank you
for your big support I appreciate it
thank you
[Music]
opening oh wow what a choice
let's go
I take your plate the Tales of Symphonia
it was my first jrpg ever and the game
that kind of influenced me into getting
into Japanese culture and everything
so it has a Symphonia had a huge
influence on me in my life yes
one can say without Tales of Symphonia I
wouldn't be here today
[Music]
there's like I would say there's like
two
um
kind of two two things that got
everything rolling but I would say it
was mostly like tips of Symphonia that
more and more
kind of opened it opened the door into a
rabbit hole for me
um
yeah
yes yes good game good game and I'm I
still didn't play
the sequel to 2007 I have it
but still didn't play it but yeah people
often told me the sequel isn't that good
but I don't care
I don't care I still want to play it I'm
sure it's great even when people say
it's not that good
and now you guys say it again I'm sure
it's great you know how I like I
appreciate things you know like rings of
power so
you know you know you know me
you guys are so extreme
[Music]
it's decent I just don't like the main
character oh why is he like you know
that energetic
but it wasn't lowered kind of the same
more or less the same word like really
energetic
um kind of boy
he's a wimp whiny and moping
ah
interesting making the
he has no emotions
[Music]
is he how can he be whiny and mopey but
also cold no
with no emotions
[Music]
he's the overly apologetic type
um
very depressed to Expresso for the whole
game thanks for using my word
and he gets taken over there
uh I'll play it sometime and I'll make
my own opinion but I'm generally like
most of the time I'm not a fan of the
male main characters anyway
uh in Tales of games except for Tales of
cilia
and
[Music]
well
tons of arise the
uh what was his name uh xion and Shion
and xion and
um the guy alphan yes I knew it was
something with a
I thought it was fine too you know I
think you can see a pattern the tales of
xilier male uh main character
and alphan they're both you know not
like Lloyd from Tesla Symphonia
you see you see the difference like what
I prefer in the in a protagonist
yeah it's probably like Yuri uh I guess
I do I guess I do
not as much as other people love him
I think Yuri is also a little bit
different
a different kind of cool
I really freaking loved the Celia main
character because like ah
he's so likable the way he takes care of
that little girl and man his story
ah it's just a lot excellent too I'm
mostly thinking of Celia too I guess
Jude was his name yeah wait no no no
wait no not truth I think of Celia too
I'm thinking cilia too
[Music]
he is
oh yes
I just
he is great
[Music]
he is just so great
use the carrying type well
yeah he well if you have to play the
game to understand
I mean how can you not care for that
little girl that joins you
l l or something was her name I think
[Music]
yeah
hell I think it was l
ah
cute big fat cat
[Music]
nexilia too I don't know why you didn't
play Celia too guys it's the one game I
always mentioned as my favorite tales
off game
my favorite yes
it also has like
I think it was the first tails off game
that did this it has uh or still the
first game it has like Bad Endings it
has several endings and uh
some of them are bad really really
really bad endings really depressing
I don't think they ever
besides Xillia 2 did that
[Music]
grinding for money to pay off the debt
was kind of a drag
if even younger not so much of a game of
Wawa was able to do it then you can do
it too
um Celia till was very different from
Celia one
in my opinion so if you play Celia one
and you didn't like it that doesn't mean
that you won't like Celia to cilia 2 is
very different
hmm
[Music]
oh my God I'm I am
tangenting so much about tails off I
just love it
I got I think I accidentally got a bad
ending once
at the end and wow it it hits so hard
[Music]
eh you didn't some people didn't like
Celia too but played sillier one
what
[Music]
why
um
yeah oh the Super Chat saying Symphonia
save your life honestly Celia one and
two I
um binge game them do people say this
um
at a time of my life where I was like
before the before the working holiday
at a different stay in Japan where I was
like kind of
stuck in Japan with nothing to do uh and
just kind of kind of
pressed
and all oh yeah I was living with a host
family in Japan
and I had my own room and my PC and
everything and my PlayStation
and
uh yeah like I lost
my job and everything and I was like in
this weird
state with
nothing
to do and no purpose
and then yeah I just played hours and
hours and hours and hours like the whole
day like maybe 15 hours per day I played
in terms of something like I wanted to
yeah it helped me so much
I really loved it it was so good
no no that's not when I fell into the
rabbit no no that was way before whole
life even started
way before
whole life was not a thing yet
[Music]
um
yeah Tales of games
[Music]
have a very special place in my heart
for making me get into Japan and also
helping me when I was in Japan when I
was in a in a rough spot
um
yeah
helping me through some rough times
[Music]
you really want you really made me want
to play more let's go
[Music]
now you're Ambassador yeah
I hope I can do some more Ambassador
work for them
but as we talked before
I doubt that you're gonna bring out
another you know big main title game
uh anytime soon
like looking at tells of History how
much time each game takes
a long time
[Music]
gotta be patient patient patient
I wouldn't even complain about another
phone game if they just do it
differently
like the Atelier attempt where it seems
like they're really trying to make a
normal athlete a game into a phone game
they're not trying to make it have too
many phone gimmicks besides the gotcha
aspect I guess
but if that takes less time to create
then I wouldn't mind having something
like this for tails off
I don't know though I don't know I
should read super chats man what am I
doing what am I doing with my life
I got I tried so hard and got so far AKA
two super chats
soon
thanks for the pinky switching to a new
job so I get a very rare week of getting
to watch it live Oh Oh you mean the in
between
of jobs
I cheer extra hard for the reborn Idol
Phoenix incarnate you inspire me to push
myself every day to be reborn to my best
self wow
wow using all my lore I don't know if
you're here today but this sounds like
your normal evolved gang thank you so
much for watching the world
watching the world's watching the vods
I'm glad that you bought Watchers are
around it's hard to pronounce these
words
but you guys are very necessary too just
like the live Watchers
thank you
thank you so much is that everyone I
hope you'll see this in the world then
if not now
[Music]
thank you and I'm I'm really happy
that I seem to be helping you
to become
the best version of yourself and also I
hope your new job is going well
foreign
sanction
uh oh
thank you chocolate insomnia thanks for
the pinky wordless Super Chat oh I
[Music]
oh yeah
thank you
speak to me yes Speak to Me Maybe maybe
maybe they can't maybe somebody
taped their mouth or put a rope in their
mouth or an apple or something
[Music]
maybe it's a cry for help
maybe wordless super chats or cry for
helps and we have to rescue them
hmm
you will start an hour also before I
leave I have to leave for what
[Music]
got to start early now
you're gonna start work later then
ask for late shift
command through Duncan
uh 13 King Junction
[Music]
I like listening to Homelite Clips at
work and I didn't realize this was live
until it cut off you thought it was like
a really long clip or what
celebrities thank you
I've been enjoying a ranger you know
that was kind of like bow shooting
classes are something I always am I in
in MMORPGs
I always have my eye on them thinking
like that would be kind of nice but I
don't know if I'm like good enough you
know but you know
next time
[Music]
no more please watch thoughts please and
good luck with your job thanks for being
around don't forget about me
[Music]
Archer stuff the words archers
thanks for telling me about the swimming
Styles I actually ended up looking them
up and also when I went swimming
yesterday which was by the way amazing
um in the summer heat
um
I since it was my day off I gave myself
a bit more time in the pool
and I also said [\h__\h] it to the gravy and
just dunked my head on the water and did
some back swimming
to backstroke
very very relaxing
ah
so relaxing
[Music]
yeah I'll say the gravy has been um
already mostly
naturally disappearing so I was like all
right might as well until my next gravy
renewal
just say [\h__\h] it at this point and just
enjoy the water as much as I can
and then I'll reapply the gravy sometime
on later at the end of the summer I
suppose
careful you don't bunk your arm yeah
that's the only problem like I always
gotta check uh um am I there yet am I
there yet
hmm
gravy proof cap I don't wanna look
stupid
[Music]
no I don't mean hair dye I mean gravy
obviously
I don't know what you mean
why would I why would I use hair dye
obviously all of this is natural
[Music]
yes yes
you really don't want your hair wet that
badly well you know when I just got my
gravy applied
that's you know it costs a lot of money
to get it done by a profession I could
do it myself but usually I like to have
it done by a professional now
and um
and it costs of you know a good amount
of money and the problem is if you dunk
the gravy on the pool or ocean water
it's gonna
yeah
Fades so quickly
so so quickly
[Music]
and then that's not worth all the money
so mostly when I swim with gravy on I
try to keep my head over the water
um
but uh gravy at this point so much gone
that I just dunk
head on the water yesterday very very
nice very nice
no I don't want to use a cap no
I'll I'll look weird because nobody else
is using it
no I don't wanna no no
might mess with your neck to say I did
read something about that yesterday
that even when doing the froggy style
swimming style
most people do it wrong by keeping their
head over the water and yeah mostly I've
never I always see people just uh having
their head of the water when they swim
like that well apparently it's not so
good for you
[Music]
um not as effective not not so good for
your neck spine
but I need to buy goggles
I think I used to have swimming goggles
but I can't find them anymore so I gotta
buy a new pair and then I can
you know put my
face emerge my face
and try to swim like that
[Music]
um
but also water in my nose
you to share one brain cell
sending the gravy funds at the same time
[Music]
water in my nose why
what are you
doing
nothing
Knows Why good question I think both
apply correctly
[Music]
anyway uh Scoville thanks for the red
super chat also wordless why
are you hiding something from me and
you're too scared to tell me thank you
though
happy birthday wow
wait I went into the wrong direction I
may or may not have have a birthday this
month that's what I thought so here's my
annual tribute thank you for all the
times you've made me smile and Love
Kiana here's another good year and I'm
looking forward to see you in Toronto
oh [\h__\h] when was that
when's Toronto
[Music]
Rhonda soon
September
[Music]
one two three
what time
[Music]
one time might be shitty time for me
wait that's next Ah that's not even in
my schedule yet what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
let me ask
uh
[Music]
uh questions
uh Toronto
is there a time
yeah
also who am I doing this with
it's confusing because there's like two
conventions right that I'm doing until
the end of the year which one is which
okay I gotta discuss
wait for Dana what we're gonna do
because usually we we have to think
about we have to come up with what to do
[Music]
um what should we do what do you guys
want to see me and Elena do should we
think of another like game play one of
those games
or you know do you guys like when you go
this maybe this question maybe only
applies to a certain amount of people
who went to conventions to see her whole
life so far
but do you guys like it to see us uh
sing there or would you prefer only
talking
I thought it would be good to always mix
some talking or a little game with the
singing because I think it's hype
to you know might as well right might as
well make it into a mini concert mix it
up a little bit of both
both
buff is good
I thought so okay
do you guys wanna
have the chance to do more q and A's I
always like we did some q and A's in in
our first conventions early on
but I thought that it takes up so much
time
[Music]
like yeah
I feel like it's uh
like Q A's where actually especially the
ones where
we don't get the questions
before but we asked the viewers live and
you know we make them raise their hand
or whatever and you ask them there
yeah I know
we haven't done those in a while I think
but
I'm I genuinely I like hearing questions
directly from you guys but maybe that's
better to just keep for meet and greets
because it takes up so much time where
we could be doing something else
because all the all the time in between
uh
oh yeah and then those aren't even
screened but most of the time I would
say even when they're not screened I
think I had one
convention where we didn't screen the
questions and we did it at the spot and
it was fine
but yeah better to if we do a q a it's
better to screen it beforehand to
actually also find the interesting ones
[Music]
okay so I'll suggest in any case
to do a mix again of talking and singing
[Music]
um
that'll be nice
let's go who's going to Toronto to see
one
[Music]
let's go
let's go I'm happy some of you guys are
going
and that's only between the people that
are in the chat right now let's go it's
okay it's okay
Canadian FPS we don't have many Canadian
FPS
hmm
is there a Toronto in the EU
no I don't think so
I'm going to get tickets try to get
tickets all right let's go
but you know only do it if there's like
something else that is worth it for you
too not just us if you're far away I
worry that just like what an almost one
hour panel might not be
really worth it to come from far away
you know
no it's not no no no no that feels so
pressuring
having people come from so far away for
such a short thing just feels like huge
pressure
[Music]
come for the poutine and maple syrup
yeah it's not just me kiwama poutine and
maple syrup
mm-hmm
anyway happy happy happy happy belated
or you say it's in this month you
weren't very specific
Edge monkey I what's when is the date
tell me
it's a secret
is it past or is it still upcoming
[Music]
you can tell me that can't you
pass why you got the dotting
okay happy
birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday and
you sure happy birthday in your pants
too happy birthday to you Jakey it's
monkey
[Music]
um
hope it was good hope you had fun maybe
the dot dot dot passed was because it's
actually today
he didn't know how to answer
if it's in the future or in the past
because it's in the present
that would be a big coincidence
[Music]
okay my tummy hurts I don't think I can
read so many
maybe only these ones
Maxwell the first time kitchen tickets
[Music]
hmm
I don't know I don't even own I only own
a couple and I don't even listen to them
I own a couple of old physical CDs yeah
but I don't I don't really I haven't
bought music in a long time it's just
I just listened on YouTube whenever I
listen to something
or
yeah that's pretty much it
foreign
[Music]
I guess some of you got a whole live CDs
almost 600k let's go
wow
I used to have an Amazon music
subscription
but ever since I logged out I couldn't
get back in and I don't know if I still
have it
haven't used it for a year or more two
years
actually maybe three years
[Music]
just like the bus card I subscribe from
the public transport card
because I realized
I'm not using it enough to make up for
the cost
of it
sadly
yeah gotta save some money that I am uh
that I'm wasting on stuff like I still
have a Geo guesser subscription I think
and I still have a Duolingo subscription
that I uh haven't used since
my last Duolingo stream maybe uh uh help
me and I need an assistant I need an
assistant to just turn all of these
Wings off for me
I was like every time I remember oh wait
I still have a geographical subscription
I'm like you know what before I turn it
off I'll do one more deal guess the
stream maybe you know I might as well
you know
uh uh I keep on forgetting and I don't
know
and now now for Duolingo I'm thinking
well you know I might as well keep it
because maybe I can use it from a Korean
study am I using it though no
but maybe maybe I could maybe I should
[Music]
seriously get an assistant not even a
joke
I know
uh
uh whole life members or mem maybe not
even that many but I know of one or two
who have an assistant and
some people some of them like maybe not
quite an assistant but they like hire
people to make like all of their
thumbnails
um I've heard that from Whole Japan
though the whole Japan one is the
thumbnails one
some of them some of them
yeah that's why they're from this looks
so good
[Music]
huh
yeah like I I I
think that's like
nice but I personally wouldn't hire
someone because I mean
yeah sometimes I also wish some
professional could make my thumbnails
sometimes when I when I make a cool one
for a special occasion and then I'm like
[\h__\h] graphic design is not so much my
passion or this my passion but not my
skill
and then I am I get sad because I can't
make it look so cool but generally I
don't wanna I don't wanna waste money on
something that I can do anyway
you know
I'm very stingy
[Music]
I remember before I joined Holo like at
the at the point of joining Hollow you
know I was told we're getting a manager
right so I'm like okay what does the
manager do like can they can they do can
they help me can they make thumbnails
for me uh because I knew I wasn't so
good at it and then I was told
yeah I guess they could do it
they could do it uh
I don't think any manager
in whole life makes thumbnails ever
ever which is fine you know but I I was
just like thinking well you know they're
a manager they're gonna help me with
this stuff right
but they already have a lot of work like
so much behind the scenes
yeah
so
making daily thumbnails
[Music]
no my first manager wasn't even was not
JMT Oldies But Goldies will know
that she wasn't my first
but she will be my last
can we get JMT fun left for special
occasion I don't know if she even make
any graphics I don't know if she ever
attempted something like that
[Music]
Jay chat was your first right yeah
not for a long time
we didn't match
let's say it that way
we were not a match
[Music]
didn't you share manager no no I share
the manager with Cali in the beginning
it was Jay chat managing me and uh Cali
and JMT was managing gouda and amen
and Edna was managing Ina
is not
a manager anymore
uh since a long time I think JMT managed
Ina partially for some time times like
now I think Ina has a different manager
and uh
[Music]
yeah I see people still like being very
confused about those symptoms
[Music]
because yeah
some people thought thought enma was
just everybody but no
you know it's not everybody
yeah amazed with hanma now
uh
but in the beginning when she was with
JMT yeah I think so later on she got
henma
hanma very good very good manager
[Music]
and now honestly we have a million
managers now
we
I have so many managers
yeah
and I'm the last one that uh at this
point JMT is fully managing
she because of workload and you know her
being
promoted hey good for her
um
had to give away some of her
you know so
of her her
[Music]
pattern Kindle
and I said don't know Jenna
she didn't even try giving me away ever
but I said Gemma you know I I'm you
don't you can't you can't let go of me
you know that right and she's like no no
I will never let go of you don't believe
you better not I'm gonna leave if she
leaves me I'm Gonna Leave
I'm Gonna Leave
can't leave me
I don't wanna I don't want to work with
anybody but General
who's your dare ah
[Music]
hmm
can't imagine you have a different
manager yeah you know I mean I mean it
could work you know but I'm just so used
to like switching manager now
when I'm so deep in here uh that just
sounds uh
it's good when I'm with someone who
knows
everything about
the time we've worked together
[Music]
um
I don't want to change
managers so
yeah
I I prefer this
even when jenma is like she has some
times where she's
quite busy
and I feel bad for bothering her but I
think we
we have to work together
we have to we have to
there's no other way
but yeah there's many many managers now
who don't have like a manager name in
the community so
yeah they're just called manage on now I
guess from a lot of the other girls
[Music]
it's good though that we have so many
hmm
there was a time when jenma was managing
for
girls
at the same time
so
that's a lot
but that was more like a transition
thing yeah
I was at the time when I went into her
hands
you know
[Music]
um
no she was also like I think she was
also partially managing you know that's
why it was for for them like amegura
you know and me
yeah
but don't worry those times are over
[Music]
yeah she's strong she's strong
you can carry all of us on her arms
[Music]
I'll stop spilling the tea now I could
spill more but I'm gonna stop
cause I'm scared I'm spilling too much
I think it's not really like any
any tea that's like I don't know
not something it's not like
bad I think but
[Music]
better better to keep the tea in the
teapot
yeah I think this stuff was like here
and there in itsy bitsy teeny miny mo
bits mentioned here and there
[Music]
tea for decoration only
nah oh yeah YouTube doesn't like it when
I spill the beans
but I was spilling tea now not the beans
I wasn't spilling the beans as long as I
don't spill the beans YouTube will be
okay with me
um
where was I
[Music]
[\h__\h] where was I
um
um I'll just like redo some of them
maybe
Skylanders
[Music]
and bottom thank you for the double
rights of a chat oh
ah yeah yeah yeah this one was so funny
I read this on stream
bottom are you here
or have you sinned and left me
completely
forgive me thank you for I have sinned
the heresy I have committed is
unforgivable three plus years of
Devotion to my favorite Yellow Ostrich
streamer tanakisha karya
[Music]
only to attempted away from the
righteous path by cute call eyes I
offered this poetry to reviewed in the
hope that it may help a tone
what happened to you where are you
are you gone forever
do you think I will forgive you again
you think you can get away another time
hmm at least he remembered your name
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
he did a good job at remembering the
name
[Music]
thank you so much for the funny super
chat I don't know if you're serious I
don't know if you're gone forever but
the Super Chat was funny and I
appreciate that mwah foreign
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
uh hi I came from the from as humans is
this where the Prius and loveliest bird
is I heard she's Kinder and really
beautiful okay that was you how can I
forget you no matter where I am I always
try to not forget you
[Music]
know
okay
[Music]
wait
ers
[Music]
go
no papa go
your turn let's go
and copy paste
a copy pet copy pet
oh
hmm
[Music]
you are the best chicken I remember
chicken huh chicken you say huh
huh
hmm I don't know I don't know I don't
know
I don't know about this one
but what same always comes and goes
you might not be here for me to sentence
him to a usual room anyway
[Music]
thanks for the membership
uh RL function unknown thank you for the
right to the chat oh no there's a hole
in my wallet oh I remember this
thank you oh no that's um that must be a
big hole
for that to follow through
thank you
[Music]
in here this is the wallet in my whole
hole in my wallet epidemic
what in the whole why
generally
Nathan cotton thanks for the pinky
haha
I've got a good hold of my Wildcat let's
see right here hold on I had 50 bucks
right here where does it go
the wall of total epidemic oh no it's
taking over I I wish I could help you
but all I can do is pick it up and buy
some food with it
oh no
[Music]
no questions
um
demo
[Music]
even more
Orange
um
ass
she posted a cute she posted her
this video
oh man I saw some of you guys doing it
thank you thank you please I want to see
more I did think that
um it was really good to keep the chorus
choreo really simple because you know we
can get some people to dance it for us
it's even it's way simpler than the do
you challenge
mm-hmm
yeah
yeah I'm hoping to see some more
participants and I'm looking forward to
watching sariton
try the Holiday Dance
yeah
thank you for the rest of the chat up I
had Marissa explain to me what that
meant it took me a while to understand
I didn't understand it until she
explained it
I tripped and fell while holding my
wallet I guess whoever finds the money
can keep it especially if they're
Phoenix
what a coincidence
I am indeed the one to find it
but are you sure you don't want it back
this kind of sounds like you wanted me
to have it
thank you so much
I'll take it
what does it mean eh it's
uh just like uh
like a like an oh
[Music]
just just uh yeah uh
yeah don't ask me
[Music]
oh oops
Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
Yeah Yeah Yeah
[Music]
yay okay
it's 10 p.m I don't know I I'm so behind
on my hello fresh
cookings hello beep because also they
came a day late and then
uh then the days after I couldn't cook
I cooked the day before yesterday and I
ate leftovers today but I still have
leftovers
today but I think today is already the
arrival of the next box
and I still have two dishes
should I eat my leftovers
what should I cook from the two leftover
dishes
recipes or should I cook from the new
box
the most comfortable choice would be
to cook to eat the leftover from the day
before yesterday which I thought was
really good I made a pasta
which was one pot pasta but it's one of
my favorite things I cooked from Halo
beef so far
it's really simple
just uh minced meat and garlic and onion
into the
into the pan and to the cooking pot the
big pot then after a little bit uh you
pour it water and cooking cream and the
broth and everything in there and some
spices
and then then you
pour the noodles
and let it like get cooked within all of
that
yeah cooking cream it's written on the
package cooking cream it's just like
cream but for cooking specifically
and then and then
uh then later uh I put like they only
gave me a really small package
of tomato pesto
to mix into it and I thought this is so
tiny I need a bit more flavor so I put a
little bit of ketchup in there too
don't admit in the Press of a talented
cook passing the sauce everybody
it actually it turned out perfectly
sometimes you gotta do what you gotta do
sometimes you gotta do it that way
um
only a little bit only like a
only like um like a spoon of ketchup
and the tomato pesto it's both tomato in
the end and
it didn't taste like ketchup at all in
the end
it's a little bit just a little bit
because it's a tiny package sometimes
with hello beef these things they
they always like give a lot of herbs
but some other things they are a little
bit
stingy with so this was kind of Stingy I
thought it needs a bit more flavor
yeah and then yeah you just mix it
yeah and then put some herbs in organic
oregano no nothing oregano was a bit
earlier and at the very end at the very
end I put a cheese
um yeah like parmesan fake cheese uh and
stirsster and yeah so it's basically
just the minced meat uh cream pasta with
a slight hint of tomato pesto flavors
only slightly and yeah and a little bit
cheesy it was really good I ate it two
days in a row
I couldn't eat it today and then I don't
have to cook
why don't I stream tomorrow
what let me check maybe if I have time I
could cook
[Music]
earlier
I don't know if I feel like cooking
before because I'm probably gonna swim
before
um maybe I'll start a little bit later
um no I'll keep this ah wait why did I
is there a reason
is there a reason for me
[Music]
let me check my schedule
not really I can start a little bit
later but I think starting
at least guarantees that I can end early
and cook
um
[Music]
I'll just I'll just cook one of the left
I just have to cook every day now
I have to cook every day to catch up
with my hello ingredients
[Music]
but I'll still eat my leftovers because
they're yummy and and and and you know I
could have Frozen them but
should have Frozen them on the first day
I don't know
yeah nutmeg Coke no don't let me clock I
don't wanna cook for me
yeah cook a bunch you say that like so
easily but
[Music]
hello beep recipes that say they take 40
50 minutes they usually take me 20
minutes longer too
it's a lie it takes a lot of time to
cook all these dishes
yeah I'm planning Final Fantasy 16 on
the weekend but of the Saturday one will
be short four hours
yeah those times are always alive yeah
also because
um the herbs and in the recipe it's like
assuming that all the leaves and
everything already picked off
and sometimes they send so many and I
have to separate them because they're
like Tangled
they sent like two different three
different herbs all in one package
tangled up so it takes me actually a lot
of time to untangle them and then pick
all the leaves off and then get to
cutting the the herbs
and in the recipe it seems like they
assume that it's already untangled and
already like all ripped off
[Music]
ah what the [\h__\h]
use the stems too no I I've I'm like
I have to pick all this off I can't use
the stems obviously I'm very very exact
with
where I pick off the herbs there is no
stem whatsoever
in my herbs which takes you know more
time to do it so so properly
[Music]
no no because some for some herbs the
stems are like
sound not bitter bitter also no I don't
know whatever whatever
[Music]
that's no that's not me no
no you don't use the stems
you're not the one cooking for me
you're not the one cooking I'm the one
cooking
I don't want to get it
I'm not I'm not gonna argue with you now
sir
[Music]
I'm tired now I'm gonna go
um the heat is making me so tired I felt
so [\h__\h] hot for most of the stream
man
damn
oh God summer why
so I'll see you guys tomorrow uh Hollow
cure for now stays at the same time
awesome
thank you for watching my POV of
Boulders gate
[Music]
uh
no
yes
music
um this
haha
[Music]
there we go
all right
[Music]
no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
oh honey
[Music]