[Music]
[Applause]
n
a
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
for
[Applause]
a
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
chicken k
key k k
key why you holding back so much I don't
know I I have trouble saying it it's
like a tongue twister for me what
[Music]
no with confidence please with
confidence I see K you have to imagine
you're a rooster on top of a roof in the
morning at 500 a.m.
there it is oh that was okay I can't go
after that no no you have to your
turn
okay no no no
no no I am a polite rooster I don't want
to wake anybody up I've never heard of a
polite rooster there are no polite
roosters you're looking at one right now
no you are a polite owl polite owl
pow a pow hope that wasn't too loud oh
my God you're so
quiet you're never going to wake me
up I'm going to sleep
forever rest rest
now welcome welcome back everybody to
girls to
Y today's girl girls are uh well M who
is is one of the I would say hosts I
would say am I yeah you kind of a host
I've been here every time haven't I yeah
oh my gosh I'm a
host which is funny can't believe I
originally you were like I think when I
invited you you were like oh well I'm
not really I'm not that girly but like I
feel like your input has always been
great you know what I think I've gotten
more girly since I joined oh
there's been a lot of changes in my life
since I joined this oh nice I feel
pretty girly now oh interesting okay the
gfic of
M and then the other host is M takanasi
who is indeed a girl of course and then
thank you I'm so
proud and then today's guest is none
other than uh
quason or
just crony cron what you prefer really
either works I think person is a cute
nick name um yeah is she loud enough
guys I think maybe I'm turn her louder
oh I can't turn her louder oh it's okay
I can fix that no no maybe yeah okay
they do say you're quiet okay okay a
little bit okay A little
bit oh that's probably oh wait I can fix
that completely can you fix that but can
you fix us too I can't fix that please
how about now oh oh know is it better
well let me turn everybody up a little
bit and then like on OBS and the music
lower here there we go how's this
guys talk hi yeah oh hi I'm talking I'm
saying things things are coming out of
my
mouth should be
what hello
nice
nice wait you're talking quietly talk
louder oh I'm talking I'm talking loud
or something that's nice that's ni okay
well crony um do you know why I invited
you this
time uh
because because you think I'm a
girl no you should know that I had an
Enlightenment about you recently right
oh yes yes I think I think because I saw
crony a few times now but uh like the
first times uh were like I I felt like
she was dressed a little bit more
tomboyish and then recently for Fest and
all those Shenanigans she was dressing
very like ladylike B and I was
like
oh wait what I didn't get to see crony
during Fest what yeah me too what kind
of lady
like oh you just like a dress you know
some dress some dressy
right yeah I mean it's because the last
time we met it was kind of
cold cold cold a cold you mean cold yeah
yeah it was it's kind of cold it sounds
like you're saying
Cal cold cold is that some kind of
accent is that an accent I have no idea
cold cold cold cold cold cold why what
you saying cold
cold cold okay I I didn't hear it yeah
true I mean it was you know the spring
Vibes were recently when we met recently
the spring Vibes were
you know vibing so maybe that's why you
wore a
dress yeah and also um you know at that
time like my face is pretty swollen ah
yeah yeah oh yeah that's also something
I was like who who who who who your
face who are
you my face is like you know like so so
so so much smaller like back then it was
like oh my God like I did not want to be
perceived
a it was no you were beautiful already
back then but like the difference was uh
like whoo whoo slapping me in my face
also it's just been a while and then I
feel like you also wore a little bit
more uh cute makeup uh or any makeup why
are you wearing makeup the first time is
when we met no cuz my face was
swoll so it's like double the effect of
oh she looks
different yeah probably yeah cuz I was
like you know so pretty so pretty I
should not have went to the amusement
park in my state I really shouldn't have
my my jaw wasn't fully healed too I had
to like hold on to my jaw while going on
rides
like I didn't realize you were holding
on to it were you like advised not to
like go on planes and not to do
certain
immediately I mean I can't miss out on
the fun you
know well then it's your fault is y but
it all went well right you didn't it all
went well it's it's perfect now oh good
you held on tight enough yeah yeah nice
well okay would you say you generally
like dress more like ladylike or is it
like a 50/50 or what what's going on in
your closet what's going on what's going
on in my
closet like it depends on what you count
as like you know feminine and not so
feminine like I just kind of sorted as
like casual and
like like I guess like dress casual or
like I don't know pants sther casual you
know how b b you know how Bales dresses
sometimes like very uh elegant
fashionable coolish do you have dress
like
that which one like I mean yeah I I I
have more of like a cuter dress I
suppose no not cute more like like you
know M what I mean when she's like
really cool hot uh she's got a style
yeah cool hot
hey CR you must have seen her like
that yeah it's most of the time I see
her like
that I I think I have like more of a
cute cute dress kind of like lady how do
I
say
like ah ah girl from next
door oh no I don't have that I have more
of like a princessy dress in a way W
that's princess
C
princess princess dress not like oh heck
no C wait don't don't I feel like
M Cottage core oh no I don't have
Cottage core
clothes no ah oh that's
cute not C for cloes when I look that up
I I I would wear that in summer I do
wear that in summer low key but I
think college cute oh my God we should
do a girls talk episode where we speak
about all the
cores the
course are you thinking M Cy are you
thinking of like old lady on a farm in
Oklahoma Cottage
Corp yeah yeah actually that's not what
it is apparently
that's not what it
is okay it's like a lot of sundresses
from what I can see like with G gam
check patterns and stuff
oh okay wait CR you seem so lost ever
since I brought you
here no no no no I'm like looking for
the the dress that I I have but I can't
seem to find it so I'm like whatever you
know what
oh Cottage
core cloes cles you have to add cloves
to
it because Cottage cor on its own shows
like the homes too right oh yeah I love
aesthetic yeah I love Cottage core and
Animal Crossing but right yeah yeah yeah
Animal Crossing good times man good
times well this is kind of cute though I
can I can see myself wearing this yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I feel like it
I mean some of these dresses remind me
of what you
wore when when I thought oh she's a
[Laughter]
girl
I I like wearing I mean I never doubted
that you were a girl but I was like oh
she she's a
girl yeah who dress thank you I
here you're here too kind
you're so
welcome well well well okay okay okay
okay so Quon is here today to talk of us
about girly things and oh by the way we
have really cute uh coffee or or cocoa
cocoa uh cups what do you prefer tea I
think it's tea yeah actually the color
is it tea it's kind of let's see mine's
I think it's tea yeah looks like tea
cute so cute thank you
wait do you want a big cup or no I'm
good I don't need that I do not need
that I will
die okay I'm back to normal it's a
little bit bigger okay um so today uh
we'll start with the with the usual uh
quason has uh sent us her ingredients
for her D daily uh girl girly
achievements um my daily girl
achievements I'm saying uh do we want to
start with your
makeup yeah um I've only like brought
out some of my
makeup wait wait wait wait okay let's
let's do it like uh
uh like slow
reveal oh uh wo H
okay well although this doesn't seem to
be in the order of how you use it so uh
I didn't know I had to order it like
that yeah no you didn't have to but okay
this is such a precise the picture
order oh man okay okay okay can you then
tell us with what you
start uh well uh I usually start off
with a
primer not the picture yeah yeah you
know like you got okay wait before that
you know you got to you got to no no no
all good you got to wash your face and
then um oh yes oh yeah start from there
yeah yeah yeah yeah start from there
like remove all the oil from your face
and then you put on toner lotion uh
maybe not cream cuz I feel like that's
going to make it too uh
caked it's going to cake your I agre I
wouldn't do cream before makeup no yeah
and then I I put on
primer um so that it like the the found
your skincare then first I guess I
should do that oh is that skin care what
you
sent yeah that that is skin care
dude okay there we have it the quason uh
what tell me about
it yeah you know like I like AA products
um aa
aa aa I never heard about them I don't
think we have them in
Austria um uh well like uh I I would use
them from time to time like I still have
it because have have like such a big
bottle um I think I think it's pretty
coste efficient like for it's a little
pricey but for how big it is I think
it's okay well can you because um
there's a lot of people who might not
understand it because there's a
purifying Gel Cleanser there's a toning
Mist which in German means uh uh
sounding trash or something like that
dad uh and it's a Hydrating Lotion so
please explain the order and what these
things do oh yeah the gel cleanser is a
face
wash and so you know you use that and
then after that you use the toner which
is the toning mist and then the
lotion and then the base is pretty much
done afterwards and yeah you should kind
of apply that um you know uh daytime
when you wake up and the night time
obviously viously oh you do you actually
do that all the
time not all the time but you know I try
to do
it I think nighttime is more important
than morning is what I was told it it
comes to Cleansing and all that of
course SPF is very important in the
morning there's no SPF on this one is
there h no there's usually an SPF not
sponsored
no SPF you're
gonna okay I only use
SPF um during summertime same same
although we should we probably should
use it all the time we probably regret
it when we're old I was told you should
even when it's cloudy you should wear
SPF it's an illusion that you're
protected from the sun's Ray you're not
completely I was also told that if you
don't use SPF the rest of your skin care
is is pointless oh oh I wouldn't go that
far I would go that far either who said
that I went to a skin place oh they have
a lot of skin we should sue them they
have a lot of skin that's
horrifying well that's how you know it's
a good place oh wow got lots lots of
skin lots to choose from amazing well I
think we probably mentioned this before
in previous episodes but quason because
you used so anything I'm uh like the
toner and stuff I'm I'm impressed
because I only really like I wash my
face but then before makeup right then
then I just use like a toner or
something like that and then I do my
makeup I don't do like like three
different types of things but then also
when I don't do my makeup I don't do
anything at all I'm I'm so slacking I'm
so
slacking it's okay because uh whenever I
bump into you your makeup's so nice M
thank you although I think the recent
times I've I've been giving less and
less [\h__\h] and have been doing my makeup
less oh don't no during fast times I've
been doing my makeup more often because
I wanted to look good for especially
like people who haven't seen me before
yeah First Impressions very important
first impressions are important I tried
I tried oh okay okay so after you like
prepare your face let's go on to the
makeup then oh right the makeup okay um
I put foundation on I know some people
use which is this one right yeah I know
some people use um like the the what is
it the the the the Whatchamacallit the
puff ah you just use yeah what's your
applier just your fingers cuz I use my
fingers oh you use your
fingers oh I use a brush like a
foundation brush oh three different
types fingers sponge brush I used to use
my fingers but I didn't feel like it
blended it out enough or what I would
what I'll do is I'll use my fingers
first and then I'll take a sponge and
blend
it I tried that but I didn't like it I'm
I just I think it's a you know I may
depends on like the type you have too
yeah and just I just have a a lot of
experience of uh putting it on with my
fingers I think oh I see but brush I see
like in makeup tutorials when like
brushes are used and it looks like so
nice but I can't imagine myself getting
it right is it easy oh it's really easy
like you just need to like you know
apply it the same like you know on your
skin and then you just need to use your
brush to blend it all out and like it
doesn't get Caked Up it's yeah it's just
super nice you don't see the brush
Strokes either no you don't I I've tried
it with a brush and when I first started
using the brush it was really good and
then I tried cleaning it maybe I didn't
clean it properly but after that the
brush has never been the same and I can
see brush Strokes now so I've abandoned
it completely I tried I I looked up how
to clean it but maybe was it a cheap
brush maybe a more expensive one would
do it better I spent money on that brush
that specific brush and I will never
spend that much money on a brush ever
again I'm so I'm still a little tilted
about it
damn cheap for applying foundation
specifically for that specifically for
foundation yeah yeah cuz guys you don't
you don't understand there's like a
million type of brushes in a makeup
section for different things for
highlighting for blushing for shading
for foundation for everything oh my God
no trust me guys I I was thinking the
same thing you're thinking now this is
stupid what's the point of this this is
just for makeup companies to get extra
money they're trick like this can't
really make that much difference it does
it it really does yeah it but then but
then sometimes I use my like cuz I can't
find the other one sometimes I've used
my foundation brush for blushing and my
shade or my blushing brush for like you
know I mix them up sometimes
but as long as it's not a contouring
brush I guess I don't know yeah I guess
I guess there's that like um I think you
can switch it around yeah they're
usually labeled too they are are mine is
labeled Foundation I think I think you
can recognize it by the brush shape also
but oh yeah you can crony M says you
really need all those different brushes
what do you say cuz I actually don't
agree really cple different yeah but
like I mean I think the only reason why
you might need all those different
brushes not because they do one thing
better than the other necessarily but uh
because otherwise you have like residue
yeah you have like pink on the on the
blushing brush and and and you have a
darker color on the shading brush and if
you you know want to use it for
something else that it's going to you
know so for that you might want to have
different ones yeah yeah do you you wash
your brushes every
time uh not every time but then um like
I I do it like once every uh like month
or two oh okay
like I don't really go outside that much
so that's why like I can just wash them
sparingly yeah same same so true do you
wash them
M well I don't use brushes that much now
I use my fingers for eyes Shadow still a
bit I did get this brush
kit and those brushes within that kit I
don't think that those ones don't make
that much of a difference depend like
for ey Shadow specifically there's like
oh this is a smudger this is I forgot
the other names I'm like sure yeah this
one does smudge a bit better but I don't
think it's worth getting all those
different brushes even for shadow
there's like a million different ey
Shadow brushes on its own it's
crazy yeah I just get like a like a
brush set and I think that has about
like seven brushes and then I got like
three more brushes on top of
that you know what I just thought of for
like I YouTubers maybe it already exists
but they should do a challenge the
makeup YouTubers should do a challenge
where they try to do their makeup with
like painting
brushes oh they have yeah I seen that
before it seems like something they
would have already thought of yeah they
do all kinds of
challenges yeah probably doesn't turn
out so well that would irritate your
skin those bristles would be they softer
painting brushes too I guess so yeah it
depends what kind of brush you get like
not wall painting brushes but like
some of them work pretty nicely too like
for foundation yeah oh you've tried
painting brushes what oh not at all like
you know from from the videos they're
pretty good know so many of those videos
are fake so many makeup videos are just
well no there's just lots of filters and
lighting and yeah yeah you know like wow
look at this coverage no it's it's
airbrushed and I'm sure they smooth it
out a lot so their skin like after doing
the foundation there's no way that it
looks like this like beautifully smooth
have you seen the ones where they're
like uh applying like this is where the
highlighter will go and the Contour and
the blush and it's insanely intense like
super harsh lines and then they cut away
to when they've definitely blended it
all together but no way they just like
took it off and then put in like applied
it
properly yeah
interesting you watch a lot of those
videos no they come up on my feed now
because the algorithm knows I'm girly
since I'm on a I host a girl
talk that's what happens I can't escape
them now yeah or sometimes um uh there's
this old lady and they're saying oh
we're going to apply this Foundation now
and they put like the foundation and the
wrinkles magically disappear and I'm
thinking to myself that's not how
Foundation works
yeah if anything have you seen those
crazy ones where they're like they're
like they it's those powdered
foundations and they powder them super
harshly all over their face and they
pour a bucket of water on their head and
then like smudge or like rub their face
and like look it's not coming
off show how good it
isic oh okay wait wait wait wait we I
guess we should continue to talk about
your order and what products you use it
so we talked about the foundation which
is from Nars very famous n Nar n Nar
it's very Nish I've noticed your your
concealer looks like it has a very
different color from your
foundation um that one I think what was
it I think that's a lighter
shade like it looks dark than the other
one well when you look at it in person
it's not a pink it's not a pink tone
it's more of a yellowish tone so they're
very consistent also that one's a bit
brighter so it kind of works as a
brightening
effect I have just
saying but honestly it might also just
be um like a smart color correction kind
of thing where normally when you apply
your concealer for example under the
eyes your eyes I mean it depends on the
person sometimes your under eyes are
more red sometimes they're more purple
or blue but then you might want to
correct it with a more pinkish concealer
or a color correcting stuff color Fury
yeah color Fury so I thought that's what
you're doing but
no um well it's it's more of a it's more
of a brightening effect kind of like
it's not really a highlighter but in a
way it does brighten up your face cuz
you know um the
concealer yeah like you kind of use the
concealer
um like to cover up like the bags under
your eyes like oh yeah yeah to light up
parts of your skin so that it looks
fuller and I've been told well yeah I've
been told uh before by a professional by
saying that you know if you use like a
slightly brighter skin tone it kind of
works as a brightening effect yeah yeah
yeah but recently I've seen concealers
where they have like three different
types of colors like blue green orange
to cover up specific
um like things you want to conceal yeah
yeah yeah yeah I was kind of interested
in looking into that more honestly but I
don't think you need to conceal that
much your skin look so smooth that's be
that's a power of makeup
baby it do you not I don't see any like
or is this supposed to be your powder is
it blush or powder or what is this
the left
one the left
one oh that's that's my blush your blush
do you not use
powder uh that's uh that
is just the picture I don't use powder
like setting powder I don't use that oh
setting powder I've been using that
recently oh oh oh so you do use okay
yeah mum you shock me every time you say
that now I use a Mist instead oh oh
fixing spray yeah fixing
spray okay for me so okay she does use
powder but it's not on there so your
order is foundation concealer powder oh
yeah Foundation concealer powder that's
something that I started using recently
I think powder is good um not just to
you know fix like get your foundation
fixed but also uh so that how should I
say like your face doesn't get too
greasy and when it yeah when your
foundation starts getting caked uh it
makes you look kind of older like it
emphasizes on your like wrinkles like
how should I
say it lines on your face disgusting yes
exactly disgusting lines signs of aging
signs that you live life disgust exactly
that's why you got to like use powder on
some parts of your face yeah I think so
too cuz if I don't use powder first of
all every time I touch my face I'll have
makeup on my fingers so I can't and then
if I don't use powder then I'll
definitely have more like lines because
just because the the the makeup is not
set in place also I think generally it
like overall gives it a more Blended
look when I have powder
on yeah but like I don't use it like
like my entire face
I think it also depends like what
coverage you're going for cuz I switched
to like more of a tinter tint thing
rather than straight up foundation so I
don't feel like powder would make sense
with
that makes sense yeah what are these
pens Quon oh those are um so I am kind
of interested in like
well not interested I I really like this
um one brand uh called Cleo Cleo and
yeah CL it's like a specific uh like a K
Beauty brand that I've been interested
in and those I thought were pretty
reliable um are they
eyeliners uh the the red the one with
the red uh
top uh that's uh that's an eyeliner
that's a water proof
eyeliner and that brow one is the
eyebrow pencil ah
ooh wait so your eyeliner is a liquid
one yes yes with like a the tip is like
a is it like a brush or is it like a
sponge or brush yeah okay okay yeah use
Liquid one
tooy people always say my my my eyeliner
is good my eyeliner both of you have
really good
eyeliner yeah it's great like brush pens
they make your ey like not eyelashes
your eyeliner look un
Fleek nice also where is
mascara mascara oh that's like I put I
only like included some of my stuff this
is only like part of it girl
girl I'm
sorry girl give your eyelashes a break
and not wear mascara every day it
affects their growth well yeah no not
every day but when when I do my makeup
it will always be with
mascara have you ever gotten your
eyelashes lifted no scary that scares me
extensions extension scare me but
eyelash lift and
tint it's not so
bad but like I saw I saw videos of like
girls doing eyelash
tens or left I'm not sure but they have
to like keep their eyes closed or so and
then like I don't know they're like
having an allergic reaction or something
everything's burning and they're dying
yeah it can I think with extensions it's
possible for you to have a reaction I
don't know if that's common at all
because what an eyelash lift is is it's
just perming your
eyelashes so it just gets them to stay
up rather than straight cuz a lot of
people's natural lashes grow out
straight and they're harder to see and
you can tint them if you want you don't
have to if they're
brighter to make them darker so it kind
of looks like you're always wearing
mascara when you're not wearing mascara
yeah but the perms and extensions have
different types too like they have like
C curl L
curl yeah UL curl like all sorts of
wacky stuff it's wow yeah I actually
want to get like an eyelash perm um soon
but well C can me give you some tips
because she did I think she did
extensions
though right extensions are nice too you
remember her lashes like recently they
they've been on
[Music]
fleek oh oh yeah I think I think I kind
of remember yeah yeah they're like a
spider
now W in a good way cool in the best way
yeah you can get ones that are clear
like clearly look like extensions
there's more natural ones too there's
like different style choices but it's
personally not my thing because you have
to be really careful too and make sure
they're clean CU yeah they're more like
they can get infected so I would not
want to bother with that I don't want to
risk it y yep I don't know if oh never
mind off topic never mind oh girly but
off topic you go ahead oh let's hear it
oh well I think it was 2 years ago now I
tried getting my ears pierced for the
first time I cleaned those those things
every day I even got like an airplane
pillow a neck pillow to sleep on oh and
still one of my ears got
infected oh one of them one of them got
infected and I could not remove the
earring you know cuz they give you an
earring that the way to remove it I
forgot they're called but you have to
like rip it apart not rip it not rip
your ear apart but you know I forgot
they're called you know like when you
remove I know like when when you first
pierce the ears then the holes then you
get like one that you have to take keep
in for a long time but I think you can
you have you have to pull it out right
so it was not coming out and it was my
first time getting my ears pierced so I
whenever I was trying I was getting a
little sick cuz I had to pull really
hard I even went to the doctor not like
I went to the doctor for something and I
said also could you please remove this
um it's infected and I cannot get the
earring out and they said I cannot get
it out I don't know but I'm going to
give you so they gave me something for
the infection and then I called where I
got my ears pierced and they said we
can't remove them we can only put them
in and then thankfully was it was it
like a Claire's or was it a proper place
it was like a Claire I did it at the
Claire's too and it's they I had like a
normal thing I didn't have to like do
some special stuff to get it
out it was just stuck I could not I
could get the other one out the one that
wasn't infected I could get out and the
other one I couldn't so yeah eventually
finally I I pulled hard enough so that
before getting sick got it out and yeah
I have not not bothered since since then
the holes have closed up so my ears are
no longer M M M have we ever talked
about this I don't know because the
moment you said you only got your ears
pierced for the first time in your life
two years ago I my heart went doy doie
doie doie because
well nor like it seems to be the norm
that kids like get their ears like girls
get their ears pierced already when
they're like I don't know 8 n 10 I don't
know really early right I wasn't one of
those and then I got older and I got
more and more scared of putting a hole
in my ear and many many years have
passed and then somewhat recently also
like a couple years ago maybe free free
yeah really aw like about as recently as
you I tried it for the first time I went
to a cla's I felt really embarrassed cuz
normally there's like only like small
girls getting their ears pierced at a
CLA and here comes the really adult
person and also freaking terrified
person getting their ears pierced for
the first time and I had a funny thing
similar to you where I kept it in I kept
it in way longer than they asked for but
I also I didn't get any infections but
when I took it out once after like
having it in for 3 months you only have
to have it in for like what one month or
so I don't know I don't remember but I
had it in way longer so the whole 60 I
think they said 60 days was ideal I
think but I don't it's been a while I
don't remember well my hole was
definitely like like formed properly and
like you know it became a proper hole
and then I took it out and then one week
later it also grew back together this is
not supposed to happen my Phoenix
regeneration is like off the roof
girls what am I supposed to do then I
never never did it again after that
because it's like
I think you're supposed keep in yeah it
closed oh you're supposed to keep in the
ones that they give you for like 2
months I think but then you want to put
like you need to keep something in them
for a good bit hey but it's not supposed
to I had it in for like months it's not
supposed to like heal back into a full
like no whole situation right
away I truly don't know we I do
not when did you get your ears
pierced um my also closed up like yeah I
got my pierc like maybe 5 years ago and
then um like my my ears were still
pretty raw after 6 months and what uh my
mom was like oh hey you know maybe it's
you know it's about time for you to try
on other nice earrings and I was like
yeah and then I tried it on and um I
have a
I had an allergic reaction because I
have um allergy towards certain metal
alloys right yeah and even though that
wasn't supposed to cause an allergic
reaction it did and then I switched it
uh back into the like you know the first
earrings that I had and it didn't work
and my face kept swelling up and then I
went to ER oh you told me this I think
oh my God think I told cuz when it was
happening to me I think I like mentioned
it or something
yeah but why why are we all so late in
getting our ears
pierced I don't know I've seen toddlers
with their ears pierc GI hoop earrings
for real like the youngest girls do it
pierced younger two like okay okay so it
wasn't your first time then okay yeah
but I still had the same experience so
it closed back up not an allergic
reaction but I still had like some puss
like foring around the yeah so I
couldn't use them anymore and I tried
again way later my so right now all of
our ears have healed back and we have no
holes yes oh we should go together next
time we're in Japan
together I'll I'll watch yeah
no you want them to be pierced but I
just it was also really annoying having
to sleep on an airplane pillow sorry a
neck
pillow cuz I can't sleep on my back
so yeah
but worth a shot I'm going to give it
another
shot okay okay okay I'll I'll watch you
watch you can watch yeah cuz I'm I'm I
might have to go to ER again
so but I mean if it's a certain like
what what if it's a
what there's there's something you're
not allergic to right you just have to
get pure gold pure
silver yeah I did use pure gold it
didn't work
really you know I I feel like I have I
think I've talked about this with my
chat before but part of why I feel like
I need my ears pierced is because I've
been gifted earrings so many times from
family members before they were ever
pierced
they just did not ask if my ears were
pierced and since I was ah they just
assume they just assumed and got me
earrings and even in the last year to be
fair I did tell this family member I got
my ears pierced and so for my birthday
she had gotten me earrings like high
quality like really really nice earrings
by the time I got them my ears were
closed and I had to say ah oh I will get
my ears pierced again just for this M
well I I get it because I think earrings
are a really nice present and I always
see such nice ones I would also just
like to buy them for myself but no holes
and yeah but they are nice presents guys
if you think about presents for girls
earrings are a good choice if you know
she has holes they are a horrible choice
though if she
has make sure she has holes
in because that's not guaranteed okay
you
text and say hey
[Laughter]
niece oh man I want to bring one thing
condition of your ears yeah is it holy
or I wanted to bring one thing up um for
all the non-ear hole people among us
like you and you uh and me um I've
noticed like here in Austria and I would
assume the same over there uh like older
shops that sell earrings and stuff
usually don't have unless it's maybe a
Claire's but then there's only a small
section of uh like Clips ear Clips right
there's just not much Choice usually
like today I went to a shop and they
didn't have any ear Clips but in
Japan yeah have you seen M me yes I've
got clipons in Japan they have so many
it's like there's more than pierced
almost there's it's not even equal is
almost a bigger section of clips than uh
actual like yeah whole earrings and I
think it's like and there must be a lot
of Japanese girls that just don't have
holes
either it's a culture difference hurt oh
they do hurt yeah they do really hurt oh
clipons do hurt they hurt a lot you can
only wear those for like two hours and
have to that yeah well eventually like I
have to find the right spot that hurts a
little bit less than the other spots on
my ear what do you call it lobe lobe
yeah the ear lobe yeah like there's one
spot that works kind of for me like I
don't I want it to cover where the
piercings once were oh you
know why but then it hurts ah oh it
still
hurts well no clipons just hurt oh yeah
clipons definitely hurt but it's really
nice if you want to buy you know
earrings in that and don't have holes
and go to Japan they have so many
different choices oh my God for those
who are not aware clipon earrings you do
not need your ear pierce you literally
clip them to your ear yeah that's what
they are painful it is so painful it
becomes it's it's only painful after
like a bit oh there's when you first
clip them it's fine but after like an
hour or two yeah it start to hurt
there's the same thing for like no like
if you want suddenly if you want a fake
nose piercing or fake lip piercing you
can get that too
same thing it's just like kind of
clipped on it's just hanging on that
would hurt more yeah probably never
tried that though H or maybe it depends
on the well like we're what kind of like
a septum piercing fake septum that's
like when it's between your
nostrils does that would that hurt
really let me a clip on I feel like that
would hurt I'm I'm
poking the septum right now
[Music]
it might be about the
same well well well well well well nice
uh whole conversation but uh we have not
finished a makeup conversation yet so
wholesome
conversation has some questions to
answer oh dear yeah well tell me more
about the other products we didn't talk
about yet
crony oh yeah so on the right side of
the foundation uh that's a glitter that
I it's a liquid
glitter and it's pretty easy to use like
you just like dab it on your eye well
not directly to your eyeball but like
you know like around the eye and then
you spread it and it's like this nice
glittering Sheen I love that oh yeah I
use something like that too for my eyes
sometimes it's nice yeah so glittery is
that a lip tint or lipstick or what
what's next to it oh that's a lipsti
stick yeah it's kind of a nude lipstick
and nude yeah you like nude colors on
your
lips yeah I feel like if you want to go
Fancy on your ey Shadow like glitter and
everything you got to make your lipstick
look subtle otherwise it's just going to
make your entire makeup look cheap
balance
wo yeah
balance and we all know probably what
that thing on the right is yay
right guys chat you know too if you
don't know by now after watching all our
girls talks what what are you doing then
you failed all the test you you have not
been progressing at all well obviously
it's a
crony yay so you know you got to put on
something light for the base
obviously and then um a darker shade for
like the the side like not shading like
the center of your Island but just the
sides and then you put on like the
darkest shade uh along the along the
eyeline so that it blends with the
[Music]
eyeliner y nice would you say it creates
a shadow perhaps around the ey around
the eye it it kind of makes your
eyeliner like blend in better I guess
like know I was hoping I I I threw it
over to you like oh it is a what crony
and then you just went on talking about
the application but you didn't say it's
an ey
Shadow Oh I thought I thought it was so
obvious that it was an ey Shadow though
no obvious no it is it is you got to say
it just for the you know just oh to make
sure yeah it's an eye shadow there we
go thank you now now that was completed
now now I'm happy oh that is that looks
like really not that much but generally
is this like your base M
everyday style it used to be and then I
changed it up
recently oh yeah I saw your Tweet you're
you didn't you needed to know what the
new meta was The Meta yeah the meta and
I did figure out the new meta so it's
all good now oh nice what what is the
new meta
the new meta H well it's like well this
one was a lot more heavy on the ey
Shadow but lately it's just more
emphasizing on the
eyelashes ah yeah kind of like you you
perm your eyelashes and then make the
makeup much lighter okay okay yeah
that's good I think I I like that meta
but I'm not I'm I'm not I have not
really changed my makeup routine for
like
centuries
so yeah I I like the new style yeah they
got like new um contact lenses
too oh that hasn't taken off you use
those uh like Circle lenses thingies
mhm I can't wear that every day I wish I
could M oh you just need to get like the
daily wear m not a monthly one why why
why can't you no because it it hurts my
eyes get super dry once I put anything
in there and then I I even I tried eye
drops but I don't get really far it
hurts I get a headache and eyes burn I
get
tired so only if I really have to
interesting yeah that sucks yeah it's
okay like it's just like a very like
subtle thing so it doesn't matter subtle
I feel like it makes a big difference
honestly I I I like it
but eyes are eyes is like the thing you
focus on you look at each other usually
when you talk to each other so eyes make
a big impact yeah it's like you have
such pretty peepers
yeah okay we're done with this section
for now um now we have a little bit
something special this time I asked you
guys for some questions and
stuff uh yeah and you guys delivered
some questions some serious ones some
not so serious ones
so so hopefully we can answer your
questions let's start with uh this I
want to know this
one uh crony do you want to read it
please uh yeah
sure can you read it is it too
small uh let me
check oh yeah no no I've heard the term
girl dinner used what does girl dinner
mean to each of you what's your go-to
girl dinner do you girls know what a
girl dinner is cuz I don't really know I
know what a girl dinner is
explain it's when you just usually eat a
weird combination of random foods that
do not take long to prepare
because you're either lazy not that
hungry
oh or just don't have much around you
forgot to go to the store
oh so what do you have such a
thing a regular goto um I wouldn't say
so but a basic dinner no it's not a
basic dinner you don't have like you
don't have a protein starch veggie
lineup thing it's like cheese crackers
and a
popsicle so it has to be something
simple very simple like
cottage cheese a brownie and I don't I
don't eat cottage cheese I don't know
why I mentioned
that I'm just
thinking so a few simple items together
and that does it have to be dinner or
can it also be lunch or breakfast uh
it's dinner
because you it's like dinner is an
important meal of the day I suppose
where you know you want to eat a bit
more
balanced but you're not it's too late
you're
tired you maybe ran out of
time it so I have sometimes I eat for
example like just a frozen pizza is that
the girl dinner cuz it's simple it's
simple I don't do anything I just throw
a frozen pizza into the oven but then
when it comes out it's it's quite tasty
and quite uh intricate honestly I don't
know I feel like anything that you make
for dinner just and it's like with being
lazy in mind but they say
proper dinner chat says it's a proper
dinner it has to be kind of cursed yeah
yeah I think so there has to be like a
weird combination or then I don't have
that at all I don't think I ever have
cursed
dinners I properly cook for myself okay
thanks to hello fresh even though I'm
not sponsored when the [\h__\h] am I going
to be
sponsored if I usually I cook but I cook
I'm trying to cook even more now because
I started using uh take out as a crutch
cuz I would like say like I'd buy enough
food to last me 3
days I don't want to do that anymore I
want to cook and make enough for 3 Days
anyways but usually usually I'll run out
and have a day where i'm like I'm too
lazy to cook I don't want to like order
takeout I'm not hungry enough so the mo
the most recent girl dinner I had was
not too
bad but it was like Mixed Nut
dried
mango and a dairyfree ice cream sandwich
that was your
dinner yes was a certified girl girl you
good that was that was a girl dinner oh
why was it satisfying though I wasn't
very hungry which is why I had a girl
dinner M understandable understandable
okay
crony girl dinner
girl dinner do you do girl
[Music]
dinner ever have you done think about it
I yeah I mean I feel like I might have
done it at one point but my meals are
usually full
[Music]
course yeah I can't I can't do girl
dinner it's too difficult maybe I would
try cereal no you should never try to do
it never try to do girl dinner it's just
sometimes you end up with a girl dinner
and it's usually if you've like eaten a
decent amount during the day I think
cereal actually um seral is does not
count as a girl dinner because it's
quite popular sometimes as like a clutch
uh that is a boy dinner that is that a
boy that could be a girl or a boy
dinner it's close to a girl dinner but I
think it's been so socially accepted and
and common that it's not it doesn't go
into that uh category that much anymore
but okay but I think generally we don't
do girl dinner so that means what we do
is man dinner no woman dinner man dinner
steak lady dinner L dinner yeah I had
steak yesterday it was really
good no man dinner is just steak nothing
else it was just steak actually all you
was steak yesterday yeah just stin it
was so good
man dinner yeah no mashed potatoes no
veggies no but that's just Sak I think
that's an unmarried man's dinner a
bachelor dinner okay you don't have to
say that I I think so because like I
mean if they're married then they
probably eat something more
proper steak is pretty proper though
sides I think they have
SS I
mean at least potatoes come on once I
had steak and just like steak and
avocado on the side for dinner is that
so that was like a hybrid girl man
dinner hybrid girl man
dinner oh Maiden lless
Behavior I didn't put avocado on the
steak I had like avocado and Sriracha on
the side CU like I can't just eat
steak yes you can yes you can you can
but I was thinking like oh what about
like a a healthy fat avocado oh damn no
it's just man I felt really gross I
didn't even finish it I I like tried
eating what I set for myself and I was
like wait I'm full like this is this is
weird I don't want to do this
anymore yeah I eat a lot so I can't do
girl dinner it's too it's too I don't
know you eat a lot really I yeah I eat a
lot how a
lot uh well like my mom's friend for
example looked at me and she was like oh
like you know she's not exactly like you
know like skinny
skinny but like you know like she's fine
and then she saw me eat she was like wow
she must have really amazing metabolism
that's amazing okay okay that's how they
mean it okay like like they would expect
you to be like you know more if you eat
this
much yeah yeah I had that growing up
like
friends I I could I I can still eat a
good amount but when I was younger I
could definitely eat more than at least
the people I was with like especially
depending on the food like I can eat so
much
Sushi yeah kind of like light in your
stomach right I don't eat sushi but it
feels like a light thing to eat but
still more I would eat more than you
know my
friends and they'd be like I'm so
jealous of your metabolism and I'm like
what do you
mean how many plates have you
had
um I oh shoot how many plates like oh
are you thinking like conveyor belt
Sushi yeah yeah yeah oh I don't know I
don't I have no idea I think I've had
like 20 at one point you a picture of
the St
yeah no it's been a while since I went
to that I've got a I've never been to a
conveyor belt sushi but I've been to a
conveyor belt like cake uh place what oh
that sounds so good right that does
sound good but I feel like like when you
have sweets that gets but they were tiny
ones from that bastard oh like little
bite siiz cake yeah yeah yeah yeah and
like all all kinds of different ones and
then I also was stacking those plates
for
once yeah cake it was in Japan yeah they
have like all kinds of these things but
but like they have all you can eat
desserts all over the place but like
conveyor belt was like an exception that
was kind of rare was a limited time
thingy oh you know go check it out oh it
was years ago but maybe they have
something like that again maybe you know
yeah last time I was in Japan um how
many there's like six of us got
mja yeah the day where I was couldn't go
we were you why do I always get sick
question mark when I want to hang out
with you girls question mark
why why I don't know you get sick like
on like during the trips but then I
usually get sick like when I get home
oh but anyways we got
mja and so for the
me and Ena were sat at a table and then
the four others had their own you know
how Muno works so you have like a grill
like or what do you call it the thing in
front of you and you prepare it yourself
so the four of them got two different
mja Ena and I also got two different mja
oh and at the end we realized we ate the
equivalent of what the other four ate oh
yeah well Ena is also generally uh like
a a big eater although she stays very SL
liim I don't know how she does it either
yeah yeah jeans shees Fast Metabolism
shees also I mean I also walking the
more you walk Walking can melt off you
walk a lot yeah I walk a lot
yeah okay I'm going to switch to
question now is that okay dam
t ah okay uh actually really fitting
because crony already brought something
like this up and which color of earrings
would you prefer silver or gold so crony
you're like allergic
to but even pure gold you said um I'm
allergic to like you know uh what was it
nickel uh then how am I ever going to
put a ring on that
finger you're getting her a nickel ring
I don't know but I was thinking gold but
like gold didn't work for your ears
right
yeah I guess you can't put a ring on it
forever and ever what about plastic
plastic
plastic yeah give me a ring pop maybe
I'll consider okay damn it like for real
though what what's how are we getting
around this for real for real does it is
it only on your ears or do you think it
will happen on your fingers
tooing uh with my fingers it's fine like
hey I wear like a necklace and a ring
oh okay so is fine okay guys and girls
and me I guess it's different when it's
like in an ear that
hasn't like like when it's still
sensitive and it goes directly into the
skin yeah but I think why this also
sorry I think why this question is um
asked is not so much like allergies but
like color preference because some
people apparently look uh like silver is
better for their skin tone
gold is better what how is it for you
girls I think I I think gold suits me
better oo now your your the the base of
your cherry or Berry earrings is gold I
see it my necklace too is gold cute but
quason you also said gold just now right
yeah cuz it matches my skin tone M I
actually don't know I think for
me might be gold too but it doesn't have
to be real can just be fake gold I'm
okay with that the color
gold oh but I also really like I mean I
don't know if it fits me better than
anything else but I really like Ros
gold oh rose gold is pretty nice too
rose gold so
pretty y I like
those well so this so we're all gold
girls Golden Girls oh we're Golden Girls
We're gold so gold Stay Gold boy
girls The Golden Girls you know you guys
know that
show we're thinking of book we were
probably there's this like show with old
ladies that's called golden the Golden
Girls sounds familiar it's just a couple
of old ladies they're really sweet I
guess but I have some history with this
Show's name because every time I told
like cie that I like Gilma girl she she
always thought I was talking of The
Golden Girls which is so
different and do you guys know or like
Gilmore Girls I've never watched it I
have never heard of
it when will I find my Gilma girl
soulmate in whole life has Nissa not
watched it I have to ask her honestly
and I feel like I feel like GL would
like it too I need to ask her too if she
watched it God damn it it's not that
it's really well known
actually I like I've heard it so many
times but I can't even think of like the
faces of the people that are in it I I
don't know anything about it it's a
perfect combination of funny comedy and
sweet
drama oh okay I thought it was going to
be like Housewives or
something the Real Housewife no it's
like you know just for housewife just
for housewi it's about a single mother I
love this house it's about a single
mother who's raising her child uh and
she doesn't have much money but her her
parents are really rich but she hates
them she doesn't want to you know use
their money because then they would be
restricting her so much with also how
she raises her child but she's trying
her best to raise her child and she's
they're like sisters cuz they get along
so well and also she got her really
young and so it's about their life
together and how the daughter she really
grows up throughout the whole series she
go from like I don't know Junior High
School to
University and even after University and
it's amazing like all the characters
there are so so so sweet and and funny
and iconic and oh man it's just so good
it's just so good you know there's
another show that has something similar
happened it's called The Sopranos the
girl and
also people keep on recommending me to
Sopranos recently I think that's
probably cuz I've been talking about
watching the sopran oh and I told G to
watch the soprano oh let let's do a
watch no it's a show right shows are
different it's pretty long I don't think
you want would you do a watchong of Game
of Thrones I would because each is like
a
movie okay that's kind of how Sopranos
is but Sopranos has some interesting
themes so I don't know if you want to do
a watch Along The
Sopranos you do actually K I'm telling
you right now you do not want to do a
watch along for sopranos watch that in
your own time wait it looks so
gangster
yes why does it look so
gangster is this MAF it's about the
mafia oh okay because it looks like
Mafia to me I see I see I see yeah they
really I thought it was going to be like
Glee cuz of Sopranos right I get when
you're going there oh my God this is way
different than what I had in mind
also yeah I thought this was like
Hairspray or Glee like these are just
like Godfathers what is going
on was there an old version of this cuz
this looks so new and I feel like the
name I've heard it since a long time ago
no it's from the late '90s to early
2000s it it's been going on for oh it's
it's it's ended it ended in the early
2000s there's six seasons oh okay okay
okay it's really good
a okay if you say so maybe I'll watch it
you should watch it you should watch it
I'll think about it only if you watch g
girls oh
God perhaps or or or The Marvelous The
Marvelous Mrs
masel I've not watched that either it's
so good it's so good I've never heard of
that it's by the maker of gimma girls
it's so
good anyway sorry sorry sorry sorry next
one next question
sorry I got a little bit hyped up um M
do you want to read this one okay # girl
stock
QA what
okay I'm
reading quiet now quiet listen listen
are you
listening what the one
makeup oh my God you have to be
listening crony I'm sorry okay you can't
listen if you're talking okay okay we're
listening
what's the one makeup item you need on a
day out who do you call up when you have
news of something what's your ideal week
can spent
doing okay um there's three questions
here uh I like
the the second one the
[Music]
most we don't have to answer all of them
unless you want to okay wa is there any
volunteers for the first question
I I guess I can okay go ahead I I don't
really bring any to be very honest but
yeah if I really need to I guess my
lipstick after eating something
same
same no for real though normally I don't
bring anything and then even when I
bring like oh maybe I should bring
something so I bring my lip tint or my
lipstick and then I don't end up using
it
anyway maybe concealer too m
[Music]
depending depending on the day but I
don't yeah I don't take makeup with me I
forget it's in my purse I still have
your nails in my
purse good keep them I I feel actually
like kind of inferior because when I um
lived in Japan uh even before Holo there
was a time where I was involved with
some Japanese school girls a lot and uh
they were really girly you know um and
somehow they always had a big fat makeup
pouch carrying along and they would
actually use it like at least once or
twice per day and I'm like I felt so
like oh should I be fixing my makeup too
like it but I feel like my makeup they
keep on fixing their makeup even though
they already look fine maybe I should be
fixing it too so I I felt like I had to
start that habit but I never really did
but like damn I I can't that sounds so
annoying having to fix your makeup a
million times per
day yeah I can't no I don't bother Shame
Shame okay okay then the second question
who do you call up when you have news of
something I okay let's all answer this
not with a specific name but like you
know can we all answer this on the
account of free because I have an answer
that I think maybe is
obvious yeah yeah yeah sure okay let's
see what comes out uh 1 2 three my
bestie best friend yeah there you
go calling
Sally oh yeah I mean my best friend is
Sally so but it's not like everyone
knows that so my best friend yeah I was
expecting Sally I'm
kid first time hearing sorry you go you
go
[Music]
oh no no I'm just
kidding oh so my best actually is I also
call
Sally really oh really yo what a
coincidence I don't without a Sally no I
was just I was trying to imply not that
my my best friend is also called Sally I
was trying to imply that my best friend
is your
Sally oh where's my Sally her Sally is
your Sally let's take her let's take
her no I can't are you sad are you okay
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm Sally I'm sorry
I'm Sally won't let you it won't happen
that she likes me most oh God I'm scared
I'm
scared she's coming for
me oh oh oh oh I wanted to ask something
related to
besties mhm so it's kind of sad that
we're not each other's besties
but oh damn okay D no just kidding I
don't mind that but we're we're good
we're good um but actually I wanted to
ask a question um is your guys' besties
also kind of like quite the opposite
from
[Music]
you answer
crony uh
that I don't know like uh we are pretty
different but like not Polar Opposites I
guess like what about not not
necessarily about Hobbies but like
personality wise yeah personalities I
think were somewhat similar we have some
overlapping
qualities oh okay okay you sound like
generally you would say you're not the
opposite
[Music]
then
we we can communicate with each other
and understand I guess I don't know no I
mean still just because you're like more
opposite doesn't mean you wouldn't be
able to communicate and all that but I
feel like so for example for me it's
because
I'm uh generally I feel like my my my
bestie she's like a million times
smarter than me and she's an extreme
workaholic she's super active I'm more
lazy and I'm not a workaholic
unless I just wouldn't call myself a
workaholic I work a lot in whole life
but yeah alcoholic like it could do you
mean like for the type of job she has do
you think it's more no she just just
does too many things and like jobs and
studies everything she does everything
and like oh my God I don't know how she
doesn't desire to sleep more and just
stop doing like she has some things that
she could to stop doing but she just
chooses to continue doing it and it's
super stressed out all the time oh I see
yeah my my friends kind of like that
too oh and you would say you're not like
that perhaps well I'm not a morning
person she is oh there you go that's
also thing yeah that's a big she's
pretty on top of things she's very like
yeah she's very proficient
yeah yeah see that there's just some
differences that I was like thinking
about because that's the case for me and
my B what about you
[Music]
m definitely like in some areas
different but I don't feel like we're
clones of each
other I guess not not would you also say
like for example I think me and my
bestie were like
cuz I'm more the creative type she can
be creative too but I think because of
her the things she does she's maybe more
on the brain mathematic side and all
that but also she's n she's really
creative she's actually both yeah never
mind I think she's more creative but not
the same type of
creative different kind of creative like
[Music]
yeah I think I'm more like visual
creative maybe she's more like writing
creative oh I see I see yeah I think my
friend's more like artistic kind of
creative and just
like just just great just greater
overall of oh I love her oh she's so
amazing a and have you gone have you
girls gone like on trips before with
your
bestie yeah yes yeah a lot me me we went
to SP kinds like y like spa or or even
across the country or to a different
country no not not like outside no
outside not out of the country oh maybe
one can't can't get a massage though cuz
my friend's very take
[Music]
Eng that's
unfortunate yeah that's okay we still do
a lot of things
together cute okay uh do you want do we
want to answer the last question what's
your ideal weekend spent
doing yes what do it I mean let's just
say that weekends for us are just
whatever day we're not streaming on
because our weekends might be spent
streaming usually so then the other days
where we're not streaming are our
weekends week days off so what do we do
I just spent the day probably trying my
best to catch up with like cleaning up
my place and uh cuddling the cats as
much as I can sleeping in watching
Netflix uh and then catching up on other
things like work and and
uh yeah that's ideal for you oh that's
oh that's not ideal I guess although I
mean the sleeping in part and the cat
cuddle and Netflix part is pretty
ideal but it's the usual weekend so to
say day off yeah it depends how much
energy I have like if I have if I'm very
tired then definitely stay
in and just hanging around yeah I just
have no energy on my my day off ever if
I have energy then I probably want to
take animal on a trip somewhere oh
that's
nice a yeah can I join nice yeah do you
remember was it was it for what was it
for oh it was for something else once I
needed to be present with you Kiara and
somebody else and but I I lost internet
I lost reception and at some point had
to say hello I am in a different town
right now I bit off more than I could
chew um I wanted to take my animal out
this morning and I can't get back in
time I'm very sorry I think you
shouldn't have your animal on the leash
I think the animal should have you in
aash I just I just went a little further
than
I should be on the leash well honestly
what happened was I went to this one
place thinking like to go on a walk with
her and I I went to the wrong start so
it was going to be like 5 miles instead
of two and I realized about like maybe
like a mile and a half into it and I was
like oh I have to not do this I can't I
can't do this
so
yeah try not getting lost
mumie was a lot well
okay okay we're going to go to the next
question wait was cronies oh oh yeah
tell me tell
me oh sleep in yes eat
yes yes simp it's that simple nice it's
a simple life simple existence I mean in
summer in summer wouldn't it be nice to
like go out swimming when it's really
hot I want to do that on my day off yeah
it's a little too cold for that right
now yeah soon soon TM soon TM soon soon
okay got to work out here's a nice one
uh crony
read so what's the best skin care advice
you can give please ladies my face needs
it especially summer's coming I need a
good SPF
moisturizer well actually yeah so I
don't care for my skin that much these
days it's so sad so I not maybe the best
one to give advice what about you I've
gotten more into it oh okay you I'll
leave it to you
too oh I want to hear movies first yeah
start yapping I went like I said I went
to a skin place and I ended up well what
I ended up doing over the last year is
too much I was trying a different things
because I had one thing I wanted to
tackle but I it I was using products
that were burned
very I might have been a little too
influenced I should
say yeah so then I kind of got lost and
was like well I don't want to use this
anymore I'm not liking the results and
it's not really helping with this so
what kind of thing was it um I was using
a certain type of uh uh uh cleanser
oh that just was not a good fit for
because I also did not fully understand
what was my issue was yeah that's the
thing everybody has a different skin
type yeah everyone has different skin
types and yeah so uh I just uh what what
was I I just ended up I think what's the
word like ruining my Skin Barrier over
it which I think a lot of uh like
dermatologists now are saying like
they're seeing lots of people come in
just having used too many different
types of products and messing up their
skin and that becomes their main issue
so I have now gone down to just using
expensive but very good it's actually
like first time I'm having very good
results immediately I just use a
cleanser and I use a moisturizer SL like
barrier thingy I forgot exactly what
it's called I also twice a week yeah
twice a week I've been using an enzyme
mask for exfoliation you can leave on
you don't have to wash it off like in
the morning obviously you wash it but
you leave it on and it's it's yeah it's
good interesting and SPF I use SPF in
the morning I use 50 SPF damn you're
taking care of your skin that's pretty
high yeah
respect yeah I'll take a closer look on
your skin next time I see you to see if
it's working else happens
between oh now you're putting her on
spotlight
what about
you um well you know I wash my face um
you know put on like toner lotion and
cream um I use a bit of um like a
heavier cream since I don't go outside
so I just you know use it at home and
then I apply it again during night time
too
and uh sometimes I want to put on clay
masks so I do that to oh I like clay
masks yeah those are my favorite yeah
those are really nice like foamy ones
are nice and scrubs are nice and then
just masks in general are pretty
nice and what would you say then like
this is your routine but is there
something that like is really important
do you think for skin
care just like be sure to to stick to
your Basics like toner lotion
cream I think those are like the the
mandatory things that have to come first
cuz hydration is so important any SPF
moisturizer recommendations this person
is
desperate yes um I don't
like a sunscreen because they're too
sticky so I usually use uh lotion that's
not like sticky like it just feels like
how should I say
lotion so that's what I use I use um
chaso uh Japanese yeah mhm okay yeah
they have pretty good sunscreen there
somebody's saying also Sera is goated
and Anessa is really
good Anessa just sounds like a name for
one of nissa's family
members I think Sera is good for like a
base like if you're starting out because
s seravee it's oh
[Music]
s it's
just yeah I think pretty that's what I
was using
before and I don't think it irritated my
skin but it didn't tackle the issue I
was having so I don't use it anymore but
I think it's good for starting out maybe
yeah honestly the best thing you can do
it depends like what you want and how
sensitive your skin is but if there's a
specific issue really go to like go to a
like a skin
spa like you can't if it's like a major
issue go to a dermatologist but if it's
just kind of like oh I have redness here
oh I have little bumps here oh I have
like I want my I want glowy skin go to a
skin spy I think it's cheaper do you
guys have Neutrogena in North America
yeah oh okay cuz like the some of these
Brands you mentioned we don't are not
that common in Austria I think but
neutrino is maybe one thing for
Europeans that I could recommend maybe
also in Japan there's a really basic
brand basic as in I feel like it's just
like a like a such a standard but it's
you know good
so just you know it's simple but good
beod have you heard
of for yeah forf yeah that's recommend I
don't know if you can buy it outside of
Japan that easily but uh Amazon has it
oh there you go okay go look
it I've seen it on Amazon
before okay all right this one's taken
care of next first said please okay I I
want to talk about this too and Mum
already brought up a theory about this m
you want to read it actually then okay
why are so many girls interested in true
crime documentaries and how would you
perform the Perfect Crime I really
recently it's gotten better but I had a
face for like a whole year I think I was
watching true crime documentaries and
stuff for almost every day until I got
like a a lot of at least all of the
famous ones I've seen and then a lot of
Nono famous ones too I've I've I've I've
heard so many stories the reason I think
that I stopped is that I've been
oversaturated with that stuff and it's
like getting me this like negative vibe
when I watch these things now they make
me feel depressed and sad and shocked
I've heard too much [\h__\h] like I'm kind
of done with that chapter in my life but
I still must agree it seems to be
somewhat a girl thing because I talked
with guda about it while I was in this
phase I I mentioned it to her and she
was like also like oh yeah I also been
watching so much crime oh do you know
this one or do you know this in and I'm
like yeah oh my God that was so
terrifying holy [\h__\h] it's so [\h__\h] up
so what is it
explain um I think okay first of all I
think there's different levels and
people looking for different things out
of it MH because I think this is not
just a girl thing for certain types like
morbid curiosity everybody has that and
I think also like wanting to understand
the psychology behind actions that like
we cannot comprehend doing or you know
to get an understanding for it so I
think that's where like a lot of people
get drawn in and also like we've talked
about a specific channel that is I think
very interesting and it's very popular
like every video has millions of views
and it's police
interrogations ah yeah yeah that one
yeah that analyzes it yeah so people
like that yeah but then it can
also JCS is famous yeah that one yeah
but then there's like other like levels
of people go to where it's like wanting
to know like current truth like I think
people like you said you be it becomes
overs saturated but also people become
like desensitized and stop seeing they
stop seeing it as like real events and
it becomes like entertainment like it it
it's just like reading a book or so I
guess then it becomes interesting story
but more exciting because it's real
which is I think when it gets to that
point you need to step back like that's
also because these stories that M the
true crime stories are usually like
really [\h__\h] up ones that and that's
exactly why you feel like your brain
thinks oh that that is so unrealistic
that it doesn't seem like a real story
because it's so [\h__\h] up so it's more
like a just a story from a book or a
show right yeah becomes hard I I don't
know why it's a girl thing though
apparently like a lot of people said oh
you girls are so into True Crime but
it's not only Girling there's also of
course everybody watches it so yeah I
mentioned one things that mention was
that uh how do I phrase this
properly a lot of true cry like I think
for girls a lot of them are kind of like
I never want to be in this situation and
they feel like they're learning from it
a bit I think is another draw like oh
this is how this happened well I'm going
to be wary of this oh like all this so
there's a bit more maybe sympathizing
but also of course it depends like what
what the cases
are yeah I would say I'm learning
anything from it but I I do think like
there's certain cases where I felt like
that is good to know just because maybe
maybe there's things that I can't keep
an
I
out uh not for myself not saying that it
will although I do think one day when I
die it will be through
murder oh hey don't say
that or I probably just get hit by a car
or or I don't know uh I just don't think
I'll die
naturally um probably I'm fing this
because of True Crime yeah you probably
watched too
much and there one thing you know that
I've realized like okay last year I got
a financial adviser and the financial
adviser um had me get all kinds of basic
insurances uh and then I I said just
kind of jokingly um that I'm One
Insurance you cannot make me get is a
life insurance I'm not going to get a
life insurance because the moment I get
a life insurance I'm going to get
murdered because that happen so often
right it's always like that whenever
there's like a spouse murder it's always
like like they get them to have get a a
a life insurance insurance yeah and it's
always for that it's always because they
want the life insurance it's it's like H
just don't get a life insurance
don't it's a death flag for real yeah be
careful that's why that's why you got to
like look out for yourself yes but then
looking out for yourself I guess counts
as like get yourself a life insurance oh
no that's
family don't get life insurance let your
family scar when you die and I thought
crony was a Doomer one I'm I'm such a
doom poster for
real oh sorry I'm sorry I'm like do c do
you watch True Crime I I do watch True
Crime I actually watched it yesterday oh
[\h__\h] yes is it a new case or an old one
it's an older one oh and for some reason
like all the documentaries that I've
been watching have been for some reason
said in Canada so it's why why in Canada
like why there are a lot of Canadian
ones yeah and most of all the True Crime
things they're almostly from what I've
seen like uh North America because they
release like there's a way to getting
those interviews I don't think you can
get these interviews in Austria for
example you don't get access to it it's
crazy that you can just just get request
access to this kind of [\h__\h] and then
upload I mean that's [\h__\h] up anyway oh
my God Oh you mean like the inter are
you talking about interrogation
interrogations yeah oh it's interesting
that you can just do that but I mean
it's also educating for me and yes well
but uh so we like the interrogation
videos and all that but I've noticed
after a while I got like kind of bored
of that and then I tried rotten mango
do you know rotten mango
Stephanie I do because I
know I know another Hol life member who
watches
her yeah she basically she tells these
stories uh in like a podcast way she
just retells everything in a really
really really good way um it's kind of
Addicting too so I watch like a million
of those videos and then I've also again
stopped because I it's too much for me
I'm getting depressed from this oh but
she's good I feel like you need to kind
of dissociate yourself in a way like in
order for you to be able to uh like
watch
them do but
still I think what like I don't watch
that type of stuff anymore I think for
two reasons well no for quite a few one
yeah I just kind of I saw enough I think
cuz I also maybe went like when I was
younger went through like watching
YouTube videos about all like the most
famous Cas like all that stuff but then
uh oh shoot what was I going to say what
was I going to say what was I going to
say oh also something I had trouble with
was I could not dis associate and I
started thinking about like would the
people like would the victims be cool
with this or are the families really
cool with this sort of thing and then
also like especially like Netflix
documentaries it's all the same like
it's just the I I'm really annoyed with
like the production of it like the stock
footage the way they set up interviews
the over like they make it so over
dramatic and it just drives me crazy so
I
just I it's not I I'm not interested
anymore I've gotten what I need it and
also kind of makes me mad if I watch it
now yeah same I also stopped pretty much
so maybe it's a phase thing I think it
is a common phase to go through I think
like and I don't think it's just a girl
thing maybe it's girls that are more
likely to get super down the rabbit hole
but I think boys and girls both have
that cuz it's I think it starts with
morbid curiosity and just wanting to
understand how and why why that's the
biggest question I think I usually have
is why the [\h__\h] would you do that what's
wrong with your brain to do such things
that's all I want to know what what did
what got them to do that but usually
their explanation is is never good so
there's no it do start with morbid
curiosity I'm sure like in order to
understand how these people work but I
usually watch them to see uh exactly
like how it happened and for those
documentaries like I kind of just use it
more as a reference MH like as in for
performing The Perfect Crime
as yes yes yes yes
no but no but more like a rough
reference as to like what the exact
story was about and then if I was
interested I can go fact check and see
like what's right what's wrong and yeah
I just want to see like exactly cuz
often times the like there's a reason
why they went like down that path the
the criminals and I just want to I just
want to find out about the cause and
hopefully like
understand like how the the the programs
could help in reducing
MH reism and all that have you ever
watched
older um like true crime documentaries
because it's very interesting cuz even
within like from the ' 80s or '90s or
early 2000s even then it's so different
because like for instance the the things
they attribute like violence to like
violence Behavior to now would be like
what on like no what on Earth that's
yeah it's just very like how quickly
things seem to get dated so it makes me
kind of curious like oh what about from
like 20 30 years from now what now are
we you know thinking that be completely
dated but
[Music]
yeah
okay he played a bunch of video games
this is why he play
doom doom is a problem it was Doom it
was Doom
posting all right let's move on to the
next one uh H this is a cute cute
question do you all agree that every
girl needs a little black dress
bre break
dress I have one I I think not that I
really wear it much but it's really cute
so maybe we all do need a little black
dress maybe we do do you have one you
have one I don't you
don't I do okay let's get Mumy one why
would I wear it to but shopping for you
is so difficult mum holy
[\h__\h] I'm not easy to shop with tried so
hard
I don't like this is weird where where
would I wear this what would I do with
this yeah I don't like this batter I
don't like this color this is too
similar it's just easier to match I feel
like for black dresses yeah and it's
flattering because it makes you look
slimmer so this where would you wear
them
anywhere yeah what I mean maybe for like
we those grocery shops no but like let's
say okay let's say we're having a nice
dinner party yeah with a whole little
girls uh after Fest or so or a nice get
together with them or I don't know
something like that even if we're
talking about instances like that or I
don't know for once a year no no no can
be on things too yeah Pro yeah possibly
a funeral but then it shouldn't be too
little the black dress shouldn't be too
little it should be a bit longer and
probably uh no Chad is bringing funerals
up so I guess yeah a nice little cute
dress for the funeral yeah I don't think
you to wear a short for fin nice s
strapless or like where
spaghetti maybe not to funeral no but
I'm sure there's many ways of using it
you just have to have one ready and then
all the opportunities will open
themselves up to you
M go get one I don't go out enough
that's okay it's just nice to have it
ready is it yeah it in the closet and be
like oh yeah there's today I feel like
mour for my day so black
dress yeah let's go let's go okay let's
go maybe maybe we don't all need a
little black dress only if you have
a event where you might need it I guess
really I don't know I thought it's
easier to match like rent one with your
bag and all that yeah yeah okay crony is
pro black
dress uh uh quason Pro black dress m is
like
H right I think it depends okay next
one H I'm not a girl but I'm into
cosplay can you suggest some ways to
make the makeup stay long especially
Under the Sun or hot temperature I would
say
powder powder or fixing spray yeah I use
a
spray it depends you might have to test
it out on your skin uh cuz like for me
settings spray didn't work really it
makes me feel stickier and like wetter
yeah you have a bad one
a May it's just that I don't have much
uh good experience with um like fixing
spray like setting same what did it do
to you I I don't know I feel like it
just doesn't make your makeup
look good like it it makes it too shiny
or something I don't like
it it dries
though I I don't know there's still like
a bit of residue left that makes your
like entire makeup look kind of shiny
maybe it depends what you're going some
people want
shiny yeah yeah true other people want
Matt so it depends yeah it depends if
you want Matt I think you can just go
for powder though yeah powder would work
well for M yeah if you want shine like I
guess you can go for like setting spray
yeah dewy skin popular
too I wish I could do that I feel like I
just can't my skin just doesn't accept
that just doesn't
work pretend with a
highlighter I of a highlighter yeah I
try my best I Salvage the situation I I
get closer to deing this every single
day yeah well that was a short one we
already solved your problem wow we're
such girls yeah fix your problem easy
peasy and next one who wants to read
this
H I will okay okay how to be cute girl
and girl but my cool side takes over
sometimes I would be cute but very shy
to do girly things what is a good start
for a boyish girl like
me so I think I I have seen uh this
person in like you know events and meet
and greets and stuff so I know I know
what Nene looks like so but I understand
what you're trying to say I think maybe
what you need to think about is what do
you think is
girly and then then then that's what you
would probably aim for because I think
you know there's all types of
girlyness there's a more like say so
girliness there's a more like sexy
girliness there's a more cool girliness
and
mature um whatever you want to be and
then I think you could start from
clothing because growing out hair and
all that will take
ages but yeah maybe clothing is like the
the easiest way to get like a a quick
image change
agree girls or
disagree uh I'd say I agree like well
this person is saying that you know
sometimes they want to be cute uh I I
think like they kind of want to go back
and forth between cool and cute so I
think uh changing your clothes would be
like the biggest thing mhm but also you
can have like cute cool too like there
you can have like a bit of both yeah you
can mix mix and match just get like I
know appar it might it might actually
feel like weird if you're so used to
your wardrobe that you've been wearing
for years and years and years and you
don't wear girly clothes and then you go
shopping for it and you put on a dress
and just feels like and that's not me
this is weird this is weird but maybe
maybe you have a friend who's kind of
girly and then you can bring her along
and then you know get her input and have
her dress you and you just have to
accept it surely it will feel weird on
you but I think if it's styled well and
maybe if you even wear maybe a little
bit makeup to go along with it just it
doesn't have to be like you know a whole
set of makeup maybe just a little bit of
mascara you know can already change the
whole vibe and yeah you just have to get
confident I have confid two
recommendations oh please go one get
your nails done you you will feel very
girly yeah I did feel that when I saw
cie with nails I was like oh damn she's
so
girly to if it's more like also how you
act in personality like if you're scared
to act girly try being girly ironically
and eventually it will not feel ironic
and you'll get used to it oh cuz you're
scared you're probably like I I I don't
want to see him like I don't want to
look like I'm trying to be girly but I'm
not so just go for being girly
ironically and it'll just become more
and more
natural I do have to say about the nails
though as someone who doesn't do their
nails but it's still like pretty girly
um I feel like like nails every time I
put on like like just temporary ones it
is so annoying it it feels like cuz I'm
not used to it like I can't touch things
and it's just I feel like it's a little
bit too high level to start off with
nails because
that's it's hard to even touch things
and
feel not gel nails on your natural nail
I think are a good way to start cuz I
also I cannot stand stick on nails they
always fall washing your hair is so
annoying it gets I do not like stick on
nails I think I don't get extensions
when I if I I don't I haven't got my
nails done in a long time but if I get
my nails done I don't get extensions I
let them grow just a tiny it and then
yeah I get gel nails cuz it's still your
nail and it doesn't feel too long then
eventually it can start to but that's
slower and then you just file them down
a little bit I actually want to get my
nails and like my eyelashes done pretty
soon so wow yeah there's like a specific
uh style of nails that I wanted to stick
on CU they show when you done show it
show it yeah but I think for me uh um I
think clothes and then second makeup are
very important things I feel like those
can really change things up and then
nails they're more of nails and
eyelashes for example they're more of an
accessory in combination to your makeup
and your outfits so I feel like uh those
can come in later but I do understand
how Nails would make it feel girly cuz
yeah it will add a lot but I still think
it's kind of high
level and yeah and if you're getting gel
gel is expensive I just hard I've tried
just painting my natural nail again but
maybe I just have way too like my nail
polish is too cheap because it just
chips immediately I forgot how annoying
it is it'll chip after a few days yoube
maybe that's what you want maybe you
want it to be able to Chip and remove
freaking YouTube chat breaks like every
2 minutes today yeah they've changed
something and it's it's been like that
for a bit ridiculous yeah I love it
Indie
company okay okay I think I have one
more question here
and ah okay yes yes I want to talk about
this uh then crony read
please okay uh there has been quite some
talk about perfume for ladies on girls
talk so far but what kind of fragrances
do you appreciate on guys any brand you
would recommend or give to a male friend
relative or
coworker so just like you guys may not
have any idea about like perfume brands
for girls I have no idea what kind of
Brands you have I don't have any idea
what smells there are I mean I've
smelled some like just walking by
someone who's wearing way too much
cologne too much so I would prefer if
you just smell neutral just not not too
strong like anything I mean a little bit
of cologne may be nice but generally I
just like if you smell neutral like
nothing yeah like if you're covered from
head to toe like with ax spray or like
some sort of perfume like it's so gross
man it's not attractive it's just gross
it seems like so many people don't
understand that theyve putting on way
too much like maybe one Spritz is okay
but like I don't know you're showering
in it stop
yeah it it has to be a bit subtle like
not like overwhelmingly obvious like hey
I have cologne on please smell me you
know it has to be subtle yes may I share
my experience please okay long long
ago I made money like this was when I
first started making money for myself
you know and I decided I want like that
year I wanted to get father Al and
mother Al birthday
gifts so for father Al I asked mother Al
I said what do I get him and she said um
go to go to Nordstrom and you get him a
cologne oh so I went to
Nordstrom all of the cologne smelled the
same all of the men I could not tell a
difference I didn't think any of them
smelled good
and I was nervous I was like what if he
doesn't like it but also these all smell
the same why didn't she just tell me the
brand that he uses mhm so I left and I
said I didn't know what to get him so
then she told me which one to get and
then I went back and I got it but that's
my other than that no clue I don't know
any brand names all I know is Axe Body
Spray or Axe deodorant because of the
commercials aside from that truly do not
know yeah I don't know I'd prefer just
uh to not have everything smell too much
around me it's
just what are you trying to cover up
huh I know I think aiming to cover up bo
bo I I think that's good I was more
joking about are you trying to cover up
like the smell of cigarettes or
or I don't think that can I don't think
anything can cover that up yeah I I feel
like if you guys want like um like some
cologne recommendation might be better
to get something more Smokey or Woody
they all have like a bit of a musk gem
for colog but uh Woody and Smokey type
of smells are pretty nice Pine too
candles why can't why can't they just
like smell like soap or so though just
like smell like you took a
shower like just soap smell like like
whatever soap smells like just like you
know I don't want a cologne smell I just
want like a neutral I to a shower smell
not saying I'm not making the joke that
like otakus need to shower more that's
not the joke I'm making I'm not making
any jokes I'm just saying I prefer like
just like a natural shower
smell I think well I could be completely
wrong okay please guys feel free to
correct me so first let me say that
girls when they choose perfume and
makeup and all that I thought they girls
that you know do it to impress guys but
a lot of the time it's for themselves
yes yes yes yes a lot of the times it's
for themselves oh is it the other way
around for boys so I do not know I do
not know how much cuz this was something
I was thinking about the other day is
shaving do guys shave for themselves or
do they shave for you know whoever
they're attracted to or if they keep a
beard do they keep it for themselves cuz
it's what they're comfortable of course
it's different for it's different I
think it depends yeah if if if a guy's
in a relationship then they he might
just be shaving because the girl is like
your stubbles are hurting
me right so well the thing is too I
think I was thinking about that cuz I
was thinking about the upcoming girls
talk and I was like I wonder if like you
know that everyone watching do like do
they realize that most girls do makeup
for themselves cuz I don't think
that's really thought of yeah I thought
it was always for themselves that's a
good like obviously what girls thing but
then also I I always thought that guys
okay I always like assume guys shave for
themselves whatever they're comfortable
with but then I started thinking well I
don't know it's like everyone's
different anyways where am I going with
this okay so yeah I remember I'm going
so with the cologne is
cologne like yeah it depends why you
wear cologne I guess it why would your
guy friend want cologne is it to attract
others or is it for himself if it's for
himself you should ask him what kind of
smells he likes I guess but is that
weird to ask your guy I don't know oh I
put up a pole is it there yeah it's
there oh oh oh oh there a lot a lot
there is a lot for ladies though there I
think that is
more common for the men then cuz I I do
agree with with your point I I do have
this feeling that girls you know we
choose a nice flower we sent because we
want to smell ourselves
nicely not so much you know whoever
smells us but I mean I don't put on
perfume but anyway I I I feel pretty
nice when I put on perfume it's like oh
oh man I'm so glad I chose the scent you
know yeah I think I'm more sensitive to
Smells actually that's why I just I just
I I prefer neutral stuff I cannot step
into a like Bath and Body Works I will
get a headache the smells are oh I can't
I can't either I it's so much it's crazy
I remember when I was younger and like
would go to the mall for funsies my
friends would want to go to Bath and but
I'd wait outside like I could not go in
there I'd get a headache yeah it's
overwhelming I actually do like those
smells but I just don't want them to be
on like my own body because then I have
to smell it all the time you
know then it's get then it gets too much
if I just walk into like a nice Lush
store that I'm like oh oh yeah let's get
a bath oh Lush smells nice L smells nice
oh is it different Bath and Body L well
Bath and Body Works is insane like it's
so many sents and they're so strong so
different Lush
too I don't think Lush is as bad as Bath
and Body no Lush is so bad you have no
idea been to one in years is it maybe I
just don't remember maybe I just didn't
get a headache oh it hurts oh I will
always remember Bath and Body Works okay
we we're pretty much at a
50/50 interestingly
nice thank you for your input
everybody well well well well so
uh I think we have answered your
question I mean we don't really I don't
think we know any brand names so
unfortunately cannot um well I have
one uh it's a perfume like for both
girls and guys um it's called Joe Malone
Joe Malone Joe Malone Malone that sounds
so
Mei Jo Malone isn't that like the Malone
isn't that like some rapper
so so who Malone there's some
Malone yeah Malone
yeah I got to pay my loan off man post
[Laughter]
Malone it's a bit on the price here so
live but I I like him no like for my
perfume who the [\h__\h] is Jo
Malone Joe Malone I don't know maybe
it's the founder who knows we've never
seen this before Mal's the last name Joe
is a first
name who it's j o oh my gosh that's also
a first name yeah
insane but isn't j o like isn't that
usually like for girls
oh they have like stuff for guys too oh
I meant the name itself if you like Joe
spelled j OE is a guy j o is usually
short for something else for a girl
right uh maybe oh yeah right yeah right
I'm looking up this per Joe Malone who
are
you I looked it up to it but like um
just seeing the brand no
person oh wait now I found the
Wikipedia Jo for Joanne
Joanne yeah okay yeah but I know some
guy friends who uh use Joe Malone and I
was like oh guys use it too I have no
idea oh so yeah not all okay now we we
see an uprise in sales for Joe Malone
perfume let's go sponsorship
do uh there were some wait was it just
was it room fragrances or was it
perfumes like a whole life was selling
some like scents before for some members
I don't know was it was it a fragrance
for rooms or for
people you guys know you guys remember
in the chat
I fragrance fra frag how do you say it
fragrance fragrance
[\h__\h] uh for people okay it was for
people m
so that one was probably more of a girly
one I wish I kind of want them to do one
for Hol and girls our perfumes even
because now I feel like they maybe open
themselves up another door in that
direction again with that girly fashion
brand did you see that we're doing like
a fashion brand now in life did you see
you see I saw I saw some yeah and uh
maybe with that because that is aimed
towards a f audience perhaps you can
also look into uh perfumes scents
again recomend anything
because once I was shopping and a JP
member was with us oh and she was like
like there was a like we were looking up
her for
perfume and we got a sample and I
smelled it and I was like oh this one's
pretty nice and she smelled it and she
was like oh that's
[Music]
disgusting was it
to
[Music]
yes I just assumed that she would be the
kind of person you would go shopping
with out of Japanese members because
yeah one of the closest ones to
[Laughter]
you I kept it to myself you yeah
you oh that sounds funny
so I I will step out of there you know
I'd recommend like berries or something
but I'm sure that's a horrible idea
that's a horrible idea no no I don't
think so I mean okay I don't know for
men uh but for girls perfume with berry
scent let's
go
yeah like black bear I don't know
something yay like rasp like mixed berry
yeah you smell like a smoothie sberry I
want to smell like a
strawberry I love strawberry yeah
yeah okay okay okay so uh good luck with
your cologne
Endeavors that's it for the questions I
mean there were more but these are the
ones I picked I think there were plenty
thank you guys for sending in the
questions I hope we could help you in
some way or another uh very helpful what
do we
think I think we were helpful I think so
I think we answered the questions yeah
we did toally did oh thank
you I love these sound effects I
recently discovered the sound effects
that are already programmed into my
roadter so I've been using it a lot nice
oh my
God although today I should have used a
bit more damn it I got more I got one
oh than I need that I need that on my
soundboard but I'm too lazy to put it in
there oh well oh what what but I have a
similar
one oh sad trumpet a these are communal
s trumpet makes me happy oh stop taking
wait these just Discord Pap are you just
play you just play this
s Ollie always uses them too a stop no
no no I remember when these sounds first
came into Discord and we had our first
like whole of English collabs with
whoever then like there were some people
who were always abusing these at least
before the stream it's like who the [\h__\h]
is pushing all these horse
sounds who who who brought them to the
server I wonder oh wait are they not
like standard ones no oh it was it
am was it m no it was it was right wait
M probably no it's
m it seems like something it's 100%
M you did all of these M no you just did
did the horse n so I can assume you're a
horse girl no I think G did some of them
too I can imagine you wow sure I don't
remember which one she did cursed we
should take away the soundboard wres
from you we should take it away I don't
think we
should I
disagree oh well okay I think uh of
course
yeah I think we're uh done being girls
for today so now as all girls do before
we sleep we will take off our skin and
go to bed as
skeletons mhm I think that was one of uh
like something like that was asked as
well do we shed we shed we totally
shed sorry I was playing undertale
yesterday
oh okay okay s I'm already of my
skeleton form yeah you ready to shed
some skin mhm especially that snaky girl
over
there was that you okay that's you
wait oh my God when you guys are making
these sounds you sound like it could be
either one of
you why are you making these sounds
you're freaking me
out girls
dismissed girls dis and
say thank you for watching guys thank
you girls for being here
today
oh
dony yeah I remember from you yeah don
don Oh yay goodbye guys thank you have a
nice day evening bye
[Music]
byebye your merch your merch up your
merch oh oh I didn't mean like I I
didn't mean I had to advertise it on
stream I just meant to I should tweet
tweet about it but thanks for reminding
me yeah my merch froggy wa merch a link
in the description is ending soon I'm
going to post the pictures on Twitter
afterwards okay the business girl
business woman helping business woman oh
and also my fake ma uh apparently
pre-order is ending soon as well if you
want a Waba faka I should tweet that out
too hey y hey yo hey yo but I didn't
really sorry I didn't want to advertise
mom I didn't want to advertise Mom I
wanted to no I wanted to well then do
you have something to advertise both of
you your merch my merch your merch it's
ending soon pretty ending soon advertise
advertise oh and then also Kima is at 1
million
soon go did you press four girls press
four you should go yeah you should go to
the Chima MV oh can you do it now can
you do it now can you open the tab both
of you and then at the same time please
wait for don't press four yet just open
the tab for Kimera pause the
video and then when I say press for you
press four
[Music]
okay are you ready okay uh please press
for
[Music]
now oh huh huh oh my why did I have the
feeling I knew exactly what this would
do are you not seeing it no oh I I'm
seeing it I are you seeing it CR oh oh
oh okay oh yeah oh yeah that's uh
that's that's something how would you do
that I it wasn't on purpose uh it's just
because it's at 40% of the
video wow I how did you do that at all
it just happens oh you mean how my butt
does that yeah yeah yeah I just um that
was amazing squat squat I see
squat whoa you got you got your like you
know curves back yeah no I mean it is
it's a nice scene but if you look
properly and you will see it's a bit of
deformed kind of ass but well I think
man y it's looking good that's the way
you are looks like you've been working
out that mean no not at all but thank
you so much for your positivity girls
that's what we do at girls talk we we
spread the girl positivity thank you
thank you so much for looking at my butt
now you're free to go
so and if again okay I'm bye bye byebye
byebye byebye
[Music]