[Music]
ah get
be
[Music]
okay guys
K
before anything begins I wanted to show
you the current state of myself
because it looks
funny it's a funny bug I think I can fix
it probably
but I feel like something is wrong with
me can you tell like
H what what what is this what is this
current state of me can you
tell
I got a stiff
[Music]
neck I'm very stabilized sleep
paralysis help
me help
me let me get out of this
[Music]
body yeah the only thing that's moving
is my my breathing
animation I
possessed help me muscle pain yeah I'm
totally [\h__\h] up
everything just by watching the
pre-recorded
footage okay let me bring in should I
just stay like this let me bring in some
bgm
though
don't worry don't
worry here elevator music I think we
need some elevator
music welcome to the
[Music]
stream I like I like this this
funny especially when I look from one
side to the the
other it's like one of those challenges
where you try to stay still because you
you're doing a Tik Tok
video where time stands still
supposedly and I'm like the best at this
nobody can beat
me
okay let me try to fix
[Music]
it this should fix it I
hope wait
wait didn't fix
it
wait really okay one one second how
about I
switch uh this is what the early stages
of life to do was like maybe
I'm not moving okay let me
restart restarting this
thing
already two heads don't don't don't no
I'm I'm still not
moving I'm still not
moving oh wait you can't even see it
thank God
let me restart the phone no no no okay
how about the different app cuz I'm
moving on my
phone but not on the PC
um wait we have
this other
application perhaps
this one will move for me yeah it does
okay no no I'm not stuck chel no no no
no don't worry don't worry okay outfit
is going to be
[Music]
this nice okay this should be this
should be
[Music]
fine nice
oh wait wait one
[Music]
second
okay all right all right sorry I I
actually I just wanted to show you cuz
it looked
funny yay y yay I'm moving I'm free I've
been free
hoay I feel so free and joyful and WI
iggly and
jiggly I am bouncy
waha I am
free hopefully I'll never be stuck again
that was a truly truly traumatic
experience yeah but yeah uh welcome to
the stream this stream is a Super Chat
reading stream because we obviously got
some reading to
do but also at the same time talking
about the live I feel like in the super
chats
probably people will say stuff like oh
my God this song with waya was so
amazing and then I will take that as a
as a prompt to talk about that
particular song So when when a song H
when a Super Chat mentions a particular
song or so I will go into that in oh
wait I will need my phone though wait
it's finally
time
[Music]
finally I wonder if I even understand
the context of my tangents
[Music]
anymore
I have this
memo which one is it
okay
um
ah
oh there's still
yeah some things I didn't talk about let
me I have this like really really good
pretty organized
note let
me let me let me
[Music]
delete
okay uh the roboco Thea tangent I told
those right the hot tangent there really
wasn't much but I told that I told you
about I told you about the the weird
lady questioning me before my flight
right I told you did I tell you about
the napping in the nap
cap and the the Beagle I
did and I told you more or less I told
you a little bit about the new staff
who's cute and
British okay so I can delete all of
those then okay then I have tangents
about dance lessons I have tangents
about
honeyworks uh recording
thingy
uh nail the nail collab I think I told
everything about how I I gave leftover
pizza to
[Music]
Iris and this and
that oh yeah this is just a small detail
but KY has this huge wheel right the cat
wheel and I thought that was huge and
then I saw roko Senai has an even bigger
one it's insane you could probably let a
toddler a pretty big toddler running
that
wheel probably almost a
child yeah a wheel for cats but like
huge especially considering how her cats
they
cats are on the smaller
side wait that just reminds me I feel
like I had a dream
where H
Senai was going to
possibly I just remembered no that was
so
sad I'm not going to say it out loud
because that was sad that was a sad
dream for
me
no don't even want to think about that
sure
okay
so p blah blah did I tell you about the
fancy Starbucks I think I did but did I
tell you about the afternoon
tea with
jenma I I did make a like a YouTube
short or like I didn't edit it yet but I
took footage for that oh b b b b hello
yesterday no the day before
yesterday I raided for M and now they
raid me again
hello this is uh the beginning of a
comfy Super Chat reading stream as well
as tangents about my 3D Live
yesterday mhm welcome welcome Mutual
rating so tit but so I did not tell
about the afternoon tea right but I
think I guess I'll keep that until I put
out the YouTube
[Music]
short the the the dude walking in front
of me I step on him tangent can be
deleted the the JMA Pokemon
cards and the fridge head incident can
be
deleted okay
okay oh I didn't write down anything
[Music]
interesting okay okay well so as I said
we're going to go for the super chats
and when there's something that I have a
tangent for I will I will give that to
you you stepped on someone proudly with
lots of confidence I stepped on someone
who walked in front of
me without any regards to how close he
is in front of me and how he's not
faster than me and still tries to cross
my path especially when the path was so
wide oh oh oh don't even get me started
don't even get me
started should have been me
no I would hate you cuz I hate that
person didn't he cut yeah yeah that's
what I mean he cut in front of
me
rude but like diagonally and then like
not even like walking faster than me
like if he cut in front of someone then
at least be faster than that
person okay okay okay
okay calm calm down calm down calm down
this is a topic that infuriates me
so no no no no no he can't hurt you
anymore but I can hurt him still right
right I can still hurt him can
[Music]
I
okay everything is
[Music]
okay he's already dead
okay
Hyer
Hyer my
analyzer please analyze my
[Music]
superjets it almost feels like it's two
days ago not just yesterday because
yesterday I I yo I ruined my sleep
schedule and that was
yeah that's why it feels so weird right
now for
me but uh it was indeed
yesterday Super Chat rating time Super
Chat should I show you guys the Super
Chat window again that's helpful
right I think that's pretty
helpful
[Music]
oh oh I have some
filter on it that makes it like this sea
[Music]
fruit cuz it was for the the timer for
our movie watch along recently which I I
don't know if you saw the schedule but
we're doing the new Chicken
Run movie watch
along this week let's go yay yay can't
believe that they would put out a new
after so many years they put out a new
Chicken Run movie and it's during my
time in whole life which means we can
watch it for the first time
together that's like so so as as if
they're doing doing it on
purpose is
there I was looking for a super chat but
I guess it doesn't
exist
was that
real was the was that Super Chat real
you guys know what I'm talking about
H I wonder if it was
real is it just like a legend a
[Music]
myth which one
um does anyone have a screenshot
it was so
[Music]
funny I wish it was
real where did you find it
B well
well
Twitter
Twitter that red one was a fake what why
why I want it to be
real oh
going back to stock CH
soon ah damn it
[Music]
okay
okay you don't even know what I
mean you know I didn't even I didn't
even say
anything okay uh so let's begin this
let's begin let's begin starting we
cannot lose time this is of the essence
unknown D Sky thanks for the pinky to my
Kami ooshi the only thing will explode
when you start the stream is carefree's
excitement I new the fact this content
will be a banger and show how your
amazing Idol thank you yeah I wrote this
in the pre- chat that I'm worried if I
press there'll be a starting stream
button or so that something will
explode I was really concerned but
everything went smoothly I don't think
there was a single like lag um I the
main stream I actually I did it with the
highest
latency so the chat delay was probably
pretty big but it didn't matter because
I didn't interact with you
guys but it said highest quality so I
went for that hoping that the quality
was good and then I didn't want the chat
to break my PC so I was looking looking
at the chat on my phone the whole time
mhm it was lagging so bad for me
what that's the first time I hear a
Benny
lag
a
a no
issues had no
issues okay
good region thing any other Australians
who had a lag was driving me
mad was fine for me oh there's the other
Australian so that that that maybe that
was an internet thing for for you I mean
I've heard I've heard the legends of
Australian
internet from B
[Music]
so well you watched the archive probably
didn't you I couldn't imagine you
watching the
archive so that was surely
smoother anyway thank you Sky junky
chunk thanks for the r Super Chat
notification 9h hour countdown oh what
you got a notification for that it's
probably just a notification of Me no
not even that probably not even that
time
wise are you just notifying yourself
very important it is important every
hour is important so that you're aware
when it's happening so you don't miss it
thank you very much M junky
chunk H J1 thank you for the pinky I
still can't believe it's only two weeks
until the end of
2023 thank you k for being with us this
year and thank you always for being our
light Kami and kagayaku Idol KF are so
proud of you I sent biggest love and
support to
[Music]
you
thank you nah don't don't let's not talk
about this man
that's but again there's I yesterday
when I talked to narissa we got like
really excited about um moldes being way
less than a month away from us and also
I'm meeting
waya also before that
so
yeah yeah
I'm excited
actually and I'm also excited to just
get over this
current time until until Christmas I'll
I think this week will be a bit
stressful for me because I have to do
the sock puppets thing and I'm
still like trying to get some things
going um you know like organizing the
among
collab and I have to do make all the
thumbnails unless I commission someone
to make them but I think I made them
last time too and they were quite decent
so I feel like I want to make
them but maybe I'll commission them I'm
not
sure did you get the okay to show steo
stream not yet I was told I'll hear back
from them in the middle or at the end of
the week well the end of the week is
going to be a
problem so hopefully it's in the middle
of the week but we'll see how how many
people will be in the
collab well almost
everybody almost everybody I think the
only ones are GAA because I didn't hear
back from her and M because she's on a
break but even Shi said she will
be
like I think she like she said something
about about like yeah she can be
there somehow it it sounded like maybe
she's just going to be in the voice chat
and not playing but I don't think that's
the case I I think she'll be there so I
think it's uh so am say yes
yes I think it's just uh M and good ah
and bailes because she has some work to
do apparently and also she doesn't like
among us
but but it's more the fact that she has
some work to
do so minus
three I
think yeah hold life minus whole life
English minus free I
think why is it a surprise that amaz
in why I mean yes she may not be doing
like solo streams much at the moment but
uh I think she said collapse are fine
like she quickly quickly agreed to it
and then I got to say I was like I was
planning first I was plan planning to do
a full Ian or like as many as I can get
um VR Christmas
stream but then we're already tanging
about something
completely unrelated to the frd life so
let me just tell you uh then I was told
that like uh Advent wouldn't be a to use
any like VR models like even if they got
some
commission and I guess like then I asked
like what about cardboard cutouts but
like eh even that like that kind of like
killed my
motivation um so then I was like okay
how about I just plan the Among Us thing
for everybody and then I planned
something for myth for
VR um but that kind of didn't work work
out either because it probably would
have been four out of five and I feel
like that's kind of sad
so so I just gave up on it now because I
also
like yeah whatever
blah so sorry I tried to get something
and we are going but it's just been kind
of
like killing my
motivation yeah it would be sad to miss
someone and in terms of like all
just like I don't want to leave out
Advent and I feel like it would have
been nice to have them in like their own
little cute um VR models but that's not
going to work out that's not
happening
yeah yeah but Among Us will be nice and
uh we're still doing the Advent calendar
and
and yeah you're going to get a sock
puppet finale with to which I have to
write the
script by tomorrow probably I should
write it I should write it tomorrow what
do I have tomorrow I only have a stream
late in the evening
right I don't even know what to write
about
help help uh
help
help yeah but as as long as it's uh not
past Christmas I'm kind of like my mind
is occupied with that of stuff so I'm
I'm I don't know why I made my schedule
so full I don't know why I made my
schedule so full why did I do
that I wanted you guys to be like oh
hype hype
schedule can FAA help I don't know I
don't want to furest at her so last
minute what the heck is a hokido game
it's a sua game but with Hokkaido and
like Japanese map and and you create
Hokkaido which is the biggest prefecture
in Japan and I know that sounds so
stupid why bring sua game back but but
but but but but when I watched the
trailer of it it it was kind of really
funny because every time you make some
prefactor by by joining smaller
prefactors together it it it's just they
made really funny noises and yeah they
say the names and it's like really
really
funny and I no I just wanted a short
stupid game for a short stream early in
the day yeah yeah yeah it was so
funny those funny noises
yeah Kyla played it no
[Laughter]
way
also played it Oh I thought I was was
going to be the first one I just found
it randomly in in all the games that we
have permission
to okay okay so you maybe know why I
want to play it the voices are funny and
they're not just in my
head I'm going to be the first probably
also the last
anyway thank you junky no wait we're not
here we're here thank you Jan
D monkey the may be almost over but
let's go out with a bang it's been
another hell of a year with everyone and
you've given us kfp so much to be happy
and proud about and I'm looking forward
to seeing another another year rev you
in kfp thank you so much I'm also
excited but also scared like okay I'm
looking forward to like
January but everything past that like is
is still a big mystery to me
although I had a meeting last night that
I first wasn't planning to attend to and
just listen to the
recording uh but I ended up going
because I was still
awake and it was a good meeting and it
made me look forward to 2024 um also a
bit more like kind of a relief reliefing
meeting very good very good very
[Music]
good not going to give any details cuz
it's confidential but it was
good yeah but that's why I stayed up so
late and then right at the end of it I I
just
like I was going to go to bed but then I
had to urgently talk to
narissa
and that turned into to like a 2hour
conversation one I think it was a one
one and a half hour meeting and then a
2hour narissa
conversation so then I went to bed at
like 700
[Music]
a.m. yeah I was I was getting tired and
extremely
hungry but um yeah I I I wanted to be uh
I wanted to talk to
nura Smoothie by the way she just
completely adjusted her thing like I
gave her dinner at 7:00 a.m. and as per
usual she woke me up after 6 hours for
her breakfast then I went back to sleep
after 2 hours like she doesn't do it
according to the date to the time of the
day no she does it according to when I
go to sleep she adjusts it she's yeah
she moves with
me it's all premeditated yeah you should
give her dinner no no no no as I said
like it makes no it doesn't matter when
I give her the
dinner like if it's before I go to sleep
and then I go to sleep she will always
wake me up 5 to 6 hours into my sleep
doesn't matter when I went to
sleep
yeah she knows she knows everything
she's all knowing alarm cat
yeah she's been very consistent in this
now looking forward to the molds falling
asleep to the sound of the ocean and
being awakened by the sound of the ocean
rather than a cat that
[Music]
goes yeah until Nissa wakes you up at
5:00 a.m. I don't know why why she would
do that I don't think so I wonder if
she's a long sleeper cuz I sleep long if
I can
but we will have to wake up for in time
for the breakfast that's for
sure cuz resort island breakfast is
dope oh oh oh Spirit snow was
listening
[Music]
ah
so
there so there but I was thinking even
if I I might do this thumnails myself
but maybe maybe Spirit snare could make
like a template for me
because I have this image in my head for
the thumnails I want I want um to have
all the girls that are in the background
of the thumpnail I want them to be kind
of on like monitors of spy cameras like
that are kind of like green is and and
uh bad
quality you know what I mean can you
imagine I want that to be in the
background and then in the front is the
person who the thumnail is for I can do
that okay but I will have to tell you I
have to count how many people are really
particip and I have to know if F
probably going to be one person
huh W moo
I would be so funny if it was if they
were separately though but are you going
to do among us as the
team one person or
separately made them play Separate I can
they though can they I don't know if
they can but they're playing they're
playing Mario Kart separately but only
like they're not allowed to be in the
same race right
cuz well they only
have well wait I don't really know I'm
not part of the Mario Kart thing so I
don't know the details
[Music]
but oh they can play split screen huh
yeah for for Mario Kart huh from the
phone Amal from the phone nah let's just
have them as a
team oh but like two
mines better than one
when like susing out people and
discussing things they're like already
overpowered oh well oh well uh blah BL
uh where was where were
we thank you J monkey you're sco in
2024 it's going to be a good year I
think from what I can tell now a good
year for some reasons but I still don't
know a lot like my I'm I still have a
lot of mysteries in my brain about
2024 but also some some good
[Music]
things very easy to have multiple in one
sitting true
yeah I
guess wait so it's 12 wait is it
12 is it 12 12 I said mine is three
right and we're 15 right are we 15 we're
15 right but then F counts as one so
it's more like 11
right that's if it's 11 it's good cuz
then we have five on like five five that
you can put in the background and one in
the front uneven number is actually
good 10 in the background and one front
person clal as one I would
say okay okay
okay let's go H Flora Flora Flora thank
you for the red chat
com why why no text only only emote but
it's a cute one heart heart heart heart
heart heart heart heart heart heart
heart did they reply no no yet I'm just
assuming also also because uneven
numbers are good not only for idle units
but also for
thumbnails for group collab
[Music]
thumbnails sorry I'm late no worries but
you're not really that late I started 20
minutes late so you're only 40 minutes
late but it's good we we barely I'm at
Super Chat number
seven I'm at Super Chat number seven
the
realization the usual
Pace uh Ultima okay thank you for the
red attat let's get this party started
let's get this
party but she sings What in
here in here
this concert is extra special because we
get to celebrate our lovely Kami at the
end of an amazing year filled with lots
of wonderful moments of you and kfp
here's to many more years to come and
even more memories to make thank you
thank you yes I think you know ideally I
would have liked to have it on my
birthday of course but having it at the
end of the year gave me a nice
opportunity to
celebrate the end of the year basically
a little bit more or less it was it was
the new reason so
yeah the end of the
year
no a good way to close the
yeara and if it wasn't for the timing if
it was around my
birthday then I wouldn't have been able
to perform
Lami you know the time where I I started
planning
this
um this live where I got the okay that
is happening and they're like okay give
us the real proposal now is where I uh
where where Lami was actually like
booming and an option to perform the
song it was the perfect
timing if it was any earlier than that I
probably would have have would not have
been able bble to implement it into my
life
yeah what about F I told you guys I will
bring up these things when they come up
in the Super chats which they surely
will will we upload the dance and fix
camera uh did we know she tweeted about
it a fixed camera um I I I I will be
getting some fixed camera angle
videos footages um but not for all of
the songs because some of them maybe
didn't turn out so
[Music]
well when you look at it from a fixed
angle so uh yeah just some of
them I mean I don't want all of them
anyway I don't need all of
them yeah I was thinking maybe making a
short of the chorus or so of
Lami m
[Music]
mhm and uh I do have a YouTube short
already recorded for sleep talking for
the
chorus then I have like a joke uh short
recorded already um that I have to edit
and decide when to upload and then I
have two shorts with Matsui
Senpai did you like the blue for real
don't talk about it don't talk about it
yet don't don't don't don't get there
let's go back to the super chats okay
don't don't bait me and tease me into
going off rail
n stay on
track anyway yeah let's go Ultimo I'm
excited for 2024 so I hope you'll be
part of it as usual looking forward to
spending more time with
you tie dye TDP thank you for the pinky
looking forward to matching to watch in
the vult stuck having to wake up early
for
work early wait you're donating in US
Dollars and you had to wake up early by
okay well I mean the stream was really
early for you but I guess you had to go
to work speaking of work you have he he
kicked a lot of asses here it brings my
joy to see my oie PR 3y lifeo thank you
did I did I kick a lot of ass I wonder
what you
mean I feel like I got my own ass has
kicked like sometimes to like not not
like being bonked or whatever but just
like me feeling like the world is
kicking my
ass a lot of like sad
things but I guess I also kicked some
ass a little bit here and
[Music]
there I kicked back Mutual ass kicking
that sounds so stupid well thank you I
hope you enjoyed the B what did you
think tell
me are you here in the chat right
now tie dye
Doo tie dye Doo tie Dy tie dye no no
TIY
TI No
okay I'm waiting for you to come back to
[Music]
me
waiting Tick Tock time is
ticking anyway thank you
B is that a carpet an orange carpet once
again nice this time it will be shorter
than last orange carpet I promise well
maybe I think it might be shorter we all
have waited a long time for this to come
it might be late but what a way to end
the year 2023 with a big bang
interesting enough it somehow worked
well to be end of the year celebration
yeah and birthday life at the same time
yeah after seeing the full guest list
really hyped up to see what kind of
performance you will be showing today
with this concert closely wrapping up
the year 2023 and hopefully you uh have
achieved all of your goals this year as
well honestly being work always uh been
overlap with streams and I have not been
able to watch most of live streams since
then jino this is a little bit hard to
read probably last two years or so so
for two you're saying for two years you
had troubles watching my streams live
okay okay okay okay
okay although I do try to jump in time
to time and hope that no one catch me
watching here in stream at work does
that work at least catching few minutes
or hour of live stream if Lucky but hey
gang isn't so bad though and I can see
he says it and I can always watch live
stream during the oh weekend anyways and
[\h__\h] sleep and time to watch ooshi yeah
I may not be able to attend most of live
streams but I will then well try to
attend as much conventions and lives
you're very very much always there with
kfp to support you that way as well
anyways thank you so much for making
this concert possible and looking
forward for more future streams you're
my Kami as always let's have more more
fun in
[Music]
2024 I'm over the
table Kiwa kiaha
[Music]
hang H hang
hang m m m
[Music]
even if I can read this I don't
understand what it means I only
understood
kiaha well well let
me
Papa
pap
but that was at least the first part
that I actually did read sounded pretty
much like what I said
right it does say I don't know anything
else but kiaha is always number one in
my
heart I always watch and support you
thank you you know I feel like even when
thinking about like whole life Ian
bands as a
whole when when you think about fans at
like conventions fans who go to
conventions and uh like concerts and so
on who stand out I'm very proud to say I
think you're one the one one of the ones
that stand out the most in terms of like
passion energy and
attire and I'm so happy that you are one
of
us you know like you got to assert
dominance the kfp dominance and you're
definitely doing that thank you for
rapping kfp
always yeah the bright orange helps a
lot yeah but like he's what I mean is
like also he's always in the front line
like doing the UT gay really loudly and
getting others to join in on that
because I feel like in a lot of
situations maybe if he wasn't there then
people would be too shy or so and
wouldn't know what to do and he kind of
leads the way in some situations I think
you guys already have learned I think by
now that you can function and do UT
without him as well but I think he
definitely helped uh bring that kind of
culture in conventions to the fans and
so on you know what I mean maybe maybe
I'm giving him too much credit but I
feel like you
know he
[Music]
helped
yeah yeah and I'm just as as the Wawa I
am whenever I
see my fans like proudly
repping their kfp status it makes me
really happy
because
because then I know that I have
fans yeah and we can show others hey waa
has fans waa is good you know
so thank you for always confidently
repping waa to jino and to all of
you thank you we Bear for the red wait
Jindo actually I guess you get a red a
red a kiss too poo
[Music]
poo where bear f for the red dad album
release first proper fry life several
appearances in other fry lives 2023 has
been quite the year you you didn't even
you you're forgetting if you counting
highlights you should have counted also
the first Ian overseas
concert our first IRL
concert you're missing something
important
here very
important no never forget how far you've
made it you even heard your hand writing
autographs for just a small section of
your fans that sounds kind of like a
roast Rising Phoenix flying even even
ever higher thank you than you thank you
getting
graded yeah I'm grading your Super Chat
F sit
down just kidding sorry sorry sorry
thank you were Bear yeah there were a
lot of good things this year a lot of
exciting things I hope that this will go
on next year or or be even
more yeah I do think there will possibly
be more 3D opportunities than this
year which
is definitely a good thing thank you
where hoping to have you around much
much
longer kle k
juice on some kit in it I think uh D FAA
D for the
rainbow W rainbow and most of it is just
nothing written why why
why is this finally going to happen
finally is the right
word yeah it did finally happen it was
so surreal to me I was so relieved when
it was finally over and when I finally
could proudly present it to you
guys yeah I was really really
glad oh wait here it is here it is you
didn't see
it thank you FAA for waiting for being
so patient and for being so excited
sharing the excitement with me thank you
so much
[Music]
Papa definitely a long time coming yeah
tii also with a
rainbow ttio this year is coming to an
end please keep up the good work next
year KY will always love and support you
we all want to see you live concert
nama
thank you why did you have to add
this this is the word for life why did
you why did you make that one
so specially
important why putting pressure on me
[Music]
here it's
yeah like let's say let's say uh let's
talk about let's let's assume that I'm
doing a 3D live for my next birthday but
this time on
time I I I will I would assume that it
will also be pre-recorded a few weeks
before
because
because it will have to be like that
it will have to be like that maybe
another time but like you
know I I yeah I want to be home in
Austria when that airs for yeah reasons
so but but I don't even I don't I I
don't think it's that important like for
a real life concert yeah live okay but
like uh for something like this a
YouTube thing I don't think there's a
difference it makes no difference
whether or not it's like actually
happening at the time when it's
streaming or or if it's pre-recorded if
I wouldn't tell you then I mean I could
just act although it would probably be
very body body very um noticeable that
it's not life because I will be in
Austria but
still I think from the
contents if anything pre-recorded will
come out better because I can fix things
I can change angles
beforehand you
know it it can be more Perfection ised
so I prefer
[Music]
that yeah it's more polished the end
product is just
nicer I mean that's what I mean what I
thought you mean with uh you know PR
recorded versus live but
there's uh another another level of
life that I don't know if with so much
dancing is realistic for someone who
spends most of their time at the PC
every
day uh dancing for 1 hour singing live
life with
really rough choreographies is uh for
someone who doesn't work out all the
time I'm going to tell you it's just not
realistic unless you are going to have a
[\h__\h] heart attack and asthma attack
yeah don't forget about
that
yeah I mean you could make really simple
coros but that's just not me that's just
not me
you got a treadmill yes yes I will be
working on that so who knows maybe I'll
I'll get really good but uh I used to be
able to do that I used to be able to
dance and sing
live I had way more stamina cuz that's
you know I was trained for
it but now that my job uh is me in front
of my computer all day at
home
like sometimes the most I walk all day
is from bedroom to
Kitchen it's pretty
[Music]
bad sometimes when I walk to the
supermarket I feel like w okay today
I've
walked that already feels like I did
something good for my
body
yeah freeing ring I can only the ring
fit if I ever find that
stupid switch thingy again can't call it
a CD what is it the game the actual
game not going to buy a new
one cartridge there we go and a
cartridge of a pear tree
[Music]
what well Partridge and cartridge sound
very similar I don't even know what
Partridge
means anyway thank you for being so
generous than than actually wow I just
realized the the last one is a
double and so these are two Reds and
this one is a double so it's kind of a
triple
triple and a
half you crazy thank you hi oh it's a
bird oh
oh
elud
elud I feel like that's a name I haven't
heard in a little bit but maybe I'm
going crazy am I going
crazy thank you but yeah thank you
[Music]
hiim have so many kisses for you thank
you so
much thank you thank you thank you thank
you for the
[Music]
support every item in 12 dayss of
Christmas is a burden somewhere what
what are you talking about what about
the onion
rings wait five on five is it golden
rings actually wait what was it again
actually five golden
rings
five five it's not
Birds it's golden rings so how is that a
bird you're just kidding
[Music]
right
there's a kind of bird called a ring
what 12 Days of
Christmas so let
[Music]
me oh oh [\h__\h] it is it is
birds
doves part Partridge
doves French
Hens calling
Birds now apparently gold rings are that
geese
aling
swamp what what about mates what about
the milking Maids how is that a bird
bird and the ladies
dancing and the Lords are
leaping and what's the I don't even know
what Piper piping
[Music]
is and the drummer
druming yeah no I don't know yeah
there's a lot of uh birds in
there but not
all
[Music]
okay back to the real business guys
don't don't get me off
track red thank you for two pinkies this
year you really showed how strong you
are Ki strong of heart strong of
mind you've shown Ambitions making an
album going to Japan for so many lives
always improving your streaming content
in so many aspects as aspects ass
p d thank you very much I I would also
say I have a strong
mind it's the end of the year so maybe I
can say this um I think it's quite
common probably anyway but
um there
was definitely a
time in the second half of the Year
where I really really really really was
not sure how I can keep on
going and was
wondering if I were to graduate when
should I do
it um but like there were a lot of
things bothering me it was several
things and I will say that a lot of the
things have resolved since then so don't
worry I am good
but I'm good now but there were lots of
ups and lots of downs this year and I
think that just
the the stressful time of having to
mostly organize my album myself and then
mostly organizing my my 3D life
myself um with so many things going
wrong and and and being difficult behind
the scenes and then me feeling really
down for other reasons as well it was
just not a good time for
me
yeah and that was just the second half
of the year because I can't even
remember the first
half I just can't remember it who knows
what happened in the first
half but I'm good I'm and I'm looking
forward to 2024 right now and I'm like
pretty positive about it right now
so I I think you guys will have to deal
with me a while
longer yeah but this is why I would
agree that
um did I even read the second part what
the hell I didn't but yeah as you're
saying I faced many hardships and
roadblocks and I still push through so
inantly proud of your attention now and
forever you will always be my kamy then
thanks for making this year a great one
now then let's get this part started
thank
you yeah this
is very true all of this is very true
but yeah we have persevered
yay thank you so much rad
m for looking over me and supporting me
always no matter what thank you soon
you're the best no you're the best no
you thank
you I appreciate
[Music]
it no you no you do you want to be timed
out huh huh
know
you and Jacob for the seven thank you
for the red chat I've had a pretty crazy
last few days at work but knowing I
would be able to wake up to this made it
worth it it's going to be great seeing
you strut your stuff I just know it
strut my
stuff strut my
stuff that word
usage feels kind of spicy is that not
kind of spicy
iing what does that actually
mean does a mean like shake the booty
booty someone might say so what do you
mean I was I was string my stuff I
guess stand up Str your Stu make some
room on the floor give us your best
clocking moves we want I see you roar
sore not
Roar
[Music]
get to show off oh okay okay okay
somehow I kind of connected with being a
little bit
spicy but I guess it's not necessarily
spicy I made it spicy though thank you
Jacob thank you thank you thank you
thank you for waking up so early too
yeah and I I hope work is looking a
little bit better in the next coming
weeks for you g
f i I'm always by your
side
the you know what it's time for a change
of Music also why is my nose so itchy
all the
time [\h__\h] it's an itchy nose
day let me try these these are the ones
that I
downloaded I the R
Music this one
[Music]
no this one what is this
one I use that for the sponsored short
oh wait actually it wasn't
[Music]
sponsored good night no okay let's use
this for now for a little
bit where was I ah Jacob catch it y Dan
JD Dan for the pinky congrats on the
free birthday so so proud of you it may
have taken a long time but it's finally
here for us to celebrate I will always
be here cheering and supporting you the
best I can my C
oi C oi you're the best glory to KY
thank
you I hope this will be forever true
come it will forever be true
right please please don't don't go
anywhere yes Koshi okay
thank you so much I'm as I said in my in
the picture that I uploaded afterwards
on Twitter I just want you guys to be
proud of me so I'm happy to hear that
you were even proud of me beforehand
thank you so
much let's enjoy 2024 together as well
and reach even bigger Heights higher
Heights together okay
G and hopefully an Australian convention
so that I can meet you and my other
Australian
chimkin
[Music]
please bgm feels goofy a little
bit hopefully praying for it me too me
too there's actually a ton of Aussie kfp
aies well AES even if I say AES raise
your hand now they're probably like some
of them might be asleep although
like I know I have these like really
dedicated Aussies who are here no matter
what time of the day it
is which is crazy but I'm
honored what do you
want
yeah act like they don't like me but
it's always here in my streams anyway
[Music]
a see it
really thank
[Music]
you really makes you think
yeah if only if only we had more than
one brain
[Music]
cell I don't like tantel well well
well well then why are you here don't
lie to
[Music]
me is there are they not going to are
you not going to say anything to your
[Music]
defense did I
win I don't see any
statement I guess I win
or you didn't feel like I was talking to
[Music]
you
you decided to be a bigger
man oh my God I got
distracted okay
whatever thank you J here comes the
[Music]
kiss the kiss
airplane is also something like an aing
kiss rocket how about a kiss
[Music]
rocket Jeff star thanks for the pinky
sticker nothing to read I
guess Jet Plane no no no no no jet
planes don't
worry it sound like Dory making whale
noises
really I can't what's with me yawning
all the
time I think it's the air there's no
air Eagle d g d and and my lungs not
being able to hold more
air g g i thank you for the red between
my upcoming trip and your upcoming life
I'm too excited to sleep congratulations
and I know you'll blow us all away I'm
always proud of you my Kam
oi Kam oi he said it he said it thank
you too excited to
sleep wasn't this
already 30 minutes before the
start don't
sleep don't sleep
you weren't planning on it
[Music]
right no sleeping 30 minutes before my
life what do you mean the the night
[Music]
before sleep talking Super Chat sleep
chatting in my dreams I'm sleep chatting
all these nights it's
you
got to send her a a a red Super
Chat sleep super talking sleep talking
sleep
chatting super
[Music]
talking it's 2:40 a.m. are you
okay are you okay don't don't uh force
yourself if you don't feel good you can
go to sleep don't worry about it this is
just a super chat reading after
all and you co wait first gar GZA come
here come
here than for the support and thank you
even even when you know the time may
have been shitty for you when you didn't
get sleep thank you for still being
there I appreciate it so
much y go thank you for the red chat for
my beloved kosi that makes me laugh
brightens my day with her cute beautiful
smile and paints my life with colors of
Happiness thank you K you're amazing
love you forever that was quite cheesy I
like it thank you for the
cheese I didn't sleep all night a but
now you got sleep right and it was so
worth it right surely it
was anyway Yoko thank you for the cheese
yum yum so
cheesy you're so sweet your words you
choice of words is so sweet what the
hell thank you for your sweet words and
your love and your support I want to
give it all back to you no thoughts were
in my brain yeah you let your heart
speak your
heart who needs brain If have heart
oaba thank you
sh H thank you for the r Super Chat
congrats on your Freddy life T your
heart working this year give me so much
energy and joy even though I was super
exhausted and barely have time to follow
stream and live
recently keep going our proud Phoenix
let's make this night on
fire thank
you also I'm assuming this one you got
to see live though because it must have
been a decent time for
you so you're
[Music]
welcome thank you so much for being
there and for trying to keep up with me
in the vault I appreciate it thank you
thank you thank you I did set the stage
on
fire did how did you know how did you
know did you watch did you hack into my
computer and watch it
beforehand I quite literally did yeah
thank you though mind reader
chicken you next than of the pinky it's
finally time ready to cheer my heart out
for this you've worked tirelessly this
year and I'm extremely proud of you for
getting for it all thank you for being
the best Kami
oi a girl could ask for love you wa and
congrats on the on the 3D live thank you
oh my god thank you for reminding
me you you are
girl you are girl you are girl I need
these reminders because I I I'm sorry
like most the time I assume because of
my
analytics that you guys are not
girl a girl a
grill nice
[Music]
Grill yes you are hen you are chicken
hen you make
egg thank you for making
egg working so hard but in my world the
male chickens can lay egg
too we all lay
eggs it's yeah kind of weird you you
guys are mutated or something I don't
know yeah yeah because I mean otherwise
we we would probably have some issues
not having enough
eggs yeah we had to adapt and
overcome or or and analyze somewhere as
well don't complain
now don't no I don't want to see no
complaining
here equality guys we all lay the eggs
we work
[Music]
together
you know what I just thought of I'll be
right back cuz I just thought of my door
because I feel like I heard a
noise make
[Music]
sure everything is fine I did I did lock
it
I was just unsure if I did for a
moment okay okay okay
[Music]
okay J has helped Psy are you like on
the 10 minute lag or 20 minute lag
[Music]
Psy we talking about jino like half an
hour ago
Australian internet austral Australian
internet KY is strong do you have like a
did you send all these comments ages ago
and it's just sending it now or
something like
that he will here this 30 minutes from
now he's lost can we help him he's lost
somewhere 20 memberships s on what the
hell thank
you wow thank you these people hopefully
will notice that they got a membership
and then watch the V of
[Music]
yesterday they late 20x yeah I told you
you guys can do it you do it all the
time why do I have
seven
oh
[Music]
okay
mo one was
more but that counted for like three
[Music]
things
what more thank
you you see all these eggs guys they're
made by you made by you cuz I know I
told you you could do it here is the
proof
[Music]
see Martin and Prince thank you for
number 10 why are you guys gifting so
many memberships right now what the hell
if somebody gets a membership gifted and
how do they get notified do they get an
email and do they get like big
notification on YouTube is it like can
you miss
it can you get a membership and then
just miss
it you get an
email
okay
[Music]
notification a little little
notification yeah like what if you're
getting the membership but you're not in
the chat cuz as far as I know that
happens as well if you're not actually
in the chat at the moment but you still
got a membership gift and I just wonder
if these people you know could miss it
thank you guys okay chill the [\h__\h] out
now
guys you already spent so much money on
the on on the stream yesterday and now
you know Christmas is coming up so calm
calm your
titties your tatas your Wawas calm
them Cal down I told I told you to let
no I told you you can do it but I don't
I don't mean you have to do it right
now oh my
God
o thank you guys but stop I have to read
super chats I'm not going to acknowledge
you
guys thank you now calm
[Music]
down
we already like honestly thank you so
much yesterday I think there were a
thousand membership gifts a
thousand
sheh and then a lot of them were so last
minute I saw in the waiting room to the
members only
uncor members were still being gifted
and there were still so many waiting for
gifts but I had to close it I had to
close it but they we're still like in
the middle of
gifting guys it was so last
minute well it was very sweet of you
guys thank you I think the members onore
is really worth the membership
so I am the first Ian to have had a
members only
Encore and I did purposefully make it so
that it has like a cozy feeling a
member's only Vibe a family Vibe the
song choice is also purposefully very
very much like cozy intimate
feeling yeah I really like the members
only part even the game the MC part I
think was really
funny I I felt so m embarrassed when I
was filming that but it came out pretty
nice I think I was actually shocked at
how difficult it was because I watched
like uh kup groups do these challenges
and they nail it so
easily but then again they usually they
have like I don't know five six seven
people in their group
and like you you watch the Coro and it
looks so intricate and so crazy but
that's often only because they have so
many people in the group and they do
like formations and all that but if you
let only one of them dance you notice
that there's some times where they don't
dance at all they just stand in a pose
while the others are dancing and so on
there's like some back and forth and the
movements are often a bit smaller but
they look bigger because there's like
several people doing the same
dance yeah so like I feel like groups
doing these challenges is generally
easier than what I did because my coros
are way busier than some of these groups
the
coros still still like surely it's
difficult to you know dance your Coro
sped up like that with the formation
changing like B bonking yeah that's
that's kind of funny when you see the
groups like bonking bumping into each
other when they try to pass each other
go to their spot because one thing
that's for sure difficult in K-pop coros
is there's a lot of formation
[Music]
changes and having that be sped up yeah
you're going to be running all
across the
[Music]
room I'm surprised talking about yeah I
know no no we're not talking about that
though it's because you guys sent so
many members uh gifts I had to talk
about it
now yeah it's early access I will talk
more
um yeah we read this right so next thank
you so much youx next is Jay slorg for
the red super chat thank you no words
only hype hype hype hype hype this was 8
minutes before the start thank you Jay
blackbrook M I was also hyped I was very
hyped I was I was nervous and
hyped
yeah like I I wrote in the chat when I
started I was like is is the sound
working is there any lag and so on and I
double checked with JMA as well but you
guys replied to me faster but I was I
was really nervous I was checking
everything double and price if
everything is okay I was double checking
the audio on OBS and
everything yeah everything went well y I
was sweating I was sweating just by
sitting there and watching my
life just sitting there I didn't even do
[Music]
anything
understandable
also smoothie I think it was smoothie
was sitting in front of me lying and
sleeping in front of me while I was
watching my live concert for an hour
that was nice I had someone to to
pet when I was
nervous emotional support cat honestly I
think my my cats for me are really
emotional support
animals too bad they can't call an
ambulance if I slip in the
shower if they could do
that can I pass out now seea did you
write this half an hour ago are you
passed out now or did you really write
that
[Music]
now thank you though good night
to yeah it would be good if you can call
if you can can get your cats to call the
ambulance probably in some way maybe but
do you really want to rely on the cat to
call the ambulance for for you I think
for dogss you could train them like you
could have some kind of like big red
button somewhere in your house and then
train them if you're like on the ground
not reacting to push the button and that
would connect to an ambulance call or
so that probably works yeah but for cats
I don't know if I want to rely on
cats yeah I mean cats are pretty smart
too not saying that they would be too
stupid to do that I just
don't I love cats
but yeah I don't know how reliable they
are yeah still still I will prefer cats
but are they reliable for that kind of
stuff probably
not yeah yeah they probably don't care I
mean now they probably do care but do
they care enough
oh well but you J swb is actually
perfect that we're talking about
cats but like randomly when I read your
Super Chat thank
you ion thanks to the pinky
congratulations Chef you've earned this
many times over and we're bursting to
cheer you on now that it's here here's
to more lives in the future hopefully
more on time should be oh yeah I'm
already planning the next one and giving
the the plan six months ahead of time
which uh should is is what they
want if you don't mind the question will
we see aoe2 again in the near future not
this year because uh game perms are
basically on vacation because the
companies may be on vacation and they
don't might not answer and I have to ask
one week in advance and I really don't
have time for AOE right now maybe back
uh to AOE in February
cuz January I'm not really here
anyway
[Music]
yeah yeah I really wish it I wouldn't
have to ask one week in advance I would
have probably played more AOE if it
didn't need one week in advance per
thingy if it wasn't for that
but yeah thank you and thank you for
watching thank you for supporting uh for
AOE you'll have to wait but uh you know
it'll come back it's not gone
forever said golden I than pinky it's a
5 minute countdown and I await your
performance with baited chicken breath
what this is the big big moment you
worked so hard for and we can't be more
proud I have more to say but I will
spare you fro and save it for another
time let's go go thank you that is so
considerate wow thank you thank you
thank you I appreciate it what's baited
what's the how do you why what does this
mean in this context baited teach me
English
guys I'll find the words later but first
help me find this
word are you ah you spelled it wrong
baited then I still don't get it though
you're excitedly waiting for something a
holding ah baited breath is holding
breath ah what I never heard that before
wow
[Music]
e
oh put I turned off yes yes cuz I'm
reading so many right now I have so many
to
read really old Shakespeare what
Shakespearean no one ever spells it out
understandable
to that's why I never saw it before I
[Music]
guess Alvaro
D and this looks like Japanese Kani for
onaku but it's
not so let me go translate oh
[Music]
it's it's also it also means music but
it's in Chinese so
it's
uh thank you
[Music]
than oh no no no thanks for the pinky
can has longer waited birthday fry
showcase is finally here congratulations
Kiana and good job this year has been
the hardest year but I think I will be
able to end it happily thanks to K as a
fan I feel like I want to repay K thank
you good
job we both worked hard for the roller
coaster that was
2023 and hopefully we we will be
rewarded for it in 2024 yeah good job
for you to hold on to it and work so
hard and persevere just like me I
applaud you I applaud
us Big O
O now I hope to see you around next year
too
Honolulu and and and maybe I will
improve my Korean skills again next year
no promises but I I don't want to give
up I I put so much money and time into
it in
2023 yeah the first half that's what I
was doing the first half in
2023 that's
it yeah I oh one more oh okay okay okay
I think I got too much from you what can
I give you I think all I can give is my
body and pray body thank you for your
hard work this year too I look forward
to seeing you again next year want to
want you and your stream until YouTube
goes back
C that's an interesting outcome that you
are
expecting you think I will stream until
YouTube goes bankrupt will will YouTube
ever go bankrupt I doubt it so I guess
that is very positive
thinking small Indie
company
[Music]
I think YouTube will yeah survive and
persever harder than anyone
[Music]
else it's so good that we have the
yawning emote what would we do about
[Music]
it did you know that YouTube operates at
a loss what what why do you write it
like that you mean they're making
minus they're not earning money they're
losing
[Music]
money
wow why do they do that why are they
okay with
that I don't think that's true anymore
that's outdated oh
okay the servers are really
expensive I guess they have enough money
from like
Google that YouTube not
being like a money machine isn't so bad
or surprised Google even bought YouTube
If YouTube has not been making
money cuz it promotes their
services now I guess for them just for
having such a huge amount of users
millions and millions of users that are
forced to make a Google account then
remember the time when we had YouTube
accounts that were not connected to a
Google account remember
[Music]
that mhm
advertisements
data human
data remember when there was still a DM
system on YouTube Remember guys do do
you guys
remember I think I can pinpoint your age
if you say you don't
[Music]
remember that's ancient
yeah yeah you don't know yeah YouTube
used to have DMS and yeah different
rating systems they they overhauled
their rating systems several times but
having DMS was quite
[Music]
something a video responses I mean you
can still kind of do that but wait now
that you say it yeah there was something
like that how is that
different how is that like you could
still do it now but it's not like it
doesn't have its own system I guess but
I think you were able to do video
responses
[Music]
yeah yeah wasn't there even like you
know how you can see the comments there
was also a section where you could see
the video
resp I accidentally pressed the thing
where you could see the video responses
like a column for the video responses so
it's like
yeah yeah you would you would find other
videos through
that but I mean is it really necessary
when nowadays you'll see related
videos in the on the side
anyway if you watch a video then know
but it was a thing
yeah multicolored
anotations
huh what you mean the subtitles
but we can do that now too don't we cuz
Hol life subtitles are always
multicolored wait annotations what's
annotations
again ah ah do you mean the the the ah
the
squares yeah the
[Music]
squares oh yeah where you can like memo
you can write you can write something
into the video afterwards like put a box
oh yeah people put up so many oh I think
I remember like some YouTube videos they
had like 500 layers of these
annotations so many of
them yeah and you you couldn't even see
the video if you wanted to click on the
video you would click on an anotation I
[Music]
think you guys remember when you were
able to put your own background on your
YouTube channel like you could put some
pattern in the background and make it
more like
individually your
style I would put like cute patterns on
there that I found on
[Music]
Google I'm
OG yeah it was like a profile it was
like Myspace but I never used
mypace
that was Peak that was
[Music]
Peak does this make some of us go dust
we are already dust
[Music]
unregistered
hyper okay let me read super chats guys
it's nice being lazy but let me read I
have to read super chats we're at 50 by
the
way Ian thank you for the pinky wait
wait there were some in between Marcus
medicon thank you for the pinky this has
been a long time coming but the waight
is definitely worth it freedy wa life is
real I'm so ready to cheer my heart for
you you worked so hard for this and
we'll cheer you on as much as our little
chicken hearts can take go be star thank
you also that is really a cute Emoji
where did you get that from where did
you get that from can you guys recognize
it I love Japanese emojis it's this one
is uh holding a heart next to its
face so
cute we're almost done with Super Chat
what do you what do you mean I mean
there's a second
page but I guess I did already get
pretty far even even though this is
before the live
starts
still the members one isn't so bad is
there just not that many super chats but
they all are big ones to the
m I'm I am surprised how far how long is
the second
page ooh okay second page still pretty
long another 100 a bit more than 100 are
on the second page
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] ads go away go away go away
Volvo I don't want to buy a
[Music]
Volvo where was I here well still I got
pretty far from
here
to
[Music]
good not bad not bad it's only been 2
hours I drive a b with they neat yeah
surely they're nice
but I don't want a car in general right
now anyway I'm not ready for a car that
is a commitment I am not ready
for when you buy a car you'll think
Volvo dot dot dot you think I'll I'll
miss
the no go away with the tangent go go
away go somewhere else anyway thank you
Marcus
men thank you for cheering for me thank
you for believing in me much much love
to you thank you Shar for the
support not the kiss I was about to kiss
but no no no no no no no it's a pinky
but thank you so much for the support I
appreciate
it I did do my best and I hope you could
see
that Mery pipp thanks to the pinky as
well thanks for shering from me it's
it's over here I made the
window there we
go thank you so much wait my chat kind
of died Let me refresh the
chat no that was a
close close call I was like so close to
your face already with puckered
[Music]
lips
no okay I fixed you guys so now we are
at iron thank you for the pinky
Cong thank
you thank
you Frey life
finally
finally it was about time thank you for
waiting and being there on that special
day
super
and Studio thanks for the pinky this is
finally where it begins but still
loading screen I
think
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] what's wrong with
me what's wrong with me three years of
your empathy has done wonders for my sad
soul almost I'm really happy to hear
that thank
you I hope no more sad soul only happy
soul I'm a New Soul living in a strange
worlding
I
and I
can't making every possible
mistake New
Soul yeah that song is nice I sang it in
one of my last
[Music]
K goof okay yeah now that you mention it
I'm sick of
it get rid of
that
PTM what do we
have what do we
got oh what do we
[Music]
got
heyo why is that not in my fan out
folder
art
fold okay I put it
in okay audio Stu what is this I have a
lot of unnamed
[Music]
files
this even has surprisingly quite a bit
of Christmas
Vibe oh it's not a Loa one
no well then it's
[Music]
useless oh my tropical music from
summertime all right let's use it
tropical Christmas
for my aie kfb let's go it's summertime
summer
time let's
go this actually such a Bop holy
[\h__\h] I really like this
one
all right it doesn't loop as smoothly
because it's not not like it takes like
a millisecond oh well anyway good luck
Studio Rob in the future I hope things
only look positive for you much love to
you R epic than soon Kimmy pH than soon
desol than soon thank
you the great RV zero Jo 777
[Music]
thank you for being there ziply also
thank you for red Super
Chat oh this was was this already
doing oh all ready at voice we're all
ready at voice
oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
[Music]
oh we're already in
voice why nobody talked about
pineapple we just skipped pineapple can
I say it
just let
me let
[Music]
me
you were stunned in
silence super chat during the concert is
hard yeah I I I I would have wanted you
guys to just like watch it without
writing super chats anyway no I was like
watching and checking the chat and all
that and then suddenly I see like super
long red super chats coming up in the
middle of the life and I'm like what why
are you writing this paragraph in the
midle love my concert you should be
looking at the
concert but yeah
pineapple was the first song and yeah
just like how it was more or less the
opener to my new Po
songs um I felt it was fitting to make
it the opener for the for the live
concert and um I think it just has great
Vibes for that it gets everybody in a
nice mood
and I think it's like very
representative so I went for that
song um you know in the music video you
didn't
see my Cho that I did in the beginning
actually um Kiana made the Coro for
pineapple but I changed some smaller
parts and one of those parts was the
very beginning where
I I I just couldn't really get the vibe
from Kiana that I personally wanted it
happen sometimes that's okay but I had a
vision in my mind and that was like just
lying on the beach because there's like
these water sounds in the beginning of
the
instrumental and yeah that's basically
what I came up with and you couldn't see
it in the music video but you could see
it here in the live concert version and
it was kind of funny because I think
pineapple
was possibly the indeed the first
song uh or okay some of these songs were
recorded in a completely different order
than in what they appeared on in the
Stream let me say that but uh uh PPP was
one of the first ones and I remember
like uh practicing a little bit and then
getting a position to record it and um I
started on the ground and for some
reason all of the staff were
laughing and they didn't take me
seriously nobody thought that I was
actually going to start the Coro from
the ground they thought I was just being
lazy and messing around and like no guys
I'm I'm I mean it this is really the
starting post and they keep on laughing
and laughing and laughing and like yeah
yeah yeah sure sure and I'm like no for
real though like just watch me it
there's like this whole movement that
I'm planning to make like I'm I mean
it no but they all thought I was just
messing around and being
lazy that was so
funny yeah witness
me I mean it let me cook yeah was that
the blooper cut
oh no no that was just like another
moment of me practicing and prepping
pineapple I think that wasn't that
moment where they were laughing at me
but they they certainly did not think I
was serious about
it in the blo nobody was laugh yeah
generally you couldn't hear the
management side uh the the the behind
the scenes sign you could only hear my
microphone cuz that's the only thing
that was
recorded but yeah I didn't know they
were recording by the way I think we
were just like setting up at that point
of time and bl um but yeah so
pineapple it's it's quite the
energetic song and I was trying my best
to get the energy across I still feel
like when I watch myself do this dance
and pretty I still
feeling I I felt like I was putting more
energy and movement into it than what it
ended up looking like but H that kind of
confused me but besides that uh it went
well and was one of the dances I felt
more more uh confident
about yeah yeah that part I was like in
the in for recording the music
video but you know that part where I'm
like looking to the side and I kind of
dive my head and my upper body in like a
wave and do the Steppy Steppy
steppies and that
part is was always kind of difficult for
me cuz I think I was doing it wrong
that's the problem when you learn coros
through a video and not in person with
the
teacher
um no I really like that move but it was
really difficult for me to do it during
the MV recording and then when I like
practice the song again closer to this
recording I hit up Kiana and I asked her
I was like yo I really want to nail this
move but I don't know what I'm doing
wrong and yeah she sent me a little
little YouTube tuto little unlisted
tutorial um yeah just for that part just
for that important part
there's some more movements right after
[Music]
the the second I movements and they keep
going I think those moves I made up
myself again because I just
uh for some sometimes I make up other
moves because I don't feel like I like
the vibe as much or it's because the
difficulty when learning the to dance I
was like whatever [\h__\h] this let me come
up with something easier that enters my
brain more
naturally yeah so some parts are
improved
mhm the neck to back ass Pop move is
amazing I don't know what you
mean neck to back ass
pop but yeah pineapple was good hope you
enjoyed this opening and then I went
straight
into where is it
Voice Now voice the Coro obviously it
wasn't made by Kiana for Keana I mostly
just asked her to do my my solo songs
but this one was uh made by Japanese
choreographers and I was first I wasn't
so happy with what you know the the
first choreo
draft um and then I asked them to change
it up quite a bit cuz what I had in my
mind you know voice I chose voice
because first of all it's an English
song and it was already originally a
duet song so it was quite fitting um and
I I thought it sounded quite sensual so
I wanted the Coro to be also pretty
sensual and fit into the lyrics and
really show off the intimate see between
me and
way so first the Coro like I feel like
generally when Japanese choreographers
take care of the
choreos um they go the extra safe route
and they make coros where there's not
much like body touching and interacting
but I really wanted it for voice and I
don't think it would have been an issue
because I had like other instances
before where you know especially with
waya with waya we we had
um that Coro for her 3D showcase where
it was also quite a bit of touching
touching oh yeah like you know I think
it works like I think they they stay
away from it because they're worried
about the tracking looking off and yeah
it it can definitely be an issue
especially when it comes to like
touching hands and all
that um but I still thought it was fine
and worth it worth trying and it's
better than just staying 2 feet 2 m away
from each other throughout the whole
dance so I stayed
quite how to
say I forgot the
word I
insisted too much
Les I insisted on on getting a more
intimate Coro and then here it is but it
was pretty embarrassing I'm not going to
lie like there was a lot of giggling and
uh embarrassment and not being able to
look at each other's eyes
um ah [\h__\h] my cable
stuck
um but at least you can't really see how
embarrassing it
was in
this version so no no
problemo the end result is awesome yeah
I think voice is uh this performance is
one of my favorites from the whole
concert because it
really it
really ended up getting the right Vibe
across that I was hoping for and I love
waya
so I love waya I love the song I
generally tried to uh at least with like
English speaking members choose English
songs and uh I will try to continue
doing that whenever
possible so thank k for some God
songs this is another song where I feel
like should have been my song just like
four
blood m
you guys like the song too didn't you
it's
so
smooth waking up in shades of
blue I don't know where I am or how I
got to
you yeah singing it really emotionally
and and
[Music]
you that was it just felt really good
such a
bob
smooth so I want to thank waya for doing
this with me and I hope I hope I can get
more opportunities to do stuff with
Wayne I love
Wayne My My Big B
lady
oh wait I will see her soon anyway
yooooo there you go that was two two
song
tangents let's
go we can move on to the super chats
where was
I here I deeply thank you for leading us
into
[Music]
it what the [\h__\h] is
this thank you vampire hail
Lord
AR are you looking forward to showing
her Hoster I don't think there will be
much showing cuz it seems like like
she's coming with her um family member I
think
and I think she's not only traveling
Austria and then she asked me the other
day which day I would prefer this day or
that day and so it seems like we're only
really meeting for one day but we got
the whole day so she also said we can do
a stream so I might try to get a stream
going in the evening and then during the
daytime I'll show her around a little
bit and have dinner together
what kind of stream would you like do
you want a k off collab or would you
like
a gaming off
collab maybe I could even do the
N64 okay in order to make a k off collab
interesting I have to do some lyrics
splitting and choosing the songs
beforehand but I'll see what I can do
should we do an should we do an an
unarchived English songs ofab
K just browse through kfun and find what
we know and then we're just going to I
would just
Pat her shoulder and be like your turn
your turn and we Pat each other on our
shoulders to indicate that the other
person should
sing okay okay let's do an archive
English
[Music]
K okay sounds fun sounds fun yeah
casual all right lots of kadas these
days uh what was I AR
Lord thanks for the
pinky I agree p p
p there will be more P Nashi love soon
TM in the new year so look forward to
it Coral gold
[Music]
an
I think that's
correct thank you for the pink Super
Chat sticker I hope you were enjoying
the concert thank you for the
[Music]
support Cru
D wait was this already at Rai
circulation wait this this one this
one I think I saw you guys in the
chat
um
sorry it's not even platinum discount it
was everyone's R ey circulation I
guess I like one hour don't worry about
it I mean you're just hyping it up I'm
just wondering is it
already is that but was it Matsui
first
yeah but did nobody talk surely some
this must be just like weird
thing oh yeah what happened there's like
3 minutes of no Super Chat did you guys
just not super chat during M nobody
talked about
it should I just bring it up let me look
at this tiger thank you for the
pinky uh you guys can't see but it's
there thank you tiger for the pinky
woohoo KF party 2023 let's go
D thank you thank
[Music]
you hope you used the hashtag also in
other places where it was actually
useful like
Twitter thank you for the support what
the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] ads go
away all these
ads can you guys give me a
recommendation for a good
adlock
please was that Alexis is that a car I
thought it was
alexas you oh every every what what is
why why does everybody know this adlock
that it's apparently so good that
everybody mentions
it you block origin what the
hell is the
standard just everybody GRE wao W wo wo
what am I missing out
on let me get it right now I can use it
on Chrome
right uh x wait what uh how does it work
again
extensions Chrome
webstone what it you block origin
oh oh this was the right question to ask
you guys
add to Chrome is this
illegal having ad block is not illegal
[Music]
right oh I'm going to jail oh
no okay so I have it now let's see if it
works
refresh I think it
works I think it
works
bless bless bless
bless okay nobody here mentions
anything so I'm going to talk about my
ching
there we go people really liked this
last scene and this was also another
thing that I was let me change the bgm
that I was really insistent
[Music]
on I like
it yay nice nice
nice so first of all let me talk about
the song Choice Rubble kiss is a pretty
old song No
ke W from a hello project unit that was
made out of morning musim members if you
guys remember morning musim is one of
the biggest Idol groups in Japan they
were kind of bigger in the past uh but
then they they keep on changing members
so um they don't have all the legendary
members anymore that they used to have
so they're not as popular anymore but
they used to be like pretty [\h__\h]
known everywhere throughout Japan and
some of their legendary members made a
unit or they were made to make a unit
that was called W and they were made to
like look like sisters even though I
don't really think they look similar but
they just I guess they you know they
were both like some of the youngest
members of morning musim at the
time and they were pretty dorky and
energetic and all that and they just had
like a good energy Vibe I guess um and
yeah apparently they weren't even
getting along long one
but yeah uh they were quite interesting
members and they formed this group W
which was one of I would say one of the
most successful
units that hello project
created um within a
group and yeah one of their most
well-known songs is rooc kiss which is
uh from 2004 that
is
19 years ago no what okay I just
realized that
now oh my
[Music]
God 19 years
ago shock shock shock shock shock shock
shock de
meal so and this group is still around
guys I'm I mean not W but morning Muslim
the group that they came from because
they keep on adding new members you
know um so yeah riss and this song you
know it it is from a two people unit and
so I I I want to honestly I want to
perform even more W songs in the future
so you might see more so maybe you guys
should look up their
discography um because like I like using
songs
with its original
choreography and the good thing is about
W that it's made for two people so it's
perfect for Duets you know for cover
Duets yeah the original Coral it's kind
of like dorky and messy and just having
fun and I think you guys noticed that a
lot of doy moves there was this like
move that comes up several times where
we like uh try each other up then get
exhausted like I charge her then I get
exhausted she charges me and then you
know we start singing that comes up
several times but it's a really cute Cho
and stuff like that that's why I really
want to use the original Cho because I
feel like those coros they have so much
personality it's a bit
more uh like stuff to do behind the
scenes because we have to for each Coral
ask them for
permission um
specifically to use it and yeah that
takes some time I feel like you know
same for R ni circulation I've seen
several Rai circulation performances in
whole life but none of them I
think or maybe only one used the
original Coral that I find so
iconic and I don't like that I I find
the like so many of those original coros
I find so iconic and I just want to even
if it's a bit more annoying to get the
rides to it I want to use
those then coming up with new
ones yeah for copyright your just
because it's easier like I feel
like a lot of these members when they
plan their lives they just say I want to
do this this this this this song and
then it just kind of happens
automatically you know
they just
uh have the coros commissioned and it
just happens I don't think they even try
to get the rights to the original coros
but I think they should try it more
because for me it worked I got the
rights to
them and I think I will continue to try
doing that yeah cuz as you I think you
could tell that this one Coro had like
already so much
charm on its own and and it was just
special like it stands out like compared
to
other like whole life coros you know
what I
mean also because it had so much body
interactions that normally our
choreographers probably wouldn't even
attempt because it's going to look weird
yeah we had some of those issues
too this this ending pose also was a bit
difficult to nail so that it looks
good yeah but
um yeah that's this is the origin of my
tweet about the butt and kissing
action so there was especially in the
very beginning
the the music
starts uh in the beginning there's a
there's a move where we uh face each
other's backs no our backs face each
other and um then we like hold hands and
we try to like with small small steps
fast steps we go away from each other
and then we go back together
and like all the time we would do this
we would bump each other's butts so our
butts were touching a lot when we were
practicing
this that's why I was tweeting that and
and I I was wondering if mat would mind
but no shees she didn't seem to
mind but on this day oh my God I was so
tired cuz if you guys remember I had
issues sleeping a lot and when I was in
Japan I just was too stressed I just
couldn't sleep and so I went to this
dance lesson with like 3 hours of sleep
or so or less I don't know and I was
drinking
monster um and yeah I just couldn't
focus so I really had problems getting
the Cho into my head I feel like matui
was learning it faster
um I thankfully we had two dance
teachers there to like focus on each
other because uh there were like
different and mirrored movements so that
made the the dance lesson way Smoother
by having two dance
teachers um but yeah I was really slow
and I apologized so many times I was
like I'm so sorry can me do this again
and this part again this part
again ah my brain was so
mushy and I don't know I wasn't sure cuz
it was also the first time in a while I
think that I met at Matsui Senai again
and um she was she was so like chill and
I I I wasn't sure how to read her on
that day and I I was just hoping she
wasn't mad at me for being so
stupid but then she would do stuff
[Music]
like give me give me a a chew on my on
my on my cheek cuz there's a part in the
dance where I don't know if it if you
were able to tell cuz that movement was
M it looked a little bit more spacious
than it actually was but she would try
to kiss me and I would try to dodge her
and I go like boo boo boo I was just
making the background noises from the
original
track yeah but somewhere in the dance
lesson I guess that led to uh us like
giggling a lot
and and and did give me a two or M I
think if I remember
correctly
yeah and I was I was so C I was
panicking I was like okay okay I think
she likes me after all cuz like I wasn't
sure I was like feeling so weird and she
was so chill you know she was like yeah
yeah she wasn't talking much I guess she
was very focused on a dance lesson and I
was worried that she maybe something I
did something wrong wrong but then then
she does stuff like you know
that so I was
relieved you know how I
um you know how I got these
tea uh souvenirs to give to
everybody so sometime during the
practice lesson I was like okay I'm
going to give her my souvenir surely
that will get me some plus points with m
s by and I gave it to her and I was like
really excitingly telling her the
ingredients like why why it tastes like
Christmas it's because it has apple and
orange and this and that and then she
[Music]
says then she says that she has an
orange
allergy and I'm like
what
[Music]
no no
you can't have an orange allergy we're
both orange pretty orange your image
color is orange my image color is orange
how can you have an orange allery orange
is so good and this is my souvenir to
you no what do I do I felt so bad
I that that really sucks when you
prepare a souvenir and they don't they
can't they literally can't consume
it
ah no that was
embarrassing
it's t
over oh man she she's missing out orange
is so
[Music]
good
she still kissed you so that says
something orange you also have orange
allergy you Kiki
what you make dinner for someone with
mushrooms and raw fish and the person
yeah like me oh wait you are you are
hitting to that well yeah similar
situation I
guess
anyway Mata was very small very
cute oh even her dance practice clothes
were really really
cute
and I came there with like lack of sleep
and eye bags of Doom no makeup and some
really Dy not cool looking practice
clothes and then she's there with cute
hair cute makeup cute
clothes and totally awake and and
getting all the moves in easily so I
felt uh conflicted on that
day yeah but after that to make up for
it I I practiced really hard until the
uh
recording and then I felt pretty
confident with my
moves in the recording yeah yeah I I
definitely caught up so all is good in
the
end
yeah I think you could see I was really
energetic
right yeah I enjoyed
it it's such a dorky song I hope you
guys liked
[Music]
it
for I loved how upbeat it
[Music]
was
was so fun it was so
fun oh do you want to hear
something that was really stressful to
me this was um a few days before the
record Rec ing um for the recording I
don't know why um they want like a
backing
track to record it but they don't want
to use the original song so they ask for
like me recording it in advance and just
so that they have something to play you
know in the back and I recorded it for
all of these songs before that's why I
kept on saying I'm recording I'm
recording I'm recording so many things
before leaving uh to go to
Japan and I I got everything done and I
was so relieved and then uh they checked
all the data um one by one but for some
reason the one for double kiss they
checked
like two days before the recording or
one day before the
recording I don't know why and then they
realized that I recorded the wrong Parts
I recorded Matsu's Parts instead of my
own I'm like
well great to know that now where I
don't have a recording environment in my
Airbnb really and I'm currently that was
like I I
uh I was at I think at a dance listen or
whatever and I it was I think there was
one more day in between I said I said
okay well this is not ideal I would have
liked to know that earlier but I will do
my best if you really need it I guess
I'll I could try to
record early in the morning after the
the panel that we had with
GAA so after the panel early in the
morning again after little little sleep
I quickly recorded just like one take
quickly quickly for the back vocals just
so that they have something
[Music]
and uh I sent the
data and then I leave the studio and I
take a nap because later I had another
dance lesson where I was just doing solo
practice in the studio that I booked but
I was I was taking a nap because I woke
so up so early for the panel
right and
then while I'm in in the
booth like this was the only opportunity
for me to record somewhere because I
don't have recording environment in the
Airbnb and you can't just walk into the
studio and say I need a booth to record
something because they're like they were
booked the whole time like Bales had a
lot of bookings and other people had a
lot of bookings and so that's why I only
could have recorded it then in the
morning after the
panel and then I'm in a lesson after my
nap uh with with my new British um
assistant
manager and I'm just trying because
there's like so many coros that I'm
still unsure about uncertain and I think
this was like a day or two before the
before the
actual like motion
capture and then during the lesson
during the self practice I
get a
notification that the day data that I
sent apparently it's like broken or
something or just the file isn't playing
any audio and I'm
[Music]
like and then we were like while I was
dancing we were like trying to
coordinate like okay like there the file
is still on the computer on the in the
studio like can we somehow get it to
them can I go there to the studio after
the a
dance booking that I have afterwards go
there go to the computer send it to them
again but then we were checking the
schedule and it seems like the rooms
were being used all the time um and I
couldn't leave right away because I had
this room booked that I just couldn't
abandon so it was like all really like
stressful you know it was stupidly
stressful but eventually we just got
them the staff who were already in the
studio to go to the PC and look for the
the original original file and they
found it eventually and and then it was
[Music]
okay but it was just lots of back and
forth that was a bit
unnecessary I mentioned it oh oh
really I was it was quite the
headache
file wrong recording then the file gets
lost then no
[Music]
access oh well all good in the
end all good in the
end tremo D Captain Jack pants thank you
for the pinky that's my comei right
there thank you k for making life a lot
better and brighter since I found you
kfp till the end yay which is apparently
when YouTube goes bankrupt let's go
let's
go thank you Captain jerkpants
[Music]
see this see this right
here the best word you can say to
me thank you so
much thank you I appreciate your support
and your determination
hope you enjoyed the concert
yeah Ana she with a rainbow but no no
words at all my
God you guys would say what a Chad but I
I
am this is not okay you have to say
something something I'm giving up on you
if you don't write your feelings down
this
time write it tell
me thank you for the beautiful
rainbow an
Dan I hope you enjoyed the stream as
well cha thank you for the pinky come
Sanita cuz it is in Korean
one but name is Japanese but I guess you
know I say I say and I
say thank
you
okay uh omlet do fromage thank you for
the red super chat
o sounds
yummy it's finally here love you you're
the best thank you you're the best oh
wait UNC you wrote a m message hi thank
you love you
too so in the memb message you can say
your feelings
huh good good good thank you very much
nice to hear from
[Music]
you nice to see that you are here are
you doing well I hope
so but yeah thank you oml let the so
much you're the best I love you too
thank you for the support omelette
you're yummy yummy egg
[Music]
omelette actually I don't eat omelets
that much for breakfast I feel like in a
hotel in a hotel breakfast I order
omelets a lot somehow they taste better
when I eat them in a hotel breakfast
room then when I do them at home
no I don't know why what what is it
about hotel breakfast that just makes
everything taste
better even if it's basic [\h__\h] like
bread or quas or uh like moly um
granola yeah okay the fake eggs are not
so nice but you know if you order an
omelette they usually they usually use
real eggs
and then make you a proper omelette so I
wouldn't say the same thing for
scrambled eggs scrambled eggs are
definitely better when you make them at
home by yourself unless you're actually
in a festar hotel except I guess the
wildor in
London but usually in a five-star hotel
when you order scrambled eggs straight
from the kitchen they would make them
for you for you with real eggs unlike
the five star lorf atoria in London uh
but
usually
usually wobbly egg
water that hotel
man I'm so
angry I'm so
[Music]
angry it's so messed up because I think
I went to a Wilder uh aoria in
Berlin yeah long time ago and it was so
much
better it was so much better like their
service the
breakfast yeah and they immediately
offered to make me something fresh from
the kitchen and it was real
eggs oh and I also ordered French Toast
French toast was so good that was one of
the best French toast I've ever eaten in
my whole life that's why I want to go
back to the wildor in
Berlin
but
wow a reason to go to
Berlin will probably not come up in a
while besides the
hotel better than your French toast I
think that valer French toast inspired
me to make French toast myself more
often mine is pretty good but theirs was
a amazing that was actually yeah it was
[Music]
better Under New Management New
Management I think it's a regional
thing how did we start talking about
food well look at look at their
name forgot to eat lunch
today I only ate um one
one uh GC pla pla GC um
fluffy fluffy breakfast bread thing that
had like it's a um it has
apricots and and and stuff on
it what's pla again in
English why can't I not breathe
today do you like ribs I like them but I
always feel like when I eat them that I
don't get much meat from it there's not
much meat around the bone and it's kind
of
annoying
just want the meat without the
[Music]
bow reminds me of that video that
someone sent me from those Korean uh
girl group girls that went to
[Music]
Austria to two cities that are very
familiar to me and then they ate in
salsburg I think they ate ribs there
because apparently ribs are really
famous there I did not know that sounds
new to me yeah the one that I Yeah Yeah
Yeah Yeah from red
velvet and they ate ribs there in a
famous ribs restaurant that I don't know
but and they really enjoyed it and I
hope they really enjoyed it and didn't
just play it up for the for the
recording um because I I feel like it
might get boring if you eat so many ribs
cuz all they had was like a [\h__\h] ton of
ribs a Danish yeah Danish Danish Danish
I had a Danish today and that's it I
have a sandwich waiting for me as
well very messy yeah that's also a thing
about ribs like I kind of like it but
it's just that I haven't been able to
enjoy it the right way
[Music]
yet
yeah
no although wait no I was thinking of K
no when you said sbur no but you're
talking about sbur no which is not even
that
good but yeah we I would say if you're
in Austria generally there are certain
foods you got to eat which is Tav Spitz
and schnitzel and
kler stuff like
that
[Music]
you can get
KAS the ones I made before on stream you
can get those at Christmas markets as
well it's quite a popular Christmas
Market food cuz it's easy to make
and just such
a such a guilty pleasure food anyway
thank
you for making me talk about
[Music]
food Kuro 99 D and rine danash thank you
for the uh R chat one of the most active
freedy lives ever the coron movements
have been so on point let's go thank you
thank you I'm glad you think so really
and since this is already apparently
passed the akiro performance I think we
should talk about it
too
[Music]
so so the thing is
like
um originally I was planning to do a
different song and all that and um I
feel like you know some things fell
apart so some things I was planning fell
apart and then I contacted contacted
akisa and I asked her can you be in my
3D live on these days we're recording
and all that and first she seemed kind
of
like it's not really a good time because
she was going to be really busy with the
hosim Matic
project and I said please I'm going to
choose a simple song maybe even a Coro
that you might be familiar with and she
was like okay okay if it's something
simple then yeah I'll do it for you and
I'm like thank you so much and then I
chose for I I I I was just like thinking
maybe R ni circulation because she s she
surely knows the song and the chal I I I
was just assuming she must have seen it
before because I think it's a famous
Coral
Ry and then I showed it to her and yeah
she knows the song but she told me she
doesn't know the choreo and I'm like
[Music]
ah but we just kind of went with it I
will say it's not an easy Coro and in
the dance lessons she was struggling a
lot because there's so much
footwork and then there's kind of like
similar moves and then there's like you
start these moves in a certain order but
then in the end of the um um song they
come up in a different order like like
for example after the
chorus it it makes you think that it
goes into um
[Music]
from where we move from side to side
while doing funky steps with our feet
but no then suddenly it goes instead of
that it
does and then it goes into
you know like it changes the
orders and it really throws you off and
catches you off guard so aisai was like
struggling with stuff like that and then
I I felt kind of bad because like I go
into the dance lesson and I already know
this
dance I I've known it for many many
years um the only thing is like we were
going to dance it mostly Mira so one was
going to dance it in the meant to be way
and the other person was going to dance
it in the opposite like mirrored way so
that it looks nice when we danc it
together and I was kind of confused on
like everything because I know the Coro
but I haven't danced it in a while and
uh I wasn't sure like sometimes I dance
the moves Mira sometimes I don't dance
in miror you know it's kind of random so
I was kind of relearning that a little
bit
but generally I already knew it and she
learned it from scratch
so basically I was just like hanging out
for 2 hours while AK said by her gears
in her brain were
like and she was
like you know having a hard time and I'm
just next to them the teacher and Aisa
and I'm just like having a good time
like m
just barely anything I have to
[Music]
learn I felt so bad cuz I made it so
easy for myself but well I had to learn
so many dances right cuz it's like how
many songs did I do 11 or so I don't
know um and and akis Senai was just
going to be there for one song
[Music]
so yeah yeah her sensors were going
overdrive yeah but in the
and we we managed to do it and I think
we had fun with it but that's probably
why you can see a little bit of a
difference between our dances because I
already knew it from long long time ago
so I was dancing it also probably more
energetically cuz I didn't have to think
so hard about the moves yeah so it's
it's not AI senpai's fault it was a
really difficult dance okay maybe it
doesn't even look so difficult um but
there's so much intricate footwork where
you step and you move on
the what do you call the the the back
part of your
foot what do you call that the soul yeah
the heel yeah yeah yeah so we had to
like like twist our legs and all
that and and and you know go around on
our heels all the time it's pretty
difficult pretty difficult
so but I had a lot of fun and the dance
teacher she um apparently like akis
Senai and the dance teacher were really
close they apparently have worked
together before several times and then
when they when akis Senai came in and
saw the dance teacher she was like she
seemed like she was more happy to see
the dance teacher didn't see me and they
were like talking all this inside of
talk that I had no idea of I was like he
what are you guys talking
[Music]
about okay interesting I was trying to
trying to join the
conversation
wait I feel like there was one more
thing I wanted to say and now I forgot
about
it what was
it no yeah yeah I'm glad I'm glad that
she knew the teacher and felt so
comfortable with the teacher thanks to
[Music]
that the MC yeah you know Matsui and
akis Senai they're really they get along
really well they know each other so well
so they were also like behind the scenes
they were like we were all hanging out
and and I was just listening to matui
Senai and Aki Senai talk about a lot of
stuff and I was
like oh I see that's going on
interesting
interesting listening to the S talk
about
stuff and um then I had this I think I
mentioned it already at some point
but after recording R
culation had this really emotional
moment or yeah I think after or before I
don't know but at some point we had this
really emotional moment I don't know
why but I think I just thanked her for
inviting me to her showcase not showcase
the anniversary birthday something like
that before and and you know I just told
her how much that means to me
um that she chose me you know and she
also thanked me that I invited her and
like we got into like some emotional
talk that I don't want to get too much
into it but it was something where I
feel like we could relate to each
other's
feelings a lot because
of
our things
and yeah there like I started crying
like I gave her a hug and I started
crying and she hugged me forever until I
stopped crying
and yeah she was like like a mommy to me
it was so
sweet and we like promised each other
that we would continue to collab more in
the future and she really really she
really really wants to play Monopoly
with me and others
yeah so we just gave each other a
promise to you know support each
other and it just really felt nice to
have someone understand some things that
I felt sad about cuz she really related
to
it yeah that was really nice I love py
Senai yeah got to set up the Monopoly I
wrote to her after that I was like okay
let's do the Monopoly but hasn't moved
since maybe in
[Music]
February yeah anyway honestly uh we did
a we did the MC together honestly in
hindsight I wish I would have known that
I would have so much left over time I
would have done more MC's with the
others as well
I I didn't know because like when we
were planning the set list and the
amount of MC's and all that with the
director I was pretty much told this is
like this is going to be close like
maybe even over an
hour like it seemed like it was already
packed but then turns out oh I actually
had a lot of
leeway
yeah
[Music]
no but now I think what I'm going to do
I mean next time I think I will have
merch to announce so that will take up
some time but I think just in case I
will uh I will plan more guest MC's too
yeah but I will also plan like one extra
waa solo MC that can be deleted if it's
really too much but if it's not too much
then we have the MC to fill the time
with you know what I mean just have some
I wouldn't want to do that with a with a
MC with guests I wouldn't want to record
it just so I would delete it later on
because that would be really like mushak
I I would feel bad about deleting
something afterwards just because of
lack of time where they were involved
but uh I think I can just make another
five minute kiaha only MC
for backup to fill
time yeah the bloopers in the end were
so good the bloopers
actually okay should I already talk
about the bloopers for a moment because
um I want to tell you the bloopers were
not originally
planned after recording almost the whole
life me and the director we were like
you know discussing and I was made aware
that
probably I'm going to not have a full
hour and I was
like can we have like some kind of
ending you know that we can come up with
now uh and then I I had this gorgeous
idea very
suddenly it was a last minute Edition
yeah but it kind of worked because we
already like I noticed that the director
was sometimes recording just randomly
when we were messing around behind the
scenes um and also when we were taking
pictures for thumbnails rather than
taking screenshots they were just
recording videos you know so I was like
is it possible to use all that behind
the scenes footage to make like a
blooper
real like an
NG
moment thing credits thingy I was going
to roll credits but uh in the end it was
just a bloopers
and it worked out and you guys really
liked it and I also thought it was
really Charming it actually gave me kind
of like a emotional feeling after such a
big moment for kfb and for me ending it
with the bloopers I feel like that that
just makes it really emotional right
looking back on stuff like you I mean
you guys weren't there but I was there
so it was extra emotional for
me yeah so that added a little bit to
the time and I think I'll I'll make it a
common thing I think I want to have
bloopers in the future too I wonder if
other people are going to do it too cuz
like that was apparently the first time
anybody did
bloopers and this is also a thing that
you can't really do if you have it
completely live it's only really
possible if you have it pre-recorded so
another good reason to have it
pre-recorded yeah it was cute right yeah
and yeah it wasn't even it wasn't even
planned so next time if I plan it out
I'm going to have them record even more
behind the
scenes so that we have even more
bloopers
[Music]
yay
bloopers how about a full hour of only
[Music]
bloopers out takes yeah the beep I like
the beep in
between that was good right let's do
more in the
future
it was so cute right when me and AIS
Senai were hugging in like a circle I
don't know why we were doing
that I think H I think it was after
recording Rai circulation I was just
really happy that we did it and then I I
gave her a celebratory hug and we turn
and we
swoosh and we
know it it's nice to hug
her feels
nice
yeah so wholesome te SP hug SP spin
[Music]
hog the meme with c yeah yeah yeah that
was also like we were just posing so
that the director would know where to
put up the image later so I was like
like maybe on this side and we're just
going to present it like this and then
it just so happened that we were making
a meme
pose
what was the one with M that was that
was us taking pictures for the
announcement and we were taking like all
kinds of poses like we were trying to
recreate poses from the dance and stuff
the the teaser image was literally a
dance move that if you are a big Liss
fan W fan you should have recognized it
but I guess you didn't guys and I I felt
U like that you probably not realize it
anyway but yeah then after a few poses
maai you know is trying to do this like
kissing pose I'm
like
okay okay all right then M don't worry
she she was still pretty far from
me it was just an
illusion but it it was a little bit
embarrassing for
me my immersion immersion broken you
could tell I think you could
tell [\h__\h] why is there no
oxygen
[Music]
should I open the
window should probably
[Music]
help let me open the window have no
oygen
[Music]
I tried to circulate
air like every other day but uh it gets
so cold too so I can't do it for too
long an oxygen
bottle but that was the thing I I found
out about in Japan that they had it in
Japan I don't even know if they have it
here
[Music]
my headaches are kind of gone guys just
so you know the headaches I was
complaining about they're not really an
issue at the
moment whoa whoa but but the past two
nights I feel like I I slept really
uncomfortably and uh woke up with even
more body
pain so that's not good anyway let's
continue and I read this so rine thank
[Music]
you made me go on a long tangent for 20
minutes my D golden d d r 41 thank you
for the pinky Fire and Ice life yeah
wait do you know what that means we're
already we're already pass
this okay guys we have to talk a little
bit about
it this
was this was quite complicated I don't
want to break your immersion guys so I'm
not going to go into detail but this
recording was
complicated
complicated air guitar you like my air
guitar immersion it turned out so good
thank you thank you yeah so I think you
could have noticed you you could notice
there is no Cho there was no real Coro
because the OG song also didn't really
have uh
Coro
basically as you may know and then many
people
guessed uh when I when I announced that
these two would be to gamma with me as
guests for a song People guessed oh must
be hello project then yes you were right
of course I purposefully put them
together so that hopefully not only I
would be the one enjoying to sing hello
project because mat said but for example
she's not really into hell project and
she didn't know the song which I was
quite surprised about because I feel
like even if you don't know hell project
you would as a Japanese person you might
be familiar with the song but
anyway uh this song yeah it's also hello
project and I chose these girls because
they're also really into hello project
especially can Senpai Lou just likes
hello project in gen uh Idols in general
I
mean
mhm there's no no no there are these
levitating platforms but they make
everything thing very complicated let's
just say it that way and the microphone
moving thing that also made a lot of
things
complicated but let's not go into
detail uh but yeah I I I I was like
wondering H what song could I sing with
these there's so many good hello project
songs that I want to sing but there were
two factors where I chose that song I
think one of them was well we're free
people so for me it was kind of an
obvious thing to go for a Bono song now
Bono has a few very famous songs and
this one is not necessarily one of their
most famous songs but I really like it
for its Vibe being kind of hype and you
know being kind of like a cheering song
where you guys can join in U but
also um the fact that they sing even in
the original they sing with these St in
microphones um so there's no Cho and I
thought that would make it easier for
myself cuz I already had so many coros
to
learn and so it would be good to have
like one song in there where there's no
Coro and I Could Just
Vibe yeah that was like one reason I
chose that to make it easier for me and
possibly also for the other two
uh yeah but I want to I want to make
more I want to cover more of bonus songs
and generally hello PR songs but in this
case I chose this one because of the
lack of
Coro and then I tried to make the whole
standing microphone thing um the gimmick
and uh I used the platforms because uh I
think um the reason you you guys were
pretty surprised about the platforms
right
I think a lot of people weren't aware
that these platforms could
move and um there's a reason for that
why it just why you guys were not aware
of it it's because
um it's
because nobody really used them until
now
because supposedly supposedly they're
kind of buggy
bugging out glitching
out thankfully it didn't happen in our
situation um so we kind of risked it I
asked them to risk it because I really
want to use them and to be honest this
stage already exists for quite a while
even before our Fredy showcases from
myth and back then I already wanted to
use them um and I think I actually did
use the middle stage but we couldn't
show it properly because it was
glitching and bugging back then already
and they were not sure if they could
show it properly so like only from a
certain
angle um and I asked them okay you know
but it would be nice if it would be
fixed in the
future now over half a year passed and I
don't think anybody worked on it and it
was still there the issue was still
there but I said well I want to use it
though because there's not really much I
can do with the stage I can be at the
top I can be at the bottom we don't have
like a catwalk like the Japanese stage
that I wish I wish we had it cuz I
really love the
catwalk we don't have a floating stage
that goes through the crowd in the
audience you know so I was I was really
really really holding on to using this
gimmick at least of the free stages that
can go
up
yeah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] C why are you in my
chair so yeah uh we made it work and
honestly it didn't glitch at all I
didn't see it glitch a single time so I
feel like they should uh be
more
like confident about using
it you know what it would glitch like
they said that the problem would be that
the reflection on the platforms
when it's like lifted when it's not
integrated in the floor the reflection
of the platforms would um just not
reflect so your the body even though
it's a glass floor or mirror floor it
wouldn't you wouldn't see the body in
there sometimes but it didn't happen at
all but that's why uh generally I just I
just said okay that's fine like how
about we just do angles from below with
which will look cool anyway because if
we're like lifted up then you want to
show that we're up high so you want to
do lower angles anyway so let's just
show it in lower angles and see what
happens goes into
details no there's even more details I'm
not even telling you the whole
story but yeah so all all it went well
it didn't glitch and I I don't know
that's
like the only gimmick that we have in
our stage so I wanted to use
it yeah yeah yeah and yeah we had fun
with this song I think I would hope that
they enjoyed singing a bonus song
because it's you know we love hello
project don't we and I assigned uh H you
know buo consists of three members and
and there's one really small member
who's called momoi who P Senai likes a
lot and momoi is like really iconic she
got like really famous um eventually in
her Idol career later on in in the later
part of her Idol career she got really
famous
for like she had this hairstyle and she
had this whole Persona that she worked
out that she didn't have from the
beginning but she just kind of
eventually started doing this yeah yeah
the the yeah the the double twin tail
the twintail girl but her twin tails are
like kind of curled upwards and a [\h__\h]
ton of hair spray in it so they don't
move they're they're like perfectly
shaped twin Tails H short twin Tails she
will always have bows in them she's
small she always wears pink always puffy
frilly dresses and uh she always lifts
her pinky finger on her microphone if
she holds it or when drink something and
then yeah she acts really funny she
would act really funny and she kind of
turned into comedian and then she's from
my favorite Idol group Betty's coobo but
Bono is if you remember from me telling
you about all of this earlier in in
earlier days but Bono is just a unit
made up of two Branny cobal members and
one C member do you guys remember
this
[Music]
I hope you
do you should remember this because they
were made up by really legendary members
and became a really legendary group that
you could almost say that
Bono is like was somehow more successful
than B kuo and K that originated groups
at some
point
why
[Music]
why why you guys see me hear
me I need to talk about
Idols please let me talk okay only one
second okay like what did you hear Last
I said I was saying that like you could
even say that Bono was more popular at
some point of time then the groups where
the girls originated from and and it was
so hype and it was such a legendary
combination of girls you know and and it
was just so crazy
and and they were I think the most
successful hello project unit there were
many units like as I mentioned remember
W yeah but Bono was the most successful
ever they put out quite a few albums and
they had quite a few concerts yeah it
was just legendary they were so
good no and my Oshi was not in this
group but whatever I still love them
because their music is legendary and the
members are still legendary I still love
them even though my OSI wasn't in the
group m so anyway I took the role of
Suzuki
idy who you have to make this connection
guys you have to make this connection
you have to understand Suzuki ID
remember that name she's the one who
[Music]
sang She after graduating after 10 years
of her original idol group in hello
project which I knew her before you guys
knew
her um after
graduating
she uh is now more po somehow she was
already the most popular member of her
group back then but somehow now she's
even more popular because she reached a
new crowd when she started her solo
career it didn't immediately take off it
didn't immediately take off until she
had that hit
[Music]
song yeah and then she got more and more
anime song deals which brought her to a
new new community
basically but it's crazy cuz she was
also in this group Bono and uh I I was
playing her part and then Louie was
playing the part of M ABI who was from
B's Coble who was really cool she's uh
she also went on after hell project
after she grad graduated from her group
to do some other stuff uh she's still
active um but not as successful as ID
sadly sadly sadly she's really dope
though I I love her too
she kind of has some G gadu Vibes and
then there's mumi
who the end of her career was her Peak
she was invited to so many variety
comedy TV shows in Japan alone without
her group members it was always her she
was so popular with her new gimmic that
was like you know she was used like a
comedian and she was was also bringing
new fame to her Idol group Betty's coal
which was my favorite Idol
group and then the group the group dies
after like over 10 years they graduate
they split up the group they don't say
graduation though they say um
Hiatus but everybody knew it was a
graduation
and M
is one of the few
members if not the only one that you
wouldn't hear from ever again after the
graduation even liso myosi she didn't
continue like doing music or whatever no
she immediately got married and now has
two
kids and I follow her on her social
media she does like Mommy
content she she like you know shows what
she cooks and she every once in a while
she like advertises some some mommy
clothing brands and all
that um but like she's still active like
like everybody's like pretty active
still some went into modeling some still
make
music some make mommy
content and then
Moi you would think she would continue
her career but I kind of understand why
she didn't she completed disappeared she
completely dipped you can't find
anything about her you don't nobody has
any idea what she's up to
and even when the group members get
together to like celebrate another
anniversary you know and get nostalgic
about what they have reached in the past
what they have experienced in the past
muchi is never there I I mean she she
probably she might be there but they
just never show her you don't know what
she's doing you know she's just like
she's completely out of the public eye
she's enjoying her private life and
honestly I totally get it like after she
was how young young was she when oh my
God let me tell
youu her real name isugu Naga Mok m is
just her
nickname she's currently
31 she was born
but she before she joined B's Kobo she
joined like kind of like a training
group in 2002 she was 10 years old old
when she joined this company this
agency and start Idol activities
10 and then she
graduated completely from all these
activities 15 years
later in
2017 6 years
ago so from 10
to
yeah she dedicated her whole childhood
and a chunk of her uh
adulthood to the idol industry Idol
entertainment never I don't think she
had a single Scandal
honestly she was always so professional
so so into it and
oh she even uh did uh University and all
that as well though while doing that she
majored in education and graduated three
years before her graduation of idol
life
so
yeah impressive career yeah but like I'm
not what I want to say is like I totally
understand that after 15
years like starting so early
too where you dedicate your whole life
to that to having no privacy and not not
even not being able to date either from
10 to
25 so totally understanding that she
just wants to like when when the when it
all ended she just went to have a normal
private
life and nobody knows what she's
doing I'm actually impressed maybe
there's some some secrets
deep deep deep in the like
tabloids maybe people have found her
before but I never heard of
it whole history yeah sorry I went on
such a long T sh about hello project
again ah you can't stop me man you can't
stop
me it was just like this Idol agency
really shaped me you know and I was so
into it I've never been so into an idol
group ever again you know they really
special to
me and I find all these connections
really interesting cuz like you guys may
never heard of hello project before I
told you about them but you a lot of you
probably heard about Suzuki
IDI and you know like all these people
who just find find out about her now
most of them have no idea that she's
been in this Idol group called cute
which was kind of like a rival SLS
sister group of Betty's Goble for all
these
years I let me tell you let me tell you
about
idy when she started
she she's born 1994 she's currently
29 she joined when she was 6 seven eight
she talk that she was
eight
eight God in 2002 she was born in 1994
she joined in
2002 so like if you look at her perform
now you can see how she sings and dances
so stable Live Well because she was
trained her whole life for this hello
project focuses so much on live
performances that's just messed up well
that's just you know kind of like how
how it is Idol
but I think maybe it changed a bit I
don't know if they really all start so
early nowadays but back then in Japan
idle stuff was booming and they started
really early and yeah but that she
started in um that was like kind of like
a training group she started in 2002
when she was eight in this training
group and then uh 3 years later when she
was
[Music]
is
yeah 11 when she was
11 she was put into cute and became the
lead
vocalist and since then let's see 2005
until
2017 that is 12
years
right 12 years right 12 years she was in
that group
cute plus another three years from the
previous training groups group so she
was 15 years in hello
Project 8 to 20 uh 8 to
2008 wait she was eight in
2002 15 years
later uh 23 wait
what 20 what what's AG +
[Music]
15 is it
23 oh my God 23 years of idol life and
then she goes on to her solo
[Music]
activities like I don't think she
remembers how life
was as a normal private person of course
not because that was when she was seven
how can you remember that when you're 29
I don't
remember like my how I was when I was
seven sounds really stressful yeah like
I'm impressed she seems to take it
really well and have like a balanced
life and really successful now too so
you
know yeah crazy crazy crazy crazy crazy
oh man I'm so deep in that rabbit hole
or at least I used
to H
she must have some strong mental
fortitude yeah yeah surely she
does I actually like an Andre and anger
me I'm do the most new stuff oh I
haven't been listening I'm sure like
some of the groups every once in a while
still release some bangers but I I just
I have not been keeping up with
them
so
yeah uh that's my tangent about this
song um yeah even though there was no
Coro I think you guys really liked this
performance it was kind of hype right
was a good song and and the the stage
thing worked out well what did you say
my oh she left Mone was like a decade
ago so I haven't yeah same same same
same
no so sad I wish I could go back to
those times I really enjoyed going to
those concerts and losing my
mind it's outright my favorite
performance oh wow thank
you was awesome love the song Choice
thank you yeah was oh wait I I wanted to
say one more thing
um when I heard how doing
Senpai have I been continuously calling
her Senai in these past like two
hours oh when I heard how D and K Senpai
are singing the lines especially do you
know the hi
[Music]
hi hi hi hi you
me um they were all singing it so strong
and this especially
Lou she was singing like
like hi hi
hi you know really strong and I was
like oh I really I really wish I knew
how to sing like that and that motivated
me I don't know if you noticed please
listen back to it and be proud of Wawa
because I tried so
hard cuz I originally was just going to
sing hi hi hi there and then I practiced
really hard I don't think I can recreate
it now but uh I I wanted to get the you
know that feeling in the beginning in
the first syllable so I sang um I I I I
made it I did it I sang hi hi
hi okay see I I didn't nail it this time
but you know you know what I mean right
hi hi
hi kind of just you know Stronger Yeah
Rocky singing
it's so difficult it's so difficult like
like a growl yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah please watch again with this in
mind and then praise the
[Music]
w
there it is there it
[Laughter]
is there it is there it is I can do
it now the bamasa works the best because
it literally like means like break it
down so even the meaning of the lyrics
works and hajima just means let's get it
started
Let's Get It
Started break it all
down and then and then kind s things
don't dream basically saying like just
make it a
reality they have such strong and
special voices so that was that was
really really inspiring to me and I
needed to keep up with that cuz I tend I
tend to sing a little bit like on the
softer side
right
yeah so they forced me to keep
up yeah hydration let me pour some
water thank you I'm rocking rock and
roll
[Music]
baby but other parts were soft on
purpose like the
[Music]
verse those parts were soft on purpose
cuz they're also soft in the
original I hope you like the song guys
I'll introduce you to more dope ass
Japanese songs okay but I'll also try to
mix in English songs just got to keep on
relying on K to give me English songs
that I am actually allowed to sing in an
archived
stream thank you k you know I I'm going
through the the library of K songs the
discography
mhm can always rely on k k
k i want to sing Wild Card the newest
[Music]
one
look get I'm a wild card ah
money
money Mone you wanted me to growl during
that song wink wonk my my Eurovision
song Oh
no that's that's wild card wink
W Maybe next time we can Implement a
growl but it's really
difficult my vocal
fry I got
[Music]
taged
uh let's go let's read super chats again
for the first time in 5 years huh how
about that how about
that thank you Rez for the pinky Again
by nice live yay I know you guys were
kind of already expecting it um and yeah
what can I do yeah it was obvious yeah
cuz CI wanted to release a song before
the uh life
performance but yeah I mean it's not not
bad to have something obvious in it too
it's fine it's fine it's fine
M
yeah it is a Super Chat reading indeed
yes yeah I uh she she you know took care
of all the MB and that stuff but I got
us a
coral I had uh a coral made for us for
the song that whenever we want to
perform it again in the future we can
dance it again cuz now we know and yeah
it was fun learning it together but
let's not let's move that tangent to
another day it's enough for now like I
tangent for hours let me just read super
chats for
[Music]
now thank you thank you thank you jackob
d uh how do you say that
again
Eugene Jen did I say that right
Eugene
[Music]
I made a p in
Japanese there's this word takamaru
takamaru which kind of means like hype
hype hype gets you excited so you can
make this pun you can say
takam Japanese
pun it could be like a like a uh a
slogan it could be a Takami slogan
Takami takamaru Takami takamaru Next
original song We'll be like chanting
this in the song Takami taku Takami
taku I can hear it I can feel
it t
t
[Music]
wait trying to find
Ryan
oh oh okay wait oh I'm going to write a
rap wow wow a progress to no no thank
you we don't need progress Tak takam
[Music]
r
taku like what there's not much that
that rhymes on Maru
let me cook do you guys have something
that rhymes on
M Haru hu
H not
quite
nice I guess Japanese works
is
[Music]
ooh
oh
o oh inspiration I'm
[Music]
cooking my lyric lyric
writer you're not going to help
me
wow
[Music]
like rhy
rhymes
with how about
this okay there's really not much in
English oh should I just keep on adding
Japanese
words
wait what could I say
about your P yeah I'm I'm mixing I'm
mixing
[Music]
okay I have something I don't know if it
fits the the vi the the Rhythm it's
really short
too this is the start
[Music]
weu Tak taku in 2022 we had a
breakthrough hey Takami taku it is the
year
2023 we don't argue takam taku all this
T we say everybody Tak
taku we even have a child who's
[Music]
a any other OTP we
say well you got understand some of
these words otherwise it makes no sense
but do you guys know these words Dagu
means I refuse Kaku I think you can tell
T tasar I think you also understand and
we hajimu we start We
Begin oh you know it from you know it
from JoJo nice okay oh success I
succeeded with my
R even money likes it oh it's fire
oo yeah CI can't really come up with a
comeback after this I think but I'm I
mean she doesn't have to because it's
basically supporting us there's no need
for a
comeback or right here to
a a a a
a mo Mory and Mooney have been real
quiet after
that aura did you just miss my 1 hour
hello project
tangent did you just come in now like I
was [\h__\h] girl you missed you missed
something I was tanging about H project
for like an hour about Bono and B kobu
and cute and how it's crazy you know
like how
mumi completely disappeared but it's
understandable and and Suzuki IDI being
like so famous now and bl blah blue and
how they started Suzuki ID started when
she was 8 years old and she's been in
the business for 25 years and all that
kind of [\h__\h] you miss
[Music]
it no no the tangent is over don't worry
guys I won't torture you anymore okay
okay okay
okay map thank
you rubbing off on each
other sounds good
[Music]
anyway
HD thank
you glory for Takami Takami
[Music]
taku
takam
[Music]
takuu
aier thank you for the r of chat I love
[Music]
my
m Kami K Taki aggressively gay doesn't
like sushi I guess that's
okay wait this this fits this Rhythm as
well agressive gay doesn't like sushi I
guess that's okay what's the rest of the
lyrics I don't remember them freestyle
it is then hey
hey when I have this music on I can't
stop but falling into a
rhythm isn't that it for the most part I
guess so that's
it yeah y y y Mo be like y
y
sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
M I can't even I can't even t a oh yeah
Mo Moy Mo Moy more like
moing moaning moaning into the back
vocals
[Music]
no I have the most utmost respect to
moany because like she can do sounds
that I can't do or I feel like
self-conscious about but like when she
does it it sounds really cool there was
this one time where she wanted me to
make the sound that I just I just
couldn't get I just we laughed we tried
we took like 20 ties and we laughed so
hard about my failures I just couldn't
do
it I think it was this this this weird
like vacuum cleaner pipe sound in my
mind I see a vacuum cleaner pipe you
know the one that has like
these ruffly Parts the the wavy parts
that so that it moves like a tube you
know an example
um I can't I can't
[Laughter]
[Music]
I don't
know I don't know I literally don't know
it's a weird kind of vocal fry I don't
know if it's really a vocal
fry
no I don't I I I don't I don't
[Music]
know just so
embarrassing I don't know
anymore vocal cheese
fries yeah let's just let's just be
productive again how about we just like
try to be productive and efficient
again thank you he thank you so much I
love you
too M Mah m thank you for the support K
Taki loves you
too so D KY D Bruno thank you for the
red
chat congrats on your fretty life Tel
watching you push for bigger and better
content this year despite its ups and
downs has been so inspiring thanks for
lighting a burning flame on so many of
our Lives love you boys love you too
thank you
yeah I want talked about the ups and
downs not
feeling so good this year but uh we're
going to
have more UPS I think it's going up
already so I hope that you can join me
on the passenger seat passenger seat and
then hold my hand because I'm [\h__\h]
terrified of roller coasters let's
go thank you so much Indigo 5 Alpha
thanks for the pinky oh it's a froggy
waa thank you on the on the profile
picture I mean thank you uh K so much
for your hard work thank you thank you
also you're working hard in kfp right
right
[Music]
right surely you are working hard just
as much as I
do I'm watching you I'm watching
you thank you for your support Indigo 5
Alpha Slavic family thanks for the red
CH a that was
awesome you say it like as if the life
is already over it's 35 minutes in it
says for me cute cool why was a rockstar
it was the best life I've ever
seen sound like it's already over oh you
thought it was ending you panic 35
minutes I mean it was not a full hour
but I mean if I would have ended at 35
minutes I
that would be
concerning how excited must you have
been when you noticed it's not over oh
my God but wait there's
more never mind disregard the super chat
then
right now I don't even think this
was was I don't even think this was
before asleep talking was it
too early I
think but yeah thank you w rockar best
life I've ever seen damn you're so sweet
a I'm happy to see you so hyped up hyped
up
chicken thank you sh for the
support I want to see your reaction you
sent another one afterwards oh okay okay
then maybe we'll get to see your
reaction C thank you for the red super
chat woo this Frey concert is pretty
hype thank you very much T you what an
amazing watch what what what what why
why why why I hope that you will have
more opportunities for things like this
in 2024 as I said I think it's looking
good so uh yeah yeah let's go let's go
but why you guys always so like early
with these ending super chats
eh you even had a members only part
still after that
you're already celebrating the end more
or less well thank you thank you I'm
glad that it already satisfied you guys
after 35 minutes
seemingly thank you sy M MJC D and
chicken thank you for the red
super I love you K that sounds so
genuine I'm so happy you finally got
your cave party for life let's go you
will forever be my C oh see I'm so
grateful uh I met you at anime Frontier
yes me too it was a surreal experience I
wanted to
cry the panel was really hype left side
yeah thank you so much K you're welcome
thank you thank you thank you for going
there in person signing up in the first
place for the meet and greet and you
know going there to uh rep kfp and
support the waa with all you God I can
always count on you guys thank you so
much for the
love thank you thank you thank you
hopefully I'll see you again sometime
see you again
sometime oh nostalgic isn't
it
co cute cute profile picture did you
draw that maybe you did cuz I know you
draw but it's so small I can't tell if
that was
yours M thanks for the
pinky I see this is this is during uh
this is
it this is during L
Gumi I think I volunteered to be locked
up in the usual room k joh
no why why did what did you do I'm just
acting Lami was not no
no you guys are not going to the usual
room no problem don't worry about
it I I want you guys to put you in a
happy room where we can all be happy
because we had such a great time and
there's only good things only Good Vibes
only things to
celebrate nobody will be punished or
hurt on such a special
day how could
I the UN unusual room
yeah oh happy
place what's your happy place guys do
you have a happy
place are you going to say kfp are you
going to say here are you going to say
my
[Music]
stream
no I knew it I knew it
oh I mean
here are you going to say something else
first
huh but you guys say either your room
your bed or here which is great cuz you
can combine being in the bed with
watching my streams
cozy good
combination favorite cheese you like
cheese your favorite cheese you just eat
cheese cheese like that and beer I guess
it is a like a
common alcohol snack cheese can't
relate
what what's this what's
this what happened
here
what happened
here freaks me out this freaks me out
guys don't do
this Matrix
glitch now
kiss don't write the same comment right
after each other as if you're in the
same room or
so [\h__\h] hi
mind
it's like exactly the
same
freaky anyway thank you m and thank you
crusty for the rest of a CH it said that
good things come to those who wait mhm
that's certainly proven true today
congrats on such a fun and well produced
fry live Teno you definitely deserve
this and I just hope that you and all of
Ian can continue to live this Weber Idol
dream oh thank you yeah I
mean why wouldn't we why wouldn't we
will will continue to live this dream it
is indeed kind of a dream still dream
job
yeah I am I don't think I would want to
uh go back to a normal job so this is
good for me now I will stay
uhhuh and May make the most out of it
crusty I can count on you right to
support me thank you for being here
thank you for being such a great chicken
employee crusty you're so crusty crunchy
and crusty here's a
kiss thank you for watching the live
hope you enjoyed it thank you soon for
being
there
Lord D cat shark
Jin no Shin
Jag
K uh Flappy Boy Thanks for the red chat
congrats on closing the year with an
eoric bang now you can finally reap the
fruits of your painful
[Music]
labor I hope they taste even more sweet
the more they have been delayed the
amounts of recent wins for kfp is simply
unreal best F of Advent oh yeah right it
was an advent yeah yeah yeah yeah I
haven't been lighting my candles at
all well I don't know if it really
tasted more sweet I would say no the
opposite it tasted more bitter because
it was so so delayed but it's
okay I'm just happy it it happened in
the first place yeah
know
Bitter
Sweet I guess you could say
Bittersweet well
but it felt great felt great and I'm
really satisfied with the outcome and
the product
so I am I am
delighted yes it was indeed painful
labor very painful labor so thank you
for holding my hand and
me thank you for watching over me Flappy
Boy Flappy
[Music]
boy our om God soon just another kfp
thank you for the pinky this concert has
been so amazing incredible guests and
solos and surprises and we're just so
proud of you y thank you
I'm happy to hear that that's all I need
to hear I'm proud of you feels good
thank you so much originally I wanted to
have like one or two more guests and you
know a bit more ambitious things going
on but even then even then it was a
learning experience
so next time I'll make even more of my
ideas come true hopefully hopefully
hopefully a thank you for waiting for it
and supporting me all along just another
kfp you're not just another one you
are the
one David es skill thanks for WR Super
Chat this aaspa is a long time coming
I'm so very grateful for celebrating
another year with you and kfb your hard
work and dedication continues to inspire
me here's to a glorious 2024 cheer yeah
all right we're already like celebrating
the new year let's go let's go happy New
Year almost but wait we didn't even have
[Music]
Christmas thank you
though I guess you're really optimistic
and excited about it me too me too so
let's go let's have fun together next
year as well thank you for the
longlasting support and always being
loyal and by my side thank you m
[Music]
David Yumi thanks for the pinky congrats
on all of your hard work with your Frey
concert I watched with no idea what to
expect you bring to the show so many
cute moments and dazzling effects and
100 out of 100 superb dancing and
singing from all of you you really are
wonderful thank you oh I appreciate that
I I worked so hard on the dancing I
really didn't have much time was kind of
SC and exhausting and you guys remember
how much I complained about pain in my
body at the time and lack of sleep and
all that
yeah but at least the second recording
day I think if I remember correctly I
did get a good amount of sleep cuz a lot
of pressure was off of me after the
first one yeah the first recording
day that was kind of tough those those
days were tough I hope next time I'll be
more relaxed and have more time cuz also
like all of these dances I learned like
not all of them but a lot of them I
learned within the
week and like so many different ones if
it's just one dance whatever easy but so
many so
next time for my birthday thingy I might
stay there a bit longer like maybe three
weeks
and yeah cuz I was doing like during the
daytime I was having dance lessons and
then in the evening I was having off
collabs like trying to make the most out
of it so that you guys also get streams
still and and so that you know I don't
disappoint by going to Japan and you
know not doing anything visually to you
guys you know you know so next time
maybe I can balance it out a bit more by
being there a bit longer you know you
know spread it out a bit more
yeah yeah
yeah I wasn't even planning originally
to have so many off collabs I was
planning to have less off collabs but
then it just kind of happened I got
excited and I scheduled a bit more than
I wanted
to better for my sanity next time see
again uh I learned it was a learning
experience next time we're going to do
better I'm going to have more time to
prepare as well
so Galu thank you Yumi for the sweet
words though you know it was really
rough behind the scenes but I'm glad
that you were able to appreciate the end
product so
much
MMO
707 thank you for the pinky the way you
performed TCW was bewitching oh
bewitching it was my most played song of
the year oh and I never get tired of it
seeing it sng with beautiful life vocals
and choreography was stunning thank you
for the amazing performance my kamhi
yeah
tgw uh because of like time
issues I for once did not ask
Tiana the
usual choreographer no I had it done by
Japanese choreographer and I was I was
pretty satisfied with the the vibe that
came from it didn't even have to like
change
much yeah so I really like the
coral it's like I don't know it has this
atmosphere in the
moves interally I'm walking by it's how
to say if if
feral eeral eeral I don't
know was it no no no I said Japanese
it's just uh basically same person as
like who was teaching me night
circulation and so
on but R culation she would just
basically learned the dance from
watching the video and then Taun it to
AKO Senai and I already knew it anyway
but it wasn't her Coro but tgw was her
Coro oh yeah
yeah but yeah uh that was fun that was
fun I hope I can perform it again but I
feel like we absolutely nailed it also
like in combination with the the light
situation the how to
say I don't know all these words but
yeah this the Stage
production it was a Vibe all
over
was
fun oh yeah the lasers and the fog yeah
I really like the fog the fog so this n
where was
I yeah thank you for the amazing
performance my yeah thank you thank you
always for supporting and drawing the
Wawa you're the best thank you so much
ghost be
tgw is indeed such a bob I'm glad you
like it so much I I danced it just for
[Music]
youon spank thank you for the red J wow
just wow wow incredible show congrats to
you and everyone involved still not sure
I'm not dreaming this it's real I know
it's early in the morning and you would
rabit sleep at that time but it was real
so
real as real as your love is to me
right thank you this was at 49 so this
was yeah seemingly pretty much the
ending I
suppose I wish it was longer yeah but
did it feel long to you guys or did it
feel really short cuz when I when I told
you when I watched it it felt really
like plenty long to
me cuz I packed so many songs into it I
guess I really should have like stalled
it with MC's but I didn't know I didn't
know fat long felt
right yeah F long in a good way good
length right yeah I think so too it
didn't feel like something was
necessarily missing unless you look at
the
timer m
and then you got to consider that there
was a members only on
Court and that was 20 minutes
surprisingly I thought it would just be
15 minutes and honestly I thought
because I saw other members on course be
like 15 minutes so I thought it it it
couldn't be longer than 15 minutes but I
was told that I would be allowed to do
up to 30
minutes in theory
but like look at how much I would was
able to record in 2
days how am I going to how am I going to
do 30 minutes and a full hour uh more
MC's more MC's more
MC's I don't know how
else but I don't know I don't think the
members Anor encor really needs to be
half an hour that almost feels Overkill
I think 15 20 minutes is The Sweet
Spot oh coyi Senai did she do 30 minutes
sheesh
shees needed more
ads Oops I did it
again just ignore it I will never learn
I I will
never
them at least I don't call the reg gloss
girls Senpai it is very obvious to my
brain that they're not Senpai don't
worry I don't
Calla Senai I don't know why it's so
different cuz it's not like our debuts
were close at all at all
they don't have big Seer energy yeah
honestly they
don't they
don't I mean I don't know why but like
coyote going so hard on the amount of
streams and Lou just kind of being such
a mature
Vibe I don't know they they just make me
want to call them
senpai
just 14 months I think that's that's
over a year so it's I wouldn't say
[Music]
just 20 minutes on her
anniversary ah I guess they were the
first new Japanese members after I
joined oh that's
crazy that's crazy if you think about
it
oh yeah I guess that that that makes
sense cuz like right before we debuted
there was a Japanese
gen and then 14
months
Los Angeles
Senpai Los
Angeles Los Angeles should I call her
Los Angeles
Senpai how do you think she would react
if I said Los Angeles
standby she wouldn't get
it she wouldn't understand you think so
we're going to test it out then anyway
back to Super Chat we thank you sp time
should I spank you so you realize it's
not a dream yes please no typen thank
you for the
rainbow big rainbow I still can't
believe it's been yet another year in KY
and this is certainly an amazing way to
celebrate and at long last I get both of
my aies together for an original song oh
wait I don't think I
realized you were
takoshi I always believed it would
happen any you two made something that
will be on Loop for years over three
years you have truly been a shining star
for it's impossible to put into words
how you have somehow kept reaching New
Heights while also keeping such an
amazing relationship with your community
as a whole it's truly something unique
the next year and how however many more
that come from here are truly going to
be amazing because we know you'll work
as hard hard as you can to keep making
us all smile yeah I will we could not
ask for someone more incredible than
you if this year brings more music more
streams or just more tangents we will
all truly be happy I think we all know
we only see a fraction of how hard you
work for us and so many different things
so wherever this is coming you this
coming you takes us coming year I guess
no we love you Ki no we appreciate you
so much and that whatever happens SC is
behind you we finally took a forever woo
yeah okay I'm going to ignore that part
because that kind of ruins the
emotion thank you so
sweet wow
wow your magical
words
they go deep deep into my heart into my
Coco thank you so much a
I hope I can continue delivering the
content you want guys and I hope I never
disappoint
you sometimes my whole existence is
disappointing I know but
um I'll try my best I don't want to
disappoint you but please if I do
someday maybe forgive me forgive
me please forgive
me please give give me one forgiving
card okay one just
one just
one and then I do V beam and you forget
okay
please and then you forget that it was
used in the first place the forgiven
card and I get it I get to use it again
and then I use the vas beu again and
then you forget it again that you know
you used to forget it's card forgive
card and it's like an endless loop so
basically I can mess up forever and you
will forever forgive
me infinite
[Music]
glitch what don't wor every time you say
debut that I'm disappointed ah deute
deute deute deute debute Deb
debut Deb debut not debut debut debut
debut debut debut debut
debut not debut
debut debut de be eh
whatever shut up I'll I'll probably
forget anyway thank you for the
membership
[Music]
welcome she's a be
de debut debut oh no tea oh my God you
guys are so
like I just go back to debut it yeah you
like
P
my I think opening the window really
helped but I'm going to close it now cuz
it's getting
cold
debuted I'm going to
debut
new bgm why are you frightening with
me me me knife
why how
about what is this unnamed
[Music]
track you're going to go insane if I
play this too long but I don't care
thank you tyon for the beautiful rainbow
and the Beautiful
words thank you so much means a lot to
me thank you very very special Super
[Music]
Chat this was animal cross
Engish
space Dominic K bgy with a pinky I'm
breathless ah I can't then I is that
what you're singing huh the choreography
cam work stage to side effects I love
this concert looking forward to the
members only inor Anor love from all of
broke kfp2 thank
you do you know do you guys know stage
the
sign
[Music]
um I I didn't even
really give any input
I didn't know I didn't know what to
do I couldn't
[Music]
really like I don't I don't know cuz I
didn't want to make it look unserious by
putting like burgers and buckets and
stuff like that all over maybe one day
if I have like a more like loose fed
life then like Phoenix is like also like
so difficult like besides feathers what
you going to do what you going to put
there anyway I mean it's not much
besides feathers anyway the thing in the
back looks like a Squan now that I look
at
it no
but I think now that we had this next
time I won't like necessarily try to Fe
it after
myself like for example it's going to be
in summer right so I could do like a
beach them again put sand on the stage I
wonder if I can put sand on the stage
then it won't be reflecting anymore but
um
um I feel like if sand on the stage was
possible somebody would have done it
already feel like it but yeah sand palm
trees stuff like that although I must
say you know what I found was really
cool surprisingly when the cie and me
Fire and Ice song
Started we were up there on the top of
the stage that we didn't use much but
just for that song I thought it would be
pretty cool and they
like the
song the way it starts and then combined
with they made those parts that are
orange now they made those
green and it gave me such a weird
tropical
Vibe but it was kind of dope it was
really
refreshening did you not notice they
made it green it was glowing
green and it's kind of
gave it this whole new
Vibe of like more tropical which somehow
even though the song isn't really like
tropical EDM whatever it's more like
just normal EDM I don't know I don't
know what that
is but it made me feel like it was kind
of tropical
tropical ad future future based ad EDM I
don't know these funky funky funny
words
[Music]
M tropical house Teddy
Lloyd the song was really difficult for
me by the way both like like singing it
cuz there was like these lower parts and
then there were some parts that I felt
really awkward about singing so it was
kind of difficult but I got used to the
song cuz I've been listening to it for
like months now it's been in the works
for months
and especially in combination with this
like life performance well I I it grew
on me it definitely grew on
[Music]
me
n what are you
[Music]
explaining why you def defining
refreshing what
[Music]
sounded amazing live thank
you cuz I said
refreshening oh you're correcting me to
refreshing or so refreshing
whatever whatever I don't want to hear
or none of
that anyway thank you
Dominic I appreciate
it broke kfb I love you guys too don't
worry about it if you can't Super Chat
that doesn't make you make me love you
any less I'm a beep Dan Eternal dive
part two
Dan Mr V
[Music]
Dan
corpse and danash thank you Sean Ian
[Music]
danash I don't really think this is
something you need to Super Chat but
okay car sodum D for the crazy triple
red Super Chat you
crazy are you
crazy are you crazy caret what's what's
going on why would you throw so much
money at me eh
why why why why why such a bang over an
event W amazing performances amazing
guest list and well worth the wait
congrats again on the end of the your
life you deserve this and so much more
thank you you know what's
absurdum this amount of
[Music]
money absurd amount of money thank you
for the red
chats absur
chicken thank
you
[Music]
yeah what what how do I even thank you
properly
huh well I'm glad you liked it so much
that you would donate so much very very
generous of
you it's a free life are you aware of
that you don't have to pay 300 buckes if
you're trying to get a ticket from that
American ticket service
whatever it's called
again I'm not trying to rip you
off yeah Ticket Master there's not
Ticket Master here
[Music]
okay oh have you guys um has anyone
applied for the the ticket overseas
ticket or package even
couldn't get Auto tickets for less than
[Music]
400 yes me ooh
oo
[Music]
o Lottery yeah not the package but
overseas
lottery I applied for the lottery
oh
oh okay I wish you
luck I hope you get
it it just says like one night in a
hotel right I wonder like is it going to
be close to the
venue where is it going to
be I wish wish you could have that kind
of information huh oh well what if it's
like a five bucks per night
Hotel
most likely be the APPA res at makali
that would be great yeah I stayed at the
APPA hotel in makali before APPA hotels
are like it's a big uh Hotel chain in
Japan normally they have like pretty
tiny
rooms but they're all over Japan and the
quality is nice the the it's always
clean it's easy to check in easy to
check out relatively although the one at
makali they have like automated
everything like years ago
was kind of
weird it's kind of overwhelming a little
bit but just because of the sheer size
of the makuh hadti Uppa Hotel so if you
end up in there maybe it will be a bit
confusing to find your room cuz also
it's like I think three different Towers
or
so and you're like instead of a room key
I think you get like a little ticket
that tells you what room you are like a
paper
ticket and then you got to find it good
luck with that
but could have changed again cuz that
was like years ago but it's like when
you when you're in your room I had a
room once when I looked out of the
window I saw the line of it was for
Tokyo game show I saw the people who
were lining up for Tokyo game show
outside to get
in I was watching them from above
[Music]
love the rest is a bonus good luck good
luck to you guys the waa watch yeah I'm
Saun I was Saun Wawa in the tower
watching over
[Music]
you
oh that was my finger I cracked my
finger anyway thank you copy are you
here who's trying to look out for you in
the
[Music]
chat are you not here oh my God thank
you though Mah mwah Mah o 176 thank you
for the red super chat as well
congratulations to finally having your
Fredy concert T the song's the guest the
stage and the performances everything
was awesome my oce once again proved
what a great singer and Entertainer she
is thank
you thank you thank you thank you I
tried my best in all of these things
except for like the stage I didn't
really do anything in the stage design
as I said yeah but I I tried to get the
gimmick to work you
know and you know I I had a lot of input
and was able to create the life that I
wanted to be more or less so I'm excited
to do more stuff like this really like
even more even more so now now that I
got a taste of it I want more more more
more more so look forward to it oh do
should I say o or oie or oie what do I
say how do I say your
name Fe the hunger
[Music]
okay they're also not here it
seems
like the wizard of o oh so
o thank youan
o Rainer thank you for the red chat Tel
thank you for working so hard and
diligently to keep us entertained I wish
you all the happiness and success in the
coming year because if anyone deserves
it it's
you I love you thank you thank you I
agree I agree I agree so much with you
we are probably the same person rer or
are you
way way in a really bad
disguise one of those things you're
either wa or you're me there's no other
choice sadly not don't lie to me don't
lie thank you so
much rain in a trench coat
[Music]
that's funny that's
funny she's more Raina than Raina
because she's Rainier or he's Rainier
he's Rainier than
Raina like next level
Raina
[Music]
wow
wow sorry for teasing your name
Unity chat thank you for the red chat
this was such an amazing experience your
dancing was so on point and the moves
were so sexy and crisp high quality
production my favorite probably was
sleep talking just now a very
intoxicating performance I also love
voice with rain Ultra cute thank you can
I just say can I just say sleep talking
the dance break where I'm like on the
phone hello baby who are you talking to
yeah yeah yeah yeah if you want to you
know what you got to do you know you
want it just want look down so don't
break down hello Bobby who are you
talking to that part I I choreographed
myself I choreographed it myself and I
still messed
up but it's not noticeable cuz you don't
know what it's supposed to look
like but that part I did myself
because the dance break that Kiana made
I didn't have enough time to learn it
first of all my brain was like
exploding
and I I also thought like man there's
like something that I had in mind that I
wanted to do
so yeah and oh my god when making your
own moves it's actually so much easier
to remember them maybe I should do it
more often
what about the love Rush dance break oh
oh oh oh thank you for
asking thank you for this perfect
question this is from Members Only I
performed love Rush as the first song
did you notice that um generally I I I I
there was some chal parts like it was
generally like more loose right but I
did make a loose Coro so during the
verses and then during the chorus I was
just like you know waving my hand waving
my arm and then letting the chicken fall
on me and so on but it was fought
through cuz I didn't just want to stand
there and sing um cuz I'm I have this
dancer reputation that I have to protect
but there was the dance break that I
wanted to be a bit more interesting
right yep
I made a mix and this was a bit
difficult I made a mix with all my uh
first five songs coros so Hony heart
challenge of uh F knight uh do you and
Sparks not in the release order just in
the order where I thought I could
squeeze it
in yeah it's a Coro medly that I thought
oh my God that it's like even more like
making the song into an emotional song
with the Cho I made it like feel even
deeper
right yeah I think heart Challenger was
the most obvious
one cuz but then it was funny because
heart Challenger you know you
[Music]
know uh where I I swing my arm in like
two big circles and then small circles
and big circle and small circle it's
really exhausting to do that move but
anyway I don't know why this is the
first time that I ever did that but I
think
I swung it in the wrong
direction I was like [\h__\h] in my brain I
was like [\h__\h] why I never did it wrong
before why did I suddenly swing it in
the wrong direction like I think I swung
it an normally goes backwards I think
and I no
from
back up it's both backwards but like I
went from bottom to up instead of bottom
to down or something like that or the
other way around but yeah I swung it the
wrong way and I was like [\h__\h] why did I
do that but generally it's a uh it's a
medling of my previous coros so I was
hoping you guys would notice it and I
think it started with
fight
H
[Music]
fa and then do
you then I went
into
no yeah and then Sparks you I do you
Sparks maybe and then heart Challenger
and then he know told you was last for
[Music]
sure you thought he was last yeah but
you know then basically Al um the night
before the
recording is when I came up with it I I
put my I I was in this relatively small
Airbnb that actually had no space to
dance and so I I moved the there was
like one relatively
small table with two
chairs the table being the size of the
chair one of the chair basically like
really small so I put it on the balcony
of the Airbnb to give myself at least a
little bit of space and then I I opened
my laptop and I I I spliced I cut the
coros of my previous coros and then I in
Adobe Premier Pro I took like the parts
I wanted to use and I tried to match it
to The Melodies some of them I had to
like speed it up a little bit some of
them slowed down so that they would fit
the Rhythm and it was quite difficult U
but eventually I got like a good
combination a good
remix of the chal and then I practice
and I practice and I practice and I
practice the flow you would think it
would be easy but no I kept on
forgetting like oh what comes after this
one uh oh yeah right
[Music]
Sparks and then I I made the the other
little like loose coros like during the
verse like a few idle steps and then uh
like box step to the right box step to
the left and then this and that you know
you know so it's it's made by waa so
please appreciate love rush there's a
lot of love in it and I had so much fun
with the chicken too do you want to know
who was the
chicken
it
was no not jenma not you I guess yeah it
was you in your brain
yeah it was
[Music]
Ed new new manager
s yes it was so fun we had so much fun
but also
oh oh do you want to know should I break
your immersion this was the first song
right of
the of the members only and I go
directly into an MC right do you know
that
actually I had to record this whole
thing including the
MC four or five
[Music]
times
because the chicken would start like
laugh lagging and losing FPS or
so in the like around the end of the
song for some reason and then like after
the first time we were like okay let's
fix it and then they were like okay we
think we fixed it let's record it again
and then I did it again the whole song
and the the the MC but it happened again
and I was just like pulling through
until the very end hoping that maybe it
will still be acceptable footage but
then it wasn't really and and then they
they're like okay I think we fixed it
now and we did it again and was still no
no so we did it again so several times I
did that so
um Eda was pretty exhausted because this
whole time she was like um
crouching and like when she was
following me she was like um uh kneeling
kneel
walking she was trying her
best we're a bit slow oh yeah you were
losing FPS it's okay like she was
holding the chicken you know she was not
the chicken she was holding the
chicken
yeah she was she was pretty exhausted
but she really I think she enjoyed the
experience because she also said it was
like her first time cuz she's still new
and like this was her first time even
seeing the the studio and all that and
she immediately got involved because I
was like okay I need a chicken I need
somebody to be my chicken Eda
you do you want to do it so we had fun
together she really did a good
job i r draw my statement a chicken is
not no it's you but like she was you
were not able to move without her
assistance
so
yeah yeah we had a good time together
was really funny even though we had to
record it several times but that just
added you know stuff like that adds to
the recording
time like we record one whole thing it
takes five six minutes and then we check
back on it the footage has to be checked
and then something has to be fixed and
then all of that takes another 10
minutes and we record again and takes
another six minutes oh it's wrong again
I have to fix it again takes 10
minutes so this is how this adds up and
then surprised now you have a 10hour
recording
day just to give you
like an understanding of how it can even
be so
long now we got some good bonding time I
really like her I really like
her I really like
her she's so sweet and she's
cute yeah I want to keep her yeah
yeah I'm going to hire her as my
assistant
manager yeah she's she she speaks the
language the accent of the Gods after
all yes adopt
adopt
[Music]
yeah yeah I I need a second manager to
be honest for like at least at least for
times that are more stress
like
that okay anyway let's continue thank
you Unity chat than you soon yeah I'm
glad you like sleep talking so much I
was really exhausted during sleep
talking but thank
you I wish I was sleeping during sleep
talking not sleep dancing not sleep
twerking I just wanted to sleep simply
sleep thank you un cat mwah mwah Mah
mwah arur it's it's finally your turn
where you like this whole time where
you're like when is she going to move on
when is she going to read the next Super
Chat thank you for the pinky congrats on
the fre life W from the set list to the
guest list everything came together to
perfectly round up the busiest year yet
was it I mean I feel like every year
feels so busy
but it's hard to tell
really maybe I did yeah I might have I
might have yeah been the busiest this
year yeah yeah no I mean otherwise I
wouldn't have almost lost my mind
looking up literally looking up rage
rooms in
Austria I told you
right still want to go but I'm not as
Angry
[Music]
Anymore yeah I found I found them
there's rage
rooms yeah
yeah next time next time
I'll go to one yeah the content yeah oh
yeah I wanted to do a retrospective
music video in the rage
room can't redo smashes television the
past and present smashes
table goes with an axe into the
chair I
can't that would be so good
though not the T no not the tally I'm on
the
tally can't destroy the
[Music]
tally sounds an ironically like a great
idea right sounds fun yeah I think so
too just be careful not to hurt yourself
oh I think you're like you have to wear
certain protection things
[Music]
yeah someone them have a car you can
destroy
yo oh is it like you know the place
where cars get destroyed what's it
called shot plats in
German anyway thank you offra wait I
didn't read the whole thing did I thanks
a lot for your hard work let's keep
going full steam into uh ahead into 2024
cheers to you my C oh C ay okay my Cami
chicken thank you so much let's go
together 2024 it's going to be our
year if this year wasn't already our
year oh yeah junkyard that's what I
meant then next year is going to be our
year yeah let's go thank you for always
supporting our thank you for being here
right now too nice to see
you P good time thank you for the red
super chat and guys we're by the way at
165 H it ends at 200 how nice or does it
wait a
second oh yeah it does there was another
arrow but it just leads back to the
beginning okay okay okay okay okay I
think I can finish the
day I've been chilling so much and going
so slow as
well the me me one members one maybe
I'll read during
members I don't think it has that much
any does it well maybe it does I don't
know the the okay hoizer deceived me I
think cuz hoizer didn't register all of
them I
guess there's only 12 yeah only 12 on H
lier
though you guys are being deceived as
well isn't there more probably uh cuz H
lier only registered them until the
point of where I switched it in two
members that's what I think happened and
that's why we are being deceived into
thinking it's not so much but it might
be it might
be let me
check 1 2 3 4
[Music]
M it's okay
well I could count as one 2 3 4 5
6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 15 15 16
[Music]
57 57 super chats
and most of them are not red or
pink no okay not half maybe half maybe
half
I can count so
well yeah maybe I'll read it during
members only we'll see we'll see oh cuz
we have a a movie watch along and that
will be kind of chill so you know so how
as always we just get absolutely spoiled
by Tanto tgw and sleeptalking coros back
to back and both looking absolutely
Stellar how am I even supposed to
contain my hype s
my hopefully we can get now fre live
next year too I promise you
will yes yes yes a good
amount so let's let's let's let's get
excited for it I
mean it will be a little bit of a wait
until my next birthday but it will
happen yeah I promise a promise a
promise I promise I promise I promise
sorry I'm doing M go right now she never
said that but I feel like she
could yeah I promise I promise I promise
I
[Music]
promise what is it about moo that's so
catchy to
[Music]
me Pro myth
yeah today today
today it's so catchy
oh
[Music]
man today
today sorry I
can't oh so
catchy thank you thank you pal thank you
for still letting me be your
Koshi you know um that's like one of my
biggest
fears you guys switching me out so I try
my best to keep you guys I'm fighting
for you fighting for your love thank
you what wet what I want to I want to
learn how they say what what it's like
what what what
what what what what like
[Music]
that qu what a little bit of an H there
right what
what can we make
AOK wet compilation or is only mukoko
the one who say something like that
wet maybe it's only
[Music]
M oh there's no wet
clip what why is there no wet clip how
am I supposed to learn
it oh
wait I wonder why Donkey Kong weighs 800
lb how many bananas do you think that is
how much do a banana we ruest do the
math numers of the
what it's not even a word m it's not
even a
word it's not even a
[Music]
word it's
SC a
banana it's SC why that was why why that
was not what that was why that one was
why she's like why does it scare
you
why it's scar me
why and
and have protein in them right and you
need to eat protein for muscle
right and then you think he's been
eating there's maybe there's other Kongs
we just don't know them anymore cuz they
were eaten maybe that's why Diddy Kong
is so small don't eat them he didn't
care to eat Diddy Kong because he was
Tiny anyways I need somebody to be My
Sacrifice
anyways
oh I wanted to say this does am I the
only one who when I hear Fu laugh I hear
a bit of Lami
s her laugh reminds me of
lamai am I the only one to let me find a
comparison Lami
laugh
okay that was maybe
not M she needs to laugh a bit
[Laughter]
longer it's like the first laugh she had
there but like
longer not not it's not a good example
but you know I feel like her laugh is f
laugh reminds me of Lami Senai sometimes
detect
[Music]
k no the the it comes from the
belly I don't know it's hard to
explain
[Music]
sticky
why does she not laugh when I want her
to
[Music]
laugh
that's not I mean people have different
kind of laughs right so this one was
also not the
[Music]
one
it's not a good example it's not a good
example okay I give up but I will stand
by my
opinion I Stand My
Ground oh oh I have received calendar
video number
there we
go clear what you need to do is organize
a for yeah maybe I do need to do that
maybe they'll just do it on their own
eventually
honestly maybe they don't need
me I love it thank you you need to prove
it
[Music]
I like their laughs they're kind of
nice it's like a laugh that gives me a
warm feeling in my tummy when I hear
it it's
so wholehearted I cannot explain it
anyway I'm sorry I'm sorry for going off
rail
again
[Music]
again again
again than you
flaming pants fried screw
for red Super
Chat the CL was amazing W couldn't
expect anything less from our amazing T
I can still feel the energy in my veins
wa in your veins congrat kiala really
you are the best k
Tim could ask her for the best Idol I
know all I want to
say thank
[Music]
you what it's hard to recreate just
while like you can't really put it down
in actual letters
you have to hear it it has to be audible
anyway I'm so sorry please forgive me
forgive me I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm
sorry thank you for your support I love
you than viva viva Fri s
than get Moko out of my head now Andre
the gameer Creed thanks for the pinky
let's go pinky pinky I'm so dang proud
and so dang happy to see all the hard
work you've put into this and not
mention all the pain and suffering
you've endured over this year be worth
it in the end congratulations K you
deserve this so much thank you thank you
thank you thank you so
much
well
yeah I don't know it's um I I I I think
uh it doesn't excuse like some of the
stuff that made me feel bad but it's
okay we're on a positive uh track to
positive lands in a positive
mindset so positive KF positive KF
positive KF positive k f positive let's
stay positive come on
positivity feel it charge it let it
out okay okay positive we are all
positive posi
sing nice nice
nice
KF Nancy positiv no no no okay okay just
positivity no no positive pregnancy test
[Music]
okay no positive Corona test
either only positive
mindset yes yes yes yes
qu
[Music]
what what do you mean h positive coron
coron but it's always positive you don't
even have to specify
that it sounds like Sakura from card
Captain sakur what really sorry I said
what so normally I
meant
uhhuh 2.0 yeah don't worry I'll I'll
forget about it I'll forget about it and
thank you the gamer queen queen thank
you for being proud of me and and for
celebrating with me let's celebrate more
together in the future every another
cold thank you for the red super chat my
o is
beautiful your dancing is so good Freddy
Wawa is too powerful I can feel my brain
melting from the W cuteness and those
hips thank you for the 3D performance K
and for always pushing for more we
appreciate it thank you thank you so
much yeah got to keep on pushing pushing
pushing if I just like expect everything
to happen on its own I will not have
anything happen so got to keep on
pushing and it may be exhausting
sometimes to always push push
push it is kind of exhausting but with
you guys behind me pushing for K of
positivity I can keep on
going I can keep
on working
hard yeah yeah at least there there was
um mhm there was a positive return
Thanks to the K of
positivity K off KF
positivity yeah thank you every another
call
yeah I'm happy to be your ory Jim Tracy
thank you for the rested of D this was
incredible fantastic singing awesome
guests and amazing choreography I can't
say enough about how great this was all
of your hard work and patience finally
paid off congratulations K you're truly
the best Aus
no you really mean it you really mean it
thank you so much I love
you
thank you for letting me be your
[Music]
o thank you for the Fantastic fry
concert Angel no thank you for being
such a fantastic
audience hey oh I've always wanted to
say y'all you were the best crowd ever
New York Los Angeles
Japan but can't really specify so
YouTube you we the best audience today
you were so great better than any other
audience I ever had
YouTube can't really say it like
that doesn't feel the same way doesn't
hit you the same
way doesn't feel like they specifically
really mean
you Earth yeah Earth you're the best Yo
sick you guys are so sick
guys but it's okay but just say kfp
you're the best kfp I love you KF
positivity let's
[Music]
go the location of every single
individual viewer well that's okay
because your location is kfp at your
local kfp so I'll just say kfp I love
you that's all I need to say I would
hope
otherwise it's going to be a bit
difficult yeah we're on the K of
[Music]
planet we had fun
r429 dler Stein D thank you Kunis thank
you for the red super chat so many great
songs I'm speechless thank you thank you
very much I'm glad you like the set list
I tried to um do as many original songs
as possible I know you guys were missing
retrospective uh I just didn't really
feel like it fitted into the vibe I was
going for um it's definitely like a you
know a banger but like it just didn't
feel like it
matched into the rest of the set
list yeah another
time next year next
year
yeah eventually down the road but yeah
I'm glad I'm glad I'm glad you like the
songs thank you
[Music]
jie thank you for the red your hard work
is appreciated I love the whole concert
thank you my
oi it's like you guys know you have to
put that into the Super Chat because it
will Tickle My
Fancy thank you thank you soon I worked
really really hard on it like you have
no idea how hard I worked on this thank
you n n
no sudden frog bird didn't know I had it
in me huh a Kermit
voice didn't know I had it I didn't know
either
I know is this how was talking the whole
time that's [\h__\h]
exhausting it's really
difficult it's really
[Music]
difficult
quack I miss frog birt I miss him n no
thank you this thank you for the red
thank you for an amazing pretty life the
work and heart you put until it was
clear from the final results I can't
wait to see what amazing new music and
work you bring into the New Year all the
years after CU Your Vessel and humble
servant
DVR thank you CU that's so
old how to how to say you're an OG
without saying
it this
way
C you
forever C you
all C
you C you too
desol thank you so much a I I don't know
if I can bring you as much new music
this coming year as last year because I
mean we got five new songs by making an
album um I'll probably be less cuz as I
said before I want to make singles uh
not necessarily another
album but yeah I'm going to try to make
them
all satisfactory at least for me bubs
and hopefully we can nail them
all I'll probably I'll have to warn you
guys I'll
probably lean hard into the K-pop in in
the future as well guys and I'm sorry I
know you don't all like K-pop but it's
what I want to do I want to focus on the
direction you know I want to like kind
of um set myself apart as well and like
show that this is the this is kada Pop
you
know is the kiaha
pop I think it's good to have something
like that cuz like Cali has her rap and
she's known for her rap I want to be
known for the kiata pup I think it's
important
to give yourself such an
image
yeah yes yes yes
yes s is there although I wouldn't mind
releasing another song like tgw sometime
in between cuz does that
one
really
yeah gave me a special
feeling yeah I don't know about
releasing more retrospective is songs
sorry sorry sorry but that's just like I
enjoyed it and I liked the outcome but
it's just not something I would normally
go to especially if it's a single if if
I do another album we can do variety
again but uh
yeah in the end I'm going to go for the
things that um I have lots of confidence
in you
know maybe we can do some remixes though
some rocky
[Music]
remixes sounds good right I think so
too pop let's
go yeah
kada fried pop
kfp yeah you like the the the Sparks
remix I'm so happy yes SP remix it's so
funny it's so good it's like
ridiculous yeah thank you green Wilder
for the pinky happy not your birthday
mhm
believe it or not it's not my birthday
too what what a coincidence what you did
amazing with this everything was great
fire night might be my favorite o the
outtakes at the went were very cute
right yeah was a good call mhm mhm wa
makes the good calls W makes all the
good calls thank you I'm I'm happy you
like fire I so much D it's a
really M unique unique
song Finally Takami Takami taku as we
like to say
mhm thank you very much for the support
green Wilder happy not birthday to you
too ziply what's going on you changed
your name you changed your name changed
your name zly enjoying 3D technology
what's going
on cute cuz I guess the cat cat has the
Fredy uh glasses on on your
picture totally bad as how you jumped
off
top yeah
right that went so
smooth such a dangerous jump it's an ALT
why did you use an ALT did you get
banned congr wa this has been long time
coming and I'm so hyped that it's
finally here what a perfect way to end
the year thank you for all the good
times awesome songs and incredible
guests Christmas came early forgive me
yeah Merry
Christmas Merry Christmas I love you
guys this is my this is my ho ho ho
present to you
guys I worked so hard in the end because
not for my not even for myself because
like even if I don't have anyone to
watch
it and why why would I be doing it right
why would I I want to perform for no
audience
H
PTSD but you guys were
there and I was honestly really happy I
didn't think so many people would watch
it um I was actually really really
concerned and worried and stressed
before the stream um but you know more
people than I thought would were coming
to the stream actually especially
consider ing how there was quite a bit
of
overlap I mean it was Japan prime time
and I don't you know I'm not I'm not
expecting them all to stop their stream
plans for me um but even like
considering that situation my my um it
was a a pleasant
[Music]
surprise advertising the guests day by
day was a good Strat strategy I think so
too I think there were certainly many
people who came to watch it because they
wanted to see a certain guest you know
and then they
stayed because actually like I was I was
done with collabs uh with Duets and all
that pretty early on right and then
there was there were threee solo songs
and I thought y people going to
leave people going to leave when they
know this oh she's done with all the
guests boring I'm going to go but no it
was still Rising after that
so I was going to
cry because I felt so so
relieved I I I I I I was worried I I
admit it I admited I was
worried
I there was
like it was lowkey intentional to put
Lordi gami right after that because I
thought it must be so
mindblowing and interesting for a lot of
the viewers that they would stay like oh
[\h__\h] she's doing LLY gumy oh my God cusa
cousa
cusa that's
funny going for a time that doesn't work
well for na yeah
I wouldn't mind attempting my next one
to be in na prime time
instead but yeah we'll see how how the
circumstances
are maybe next time na prime
time
maybe I'm not sure if if I do any prime
time I will be really worried if people
come
again wait
2024 if we stream on my actual birthday
is it going to be a weekend let me check
the
calendar oh it will be it's a Saturday
let's go jackpot
jackpot yo yo yo yo yo yo it's a
s
[Music]
it's the 6th of July
right right well then it's a
Saturday let's
[Music]
go
Get Hype my birthday is July 1 or right
before
Oh July 1st that's a nice birthday to
[Music]
have and that's how one Saturday for my
schedule filled already yeah so much
ahead of time you guys Reserve that
Saturday and protect it like it's your
baby okay don't let anything go onto
that day
you are busy on that
day no matter
[Music]
what defend it with your life yeah make
sure to be
free Pinky Promise Pinky
Promise intern it's International
kissing day no it's National Fried
Chicken day
anyway let's finish this up I'm pretty
close to the end pretty close thank you
deeply
alola unknown thanks for the red this is
the best concert ever words can't even
describe how much I love everything
about it I'm definitely re-watching this
at least 100 times if you say it like
this I actually believe you you always
make me extremely proud and happy to be
your fan
thank you love you love
you yeah we watch it 100 times until
until the next one that's good amount of
time every like every week
maybe once a
week I just finished my four free watch
right before the stream started oh
wow damn I hope you don't get sick of it
but it's almost like a
radio yeah even I uh re-watched it a
little
bit some
parts no I feel like it has rewatching
[Music]
potential I watch it with my baby niece
a cute you you showed her you showed her
the spicy Voice song performs with
Winer are you sure that's appropriate
for your baby
niece I will not get sued please by your
niece's
parents thank you unknown enjoy all the
rewatches thank you so much I really
really really am always happy to hear
from you thank you B Jones thanks for
the pinky the concert was amazing
in you worked so hard for this and for
so long now truly you deserve everything
the stage and even more love you and I
can't wait until we can do this again me
I love you too thank you thank you thank
you I'm also
[Music]
excited well don't worry we can Bridge
the time until the next birthday concert
with um the fifth Fest the fifth one
right Fifth Fifth
F I'll be there I'll be
square we'll be
nice slabic fellow thank you for the red
that there you go here's the second one
but this one's like kind of less excited
than the other
one it's okay it's okay it's just an
addition right just an extension
incredible work thank you thank you
sling
[Music]
fellow
hope you had a good time all out of
words yeah I was a bit speechless
too filthy
F who oh filthy
dirty
[Music]
sheesh
okay
dirty how dirty Christina agilera amount
of
dirty because she has a song that's
called Dirty you know get
it yeah
spicy thank you again Alex Alvar thanks
for the pinky sticker yay thank you so
much you're amazing too
J swamp thank you for the r chat
literally just Bop after Bop after Bop b
b the song with Lou and kind that was so
fun takoni is too silly for this world
kabach is so cute when you spawn mly
around I
smiled ah during the dance part of the
Coro yeah awesome performance keep being
amazing thank you Tak yeah we were kind
of silly we were kind of
silly but yeah it's nice me and cie I
feel like
we've uh just reached a level
of being used to being around each other
and just knowing each other where we can
be really comfortable with uh each
other's presence
so took us a while but we're at a good
point yeah so this thank you J SW book
hi home Chris plens thanks for the pinky
fantastic fry coner dential I'm always
vow w wow wow by your dance moves to
hear Fire and Ice
life you always look like fire and lice
to me for a
moment Fire and Ice life so s is
definitely a highlight yeah well timed
well timed it was all timed on purpose
like
this yeah cuz we were working on it and
we were just was taking her time or like
cie was taking her time cuz she was busy
with her other Universal Music releases
and then I was like
Callie um do you want to get this done
now wish so we can perform it at my
live
yeah we wouldn't have to go bald
no that's too
much very different
music yeah yeah set the lights on
fire but yeah it was timed well and now
it's finally there you we need something
something to push us like a deadline we
didn't have that before now we had the
deadline and then it was magically done
faster yeah Fire and Ice Fire and Ice
death life now passion never
give the myth
s the the myth
song okay so the myth song is now
done well yeah sorry for the
delay it is done now but it's now such
an awkward time that it would be weird
to release it now it will be released
soon MV has been done before the song
even was finished with mixing and all
that so it wasn't that be or
[Music]
anything yeah so delays
happened um yeah took a
while uh I forgot when I think soon soon
not this month though because there's a
lot going on you know and it would
probably overlap and then like be
forgotten
quickly I like how your girls mention it
never again yeah cuz I was just waiting
I was waiting waiting waiting waiting
waiting and waiting longer than expected
so not much I could say all there was to
do is
wait but it's coming don't
worry it is on its way maybe there will
even be a myth collab uh together with
the
release
possibly what's coming another myth
original song that we announced in
September in
our um an anniversary stream thingy uh
yeah we thought it would be done sooner
okay we really deeply believed in it
otherwise if we knew it was going to
take so long we wouldn't have announced
it but
yeah now it's kind of embarrassing let's
not talk about
it September's already so long ago what
the
hell ah thank you El St EV thanks for
the pinky a let me read it quietly
[Music]
then although I'm I'm like fine though
thank you thank
you EV down so considerate wow you just
you just feel embarrassed about having
your name mentioned and your sweet sweet
message read out loud for all people to
hear and see right let's be
honest that's the reason why you offer
me to not R
it you are embarrassed
that you actually like
[Music]
me caught in 180
1080p 60
FPS mhm mhm you can't fool me I know I
know
mhm uh the koala Universe thank you
d EO thank you for the red super chat
EO that was such an awesome concert I
haven't been able to watch too many
streams live lately but I'm glad I was
able to catch this one me too thank you
k for all the effort and the others and
the others put for this for all the ah
you and the others put for this thank
you
than yeah I also want to thank all the
others
indeed that were part of my live that
were that took the time to be a guest
especially on this like kind of yeah
tight schedule well hopefully next time
won't be so tight
because 6 months I basically have my
proposal ready already I was like
starting to write it a couple days ago
[Music]
um but I was like waiting on some
information and then now I have to
change some things probably oh but
yeah oh I yes I made a PowerPoint
y' choosing the songs and the guests and
all that
already yeah and then this way it should
hopefully not be as stressful I think so
because uh last time I guess it really
was guy guy let me see I'm
curious
[Music]
yeah
o the discussion kind of
started middle of
September and from there on stuff like
St stage
creation and then instrumental creation
for the
songs cuz we have to make our own
instrumentals commission them
choreography creation this and that
that's 3
months as opposed to normally 6 months
of preparation
time but I mean I put my uh PowerPoint
proposal out there in January
February but it didn't get green lit
until 3 months before it was going to
happen that's the
[Music]
issue as I
said a learning
[Music]
experience so thank you e thank you to
you guys kfb for waiting for me for
tolerating all this like you know
Shenanigans and to the dear dear sweet
guests who are not going to hear this
anyway but still thank you to the guests
in spirit maybe my telepathy can reach
them surely they felt that right it was
a big
hug yeah
than thank you
grunt grunting noises na thank you for
the red super chat it's cut off
there where're this are these are the
last
[Music]
two and let's go kiaha that was amazing
those moves you Dazzle us every time
boss how tough was it learning recm
because she I didn't know somebody could
actually dance it congratulations on all
you have accomplished this year 202 for
is going to bring even more thank you
yeah Rec was probably one of the most
difficult ones um but I really wanted to
nail it because the dance is so iconic
and I was hoping for it to like become
like a little bit of a buzzing topic you
know um I saw a chance in
that so yeah had a lot of fun with it
it's like pretty dramatic and yeah the
the the most iconic uh parts of it were
really difficult um besides that was
like original choreography basically I
asked um for the choreography to have
the OG little dances from the music
video and then add fitting original cor
choreography because there isn't really
much other choreography officially there
I think I think wean she could in her
performance of the song between those
parts that she recreated a little bit
she was just like kind of
vibing just maybe simple Idol steps and
all that so those parts we filled up
with some more proper
Coral yeah
yeah the beam
be be also all the back voices I I
recorded them there's so
many cuz I wanted it to sound like a
crowd and I didn't have anyone else to
record these vocals I mean ideally it
should have been like male voices but
well I am me I don't really have a male
voice
[Music]
um
uh
I'm looking for it
I'm looking for the the screams that I
recorded during
the parts the background suffering
voices is it this
one I found
I tried to do different kinds
of voices
for Fore
fore
uhhuh
[Music]
ah
there's
[Music]
more
I heard myself laugh there at the end do
you hear that
wait oh wait what where did it
go
couldn't take myself seriously anymore
so I I did several of those recordings
and had them overlapped several times
and doubled and more overlapping and
more
overlapping
yeah stuff like that I have to record
you know
so can you imagine how much work all of
this was in three months
man did I sound
constipated h highly unconventional
voice
pack don't don't
don't laying
egg laying egg ASMR mm imagine being the
mixer I was thinking surely they'll
enjoy this one
yeah very very good
stuff oh man um where was
I thank
you you brought some voice behind the
scenes too light good job and Trevor G
thank you for the of the chat the last
one wow damn wa another legendary
birthday life this performance had
everything from your wives to tears to
surprises to laughes this was too good
even a blue bar real at the end yeah
congratulations you killed it getting up
at 5:00 a.m. 3 hours after getting off
work was worth oh PST
gang I'm sorry 3 hours after getting
holy [\h__\h] you worked until like 2: a.m.
oh my
God I'm sorry couldn't couldn't you have
stayed
up or were you that tired man I'm sorry
I'm sorry to make up for it next time
maybe I'll do an
NA Prim Time
I'll consider it okay okay thank you for
suffering through with Trevy and all the
other PST and also a little bit EST
gangs and the CST or whatever whatever
there is in between thank you for
supporting me coming down to YouTube on
that special special day for me that
meant so much to me okay
okay yeah e was fine I guess yeah 800
a.m. is fine fine
yeah wasn't suffering the minute it
started I woke up nicely a I'm happy to
hear that
yeah and hopefully you went straight
back to bed after that cuz you deserve
it after a long hard working
day thank you Trevor G for the CH and
that's
it that's where I will leave it cuz it's
been 5 hours and 45 minutes oh my
God I'm hungry so I go now uh tomorrow
uh we have a stream that is in the
evening do I have anything during the
day no okay so I don't have to sleep
super early my sleep schedule is [\h__\h]
anyway so you
know uh the exit 8 it's not quite a
horror game seems like it's more like a
find the exit game and every once in a
while something's weird if I understand
correctly so it's probably
fine oh wait I might need
um I might need a new steam
card I might need a new steam
card I don't know if I can buy the game
right
now
JMA can you buy me a new steam card
several
ones when you wake you sometime during
the
day please
just get a credit card
already yeah sometime it's it's annoying
cuz they want to authenticate me like
you know who you're talking
to why do I need
authentication I should authenticate
you
yeah oh well thank you guys for watching
I didn't I didn't talk about everything
just yet so I can attang a bit more
another time but I hope you liked the
tangents that I brought to the table
today and thank you for being patient
and listening to my dun assurance and
the DS and the DS and more DS and even
more DS wow so many
ds yeah see you
tomorrow buy card super it's not that
easy because my cards only my my same
accounts they only use they can only
accept Japanese steam card for some
reason it's ridiculous don't even don't
even don't even
[Music]
ask I feel like I can relate to the game
because it's like getting lost
underground in a Japanese train station
so I feel that that's why I want to play
it see you there byebye J byebye love
you
guys thank you so much for all the
donations you generous little
[Music]
shits
thank you for the memberships tool
oh my God thank
[Music]
you