[Music]
So this is here.
[Music] It's
starting. It's probably
starting. I made a
mistake. We
have to line up.
[Music]
[Laughter]
It's okay.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I
don't think so, but the ax looks really strong
. It
's scary. It's fast. It's
strong.
Well, it's low.
[Music]
[Music]  It
's a style where you don't really care about what is communicated in advance. It's
fashion. It's
scary! Everyone
doesn't get along well.
[Laughs]
So
let's go to the yellow team.
[Music] [Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
[  Music]
[Laughter]
Opening remarks from Miko Sakura, chairperson of the sports day executive committee.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much to everyone for all your support and practice.
Thank you very much, you're busy
. I'm very, very happy to be able to gather together again like this. I'm so
happy. I
hope you all enjoy today.
[Music]
Hey,
by the way, you all noticed that I opened the black box in the back.
[Music]
[Applause]
Since we are named 54, I would like to mark the 3 marks for 54 people.
[Music]
But it
is also thanks to the fans and everyone who support us.
Everyone, let's show our fans what we're good at today.
[Applause]
Thank you very much.
[Music]
Next, we've received a message from Mr. Yago of Cover Co., Ltd.
Now, please give us a greeting from Mr. Yago.  Thank you
very much for your hard work, V. Thank you very much for your hard work.
[Music] I
remember feeling relieved.
Mr. Subaru. Thank you
to all the Hololive members who helped out.
Thank you.
To all the listeners, thank you for your continued support.
Thank you.  There is  I
would like to replace this with my greetings as I hope that the organizers and listeners will work together to make the sports day a wonderful event. I
hope everyone does their best.
[Music] -
[Music]
Teacher  It's like how excited I was when I heard his greeting. I wonder if it's
okay. So, now
that
Yago's greeting is over,
let's move on to the oath of the players. Yes, Mr.
Fubuki Shirakami from the red team and Mr.
Amaneko from the white team.
Mr. Subaru Ozora from the yellow team,
please come to the top of the morning assembly. Welcome! This
is my friend A, the announcer. And it's
peaceful in the early spring. Thank you very much.
Please, please. The
three athlete-sensei figures are
on the voice channel and the athlete channel.  Please come.
[Music] It
's today.
A-chan and Nodo-chan
will be in charge of making announcements to everyone in the competition, such as moving Nea's voice channel.
Thank you. Yes, that's it.
Other than that, I'm
standing on the morning assembly table. Okay, let me start.
Sensei, all of us, the players, are the
children.
[Music]
2022,
Lesson
11, 6th
[Laughter]
Ozora is amazing.
How did this happen?
Thank you very much. It
was great.
It was great.
[Music]
Please return to each group's channel for the three sworn players.
Thank you for your apology. You
were a great instructor. It
went smoothly.
That concludes the opening ceremony.
Everyone,
please move to the fencing PvP venue.
[Music] What is
fencing PVP?  It's
going to be a battle where we'll have to switch places. Let's
fight one by one. Shall we go?
[Music]
[Laughter] The
winning side will get 10 points.  It's so
heavy, I wonder if it'll be bad if I restart it.I wonder what
the point of this game is,
what is this game?I wonder what kind of game this game is, and
what I can do to win.
[Music]
[Music] It's
hard to turn it up or down.
[Music] It's a
good idea to lower the volume of the user on the top voice channel here.  Even
if I turn it all the way down, you still
listen to me.
[Music]
The door is on the other side, and the time signal is Subaru-
chan. I
said, ``Maybe it's okay for me to be your senior.''
[Music] Ca
n't you just get the flow? I'll
get the flow.  I think I have the confidence that I will definitely enter the game and not lose.The
scenery of the incision.The
direction of the incision.Mugi
of barley juice,
Subaru the middle manager, and the general manager.
Mr. Koyama from Mr. Koyama: You're a
serious manager.
Don't say your name suits you. Okay, then let's do our best.
[Music]
The god of rising is Louisy, huh
? How did I rise in the beginning of the year? Eh, I'm winning this year.  Is that so?
Let's make her the goddess of victory.
[Laughs]
By the way,
there are some
tips for fencing PvP.  I
think it's strong, but ah,
surprisingly, the jump cut might
not be that strong. It's not strong, right? Yeah,
I get it. That's
what it was like. There
's no strategy.
[Laughs]
Mel-chan, I guess you
ran out of morning drama juice. What,
vampire?  So, this is the
first time I've seen it, and
Mel-chan has it. She's
going to cause more miracles in the second half, so stop it. Good
luck in the first half as well.
Well, we're planning to do our best in the first half,
but we're a team, so there's also the possibility that Nedaruma-san fell down.Everyone was too good to be
true, so I asked for help, but thank you
[Music] It's
Subaru, but I'm starting to worry.It
's okay.  Even if it looks like this, please do it.
There's a boring rosette of middle managers,
but today I'm going to be a bit of a super person. I see
.
Well, I'm going to do a little bit today,
even though it's on a water boat.
[Music] I
practiced. I
woke up an hour ago and did it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
[Laughs]
What time are we doing now? Now that's that first battle.  It's
time for that interview before it starts.
Ah, the
interview is going to go up.
OK,
there's an interview.
No, it's not the game yet.
VS
Oh, I'd
like to make it 50%. It's about to
start. It's about to
start.  I'm
still watching the entry and it's making me nervous. It's going to get
worse
soon. I want it to be easier.
[Music]
Right?
[Music] If you
aim for the neck, it'll only take a moment.
People are starting to realize that the repeated jumps that hit the base of the neck aren't that strong. [Music]  [
Music] I
guess it's because I have a strong passion.
Fashion has definitely been around since 4 years ago.
Fashion.
Let's do it while shouting.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Laughter] When I
rewrite the guitar, it's
hot rock. Hot,
hot rock.
[Music]
[Laughter] That's a
summary.
Players, please come as you please.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Well, it seems like they only specialize in beer. They
have barley juice, so there's
not enough alcohol for the
sports day.  But if you don't have enough alcohol, you're in trouble.
[Music] I'm really
worried.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
[Music]
[Laughter]
It's a feeling
[Music]
Mental-Physical Passion Watanabe
Isn't it better to attack? That's right. I'm
going to cross the red line a little bit.
[Music]
Thank you, congratulations,
that's it.
Noel-san, Iroha-san, both knees Move to the channel.
Let's see.
Next symmetry.
[Music]
That
's it.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Who are you
? What do you look like
? Well, that's
fine. If it makes you laugh, then it's fine.
If it makes you laugh, let's lick it.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Right now, the right side isn't winning. It's a
chore. I'm
going to get to the right side as soon as possible. The
right side. [Laughs] There might be a jinx for the right side.
It's the next battle.Or
yellow, red vs. yellow
guy
Which one is it?
Okay, okay, okay, OK
[Music]
Google
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
No, I lost to Serious Mentality. It's white. That's
right. You're strong. If you can
defeat me, you'll be strong. Thank you. Thank
you.
But are you okay? Thank
you. I think I'm
feeling a little uneasy now that I've won everything.
[Music]
[Music]  ]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Good luck, Aki-chan is doing something right now
-
[Music]
[Applause]
Mental Physical Punsion What?
Death Voice Group
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] I'm feeling a lot
better now.
Good thing.
Oh my god,
next big sky Subaru
is depressed
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music]
[Applause] It's okay, it's
okay, it's okay
Shoes  Lick it, it's okay. It's okay.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
Please do your best.
[Music] It's
not a defeat. This is normal, so I made the decision earlier.
Tajan, that's it, that's normal.
After being gentle, he said he would really lick you.
[Laughs]
Please, that's fine.  It's a
metal physical version.
[Laughs]
[Music] It's
like practicing. Ah,
it's true.
Towa-sama must have gotten a lot stronger with practice since then. I'm
a little freaked out.  I do
n't think so. It's not like that. You
may be thinking about various things, but the leader is
just going to have a little fun just like practicing.
[Music]
Please let me enter the door until the end.  Please stand in front of me. Ah,
thank you. Thank you. Yes, thank you. The
red vs. yellow line is here. Yes, I
bought a lot of red just now, so why not now? It's
too strong.
[Applause]
[Music]
Thank you very much. I'm so
frustrated.
A while ago, I
finished with Red, and I'm
glad it was fashion.In Passion Gate,
Towa-san didn't speak a single word of Japanese.
[Laughs]
Hey, yes
[Music]
[Laughs]
[Music]  Is
n't it okay to just scream and buy it?I don't care if it's better for both of us to fight.On the
contrary, why
don't you do it?Yes, on the contrary, I can't do it tomorrow,
sorry.I'm sorry, please excuse me.Yes.
[
Music] That's serious. [Music]
[Laughter]
If we can just barely understand each other, that's
right.  I'm crazy because I said that.
Now they say I can't show you that stream.
No, it's no good if you criticize this big senior. I'll
show it to you. It's going to go round and round.
You
saved me on YouTube.
[Music]
This is the
third and final episode
of Nee-no.What do you think of all of us who fight against garbage?
No, after all, Neto-wa-san,
please say
what you always say. We'll fight at the volume. There's something different about what you're saying.
Excuse me,
please say what you always say.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter] I
want the whole school to go.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter] Do your
best. I'm bored.
[Applause]
[Music]
A scene where you get a word like that.  You're nervous, aren't you?
[Laughter]
I see. I'm tired of it. It
's evil.
Tying it to a gorilla's hand is like that.
Game
Gorilla. Hey, it's pretty
tough. Gorilla. It's
too small. Gorilla, help the gorilla too.
Gorilla
[  [Music]
Oh,
no. Good
luck,
good luck!
[Applause]
[Music]
This
might have been a very high-level gorilla.
Well,
maybe it was a gorilla. It's
saying something. It's
licking your ass. It's licking your ass. I
'm going to lick it.
[Laughs]
[Music]
Good luck, good
luck, good luck, good luck. It's
deep. It's
frustrating. It
was the last minute. Yeah,
just one more shot.  Hey, I
didn't sleep. I
didn't fall into a coma at all. Maybe the sword got in the way a little.
Hey
[Laughter]
[Music]
As expected, as expected,
I became the epitome of fashion before I knew it.The only thing left to do is to have a mental passion
and
become fashionable myself.I'll
go with the loudness, okay,
Senpai
[laughter]
[music]
That's right,
in the final battle.  No,
I'm in it for a bit, but it's fine.
This is
what's going on, what's going on, what's going on.
Kakogawa, where are you going?
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Let's
fight
[Laughter]
Hey
[Music]
This is the final battle.
Everyone, please do your best. Here we go.
[Music]
[Applause] There's
so little substance in the conversation, it's scary.
Even the bullies aren't saying anything important.  So,
yeah, it's
really pretty good, no, it's true.
[Laughs] You've
got to be responsible for what you say. That's
stabbing you.
Now, it seems like you thought it was a punishment. Go ahead.
[Music] It
's no better than red.
[Music]
The bonus is okay, but everyone seems to be able to see it. Yes
[Applause]
Yay
[Music] Let's
move.
Please. I'm
suddenly nervous. It's okay, it's okay. It
's the voice channel.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Even if I ask.  Okay, I'll
take a look at you.
[Music]
Other than that, you know, Aki-senpai is also in this audience seat, and I'd like you to
sit here in the yellow section. I wonder
what Fubuki Shirakami of the Red Team should do
.
[Music]
Please.  Masu
Divided into those in charge of operation and those in charge of sabotage, the
players can use fireworks and darkness attacks to
disrupt the opposing team.It
is a competition where 2nd place in the top ten earns 20 points and 3rd place receives 10 points.
Yes, in this competition, everyone seems to be practicing the controls to a certain degree,
so being
able to do the right and wrong movements is
very
important.
[Music]
So it was skipping.  I
thought something about each team earlier. They
said that if Ramy lost when they played against the white team, it would be scary if they changed to the white team.
[Music] They
got angry, right?
[Applause]
[Music] That's
nice.
[Music]
Who is the actant? Is
n't
it a devil and a talisman?
[Music]
[Laughter]
That's amazing. I'm tapping into my inner core. I don't care. I'm serious. I have no intention of giving up on this.
No, I've been practicing a lot.These two
and all of them are trying not to fall out of this place.I
wonder if
that's
right.But it's
Mom's.Wow, I want you to buy this.Ayame is spinning around in the head and
is hitting me.
[Music] I'm
sure you'll become a legend. I'll
do whatever it takes to win.
[Music] That's what I'm
aiming for.
Did you do something? It
's a competition where you have to do two laps.
[Music]
Yes, do
your best, Rui Ayame, do your best,
let's go!
[Music]
Ah, you
're stuck, good, good, good,
everyone in the middle, on the
left of what's decided, it's
okay, it's okay, you
're panicking, do your
best,
do your best, it's okay, mental and physical
Passion in the second half  I
want to do my
best. I wonder if the darkness has been activated. It's true. [Music] It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's going to be good.
Passion Passion Physical
Version What's this? No, no, I
can't do my best.
Do my best. It's
faster than before.
[Music]
Do your best, do your best.
Cheers
[Music]
Winning run. This
is the mental-physical winning run.
Alright, OK. I do
n't want to hear what happened at first. That's right. At
first, well,
on the contrary.  I wonder if he
did it because he said he had done something.
[Music]
Apparently there was a scuffle outside the venue.  Are you
okay? What happened? What on earth is
going on down here? I don't know anything. I
can see a lot of names below, but it's
definitely this one.
Lol lol
Now that's it. I'm
standing on that pedestal of awards. I see. It's
kind of weird.  chan is
listening to me New Year is standing there I'm scared of my senior I'm scared of my senior I'm scared of my senior Hey, are you okay? Are you okay? This is a polka. Are you digging it? That's what I was thinking at all, but that guy [music] sounded like he just said it.
But I don't know.
Shiro seems to be dark, so now I'm
sure.
[Music] I
need to lick Rui-chan's ass quickly.
Pull it out.
That's the kind of relationship Subaru-chan has.
Sorry, I shouldn't have said this on the stream.
Well, you promised not to say it on the stream.
You've got a trident and it's too chaotic. Hey,
what are you doing? It's
dangerous. Put it away.
Kid. You're
tired. Everyone has gone back. Are you going back? I'm
back.  I wonder
where the electric wire should go. Should I
go back to the middle? I
should go back. I wonder if the program will be on. That's right.
[Music]
It's already been two hours. It's
early. Let's get on the yellow bus.
Look at my senior's legs. I'm the
senior carpenter on the bus.  Look, their legs are the same color. It's true.
[Music]
Okay.
[Laughs] You
said that you were getting too carried away, and I
'm curious. On the other hand, it makes me wonder
if the interference came from me. It
's so fashionable.  It's an
empty result. Well, that's the case
. Well, that's true. There are some good points,
too.
Well, if you're on the contestant's channel, please
go back to the respective team's channel, the Mois channel.
Thank you
[Music]
That kind of thing happens when there are people around.
[Music] It
's about time. Well, I have some time left,
so I'm going to go to Daruma-san.  The
most important thing about the team right now is that
before that, there
's the friendship.It
's stored in the morning assembly table, so
if you're looking for a specific person, here's a little interview with the Red Team.Miko Sakura Interview with the Red Team
[Music]
[Music]  ]
That's right, Daruma-san is next.
[Music]
[Music] It's
embarrassing. No
one noticed, seriously.
It's MPP.
[Music]
Let's do our best. [Music] [Music] [Music]
music]
So, we are currently in 2nd place. How did you feel about it?
In the first half, we showed the strength we could, even if it was reluctant, so
I hope that this strength will be carried over to the second half of the team, and we will all work together to aim for the championship.  I'll
do my best.
[Applause] It's
my slogan, so please
stop.
That's why I say yes. Please do your best in the second half.
[Music] Well
then, it's
about time. I see, the
members are still getting ready.  It looks like we do
n't have everything, so I'd like to ask you to wait a little bit longer,
and I'd
like to talk a little bit about us and connect with you. I
wonder how you've been looking so far, Miko.
[Music]
Well, maybe now.
Next,
there's that entrance.
[Music]
So it's been a long time since then. It looks like it's
going to end very quickly. That doesn't mean the
plumbing is going
smoothly.
[Music]
There are definitely people who aren't nervous and make mistakes due to mental breakdown.  It's
true that you have to calmly
cover it up with your mental and physical passion.You're
shaking, you
're sweating strangely.You're
nervous,
but it's good to have some direction.Beautiful people
understand this and that.No,
seriously, your voice  It seems that human beings have the detergent ability when they let it out,
so let's just say it out loud, ``Yes,'' my
voice says every time.Oh, what's that?That's the
connection.Why
does it feel like it's finally here?
[Music]It's
fashion, isn't it?  The
ID members from the house are coming. Good luck!
[Music]
[Applause]
Why,
Mel-chan, hello-hello
[Music]
[Applause] You look
really good in pompoms. You're definitely
cute, you're cute.
Yes, I
guess we'll start with Olly.
Where do you start from,
selfie?
[Music] Yes.
So what's next?
[Laughs] I
hope you're
strong enough to risk your life. It's a bit
different. And the third one is Kaela.
Hello.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
I have a lot of things.
First of all, it's
amazing. - The hardships are amazing. So, I'm
going to ask these three to do their best. And the
white group will be
Bei-chan
[  [Laughter]
[Music]
Sorry everyone, this is a bit difficult
. It's
hard to adjust the doll. It
's Bales. I'm
Iris. Today, I
'm going to win.
Yay,
thank you very much.  Go,
go, go,
please. I
'm looking forward to it. That's why I would like to introduce the yellow team.
It's Friday
[Music] I've
been practicing the relay with Muna-chan.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
Thank you very much for coming. Thank you very
much. Yes, and next,
Amelia Ame-chan.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
So, I would
like these nine members of en and ID to join us as guests, and then the second half of the team will also join us and we will move to the venue for Daruma-san ga Fallen.
Yes,
please.
Now for the
second half.
Since we're starting the team broadcast, we're
moving around, and
since the competition is going to start a little later, I
think we should take it easy.We're also
taking a break in between.Okay,
so Daruma-san fell down.  While heading to the venue
Miko-chan, is it
okay if I ask the members of the second half of the team to listen to the story?
Yes, I understand.Then I'll call the team below Subaru.Thank
you, please.I'm thinking
of making an entry.As for that, please click
that
button.  That's right, because all you have to do is press the button.
Yes, I
destroyed the button yesterday, so
I'd like to go into survival mode.
[Music]
[Music] The
yellow color in the first half has been decided as the slogan.
No.
[Music]  I don't
care if it's a handover or a handover, it's mental and physical passion, so MPT is fpp, mental fashion, fashion, that's not the case. [Music] Fashion [Applause] [Music] Because I'm here [Music] I have a feeling they'll translate it for me.
Please,
White.  1ml
[Laughs] You're so
eager to get into position. Wait a minute. It's
dangerous. What's the point?
[Music] I wonder [Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh, that thing makes you slow so you don't step on anything.
[Laughter]
[Music] The
countdown to the start will begin, so if you
eat then you'll be on time.
[Music] [Music
]
Oh, the
second half of the program is being streamed, so please wait.
Because
[Music] I
guess it's better to go there.
Choco-sensei.  Help Mu on the left I'm
sorry I hit you
I'm sorry Entry
Thank you very much
[Applause]
Yellow is also ready
Hey ok
Ladies
[Music]
[Applause]
Hmm
NP
Nice nice.  It
's not over. It's
not the same language. I guess I
'm here for the retirement interview.
Oh, I see. I'm
sorry about that fall. That must have been it.
Someone attacked me and got in. [
Laughter]
[Music]
Thank you.
[Applause]
[Music]
We
won.
[Laughter]
Let's do our best.
So Nedaruma-san fell down. The shoes were pretty
big, so everyone.
It's like it's time to start competing.
[Music]
So,
after the introduction of the competition, we will start.
Yes, this is Daruma-san, but this is a
competition for everyone. If
you head towards the goal when the sign says ``Yes, Daruma-san''
and move when the corona sign appears, you will die instantly.
Yes, so the competition is for Daruma-san to
run as close to the goal as possible by 321,
but it is
also important to act carefully so as not to die
.
First of all, everyone will participate in a preliminary round, and after that preliminary round, the
top 15
will be selected for the finals.  It
was high, but this year, it's
quite severe because the system makes it really pitchy.
[Music]
Well, yeah, just to everyone,
before we start the competition, I'd
like to say a few words: It's about to start.  is
However, can I ask Ei-chan from that announcement?
Ah,
yes, it's just starting. Is it okay if I just say a few words? It's
about to start, so can I just ask?
Okay,
everyone,
get ready.
[Applause]
[Music] I
'm sure you're canceling your entry or making an entry, but
Fubuki says she'd like to have a chat when you start, so I see.
Everyone's out of golden apples. They
're probably eating them.  It
's real.
Check it again.
[Music]
[Applause] Are you
ready?
[Music]
I'd like to start
[Applause]
[Music]
Daruma-
san, Daruma-san
[Applause] I've
lost faith in something.
[Music] I'm dying. [Music]
Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
Yes and 12
Um
Sakamoto Sakamoto 11th place Da Ando
Ranking
Toner
Nii I like it
[Music]
[Applause]
Well, Amane Kanata-san, who came in first place, I would like to do it. It's pretty much here, here, here,
here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, and here. So, I
did it. I practiced a lot.
Today, I got up really early in the morning and
practiced.  So I
practiced,
but somehow I got 1st place,
but I
heard someone say, ``Well, there's no point in qualifying.'
'  Do I
get points even if I'm in the bottom?
Finals
[Music] Please do it. There
's meat in it, so thank you
. Hello,
everyone. That's it.
[Music]
[Applause] What is it?
No, it's really a shame. No, it's me, really. What do you
mean, left and right?  I didn't watch it,
and I thought I was number 1, but it was definitely number 2. I
won't
forgive you
. I'll take the number 1 spot next time.
That's right, this competition is about how you can stick to your own pace without being distracted by other things,
right?
[Music]
That's right, I
'm going to run my own way at my own pace.
[Music]
Next,
yes, me.  3rd place, did you say you saw the barber
?
[Laughter]
[Music]
Next, I'll defeat Chuto.
After that, it's a battle between an angel and a human, and it's this bastard. Well then, still, I
see.
Really, really barbaric people.  I
might get disqualified, so let's play this game. I
said yes. Thank you very much. I'll
be waiting for a moment.
So, all the countries in 4th to 15th place are also contestants.
Please move to the channel already.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Please, please, please,
thank you very much.
[Music] Let's
start
[Music]
[Applause]
[  music]
[Music]
Well then, I'm going to announce the rankings.
Yes, please, yes.
13th place is a lie. That's fine.
[Music] I
was in a hurry.  But it was okay for now. It's
important to do something dangerous.
[Music] -
[Music]
And there were 5 points over there.
[Music] I
pressed the wrong button at first. I'll do my best.
Yes, you did a great job. Thank you very much.
Thank
you very much. 1
[Music] I was
going to take first place, but yesterday you
gave me an excuse.
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm the winner.
Everyone's dialect
[Music] It's
amazing that you're being bullied.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I
like that the button came out right. That's
great. Just a little white here.  I'm
happy to be able to catch up with this.
[Music] -
[
Laughter] [Applause]
[Music]
Just the settings
If you set the graphics in the settings to priority processing, the
lag will be a little less.  That might be the case for me too,
so
thank you for giving priority to graphics processing in the video settings.
[Music] I'm
trying harder to lower it, but
[Music]
[Music] The
camera arc in the first half of the yellow group.  I was
entrusted with it,
but I wonder if I did it properly.It was really fun.I think I got points with that full
max.Daruma-san got
30 points like that.He won
two consecutive times in fencing, both times.
Since we won, I
think I was able to contribute to the team.With this contribution,
for example, everyone on the team felt a little bit like that.Even if we
didn't win, we'll say this again.
I'd be happy if the team could earn points for their contribution, and I'd be
happy if that person's compassion grew.It
's team gear, so I said yes, and everyone,
Pekoro, cheering for the yellow team in the second half.  It
will be in the slot
for Pecola-chan, so I
hope you can go there and watch it on that streaming site and support me.You can
also watch the first half of the show until the closing ceremony,
so you can watch it there.  If you could take a look at Moa
Thank you for today.
See you later. Bye
Bye
[Music] -
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]