[Music]
do
oh
[Music]
me
oh yeah
[Music]
okay papa
are you there papa
[Music]
i love you papa
love you
ah look at this beautiful artwork
look at it look at it
my papa made this for me
it's me kiara
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
look at it
you
it's so beautiful
i i retweeted it i retweeted it on
uh twitter so if you didn't
retweet it and like it do it now
so beautiful i wanna put it i wanna
leave it
on on the stream today
where do i put this just hide the
comments
can i put it here
it takes a bit space away from you guys
but
i want to showcase it
i knew i knew that he was drawing
something for
a little while
but he finished it today
and when i saw it i was like
looks so amazing
it looks so amazing and he told me those
flowers
they're like um phoenix flowers like
they actually exist
and they're called something like
phoenix flowers i never heard of those
flowers before
[Music]
yeah i gotta check out the flower store
if they have
that flower
aren't they definitely it
seems like almost the same thing
it's so pretty uh
look at it me they all
it's so pretty
the lightning that lighting the lighting
is so pretty
it's so so holy
like the way the sun shines on me
but very softly very softly and kindly
beautiful beautiful just beautiful
i have the best papa in the world
what's your favorite italian game oh my
favorite
oh my favorite
i played a bunch of them but i i kind of
like them
but maybe not the same amount let me see
the one
which one was the one i played the most
recently
uh
i think ah yeah
i think i liked uh
yeah i think yeah probably sophie sofino
attorney
because i just really like plata
i love her design yeah
um i'm still waiting for a
permission to stream atelier riza
but once i get it what echo is still
there
echoes oh i thought i turned it up
okay well now it's gone
i turned it on for the i love you papa
wow what was i gonna say i am
still waiting for a little blood
for what what am i waiting for
permission permission waiting for
permission
waiting for permission to play at the
horizon so that we can also play at the
riser i tell you rise up too
i'll tell your games are pretty chill so
uh it's maybe not the most exciting game
to play
i just really appreciate the character
designs
it i look like an arc knights operator
are you sure about that
since i love arc nights i'm happy to
hear that
but i personally did not think
that way
i i never thought that it
but i'm happy about the that opinion
kento today
since that drawing is next to me i'm uh
carrying the sword and the
shield usually i don't have it on my
chatting and gaming streams because i
just feel like uh
it's a bit weird to always be
uh in my full attire
i've always felt like the chicken is
more fitting
don't you think your life today is the
best thank you
i always feel like sometimes i'm like
wait am i really not 3d
is this really shooting it seems like 3d
yeah fighting mode always ready for
battle
they have the trails games what i don't
know any trails games
while the
so what are we gonna do today we're
gonna have some small talk
i was uh going to uh
rest today but then i felt like oh i
don't mind doing some super chat reading
because i
uh for the collab since it was like a
a fixed time slot and after that i went
uh for a long long long long long long
nap
i uh i couldn't read the super chat but
i still feel like i need to read the
super chat
so that's why today even though i wanted
to take the day off i'm reading the
super chat
it's no problem don't worry um it's just
reading so really no it's true
but um i'm definitely gonna take
first day off that's for sure
yeah seven hour nap so that's why i felt
like actually maybe i don't need to rest
on monday because i
uh the seven hour nap and then later i
slept again so
i already feel kind of rested but it's
not only about feeling rested of course
we all need some um mental break
every now and then uh even though i
wanna like you know really power through
and stream every day but it's probably
not good for
for my mentality i need some time to
just
shut off the brain and chill you know
[Music]
so if you hang out with me today i'd be
really glad but we're only really only
doing super chat reading and some small
talk in between so
uh it's okay if you don't want to watch
i i guess it's kind of boring
to just listen to super chat's name
that gets your name back is your name
thank you the whole time
i get it i get it oh
love your feather earrings so i want to
clear it up again
these are not earrings
they come they grow from behind my ears
some people have been unclear about it
so i would like to
officially state it again and they if
you look closely they come out of my
ears but
my right ear maybe you see it but the
sword is in the way right now
maybe you say but my right ear has no uh
nothing there
but my left ear has a small blue uh ear
not an earring earpiece piercing so
earrings
again
this ear doesn't have it but this ear
does
yeah those details but that
the i don't need a feather earrings i'm
i'm a phoenix of course i have some
feathers and they're natural
those are feathers yeah phoenix feathers
very fancy huh oh shall
yeah because i saw some fan art where
they uh
drew the the feathers as earrings it's
fine but
i'm just like oh i gotta make it clearer
those are not earrings
they come from behind my ears so
anyone who plans to make some fan art
from now on i would recommend you
to draw them not as earrings but uh
as actual feathers yep
yep that's how it is
thanks for the lord you are welcome
so like permanently attached earrings
nose
it's part of my hair basically
take notes yeah take notes do you have
feathers in your nose
too
no no
all right so uh
what else what
tomorrow and there will be
a collab with ina on my channel
which will actually be arc nights
[Music]
we're not gonna actually play the game
but we'll
it will be uh very arc nights related
i hope that i know this probably a lot
of people don't play agnes so it might
be a
kind of weird for those people
but i see a lot of people reacting very
excited so i guess there's a lot of
people who play arc nets here as well
now we're not gonna play susie we're not
gonna play the actual game
uh but i
i do play the game but we're not gonna
do it on stream
we're gonna do something else i hope you
will watch it
i forgot what time i chose but
i think ina wrote it on her schedule on
twitter
no no we will not be drawing either
also i'll probably also stream
uh solo tomorrow probably mario
super mario we're gonna do a
continuation
of ah why did i close that window god
damn it
we're gonna continue with them what was
it super mario 64.
yay more frustration
more crying
i must say i'm not
not so excited but you guys seem to be
so
all good you guys seem to have enjoyed
my suffering
no i don't have a pro controller does it
really make such a big difference
because i had huge issues with uh the
the the controls and all that
huge issues
pro control is a lot better really not
really
really much better makes everything
you sure even in a game like um super
mario
64 will make me less movie smaller
even in such a game because originally i
know the game originally already had
like a really iffy camera
and stuff oh my god so many donations
thank you guys i'll
be reading them all all of uh the
collaboration donations and the ones
from today
in a second maybe change the camera
settings there's such a thing you can
change it
if you like classic control oh you can
change button mapping
in the switch panel
no pro con is way better than joycon
does it i never even saw it before what
does it even look like
switch pro controller
oh it looks like a like a traditional
controller
how much how much oh it's not so
expensive
maybe i'll buy one
maybe i should buy one yeah
it's not so expensive but i'm also
the thing is um i will uh
buy a new microphone yes finally
it should come on friday
and it's a very expensive one
yay yay
um i was gonna wait for uh
that kelly said she'll give me another
one because the one i currently have
is from her her old one but she's gonna
buy a new one again
and so she said she'll give me the one
she currently uses but
uh i think um i should just get my own
one
at this point i don't want to um
put any trouble on anyone anymore so i'm
gonna buy my
own new microphone i originally already
had a microphone but i just felt like it
wasn't good enough that's why cali
eventually gave me her old one blah blah
blah
and now i don't know i just kind of
messed up the settings it's supposed to
be better i already told you guys
it's supposed to be better than this but
yeah and the new one i'm buying
is i think supposedly the same one that
gouda uses
so my voice should be very crispy
after that i think it's it will
it's uh cali told me it's probably the
same one as gura
quite expensive crispy a crispy
crispy chiata crispy
no no no not crispy chicken no no no no
no no no
crispy crispy voice crispy voice no
crispy chicken
and with that microphone i'll start uh
the thing that i mentioned which is
german i said asmr
but it's not gonna be so much uh a real
asmr
i'm planning like um
german uh
old traditional scary
children fairytale reading
so i will not be like whispering the
whole time because
i cannot stand it
i just personally and don't enjoy
asmr i don't enjoy it
so a little bit just like you know uh as
in the video
from my debut the storytelling it will
be like that
it will be like a soft kind of
reading i'll be reading you a story in
german
but i'll put subtitles too so that's
what i'm planning right now
you may
no stream no stream it'll be videos
because i gotta subtitle it and stuff
you
[Music]
german fairy tales are well you guys
probably know but german fairy tales are
kind of known
for being
intense a bit uh
creepy yeah cruel dark yeah
yeah yeah i think the first one i'll be
reading
so good emo good emo yeah cream screams
they are apparently they don't really
have copyright
so it should be fine that i read those
yeah uh i'll be reading those i think
the first one i want to do is hansel on
twitter
but they have so many um a lot of them
are the base of am i allowed to say
disney a lot of them are the base
of many movies from
that company
but that company usually uh makes it
a lot prettier than it actually is
thanks for the mic money don't worry
i'll use my
i have some savings from a while ago
so i'll be using my savings somewhere
you don't need to pay for my microphone
oh yeah i don't know why are german
fairy tales so scary it's not only fairy
tales
uh i mentioned this in the collab stream
and a few people noticed and put it on
reddit
you know when we were doing the clapping
thing the clap clap something something
clap clap something something
and um
who was before me was it amelia i think
amelia said scissors
and then i was the next one and i said
german
scary children books and i think at the
moment
many people did not understand why i
said that
but if you look up
you'll probably have no idea how to
write that but there's a
german children's book called
struvelpeta
and scissors
have a big role in there and when i was
a child
i i did read that children's book
and i will never forget it i'll never
forget it
it was quite spooky it was basically
about um there's like there's like these
small stories
and there's a story where a boy i think
keeps sucking his fingers
and in order to make him get rid of that
habit i i can barely remember it
but some big dude
with huge scissors cuts off
his fingers and in his children's book i
think you can even see the blood
and how that how the blood is dripping
from the fingers
and that is a german children's book
and there's much more of that i don't
know
what is wrong with us
i didn't even think much of it when i
was a child
um
we should show her that's your friend's
book then she will not be saying you be
you be anymore
no more you be you be no more ubi
that big scissor guy will show up and
now there will be no more uv
yeah if you want to look it up actually
let me
if you want to look it up
look this up or maybe don't
if you want to get traumatized or
have a good story for your own children
i don't recommend it
corner
what was it one w i think it was like
for some reason
wait let me open it up yeah it's double
w
[Music]
peter
there's a japanese version oh
dear why did they why is there japanese
version
don't traumatize those japanese children
oh my god this should never leave the
german speaking
countries
no no no one outside of the
german-speaking countries
should ever experience something like
that
i have experienced it and this is who i
am now
ah yeah it's originally from
germany yeah oh wow that's enough of
that
that's enough of that
did you see it did you google it guys
i think there's like a bunch of short
stories in there and one is the one with
the scissors but it's really bad
it's really bad it's really bad
what what was that what what what were
we talking about anyway
why did i get to the story
ah because of the german fairy tales and
the asmr and that because that was
because of the
microphone and the microphone was
because of whatever reason i don't know
well now you know the more you know
so i hope you'll enjoy my future plans
micro new microphone on friday oh maybe
to celebrate the new microphone we
should do a karaoke stream again on on
friday
yay you guys all enjoyed the karaoke
stream from before so much i was so
happy i didn't think you'll
enjoy it so much but i think it will be
much better with a better microphone
yay because i listened to it too and i
was like ah
that's kind of a waste i mean i'm not
the
not such a super good singer but
it would sound better with a better
microphone indeed
english karaoke ah the thing is like we
kind of have a list of
songs that we can sing uh
songs that we have like
kind of the permission i guess to sing
and that's mostly japanese songs and for
english it's a bit more difficult
that's why oh and also i just prefer to
sing japanese songs
because um
i feel like uh it's easier for me to
sing japanese songs
fly away to the moon oh yeah i think i
think i can sing that one
i like that song i i do like that song
but yeah we you know we are
very careful when it comes to these
things
so yeah please bear with me i hope it's
okay
it will mostly be japanese songs in the
future as well
it's just uh i prefer singing those
songs
and it's easier when it comes to
copywriting stuff german lullaby
german song
i personally can't even think
of so many good german songs
[Music]
but what we could do possibly
i was thinking of translating some
famous japanese songs anime songs or
whatever
to german
and then sing it for you that we can do
are there so many german speaking people
in my chat or
why do you all demand it
it seems like i do have a lot of german
speaking
audience apparently
uh
because it sounds fun and no i'm not
going to sing
rammstein no
no no no
no
no god damn it
can you even imagine me singing
rammstein no
so it's not supposed to be what's up
no no no all right should we get started
away from
the the super chat
by the way i'm gonna warn you guys uh
this time slot that i'm streaming in
right now
sometimes my internet
just says bye
because it's a busy time for my internet
that's why i usually never streamed in
this time slot
but today i felt like i had no choice
sometimes it just says bye we'll see
what happens right now it seems fine
but don't be surprised if it cuts off at
some point
um
i'm starting with uh yesterday
yesterday's collab and then we'll move
on to today and then
some at some point i'll cut it off and
you will not
read anymore because
one thing i was told people
told me i don't need to read the super
chats but i want to
because i feel like i have to thank you
i have to there's no way that i will not
thank you
uh if it's like
i to me it's not an option it's not an
option
and especially actually for a certain
super chat like if someone
spends a hundred dollars for a red super
chat
i don't want to be like name thank you
next one
i wish i could like actually spend more
time thanking each and every one of you
because like that's
insane i can't just brush it off like
that i wish i could spend more time but
the least i can do is just read all of
you i hope it's okay
first one
you all worked so hard to get here
thanks for all the smiles and loves with
every stream to keep on doing your best
thank you
sorry number six number six with
japanese whole live fans and oversee
raw whole life and things so same we
only think of one thing
it's our favorite thing in the number
one we'll have japan hold up at the end
right yes i think i got the gist
[Music]
rule six where was rule six they're
talking about rule six what was rule six
sorry rip rule six too excited
is it about not chatting
i don't even i don't even remember the
rose
does anyone know don't talk in cha ah
yeah i saw that um
in the collab stream a lot of things
were going on in the chat
and once i i was sleeping for most of it
but
when i woke up i saw people were
spamming viva la chiara
what happened there does that did that
have any specific
origin why was everyone spamming viva la
chiara
i saw it but i don't get it why was
there a reason
doesn't doesn't it mean long live chiara
well why did that why did that happen
simple
here we go again what happened
oh well jeremy thank you jeremy
thank you general piccolin
thank you general why is everyone
donating twice
general
that is before the stream actually
started and they're like chatting over
super chat
emma caulfield thank you
oh my god they tried i think they tried
to one-up themselves they started with
one u.s dollar or canada dollar then 10
and 20 then 50 then 50 then 75 and 100
what are you guys doing why do you guys
do it
and they're like is this a sim
competition
save your sims for later man forever our
empress
phoenix kiala glory glory to the kfp
galaxy swirl thank you he eats
you're always able to make us laugh keep
optical org
and the kfp employees will always
support you yay thank you
glory to tj
you all are taking this a bit too
serious
oh yeah i overlapped so much with becca
senpai she's starting in 20 minutes god
damn it
now i don't do it on purpose
i wish i i wish the day had
more like more time
and yeah i kind of have um i think i
have a similar
sleep schedule as peculiar senpai that's
why we often stream at the same time
um
emma caulfield thank you thank you so
much
lego oh oh oh hello i just um
oh no don't worry i don't i'm i'm
actually not gonna read this because i
don't want to stir it up anymore but i
did see your message
and it's all good it's all good don't
worry about it
i just i'm not gonna read it because i
don't want it to start all over again
but thank you jeremy thank you
thank you so much
all who can send super chat we love you
it's really appreciated twitching
he eats it thank you so much wow
everyone is so generous what the hell
djf96797 thank you
thank you wow what the hell
again oh my god
you all are too generous stop
stop being so generous please stop
i feel bad and this was even before the
stream even started there were so many
red super chats
it's too much mario c2
thank you another kfb and toy donation
thank you
dj djf96797 oh my god
are you okay
okay
by the way can we get some popcorn
phoenix on the menu and out of curiosity
what language do phoenix think in
i think normal phoenixes think only in
bird language
but me i speak many languages so
i think in all of them
and popcorn phoenix
we are not selling phoenix meat
so no but if you mean popcorn chicken
i've heard of it but i never tried it
but i will think about it i will first
have to test it myself
[Music]
calm down
congrats on the milestones whole live
ian thank you
happy life checker again thank you so so
so so much
oh my god everyone is like going crazy
in these super chats
pencil on fire thank you never give up
like a phoenix you have to always rise
no matter what in korean we often use
the phrase
i think is it like fighting
i think and it's used to say that we
should always keep fighting no matter
the challenge keep doing what you do
always keep fighting
thank you
nine thank you general thank you soon
again oh my god
these donations are crazy thank you
zero four five one zoom thank you
i hope you read this we all want you to
be here you make
en a group oh
we all love you are exactly where you
should be you don't need to worry oh
come on
[Music]
stop fighting in a super chat
lives matters please
it's a collab now everyone kfc show some
respect and make kara proud
yay indeed thank you thank you
thank you soon
thank you so much don't overdo yourself
general pickling robert cole dan kashan
it can wait 75 sanctions
tab typo xpx
with the will and charm to brighten
anyone's day the reason why some of us
come back here is to see
you being you oh come on
whatever you do your loyal carefree
employees will be right behind you oh my
god you guys are just so
sweet
god damn it
you're too sweet stop it
yes yes i dropped the f-bump because
it's just unbelievable
thank oh man you guys are so sweet
oh man
[Music]
oh no i will not read your message no no
no
vanilla thunder thank you empty thank
you
the one true magical thank magical
magical
kashan finally had time to watch
kellogg's stream last night i'm a cynic
when it comes to the internet but when i
sat up for 90 minutes listening to you
thank your donors i knew you were worthy
of my first super chat
thank you i am glad
that you found me worthy
thank you thank you uh zero to grab
greg
thank you thank you so many
congratulations
uh for the 200k thank you guys i'm
really happy that
we reached it before the collab piercing
happened
hold on
yeah please don't feel sad when someone
tells you to not dub for your japanese
fears
just do what you like to do and if you
want to die for them during english
i love you thank you thank you shannon
[Music]
i'm so glad you were all able to join
whole life me too
here's so many more bumps and years of
fun in the future yay
hopefully hopefully the future will be
bright for all of us
thank you daniel's spread thank
[Music]
my brothers and sisters rise for this is
the great revolution of our time viva la
holla maybe
in some way it's funny that you guys are
uh
so dramatic
[Music]
thank you thank you for coming thank you
so much
senpai
and your bright attitude always cheers
me everyone up
i'm so glad to hear that thank you
saw blade 19 danger delta
is this about the time where the
where the stream started i think oh
benjamin
stark oh superb
ryan h dustin paddy
[Music]
it's been one week first gen ian crew
and kiara who seems to be the mc today
may this be the beginning of a wonderful
new hollow life for you all maury x
kiara or tv
otp yay
thank you
actually before the stream i was
thinking maybe gulas should sit
on uh on the um
on top of cali or whatever like on on
her ties
that would have been so cute and so
fitting but kind of forgot about that i
forgot about it
ashley miner dan kashan cyborg l
bankeshan
empty duncan arctic fox pancajan nate
pickett thank you
congratulations to the newlyweds
yeah she looks really small when she's
like in the middle of all of us
she looks so small gabriel chronos
thank you hi julius thank you
cantaloupe farmer tell kelly that that
the cantaloupe
farmer says hi i'll tell her thank you
j.r hawker 12 satanic sunshine
r6
thank you for everyone getting 200 k
plus all the idols
should do a kazoo version of their song
but also love you all whole life in
elevated the pandemic depression
yes we came to save the world from
depression
yes no one shall be sad anymore
thank you that's craven367 thank you
thank you for all your hard work
everyone you've brought me so many
smiles this week
my face hurts big congrats to kiara for
reaching 200k subs
thank you thank you
jeff sukas
thank you
i love everyone in whole life and you're
all doing a great job i love watching
the streams afterwards
oh i'm so glad you guys enjoyed the
content thank you
thank you thank you nephews
maybe i don't know
thank you
you thank you another good username 360.
you're all fantastic also good job
keeping the chats reasonable canada
again
no need to break kiara in front of her
friends
thank you
members here to celebrate a successful
week don't forget to take the occasional
occasional well-deserved race thank you
omega red x-channel royals thank you
soon
[Music]
you are so great i just want to say that
you're doing an amazing job and i love
your
personality keep up the great work all
of hello life and are great
thank you thank you
thank you dr frank chibi pakistan
and everyone is still celebrating the
first week so nice
sergio taco thank you again
congratulations to all the girls for
such an entertaining and successful
first week
i'm happy for all of you and and
genuinely looking forward to seeing what
the future holds
me too
the future will hopefully be a good
future
i hope i can bring everyone as much joy
as we did in the first week
all together with all five members in
the future too
i love i love all of them
thanks jaden
[Music]
oh my god the 500 super chat donation we
all love the effort you all put into
making a smile
thank you thank you
[Music]
too much though too much
too much please take care of yourself
first
but thank you thank you i really really
really really
really appreciate it really appreciate
it
i can't find the right words to say but
you deserve every last bit of love and
support that's in descent your way
you're on your way just keep going
[Music]
thank you sir
it was a good choice that i'm doing this
today i wasn't
uh having one of these moments again
today
about a good choice to stream you guys
are always there for me
thank you i love refrigerators
[Music]
john uk i look forward to seeing more of
your bilingual content and collabs with
your friends in heaven
thank you soon thank you homeless man
on mcdonald's the rest is caught up
i have five american bucks is this
enough to buy something in kfc i'm very
hungry
thank you i'll give you something
for free
yes yes fresh kfp buckets coming right
up
keep it up thank you so so so so so so
so much
thank you
already wearing a reel so i look forward
to canada making
kelly a blushing bride but
can we both be brides i also want to
wear a pretty wedding dress
i want both of us to wear a pretty
wedding dress
[Music]
waiting for a wedding dress fan art
what if callie and kiara kissed during
the mafia movie watching
embarrassed emoji
well we're not going to watch the mafia
movie together but
but
a good fall
why are you guys eh
imagining these things though
it's that's that only i
only me and and cali can imagine these
things
stop thinking about about us making out
okay
congrats on a successful week we love
you all take some rest if you need
ps try some falcon games if you can
top-notch characters music and stories
welcome games welcome
thank you
ah
trails in the sky haruko
look they look um close
to my taste
but i will need permission
trails of cold steel
trails in the sky is it like a series
where i have to play the first one to
understand the rest
you would love trails in the sky it
looks good
no yes ah it's serious
no yes except
is a good place to start they're all
connected
well which one do you start with trails
of cold steel
whether is there free parts for trails
i just saw trails of cold steel free
oh my god the sky is first ah trails
trails in the sky is first trails
in the sky
but wait is that oh is it oh the trilogy
is on switch nice because i currently
only have a switch
and a pc
i'll check it out i'll check it out but
i'll have to you know it takes a long
time to get permission
uh for games that have not already been
played by japanese talent
takes a long time could take months
it could take months so don't get too
excited yet
ah you have animal questions
are they all on pc oh
all right i see that you guys are all
really waiting for me to start
uh rpg and me too
me too my friends but be patient please
well we'll have we have something to do
right now anyway with super mario
yeah might want to check out atleasters
i'm playing the utility stairs i played
a bunch of them
of course i did if you watched my debut
stream i
i wrote down that it was one of my
favorite series besides tails off series
but an rpg that i wanted to play that is
currently
already like we already have the
permission would be xenoblade
and i own the game but
i feel kind of awkward starting it right
now
because peculiar senpai just finished it
yesterday
i don't know i feel like i should wait
like a couple of weeks
to start it i don't know
well we definitely have permission for
that and for all nintendo games so i
could play
zelda games as well like zelda breath of
the wild and so on
but then again isn't this week isn't
gentian impact coming out this
uh next week i think so against an
impact i also wanna play
and there are some similarities between
genji and impact and breath of the wild
so i'm not gonna play them both at the
same time
don't worry don't worry maybe okay maybe
that's good enough for now
and then we'll wait maybe if i'm done
with kenshin impact we can start
xenoblade and then maybe at some point
we finally get permission for
all the other games i want to play
and i have to start minecraft too
what do you want to see first uh
actually no i can't even give you that
choice because i wanted to play it from
the beginning like when it releases
so we'll be starting ganjin impact next
week i think
stay tuned
can i suggest a game i think it would be
great to see you all play
ahead in time if possible in a collab i
think you tweeted that at me didn't you
because i saw a tweet with that game
it's very cute and has online capability
plus there's a case
and a costume for emilia huh
okay oh i'll check it out
we did well i want to play some games in
the future together that we can play
with five people
so if you have any uh suggestions uh
send them over to us on twitter
um i'm checking all my replies anyway so
just send them to me on twitter and i'll
check it out if we can play it together
but again
we need permission so the best is always
just
uh the easiest is always just for us to
play something that someone else from
the japanese side already played us
because that means we already have
permission anyway
yeah i don't know about among us i don't
even i i have no idea what that game
even is i just know everyone's talking
about it
[Music]
everyone loves and supports how much
time you put into everything you do
times might get tough and or emotional
but all as fans are
you'll be there are you there to show
you how much you mean to us
thank you that's so sweet
thank you thank you
did you hear that
did you hear that probably too far away
nick the mean daddy thank you
you did hear it i have a habit of uh
cracking my neck because
it hurts
it was my neck yeah yeah yeah
i try to not do it during stream but
sometimes it just
happens and it's a good thing that my my
live 2d
goes so far to the side because you can
kind of see when i do it i go like
showcasing the softness of spoken german
eagerly awaiting future german language
yeah well that's coming soon no
streaming but
uh i'm making some german videos soon
roberto
marin thank you
very much
oh my god are the donations still coming
no did they calm down thank god
where was i i keep on checking the chat
so i keep on losing track
round one day sniff thank you
i'll turn the super chat off probably
soon
and michael bolton thank you shane jack
thank you
thank you chaos thank you justin bieber
black mage 666
crimson 817 nintendo dance 64
dan kashan john 07 benction danny
zankachen
roloff warlord dankeshen mario overall
dan kashan the real robot dankeshon fury
danishan
matthias variantox lxx530 thank you
thank you oh i think that was during the
game because
they mentioned they heard uh a word
during the game
yes thank you lunchboxing cupcake
look energetic personality is awesome i
love hearing your japanese voice it is
just as beautiful as your fellows
that's a good pickup line my friend good
pickup line
thank you thank you
it's been a heartwarming rise of the
phoenix so far and i'm looking forward
to your continued success
i believe i owe you one double order of
shrimp i'll double the double egg
oh was that the person who donated
100 when i reached 100k and he said
he'll double it when i reach 200k
because now it's 200 and now he says
he'll he will double the double again as
free
he will double the double when i'm at
300k doesn't mean 400.
damn don't
i'm now i feel obligated to go slow
because of you because i don't want to
take
so much money from you so quickly
i'm gonna keep on doing that you kind of
started something there
you're kind of like
what what happens after i reach 300k
what happens then are you gonna double
the the double double
i hope you're not gonna do that stop
doubling the double
stop it please don't
thank you
use this to fix the internet you know uh
guys that the the problem with the
this the freezing during the collab is
not because of the internet
but uh we are working on fixing it it
wasn't both collapsed it happened a lot
involved collabs but we're gonna
try our best to fix it until the next
collaboration i think it just happens
when
we are all gathered together our
mythical powers combined or just
too much too much it has nothing to do
with the internet
[Music]
don't make me speak german
stop creme brulee sanctions
how many shoes have been dunked
hopefully when the collab ban
lip set i would love to collab with her
i have to say
besides pekura senpai one of my
other favorite senpais is malinsen
senpai
so it would be a big honor
she's one of my favorites
it can wait 75 functions
and
let me drink my favorite icing
i'm what
why is nobody crying is one of my
favorite favorite
birds and bikes
and while there is only one bird senpai
she is my favorite for senpai
tonight
i
thank you add that to the list of skills
thank you
i've heard a lot of people saying that i
did a great job as a collab and
as a as a host thank you so much i'm so
happy to hear that
i'm so happy i'm really happy to hear
that
thank you congrats on 200k has more
more kfp investment thank you
thank
[Music]
have been totally fine if i ended up
because it's written here in the super
chat kiara is bottom left
then right pickle i i honestly wouldn't
have minded
any any spot on the map because i felt
like i
i'm quite all over the place
i see why why some people would see me
as pure and i see why some people would
see me as not
peer and i see why people would see me
as smart
and other people would see me as stupid
i see it all
i get it but
you know
i tried to make a discussion out of it
for the purpose of keeping the stream
interesting
but they just they just gave it to me
i was hoping that that would make me
more stupid on the charts
i was hoping for it
but some people think i'm just not that
stupid
apparently
thank you all much we could never be
disappointed in any of you long live the
deadbeat phoenix fan chum buddies that
support your tentacle teammates
thank you daddy
twerk night thank you and also there
have been some arguments that i
should have been smarter on the chart
because i speak more languages
but speaking more language doesn't
the language just doesn't necessarily
mean that you're smarter
unfortunately i have to admit that
because i'm
i'm not uh yeah i'm not
i will admit i'm not that smart
[Music]
there it's not
uh it's nothing special especially um
where i grew up speaking free languages
was is kind of um
you
thank you thank you marcel thank you for
trying to make me think i'm smart i
appreciate it
where was i twerp knight thank you
too ecstatic
uh bear wizard twitching blue spouse
thank you i will never know how to say
your name please next time you throw in
a super chat tell me how to pronounce it
thank
[Music]
oh thank you guys you guys say that
well japanese is a difficult language
yeah but
when i tried to learn it it was pretty
easy for me because i just was so
passionate about
it um i think um
when you're really passionate about a
language it's much easier to learn it
yeah and especially if you like
communicate with them every day
with japanese people then you'll learn
the language
instantly
[Music]
as a language learner myself your
streams are a great incentive for me to
watch
feel free to do so as you please
[Music]
don't
foreign
i can't read everything
[Music]
i don't want to admit whenever i can't
read something
i hope that was right
i think
[Music]
that i cannot reach no no no
andrew smarlack thank you alex keeps
thanking
gilbert's pancake
[Music]
be
you
[Music]
thank you
chat i suppose so i suppose i have to
read this
text i'll have two number nines number
nine large and number six with extra dip
and number seven
two number forty fives one cheese and
marshmallow there you go
[Music]
i think my popeye's watching yeah
probably has it like in the background
he always has my stream on
shady d 76 thank you
pepper jackson
[Music]
and here we have reached uh
the end of where i
when the end of
at the point where i first
opened up the super chat today so now i
shall reload
i shall reload
superchat i will
also cut
off the super chats in
10 seconds 10
9 8
7 6
5 am i counting right i can't count
backwards
four three
two
one and
zero
i'll cut it off
panic disable super stickers
okay disable super chat yes
yes kitty masa
thank you guys
youtube what are you doing
okay now i load again
and it should only be the ones from the
stream although i already read them that
came
uh in the beginning
of
shouldn't be too many so we should be
done soon
come on scrolling swirling scrolling up
actually it's quite a few actually yeah
they were a bunch
i'm surprised you guys donate during a
super chat reading
like what are you donating for i'm not
even doing anything funny
oh my god oh
it's quite a lot goddammit
ah
[Music]
good that i cut it up now good choice
all right here we go we stopped here
it's round two
thank you
i was going to try to get at least a few
hours of sleep before class but my
desire to simple is too strong
thank you shin patrick chen thank you
thank you for the bonus
super chat stream you're too good to us
that we can't help but support you
oh by the way does anyone want to make
another super mario something for me
[Laughter]
maybe
last time i got a bunch now it's kind of
hard to find them again
because i got like a million replies and
but if you send it to me this time could
you tag it with my
fan art tag so i can find them again
someone make some more
i you know usually i would make them
myself but
recently you guys made such good
thumbnails so
i thought like if you want to do it so
badly then
i'll take it
but um
request and the last ones were really
fitting for like
the first super mario stream
and now we're kind of more very into the
game so
if if you could possibly make it like
with a screenshot
from in-game you know that we see some
progress and not
the typical outside of the of the
of the castle
maybe put mario hat on me
but leave it to you guys though i'll
leave it to you guys
yeah a little mario hat and
maybe maybe right right on it something
like the suffering continues
something like that
maybe maybe like a nice border
maybe a nice border on the side maybe
not
red because red apparently someone told
me that if you make a red border
on the edge then it kind of interferes
with the
like seeing how far you already watched
the stream because that's also red
so maybe something like maybe blue
or green or yellow
you know but i'll leave it to you you
know
your freedom
i'll do my own thumbnails again soon
i kind of need to make one for
tomorrow's collaboration soon
should i should i repeat my my requests
or
did you get that you remember you
remember my reference
i actually forgot myself what did i say
maybe something
screenshots from like where you can see
some paragraph
and maybe a hat and mario hat
on me and uh
repeat please and uh
uh maybe right on it the suffering
continues and when you use the logo
maybe use the new logo and not the old
logo
okay
[Music]
if i tweet it out people will all see
how i'm i'm lazy
offering you the chance to make a
thumbnail
on stream but that's totally totally
um your choice
it's not like i need your help or
anything i
i don't need your help so i would really
appreciate it
they were so good last time
[Music]
found out how lazy i am
it's not really that i'm lazy it's like
uh the ones i made until now
i don't know uh it's hard to get a good
one but i guess it's easy
oh my god why is my alarm going up for
what is this alarm anyway
yeah um for for games it's kind of easy
because you just got to put like a
screenshot of the game
behind but for like uh chatting or
karaoke
streams i just don't know what to put in
the in the background
you know it's hard it looks stupid
whatever i do it just looks stupid
but yeah the recent ones i think they
look good
my papa is too busy to help me for that
he's already done so much for me
[Music]
i'm looking forward to your submissions
guys please please use the fan art tag
thank you
mercury lamp thank you
ninjin
thank you
tragic the garnering
is this supposed to be a pun on magic
the gathering
tragic the garnering seems like a pun
i played magic magic the gathering
years ago so many years ago
that's so nostalgic
must be a pop pun
thank you
all of us fans appreciate the hard work
uh
you put into every stream you give up
such a cozy warm excitable feeling
fitting for our phoenix just continue
writing our livestream
yeah magic the gathering i was really
horrible at it like
so horrible i used to play with my
phoenix family
we played together but they were so good
especially my phoenix mom
and my phoenix brother oh my god they
were so good
i think my mom my phoenix mom used to
use a a black deck
machine was so strong and i was like so
bad
i secretly cheated but even then
i could not compete with my phoenix
family
yeah my whole family played magic the
gathering
my whole family yeah i cheated and i
still
had no chance and i always played like i
think a white stack or
a but mostly a white deck because just
because i thought it was so pretty
i i played it because it was the
prettiest even though it was weak
as sorry oh yeah
yeah i cheated wait a long time ago i
wouldn't cheat anymore
magic the gathering yeah yeah quite the
interesting
foreign
all of us fans appreciate the hot work
you put into every stream you give up
such a cozy warm excited
feeling fitting for phoenix please
continue writing our lives with your
flame
thank you christopher door and dankeshen
wow she donated the amount of
subscribers i have
congrats on 200k subs but 214 now
you always bring joy when you stream my
faithful life and remember i love you
thank you
actually i also played wig sauce this is
one thing i i was
i wanted to tell you guys in the in the
debut stream but i totally forgot to add
it on my slide
i i uh i'm a wig sauce fan
we could also mostly
[Laughter]
w-i-x-o-s-s the name is
[Music]
w-i-x-o-s-s it's the anime it's already
like a card game but it also has an
anime and a movie
could i social it's actually like when
you look at the anime
and don't watch it yet like you just
look at the artwork or whatever you
would think like it's a happy game with
magical girls but it's such a dark
dark depressing story
so if you're looking for a card game
anime that's actually good
watch wickress
hunts that impaired thank you colton
surek thank you
kiara you're such a ray of sunshine you
have a sweetheart and a truly good solo
come on you're too sweet
you have a gift of warming people's
hearts and making their days a bit
brighter
oh thank you for all the effort you care
and give
stop it daniel h thank you
i hope you i hope you will continue to
be your most genuine self
we might bully you because your
reactions are cute but in the end we
like
you for you
thank
brian thank you soon kikiriki hey ken i
just want to let you know
that you have far in the way become my
favorite member
you know getting told that
oh no roses are red violets are blue um
pepper jacks thank you
this is the first super chat i've ever
sent you're not just my favorite feature
but you're quickly becoming one of my
favorite creators on the entire platform
what your unyielding optimism and
dedication to your fans inspires me
oh my god you guys are too
sweet thank you i appreciate
supersonic 1995 thank you soon i just
want to say all of us love and support
you
stop
don't make me speak german
oh yeah i also love all the burger
recreations on twitter
indeed they look so good misty night
thank you soon congratulations on your
200k subscribers since you look uh
like an operator with your sword and
shield out do you think you'd be the
best as a guard or defender
i guess with the shield i must be a
defender
i don't know i mean honestly i feel like
most of the archives designs are uh
more not really in the style of how i
look but
i would be honored to be in the game
it's pretty pretty difficult game
yeah tower defense but top-notch
top-notch
tower defense
mercury
michael
no no he's not playing art night busy
man busy man
the very hungry singularity
thank you
do the feathers revive people yes they
do
yes they do so don't don't try to pull
out
the feathers behind my ears i need them
i already gave one to pekkora senpai
rusty is cool dankeshen furlog
my favorites your favorite is our lunar
eternal blue complete i have never heard
of that one
and fantasy star 4. i heard of that one
but never played it
[Music]
me yeah
maybe maybe i would uh fit into the um
penguin logistics i have a
your precious your energy is amazing and
your mood
spreads like wildfire i love your
students please keep them up i've
watched all of them since your debut
when you started my heart broke
[Music]
and yeah your enthusiasm for japanese
restored my hope that i will be able to
learn the language someday
i'm still bad but i will try my best
[Music]
for
though i kind of have to watch this
without sound because it's work hours
to me and bosses in the same cafe
ah
always good to have a victory stream on
while you're working yes yes it's very
recommendable
joseph thank you i'm having a tough time
figuring out who is best girl for
halloween and all of you are doing
great and i hope that you are all having
fun doing this i guess
you don't need to have one best girl we
can all be your best girl
no problem with that oh
[Music]
i love your personality and you always
cheer me up when i feel dumb
how do i do that i would love you i
would love if you've
taught us a few japanese words sometimes
too have you ever considered streaming
the call now
criminals i always say colonels colonel
carl xander danison
yes i have considered
need permission i wanted to play it as
my first
uh game actually but
thank
have healing properties apparently they
do
but don't make me cry i cry too much
already
by like the feeling like i have that um
that that thing that i think it came
with the switch anyway where you where
you uh
put in those single con control thingies
and it feels okay to play with it but i
guess like a real
traditional controller just feels better
i'll probably get one
thank you soon
you will not make me read this in
germany
sessions any language is fine to or do a
karaoke night
yeah yeah once i got the new a mic i
might do it quickly
i might join with me
this is my first time watching youtube
streaming oh you should watch when i'm
actually doing something
ew thank you though thank you shin i
hope you're enjoying it anyway i'm just
thanking people
it's just that there thank you you can
get an adapted user
ah but i don't have any xbox ps4
controller right now
i'll just buy a or is there is a pro
controller
better than using an adapter for
a different controller does it still
have better options like
better functionalities
or would uh would it do the job
oh okay i'll say yes i'll trust you yep
okay
how did you learn to switch so
seamlessly between several different
languages
it's incredibly hard and you make it
look easy i think it's just because i
speak them so fluently
that switching is just no problem
anymore i think probably
i never had problem i never experienced
problems
with switching between languages
i wonder when i started learning
japanese i wonder if i had
issues with that i feel like i didn't
i feel like i never even when i was
still bad at japanese
yeah and you guys say i have a bird ring
i tell you bird brain is big brain
language flex
it's not is it hard for other people to
switch between languages
this is it so hard for you
flexing yeah
yeah no for me yes
yeah i can switch in the middle of the
sentence
wow you guys are spamming i can't read
that fast yay
multilingual who here
has english as their first language
say yay or ah
me me me i
i meant like actually i'm an i
there's so many who has english not as
their first language go
say
actually wasn't so many who have english
as their first language
it wasn't even so many oh my god that's
much more
interesting how there's like a lot of
like holo yen is really international we
got
viewers from all over the world that's
this just made it really noticeable
wow i think probably because of my
streaming times i have much more
uh audience from non-american
places like i probably have a lot of
european
audience i guess
i guess or like i don't know
uk australia australia
australia
european you you're being yay cea
yay wow
wow you see it's barely any is there i
didn't even see a single person who
sat there from america
oh canada
sweden finland china europe
brazil or brazil philippines
america hong kong
italy denmark philippines canada
malaysia england usa
portugal you say philippines
myanmar uk us romania
brazil brazil singapore ukraine malaysia
vietnam mexico usa brazil singapore
that's because germany
philippines france
europe japanese
all right i think i got enough countries
thank you
let's move on
[Music]
ali thank you
oh thank you i can safely say it's a
better place for viewing it all
keep being awesome yes this is my first
ever super chat so chase yourself
thank you you're so sweet you guys are
just so sweet
james
here's my early investment in a
five-piece chicken nugget come for
provocation
magazine
i felt like the only one who didn't like
whispering and weird ear stuffing asmr
you also like pineapple and pizza best
girl yeah
good taste but yeah uh i don't know
especially like the ear stuff
so weird like gives me shivers
no hate no hate but not for me
so i will also not be doing it myself
thank you
alexander hello thank you thank you so
much why don't you write anything it's a
big donation you should write something
crazy peanut thank you
tiny dancer not a good kind of
oh that's so popular though
so popular ensemble is so popular
time if you want to hear some good
asmr go to
[Music]
entertaining content you are the only
source of entertainment i have in these
trying times of mine the short
the stored three i wrote the selling
prime myself oh you're writing the story
looking forward to it
if you want to listen to chicken and
some more there is no
such thing as chicken asmr if anything
it's phoenix asmr
the casual otaku guy thank you have some
mic money thank you
emperor vaseline thank you
fisher duncan
[Music]
well like i said it's not gonna be real
asmr too i don't think it's necessary
also i don't know what that is thank you
and thank you skipper thank you
james player dan cashier and evermore
thank you we love you kiki keeping you
kiki
thank you thank you saint game
speaking of creepy stuff halloween is
coming up do you have a costume in mind
yeah a bit more than a month ago
a costume i think i'll have to leave it
to you guys to
give me a costume
i don't think my papa has time for a
costume
halloween costume now
oh chicken costume eh
no no
he said i already look like i'm wearing
a costume ah
i'm majestic
i guess orange is kind of the color of
halloween huh
thank you
audiobook money for the upcoming star
reading i need the audio book to help my
sleeping issue
i might do some fairy tale readings for
membership only in the future as well
if you guys enjoy it like i really
wonder if people are actually really
gonna enjoy it you guys are all acting
excited about the idea but
are you really gonna watch it i really
gonna watch
it
[Music]
can you sing the hands-on creator song i
don't know a hands-on creator song
maybe i've heard it before but i don't
remember
[Music]
doing some german fairy tales can you
please do bruno hilda on one of those
streams
i don't i don't know that one
but i have a list of all the queen's
fairy tales
we'll do them until we run out of them
what do we do when i run out of them i
need a copyright free story
but yeah it will be over once i'm done
with them it will be over
that's just how it is but there's a lot
william alexander thank you nightmare
printing
r6 joshua
[Music]
those fairy tales are meant to teach
children a lesson back then if you keep
sucking your thumb it will be cut off by
a bad guy yeah exactly
so the kids stopped doing it because
they're scared it's brutal effective
i indeed wasn't i did not have
a habit of sucking my thumbs indeed
um brian thank you soon kiara i wanted
to use my first ever super chat to let
you know that your constant positivity
has really been a bright light for me
during the dark
period of my life thank you so much
[Music]
references to scissors in his discworld
series
i i liked harry potter i haven't been
i haven't read a book from terry
pratchett in a long time
but good books good books that finished
dude thank you
[Music]
if it turned out like this by reading
these stories i would read them to my
children every night
okay
german folk stories turned you into a
phoenix that doesn't seem like a bad
deal also love your stream
yeah indeed it doesn't even sound
[Music]
a german fairy tale about a witch or
something as a tiny italian child i was
it was very scary and traumatizing
thank you
[Music]
keep coming please don't make them stop
that was just made up i could write a
song about that
that was good
ah super chat song
hey
thank you for speaking in both language
kiara it really helps me start thinking
in japanese just a little bit more keep
being your wonderful self i love you
thank you soon
[Music]
russian kfp employee what
hi kiara i'm from russia this is my
first super chat ever i just want to say
you're a great person and
i want to say you're the reason i got
into your whole life i never leave you
what
i'm the reason you got your whole life i
just debuted
thank you what's thank you in russian
again
i can't stay for the whole stream but
i'm glad i got to see a little bit of it
and hear you speak german you're doing a
great job
virtuous thank you and while you have an
international appeal my dear phoenix
keep working hard and it will only get
better from here
tomato man apparently one of the stories
in childbirth is about a strong boy who
proclaims to not drink soup anymore and
then wastes away and dies
i probably saw that one oh my god that's
absolutely ridiculous
and the rest of the individuals have
made this deployment easier to deal
oh you're on like uh on the base or
something like that
yeah thank you and i hope you um
have a good time i don't know how that
stuff works
okay american soldier thank you
oh
yeah yeah i disabled super chat in the
after a while because i
i gotta stop stop them from coming
otherwise i'll never be
done with it but thank you all so much
you can i'm streaming tomorrow again and
then
it will be open again
[Music]
tomorrow just take a break
take a break this month thank you do you
have any songs stuck in your head
recently i've been listening to waiting
for rain
by nima oh
songs oh man i i loved listening to
music but recently i barely listened to
music at all
because uh no time
what have i been listening to recently
i actually i listened to maddie and
senpai's songs a lot
recently but besides that
yeah i guess uh cali songs just because
like
i don't have time to listen to anything
else recently yeah
should we try to wrap kali's
look at that
i never tried before
i thought can i even play that
probably not
right was it originally always our or
did you change it
does she have the lyrics in there
oh no she doesn't need
you're not going to advertise on my
stream
my dear friend
james
why do i not have adblock good question
skip ad
i think she sent me the lyrics before
lyrics
are they here oh not that one
ah
uh but the thing is i never practiced it
so obviously i'll fail
maybe the maybe down the chorus
where's the chorus
where's the chorus huh
why the hell
extermination
[Music]
rap god
can i join the co it's a remix con it's
not a cover contest
hey it's a bit confusing because in the
lyrics that she sent me she
has the translation right below it but
then again
she keeps on switching between uh
japanese and english it's kind of hard
to
to figure out what i'm supposed to say
i want to do that part man i want to do
that part
[Music]
is
good i'm gonna practice it and one day
i'm gonna kill it
and then we're gonna have a red babble
between me and callie
can someone make me a rap song so i can
battle her
ah it's so fast so confusing she raps so
[Laughter]
fast
[Music]
now i want to listen to it the whole
time why did you give me this ear
warm did you say that in english ear
warm
or do you say that only in german
oh you do oh you do
it's funny funny
i wanna practice it so confusing though
because of the translation man it's so
confusing
oh well i'll i'll get back to my super
chat i'll get back to my super chat
okay okay okay
no more playing around
right on time from good you say that as
if it was her song
[Music]
um
ever super chat i usually don't like
watching streams much but i can't get
enough of you and the whole
angles keep it up but don't work
yourself so hard um
thank you i was actually the same uh
not so long ago maybe like a year ago
i didn't really like watching streams i
preferred like just videos or
netflix series whatever but what's up
the bgm
what's it bro why you say it's cursed
oh it's fire okay okay
but now yeah i also like keep on
watching streams i mean i'll mostly
watch them in archive but
assume if that's audio
[Music]
but most important chicken that keeps
the bond between everyone oh i'm not
sure about that
no i think we all we all are keeping our
bones
together it's not me it's not me
thank you though purple ghost and kashan
jay smith six to four tangashin spatula
oh
button is turned off we'll be back
tomorrow
again i already sang it last time
can't sing it every day every time it's
gonna be boring
thank you thank you
the flow of the river japan's
[Music]
a question my question my question mark
thank you is that a charge plate you're
holding
what no it's my weapon
bronx 819 function be gamer free and
loving packaging
use this to buy some popcorn chicken
i don't know where to get it though i
guess i guess
kf
membership soon please also keep up the
multi-language streams please don't be
i've been waiting to send this thank you
yeah i'll keep going um the way i think
it's best
because i mean i've got a lot of
japanese brews i actually got the most
uh out of all of the whole life young
girls
so i don't want to lose them i don't
want to lose them
so i'm gonna the less i speak the more
they're gonna leave and i don't want
them to leave
i want all of you to stay all of you the
english-speaking people and the japanese
speaking people so i'll just continue
um
but i mean for games i definitely
won't speak so much anymore but maybe
this week
this week today's monday right yeah this
week i maybe i'll do my first japanese
only stream
but will you guys come too you
non-japanese speaking people will you
come too
yeah really really even if you don't
understand what i'm saying
again
we're used to it
please come to my japanese only stream
as well
speak in bird okay i'll do a whole one
hour stream
just saying me beep beep beep beep
beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep
beep beep beep
but actually that hurts my throat that
that's actually hurting my fruit
no don't do it yeah okay thank you
please please i don't want to do it
time to learn dirt
can you fly in human form i'm curious no
i can't
i can't unfortunately i can't but don't
tell the others
amazon blocks thank you
okay people she doesn't like seeing red
so just break up your super chats to add
up to red thank you
[Music]
i was happy to see that you also like
the monogatari series
it actually inspired me to begin
learning japanese i hope to one day read
the novels in japanese who is your
favorite character
um
[Music]
yay i sang this song like three million
times
but that that little wrap
like it's kind of a tongue twister
so hard
bad apple oh man
what you guys are asking for
that's kind of hard to start off on
[Music]
m
a good song nostalgic song
and then you start dancing like ding
if only she had super chat on right now
oh well
oh well too bad
if i cannot scratch
but without the pgm switch to sing that
foreign
[Music]
um
care
oh cali
cali you're here
i want to sing the full song for my papa
but i can't copyright
[Music]
oh actually uh i remember one song i've
been listening to
a lot recently is like a a remix
of hacking to the gate
oh i love i love that remix man
ah it's so good
what remix was that
hacking hacking to the gate
oh yeah hacking to the gate steins gate
opening synthwave 80s remix by
astrophysics
guys listen to that that's such a good
remix it's such a good remix man
ah oh yeah the 90s version
i've been listening to it the whole time
to get the opening no i
you knew it i said i'm going to listen
to it now
but i'll probably get copyright strength
i want to listen to it well
maybe if i mute it here and i just
listen to it on my own
wait you don't hear anything right now
don't you i hear some ads right now
you don't hear anything right
you don't hear all right okay let's just
let me listen to my music here
oh yeah it's so good
[Music]
foreign
no
[Music]
is
oh it's so good it's so so good
okay i can't sing more because otherwise
i'll get copyright strikes
[Music]
after the stream is over i'll listen to
the song like 10 times again
so let's end the stream quickly let me
read the last super chats
i still have some money god dammit i've
been playing around too much
for
[Music]
that you decide to not make traditional
rsmr i was already fearing that you
would give up
uh your german dignity in order to
change the mind of those that being
narrow minded
in the end i don't think that would have
worked out this way better
i agree
[Music]
is it too loud
call those clips i guess oh it's eclipse
do they call them clips
with japanese subtitles and this person
apparently
came from such a club
um
watch those clips not only the japanese
ones but the english ones of course
of course
thank you so much you can brighten up
anyone's day we love you you are the
sweetest can't wait to start working for
kiki thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you for everything you've done up
to now you're blessing all the love from
you fantastic
thank you i'm sorry i can't join you
guys but i'm happy it exists in the
first place
no
i'm just really surprised right now
about
yeah but since when does salt have two
cleanses none of that
rule
that's one
buffering oh no
do your best internet
interesting the salt is causing lag
i hope you some of you can at least
still uh
i know some of you can still see the
stream cali is the salt the reason why
you stream
sometimes eh no lag okay interesting
like sometimes some people have the
problems and other people don't
a tide
hey uh i'll check up that country later
hope you don't miss piccolos and by too
much you've got us with your lds
[Music]
thank you thank you
uh
you should never have to apologize for
existing or feeling simply face forward
with all your height
after all even a phoenix with no failure
it's just an opportune opportunity to
try again true
and also don't be afraid we offer this
gift happily
oh but i wish i could like thank you
guys more properly i feel like this
isn't even enough
but thank you
for humanoid i can't read that i think
it's
not japanese names
i'll read your message because i can't
read your name
uh 520
mean i love you in chinese not language
what i need the best
streams by google translator
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you kelly
united states employee please enjoy this
as an american taxpayer's expense
thank you yo is that the chat is full
with
uh people not being able to see me can
anyone even see me
someone see me
[Music]
wow so many people can see me all right
stewie
138 in lafayette
the most wholesome and supportive fan
base of any of the hauling angles
really your very best chicken i am
indeed blessed
thank you thank you for coming over from
the other camp
thank you thank you soon
fill in the blanks thank you youtube422
moronic crap thank you soon
hey camera thank you for retreating all
the fan art of yourself and friends on
twitter it allows me to follow more
great artists oh
you're welcome um i like to retweet as
much as possible without spamming my
timeline hopefully
and we're ending soon anyway so
uh i'm sorry for the guys who are
buffering
well we're ending soon generally
thank you so much
can't wait for you to pick up monster
hunter with the charge plate above all
else don't forget to have fun happy
chaos
roberto is playing xenoblade right now
too i'd wait a while yeah
too many people playing xenoblade i need
to wait thank you
super ssg thank you
thank you so much
you can play trail scans in order but
you don't need to do so in order to
understand
ah it is more for the sake of getting
references in video games
[Music]
oh again i can't read your name but
unlimited super chat works
thank you thank you thank you
thank you soon thank you soon come read
me thank you i love refrigerators
[Music]
time to fully care with money
what the hell we getting right thank you
remember to always stay positive and
never compare yourself to anyone
that's a hard thing to do though there
are a lot of things that you bet do
better than anyone else even if it's
sometimes hard for you to see them
[Music]
don't know what to say about thank you
break box thank you
scary game sometimes now we can hear you
scream you're amazing you're interested
introduced me to her life so thank you
and keep up thank you
uh i don't want to play scary games
though
you have to force me to do that
thank you soon i bet ten dollars for you
don't know how to read my name god damn
it
and did i read it right i wonder
[Music]
i love your positivity and enthusiasm in
streams i can't wait for your rpg
streams
you have a good taste in liking tales
and attenuators right
you are really amazing you don't need to
change be yourself please play golden
sun golden song
cold and sun
oh
oh i don't know that one
[Music]
i have to confess i am
i it
i have to confess i
you're going to hurt me for this but i
don't like old old
looking games that much i
prefer the one some that have like
new graphics
i'm not saying that i will not give
those games a chance
same i know a lot of people like those
classics but i prefer you know some
pretty beautiful graphics
you know it just makes everything even
even much better
yeah but to me
um as long as it's like
3d i'm good with it
would you play okami oh yeah actually i
want to play um
what was it again what was it again
uh from square enix um similar game
uh octopath travel i will probably play
eventually even though it doesn't have
my desired graphics
but i will play it eventually once i get
permission
what was that other game uh what was it
what
[Music]
i know i gave you basically no hints
wasn't it something with oni
huh
i'm waiting for permission to stream
onignaki
would you like to watch that
would you watch that oninaki
i'll watch anything you play that's good
to hear
i'm glad i have so many people that are
like excited for me playing rpgs because
i originally thought
that rpgs are not gonna interest you
guys because it seems like um
usually it's like different type of
games that are more popular
for streaming but i'm glad if i can
play rpgs and you'll still watch me
yay
my bravely default yes yes yes
i will play i want to play so many rpgs
we have
we have many many years in front of us
my friends
my investors my chickens pepper jacks
thank you
i wonder if there's a like often for
children songs there's like
a version of it in english too i won't
say for this song there's a
german english version
[Music]
of them
is there have you ever heard of that one
is there an english version
it's not the alphabet song that goes
on
i never know the end of that
eh i think the duck song you don't have
the one that i sang before that
you don't have that in english
apparently
all right let's go on don't have time
for this
pepper chex knock down twenty one
dangerous pepper chips
redundant why are the same people keep
on donating one dollar
each crimson eight seventy thank you
soon like isn't that like
aren't they are they charging you like
uh
a fee for each transaction wouldn't it
be smarter to just make one transaction
i don't know but if you want to do that
keep on doing
someone important to me studied very
hard to learn a new language but no one
to practice with so i tried to study it
as well she's gone now but you filled
that whole
i'm glad i could
oh nice i'm glad you like this song i
have haven't been using it so much
i got two uh original big gems made for
my debut
this is one of them
[Music]
calling quests when you were learning
japanese what
recourses programs did you use to learn
the language oh everyone always yelled
at me that's feeling was bad i have a
bad
i have bad news for you
i did not use anything
i did not use any apps i did not use any
books i did not take lessons i did not
have a teacher
i had nothing i
taught myself a little communication
maybe you can give it a try
no worries don't worry arizona
see you soon
oh yeah flex how is that possible
it communication is the most important
thing
you're on a on a student
exchange for example haven't you heard
of like people coming back from their
student exchange and then being
completely
fluent in the language even though they
were not going at all in the beginning
well they also probably had lessons
while they were in that country but
mostly
they learned it through talking and
that's the most important thing
now don't need books who wants to use
books and actually study
[Music]
did you just say a few super chats ago
that the
last super chat was your last super chat
and now you're super chatting again
gamer three one one thank you and i love
refrigerators
erasmus
you go again didn't you say you stopped
do i have to take the super chat button
away from you
i think i know what he did because that
was the last quick
uh super chat rush because we are at the
end zankashen amazon black stank is
amazing
mr allen ninja duncan and rental
i was reading it with so many breaks in
between so that's why it took so long
but
thank you everyone for super chatting
during the collab stream and during
today's
stream and thank you very much for your
support i
really really appreciate it
i want a massage right oh did you hear
that
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh have you thought ff7r no
i'm gonna be honest i'm gonna make a
shocking statement because you all know
i love rpgs right
now here it goes here it goes shocking
statement
the only ff game i played is ff14
what
i have never played
a persona game before
what dragon quest
i have never played a dragon quest
game before
what did she just think
although i have been very interested in
it i have
never played a higher emblem game before
but i think i bought one recently with
the plan to play it yeah i think i think
i
i bought a switch game of fire emblem
before recently
i didn't i didn't play it because i want
to play it on stream but i have not
played one before nani
yeah we can experience all of that
together
zelda i played a bunch of zelda games i
think i never actually
cleared one on my own before
i i kind of um
always like um let my um
phoenix brother um clear them for me
because um i suck and uh
i just i wanted i could never beat the
bosses so it's gonna be fun if i
ever stream zelda
pokemon yes yes okay
i'm playing organized already monster
hunter
i have never played monster hunter ever
before
this guy i don't know how to say that
but i have never played one of those
before
trails no dark souls no
fallout no dark souls no
chad explodes kingdom hearts
i have never played kingdom hearts
before
oh my god you must be thinking
how can she say she likes rpgs
when she has not played any of these
things
what rpg did you
i'm like a huge huge fan of the tales of
supers i played pretty much every tells
off game
and the actually serious and you know i
i didn't play some zelda games
never cleared one skyrim no
that's stranding no that's not cute
doesn't look cute i like
cute games
huh star ocean yeah i have interest in
that one before after year i applied
before of course
a bunch of them why do i say of course i
can't even say of course anymore
after i turned down so many games
you're hurting me
rune factory no i'm sorry
neptunia yes yes
i have i have bravely default no but i
plan on it
stand up late i have played a little bit
of the beginning but i want to play it
on stream that's why i
have not finished it have you heard of
ken yeah i'm planning to stream it as
soon as it comes out
harvest moon no lost odyssey
no grand blue fantasy no
chrono cross no undertale no
[Laughter]
uh dragon age no
oblivion no start your valley
no any fps games no
no persona 5 no
no yes but i never even after hours of
playing near
automata i never got past the
tutorial box because i suck
but this is a good thing we have so many
games to play this is a good thing
fire emblem no but as i said i already
ordered and i have one of them
here i just need to play them paper
mario
you see paper mario as an rpg i see i
guess you only mean like
uh i heard like it it was really rpg-ish
and the second
paper mario but after that it lost its
rpg
ishness i guess i don't know but no i
have not played it
another classic yeah but that's not an
rpg
and i think you guys ran
out of rpgs now so
i have played world of warcraft with my
whole phoenix family
we played it all together
my phoenix mom my phoenix brother my
phoenix sister
my phoenix mom boyfriend we all played
world of warcraft we were in a guild
can you believe it can you believe it
i'm a baby arpeggio no it's just that
many of them never really spoke to me
that much besides tells off how's off is
just the best
ever and zelda yes
yeah well before i make you guys any
more angry and shocked
i should maybe stop
i should stop
favorite tales of game tales of celia
two tells of berseria
tales of vesperia um don't have a
favorite character
i'll tell oh yeah table of graces is
super good too
yeah tesla visery is like so different
so
dark so different from the usual tales
of games
of course symphonia is the is the first
game that got me into everything
say no gear no
oh celia 2 especially is like
so special cilia 2 especially
so special you know why because like
tails off games usually don't give you
choices
never but celia too
was revolutionary because it gave you
choices
and you had like so many like story
endings and
the first time i played it i think i got
the bad ending it was so
dark and so depressing xelia too
is so dark tales of celia too so dark
and so
so different so
wow
so if you have not played piles of cilia
2 but the other tales of games you need
to play tesla too man
[Music]
well i think i'll leave you guys now i
need to prepare some things let's see if
i got some
super mario thumbnails let me check
twitter in a second
thank you for hanging out with me until
the end i had quite some fun
uh talking to you guys while i kept on
repeating thank
and so tomorrow there will be collab
with ina uh what time i don't know
yeah i don't know i'll let you know i
have to reserve and make a thumbnail and
stuff
and um possibly
super mario we will play before because
i think now let me check the calendar
tomorrow the collaboration is like
around this time
a little bit earlier around this time
though
yeah when are we gonna do super mario
kali
might be streaming here amelia is
streaming here
don't want to overlap gonna be sleeping
anyway let's be real
maybe i'll start around
[Music]
you're already saying avidas in
wow don't wanna leave me i don't wanna
leave you guys but you always
say goodbye
tomorrow around 1 pm possibly i will not
promise you
maybe 2 p.m japanese study time
so i guess i have to say goodbye i don't
want to say goodbye but i guess i have
to say goodbye
[Music]
thank you guys i had fun
no you just joined you're too late
i've been streaming for what three hours
over three and a half hours i could have
done this much quicker
this this super chat reading i really
took my time
and everyone the the picture on the left
side
is on twitter i retweeted it my papa
drew it for me and he uploaded it on
twitter and i retweeted it so if you
didn't like it yet um please do and
please retweet it
because my papa did such a good job and
i love his art papa
do i really have to go i don't wanna go
oh i gotta go gotta eat dinner
i love you papa it's so beautiful and so
it's just so
beautiful
okay
[Music]
cheers
what the hell
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
you missed that one
again what the hell are you doing
you