[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I'm so small
how are you guys
this small Wawa it's been a long time I
know I know I thought maybe
maybe we would all like to see
small wow
again
because this game is funny I think
from the few things that I've seen I
think it's funny
so we might as well do a small one yeah
big Wawa is busy big Wawa has no time
for our stupid games today
so today small lava is great seeing you
guys yes yes
oh wait what the [\h__\h]
um
wait
let's stall a little bit there has been
unexpected
[Music]
um
disturbances
it's okay yeah yeah okay
oh oh yeah it's okay I mean we can talk
about things what did you guys do today
it's 7 P.M it's Monday
a mundane Monday
of Christmas
probably also loves you
otherwise it stays pretty small all the
time oh my God
it's been a while
[Music]
and don't don't do that don't give me
hope hope for what does small what I
like question
[Music]
of course
but small Mama gets small quasel oh sure
[Music]
wait you don't hear the music
now you hear it but it's very loud
[Music]
I I watched a little bit of play this
and I know that you have to escape I
think the island
uh and and that everybody dies or so no
uh but that the music was kind of
bopping that's that's all I know
spoilers
oh
that's just Oh I thought that was like
the whole the spot
spots long long name
did I get spoiled I thought that was the
whole game
oh is that
just randomly I went into sort of stream
and I saw her oh
oh
that's a spoiler
I mean
so that's not the main part of the game
that's the whole yeah I mean of course
it's the whole game I think if I say one
thing about the game it will take up
like uh 10 of the game because it's 15
minutes long apparently
[Laughter]
from what I know is that there's
different ways of going into it right so
I don't know I don't know let's let's
play it okay don't worry so much oh
okay cute yeah they're dancing um
everyone's dancing I don't know maybe
it's someone's birthday party
can you talk to them no
but I can Crouch and maybe dance a
little bit with them
crouching is that crouching or is it
jumping it's crouching
oh hey
collapse and Rhythm by the way this game
is free
hey it's 50 bucks for this they're doing
a chicken dance kind of no they're
actually no they're punching their chest
this amazing dance
[Music]
how addicting whoa what is this like big
teeth stuck in the in the ground
[Music]
oh and they're doing more something like
yoga
more dancing lots of children here too
oh no so but what am I supposed to do
what do I do
what is mine hi what is my role in this
am I the pizza delivery guy
who delivers the pizza oh
is he teaching them how to do another
dance
[Music]
I like this one it's like he's wiping
the floor wiping the floor and then
wiping his hands wiping the floor wiping
the floor wiping the floor wiping the
floor wiping the floor and wipe your
hands
can I run
no I don't think so oh
[Music]
faster I know
the music is calming down
and damn damn he is his his
he's got like
I kind of achievement for watching him
because he's a skilled dancer yeah I can
see that like his feet are on fire like
he's dancing on blah blah
spoiler alert
oh he'll be fine he'll be fine then with
those pizzas I think
[Music]
what if I jump on the turtle could lava
going somewhere let's go come on let's
go
back
[Music]
let's go here oh
okay yeah so this island
is
in the middle of it is a volcano
oh and I I feel like I hear it
being kind of angry already
today like today are they happy are they
happy about it oh
nice nice path this place I feel like
Cliff Cliff achievement oh should I just
find every place on the island just go
sightseeing before it's too late
but this place seems pretty sad I feel
like the the lava would not go to the
tip of the cliff
I mean unless it's like
it's like The View kind of eruption I
don't know I don't know really what
what's a normal volcano eruption is like
but if it's if it just flows down then
it would go around the sides and then
they're probably fine huh
gobs
[Music]
what can we find oh what is this we have
some farming going on here oh come on
pizza and corn on Pizza My Favorite
Things plantations wow
ew that's cauliflower what the [\h__\h]
is cauliflower like considered to be
tropical I don't really see it as
something tropical
but I got an achievement for that too
for seeing that cabbage
nah that's not cabbage I feel like
that's cauliflower
[Music]
cab I don't think that's happened you
guys what kind of cabbage have you seen
until now
oh so
they need a boat they honestly need a
big ship
because swimming is dangerous
Bird Goes
Bye Bye Bird
nice
hips
[Music]
all they're doing a pushy dance actually
purpose of this game is for you guys and
me as well to get some new dance moves
is this have I seen this one before
I think so
there's so many different dance moves
that you could use in the Disco
I mean come on look at that I mean
there's probably people in the disco
dancing like that probably
I mean oh this
oh That's a classic that's actually lame
very lame don't do this one
not so 10 of the 10 this one though oh
yeah oh yeah oh yeah that's confident
yeah oh and also clapping along the
music when you don't know what to do oh
wait a second
thank you
there's a
there's a monument with some
hints
when it's puffy
they're dancing happily with arms up
when it's about to erupt they're still
happy dancing
and when it's a wrapping
they just still are there
but with the arms down
um maybe by the time that it's already
starting to erupt you guys should go
somewhere else I don't know just an idea
oh
yeah show me show me wow she's she's
kind of like in her own Zone
[Music]
so
I can support the chicken dance
oh baby
oh
this is so small
[Music]
it looks funny it looks like a puppet
I mean y'all all of you look like a
puppet
so baby baby also gonna die
remember to go back to here later oh my
God okay what to see the baby die
you want to see that why does he have a
sausage on his head
oh wait maybe it's a mohawk
but it could also be a sausage I mean
who knows
ah cute
wait then what's close the monument was
close to the baby
and this Cliff is close to the baby okay
okay
oh
this is Advanced very Advanced you're
creating new Rhythm within the Rhythm
so Advanced that you have your own like
fan fan boys and girls hyping you up
[Music]
well yeah I was also thinking of shoe
flatless uh Austrian or or
South in German maybe also
um
count Countryside dance move
oh
[Music]
yeah okay I like that I feel like
they're about to dance to suzumiyah how
do he dance they already have a good
formation
and they're five people I mean that's
perfect oh wait
[Music]
ah
aha
let's go yeah sheesh
why did I not have nipples by the way
that's the problem
my opinion that's a problem we need
nipples on these people
oh achievement for this for some reason
wait there
wait there also there are Shippy ships
thank you
everybody
you wanna Maybe
[Music]
do you want to maybe
maybe jump in here
I I would I would recommend it
personally
um
no
you're not concerned I mean it's still
only
puffing and huffing and puffing
so I guess it's not very concerning to
you guys do I have to activate it
but jumping into it by any chance
am I the one who's gonna bring
the end to this island
get ready to get on the boat I mean yeah
but what about the others
all about the others where the boats are
over there
okay I think I saw like at least a whole
like the the full
roundness of the island maybe not every
detail but
where is it where the boat should I lost
why did I walk away
why did I walk around uh
here okay
so I go in
foreign
I just saw my body I survived it
I survived the lava
but I have the same body as them why why
can they not survive it
[Music]
added the tomato sauce
let's go wait ships
[Music]
there
yay
I was in the wrong place
I want to watch them though let me watch
them die
oh yeah let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
the baby is close by
Circle I got a circle treatment oh wait
is this still the baby lady
I'm not sure anymore this is the baby
lady baby lady
[Music]
give me the baby
what
[Music]
do you almost saved the baby but Frozen
like a basketball oh hi
ah
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah maybe you shouldn't be
wearing flammables
what
[Music]
helped them at all am I just here to
watch them the demise of this island
is that all I'm here to do
I'll imagine what did you mean with this
album
explain
no so
we're gonna play it several times
of course
um but I don't yeah
to my completed games list let's go
oh that's just screaming
I still hear there's screams in my head
ah I don't I don't but what kind of
endings like how do I get a different
ending isn't the ending always death
can I do something can I save the baby
or
or is the baby doomed I mean
did she just start from no she only
starts throwing in when she's already in
the lava right so she can't throw it
earlier
I wanna oh wait maybe I can catch it if
I stand there now that I know kind of
where it's falling
Maybe
maybe okay
I can I can attempt it
no one survives pineapple pizza is that
what you're like supposed to learn oh
Bird friend I'm a bird friend
ah
I wasn't in Rhythm yeah
[Music]
okay
you're the same Turtle I think you're in
the same turtle
oh you're in the woods okay
where is the closest path to the
okay now let me hear
[Music]
that
[\h__\h] not there maybe the other way
[Music]
maybe the turtle can just like swim
maybe it's I mean realistically I don't
think a turtle shell would survive
lava I mean correct me if I'm wrong
[Music]
that's crazy that's messed up
okay let's try it
I want to try it oh [\h__\h] did I activate
it surely I did right
okay
[Music]
we were I think it was the right side
was it yes okay I mean how can I help
you can I maybe if I ride on the turtle
it's it's coming
turtle turtle turtle turtle turtle
[Music]
s
screaming don't you hear it do turtles
have ears let me turn this a little bit
down I'm gonna have to scream in order
to hear myself
[Applause]
[Music]
come on
okay I'll stand on the third I'll try to
stand on the turtle
[Music]
oh
pushed out here it comes
and I lost it I lost it but I was riding
on it
longer why do they fall off
[Music]
ah how are you feeling oh I feel like
that's interesting is it not that might
lead us to a solution of uh you guys saw
that again
[Applause]
turtle was suddenly zooming yeah hmm
I can restart it okay okay okay
yeah it was going towards an iceberg I
mean I guess it's an iceberg for the
turtle because it's very big only in the
eyes of the turtle
but okay
um
actually before we try the turtle again
let's try to
the baby catching if that is even a
possibility I do not know
but do I have to stand exactly on like
the exact pixel
of where I think it will land I hope not
oh so I'm not sure anymore where exactly
[Music]
um
hi turtle
how are you I I'm not so worried about
the turtle anymore at least I know that
the turtle Will Survive
with or without me it doesn't matter
so
maybe maybe we should let the turtle
just be
on its own
hmm
okay I mean
oh what the hell
kids playing
oh fun damn those are some white long
jumps you're doing sheesh
still finding new things
so something I missed
you
okay oh baby person is here and it
landed like here I think
yeah after he does not manage to
freaking catch the baby which is like so
important
who can he not
okay
is this a path yes it is
yeah he gets smacked in the head and it
just falls off his head
down on the ground and then it gets like
emerged
dissolved in the lava
let me go faster let me go faster I need
to be faster
ah tomato sauce thing coming
okay
okay I'm ready I'm ready to catch it
but it will take a while
because even after she's so many
standing basically in the lava it will
take her a moment
[Music]
[Applause]
s
[Music]
finally
my hair looks like lava sauce
lava sauce
[Music]
[\h__\h] Sports class
I mean
[Music]
there she goes I think she's gonna do it
she's gonna do it three two one oh
oh wait I never I never wake up
no I was kind of there
[Music]
uh all day old all of them all of them
oh oh wait oh maybe she can make it
because the other sharks are already
nope nope nope
I thought maybe because the other side's
already fed she would have a chance with
no
[Music]
um I don't know if I missed baby I mean
I panicked a little bit I'm not very
good at catching balls
that is true
[Music]
but
yeah I guess you cannot actually
catch the baby
hmm so can I like do anything though
anything
or is his chest
is this really no no
are we just like kind of like a god-like
person
roll I had a bone where were the bones
maybe we're just supposed to witness it
to then tell uh historians
what has transpired that's also
important you know because if no one
survives except the turtle
a turtle is not gonna be able to tell
what happened on this island
an infinite Loop
it's only a loop if you make it into a
loop
because
you cannot accept the reality sometimes
you just have to accept
but everyone's gonna die
because natural disasters are [\h__\h]
natural disasters
are they just flying because I'm getting
closer
well at least I'm saving the birds at
least I'm saving the birds okay I found
the boats again
well maybe actually they won't even be
space for me maybe they will be
um
used by these people but there's not
even that much space there's like
assuming that they'll only sit in these
holes there's one two three four five
six seven eight
spaces but you would hope that they
would try to squeeze in a few more
people
right you guys I think I see
a path there so let's go up and then
just go straight
straight straight
downwards to the boats and see what
happens if there's people who are smart
enough eight is better than nothing that
is true I would like to see some people
survive besides me otherwise it's just
very depressing
these aren't exactly the ripest Coconuts
on the island are you calling them
coconuts like their heads because
they're
yeah not very ripe
just I mean you should know what's going
on you should hear it you should smell
it can you smell lava but I feel like it
would get hot and you should you should
realize what's going on a little bit
early yeah
put their toys and they're dancing
well the music is amazing so
it's understandable
[Music]
oh I see them jumping off the cliff I
think
what exactly are they doing well now
they're climbing down also
we gotta check out what the cliff people
do
a lovely cooking stream thank you I was
thinking about swimming this while
eating pineapple pizza too
trigger people even more but
[Music]
uh-huh
let's go
don't push me up oh but there's like
plenty of people coming up here yeah
I'm getting an escape achievement
yay oh no she's not gonna make it she's
not gonna make it
[Applause]
[Music]
you can just wait
no
no no no no no no no no
[Music]
foreign
but wait didn't it only land on on my
boat nah nah it landed in the middle
somewhere and the wave kind of flipped
over everyone's boat I guess
[Music]
oh my God
but I mean unless they immediately got
eaten by sharks I don't see the votes
flipping over being such a big issue
[Music]
turtle and birds win yeah the animals
which I mean
Maybe
that's good
humans have taken over this island
and the animals are losing their space
they shall soon return after the humans
are all dead
should I
is there something specific I should
check out should I check out maybe the
turtle look in and see if I can really
ride on it until the end
but I think eventually it just like
dives into the water right so I just get
lost in there
the cornfield oh what happens with the
cornfield
is there something with the cornfield
I'm insane actually maybe we can combine
the Cliffs of the cornfield
Cliffs are is that a cliff no not really
ah okay okay I'll just
popcorn
that makes me question again if that
works because I questioned it before but
of course it doesn't work I mean I mean
I mean it has to be like breakfast right
like
like dried dried corn that's what it has
to be first right
but okay I can see them doing that
but what happens to the salad I also
want to know what happens with salad
show me show me
I mean it's not salad you guys convinced
me now but it's in my mind but I don't
want to be brainwashed this is
cauliflower
nothing else
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
ah
a and leaves
why is it turning into leaves it's just
okay but
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
these are the strongest Birds I've ever
seen oh my God
holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] what's gonna happen
to me
I should save myself first Maybe
but I'm curious about this man's story
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
there is
there's no
no fix There's No Escape
I can't help him
they tried though those are like some
Chad Birds
um
I mean
I don't think Birds in real life would
ever do this attempt this
even attempting it okay
of even thinking about it
I don't think they would think about
trying to carry their human
seems kind of unrealistic
oh okay what's next why don't we check
out next
we gotta squeeze as much content out of
this game as possible
after all
I mean I know I I like it as a short
stream but I mean at least an hour come
on
the cliff okay when was the cliff
Let Me Maybe see from the top
but I'll read Super Chat still so it
will make it a bit longer anyway
I can then like for real for real catch
up on my super chats finally okay here
are the cliff people I saw them from a
distance just climbing down though I
think
there's one single dude there
who might do something special I guess
okay
[Music]
right now I just started the process
wait a minute I don't hate promo I love
promo
wait
um
[Music]
Pomeranian I cannot find her message
what did she say
hi Paul I see the high poem was high
Palmer high Palm
that's it that's all the way no I can't
stop jamming I don't even notice the
lava
you're one of these people mama how can
I save y'all
worth it oh my God you know what I
watched
I watched a little bit of funnels
um
today so yesterday's
frog stream
[Music]
oh let's go
what happened did he oh he broke
everything okay
um she has like a a a a frog Bird yeah a
frog personas wow
Brock should go on the Dig with my frog
too
[Music]
but
by the looks of it it would have been
smarter if you would have actually
it stayed up here what are you doing
[Music]
stupid [\h__\h] what happens if I stay
unless another [\h__\h] rock hits me out
of nowhere
[Music]
Mama wait
I'm gonna I'm gonna try to make our
frogs have a a date ah froggy dead yeah
yeah your frog voice is so cute
frog bird is so cute I really like it oh
everything's moving
what why is it lifting the trees
[Applause]
[Music]
I
oh wait what the [\h__\h] that face
statues statue always there
[Music]
it's a rock man with the the tree as
well so being lifted off what exactly is
going on there
why why was there
yeah I got the achievement actually just
by looking at it from a distance
mmm huh
thank you
the Rocks melted
you can melt rocks
what
okay wait I will find the Statue again
but it didn't seem like anything special
was happening with the Statue but what
happens with the Statue before the lava
is flowing
let me up let me go up let me go up I
want to go up
that's what lava is
bad melted
this is mounted rocks
why
I guess I'll need to watch a YouTube
video to educate me on that
okay
interesting what
[Music]
nanny
oh
the statue should be like here though ah
here it is
all chilling there and the bird on the
top and that's it
[\h__\h]
what does it mean what does it mean guys
wait till she learns Ice's frozen water
what
[Music]
excuse me
you're like breaking all my dreams
and hopes
and believes
now I know that of course
um
I wanna see something special
show me something special
or did I see all the cool things
I feel like I saw the cool things
okay I want I want I will find try
watching a cliff from the bottom
well I couldn't imagine what's happening
oh we should check out the kids
do we want to see more of them die
okay let me find the closest
half up oh it's close to the baby too
ride a rock I can't really jump though I
would have to find the right Rock to
ride
yeah where is the proof
proof or it didn't happen ice being
melted water
and what the [\h__\h] I can't find
a close path to go up
I want to stay close to the
I want to stay close to the kids
it's so ironic that
they have they're aware that the volcano
can erupt otherwise they wouldn't have
painted it up there
they know it can happen and yet their
reaction is so [\h__\h]
so unbelievably [\h__\h]
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] uh how can I not find it
anymore
suddenly everything's closed off I feel
like I went around half of the island
bye
try staying inside the volcano
oh okay up here
should I really
maybe inside the volcano is the safest
place
maybe it will be emptied out but no no
no I don't want to end I don't wanna I
wanna I wanna hear can I go here
this feels fairly close it
this was not where the children are
[Music]
okay I'm here I'm here
we can see maybe they react to The
Monuments again or
sing it
baby
they're okay with this happening
they think you know it's a time oh
it's how it's supposed to be
look at them go wow they're actually
reacting pretty fast
and then
you follow up okay but some of them made
us
[Music]
and then oh holy [\h__\h]
it's just like
foreign
okay okay she's still going she's still
dancing she might be the longest lasting
dancer oh
well
[Music]
the house
it's in other houses
that's the only house that happens too
what the [\h__\h]
if they would have done it on a
different house
um
here no I cannot accept that
the proof the roof was always like it
must have it must have been the person
who first started to say hey let's go up
this roof let's make a human ladder and
let's go up this roof must have been the
person behind it must have been like
extremely sadistic and already like
manipulated the roof
the weight nah it's a
nah I don't believe it yeah I mean I
guess it's probably made out of like
like something like grassy like hanging
or whatever right it didn't look like it
but maybe it was thatch straw hmm
hmm
damn it
okay we can watch one more thing
what should we watch
is there something I have to see
you know this will never happen if I
don't jump into the volcano
but you guys are not doomed
pretty doomed
fan okay we'll stay in the volcano
but I mean
I just had this genius revelation
you don't have to let all these people
die
it's just your sadistic choice to do so
you don't have to
[Laughter]
oh well actually this is great music for
Super Chat so I will just let the game
Run in the background afterwards
um but you want no
no aren't you I mean I want to make this
island into a pineapple pizza
because I love pineapple wait is are
they saying that pineapple pizza brings
doom and Sorrel and despair upon the
people
is that the message of the art is the
are the makers of the game anti
pineapple pizza
[\h__\h]
zero zero ten
I do not agree
I'm so offended pineapple pizza is green
most people who say they don't like
pineapple pizza they just don't even
they have not even tried it before
pineapple pizza is good trust me guys
give it a try you just have to give it a
try
it brings you happiness not
a lava a volcano eruption really
[Music]
yeah yay
what's going on
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
the Phoenix Naturals not really not
really my natural habitat
although it seems like we're pretty safe
here
bam
[Music]
hey hey
hey hey hey hey hey
it's getting taller every time
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
I think I heard popcorn or something
burning at least
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't know
I don't like the message of this game at
all
[Music]
it makes me feel like I'm the villain
which I am obviously not
just because I put pineapple on pizza
[Music]
I got the murderer no
you guys are just so so negative and
pessimistic
um
no no
you guys are wrong wrong wrong
no I just [\h__\h] password to you're the
bad guy no no pineapple pizza is just
this is good
you intolerant [\h__\h]
okay well
I tried my best to get an hour out of a
15 minute game
a meow cat meowing in the distance
so you know what this means guys
I I am going to read super chats now
it's in a while just sugar
oh
[Music]
Alicia
where's kiwawa I hear
isn't this wonderfully nostalgic
haven't used it so often but it's small
small Baba office where do I go
ah yeah a wonderful
yeah I I I rarely use this one
so I'll I think a lot of people haven't
seen it before
[Music]
yourself
Chad can be here too it's a bit hard
because I don't really I don't really
have a window for you guys
it's fine Ryan
wow I'm here
I mean I'm small level but that's good
enough right
have you tried beans on a pizza
um
yeah I think I have um it was um
but wait what else what it was like one
of those thicker pizzas
it have beans
and
whoa what else was that
it's actually pretty good
there's this it's this one um frozen
pizza that they have here in Austria or
in Germany to
um
wait let me see
[Music]
it's the big Pizza Western oh yeah oh
yeah it got the pepperoni it's actually
really good
let me show you
because like we have a big frozen pizza
culture here
this is it
it has pepperoni
and the and the pepperoni and corn and
beans but it's a thick Pizza it's even
thicker and fluffier than it looks like
on the picture to be honest normally the
most common pizza here are really thin
pizzas
um but this one's
this one's a thick type
yeah I'll call it Western they also have
like a barbecue chicken pizza from this
brand I like barbecue Pizza barbecue
chicken pizza very good
mmm
it looks yummy it is it is I don't eat
it often but it actually really is
normally I always feel like you know I
already have trouble finishing a normal
Pizza sometimes and this one's bigger so
I mean thicker so it feels like more
filling
[Music]
um
not sure how I feel about corn on Pizza
being cold Western and I don't know it's
a it's a German I think a German Pizza
brand so
you know things are named
however they feel like
Chicago's the best I only hear bad
things about Chicago style pizza but
I've never had one but I think
um I know a place that does Chicago
style pizza is it is it the Deep the the
the the the the one that's like like
what wait
yeah deep dish pizza
that's it right
it's just really messy wait is that the
same thing no yeah yeah right Chicago
style deep dish pizza
I want to try that but it seems weird
it's just a lot of tomato sauce it looks
like there's a [\h__\h] ton of like you know
the ratio between toppings and pizza and
then looks like a cake
like a cake mean like it looks fresh if
you don't look closely and if you're
maybe if you have bad eyesight you could
think that it's a strawberry cake
honestly
I'm looking at pictures on Google right
now deep dish pizza
and if I make my if I squint my eyes oh
yeah
I leave I said all looks like strawberry
Pizza like a really basic one pizza a
strawberry cake I mean
strawberry cake just look like uh
strawberry in in like delay type uh like
um
jelly
it has the right shape and the right red
mmm
I'm squinting my eyes
you see a difference
uh
as hard to say
no difference
um like a cheesecake yeah yeah
strawberry Pizza ew but
but
um I've had a chocolate self-made not
from me but from a friend my pizza
friend made me and my friends when we
had like a pizza day
um made first like a dessert pizza and
it was like a chocolate pizza and it was
honestly really good so I think dessert
pizza on its own is not a bad idea it's
just about like the how like if
um
if you mess it up or not
I have a pizza friend yeah hmm
chocolate pizza can be good and like
um
um I would say like mascarpone
and also
uh what's it called again cinnamon
cinnamon on just pizza dough fried pizza
dough cinnamon perfect carbonation mmm
oh I'm not a big fan of marshmallows so
I don't know what to say about that
yep I've not tried the doctor atka
chocolate pizza I haven't tried and I
don't plan on trying because I
I know I don't know I don't think it's
good I can't believe that it would be
good
um there's many more actually good
desserts in Austria that are frozen
that I would choose over it
hmm
orange juice
so close-minded so
stream where I'm being criticized for
being a fan of pineapple pizza
where everybody's ganging up on me for
loving openly loving pineapple pizza
unbelievable
pineapple and pizza with cherries and
caramel no no no no just because there's
pineapple in the pizza doesn't mean that
it's like a dessert fruit pizza no no no
no
pineapple is like the only fruit
besides I guess tomatoes because
apparently apparently according to some
propaganda
tomatoes are fruit
have you guys heard of that [\h__\h]
it's incredible
olives I'm not a fan of Olives but
whatever if you want to put it there
whatever do it do it
fine sure
I've had like a bruschetta
the other day that was like tomato and
olives mixed
and yeah I ignored the olives because
they were chopped up and they were like
mixed with the tomatoes so it was
acceptable
Tomatoes were considered poisonous for
centuries
did they even try it I mean maybe humans
needed to build up like a immunity
against something from the tomato
because they are a Nightshade what
what
tomatoes
poison
tomatoes are members of the nightshade
family they actually produce a slightly
different alkaloid called humatine
tomatine is also toxic but less so
however when ingested in extremely large
doses it may cause gastrointestinal
problems liver and even heart damage
oh what how much is extremely because I
feel like we use tomatoes for some any
dishes
in quite a lot of
uh amounts but okay I guess it has to be
crazy much ah only the green pads oh
okay like who eats that nobody okay okay
oh
I see
oh we don't mess together Tomatoes like
we did with animals
making them even more
tolerable
would you take a bite into a tomato of
course I mean I wouldn't take a bite
into a stem
it's kind of annoying because it will go
poof
and sploosh all over you but no
okay guys
I will use this opportunity of a short
stream
to make some paralysis of super chats
and so
we'll hopefully finish them
do you guys remember where I left off
please tell me and I'll take a throat
candy because I screamed
trying to I tried to be high energy in
case you haven't noticed
I thought the game would give me a bit
more
a bit more content
oh man oh yeah
um
calm down calm down everybody
it's it's a cute game though I mean it
was even free so honestly like I don't
know what I was expecting but I was
happy it was free
and it's short
I was when I was watching Subaru Senpai
player though I was like so confused
because
um
like she had
she had this like uh voice this like
cute girl voice on that reads out the
whole chat and I think it was always
behind crazily because you can't use
something like that when you get 500
messages in one minute
[Laughter]
what's up with that and it is actually I
will I will have you know because I know
um
from uh the past but on Nico nicodoga
you know where Japanese people used to
stream before they all found out about
YouTube and twitch and all that and even
now they still use it
um
um it is pretty normal to use TTS like
espec maybe if you're like super super
super super super crazy crazy crazy
crazy crazy crazy crazy popular then you
wouldn't use it because it's too many
messages but even even the very busy
chats use TTS and the not not busy chats
they almost always use TTS
um
so it gets read out to them and but they
they I have never heard of this cute
um new TTS that has this cute voice it's
very cute
hmm
the review is overwhelmingly positive it
made for the pineapple and pizza
actually I think it's like really useful
I would use a jewel
but
yeah only if my chat was way less busy
then I would use it too because like
every comment gets read out and then you
always react and if I were to try to
read out all my comments on my own my
voice would die
maybe the members not even the members
chat you guys go
[Music]
oh that noise reminds me I was watching
up
a video of um
some professional guy vacuuming out uh
yellow hornet
eastern northern I don't [\h__\h] know he
kept on mentioning different
variations uh Nest or in the ground
yeah the yellow jackets
yeah it was recommended to me ah no a
shortcut recommended to me and then I
was like hmm actually I'm curious like
he linked in the chat in the in the
comments he linked like the the full
video and I was actually kind of curious
because I I felt like I want to know
what happens to them
after he vacuums them up
and uh turns out he feeds them to his
chickens
he feeds them to his chickens
they looked so happy actually no he
doesn't feed the the uh the bees the
yellow jackets to the chickens no
he feeds the larvae
to the chickens and they were so happy
he's so nice to his chickens but it was
interesting because they kept on going
coming and coming and coming
and they don't stop coming
he was like vacuuming the nest for 40-50
minutes and they like never stopped
never stopped it was endless
one of the biggest nests ever
terrifying I've never seen
I think IRL I've seen like one Hornet
maybe before in a bus
which is which is terrifying hmm but
generally another blessed with not
making many acquaintances with Hornets
yeah bugs in closed spaces
actually a couple days ago or a week or
two
um a library full of protein right yeah
so it must be really good for the
chickens
um but I was like
um I bought a plant somewhere
um and then I went uh I was like waiting
at the station
to get into a train I was sitting down
and then right before the train comes uh
a b
I don't know if it was like you know
because they huh they all look the same
to me but I I don't know if it was a b
that can sting you or just one of those
like floating bees that don't look that
look like bees but are not bees I don't
know but something like that landed on
my plant and I had to go inside and I
thought it would fly away but no I
walked into the train and it just stayed
on my plan so I was like hey hey I
brought up a bee into the into the train
oh [\h__\h] I'm so sorry but I I didn't want
to like anger it by like by pushing it
off
um
yeah I wanted a free ride yeah
and so I was sitting next to my plant I
put the plant on on the seat next to me
and I was watching the the beat because
I I felt like I had to keep my eyes on
the bee unless because I didn't want it
to fly I don't know on my on my leg and
then and then give me um
a people
you know
yeah yeah if only froggy wow was around
froggy Wawa could have eaten the being
against
why is the mouth tracking so [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I had to I have to talk like this
all the time I feel like a [\h__\h] idiot
um
a beep I don't know words don't come to
my brain anymore they have left me
um
very cute small Wawa
besides not a sting yeah besides not
being able to move her [\h__\h] mouth
um
so on the end it eventually left the
plant and was just flying around the
train not felt bad but nobody knew that
it came from me
[Music]
I would hope not to get used to that way
of talking
I don't know if I'm allergic to bee
venom I I don't remember ever getting
stung by a beer
no I don't I wouldn't remember
actually quite lucky I've been alive for
a long time
hmm
hey
lucky lucky
I do get stung by mosquitoes though one
time I got I was like on a vacation as a
child and uh some mosquito or or one or
two I don't know they decided to sting
me on my
um the front of my lower leg when you
call that again
um but not once not twice not fries not
force not fives
like shin yeah it was like six or seven
stings
all on the same like
three four centimeters circumference
area and even my mom was like what what
what what happened what
it was it was weird
it's like they found my sweet spot
damn
that was weird
no I was just it was summer and I wasn't
wearing pants I was just probably
wearing a dress or something
why all in the same spot
so weird like kiwama Buffet
take my blood take it I have plenty
I wouldn't mind as much to be be stung
if if it wasn't so itchy
if it wasn't itchy I don't think you
know mosquitoes I think people wouldn't
mind mosquitoes if it wasn't so itchy if
they if they made it on not itchy
then people wouldn't mind so much and
people wouldn't have to kill them all
the time so maybe they should like think
about what they're doing
hmm
the disease well okay our mosquitoes are
not dangerous in Austria so I don't have
that problem
hmm
no
thank God
I think I was told I looked it up and I
was told I think
that in Indonesia the mosquitoes do
or our past a possible
um carriers of diseases right
so when I was there I was like so scared
I was so scared
because I also don't have like I don't
think I have any active
um
[Music]
vaccinations for that kind of stuff
um
but it's hot and humid
so I feel like there must be a lot of
mosquitoes lying around
um How can you
how can you stay safe
huh
sounds really dangerous but thankfully
nothing happened but that was one of my
concerns
um
yeah tropical diseases especially
[Music]
um
they are like extra dangerous it seems
you should get those especially when I
go to Bali oh yeah maybe I should up
update all my vaccinations
but I probably have to start from zero
for most of them or all of them
um
anti-mosquito spray thing oh yeah yeah I
think I had one even the the hotel I
think the Maldives the Maldives Hotel
I think gave us one like a repellent
like in the room there was a repellent I
think
which is nice yeah
um
very necessary
[Music]
by the way this night I did not have
night nightmares and and this movie did
wake me up early uh to ask for food but
I ignored her and this time she actually
did stop after
couple minutes
so I was able to fall back asleep again
and I was able to sleep rather calmly
I think it was still a weird dream but
not really a nightmare
yeah
yeah thank God okay
let's watch uh let's read some super
chats uh somebody said I think
um
the Korean stream
Maybe
Korean study stream okay
yeah it makes sense okay
oh yeah yeah okay okay let me put up the
thumbnail
I wish I had a smallified thumbnail
because everything's modified now I want
a smallified version of the thumbnail
but no no I don't have
um
[Music]
big Wawa is so pretty I wanna be as big
pretty as big Wawa one day when I grow
up
and and grow actually more face features
I wanna be like her
she's so pretty
Mamma Mia
she's gonna make me swoon
okay so let's see what we got tickets
monkey donkey soon Evans
Jacob 47 ounce
perfect family for the stream which I
had a chance to see it doing popcorn
anyways good luck on your Korean
starving Dental if there is another
chance for Korean con maybe you can Flex
the Korean to the crowd next time that's
what I'm hoping for but I still don't
um
but I still don't have any invitation if
I have one I would not mention it at all
so in order to keep it a secret but I
don't have one so I'm mentioning it
that is I have not been invited to
anything for this year yet and we're
already almost in summer I'm panicking
I want to be guest in
Korean convention please
please
[Music]
invitation truthio
hmm
I don't know maybe they're going with
different
members this year
what
they're not sorry instead of a popcorn
so my chances are dead
when did they get announced
no
no it's here no
Korea has like two big conventions
this one the popcorn and one more but
[Music]
so
cool
[Music]
popcorn
Kiara
[Music]
um
so sad they have agf still maybe you
might have been longer what did you have
please I want to be invited I want to
meet my Korean Bros
and girls
um
I learned I put I'm putting so much
effort into my Korean studies this year
I want to show it off I want to sing do
you in Korean
eh
can you ask I I did tell jenma
um you know hey can we get me on a
Korean convention this year too
and I think she related to the people in
charge but I feel like normally it's
like the convention would say who they
want unless they don't want anyone in
particular then maybe our events team
will suggest someone
but usually usually the event would say
hey I want this person I think
[Music]
no
now agf the only other big one that
would probably have the funds
to invite some of us is agf I would say
um
damn
Cruise
duncanians well
soon
thank you
um
[Music]
song
Young
for the pink Super Chat cool
ah
oh you're trying to say good morning
good evening to me
thank you oh thanks for 50 and 20
memberships holy [\h__\h] you guys are crazy
hmm
damn
are you here now
because now it's probably in the middle
of the night for you hope you're doing
well everybody
[Music]
wait I read it wrong before but good
then you came up again now I read it
right
son Young
um
foreign
[Music]
York
Shire
um
hey
[Music]
thank you you know
foreign
[Music]
see how smoothly I can read all the
Korean names now yeah yeah yeah I don't
have to bring up Papa go just for the
names anymore
very very convenient alone that is worth
it hmm
yes yes yes
thank you very much part of you Mama
thank you me too you're doing so well
right
good job thank you
um
[Music]
maybe you could come up with like a
Korean uh
um prank name
to prank me with because it's been a
while
blank thanks for the pinky
pinky watching you study Korean inspired
me to study English even more I will try
harder finding blank fighting for team I
believe in you blank
didn't I do that once maybe yeah well
it's been a long time
anyway yeah study English blank just by
watching my streams surely you're all
ready naturally studying English so
I think first step is watching koala
streams and that step you have
accomplished so just gotta go from there
good luck
ogre battle Danke Schoen
um
[Music]
some kind of joke
never heard of Gauntlet classic game
like Diablo but it's more focused on
color play and overall simpler there's a
new remake that looks fun feel free to
reject it rudely
sorry about MTG frames a lot of us we're
looking forward to it I mean don't need
to give up on it uh right away
who knows maybe I just need to
send in my request again and again and
again and eventually maybe it will work
but speaking of Diablo
I was shocked to realize there's already
about to be released
oh my God
oh my God oh my God because it's like
it's pretty much
June
oh yeah [\h__\h] okay oh my God
what do I do
busy busy busy
I'm busy how did updating your PC before
Diablo workout was that the plan
was that the plan
I haven't done it yet
the time
just what the [\h__\h]
I'm gonna I can't I can't
I can't catch up with it
but I don't did the game not work I
think it was just a little bit
um rough and in like Villages wasn't it
but that was more like a problem because
of all the MMORPG elements in it oh I
did fix it
uh ah because I love the graphics yeah
yeah
but I mean it didn't look bad I think
the collab plan yeah I think we can make
that happen sure sure
uh there's like four random super chats
from today squeezed in here
Mike Ray thank you
oh mac and cheese pizza
hello
back to the the Korean ones looking for
the top 10 questions
like friction Duncan Randolph Van Damme
secret identity Studio
German clip catching dust then
it took me a second because I first just
read it like a normal name
I didn't register the meaning
ah when I am small Waba I am not in
charge of such things you have to tell
big voila I I I I I I I can't I don't
have the um ability to upload it I don't
even have thumbs okay or fingers to
begin with I mean look at this
that I can't upload clips
gotta ask a big Wawa
passing of responsibility
no no
she'll do it I'm sure she will do it
eventually
have another Cloud thank you for the
words of a chat funds for forgotten Bill
fees
yeah I have decided to just pay by the
way
pay up it's big Wawa's money anyway
not small hours money
um
I'm just gonna pay it
yeah
yeah whatever [\h__\h] it
I'll I'll I'll bring the money back in
by working harder
yeah [\h__\h] hell
the best part about multiple
personalities is you always have someone
else to blame
someone else's hand is definitely not my
head no no no no
whoa nice
Bam Bam Bam Bam
[Music]
Squidward what love did I do a Squidward
laugh I wouldn't know
yo you know yesterday Sunday
I didn't have anything for like eating
breakfast
so I ended up ordering breakfast because
Sunday nothing's open
and then I was like okay I woke up today
and recently I've been going to the
supermarket or Bakery like every morning
to get like fresh bread breakfast
just something freshly baked this is the
best
so uh I thought okay Sunday I survived
Sunday
it's Monday now let's get some fresh
breakfast so I put on gloves I put on
shoes I go and it's closed
you guys don't please tell me when
there's an Austrian holiday I don't want
to go outside for nothing
ah it's another [\h__\h] holiday what
[\h__\h] holiday is today why is it
always a holiday what the [\h__\h] there's
so many holidays
okay I would probably be happy if I had
a normal job or if I was going to school
thanks to Montauk
huh thanks tomorrow is fine hopefully
Memorial Day in USA or is that like the
same thing
it's not the same thing
it's just I don't really uh
uh you know when I was working in a
normal place you know you just get
um
like you you notice these things because
it's either in a calendar or you know
it's a it's a vacation day so you see it
reflected in the schedule I mean I would
still have to work but some people you
know I don't know it would be there you
would see it and the opening times would
change and all that so you noticing you
know but I'm I'm just like always at
home and I'm just doing my thing hi
chunky monkey what are you doing what
what are you doing
why are you walking oh my God
do not push the Pogba Puck she always
pushes the buck buck
now she's just
okay why are you here
why are you here why you expect EX
checking out my table hmm
it's just walking around my table
now she's just chilling you're killing
hmm
why are you why why I'm so confused when
they visit me while I'm still talking so
much they don't like that normally
and not sometimes she comes in and then
she just says meow and then leaves
without explaining now she's leaving
okay
I said short stream so she thought I was
done
well we're still under two hours
if I do under two hours it's not a short
stream
anything under two hours is a minis mini
and then two to three hours two to four
hours is a short stream
four to six hours is a normal stream
eight hours is a lengthy stream
and eight two
ten hours is a long stream
and 10 to 12 hours is a extreme stream
this is the kiwawa
um
ladder of stream lengths
thinking you know yesterday after having
a mental breakdown over the fact that I
streamed the whole day 10 hours
and would have personally liked to
continue even longer to run away from
all my
[Music]
um
duties but I realized
that you know I I basically in that one
day
no hate or no shade but I was just
trying to make myself feel better
because like
um I took two days off before that right
and I felt like I had to stream longer
to makeup for not streaming for two days
or so but generally I also couldn't stop
myself but you know I kind of want to
make up for it but in that one day I
streamed as much as many uh and members
do in the whole week
hahaha so which I I'm not saying that
that's not enough I'm saying that that's
why I shouldn't feel like bad about
how supposedly little I streamed this
last week
and I I could do one stream of 10 hours
in a week and I could say okay that's it
I'm calling it a day
I'm all calling it a week this is enough
content like divide divided by I don't
know
bye take take two and a half or three
hour streams out of those ten hours and
I could fill a whole week
um
no no no no I'm not even thinking about
good no no no no no no no generally
there's no shade or no hate it's more
healthy anyway I can't even get anything
done
I can't get [\h__\h] done streaming like
this
um
but there's like you know a lot of
members who stream like maybe two to
three to four hours and that's like way
more healthy
that's so much more healthy
for their lives their private lives and
getting [\h__\h] done
and their voices and all that um
yeah I'm on par with whole Japan's
dreamers yeah that's a bit closer too
um
uh yeah so
I just I don't know I was like wait wait
wait wait why am I why am I feeling bad
about how little I stream and then I
have to make up for it no no no I should
I don't have to but I don't know
but I can't
can't talk I don't know to our tutk
stream like once I am in cot it's just
never ending there's so much you have to
do
or you can do it's you how can anyone
stop themselves
you can't do a short totk stream it's
like literally impossible that's why
even though I would have liked to
continue playing today I had to force
myself to play something else
um
yeah
yeah yeah
I did watch some tltk content though
I watched some Nintendo videos and oh I
watched a video about the best
um attachments to
um Shields
uh yeah
some cool fusions that
you didn't know yet stuff like that no
but about I'm about to watch a video of
I just already opened the tab to watch
it afterwards because I got it
recommended when I was about to start
the Stream
uh flurry Rush versus the fastest enemy
in the game AKA Adder the Gloom hands I
wanna watch that
um don't handle is just a
he's so far behind and he does so many
other things besides doing the story he
just finished the temple right the first
temple now you know what he just did he
went to the [\h__\h] maze he did the Maze
and now he wants to do the maze in the
sky as well because now he's curious
ah there's so many other things come on
he doesn't do the storm by which I
understand because he wants to do 100
and he's trying to
like even it out the interesting things
you know
uh yeah he's taking his time and he
wants things to be like
balanced
content-wise but I feel like but I feel
like he doesn't even there's so many
important things
that he has no idea about yet
he hasn't even gone to the the place
that tells you the order of the memories
but already watched
you know random ass memories on his own
I did that right away because like
um she tells you right after you watch
the first memory
she tells you to
um go with her to the those ruins right
the quest tells you
she encourages you
back
[Music]
flesh streamer why well he's not a
streamer he makes videos
um
but um
he'll get there he will get there
hopefully
hopefully hopefully hopefully
but he already has like 200 koroks just
by being in mostly the first uh area and
the the the snow areas
that's like he does everything so
thoroughly holy [\h__\h]
oh my God
I only have over 100 in total I don't
think I've even gotten a hundred yet
some of them are story locked yeah yeah
I understand I understand and then that
list is not even like all memories like
the the archive it's not even all
memories some of them in between are
just normal like story thingies
um
yeah right oh there's a Kodak mask but
he probably doesn't even realize that
there like all these masks exist again
um in the game
yeah
oh well
let's continue we're almost done with
the study stream ones uh
oh yeah so every another cult everything
you
um
[Music]
you're the best thank you so much you're
crazy you crazy Abby
ha
num yum yum yum yum yum yum make you
chicken
my beloved baby thank you
and then we have a pinky from will adult
thank you for the pinky
ah
you just woke back up with the kisses
good morning not wanting to check your
mail because bills are scary is too
relatable yeah
I looked I looked into my
post box today I saw a new letter in it
and you know what I did
I closed it and I finned feigned
ignorance
but I
don't know
it's not like not like if I would have
got like carried it up with me in that
moment as if I would have paid it right
away
that's a neat trick right and just close
it
just closed it just just no no no it's
not taxes no although
that's yeah something I have to pay
still I will pay it after the stream
I'll pay it after the stream my tax lady
wrote me one and a half weeks ago a
reminder to pay my upfront
taxes part of it
um
and update my documents
yeah but I feel like I just paid the
ones from like before like I feel like I
just made a payment so I don't want to
already make another payment
but okay
be a good citizen and pay or else
I I am a good citizen I I even pay for
Photoshop
laughs
you need to listen to your Just Do It
video so true so true
ah nobody wants to pay taxes yeah
especially after my brother once told me
because he did this kind of accounting
job for a while he once told me
how when your accountant tells you it's
time to pay up
um it it's not that urgent most of the
time
you can take your time one day I mean my
accountant also told me that
you know like months later is still okay
I have to pay this now okay
fine too is what she told me last year
in I don't know may or so
you have until October to pay this
something like that no no penalty no oh
no I don't get it
I don't get it it's just really really
like you have a long long long time to
take your time
my accountant told me to hmm
no I don't I don't understand this might
might be different here
pineapple
mean Apple
pineapple pineapple pineapple Pine
pineapple pineapple
pineapple
Pine yeah
you've got that pineapple
well just a song I have in my hand
I don't know what that song was
that song
you can't have pineapple without ham I
think you can have pineapple with bacon
too
[Music]
no no no
I don't remember it
bye
pineapple
pineapple pineapple papaya
it's a song
with some K-pop I think
hmm oh what was I
um
that's that's it
that's it
I want to ride my pan pineapple I want
to ride my Pine no that's that's that's
that's not even the lyrics of that song
is it
right my what
I want to ride my what was that
human ity
foolish
Ambitions you will have
no not by Circle
what if I don't know
we are confused beings we need to follow
the guidance of uh God Wawa
what does she say
thank you okay thank you
sure sure sure Mike sure I I believe you
because this is just small lava
I want to ride my bike bicycle I want to
ride my bike I want to ride my bicycle I
want to ride it where I like
something feels off there
ow like little pinkies
thank you please do not compare kfp with
others kfp
the main point of this acting is to make
me look like a clown and make everyone
laugh I don't want to hurt anyone uh an
outstand hurt really bad all right I
think it's time to stop recommending for
now on no I'm so very sorry don't worry
about it it's not boss it's me I'm out
of ideas because last time I didn't know
how to respond so I'm sorry everyone on
kfp and boss you ran out of ideas
no but there's so many games out there
it's okay though if you don't want to do
it anymore don't worry about it
it was fun while it lasted thank you so
much ow for two pinkies it makes a kiss
for you
thank you
[Laughter]
um
don't steal your mom's credit card or is
it mine are you saying it's mine I don't
have a credit card maybe I don't have it
because you stole it
thank you indeed I agree
thank you for the support
[Music]
thank you you're starting your PhD in AI
in September
and happy late birthday congratulations
well good luck with your PhD it must
take a while
downstairs
[Music]
and my angel and my God I don't know in
my head somehow it was kind of the same
thing
um
but Angel sounds kind of cuter
I'll take it thank you blank
[Music]
you're an angel too angel angel
who is blessing everybody with
memberships
everybody's like oh oh my God a gift
from the heavens
brought upon me I have been blessed
the god of of membership gifting
thank you
[Music]
May believe thanks for the pinky embrace
the words of our Phoenix goddess Kiara
takanashi amen lay her wisdom guide us
kfp let you mean Crush our enemies see
them driven before us and hear the
Lamentations of the women
Crusher and I feel like today
you know I was trying to save people but
the one behind those
terrible terrible
accidents that we have witnessed today
must have been
big Wawa
she is God
it was her
she's evil
the devs are to blame okay I mean yeah
sure yeah yeah I wasn't trying to blame
big while no no yeah it's the deaths to
death it's the deaths
if evil why hot
true see makes no sense it's deaths
after all not kiwawa yeah
thanks for the pinky pray to the one and
only true God takanasi kimawa Viva lucky
glory to the all-powerful
Eternal Divine Phoenix goddess guava is
love Wawa is life hashtag vote forever
unknown you're you're so deep
in the cult
nothing could ever save you
you're absolutely lost
there's no saving you
and that's a good thing
and you at least you like um you may be
lost but you're able to deal with it in
still a controlled and and positive way
yes nothing wavers your faith
lost but also saved I I understand yeah
you were lost but you were found
sure yeah yeah keep on telling yourself
that guys
that's what a cult member would say
sorry
[Music]
um
thank you
soon
um
kill big Phantom this is from today but
thank you Danke Schoen it's just mixed
in here I'll read it while it's here and
crayons 80. thank you
thank you foreign
[Music]
how can I watch Hulu talk and drink out
of the mug while watching holotalk if I
use the mug as my new office Monk
we'll bring it back from the office
after you're leaving the office
if whole talk watches outside it happens
outside of your work hours
should have bought two mugs I mean you
can put the sticker on a on a white mug
and drink out of it too
but don't don't wash the outside don't
only watch the inside with your hand
maybe then the sticker will not be
damaged I don't know
um
this is it
humanity is finished
I like the sound of that
next is this Zelda t-o-t-k from
yesterday
a catching up
hmm
who would have known it would be small
mama
to get big Wawa back on track
smoothies
oh what's the big sneeze
you're doing great am I I think I am
indeed thank you
sometimes
thank you thank you thank you thank you
oh thank you thank you thank you thank
you
[Music]
Jacob 4700
foreign
um
Sheldon thank you for the right to the
chat oh
such a weird number I wonder if if
there's a meaning behind it
hello Kiana can you whisper it colors
your kfb Discord Jenkins it would make a
certain Sunshine's day
fine I guess you are my little kfb disco
champion
huh
why
I don't understand
[Music]
it's not even a name it's just a
hmm
I was relaxing oh
small Wawa ASMR
ah oh oh it's a reference I told this
quick ah
[Music]
now I get it somehow I didn't make that
connection
okay
thank you Sheldon mwah
everyday
thank you
totally German stream flat Sea Fox
thanks for the pinky I left Japan
yesterday after a much needed vacation
it was a great experience but it also
made me want to travel more austro seems
very appealing to me maybe because of
you would you recommend any places there
Duncan
so yeah I think I I touched upon this
subject
uh during my stream I was like oh you
should go somewhere else
if you especially if you've never been
to Europe like I don't know which places
you've been to until now but
I might recommend you oh no Italy
Switzerland
France
wherever
because
[Music]
I don't want you to be disappointed
there's cooler places
I feel like Austria is very pretty but
there's not much to do I mean I mean
yeah I mean you can walk around and look
at
all sides yeah but I don't know I just
don't want you to be disappointed but
yeah Italy I think is cooler
laughs
but if you want to come then I guess
um
I mean people always recently talk about
Innsbruck
but I would say
uh hashtag science book obviously the
capital Vienna
and there's many other pretty places but
I haven't even seen many places in
Austria
but I think
probably
like
down there in the south of Austria
there's some some pretty places too
I think Hmm
it also depends on the season and what
exactly you want to see do you want to
see
like Austria in the winter because
that's very pretty
then you should check out like all the
Christmas markets
or do you want to go in the summer it's
also nice in the summer then you should
go to an area that has a lot of our
beautiful lakes
Maybe
we have many beautiful lakes
y Fox thank you anyway
Lily thank you for the pinky hecka I
don't know if you remember the Kiwi kfp
member moving to Germany but just wanted
to let you know I'm settling when well
eating my Sparkle and separating my
rubbish properly
um
yeah I also talked about this one on
stream but I now really want to eat some
sparkle
ah asparagus by the way in German is
yeah
I only like the green one by the way
however I'm saying that while never
having eaten the white one before
but I just I just have this feeling
I once ate the green one and I was like
okay I like the green one actually
but I just feel like I wouldn't like the
white
does it taste the same green is better
right I think a lot of people agree with
that but there's like this classic uh
asparagus dish
here like the classic way of eating it
and the classic one is with the white
asparagus
the white one with this like hollandaise
sauce
but it seems like most people agree with
me
the green one is better
oh there you look there you go then
ah maybe for the soup you you also use
the white one though because it's always
white I always see it being white
Mmm Yeah potato ham butter hollandaise
yeah
is that an
um that dish is it from the Netherlands
didn't know there was white ones we
didn't know
seems it looks like such a simple dish
but
um
you always make that one with white
well I I like the green one yeah like
grilled green asparagus
or even with pasta yum so good
oh good so good
so good I should try it once though I
mean you guys say that it's like a bit
more of a
Woody wooden taste hot sick
well but the base taste does it still
like taste like asparagus though
wooden taster that sounds weird
with poison oh
purple asparagus tastes nuttier I've
never seen purple one
laughs
they're bigger and more Woody roasting
asparagus with a drizzle of olive oil
and some pepper yeah
um
devices
yeah I love the tips of the sparkle for
some reason hey
so good you get it you guys get it
okay
soon I think I have good intuition
thinking that I wouldn't like the white
one usually I'm right with my intuition
you know
hey
um
[Music]
today is my Revival day I will miss my
bucket but I will make this step forward
for the glory of kfp thank you so much
for that two years full of great streams
fun and a lot of memories and looking
forward to what awaits us in the future
congratulations
[Music]
a bucket no more bucket bye bye sayonara
bucket you should put it on on the Shelf
give it its own shelf space
your old bucket
you can look back to it and be like ah
that was that was a comfortable time I
was just chilling I was just vibing in
my bucket so comfy
now you're a big chicken
so cute
thank you for supporting me for such a
long time
well who knows eventually you know there
will be even more member badges who know
what happens
you might see the bucket again or or who
knows
you might get burnt to crisp into ashes
we will find out in the future it will
be a surprise
but you guys are
into that right you guys that's what you
joined for right
yeah just an ash pile
it will be so confusing
foreign
I don't know it could also be a golden
and a rainbow chicken
I still got time to think but remind me
guys you by the way you didn't remind me
of using the new function
in tutk
I'm gonna ask you guys to remind me but
you didn't remind me you forgot
oh God
no no not like within tutk but our
applications new function
no so
God damn it
we have to try it remind me remind me
another time
we could do it oh
[Music]
maybe maybe oh wait a second
how about members watch along tomorrow
guys are you okay with that
something I don't know what
how about 8 P.M kiwawa time so now minus
one hour and 21 minutes
we watch something and remind me to use
my new function please
I knew my new thing okay
okay I have to use it
I don't know what to watch I'll I'll
I'll think about it maybe maybe you guys
can
um I'll make a community post
you guys certainly already have
recommended things to me before
um
I don't know what we're watching no Star
Wars no more wait I guess now we could
watch Mario movie together
hmm
I guess so but I already watched it
I don't know I don't want I'd prefer
watching something new
[Music]
Indiana Jones
Terminator
[Applause]
[Music]
not impressed
what the [\h__\h] is Spaceballs what is that
look it up
oh
Commando wait is that the one with
Melissa Milano Spain spells for me what
the [\h__\h] are you guys recommending me
1987's baseball sci-fi
okay but this one looks kind of like
comedy science but like looks ridiculous
who are these what
it's like that one movie that we watched
but in sci-fi setting
ridiculous
good I love Spaceballs
it's a parody of Star Wars oh
so they're making fun of it
hmm
[Music]
well now you got me hooked
hmm
they're making fun with it sure
[Music]
uh-huh
ah tomship surprise battle guys that's
also this is like a German movie that I
really enjoyed that also makes fun I
guess of
Star Wars and
Maybe Star Trek 2 I don't know
I watched that and many many years ago
hmm it is really funny yeah
space taxi to the sky
foreign
spread your legs now close them up again
and you are out
hahaha
and but I don't know where I think we
should watch that but it's a German
movie and I think last time I looked it
up uh it was like oh no I I don't know
where you could watch it
but you guys would love that
and I wouldn't mind watching that one
again it's been 20 years
um there should be I think there's maybe
no dub but there should be a sub title
version I have it on Amazon Prime but
mine's German Amazon wait I'll give you
the title and you guys look it up on
your Amazon
on your American Canadian Australian
whatever Amazon and can you check if it
comes up
can I watch
I'll type it in English
maybe they have it
oh it might be on German Netflix
not available in my region
well check on no no check on your Google
for me it just gives me providers that
are in my region Netflix has it my my
regions Netflix has it it seems like
do you guys wanna
make an effort to watch it with me
because I think you guys would love it
the intention this looks awful no
[Music]
I love it okay
for once for once let me introduce you
guys to something
it looks so bad what no I mean it's a
parody as well
from like some really famous German
Comedians and actors
oh yeah but looking at it it's more I
think of a Star Trek parody
I doubt the human will translate well to
English
that is possible yeah
um
[Laughter]
but I watch English and Japanese things
and all that with subtitles too and I
mean I get it
most of the time and even things that I
don't get I mean they're still enjoyable
[Music]
yes are not committed to the cult
quite disappointing
okay
different movie you little shits
ah
thank you to the ones who were down to
do it
y'all the real ones
um
[Music]
maybe maybe I should have never watched
cats with you guys seems like that has
kind of like tainted our relationship
yeah bully movies are funny
no if you don't watch my space parody
movie I don't watch your space part
[Music]
true true
damaged you oh man
um
I want to watch Lord of the Rings
[Laughter]
to be a movie
P movie is a [\h__\h] joke
um I'll make a poll Maybe
on my community board
but
I'll first uh after the stream maybe
take some more recommendations on
Twitter
and then I'll look at the ones that are
interesting to me and then I'll make a
poll
Democrats
democracy democracy
[Music]
you were both Spaceballs you will not if
it's not in the poll in the first place
[Music]
don't put the beat movie it will win
yeah it seems like whenever if I would
put like a joke in there everybody would
go for the joke so let's not do that
hmm
I wonder if there's like any kind of
like
Titanic level
legendary movie that I haven't seen yet
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
I would be more interested in Jurassic
Park but I think I've seen the first
wait
guys hi
hi baby
you know what's recently come out in the
in the cinema
where I'm not sure if I watched the
prequels
man Guardians of the Galaxy
the the third one came out right and I'm
I know I watched at least the first one
but I don't know if I watched the second
one
when that would be really good if I
could watch it then I could finally
watch the third one in the cinema before
it is gone
[Music]
um
I liked the first one I I thought it was
good even though I didn't know much
about the Marvel Universe at all but you
can skip in between movies but they're
all very good
um
no Marvel why I'm not a big like fan of
Marvel and whatever that other company
was called but but uh
I mean some of them are
cool every once in a while
ah DC
oh I forgot
[Music]
I'll put it in the poll okay
and then you guys can also decide
against it if you don't want to watch it
with me democracy
democracy
Fair
okay
I I I I
um Jurassic Park but are you guys asking
me to watch the first one because I've
seen the first one as a child
why are you asking me to watch a
different one
[Music]
I'm talking too chunky
the first one do you remember it I mean
there were dinosaurs and they attacked
humans
well
yeah
[Music]
oh
she has such a funny way of purring
weird usually
[Music]
foreign
she's a pigeon yeah
yeah
he's a sweet idea she is she's so sweet
but she's so stupid too because like
um uh for a while you know um because
smoothie always gets wet food in the
morning and Chunky Monkey doesn't want
wet food but I felt bad for her that she
never got something special and she's
always like always asking for something
and I'm like well you don't eat wet food
so what am I supposed to do so you know
at some point I started giving her
um like sometimes not every day but
sometimes I would give her treats in the
morning
those stick treats that that not the not
the liquid ones just uh actually a
little solid sticks treats and she would
um actually enjoy it in the morning I
would crack it into small pieces
yeah she would enjoy don't eat the
plastic Junkie
but now yeah like jerky now
she's still like in the morning like I
want something too and I give her the
snack and she eats one piece and then
she leaves it like one tiny like one
millimeter piece
and then she's like I don't wanna
anymore she walks away
I opened a whole stick for her and she
doesn't eat it at all
she's sick of it
yeah I don't know what she wants from me
difficult cat yeah she's a diva
saving the rest of it I thought so so I
left it and I offered it to her
throughout the day on several occasions
and she doesn't want it
this happened
several days now and she's she's weird
she's she's taking shade under my table
lying under my table right now
it's relaxing
she's on vacation mode
and you what are you doing hmm
that's what your baby
um no they don't really eat each other's
snacks this movie also didn't want to
eat the rest of the stick
uh
anyway
I bought a different type of snack
actually at the pet uh food shop so I'll
try that on her
different one
anyway where was I
where was I
have to scroll because I had to reopen
it oh I think somewhere here
foreign
[Music]
it's been a little over a year since I
started watching you and the first thing
I did was binge watch your Skyward Sword
series
wait so I a little over a year ago when
you started watching me what what I was
like actively streaming was that or did
you just like I was doing something else
and and you just went with that with the
words
but yeah that was I think around that
time we had fun with that too while also
being frustrated
I love watching you play Zelda and see
Panic draw can't wait to see you in
person in L.A ah yeah I've played a
couple of Zelda games on my channel
until now and this one so far doesn't
even have that much Panic even though I
was panicking before I watched the Bots
thank you I was panicking before I
started playing tltk I was like worried
about playing it that I would be not
good at it
but turned out it was actually fine
I mean I think my my my couple of panic
moments are
um you know whenever I get startled by a
tree or started by something else
I'm just easily startled
and I mean the Gloom hands honestly they
make everybody Panic even Dom tendo
especially the first time
so I don't think you can blame someone
for panicking about the Gloom hands
everybody panics
hmm
but generally you guys have also been
praising me for playing the game so well
and I'm very happy about that thank you
[Music]
yeah so I hope that after uh tltk we can
play another Zelda game I'm thinking oh
uh Ocarina of Time or Majora's Mask or
something like that
she left the room suddenly hmm
I'm always open for more
Zelda games oh yeah Twilight Princess
could also be a possibility
Ocarina of Time and then Majora's Mask
makes sense
oh okay we can do Ocarina of Time
Majora's Mask and then Twilight Princess
hmm
Twilight Princess I'm I'm interested in
because
I remember seeing my brother play it
and it just it just looked too spooky to
me
very very spooky
but now that I am mature enough I think
I can handle it
oh yeah I ended up buying it didn't I oh
thank God
I did buy that one I think it is on my
Wii U
H thank God
what what
hmm
huh
she's she's I don't know curious very
curious today
zero nine one one two Duncan Alex Tavera
Duncan
um
I have a random dumb question if I want
to get custom Ayah I already answered
that so I'm gonna skip it thanks for the
red super chat thank you awesome stream
today but gotta go for now have to
prepare a barbecue for family and
friends for Memorial weekend have a
great night and food yourself oh I want
to do barbecue with my friends too
but
the season has just begun
there is still much time for barbecue
no need to fret just yet
[Music]
um
do you know how to work a barbecue no
but I feel like I could
work it
[Music]
I just wanna eat sausages most of the
time
I mean the steak would be fine too
though
yeah
and coin corn on the cob
please
I want the coin
actually I I do have two
um vacuum packed corn crops in my fridge
for like a month or two now but it's
still uh good for another two or three
months
so should be fine
cup yeah it's the emergency corn but
um I always forget about it
yes it is I think maybe from oh no wait
no not necessarily from that stream
but probably
yeah
the corn cup Pizza stream
yummy corn grilled with butter sprinkle
some salt
yeah I had some leftovers I made pizza
with it
and look I mean pasta
[Music]
all those I guess over now because the
weekend is over
I hope it was yummy
okay thank you for the pinky some time
ago I got myself a play mat ah I also
read this that's compliment for you the
cute out cuteness transcends everything
now I want to get a custom card sleeve
but can decide on the art maybe next
month wallpaper
wait how long is this month 40 or 41.
31. oh
please don't make corn on pizza or else
I'm canceling my membership
uh
don't tell him I guess
don't don't tell him
he's lacking critical information
what the [\h__\h] pudding
what do you mean not again
yeah I mean how could you not know
what I will I will I will have to be
honest with you
I will make
pizza with corn
throughout my life many many more times
what was I saying though
Aya wallpaper so it's pretty one day so
yeah wallpaper coming soon
but I don't think I've seen
um this one's actually like it was kind
of last minute
I had the artist lined up but I didn't
give instructions until pretty
pretty late
oh oh but wait yes oh it's really good
it's really good I just looked back on
the draft that I saw
sometimes I don't know like because they
they're the artist is always like hey
what what theme would you like and I I
often don't know
well that should come up with and this
one's pretty random too I don't know
you guys are welcome to give me ideas
too
I think you like the theme but
um I I just didn't know what to do like
with June
sometimes if something special is
happening I like it to be
um related to whatever is happening
in that month
but June for me
I had no idea honestly
okay you'll see it's just something
random not really related to June
but it will be cute
on the motorcycle in cyberpunk Miami
Beach Fever Night setting
why not why not
ah
[Music]
um
why have I gotten so slow
suddenly
I feel
my throat and my voice is very dry today
man
um
sorry to hear you ha you're having
trouble getting us getting good food for
your cartos I've just had to switch
switch to
anti-allergy prescription food good news
they love it bad news it's ridiculously
expensive
chunkers turned on the printer
good job chunkers but I don't need the
printer now
sometimes it jumps on the printer and
she turns it on
let her print
what is she cooking she's what is she
printing is the right question
maybe she's printing her resume
oh
it's making sounds
it's making funny sounds
I'm trying to print
what are you trying to
are you trying to are you trying to copy
or scan your butt um
I like your floppy butt
I got you
spankenheim a kiss from from chunky
wonky perhaps
[Music]
special cat kiss
don't tell your cat about it
she's so soft
you know she's always purring I just
have to look at her and she will purr
okay donkey monkey read this with me mac
billion thank you
mmm
wonderful
Alex is sure
gamer than 92 Junction
holiday the one that started the tangent
about Elizabeth yum
and what okay thank you
she didn't know
but she likes that fact
okay
superchat from today
conjunction
um
I have to hold her up to the microphone
foreign
what's up
thank you for the pinky
that thing I've never eaten is so gross
I just know no need to ever try it but
yeah I feel it while pineapple pizza
isn't my favorite kind of pizza I just
don't get that word Obsession have about
hating it right I think it's like a
they're just trying to be cool thing
um
they just think they're sad they're so
stuck with their opinion because they
think pineapple doesn't belong on pizza
because it sounds weird at first maybe
if you've never tried it yeah
yes Mimi and edgy
I I don't know I mean if you like if you
don't like pineapple generally then I
get it then it makes sense
but if you do like pineapple in general
then I think you would enjoy it on pizza
okay I'm gonna let chunky wonky go
because she's getting squirmy
you don't like the idea of hot pineapple
but it's not even that hot
it might not be cold but whenever I eat
pineapple pizza
it's just like medium warm like warm
most of the time and and and and and
trust me it's not that weird really
it's like eating you know
um you know how there's like
um
uh fried
bananas and all that stuff as desserts
as well
but that stuff is yummy too
like from the when I order from the
Chinese place the fried banana bananas
dessert is so good the honey
honey the fried whatever banana so good
[Music]
gotta give it a chance yeah
but only eat pepperoni for real for real
they don't experiment at all
if they only eat like pepperoni pizza
there's so much more that's possible
with pizza man
and I mean okay tuna and pineapple pizza
may not be like like like a like the OG
lineup of Italian pizzas but tuna pizza
for example is definitely up there and
tuna Pizza even even tuna Pizza is like
denied by so many people
while it's just because for some reason
it has made it over to America I guess
mostly but tuna Pizza is really
um
please go to Italian restaurant I say it
every time go to Italian restaurant and
order a tunnel
please please please please please
please please please just do it I also
don't like seafood but tondo is another
story
it's so good
it's it's a classic so you can't even
criticize me for putting something
supposedly wrong on a pizza because it's
a classic
if especially if you can get an
authentic one then it's amazing
not other fish I do like some other fish
too I just don't like you know anything
that goes beyond fish most of the time
the only one more thing that I can
tolerate I guess is uh eel
unless it's raw
yeah I don't eat shrimp I don't eat crab
I don't eat squid
I don't eat clams or whatever
nothing
and no nothing normal fish uh raw also
no no
but yeah I I I I I don't enjoy being
against Seafood because it always looks
so good and then often on vacation
especially like the restaurants that we
would go to
um with rmt for example would be like
seafood focused a lot of the time and
then there's just not so much good stuff
from me
um
thank you I'm glad you had fun at
MomoCon I've heard that the panel with
mermaid and crony
was absolutely crazily packed that they
opened up the the second like floor the
balcony
apparently
it didn't uh think
so many people
and it was like 2500
seats panel room I think
that's crazy
thank you guys for coming in so many
numbers I wasn't there but thank you
[Music]
foreign
I would like to see them too
I got a commission of you and Valencia
Lynn said Mama con what
me
what is it is it ready
does it exist yet
or is it gonna come later
you already tweeted it
the [\h__\h] is it in my art tag
I need to see it
wait wasn't this cute Christina wants
Anita cluster
oh my God
no Chris saw anything
oh that's cute that's so cute
okay scrolling scrolling
um
which one is it
this one's so good
which one
when did you upload it ah I see this one
ah it's a sketchy
almost I almost missed it
because it's just like a monochrome
it is pretty
cute and I'm holding a chicken
ah the necklace says kfp
thank you it's pretty
[Music]
finished the
almost finished
I already retweeted that now but you
know the the song that mikuchi covered
with the windy
the windiness
for once you know for once I'm I'm
having a short stream let me keep it
short
um
for the pinky pineapple belongs to a
pizza fight me it's delicious combined
with ham or pepperoni thank you I
wouldn't combine with pepperoni if you
mean salami
um what do you have or or bacon but sure
sure
why not
thank you for understanding and getting
it but you're donating an URL and I
guess you're you know you're from this
area I think in Europe it's pretty
accepted generally
oh
even if you don't like it it's pretty
accepted as a thing overall Maxwell the
first time question cougar is 48 Duncan
um
super thanks ah
I feel like we were asked possibly to
turn it off generally because I think I
had it on and then it was turned off so
no need for that
it's okay we we don't need it we'll just
have normal super chats that's fine
[Music]
um
yeah pineapple is one of the most light
toppings in Austrian Germany
it's true it's true it is true
all my friends like it I think my whole
friend Circle likes it
[Music]
um
blank thanks for the pinky
there was a special pizza with
marshmallow called snowy pizza at one of
the pizza stores in Thailand pineapple
is much better compared to snowy oh
yeah as I said I don't really like
marshmallow so
and you also say it's not that good
I believe you
um
I don't know about that sounds kind of
blah
blah that's a good
she's on edge right now what did you do
did you go to the toilet
you're always on edge when you're on the
toilet afterwards
cubic Phantom
tanks
thank you
[Music]
and green ghost thanks for the recipe
chat how did kiwawa in the US we are
celebrating Memorial Day it's a day to
honor our award that oh so it is very
different from our holiday today
those who have died defending us it's
different than Veterans Day in that
Veterans Day celebrates those of us who
still serve and live while Memorial Day
only those who died
oh I didn't know that that was the day
today
I mean I've heard of these kind of
holidays but I didn't know that was
today what's your holiday some like
Christian thing
Jesus did something
I don't know what
[Music]
um
it's just one of those days
thank you angry ghosts for educating me
thank you soon
[Music]
super snake mommy thanks for the pinky
hi Kevin finally got around buying my
tickets for the Ian concert
unfortunately it's just a streaming
ticket but I'm okay with that that will
be fun too I'm I'm 100 sure I'll return
you on from the comfort of my help
looking forward to seeing you on the big
stage I love you thank you thank you
Sean I love you too and please enjoy it
it's getting closer and closer day by
day and it feels like right now my
throat is burning is it all the orange
juice I've been drinking today I think
so
I think orange juice is not really good
for my fruit but I just wanted something
juicy
um
the acidic
[\h__\h]
yeah
lunchbox
for Chad
since you learned about lava today
depending on various factors like how
fast it cools or if it solidifies under
or above the surface it can become
different rocks such as Grand granite
from mice or obsidian
is real
Syrian Israel
oh
I thought it was I feel like I thought
it was something like you know donut
do you need a diamond pickaxe IRL to
farm obsidian
I don't know what's the German name of
obsidian maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe
maybe maybe it was probably just
obsidian
oh it's just obsidian
um I don't know if I
find but maybe I did I just I know like
by playing Minecraft you know Minecraft
brain rods and since obsidian was like
such a special product that also like
was blowing purple it just felt
otherworldly you know what I mean
and made me think
maybe it's something
from not from the real one yeah you use
it to make a portal to the underworld
after all
it just doesn't it even the name sounds
just too Fantastical like fan yeah yeah
fantasy like yeah
yeah that's what I mean thank you for
understanding
um
I think I've read that word before
German
bin Stein what the [\h__\h]
I've never read it in German before only
in
English
[Music]
yeah and well Granite Granite dinos
Granite interesting
yesterday was a long day for Ina number
two thank you thank you yeah I saw
everybody was playing it
and while I was playing tltk
what was that did that uh like Outlast
trials collab happened while I was
playing
I feel like it didn't
ah
what
was the night before oh what the [\h__\h]
I felt like it happened while I was
streaming
oh I'm confused I'm confused
is just making everything so blurry and
weird
surprised you know about it I saw one
clip
and I saw a message from management
[Music]
about
maybe not playing it anymore because of
you know
private parts
but I was I was just thinking when I saw
that message well
we haven't received such a message after
Bale's played uh genital jousting kind
of double standards don't you think
I have yet to see such a message after
genital jousting
maybe I guess the ones in outlast trials
look more realistic yeah
um and and YouTube could
be more
uh strict with realistic PPS versus uh
unrealistic ones
um
but I would say that the things that
happen in genital jousting are even more
terrifying and and and painful to watch
especially for
men than Outlast trials am I wrong
yeah I have heard that
it gets like very injured
and all kinds of crazy [\h__\h] happens so
I I I I I I don't think that's
um
yeah
so uh yeah no thank you
no thank you
it's got cute visuals in theory
it gets bright and it's pastel colored
and all the comic look but no
no
I'm not gonna play it no no no I told
you already
um
the cute visual says and you know I mean
like you know
I mean
in comparison to outlast trials
obviously
yeah anyway
ah where was I I'm almost done come on
let's go
uh where was I
um
[Music]
yeah oh man but I don't think you guys
feel the same way about my tltk
playthrough as I feel about Dom tando's
trtk playthrough
cause like you could not complain about
me not making progress
I'm constantly making progress
I don't know what there is to complain
about in my tftk playthrough I don't
think there's anything
I have the perfect the most ideal the
most efficient
tltk stream
period
out of everyone in the world
not enough dance gameplay yeah true true
um
we can go back
uh if there's something interesting
again like you know those those statues
last time we went down we had a purpose
right now I don't really have a purpose
I do want to make one stream that where
I do the Colosseum and maybe some other
non-story related things and I would
also say like hey this this part is lure
free so you don't get spoiled
um the only thing you will see you know
is like you know the underground and all
that
um and I want to do uh yeah some things
that are not Story related
especially the Colosseum
at some point
um
yeah making too much progress that could
be the only problem
yeah I also don't want to do the the
Koga said true true true we could do
that I'm not in a not spoiler uh stream
because that those are spoilers but
um true that is currently our purpose
down there
[Music]
maybe we can do that soon
um I'm gonna make a bag
Brewster
lunchbox
wait I read those
um
[Music]
we're done I'm gonna go cook now
yeah and pay my taxes I guess
[Music]
just kidding thank you guys for watching
today I'll see you in the member stream
tomorrow we'll watch a movie you are
welcome to send me serious suggestions
uh on Twitter
and I will look what's tickles my fancy
and put it in a poll
um
[Music]
in German we say
nothing
[Music]
she is so so weird so needy cute I'm
gonna cuddle chunky wonky here
bye bye she's saying goodbye too bye bye
[Music]
oh
I'm right now
[Music]
foreign