[Music]
they let R br
intoxicating DJ keep
[Music]
playing
dancing sry so emotion
[Music]
feel it R me
sh feel it me
B
[Music]
honey night is
it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
dancing sry about so emotion
K
oh and let me shut up the
[Music]
TV my
hello yeah know let me change the things
obviously we are not playing against
nevland right now
but it looks like we will play against
the Netherlands again how funny because
it seems like they won their match
against Romania right they uh uh Romania
didn't suddenly get a million goals out
of nowhere pretty sure they
won so if we win against turkey today we
will play against Neverland again which
it could I I just because we won last
time doesn't mean that we WN win
again um but yeah uh there's some people
who are maybe doubting that we will win
but guys you know whose stream you're
watching
here first of all wa will always believe
in Austria now and second of
all last time Austria played against
turkey not so long ago a few weeks ago
or so we won six to one six to one
against
turkey guys remember that day I didn't
watch it but it happened it's in the
history
books you guys don't have the best
reputation right now so okay let's do a
bet who will win don't jinx people have
been saying that last time too and I
didn't really jinx
it a little bit of flum a little bit of
flum first of all also I don't know I
started I'm starting to stream a little
bit earlier than last time because I
wanted to talk a little bit obviously I
have not been here the past few days um
so thank you for waiting for me sorry
I'm kind of like not
there uh this whole month will be a
little bit difficult I will not like
take the whole month off but I'm
streaming less obviously
so that's how it is also austrial turkey
and the
thae the once was a a turkey and an
Austria and a Tha they walked into a bar
and the
turkey tied up the
Austria
H it can't end oh you're right oh they
will just extend forever and ever and
ever and ever oh wait that's interesting
I I I realized that yeah I was thinking
about it the like the other day I was
like wait this time we can't tie right
so somebody has to move on so this could
be long but I I think not
necessarily I we'll just get like
endless elf meta season right elf met
season wait I have my ears on a one
ear that ear is still here so many
accessories I'm I've been using lot of
accessories accidentally click turkey
okay let's do it again because uh
there's no tie there's no
tie who will win
Austria turkey
y so I've been in Germany these past
days and Germany you know is very hyped
about football of course
and
uh I can't believe I'm So Into football
but I've been talking with everyone
everyone about football taxi drivers you
know
but also people Rand I'm dragging
friends into it
too yesterday for lunch was it yesterday
yeah yesterday for lunch uh I I dragged
our our lunch conversation I I dragged
football into it there was um I had a I
had a Netherlands friend sitting next to
me so I was kind of roasting her and I
was like are you watching football and
she's like no and I'm like oh my God
like
you guys you guys are supposed to be
good but you lost against us Austria
kind of [\h__\h] you up and all that but
we might play against again against each
other that's exciting
too and me me talking to her about that
kind of seems to have gotten her into it
too because um she sent me a message she
sent me a message uh about Netherlands
winning against
Romania and and was like oh I guess this
means we're going to be playing against
each other again and yes that's exactly
what it means
probably yeah
he you guys you never guys I can't
believe we have to play against each
other again I wish it was someone else
but
maybe it will either be we can either
use it to our advantage or Netherlands
will use it to their advantage some will
someone will use the fact that they
played against each other before against
to their advantage but any that's
something we'll talk about later what if
Turkey wins hold hold up be turkey fans
you guys we're easily
winning um but yeah I have adjusted my
schedule uh of this
week uh so that I can watch the next
game so Austria will win because I am
going to be in the studio at 400 a.m.
watching the next game with you guys
from
[Music]
Japan I have uh reserved the studio
unfortunately that means jenma will be
forced to be there too I told her she
doesn't have to be there and she's like
no no I have to accompany you I'm like
okay no I'm sorry I'm sorry you have you
have to I'm sorry apparently she has to
I guess I can't yeah I can't be alone in
the
studio uh I can't be the only one in the
studio at 4:00 a.m. they don't trust me
but that means yeah she has to stay up
too but it's okay we'll sleep before
we'll SLE sleep
after no I don't think she cares about
uh football I don't think she
does but I told her we'll have fun
together you you'll watch silently next
to me let's
go or in another room or you can take a
nap while I'm there um but yeah and uh
I've been I've been in I've been in
Ubers right and so I get into an Uber
okay okay okay so I think I've talked to
every Uber driver about football so one
one guy let me see my notes I've been
getting confused I start I I tried to
write some notes because I've been
slacking on writing
notes I tried them
again
a but first of all there was one Uber
driver he wasn't uh German but lived
most of these Uber drivers aren't German
but uh he lived in Germany for a long
time and
uh I think he was supporting Germany
kind of but uh we were talking about it
and he asked me like where you from and
I'm like I'm from Austria and and then
he's like you guys are really good
actually I'm like if you think so yeah
right we're good right aren't we and
he's like yeah totally I think you you
guys can actually win this and I'm like
wow okay that's quite the support DN
thank you
for I didn't think you would go that far
because then then I was like yeah we we
played really well didn't we like but we
just won against Netherlands and Poland
and and we both agreed that like you
know a lot of the other matches are
really boring but Austria plays really
entertainingly so we were getting along
really well uh and he really really said
like oh my God you could totally make it
not not like not like oh my God like you
can totally make it no okay the the way
I'm resigning this is not 100%
accurate but yeah uh and then and then I
think we even mentioned that like yeah
cuz he was definitely supportive of
Germany like that was his number one
because he lives in Germany and for a
long time and so um I was like I don't
know I don't know about winning against
Germany though and he's like no I think
even against Germany you could win says
the one that supports Germany I'm like
[Music]
I don't know about that one
but I I didn't agree with that
no but I don't know how how Germany is
going so
far uh in their bracket but whatever and
there was another one after after dinner
in the evening um it was already pretty
late uh it was on a day where German no
was
Germany I I think Germany was playing
and uh I got into the Uber and it was
raining a little bit and they were
playing in in a different city but it
was raining there too where they were
actually playing and uh the Uber driver
had football on the radio on and I'm
like I get in I'm like oh
football who's playing right now and he
tells me who's playing and and I'm like
what at this time they're still playing
because it was pasted like if it went on
normally it would already be over yeah
it was Germany versus Denmark I think
yeah probably and he was like no because
they took a break because it was raining
and they're only in their 60th minute
now uh even though normally it would
already to be over by that time I think
yeah that was a a big storm I guess mhm
so they took a break yeah so they played
really late so um once he knew that I
was into football he turned up his radio
and we were just like listening to the
radio and and and reacting to it but I
was just like this is the first time I
listened to football on the radio and I
felt kind of perplexed
like I I can't really he's yapping
yapping Yapp the commentator is yapping
yapping yapping quite well I guess but
it's hard to imagine anything this is
like football
ASMR I don't know if I really like it I
I can't really
understand it but yeah like even even at
the slightest chance like of the
slightest excitement from the
commentator the football guy uh the the
Uber guy would like turn it up louder
and be like oh oh oh oh goal goal coming
go coming and I'm
like and then every time it was like nah
n no nothing
a yeah it was real football ASMR what
the hell commentator football
commentator
[Music]
ASMR yeah you can tell even less you
can't really judge how excited you
should be if you're just listening to
it and then they won and I uh but they
won I think after I got out of the Uber
I go into my hotel room and I like get
ready to bed I'm really [\h__\h] tired
these past days have been extremely in
for me let me just say that I was I'm
just like generally these days um really
really stressful but like I get to bed
and like just chilling a little bit and
then I hear cars outside Sasa I in
Germany right I hear cars driving by
Hong Kong Kong Kong another one Hong
Kong Kong Kong Kong and another one
[Music]
Hong h
I'm like oh they won they have
won so oh was I Rob voice for a moment I
think my my stream or my PC uh just
stopped for a
moment yeah very much honking oh and in
my hotel there were I think there were
like 70% football fans but all kinds of
countries not German fans like I think
it was a lot of English
people and I don't know some other
people your PC concerns me same
same oh now I haven't been really
watching anything besides the Austrian
matches cuz I haven't had the time at
all and even just now I I took a tiny
nap because I was exhausted I already
got so much work done today um and then
I wanted to cuddle with my cats so we
took a tiny nap cuddling with each other
that was really
[Music]
nice yeah yeah yeah teach us how to sing
the Austrian Nation I still don't know
it okay new new promise I will learn it
if we get to the
finals
yeah oh yeah I okay you want to hear see
I'm using this time to tangent really
quickly for you guys keep you updated um
I was gone for you a few days I was in
Germany and I uh was originally going to
ask my mom to take care of my cats but
she uh she she has like a lot to a lot
to do in her garden right now the
million veggies have to be um picked
each day and she has some problem with
like some illness in the
fields uh so it's kind of difficult so I
had to organize someone else but a lot
of my friends were coming with
me to Germany and uh uh the other
friends like the okay let's say pizza
friend and Pizza friend's uh girlfriend
Pizza friend's girlfriend doesn't like
cats and pizza friend was like no if I
go take care of your cats at your place
I'm going to be so unproductive I'm like
bring a bring a laptop or something but
no he was not open to doing it and then
I I have one more close friend who was
not coming uh with us to um Germany so I
asked this other friend
and uh he really likes my cats so he
said yes
but so I leave and later he comes to my
home uh and then he
notices I guess I guess I think this was
the first time he was there since I had
a new home so this is the first time he
noticed I guess or he just hasn't
visited me in a long time so he didn't
notice but he comes in and he notices he
can't
be in my house because he gets strong
allergy
reaction allergic reaction not because
of the cats but because of some plants I
have so he couldn't sleep over and
that's what kind of what I was want
hoping for because my cats they're used
to you know having someone over the
night all the time and you know I wanted
someone who can beat her as much as
possible but he couldn't sleep over he
noticed you know no my brooy Al my
brother also had no time no one has time
right now and then he still took care of
the cats thank God what a Chad uh he
just like spent the whole time in the
garden and the reason I even I was too
busy really to communicate with him the
the following day uh after I left uh to
go to Germany I check out my uh security
camera footage and I see him running
around with a mask on his face in the
garden I'm like why is this guy wearing
a mask in my garden and I call him and
he's like oh yeah sorry I I have
allergies in your home I can't stand
being in your home it's really bad I
think it's one of the plants I'm like
no
[\h__\h] man yeah he's still been going
there once or twice a day feeding them
and cuddling with them and hanging out
with them like just in the
garden anms right now okay wait I I we
have to skip the an because I'm really I
need to talk with you guys okay I've
been missing you guys I'm sorry I'm so
busy yeah um and then so the thing is
I'm going on so many trips I'm so busy
I'm flying back and forth back and forth
like I think I'm flying twice per week
TW twice per
week I came back yesterday on Monday
from Germany and I'm flying this week
again to
Japan okay not twice per week every week
sometimes I fly twice per week sometimes
once per
week um so it's really [\h__\h] stressful
right now um I I can only say I'm not
streaming
tomorrow take that as you may uh
whatever that means but I'm really
stressed out I just came back yesterday
I have to unpack my thing still and my
there's a lot to unpack unpack I have to
pack again okay Taylor
Swift I saw this video where people were
like pissed off that she um flies around
back and forth back and forth back and
forth back and forth for her stupid Aros
tore um yeah what was I gonna say
uh I don't know ah yeah so for the next
trip I was going to ask my mom because
like last time I talked to her she meant
she she kind of said that yeah she just
has to take care of this illness once
and then the then she she can probably
take care but she couldn't she said nah
still difficult uh because too long the
trip is a little bit too long uh it's
not that short but also not that long
but I was like [\h__\h] who I who do I ask
because the friends I went to Germany
with they are still not uh they're
they're not home yet they're not coming
for a while and
um now the other friend right he has
allergies so I don't know if I really
want to do do this to him again maybe
for one day or so yeah but not for the
whole
time then as I said pizza guy and pizza
guy's girlfriend
are um but I managed to find a solution
it's the the coming trip uh there's
three
different teams of people who will take
care of my uh cats yeah first my mom for
a few days then allergy guy and then and
then uh friends so they will like one
after
another yeah almost time no my my
yapping my
yapping and then okay one more thing I
want to say ahead of time so you guys
can be ready for it uh I will not stream
until my B birth yeah my birth probably
My
Birthday Countdown which I've moved to
be the a proper countdown now my
countdown would have somehow been one
day late I'm so stupid the way I had it
planned we have a countdown in PST PST
uh 11:00
p.m. to
midnight uh PST time uh from 5th to 6th
because my birthday is on the 6th okay
and then and then uh we stop the stream
and then hours hours later I will do at
4:00 a.m. JD I will do the watch along
of the next match and then I okay I got
it um and then after that I go to sleep
I come back to the studio and then we do
uh stream for uh
K birthday K with uh the other girls and
also
uh merch merch will be announced there
okay thanks for the memberships and for
the super chats by the way um okay I
have ads what are you guys
[Music]
seeing I have ads
guys what are you even seeing
you got adds to
okay oh okay so as always I'll be having
quite a delay but that has been actually
kind of fun so
far okay end it's over the ad over we
are getting into this guys Austria
86% in the poll
I am excited I believe in Austria I will
bet for Austria um threee to three to
one three to one and the one goal that
turkey will get will be maybe even a
self goal from
us kria
go if they win if Turkey wins I will um
just um eat some Turkish
food um as a punishment for me which is
not a punishment because it's good but
it's the same as I said last time if I
will eat strop WAFF waffle strop
waffle if Neverland
wins all right let's [\h__\h]
go W red we're so red today we can wear
red today
yeah some motivating music in the
stadium oh let's go that's let the
finale oh wait are we the last
ones for this ah six five 4 three two
one oh they kind of the way they started
is kind of
almost felt
anticlimactic okay turkey against
Austria come on AA go go go almost
Sab Sab wanted to go straight into it
yeah we almost have 40 second delay
approximately that's
okay sh
sh are you guys just saying go because I
said go
turkey has a go like one minute
in what the [\h__\h] happened wait wait wait
what's
happening oh EEG
Corner no way that's so what what
the what the what the [\h__\h] just
happened n no problem that's uh we have
so much time getting a goal that early
no problem we have so much we have
literally still uh the whole match in
front of us uh 89 minutes stop guys
don't even celebrate this is
[Laughter]
nothing sorry if there's any Turkish
fans in the chat sorry I'll be roasting
your
asses but like but that was so weird the
way the Austrian guys were like
awkwardly standing there and it it went
in the triangle between them they should
have just stopped it properly the goalie
should have just picked the ball [\h__\h]
up and hold it in his
hands I was like what the [\h__\h] was
that a man that was just really really
um clutzy very clutzy
go no not go
[Laughter]
again
what wait that what was that just
now oh it went by I thought that I
thought I saw a goal but chat wasn't
even saying goal but okay this is this
is going fast oh my God this is going
fast this is this is the one goal that I
was giving turkey remember I said you
get one goal for
turkey uh but yeah yeah don't worry
about the delay you guys you guys can
scream goal in the chat if you want to
but it would be cool if you wouldn't say
for who so that I still get some
suspense oh oh a lot of headers should I
I want to make another
poll so that we get a crazy number again
at the
end what poll should we have should we
just have another who wins poll nah what
else could we pull
about it
go no shut up shut up don't troll me
don't troll
me an exact score goal would be
different
difficult there's so many choices that
would would be necessary po p po not go
po H oh will will sabito
score red cards
m in the whole game you
mean let's say
let's ah get the ball okay
okay why is Turkey in the lead I don't
know worry um I that's exactly what I
said before the game started that they
will get one goal so that's just
fulfilling my bet that's
it okay nice the way they celebrate Sab
has some really nice braids today
sheesh no I said maybe it will be a self
goal maybe but and the way we were
involved in this it was almost a self
goal oh did we get a close one again
almost uhoh uhoh uh
uh
uh oh oh oh
oh okay I have an idea for a pole woo
b
[Music]
b my birthday is this
weekend H happy
birthday happy
birthday a he's like he's in a baby Fus
position
bana
no batana you have to be careful the
match should start
it boo boo
boo are we booing what right what are we
Bo booing right now because we're
supportive are they supportive of the
fact that it's it should be counted as a
a
foul yeah so much already happened
[Laughter]
they showed a repeat of the stupid
situation with the goal again it's so
embarrassing it's so
weird they're booing the tree man for
wasting time the tree man what the
Austrian you
mean but I think mostly and I guess not
it could be pretty mixed I think I see
mostly red but in the audience I'm sure
there's a lot of Turkish people
too from here I see mostly Austria
though ooh on top of the
goal oh a tree ah bat tree guy
ah it o it was indeed a a weird
beginning it oh there the Turkish are
also wearing red shirts so that's very
confusing I yeah I see I saw a few of
them in the closeup now they're wearing
white but also red shirts
confusing there might actually be more
Turkish fans in the audience who
knows like there's a lot of Turkish
people live who live in like Germany and
Austria they don't even have to
travel they don't even have to travel
from afar
yeah is this in liic I don't know where
it is I just came from
dorf the Japan of
Germany come on come on Austria fighter
we have to win we have to
win we have to win because I already
planned to stay
up to be up in the studio at 4:00 a.m. I
already planned
it you to cheer against me wow I F
there's a lot more uh like people who
cheer for the opponent today in the chat
compared to Netherlands we didn't I feel
like we didn't have as many Netherlands
supporters in the chat back
[Music]
then don't be like Bae the funny thing
is I was actually originally I was
planning to do a little so to say panel
at Anime
Expo uh at the whole life
Booth um but like it was going to be a
really bad time for me in Japan I would
have to get up at a shitty time be there
really shitty time I was planning that
and then the more and more I waited the
more I realized I don't want to do that
because it's going to be too stressful
so I canceled the
plans I'll be doing something at other
events uh possibly so um that's that
sorry I won't really be at Anime
Expo not like
that yeah like like the S to panel or so
before it's just too much right now
[Music]
um yeah but now now I'm doing football
because football at 400 a.m. it takes
priority I even moved my birthday
stream around the countdown stream I
moved it so that I can make this
work just so just so that I have enough
sleep and time in between priorities my
friends
priorities if it doesn't work it doesn't
work then I might still change things
around
again m
10 minutes in
nil uh to
[Music]
one it's okay I'm not concerned I'm Not
Who whoa whoa people are falling my tree
men got fouled and there's a yellow card
woohoo o
consequen he misses the next match he
did he already get so many yellow cards
in other
matches I see the I see the intentions
in your eyes
man we only need two wow wow it's really
strict okay we're getting like a a free
kick oh sabit looks
exhausted already it's only been 10
minutes come on he's giving his best
though stop pulling for [\h__\h]
sake
okay
okay oh oh I'm oh I'm a little bit naked
yeah no I'm wearing I'm wearing my
Austrian
shirt well I hope that Turkish defenses
will be slowing down and and weakening
I don't I can't really tell so far if
their defense is that
strong we need we need to get those
goals
in stop buling
fory
ah both teams are not playing great I
don't know I wouldn't say that the
beginning was weird but
besides
that we can still get
it boo boo boo what's Boo Boo Boo
Boo come on come
on stop holding each other this isn't
not this is not American football that
Austria apparently
won against
America today
yesterday oh
yeah we in yeah in American
football World
Championship Austria won against America
apparently very recent thing we're
winning
everywhere oh ah under 20 ah like
Teenage J
huh
who there's a world champion I I I think
world championship for under
20 not that serious I guess if it's
under
20 come on come
on come on come
on come on
nice block though nice block goalie
Chan they can have some major talents
yeah sure but like I feel like nobody
takes teenager matches that
seriously grow grow some body hair first
I can't speak grow some body hair first
oh oh what was
that what was that but there's a
19yearold playing on the field right
now some of
these boys will be balling early on
[Music]
huh you got me tripping oh stumbling oh
wait that should be a theme song for
Neymar they should make a maybe they
already did a clip compilation of Namar
with Fergie singing in the background
you got me tripping oh stumbling oh
flipping oh fumbling
oh crazy cuz I'm falling in
love you got me slipping oh bubbling oh
dripping oh tumbling
oh shut the [\h__\h] up audience shut the
[\h__\h]
up shut the [\h__\h] up
mate oh yeah in my
hotel I told you that there were like so
many football fans
right I had to explain to them why they
were a lot of weird looking
people like what is going
on with like dressed up people in the
hotel it was like a weird mix of
football people and then dressed up
people for a certain anime convention I
explained it to
them it's
funny world Collide
yeah and then also like on on the day
where I checked
out on the on the night before I just go
into my hotel room and I notice like
some
vandalization like a knocked over and
like
punched
metal uh trash
can like a big ass
dent on the metal trash can and the
trash all over on the floor not outside
on a hotel room floor in front of the
elevator I took a photo and I brought it
to the uh
reception and I was like hey I think um
somebody may have
been yeah drunk vandalizing
[\h__\h] his team probably lost maybe but
yeah
holigans [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
holigans the poor trash cans yeah prime
target [\h__\h]
elmate classic holigan
cosplayer now imagine imagine no it
wasn't it wasn't the football fans no it
was totally the
cosplayers it was totally the the
cosplay weebs and
nerds going to the anime
convention check the security camera
check it
out I didn't sit on it it was already on
the
floor M hatsun Miku that's funny that
you mention hatsun Miku that remembers
reminds me of another
thing I was like talking
to um like a
stranger actually like a staff
member at the
event
and and we were talking a little bit
about like
YouTubers and she says oh yeah vtubers
like I know like hat Miku right and I'm
like wow
I'm met an anime convention that oh the
ball flies over the whole field I'm in
an anime convention that for a few years
now has been big with vtubers like
supporting vtubers and and and hosting
vtubers a lot they're like
everywhere and you say h is a vtuber I'm
like I I was like h
no no ham is not a YouTuber no no she's
uh no and she's like no no I'm sure to
me she's a vtuber I'm
like uh okay sure
sure
sure I suppose
so to you she
is what do you mean to you
H she's she's really not a v Widow by
definition k um
actually funny anyway see I have
tangents pent up I wanted to talk to you
guys but I also want to win in football
come
on come on come on come
on don't disappoint me and all the taxi
driver who said that Austria will win
easily against
turkey what about the time we won
against turkey very recently last time 6
to one or whatever it
was do it for the taxi drivers
yeah don't disappoint the taxi drivers
they be listening on the radio right now
while they're
driving and they'll be thinking about me
and they'll cry some manly tears if we
don't win Austria right now if we don't
win for Austria right now w w what was
that the way he tumbled over very Neymar
very neyar
[Laughter]
like a little
turtle what's happening that was another
fall did I just see two different
Falls Neymar catching all the
Strays turtle on its shell a little
smaller smaller turtle on its
shell small small turtle turle
the name or slander will not be
tolerated what you going to do what you
going to do about it how you going to
punch me I'm a [\h__\h] vtuber come here
punch me now punch your screen yeah yeah
yeah try oh yeah punch your screen try
give it a try ah I think the only one
who would lose something from that is
you you lose your monitor I'll go ahead
and bunch your [\h__\h] monitor try it
try me mate try me
mate I will not be paying for your new
monitor fight me fight me
what what was that I'm sorry about the
way the Austrian guy just fell down like
like a straight
mannequin look he fell down like so
straight like the letter I you know what
I
mean so
stiff that was
silly that was
silly yeah like a leg oh stop guys to
stop you what is this [\h__\h]
show
POS ah come
on he's
like bigest pain of my life this hurts
more than bfing a
baby the can you imagine some of these
guys they have wives they go go back
home after a long day of faking injuries
on the field and they and and their
wife's like dude the way the way you
fake that pain is kind of disrespectful
for how much pain I've endured biring
your
child you piece of [\h__\h]
oh is that the that number eight guy he
looks so young he looks like 15 but he's
probably the 19y old they talked about
right he looks so
young he's kind of tiny
too he's
what I thought they said 19 on the
commentator he's their best player well
he's got the youth
is is 18 the minimum age you got to
be because like feels kind of weird to
have such young people among
these 30 year
olds 16 is the minimum Spain is a six oh
my
God that's just I don't know I
mean I would say like that's not fair
they they're way more uh
Spelunky but I guess uh the 25 30 year
olds they're they're still energetic and
they got they got um the the experience
I suppose at least going for
them I don't know what I'm what Spelunky
means is that the the right
word 16 that's too young I feel like
I mean it doesn't matter it's just a a
sport it's not like you know K-pop Jpop
Idols who might feel like they're too
young to be doing that
but which still feels weird I don't know
something about that feels weird cuz
there's all these grown ass men do they
even have conversations 16 yearolds like
I got to I got to do my homework and uh
uh I don't know watching what do six H
uh playing playing Roblox in between the
matches playing [\h__\h]
Roblox there's 30y old who might have a
child the same [\h__\h]
age okay okay come on Austria get me get
me excited do something fun
Austria
please come
on don't let that one gold
stand don't let it
[Music]
[Laughter]
stand come
on that that number 21
guy from the above angle so far away he
his whole body looks like twice the size
of everybody like not really height but
like
[Music]
width 21 from uh Turk tury T tur tur
turke tur turkey turkey I
mean good goalkeeping at least that was
Turkish goalkeeping wasn't it just now I
guess that was uh good yeah but not good
for
me stop playing like England Austria
maybe they're
nervous maybe they're
nervous [\h__\h] they might be nervous
because they now they know word has
gotten around that I'm watching
them they didn't know yet before and now
they know and now they're [\h__\h]
nervous
man takii of H life englishan is
watching
them their heart is going doy
doie ah
[Laughter]
understandable performance anxiety no
spaghetti they're spilling the spaghetti
no it's okay I'll close my eyes
Austria until you get a
goal how about
that maybe they'll play better when I
close my
eyes yeah well 30 minutes in no goal for
Austria does make me a little bit
nervous
too just a little
bit but anything can
happen anything can and will
happen at least now they kind of
stopped I'm saying this while I'm
watching these guys wrangling each other
he's got nice hair that Turkish
guy number
20 but they kind of lessened the amount
of wranglings that's
good England got their win last minut
England won what do you mean England won
against
who what match was
that no on out ofic what did you
do he's
thinking blue guy
thinking what he didn't do [\h__\h] arov
didn't didn't do [\h__\h] they both didn't
do
[\h__\h] against against
Slovakia
ah wait when was
that when was that when was
that England did not deserve the win
even though you're England
supporter two days AG on Sunday ah
Sunday
Sunday oh
yeah I think I I didn't watch it but I
was like
uh when they were playing I think I was
eating
dinner and there were a lot of people
watching in the
restaurants on
TV cuz for once we didn't go to Japanese
restaurant on that day cuz we were just
like too late for everything
come on get that ball for real for real
there were also like what like I don't
know professional an analytics that said
Austria will win so I believe in that
too not that their judgment is
more any any more professional than my
own obviously first and foremost you
should judge me uh uh believe
me yeah that first goal was weird as
[\h__\h]
weird don't judge me don't judge me I'm
always being judged I'm being judged by
these random random turkey supporters
coming into My
Stream I want I I'm curious the turkey
support us in my stream I'm sure there's
some whole life fans but are there some
in here that uh are
not are not all life
fans what do you mean random okay okay
good good you're not random okay but it
would be funny if there were some
randoms in here
we love you K but we love our country
more as you should as you
should not random regular viewer okay
okay all right all right all right
actually I am kind of random you
are do you know vtubers it's not
[Laughter]
hatu you're not random you're not random
run M M M
run sa run for it come on come on
sa yeah you tried good try good try
never give up never going to give the
ball up never going to let me
down the Wawa oh Dano is here today too
of course he's here go Dano go
Dano stop buling
I only know VBA
VBA we boobers let's
go red
card what happened what
happened we got
got hey Goldie don't go that far outside
of your gold
[Music]
Zone scares me
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] scares me all back to
the
goly back and
forth back and forth forth to the
gay uhhuh sabita on the ball sabita run
run run to the ball back to AR aric back
to sabita and he runs with the ball and
shoots to the guy with the number 20 and
shoots to 16 which is maybe Dan so no
maybe it's not s Dano I'm not
sure oh he pushed the ball outside the
field oh yeah oh
yeah the ball has left the field like
you has left the
chat oh no stay in the chat please and
stay in the field
oh
man it's not boring though I'm I have to
say not boring yet like that one match
we watched
before after the Austria match against
Poland that was boring
at least we had a goal that was really
entertaining is this woman German no
this woman is
Austrian a beautiful Austria is is
playing right now who do who do you
think I'm
supporting the ball goes into the sky
never to be seen ever
again because where the screen ends is
where the world ends as you know or Dano
has the ball let's go Dano I think it's
Dan
so into
[Music]
space I love that song too I love the
meme
surely someone made that meem with neyar
before when he starts rolling and then
he rolls into
space w Neymar living rentree in my
[Music]
brain okay come on Romano Schmid
be a gam
man
oh I like the way the people are spread
on the field right now we need a little
bit more fire a little bit more heat
heat those Turkish people
up we need to make him sweat and need to
make him
forget about
theall a football
H that was cute the way the fan looked
into the
camera they're not letting it in let me
in I am SLE let me in to se oh wow that
was a beautiful jump was he a ballerina
before the goalies
jump was so beautiful like is he a
ballerina oh oh
whoa whoa that was so so much grace so
much
Elegance Majestic perfect
form stupid foul yellow
card for S Romano
Schmid wait I thought Romano Schmid was
his whole name because the whole time
the commentator says Romanos Schmid the
way as if it's the full name
it really sounds like a full name the
way he says that it's just Rano and
Schmid cuz all the other guys they call
like only with their last name Dano Sab
and romanish they always call ranid I
just not notice that
now it could
be it has the same length like
anovich oh zom come on don't lose the
[\h__\h] ball no they fell down you lost
the [\h__\h] ball no no no thanks for the
egg thanks for the
egg
bro bro please
[Music]
40 minutes 40
minutes Boo Boo
Boo Hy side oh no what
come on Austria score some [\h__\h]
goals
girls if you want to score a g you got
to score some [\h__\h] goals you
know you know what I mean right you know
what I mean
score go get
g
o it's like they're bullying us stop
bullying
us a
the [\h__\h] was that
turkey number 90 [\h__\h] you what you this
what the [\h__\h] was that you better be
getting a card for
that yellow card huh did you get a
yellow card or what no nothing happened
no follow up on
that oh
what what
[Music]
yellow what what yellow oh ow ow I
what the [\h__\h] shety is so biased oh
was for turkey
okay never mind he's not
biased it's raining it's not fair can we
wait for the rain to
end [\h__\h] the rain the rain is biased the
rain is ruining it all Austria is made
out of sugar we're melting because of
the rain we can't can't play in these
conditions we're
sugar they don't
understand pants
way he's running dashing for his life
the only thing that's missing is a piece
of toast in his
mouth and maybe a cute
skirt anything I say could be applied
even with 40 seconds delay
probably thanks for the
membership oh yeah I guess we're made
out of salts yeah no sugar we're made
out of salt because uh we're a very
salty country we just put salt on a lot
of
things a lot of of salt on
bread thanks for the membership
gifts maybe I'll refresh once we're in
halim
come on come
on Austria
please Austria please please don't
disappoint this anime girl I'm going to
cry anime
tears oh
B hey
I don't know what's
[Music]
happening the blonde Turkish guy the way
he screamed on the floor the sheety the
the sheety is like the blue guy he's
like the whole time they gave us a
closeup of him his eyes are
like this [\h__\h] baby
these [\h__\h] babies be crying about
every [\h__\h] [\h__\h] don't be taking this
seriously his face every
time at a time
okay why was he doing jazz
hands you having a laugh I'm having a
laugh a laugh a laugh I'm having a laugh
I'm having a I'm having a laugh a laugh
I'm having a
laugh thanks
pants for holding the
ball
oh oh now I got the extra
minute oh wait we're actually already 20
seconds into the extra
minute
o are these Boo and oh my God you guys
are Turkish fans mad for the extra
minute what you need to piss that hard
you need to go piss and go [\h__\h]
piss instead of go piss girl I say go
piss
turkey they're so
Whimsical unhappy one second and happy
as the
other see
are we are we are we
done are
we half time right I
stop okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
H you the reason American is watching
football today
yeah the this event should be sponsoring
me there's a lot of Americans only
watching because of
me oh look at the Son and the dad that's
what they look
like okay I will refresh my browser even
though I don't think it will really
change my delay much at
all yeah well that is the first half
H we can get at least one goal in and
make it a tie and then we have to fight
it out
and that could go
well it doesn't look bad no it doesn't
look bad it doesn't look stop saying
that stop saying that you were so
motivated and supportive and believing
in
Austria don't don't be like this now
come on we still have the wa
support maybe maybe I got
to maybe I have to free the
waas maybe that's what's the only thing
I can do
now
yes
my my hands that's yeah that's that's
all I can do that's the best I can
do
wait one more thing that I can
contribute
uh
here where is
it slow where is it
a there it's on my
chin can I
[Music]
paint I don't know put them
here I want to put them like one here
and one here so like ideally I wouldn't
be wearing anything but it is what it
is I W got
yeah why is the stream H it's a short
stream you can watch on on the
phone there's been so much football Wawa
uh fan
art can
you draw me naked like the French girls
but in Austrian and like body paint uh
Austrian flag
on saies um draw me like one of your
Austrian French
girls is my request
questionable is is something wrong with
what I'm asking
for no right it's all
good so how much time do we have 15
minutes I hope those Turkish fans are
going to relieve themselves into the
toilet so that they can stop pissing
around whenever there's austrians on the
on the
ball for real shut the [\h__\h]
up
mate it's
[Laughter]
unbelievable ah
commission your smart in private like
everyone is that smart is that what
smart smart as something else
no shut the [\h__\h] up proof proof I will
call
sna if Austria wins I'm joining
membership a okay that better be a
promise
smut means loot things is definitely
smart it sounds like the German word for
dirt
Schmutz or like it doesn't sound like it
quite but it looks like
it all least in the ads Austrian
snake Austrian
snake I have to pack my bags
my schedule is so weird right now
guys it's just so weird I have so much
going on I think I can in theory make a
schedule though if you guys want just
for a nicer overview uh over the streams
on the
weekend but probably no streams until
the
weekend yes
[Music]
please yeah I think that would be smort
smart
yes I have a lot of dancing to do while
I'm in Japan so a lot of dancing anding
and prancing so that's why I'll be very
[Music]
busy no h and collab crab
well I would have liked to participate
but they chose my birthday date and I'm
already already busy with other streams
on my birthday
date one of them being
football big fan from Turkey hey what's
up what's
up they're actually like when I was like
planning my countdown uh uh Birthday
Countdown Callin stream I wanted to do
EST
but it would have overlapped with their
crap game stream so now I'm doing PST
PST is better anyway I can sleep a
little bit
longer yeah I don't know it and then now
right before the PST countdown stream
there is crab game and that that's a
little bit too close
together works better for EU gang yeah
yeah a little bit better
yeah luckily it's a weekend so I can
stay up late easy yay you have to you
have to when does the countdown start
11:00 p.m. PST on the
fifth on the
fifth wait I'm
thinking I'm doing a think I thought I
wanted to tangent about something what I
you
know oh should I No Maybe not maybe not
never mind
too bad you won't be on crab game yeah I
was like I don't know we never played
crab game in Hol life before I think so
I would have loved to be part of it but
there's just too much right now I
can't I
can't feels like you didn't have perms I
think for a while we we had
oh uh no never mind never mind waah waah
don't say things at
all oh there was one before ah you're
right there were like clips of cobal and
so on yeah yeah so we do have it for a
while
now yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh yeah members only streams have
to probably also be uh put on the back
bur now for a little bit for now you had
like day weekly members only streams for
a while now so you can forgive me right
but we also have to wait with monar so
don't watch the new season yet when it
comes out wait for us our thing we have
a thing don't watch the new season
[Music]
yet membership wallpaper ah oh it's
July oh yeah I can put that up let me
put it up right now I guess I still have
time right
let me try wait why am I I'm so brain
brain
empty
uh where is it where is it it's been
finished for a little while it's really
good
July
wallpaper
wait are it it's not finished
yet oh it should it should have been
finished let
me let me ask the artist oopsie I
thought it was finished
sorry
[Music]
hey is the art finished yet
they may have lost track of it it's okay
I also lose track of things thanks for
the membership thank
[Music]
you he not finished what is it in
Swedish
how are things looking for justice H do
I was I suggested it I was going to do
it uh I think this weekend even I said
hey everything's
looking uh stressful the coming
weeks and normally I want to do it right
away
anyway I will like sacrifice one of my
birthday streams for this
but unfortunately it didn't work out um
for
some
participants so it's not
happening at least not for a while and I
don't know how I feel about doing it one
one month
in it was kind of cool with Advent cuz I
could do it right
away I don't
know um I'll think about it but for now
it didn't work
out
[Music]
yeah but now that I did one with admin I
feel like I have to so even if it's late
I I think I still have to do it
eventually h
we need their panty
colors H I'll see what I can
do I'll see what I can
do oneon-one or pairs no that would take
up way too much time we could have done
it with a member missing but I said
nah nah that's just wrong we're not
going to it's even the full group or or
Nothing All or Nothing I'm all
in nowadays we need to know if they wear
any at all oh shall we play place bets
like
predictions something cute it will be
something cute
M uh herb
black
gigy G possibly no
panties
but I will say like
striped her is red not every
day and then Cil
[Music]
uh she doesn't she wear Bloomers maybe
all she wears is Bloomers those which is
basically no panties
too maybe maybe she thinks Bloomers is
enough and she doesn't need anything
else KY a gy spats like how with nothing
underneath normally you wear things
under the spats normally you supposed to
wear I think or do you I
would I
would Should I reset the timer to
45 wait [\h__\h] are we starting right away
I can't I don't know if I can uh do it
that
fast wait what was that website that I
used uh stopwatch where you can set the
starting
time
um was it this one
no [\h__\h] which one was
it just wait I wait till okay I'll wait
until it hits
4610 and Gregor coming
in It's the final
countdown Austria having fun austri
still motivated players are coming back
[Music]
in now last time I reset it to zero but
I think that's confusing too you have to
do math because of that cuz all those
little things in the field when they're
coming
in no but um I think it's better if I
just have it at 45 because that's where
it
continues don't do math
kids okay here we go
guys come on
PR where's the timer come on show me the
timer
45 10
okay soon soon I am pressing go on my
timer
soon right I'm
focusing I'm focusing sabit will score
yes yes he will he
will he will
I'm not there
yet so what what's
close what happened W you
duck he ducked under that
ball what did we almost get a goal
no are you guys so far ahead of me
again what the
and go okay my time oh I see it I see I
see something bana oh
oh okay Austria wanted an early one in
the half time almost had
it almost had it
man yeah he was out anyway
[Music]
but this makes me
hope that we can do it oh yeah we switch
sides too right so we're
playing towards the right side towards
the right
side yeah it's Z1 nil
one but things can change things are
looking up
to change for the
better Austria looking rotten oh oh oh
you little [\h__\h] I have a roast that I
could say now but it will be kind
of kind of
[Laughter]
smudy it it be kind of
ludd cuz that's the only
thing I can think of not because I'm
horny or
anything just cuz I'm thinking what
could be rotten in your room right
now of possibly a a guy a male viewer
what could I say that Austria might be
rotten but what about all those
rotten in your room
clean him
up so I said it because I need to roast
you back you little
[\h__\h] sorry stop to go please do
something about
this what do you mean not all my bottles
what do you mean gamer
bottles e
we Germans can be funny too well good
for you you're defending the Germans but
I'm Austrian so you don't have to defend
yourself for
me it's okay
H did it stop raining I wonder do you
think it's like
affecting the players if it
rains get slippery
ah what do you call
a never mind it's too far back already
it's not even
funny affects the ball I I guess the
ball gets slippery too
raining for both teams no it's only
raining for Austria it's so unfair it's
so
biased don't you see the rain clouds
above the Austrian
players too far back joke expired
exactly
man expiration dates too soon
what almost
go good safe safe go almost
go
oh ah it's
like it's like he was like only looking
like behind himself to catch the ball
and then immediately shot he didn't even
see that the goalie was right in front
of him
possibly he was too focused on getting
the ball is how I
shall analyze this
situation stop holding okay wait that's
an Austrian I guess I I shall not I
shall shall not
complain about manly holding each other
manly
[Music]
yeah ah go go go go go go go go B no no
stop planting trees on the
ground your job is not being the tree
man anymore you're playing [\h__\h]
football score some [\h__\h] goals
the Heathers are funny
sometimes hey who's getting
yellow who the [\h__\h] is getting yellow
there there was a lot going
on close
again
[Music]
bro I mean you can't you can't have like
a 90 minute match and the only goal from
it was in the first minute that just
feels so [\h__\h]
up I just feels so [\h__\h] up no we this
can't be we can't have it be that
way okay
okay that's the close one you were
talking about again
okay disgusting
disgusting o
a trying
hard we'll be rewarded for it don't
worry soon the chat will tell me 40
seconds ahead of time that there was a
go for Austria and we will all be
celebrating I see it coming I can sense
it the chat goes like go woohoo and I'm
like wo wo
woooooo mm
ow ow ow ow are you okay buddy ow ow
he's
hurt go
go nah no way no
way
cor you could gas light me into winning
yeah and I'll just be there at 4:00 a.m.
in Japan waiting to play against
never because you gasl me
successfully oh
I not a close one and we're doing good
we're aggressive we're giving it a lot
of tries one of those balls will go in
eventually it's okay one of them will go
in you just got to keep on
trying goal
no
no shut up no
ostrich yeah when we're talking about uh
Austria and
turkey it's not quite chicken or Phoenix
versus Turkey ostrich would
be the more
[Music]
fitting analogy I don't know no penalty
no what's up what's up what's
up close again
Bruh Bruh see we're getting there we're
getting there don't
worry that was the offside I saw it
I saw
it even if he got it in it would have
been for nothing so it's okay it's
okay don't lose hope did my wa was not
give you more hope look at those
wers I'm shaking them just for you like
I'm a
Cheerleader I'm your cheerleader
Austria these are my tatas I'm shaking
them for you like my pom poms my
imaginary pom
poms filled with hope now let's go
[Music]
okay
okay I need some I need it I need the
win I need the
win oh s please you've been playing so
good you're good don't drop you
spaghetti please
please please
don't I'm getting desperate now I can't
can't I can't take this top off too I
wish I could I would if I could I would
if I could I don't have any
more reveals of the
tatas what can I do what can I do what
more can this anime girl
[Music]
do please y yle please
yle Austria needs me right now let me
take off my turquoise top please
jugle please
jugle I really I really trying and
they're trying their best but they
really need it they really need me to
Freed them
[Laughter]
do it for Austria do it for Austria
please you know what I need instead of
the shirt uh the auster shirt you know
those shirts that are basically like
those like from the shirt quality
they're like those soccer shirts the
football shirts let's do that but with
like naked body painted on it you know
there are shirts like that mostly for
male bodies I think but can we get
one for
me no no what no don't no no no no no no
no no how just how just no what do you
mean no no oh they're doing they're
doing a kick from the side corner or
what is it a corner
kick no
I'm not even there yet make it not be
true dummy
no no oh it's a corner from the [\h__\h]
yearold get that [\h__\h] kid out of here
he his better it's literally can he even
play legally here I guess he's 18
actually no no
[Laughter]
get that [\h__\h] kid out of
[Applause]
here what about his
[Music]
education
bro we should be on [\h__\h] Tik Tok
right
now turn off that [\h__\h] music there's
no time for music right now
no no no Yago yo I am I need to talk to
you again yo I said it was a joke but I
might be quite serious about freeing the
waas even
further we need to do it for
Austria we need to do it for Austria
please
time to cancel the 4 a.m. Boogie no no I
will be there I will be there and I but
if I have to I will be supporting an
imaginary Austria Netherlands
match wait are both goals from the same
dude no I I guess I would say still it's
like you can't
even credit that dude you should credit
the stupid 18y
old 2 zero is
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I could make my own match in
FIFA h i could play some football game
pretend it's a real
match coping the cop of all football
lovers this is how you should have
played this is how you should have
played my my dear
austrians uh the way he caught that
ball so much
love Austria
please anime girl support needs to
become a thing tradition
oh there's so much rain
bro stop laughing stop smiling you
little
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] man it's raining really
strong when you can even
ow m
L
not he hurt that little
boy but if you can see it on the
camera that clearly it must be raining a
lot
[\h__\h] is that 18-year-old going out to
play Minecraft
now and watch Tik
Tok what the what the [\h__\h] is
happening what the are we St
are we getting like a special
kick go play some fortnite
yeah REM remind you play Minecraft
yeah skippity
[Laughter]
skippity a fake out that was a really
obvious fake
out okay pants got the ball pants pants
is
[Music]
good can we take a break because of
s
please please
goal no more people would be screaming
goal if there was
one come on ostrich score some [\h__\h]
goals maybe if they had lighting uh do
we have any can Cobble summon
lightning do we have someone who can
summon some
lightning brah
Limer leanard going out Grillage River
wow we're we're switching out so many
four players in total
now I hope this will be
good I don't think kble can do it we
need some thunder godddess in whole life
please please
Austria y
b yeah B
I'm on a football high don't ruin it
turkey don't ruin it for
me football is my everything right now
footall is all I've got right
now
literally
go p p
p p lost the ball it's it's out right
now wait nothing's happening right did I
actually get
a it's just a slow motion right now okay
he's ah corner it's the corner shots
it's the corner shots
baby it's the [\h__\h] Corner shots let's
[\h__\h]
go
sa thank you so much GRE that's your
name I knew that totally before the
commentator said it finally a [\h__\h]
win for we're in we're so back we're so
back we're so back we're so back
guys we're so
[Music]
back woohoo wo wo it's a start it's a
start come on one more then at least we
have a tie then they can't [\h__\h] leave
we're going to keep everybody here until
Justice is
served I sa a Nation Army can't keep me
down
bro CL another close
one close [\h__\h] [\h__\h] okay but see see see
we're catching up we're catching up
[Laughter]
baby ah I see I see I saw it now
gor looking happy though I think
obviously not a goal uh by far but he's
happy that his header almost did it his
backwards header without watching where
he's
going almost did
it bruh
if they tied this up in this rain it's
going to be an instant classic what do
you
mean the game of the tournament dude
said on the announcing what are you
talking
about face for the
memberships you it's so
winnable it is so winnable
hey Austria Flags thanks guys thank
you oh [\h__\h] D these people are so wet
bro it's [\h__\h] pouring and
pissing is it pissing because I told the
Turkish people to go
piss that's not what I meant
bro soaked it
who the the rain looks so cool in the
slow motion shots
whoa It's Raining man hallelujah it's
raining man
H hey
it's a [\h__\h] fly flying around me get
out football is not for
you by the way I bought donuts with a
football on top of it the the football
kind of fills the the hole of the
donut football donut
I will
eat
after uh this and hopefully it will be a
reward not a consolation
crying uh uh
[Laughter]
thing filled with vanilla sauce by the
way what about your diet I'm fine I'm
hot I'm hot anyway I don't need to diet
I just need to do
sport I have realized I'm
hot all I need is uh
some some
stamina I me look at me I me look at me
no I mean I told you before I never
thought of myself as like you know
overweight I'm not I'm factually not uh
and you
know I'm I'm I'm very much
not you know I'm not like I'm so
fat while I'm not I'm not one of those
stop austrians come on stop stop what
are you doing austrians on the field the
pass from the
friends to vava
stop are we getting a corner again what
Vos sria let's go
ostrich okay okay okay okay they're
they're playing slow now they're they're
like hey we're here now we got to do
something we got to make something
happen corner but no
goal ah
man no goal too bad
too
bad whoa It's so dramatic with the
rain that guy is so smiley I think
number 11 was it gregorich he's so
smiley
cute ah that was
difficult oh that's was kind of
difficult
the corner shot they were all like in
one pack of
people he Y what the [\h__\h] all the trash
did they throw that did the [\h__\h]
Turkish fans throw it there just because
we got a goal people haven't been so
[\h__\h] pissy in the last matches
throwing trash in there can somebody
clean that up though hello staff
I guess are they not allowed to enter
that part of the field
maybe it's pretty much outside of the
field
though again close something close again
they'll get it
later s Behavior pisses me
off I'm just going to complain about
everything that is not nice towards us
Austria um stuff son hello clean it up
oh somebody's cleaning it up I see right
now oh
she's looks it looks like a girl and she
tripped on on the
[Music]
trash that was that was a close one
vamos vamos
Austria is she
single
Savage
Savage arnovic with the
ball and it was blocked so the turkey
can
counter the ball attack but Austria has
the ball
back and he going towards the goal
but it's go
outside yeah we need to be Speedy we
need to be Speedy make some good passes
I'm
just copying what the commentators are
saying come
on come
on only 15 minutes
left only 15 minutes
left we need to make this into a tie in
these 15 minutes and that will be our
chance I don't know how these boys are
with penalty kicks
but that's our only chance there's no
way we're getting two goals
so we need we need just one one goal one
goal 15 it is it is time any any minute
could be a goal like could get 15
goals no but Sab Sab Sab off ah close
close
close you can do it stay stay relaxed as
much as you can my
boys come
on my fruit has been used a lot on the
weekend I cannot scream loud enough that
you guys can hear
me I
cannot I also sung a lot today and
yesterday trying to catch up on deadline
so I want to
scream what happened what happened
what's the hey yo Oh you mean oh I mean
man a man you made me think of something
about
football 2 two let's go I mean
please
[Music]
please please please
please please please please please
please please please pleas pleas
pleas maybe instead of talking to the
coaches they should be talking to me
maybe maybe you know how vtubers are on
like little screens on conventions
walking around with a
screen can they like put me on there and
now will do a motivational speech for
them Corner o well obviously not a goal
because you guys are not reacting sabit
getting the goal again the the corner
shot
again
braah
braah as a Dane have to root for someone
else thank you for rooting for us
ah damn
it damn
it Sab could have done that better oh he
gets another
one
bruh why does he get another
one not a hold that was at least not
that didn't go da da da da at least h
damn it's hard to kick Corners in the
rain
really damn damn damn damn
damn
why do you need a
grip or
what 10 minutes
[Music]
left pleas
a tutu what do you mean tutu you're just
hoping for it right you're not typing it
because it
happened stop [\h__\h] booing my
men yeah we need to force the
extension we have to force the extension
guys you got Austra you got to play
faster you don't have much time you
can't be like pushing the B from one
side to another that o that was you got
so close there you got close to the
go we need a to we need a
to Callie please Callie Kelly
K I need the
to I need your cat right
[Music]
now help I need somebody help
[\h__\h] elmate get the ball back get the
ball back turkey is defending this with
their life
[Music]
obviously please there's still a chance
there's still a chance man I feel like I
feel like this is so weird I'm living in
the moment right now it's
crazy aren't we all you guys are know
the you you guys are in the future
though I'm going to cry when the game
ends for you guys 40 seconds
early and you're going to tell me it's
over and I'm like no no it's not no it's
not I'm so close you can't do it guys I
know you
[Music]
can't yeah yeah you know canel
commentator I that's what I'm saying
we're doing it the right way we got to
keep on trying we're we're trying many
many many many attempts one of those
will go
[Music]
in oh
no please guys don't waste my [\h__\h]
time now
with your stupid
injuries no this is like the end of the
match so now they're like doing this
[\h__\h] I can't I can't deal with this
now they're stalling stop I'm going to
[\h__\h]
stop stop stop stop stop I hate you so
much I hate you get the the [\h__\h]
up you want an injury I'm going to
[\h__\h] I'm going to I'm going to do it
I'm going to [\h__\h] do it for
you okay
okay oh now you can walk again oh now
you can walk
again wasn't so bad
huh why she so bad
[Laughter]
no we can do it they stole a [\h__\h]
minute of my
life yeah d add on to it right for this
[\h__\h]
show they better be adding on to it so
close close
again I need
this I need
this I'm going to burf I'm going to burf
a goal now I'm going to I'm going to
burth the goal
[Music]
I'm going to I'm going to bur
it come on
[Laughter]
I can't I can't I'm too
exhausted you guys will let me know 40
seconds ahead of time when there will be
a goal and then I will start
bfing come
on come
on go
no please please
please begging begging you
put a [\h__\h] ball in the
go
begging stop playing with the [\h__\h]
ball begging begging
you score some [\h__\h] goals now
mate lagging we got we shot Corner over
a [\h__\h]
bar oh my [\h__\h] god
is that sabit
again on the corner it's always sabit
isn't it yeah it's like default
Choice way too high way too high B
now way too hot wow the way the water
[Music]
no we going it we
it five minutes left we going do it
[Music]
please by the way subscribe Please
Subscribe if you
subscribe then the country of your
choice will
win only if you subscribe
it's not a scam it's
real it's totally
[Music]
real no [\h__\h] get out of this side of
the field
now thanks bro let SC my
[Music]
now why are they getting so aggressive
stop going to the side of the field stop
it
so much flag him the
[\h__\h] please
please please
please Sab Sab Sab the man of the men
come on I'm counting on you together
with the three man the bomb Gardner
fast you you guys got to be faster have
you looked at the [\h__\h] clock or can't
you read it like me just like
me I've learned how to read it
though it's not always easy
but no no no it's
not oh my goalie is so far out oh
no that reminds me of German me getting
[\h__\h] absolutely
[\h__\h] come
on I'm going to
cry 4 minutes four four minutes 4
minutes
okay 4 minutes well that's that's that's
a good amount thank
you stop
wow Pence be sliding further than ever
before man nice bonso
nice Oh wrong side of the field please
go to the
right four minutes and a
dream mom
[Music]
hey
who's cramping now is it that time of
the month for you huh
oh Mama Mia don't salute don't [\h__\h]
so this [\h__\h] bastard this
[\h__\h] get the [\h__\h] up
no oh my [\h__\h] god oh my oh my I
cannot guarantee that I will not be
using extreme violence when this is over
no please I I had a meeting with JMA
before the stream and I told her like
really confidently that we'll be going
to the studio at 4:00 a.m. streaming the
next football
match I was so
confident probably J is probably rooting
for turkey right
now so that she doesn't have to go to
the
[Music]
studio p
p p
[Music]
P oh oh they almost got to go thank you
pants best
boy how the [\h__\h] are you guys on that
side of the
field I'm still on the right side oh now
now he's dashing towards the left told
you you don't need a goal I need a goal
why are you so selfish I need to goal I
need the [\h__\h]
goal
no no don't say no it's not don't say is
it
no no no don't say it's not over for me
yet no no
no no it's not over maybe no are you
saying it's over because it's really
over or is
it no no
no no zop it stop
please do
something what what that
was so close
that
was B
God
what we're get
what what what's happening we're getting
one more
Corner holy [\h__\h] no
[Music]
no you're playing with my
heart that almost went in that almost
went in from bomana and now we get in
the
corner e
m
[Music]
no
no no
[Laughter]
[Music]
no
no no
[Music]
[Laughter]
no well
[Music]
I need to
you my face hurts
my wait
what no
[Music]
JMA DM
me
me JMA said she's not rooting for turkey
and she said go
buddy JMA why the [\h__\h] were you watching
I told you to go to
[Laughter]
sleep oh
subscribe no
no no no we that would have been so epic
that last like last second shot from
bumgardner that led to the corner
shot that was actually so good
that was so close not the corner shot
itself but the last shot from bomb GNA
that that literally looked like it went
in from one angle with the excitement
surrounding it man A F that was so
cold but to be honest like I was kind of
like maybe it's my subconscious that
made this
happen because even if I could have made
the following watch long happen against
Netherlands I think the one after that
was pretty
impossible
so it I I wouldn't even have been able
to watch it all I need a I need a tissue
there's so much snot e
okay okay I don't know man that this was
such a nice AR I don't I didn't want it
to end I don't want it to
end no I'm not going to be I'm not going
to cheat on Austria and cheer for
someone else although I will be cheering
for Netherlands when they play against
Turkey
um they better win they better kick
their [\h__\h]
asses those [\h__\h] bastards better kick
their [\h__\h] [\h__\h] asses
Ares potential turkey hate what I mean b
me wants to do
[Music]
it I want to see you lose now this I
think the feelings I'm feeling right now
sorry Turkish fans I'm sorry but you
know I I you have to understand and I'm
very
sad and I think this feeling that I'm
feeling right now must be
like do other football fans do they just
completely turn it off after afterwards
and never watch any matches again or do
they also want to watch the one team
that defeated them
lose and this this must be a
common thing right
depends on the
person I I would assume yeah that a lot
of fans are just like they accept what
it is it is what it is and they move on
but then there surely there's also
others who are like man I know I need to
see them lose
now I would have been so epic if we
could have continued this
arc when is the world Championship H
when when is
it
2026 okay guess I'll
stay guess I'll stay in
Holo
uh well I don't know if we would even
qualify for that
normally we don't really qualify for
that not that good in America the world
championship is in America isn't it like
wherever where the country won like the
last country that won it's there
shouldn't it be there there's no way
that America who America is a team
what no I guess it's in different
countries
not only America
right it's the side ofer raffle
oh well is it early 2026 or like middle
or
end I need to make
[Laughter]
plans
summer ah it's randomly randomly
I wanted this to continue the odds were
really good for Austria we're good team
and turkey was known to be not so good
so I'm really confused I mean you're
fine turkey you made it this far but
like people have been telling me I don't
really know you know I may I base my
opinions upon what people tell me and
people were saying that turkey was not
particularly like one of the those good
teams that every everybody talks about
obviously you surprised
too good for you good for you okay I
calm down a little bit good for you good
for you Turkish fans good for you I'm
happy for you and I'm very sad for
myself I can be sad for myself and happy
for you but only if you
[Laughter]
subscribe it's my birthday this week
weekend it's my birthday this
weekend as I said you will win if you
subscribe they really aren't that good
you just didn't play it well yeah I mean
our second half was surprisingly better
than the
first we didn't play
completely
like we were not like dead animals in
the first half it wasn't dad uh what's
the word not um the opposite of active
we weren't so passive s like we were
super passive yeah but the first minute
goal just [\h__\h] everything
up if the if that if it wasn't for
that man things would have been very
different and then the second half was
really good in terms of like desperation
desperation leading to a lot of attempts
at uh you know evening it
out we had the bowl most of the time
yeah we definitely
did what the hell is try TR Y what what
is that wait is it Turkish money giving
me the Turkish money true that looks
that sounds like
turkey but don't you have your oh you
don't have Euro
oh Turkish C wait I feel like I never
got a Turkish donation ever
before this the first time I see TR Y is
it new do you guys did you guys get
super chats added recently or
what
oh try it good try a TR y donation for
good try
[Laughter]
right it's not part well you're kind of
part of of it you're pretty much part of
it I mean for for years now you've been
you're pretty much part of it Turkish
Yen or try to beat us we definitely
tried oh
whoa try is official in banking it's TL
Turkish L Naro oh thank you oh an egg
did you join today or
what so you had a very great campaign it
was a really good Arc I had so much fun
with like these streams winning is fun
man losing is not fun breaking news in
the waa news Studio no one ever knew
this before a local Austrian ostrich has
experienced that winning is fun
and she says that losing is indeed not
fun she does not recommend for other
people to lose because they might
experience some complicated despera
feelings that are not good for your
health and might result in uh hydration
leaving your body through your eyes
which is
weird do not feel uh uh stressed or or P
do not panic when this happens to
you uh it is a thing that science
scientists are currently looking
into
urgently but for now please do not panic
when you are losing and then feeling sad
feelings from it sad feelings are we
have been reported on before in the past
centuries H ever since
like oaba times we have heard of it
before it is still a mystery but one can
only hope to continue winning so that
the hydration stays in your body so
please continue to win guys try to win
so that you can be
happy that would be the best course of
action we will not know probably for the
longest time why today takik had to lose
that is something that our detectives
especially Emelia Watson will be looking
into thanks for the 20 memberships
hey we'll be looking into that and we'll
be reporting further information once we
are uh sure and certain about the
developments of winning and
losing and the causes of the loss
that led to the loss of hydration in
takanashi ki from Whole Life English
yeah
yeah best I'm better I'm a better
newscaster and commentator
huh thanks for the
[Music]
membership did the artist reply to you
not yet it's of the night for them so uh
Korean
artist I might ask JMA to upload it if
I'm not around when it uh comes
up yeah yeah no more watch alongs I kind
of want to do them but I don't know if I
can even get that into it if it's not
Austria and it just feels
like H I'll think about it I kind of
want to do
I kind of do want to do it but then
which now I've been just watching the
Austria matches you know but what what
matches do I choose to watch if I don't
have a particular team that I'm
following I would want to watch the
Netherlands one to see turkey
lose
Germany Germany I'm not German though
but and I don't know I think German team
is too
cocky Taxi Driver said the same
thing
England England sucks though like you
guys are not going to get far you may
have won previously but that was just
luck you if I start supporting England
I'm just going to be
disappointed I'm just going to be like
very disappointed and embarrassed again
from your
suckiness I can't support like that
would be such a stupid choice to make
for me which suckish food are you going
to try I don't even have to like try for
the first time I can just eat you know
you know we have a lot of Turkish food
in Austria so can just go eat a
kbab or or a durum or something like
that thanks for the raid
soon a man oh hey we have 21,000 votes
see these polls are fun birthday wait
it's 5050
literally woo happy
birthday on Saturday Sunday I'll be
having birthday
streams both Saturday and Sunday Sunday
is the merchandise stream so check it
out check it out I'll be in Japan during
it though so times will be a little bit
different different uh from my usual
streaming times I'd say Netherlands
they're orange
True they're orange and don't they have
the chicken what no that was France
France has a chicken on their
chest so France France actually has
great winning
chances and they have a chicken on their
chest maybe we should cheer from France
no
Sak m m
no I don't want to cheer for France I
don't feel connected to France at
all I don't
know ah women's women's European
Championship
2025 I think you need to stop doing the
streams you I think you won't be happy
if it's not Austria h
I don't know we we have to see maybe we
got to try it out once and see if I can
be happy for like into it if it if it's
even interesting if anybody else does it
I don't know like definitely for Austria
there's like this
personal like hope and
hype stream the Olympics when oh yeah
there yeah I was actually like
so like whoa Bamboozled that was just
two days ago or so somebody told me oh
yeah the Olympics haaha and I'm like
what do you mean Olympics like
what they're not happening anytime soon
and they just happened recently more or
less and I realized nope they are
happening this
year
soon
uh and I was like
it I was in I was in
Japan when the Olympics were supposed to
happen for a full year and they kept on
delaying it because of the seaing and I
waited and I waited uh and then I left
and the Olympics just happened after I
left I think um but it's already been
four years huh it's already been four
that's like
literally you can
measure that I've been in here four
years by realizing that the Olympics are
happening
but with Olympics I don't know like um
if I were to watch the
Olympics H surely there's some like what
would we even be watching there's so
much and I wonder how is is it like
really connected or is it like super
scattered like is there things that are
easy to watch and what what there's some
things that that austri is good at but
that's usually winter sports and I think
that would be winter
Olympics I mean honestly I don't maybe
maybe I wouldn't even care so much I
just want to watch it generally out of
Interest maybe am I going to be a
[\h__\h] Sports YouTuber what the [\h__\h]
what the
[\h__\h] beach volleyball what what's with
all the volleyball why why are you all
asking for volleyball is it because it's
hot or is there going to be hot
girls is that why you're asking for that
it's mixed genders right
Olympics it's not just guys like what
we've been seeing this like
these guys swinging their legs
around it's mix are you asking is there
a particular reason why you're asking
for
volleyball
why who's
it is it because it's cute women or
what what's up what's the
why booty
shorts bro I don't give a [\h__\h] about
volleyball
H I feel like golf would be
interesting actually probably not golf
what what what are Olympic wait let me
look it
up what are Summer Olympic
sports okay we
have oh wow there so much archery
artistic gymnastics artistic swimming
Athletics badminton baseball softball
what basketball basketball free times
free beach volleyball
boxing maybe we should watch Boxing
breaking what the [\h__\h] is breaking break
a leg or what Cano slum Cano Sprint
Cricket I think we might need to watch
cricket we should make a list of things
we want is is break dancing for no way
that's not a Olympic sport cycling BMX
freestyle cycling BMX racing cycling
mountain bikes cycling roads cycling
track sheesh so many D for diving ooh I
want to see that what do you mean what
are they diving for what is the what did
what do they do equestrian what the [\h__\h]
is equestrian is this on a horse this
picture shows me something like riding a
horse I think
horses is it just horse riding Speedy do
they just want to be
fast okay what do they dive for in
diving
though ah wait diving is not diving H
it's just like diving into the water
beautifully right like e wait that's
yeah it's ah [\h__\h] I just was thinking
about diving on the water it's just
jumping into it uh I'm I do uh I kind of
have an interest in that just because in
in Germany uh there was this
um Germans immediately know what I'm
talking about there was this
uh like U comedian guy Stefan laab who
made a show where uh amateure um
celebrities T spring and you now learn
how to do cool jumps to Spring and jump
diving you know into on the board from
up there into the
and they're all amateurs but like they
actually get good at it and it's like
actually really really
fun it it was an interesting watch I
used to watch that I didn't even know
most of the celebrities but
yeah yeah okay we have fencing ooh kind
of interest I'm kind of am interested in
that flag
football
what what is
that the picture shows like you have a
little thing hanging
[Music]
around your waist or your hip or so just
Capture the Flag or like what what is
that and he's holding the football in
his hand so it's like American
football American football but Flags
what the [\h__\h] and then there's wait
there's football in the Olympics there's
football in the
Olympics what do you mean there's
Olympics will Austria play
whoa
okay under 23
year that's kind of lame then golf
handball hockey hockey I think Austria
maybe has a good team cuz we are good at
winter sports so I'm just
assuming then there's a judo cool
Kate uh maybe lacrosse is to to me same
as Cricket
so maybe and there's some things that
are interesting to me Marathon swimming
modern pent pentatlon that kind of [\h__\h]
is
interesting cuz there's like uh five
different sports involved is that that
sounds fun and it's
modern it has uh I see someone shooting
it has someone uh is that fencing
swimming on a horse and running
that's
fun shooting you
say so no no not swimming on a horse no
it's
separate and there rithmic gymnastics
nah rowing nah that's not fun what the
[\h__\h] Rock B
sevens
sailing nah shooting shooting on its own
yeah y
well let's should I do a
no uh no
skateboarding uh
ooh sick maybe we should watch
skateboarding because of Tony
Hawk sport
climbing nah lame squash squash squash
is fun surfing
nah don't want to see stupid surf dudes
that are like yeah
bro
swimming nah table
tennis nah Tech W door ooh tennis I have
to watch Tennis cute can we see cute
tennis
skirts and then hear them go
like we got to watch tennis I care more
about tennis than beach
volleyball but I don't think Austria is
good at tennis
trampoline triatlon but that that one's
running swimming and uh cycling and
volleyball and water polo weightlifting
and
wrestling okay that are the sports I
think some of these I I'm interested in
if it aligns with my schedule
somehow maybe I'll want watch a bit is
it during like August because in August
I'm in Japan the whole
month and if it's like in
America I think the time zones would
be in my n maybe not in my favor because
it's not going to be American Prime Time
American prime time is okay for Japan
but it's going to be like noon and
afternoon right that's not so good in
Japan oh wait it's it was France never
mind that was uh America was something
else
oh
oh yeah I mean that's not that's not bad
actually if things are happening during
the day in France and it's like evening
in
Japan 26th July to 11th August oh that's
relatively short for doing so many
sports H are you guys interested in
another Sports
Arc I don't know
how it would like work
but like what the schedule would be how
long the streams would be how it's
connected but there's some interesting
Sports I would be especially down for it
if Austria is in any of
these right Sports a sporty maybe my
next outfit should be sports related
although the aerobics outfit is kind of
sporty where what the [\h__\h] are the
aerobics erotic aerobics where is that
sport in the Olympics
hey Olympics are fun you think
so you should watch the Olympics
openings wait I've always wanted to we
should like kind of make some something
out of this because I've always wanted
to um be the
torch first of all I should have uh
Olympic torch streaming asset but I also
should like somehow run a
marathon uh or so to represent the
torness of myself I don't
know I should just become the
torch yeah I I I've been the torch
before yeah yeah past Olympics I've been
the torch yeah yeah sure
yeah I have been once again commissioned
to be the torch I have to go run may
maybe we do like a marathon on my
treadmill how long does the torch run
normally is there even like uh
olymics how long does the torch run what
what kind of question is
that I think I didn't
even but am I asking the wrong question
wait
uh from at
a to
Paris I mean I mean not like during the
games I mean like how long do they run
until it reaches the venue or do they
not do that is that just in my
brain no wait there's a 68 day
3,100 mile
relay pre it says here
[Music]
um
uh better start
running what the [\h__\h] do you
[Music]
mean what the [\h__\h] do you mean 68
days this is like that
uh tears of the Kingdom
Quest why you have to I mean there's
several probably where you have to turn
on the
Torches gets pass around yeah just run
one part of the relay does it like ever
pass through
Austria where how do I where is the
route 10,000 athletes will carry the FL
I'll be one of
them I'll be one of
them oh it's just for France not other
countries
oh n where are they running would be
funny if they just one day one day in
the future in the future years like
running out side will be too hot so
they'll just run inside in an air
conditioned uh uh Sports Center and like
just run on a treadmill for 3,100
Miles the future is bright isn't it it's
bright from the apocalypse that is upon
us wa once again Doom posting
yeah okay I have um thanks to tangent
thing I have calm down my tears have
dried uh I
am still sad somewhere deep in my heart
there's a deep
sadness we just support Germany next now
you guys are too
cocky I no I don't want to
I I don't know maybe Netherlands cuz
they're orange
and you
know no we're not yes you are yes you
are Netherlands at least gave us a win
before that made me feel really good and
I appreciate
that they totally did that for me
they're so sweet they love me and and
they're not bad but I don't think they
will win either now this is going to age
badly if they
win but I feel like they will
not maybe I just don't support anyone
overall just in singular matches I'll
support one team and then we'll see how
that
goes they're trying Neverland is strong
I don't know if they're strong
enough Switzerland I didn't forget about
Switzerland I just don't know
if you guys are good I don't
know I don't have I know I don't know
man I'll have to think a bit about about
it I have a lot of time to think about
it but I think jenma would be very
relieved if I don't watch the next
match cuz she will be be forced to go to
the
studio and pull an all nighter for
me yeah maybe yeah the finale
honestly depends on when it is I
forgot I feel like I was not sure if I
could make it but the finale no matter
who it is it's just uh interesting in
general for
14th
ah uh yeah no I can make it I'm back
home on the
14th yeah and I have the evening free
have have something uh during the like
the like noon
afternoon
oo okay guys wait will watch the finale
for sure whoever it will be that'll be
exciting Yeah final watch okay we
probably won't do any more watchs in
between I'm too busy anyway honestly
it's it's really kind of my subconscious
was like I don't want to go too far
because I don't have time to watch them
it would be too sad if we continue and I
can't watch
it but we can watch watch the
finale I wonder who it will
be I wonder who it will
be Spain versus Netherlands that's
actually what I was just thinking about
but that's I was like maybe I just can't
think of any other countries but I I do
think there's a chance for
that h
H always ready for more fun streams yay
now I think I'll read some super chats
you know since I got a little bit more
time still or do
I yeah I should though no matter if I
have time I
should uh I still have to unpack and
pack
but it's okay you guys just got to tell
me when where where
let's spend some more time together
guys
boys yeah I don't think turkey will not
be in the final sorry sorry I I should I
should not piss off my Turkish fans too
much
but the ones that I here
now
um anyone who knows uh oh thank you
DD bu BL Minecraft birday 6 thank you
you're the
best I am my tummy you know the past
weeks this is not something you want to
hear but I am um without even trying I
am kind of like you know parasocial and
oversharing and uh I guess U I don't
even want to like do this girlfriend
thing but like it I'm un unwan thingly
doing it um so let me just tell you I
was so confused the past two weeks or
so
I have had constant tummy
issues and okay the past six seven days
I could blame it on
stress because uh is definitely
stressful
but it it was even before that and I've
been eating all kinds of things so I
don't know what the hell was the
issue but I think today was
fine today today this is interesting
maybe my stress is lifted not really
though today might actually no maybe
it's still kind ah it might still be
kind of now it's mostly no today was
normal why am I telling you this though
I don't know I want to tell you I want
to tell you because it was
like why is my tummy like
this need to get those fibers not too
much sugar not too much fat but it's not
like I really changed my food intake
much like the stuff that I eat wasn't
that different that it would [\h__\h] me up
for like two or 3
weeks maybe it's still aftermath
from getting food poison no I don't
believe it
though when's your baby due it was due
in this match but some reason I just
couldn't burf it
out it was
stuck it got [\h__\h] stuck I had the
goal in my tummy and I just couldn't get
it out no it's it it was more like like
that's not how my tummy HT was going um
but yeah whatever I'm
oversharing uh sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry
um H uh day six day six day six day six
okay sad Super Chat raing no
I'm not that sad but
um I'm not anymore but we put it
there I'm going get rid get rid of the
timer
um
there no I didn't have girl
dinners no
look up the conversion rate for those
try super for
fun for which
one what one why I just saying that
because it's like ARS like really really
bad don't look it
up they're joking about it in the Super
Chat
M I cannot I can only see the orange one
right
now don't look it up it's so bad because
it's like ARS you mean are you saying
it's just really bad I don't
understand it's still money don't look
it
up what
okay
a okay it's just bad okay okay I thought
it was like something like if you
converted the the number is funny
haha oh thank you
FR
oh exchange R bad rate bad same like
Japan man same with Japan man come on
come on
convert
better do you guys want
bgm you want some bgm H do you want some
HH you want you want what do you what do
you want some
bgm you want a bgm sad
bgm sad Sparks Alexa play sad
Sparks I don't have that much sad music
to be
honest I don't want to no no not for the
Super Chat reading like what like
this
wait I used this bgm long time ago was
it my first or second anniversary or
so I played this and you guys thought I
would say
something like really bad
oh please accept my hyper FL currency it
can buy one Kebab extra tahini and a
slice of
apple thank you I've been kind of like I
normally don't eat kbop and that kind of
stuff
but I don't dislike it I just I I I I
kind
of just I don't know I I like the
food and this is weird but I feel a
little bit intimidated to
go um not like they I don't know it's
just not intimidated I just don't feel
like
uh and I don't
know I
don't I want to I don't
know I don't know what's the right word
something like intimidating but I just
feel like
this I'm not like I feel like
I don't know like they'll think I'm like
some dumb ass little white
little I don't know anime wee girl
feeling think
I'm like what
the I don't know I'm not I'm not like
cool enough to go get a kbop oh this sad
music is making this speech kind of
weird
no no I'm not cool enough to order
[Music]
kop why is this so sad it's like oh I
really want give up I really want some
give up but I'm not cool
enough someone stopped this music man
it's going to make me cry
M you cool to me really a thank you so
much brain rot music let's go okay we're
going to read
from wait let me find the
thumbnail this one
[Music]
okay D Cod than py she don't stop won't
stop W goes her own way if this is what
you want boss kfp I will be kfp will be
there day six let's go man Minecraft Arc
was followed directly by football Arc or
like kind of interjected a little bit
but I like I like I've been liking these
arcs hope you guys have been having fun
with those arcs now the the next Arc is
kind of sad because the next Arc is just
Wawa being mostly gone
Arc but I I do want to say these past
arcs like okay now I was gone for a few
days but before that I was really on a
grind I've been streaming a lot and yeah
the Minecraft streams you know I've been
putting a lot into
that I've been streaming a lot
[Music]
so I was hoping to like ahead of time
make up a little bit for me being gone
the following
[Music]
days yeah but I I've been having fun so
hopefully you guys too thank you D hood
for the pinky take a 47 d space
wonderful D and D Hood again D and zip
thanks for the r Super Chat I escaped
from the bucket two years baby what
thanks for the right super chat but I
feel like you've been around for four
years
huh
simply feel you've been around
longer but wait escaping the
bucket isn't
it oh wait no then you get armor why
don't you have arm I feel like you've
been been around forever my calendar
says otherwise what to me yeah you
you're basically an
OG my brain tells me you knew me before
you even knew that you knew
[Music]
me speaking of a at the Olympics one of
my favorite
moment the
gold
oh no idea never I don't I didn't watch
anything
Olympic no Olympic input for me
in generally not just
2020 not not just that year 2020 but
before
[Music]
to yeah anyway diply thank you for the
red super chat Mah M
[Music]
dly thank you so much for the support
finally you're freed from the bucket and
now you're a hybrid hey bird hi
bird Maxim kick d ID business regulation
Director D
P I need to upload the the freaking clip
man marinski D sounds like a sininsky
soundss like a the name of a football
player like somebody would have that
name Common Sense bro thanks Shan I like
your name
dratic
Arrow thank you
Quin Mig
dur J monkey golden
Lord evang Mac 4906 tun late fee late
fee late
fee I need to pay my bills [\h__\h] check
your channel D orbit Till Dawn thanks
for the pinky AI summary wah an idol
vtuber discusses her busy schedule for
the year which includes her birthday
World Tour 3D showcases and other
appearances meanwhile she faces an issue
of potentially getting arrested for tax
evation this is so good so good it's not
t tax
evasion not no it's just the
delay
delay but I just wish you know I would
have been reminded like telling me one
month prior and uh or so to pay my taxes
and then and then Telling Me 2 weeks
after I'm late that oh by the way you
were
[Music]
late but I Jones D King Jim
Tracy
mrf golden Dan Ohio enjoyer Dan I want
to enjoy Ohio
too D
Dan what is
this baby growing up behind the brown
doors start to grow change your job to
something new boss don't need need no
Sleeps
Tonight
nice Minecraft villager version of fever
night I like
it and GD D thank
you yeah with all the stress and the
traveling that I am about to do and have
been doing I'm I also realized that I'm
in high danger of getting
sick so I got to be
careful take out the vitamin yeah Now's
the Time I should take
it Now's the
Time okay next is uh one super chat from
the first watch along
from Cruz
dun the first uh football watch long and
then the
[Music]
k
k h
thumbnail don't don't bibl no don't the
thumbnail don't
thumbnail what the [\h__\h] is it here
I don't I don't know where it
is ah
here
okay
Min Cru d py d ja Monkey D jaob 47 D and
dark Hood with the red super chat thank
you we are living in the material world
and W is a cutie PTI did I I didn't even
sing material world but I love that song
Thank you very much D
good yeah Material World cute song next
time I'll sing it again maybe so
fun good song yeah good choice madon wa
[Music]
gaming thank
you Ron D El Dang d
attack why D attack are you here I have
a question thank you for your red super
chat but I have a question
why are we attacking the Ducks all the
time duck
attack why what has the duck
done literally today was Duck's birthday
we shall not be attacking the
ducks on such a beautiful
day
yeah you sit what wa is his name duck
attack you say duck attack all the time
yeah imagine if the name was just duck
attack literally like written like
that and I was never
reading super chats ever that was never
the case but no DCH doesn't seem to be
here maybe once you're back tell me why
we're attacking those Ducks love the 80s
outfit Tel glad you're bringing his
historical attire back from the previous
century and lots of good music from that
time as well you and your colleagues at
Hol life continue to impress glory to KY
thank
you yay yay yay yay I we have we went
back a little bit in time and honestly a
part of me even wants to do like a a
beautiful like anbin style medieval
outfit but I just feel like it wouldn't
translate very well and it wouldn't be
like you
know that's just my
personal preference of like I love his
medieval beautiful dresses they can be
so beautiful but I feel like they're
more beautiful in reality by far than
they are uh in as like an anime style
illustration I don't think we can do it
that much Justice and it's not going to
be
[Music]
very like for example it would cover all
of the legs the only spiciness we have
is like a nice a nice pushed up
BBA and that's nice but like would it
become such a popular choice to draw fan
art for
no for example I don't think many people
would be drawing it you know sadly
ankles ankles
y so yeah I don't know yeah but anyway
thank you for enjoying my new outfit
thanks J
D I appreciate
it yeah now I have to think really hard
what I should do for the next outfit I
really need to make a decision soon so
that we can have it maybe in winter time
at this point it might be winter if I
make a decision
nowish
scandalous ankles oh yeah
oh
y thank
[Music]
you thanks for the pinky I got you ma'am
thank you what is this for thank you so
oh for holding the
waas did I ask you guys to hold the waas
there's no
way I didn't actually ask you to do that
did you did I
thank you I did what is the
context now must be some special
circumstances
nah oh s oh I was making some jokes
during SOS ah yeah I was just like
thinking SOS what could I be needing
help with I guess my booies
and you're the first to volunteer for it
wow thank you chicken okab d space
waterfall dun so many volunteers
but it's over it's too late maxic King n
Studio ra thanks pinky SOS is my
favorite ala song Thank you so much
really wa you're welcome I knew that of
course I knew that that's why dang it
just for
you thank you thank you thank you so
much Studio
Rob want to sing more ABA songs there's
just so many good
ones Elis come back D soon Modern
Talking next time hopefully if I don't
forget time for the gimer cree D chicken
Pump It Up p p Pump It Up Sky d the Mad
kitten D Kashi f for the pinky hi Teno
love the new outfit it's actually my
birthday
today um actually really happy birthday
so glad to spend a part of it with you
your energy and incredible heart art I
don't know why I'm reading it like that
continue to be a bright light and make
me proud to be KY looking forward to the
rest of the year review thank you me too
me
too it's kind of
devastatingly shocking that half a year
is already over and my birthday is
coming up and I don't know I don't know
why are we so far into
2024 I don't like
it this stressing me
out it's like ever since I joined Holo
time has been flying so much so
fast
yeah because I've been working so much
time flies
faster which means like I feel like I
can't I can't live in the moment as
much 14
years time moves so fast
yeah well happy birthday
Kobayashi happy birthday day I hope you
had a wonderful birthday I'm a little
bit late in congratulating you but I
wish you a lovely
lovely
uh continuous
life that reminds me I was like in the
airplane on the way to Germany and then
like people were B deboarding they were
leaving the plane right and in front of
me there was like a young lad maybe like
let's say 15 16 or whatever and he sat
next to an older lady but not that old
she looked like
maybe 50 60
maybe and I was like we were getting up
we were waiting for a turn to leave uh
the airplane one by one
and the young lad I just I had my noise
cancelling headphones on but I kind of
overheard this like greeting they said
to each other or more like he said it to
the lady they didn't seem to be together
right so he
says he says in German he
says to the older
lady which
means a a a nice remaining life
I'm I'm like did you really just say
that isn't that somehow so
like like come on she's she didn't even
look that old but he's like in his
[\h__\h] teens like you don't say that
normally when I like like sometimes when
I'm like friendly with a stranger on the
airplane and we have a nice conversation
and then we like go separate ways and I
say goodbye I just like say safe travels
or
something what was her reaction she was
just like thank you or so I didn't hear
their reaction so well
but yeah just like normal thank you kind
of but I was I heard it I was like did I
just hear that correctly like did you
actually that's so rude
somehow you're like making her feel
older and it sounds like you are you're
looking at her in a way that you're like
oh she this this woman is so old she
looks like she's gonna die soon so I
better wish her a nice remaining
life no he said friendly but it sound
it's just so ignorant like so naive and
ignorant like don't say that I never
heard that before you don't say that to
Old older people just because they are
old looking to you you don't say I wish
you're a nice remaining life and it's
also kind of threatening but it's wasn't
meant frightening but it's like you're
going to make that person feel even
older I've never heard that before
that's not a thing German
[Music]
say like the only context where I can
see this work but even then I I'm not
sure if I would say this to a stranger
if they have a conversation on the
airplane where the older person is like
I I have cancer or something and I will
die in uh one month or so
then that would be a like fitting but
would it be appropriate to hear from no
I I don't think that's
appropriate
bro but it would make more sense right
because teenager thinks old woman dies
soon but anyway that's just
weird I'm like did you just say that
you've got no manners you don't you
don't understand how to greet people
that's
funny
hul Flappy pinky T Tu you mean turbular
turbular and red K right now even more K
and Skyrim coming up very soon what Oh
you mean the new members H EU is
thriving at long last don't think we'd
ever got gotten here without years of
passionate and sometimes only Pioneer
work done by
youo yeah it took them a long time to
get some EUR some other Europeans in um
I wouldn't really say that it's that I
had any I mean I I have been saying for
many years now like we're the Europeans
but I wouldn't say they tried harder to
get
Europeans for the sake of me or if
anything they just maybe generally felt
like they want Europeans now because
that's one market that they haven't
really pushed much it was probably more
of a strategic kind of thing
yeah I will say though like it's kind
of I've seen like
some like clip titles or so where it's
like put in a light as if like there was
no European in whole life before and
it's like all Europeans are saved by
these new
members you're Europe has been saved but
whole Justice or these new me yeah I'm
like bro and then I go into the comment
section just to see if people like if if
I'm just like completely taking this the
wrong way if there's anyone else
who felt the same way and there were
others who felt the same way and there
were also others who were like
continuing the sentiment and I was like
brah
brh I'm right here I'm right here
yo will you still give twitch multi
streaming a
chance yes I know I always say this but
just don't I'm just like there's too
much other [\h__\h] on my mind so I can't
really think about it
[Music]
mistook me as an
Australian no I don't
think so
but yeah it's just
um I'm going to give them the benefit of
the doubt and say they just
uh you
know I don't know whatever
[Music]
yeah I don't think like we need to
be like too strict at uh like I think
like clip Clippers in the end like they
are just trying their best to get the
clips watched so sometimes maybe a
thumbnail or a title will be a little
bit click baity I don't think I don't
think you like we should be um mad at
every single little clip bity thing
that's just how YouTube is and that's
what you got to do to um get through you
know to grind get the views and all that
it's like not generally I don't think
it's a problem you know
um click
baiting as long as it's not
malicious then I think it's oh
you know they're just doing what they
got to do just don't be malicious with
it now I'm not saying that that was
malicious though that wasn't malicious
it was probably just a little
bit ignorant maybe but it's
okay there's been some good Wawa clips
and I appreciate that oh yeah recently
there's been some good ones yeah
appreciate
that yeah thanks guys but but really no
need to like um defend me too much or
anything like it's sweet of you guys but
don't worry too much about
it oh like unless it's it's really
bad thank you thank you thank you we
don't want to like make Clippers scared
of clipping
me that would be not not good because
there's a lot of people who you know
could potentially become a fan for Clips
so a lot of clip Watchers is out
[Music]
there let's make Clippers scared of not
clipping you
oh
exactly looks at putting channel in the
chat at this very
moment as we have you in the chat right
now I shall point fingers at
you all righty okay don't attack me
please ah KB bring out the knives come
on nice
nice
nice sweats profusely as he should as he
should thank you yeah I do want to say
thanks to the people who have been
clipping me um these past weeks thank
you very much very nicely nice Clips out
[Music]
there I did like the one clip of my
first football watch along was a
compilation of me screaming
and and screaming some more that was
funny spanking face love pinky okay
here's some love for the 80s woo woo my
mom also really enjoyed the the outfit
and the music but she did say that it
was too wobbly like too much wobbling
going
on um so she would probably appreciate a
little bit less wobbliness but she did
like the the music choices and the the
theme
itself yeah too much water in your
boobies
understandable yeah I I kind of agree
with it to a certain extent probably not
as much as she dislikes like how much
she would remove the
wobbliness she would probably remove too
much oh yeah 3D model yeah yeah yeah
yeah how is that um I'm going to buy it
off
of uh the
Creator and I think we I'm I
I'm going to buy it
yeah yeah I'm allowed to use it but I
I'm going to pay some money and then I
get to use it so you found one yeah I
think I retweeted it on
Twitter or did I just reply to it I
don't know fite 3D model it looks really
good cheap
skate the cre cre is right here is it
slan or Sian I don't
know I retweeted
it can you use it for mvs well I don't
know if I would use it for upcoming mvs
because it was the fite outfit it would
have had to be used for fite but I am
thinking maybe I could
commission you
for like future MV outfits can you work
off of a reference that I give you and
if I give you like a naked model of uh
official naked model of myself can you
like model it onto
that cuz I am looking for someone who
can do
that for future mvs
possibly actually speaking of that we
need to hurry the [\h__\h] up on uh creating
the next
song yeah B we need to speed that
process up and I've been too busy
to speed it up myself um
God damn
[Music]
it yes okay it's a
yes
uh why does
[Music]
okay what the
[\h__\h] it says you know my my Angels team
who creates my songs all of them
recently Johnny it says on on Discord
that Johnny is playing
Roblox the [\h__\h] why are you playing
Roblox isn't that a children's game does
anybody over 12 play that
game
inspiration why aren't you playing robo
I'm over 12 that's
why okay um yeah thanks for the love for
the 80s d d d for the
pinky I love you all these K these are
the best thank
you H it has been like um pretty
nostalgic for me to like learning some
of the songs I've only heard before a
few times but like never was able to
sing them
like that
one spicy song that I
[Music]
did I love that I had uh was like yeah
Careless Whisper I love that I finally
gave myself an opportunity to learn that
song Dax Jaden d c beans D J D B Jones D
glass d h d Lord D Mr v d Peter Cy
Tim Fusion AR or
form pinky hi how you feeling are you
did you write that Super Chat like
thinking about the future waa reading
this are you ask did you ask the future
w
wow wow what a
foresight current waa is feeling like
terrified of ending the stream
because um I don't even want I just want
to stay home
I just want to stay
[Music]
home oh that still dead I worked uh all
of them uh away I still have like a few
more things to do um until like the
weekend but I can do that on the weekend
when I have studio
time when I have the PC at the studio
can you stay with us a while longer no
if I stay longer I won't get a get to
sleep because I still have to pack and
eat so I'm just going to finish these
super chats and then I'll probably go wa
thank you watermelon
[Music]
waiter W thank you so much for the red
super chat and happy birthday to
us
a you learn you start started to learn
German
good luck with that are you learning
with the green bird
huh thank you so much M I'll read it
again properly when I get to those super
chats oh man I really I really don't
like how this summer is looking like so
much work and stress and traveling it's
like I think it's the worst year so far
in terms of the amount of work and I'm
I've been seeing I'm not the only one
complaining like I see other
members complaining about deadlines a
lot
too I think it might be especially bad
for me because it's all clashing
together right now the the myth uh
anniversary
preparations my own 3D birthday live
stream uh like that is going to be like
later delayed but still I'm I've been
working on that uh 3D and the Ian
concert uh all kinds of
conventions and the world tour which I
have been one of the few selected ones
to be
in yeah I have lots of studio time this
year
but uh maybe it's a little bit too
much it's so much on my plate this
summer and I'm trying to still balance
it with some of my own fun things that I
wanted to do like you know going to
Germany just now and you know I don't
want to that that I booked that my hotel
and all that like almost a year in
advance I decided to go like really
early last year so
I kept that schedule open for like a
year so that I could
go um and I wasn't going to cancel it
just because things get busy I'm not
going to not going to cancel something
I've been planning for so long just
because the rest is
overwhelming I hope you're still not
still air conditioner challenge for
learning coros what do you mean hot you
mean in my home actually right now like
uh recently the like fake weird air
conditioning has been starting to work
again and it's been pretty chilly but
it's been uh kind of chilly outside too
so I've been
fine but I got to learn
some coros the next coming days
yeah yeah anyway let me continue and
finish this up I wish I could talk more
of you and just chill at home this week
and chill with my cats but we'll get
through this we'll get through this
summer together okay we got to stay
strong August will be fine because I I
think it will be fine because I have
I'll have a stream set up but this month
is just [\h__\h] I'm so
sorry I I didn't want it to be this bad
either but it just this is the
result of me like I I can't just like
pass up on you know being part of the
the world tour or something like that
you know that I would regret that that's
not even in my head that option is not
even in my head
so you know it'll be worth it it'll be
worth
it um so yeah that's how I'm feeling
Nathan thanks for asking but I dou Jones
D for the pinky I love it when K does
her addition of King ha
thank you ah new new people will not
understand this joke anybody like who
does who comes to kfp in the past two
years or three years even and doesn't
look up old memes of kfp will not
understand
this pyro okarina CH
Wang Luna loyalist ooh from
Australia I unironically actually enjoy
Rick and his autotuned vocals I find him
and your cover of his iconic song lar
pleasing
autotuned is he so autotuned that you
would say that I I've never
really
like I'm confused but thank you for the
red super chat
doesn't really come across that auditude
to me maybe nowadays
or he just sounds like that it doesn't
even
sound that how some people perceive
it
[Music]
confused yeah I mean he's surely a good
singer
and people say autotude but I feel like
most of the time it's it's not that
automatic like it's very carefully tuned
rather Auto
autotune I think autotune is just
something for
amateurs um it's not it's more like
manually tuned most of the
time oh man this [\h__\h] is so manually
tuned she sucks she can't sing she's
manually tuned
people just say aune to
everything yeah pitch corrected
bro that's what's
happening and and like any even the best
singers get pitch corrected and you
know adjusted in
post everything there's no raw vocals on
any CD ever
is to is how it is Luna loyalist thank
you
just
wonderful
a no that's that's
crickets go
D simply D FR Jim Tracy thanks for the
pinky thanks for the great K you totally
rocked it it's always cool to see you
singing Classics and the feite outfit is
purfect for this yay throw in some rent
songs and even a Korean song and it was
another classic K okay yay one k one
Korean one
yeah oh [\h__\h] I just sneezed out the
goal I just sneezed out the goal
referee That was supposed to come out a
different way and way earlier can we
still get the goal is it too
late man [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it's all my fault
it's all my
fault thanks for the
[Music]
membership sorry man sorry Austria I'll
take I'll take the responsibility
[Laughter]
thank you for the
[Music]
membership don't say that game
8910 what the [\h__\h] am I even supposed to
call you game game is like not really a
proper nickname I'll call you gamey from
now on if I address you like
this I think they were definitely in
nervous if if these like like super
successful football players can't even
be nervous do you think they'll they're
nervous
guys I wonder if they're I would say
they're nervous but maybe they just are
not nervous anymore and yeah the rain
definitely didn't help but I mean the
rain affects everyone so
early gold ruined the whole morale I I
feel like an early goal wouldn't ruin
their morale because they would be like
easy we can still totally do it like
there's no problem with this this is so
early that it's actually like if
anything it's
welcome it's more motivating even that's
how I would think
but it it it might throw him off but at
the same time I feel like it's no
[Music]
concern you don't think so
huh
damn maybe I should be the coach and
teach them to not have it [\h__\h] up their
morale a where was
I I know here I was
here no I was here Jim Tracy
[\h__\h] thank you Jim Tracy for the G
again hey thanks for enjoying the k m JT
D Al D and GD D how the [\h__\h] did I take
like 50 minutes since that one time when
I said I'll read uh
what what what but wait did I read two
streams in 50 minutes that's not too bad
for
[Music]
my my
normal
Pace yeah okay I got to
go I got to go
[Music]
I got to
go
uh
uh kind of want to I don't even I want
to make the schedule but I don't have
the schedule art yet the new one and
[\h__\h] it's kind of late I don't know I
don't have have time maybe maybe I'll
make make like a a small smaller smaller
schedule smaller smaller schedule for uh
the weekend
only is there any point in making a
schedule yeah because it's birthday
weekend and I uh it will like get more
people's attention ahead of time that
there's waha birthday on the weekend
that they should be
there definitely makes sense
um yeah I'll just probably throw
together
something uh once I'm in
Japan W
birday I can't believe it I wish I had
something more exciting planned but I've
never done the Koka thing before and
well you know Tot so much is always fun
I hope some members have time though I
hope they have time um it's PST prime
time so
it's actually good time for Japan and
na so I hope some people will show up
for
it if you guys can think of any like
special gimmick for it that doesn't
require too much preparation let me know
maybe maybe cuz I don't have anything
currently I don't have a gimmick
whatsoever
[Music]
remember the message with Japanese SES
right of the manag um I might just throw
we have like a shared server finally
where people are telling others about
these kind of events I just I'll throw a
message in there but I I don't really
think I think it'll be main mainly Ian
and ID calls and that's
fine not necessarily a spin the wheel
but like whatever is just a theme or
gimmick I don't
know yeah so we're will the merch also
be available on geek Jack yeah as per
[Music]
usual
so but I don't want to
gol but I really got to
go
and bye next stream is
ah I
I what no no next stream
is possibly the earliest stream will be
well the countdown stream PST Friday uh
11:00
p.m.
yeah I'm a bit busy the days before for
already immediately getting to work and
I don't have the studio reserved anyway
but maybe Twitter
space I'm
stalling and in German we say you new
you're welcome what it's three months
you're not that well I guess it's new
compared to others but
welcome yellow card for stalling ah at
least I'm not faking an
injury I'll V
in it's okay it will be fun it will be
fun waa it will be
fun right will it be
[Music]
fun I don't know I don't like things
right now [\h__\h] I just had a really fun
weekend that was but also really
exhausting I just want to I just want to
take it easy but [\h__\h] I got to go I'm
got to go and grind go
grind trust the process yay let's trust
the
process I trusted the Austrian process
and it failed me
though see you on my birthday weekend
guys uh see you in
Japan and German he
doesn't I'll miss you and my
cats bye bye I to pack
[Music]
wo YouTube kind of loading super fast
YouTube Studio what's wrong also the the
some some of the UI kind of
changed everything is loading
surprisingly fast today wow did YouTube
actually make some
improvements y
[Music]