[Music]
so
uh
[Music]
hmm
oh my god help me oh
the game is not being
considerate because we i tapped out and
now it's like
not where where it's supposed to be
anymore what the hell
and also my cats are being not very
considerate either because
because because they took a nap before
the stream a long nap
and then and now yeah she's like
they were like hello hello hello i'm a
cat hello hello hello i
know you now now now please please pay
attention to me please
pay attention to me pay attention to me
look at me look at me look at me i'm a
cat i'm a cat meow meow meow meow meow
meow meow cat i'm okay
and a meow meow meow meow
[Music]
let's read the air today
wait a second go here
wow oh you don't even hear that there we
go
uh jotun music
oh it's like you could you could dance
the waltz
to that i think you call it the waltz in
english right it's
you hear that don't ya wow
just imagine swaying over the dance
floor with a beautiful
beautiful phoenix girl like me
hand in hand body
close to one another doing
steps and then kiada being super
inconsiderate because she's stupid and
steps on your foot
a million times a million times because
even though kiara is australian
she cannot i repeat she cannot dance the
wolves
uh think that dance comes from our
country
unfortunately i cannot dance it so i
would step on your foot the whole time
but
if you would take me anyway then let's
do it
the dance i mean
uh sorry every time every time we tab
out it's the music stop so oopsie
today uh is the continuation
today's the continuation i wonder
if one day i get a 3d
maybe i maybe aki senpai knows how to
dance the walls
maybe she could teach me how to do but i
mean even then i would probably not be
able to dance it because i've been
taught
loki taught it before but i just can't
wrap my head
my head around it i just can't
which by the way reminds me of before we
get into it let me just remind you guys
that it reminds me of something
uh hold up this weekend on
uh for american countries it's on it's
my on my schedule on sunday but for
american countries we said it again
it's uh
saturday um
canada and so on also must be
so like over there you know on the on
the west side of the globe
it's mostly saturday but for me it's a
sunday
uh 1am
it gets worse it doesn't even start at
midnight anymore
it gets worse starts at 1am
i was like when i was when i was asking
aki senpai
um i didn't even think about it much i
was like aki senpai
would you wanna do you wanna um be a
guest on holotalk
at 8 00 am japanese standard time
because that's the
uh the time we did it last time and i
didn't realize that that now means for
me because daylight saving time it now
doesn't mean midnight anymore for me
which was still okay
it now means 1am yeah i'm usually awake
at that time but starting a stream at
that time
is not very smart because that would
take like
probably one and a half hours so it
would be half past two when it ends
and then you know i can't sleep in a
minute i need like
two hours or something like that to you
know
get to sleep for real so it doesn't work
like that i can't be like okay
bam stream is over one minute later
kiana is sleeping
no so that's why i try to even though
i'm awake at that time i don't want to
start a stream at that time but
that's what happened um but trust me
this is probably
we got to do something about the time
because
i can't do holo talk at 00 am the whole
summer until it's uh winter time again i
can't do that
uh but yeah anyway this weekend this
whole talk with aki
rosenthal senpai from the first
generation so please check it out she's
very interesting and i think i mean
i've seen that a lot of english-speaking
viewers uh have paid attention to her
anyway already
um but she maybe doesn't get as much
attention as others
however she definitely deserves so so so
so much attention
she has so much experience has a
beautiful singing voice has a bunch of
singles out
dance is like a ballerina and
she's she's a really good project
planner and all that kind of stuff like
she has a lot of stuff to talk about too
so i'm really really looking forward to
um interview her she has interesting
stories like if you watch her clips as
well she talks a lot of
a lot of deep stuff as well so i think
it's going to be a great
um great whole talk episode
[Music]
um what uh
i'll catch zaka that's okay too if i was
you
then if you were me no if i was if you
were me you would be doing home talk
if i was you i would i don't know if i
was myself i'd probably do that too
because it starts at freaking 1 a.m for
me
[Music]
ah yeah we're gonna do a different kind
of
time it doesn't work like that
so anyway today we're playing the
continuation of consider it which is in
english it's called consider it more
and it's kooky yummy i explained this
last time
because we played it exactly one week
ago we played the first game
it's a small game with cute funny
drawings
that show you situations
uh very quickly with a really short
time limit and you have to instantly be
like
have like a light bulb above your head
and be like okay that's what i gotta do
and you gotta instantly react to the
situation
uh and adjust yourself to reach the air
read the room in japanese you call
such a situation uh yeah
[Music]
well read the air and if you can't read
it then you are a ky
we have learned that last time um i
think
i think the ky stands for cookie yomu or
like yuma yomanai someone who cannot
read the air
we don't want to be that kind of person
can't shut up
i was really good at reading the air
last time and i have to say
cause i i didn't want to be the one that
pointed it out but
yes pankora pagoda senpai said i am
a genius at reading the room she said
that
two days after my last considerate
stream because
because of the minecraft stream where
she built
uh a trap for me and muna
senpai and uh i
knew it was a freaking trap but i went
in there anyway and i was like
because muna senpai was about to sleep
in her own bed
instead of the trap and i was like when
a senpai said bye
wouldn't you like to sleep together with
me because i'm scared in the dark you
know i can't sleep alone
that was me being super considerate
towards piccolo doesn't fight because i
didn't want you know i wanted to travel
to work the way she wanted it because i
knew
i knew that she wanted it to happen
because obviously it was obvious
you know and then later on i did i did
some
eco search in japanese i typed in
and it wasn't because pekuda senpai um
like especially a japanese audience they
all
write tweets uh uh
after a stream with the stream hashtag
they all do there's like always millions
of them
and then there were like a million of
tweets of piccolo senpai's fans
mentioning me saying kiara
is uh so good at reading the air
she everyone said oh she's so good at
kooky you'll move
oh she's such a good area everyone said
it
everyone agreed no not ex
look at the [\h__\h] off you by yourself
it's not true
[Music]
it's true they didn't even know that
they would be read by me it's
joke it's
you look at the kiara chan and then you
see all the tweets from the nosagies who
are writing
cookies
that's what they've been saying okay so
and i think we all know
that i can read the room so i'm ready
for the second part uh
are you guys ready too i think there's
one addition
i mean obviously it's new situations but
i think also
uh that this time we get a
real evaluation like with actual text
uh from what i've heard it starts from
the second game on there's three games
now
the second one gives you a proper
evaluation with a lot of
deep insight which i'm really excited
[Music]
okay okay let's go let's consider some
situations shall we you can do it
together with me you can think what
would i do
in that moment it's it's still like
[Music]
built like in in the japanese culture
setting so some of you guys might not
get it that much me neighbors sometimes
because it's too quick but over let's go
let's go
this is a space where you're free to
consider things as you like there is no
one here to stop you from being as
considerate as you please
after considering the situation move the
red object on the screen
sometimes there may be nothing to move
just do what you consider the
appropriate action
if you wish to stop playing just push
the escape key
okay number one
it must be visible it must be visible
they did that in japanese uh
tv and everywhere yeah yeah they
announced a new era
the area of the phoenix okay what is
this oh
huh i think that was okay
what ah the boy give it to the boy
nice he deserves it
number four
oh uh let's make it green so she can
go good grandma good good good good that
was for a moment i was scared that the
cars would drive over her number five
i'll do it ah
i'm good i'll do it and then yes i
understand let me let me say i'll do it
i want to say i'll do it no what huh
i knew what i had to do and you you
you're like i'll do it i'll do it
know i like i only know that there is
the arrow keys and
that's basically it in japanese comedy
shows they're like
uh i'll do it and the next person says
i'll do it and the next person says
abdullah and then they're all like ah
then then you can do it those are those
space was it space god damn it
i thought most most of the times if you
want to raise your hand in the game it's
up arrow i did that
let's eat ramen
ramen your salt that's for for
uh amelia there's a salt ramen did you
guys know that
let's get some amelia ramen huh
i mean it's assault focused ramen chip
right and we're going to get that thanks
for the meal
those waiting for recipes from a line
starting here oh i'm done
i wanna i wanna get out i wanna i wanna
get out how do i get out
i was pressing everything i was pressing
uh a space too here we go
oh wait what the oh my god what i'm so
fast why am i so fast
[Music]
cheese ah
oh oh wait oh wait oh that was being in
concert i was like i know this situation
i wanted to take a photo of what i was
supposed to go by
oops main tablet take it take it i can't
i can't do anything
wait why why why why what
is there a controller
the mouse you use the mouse now
you sure books close what
sorry i didn't really read i guess i'll
go for
[Music]
escaping it's not working either didn't
they say press escape if you're done
huh huh
didn't i can't i can't i can't break
this game
[Music]
i know okay
yes that's not cool
there is no race is
settings either video
no how to play is just the same thing
that you
told us in the beginning
interrupting the game is inconsiderate
shut up now
how to play fingers is the same that
they told us in the beginning like
remove the red object blah blah
i'll try again and see if the
if the if the mouse really
oh i can continue no but i want to do
new because i knew what to do
i don't have a controller plugged in no
no at the moment
no but let's try but it shouldn't be the
mouse
that keyboard i wonder is it dead
keyboard
wait let me change it to german keyboard
jeremy keyboard is technological
improvement
deutsche technology
okay let's try i'll keep the mouse here
don't don't
mind my mouse maybe i need it
[Music]
yes
there we go okay
german science german keyboard secretary
oh okay still learning i'll just do the
same thing because i
i'm not sure i'm not what are you doing
should i
did i move too far um
can i really do anything with the mouse
no
you take the ball you take it you take
the ball i take the foul
because i love you son
steal it now okay green
go good grandma good grandma
okay i want to say i'll do it i'll do it
i'll click i do everything no no
it doesn't no i pressed everything on
the keyboard
i wanna say i'll do it i wanna
like sometimes it works though
but at this i think if it would if
it would be a bad keyboard it would like
stop working at certain like uh and
random times but now it stopped working
again at that specific time
um let's continue
this game is not being considered kooky
under your gamer
wasd i'll try those
i'm sorry i'm salt ramen oh yeah
wasd works too let's try with those
[Music]
okay ctrl w
i don't trust you i
[Music]
i clicked on the character too hmm okay
anyway
so i'm gonna
spacebar i pressed the spacebar too
because the spacebar seems to be
okay in the game
okay what about here like no
no
i wanna
i couldn't give him a mint i tried
[Music]
what i still didn't really about the
book ah because the books are heavier
okay i went there by instinct but
the books are heavier so that's why they
want me to go
i was trying to give him some risks what
the hell
the game is is manipulating me but okay
whatever we'll be considering anyway
ah yay i'll have you let's hit
one bite okay being considered let's
take a small bite
i wish i could get the strawberry but
i'll tickle
tiny bite from the tip
here this bite oh
i didn't get to bite but was that okay
starting school i remember when i mean i
don't really
but i just just barely remember yep
go on oh what you got king
what i'm boss
that's not me me that's me hi but i
stood up but
maybe we shouldn't have stood up
god liars these
childrens are freaking liars oh not a
kid not again oh no no
no oh no let's turn it up i did that i
did that oh my god i didn't know that
that would happen i just pressed the up
arrow i didn't i thought i could turn it
up
oh oh yes what is it
blue butter whoa
wait i didn't do anything
fifteen this isn't my stop
[Music]
okay aha okay i i get the situation let
me get up
yup and sit there this is typical
japanese train behavior
yokota yokota
very very shut up stupid stop it just
because you won't let me control the
things the way i want to want them to
be controlled i know exactly what to do
in those situations
vaguely oh
okay i'll walk with them because we're a
group of four
[Music]
oh this is going to be difficult to get
the curve right
[Music]
okay
was that okay just don't walk in front
of them i guess or
block their path or something i guess
why are we standing right here
next to each other ready for all
arms i'm sorry i'm out
i would get out though i would have
gotten out i was trying to get out for
you guys
no well i mean
i guess i have a right to be in here
i'll look up to you
oh not no i guess i can turn away all
all the way to the other side now just
look up
to yep yep because it's awkward in a
filled elevator you never know where to
look right
well
that was a long elevator
oh oh
no no no no no
what the hell it's nice to meet you too
nice to meet you on the person your name
is other person i know that
oh no no no no no no no
no at least look at her face what the
hell there we go
oh i'm a strawberry i always wanted to
be strawberry nice
yeah yeah dancing together
this is reading the air repair
apparently where is it i don't know i
mean that
who would have known what to do in that
situation
[Music]
inside strawberry even
better yeah that is apparently from
son uh a show
okay
it was it was correct according to my
japanese viewers
yes okay actually i don't really know
that show i've heard of it
but i don't really know it continue
with 21 21
oh my stomach oh no
you know oh what the hell we're doing
what something's wrong with the control
still here
what the hell
[Music]
am i supposed to be so slow here what
the hell
is should i use my controller for this
what what go back no what what
oh because okay he's tapping in his
password so i guess i don't want to see
it anyway
ah what's going on
because i'm the most considerate member
oh oh it's hot so outdoor cafe
no he's not stuck but weird 25
anyway it's funny anyway oh
yes what is it i guess i'm just gonna
i guess i guess i'll die
i guess i'll die
[Music]
oh i should have fight i didn't try the
button up
uh maybe maybe i could have uh
ah maybe i could have raised my hands
yeah
i mean i don't care how the phoenix kill
me whatever kill me i don't care
do i look like i give a [\h__\h] i don't
give a [\h__\h] try to kill me try it try it
huh give it a try come on come on kelly
has failed a million times you're gonna
fail too
[Laughter]
okay i guess i'll die
i guess i'll die oh this one again oh oh
my gosh oh i think
they probably want me to be in there
don't you think
wouldn't that be a cool photo hey
[Music]
um
um cool ghost yes
ah could i have posed i'm not sure i'm
casper
let's noodle your salt amelia
ah isn't it three minutes
wait wait dun dun dun dun dun dun dun
i thought it was counting down from
three minutes but it was counting up to
three minutes and we were pretty much
done okay that was my thing okay
ooh
what what what what
the speed is not here i'll help you so
i'll go up
have some have some of me i don't really
like the
the the the pearls in the in the one so
what's it called the baba tea with the
bubbles i don't like the bubbles in the
bubble bubble
[Music]
oh what personal answers
what too fast
what ah in in japan
correct correct correct i guess i think
yeah
[Music]
sunday night fever not as good as
saturday night feverish
senpai hey [\h__\h]
oh there we go oh but the girl is cuter
[Music]
yeah dance dance dance
oh show me those hips oh wait she also
doesn't have a uh
a belt a belly thingy i can't talk
english today
why do you call that hole in your belly
oh belly button thank you
try a challenge number 41
[Music]
this is a natural sense
it's not something that can be trained
looks like i was right about this i'm
i'm i'm giving you back here
although it's pretty cool to have the
glasses down like that too i think
even the renowned reiko jogasaki
wouldn't hold
a camel to this kid i'm looking forward
to the next four years
they made me a mere cocoon right now
like his chest hair but one day they'll
become a butterfly
one that encircles the entire world my
intuition doesn't lie
[Music]
okay okay dude okay dude
you know from monster hunt i'm bob ross
[Music]
thank you for finishing move oh i'm dead
oh my god
wow are this ready to never end
what let me let me die here oh what what
what
what what just happened i i pressed some
buttons i don't know what i don't know
what happened
i was trying to lay down but didn't
quite
what what what did it say what's in ev
what's that i guess
e
[\h__\h] i get it
okay sorry i'm not i'm not completely
dry yet but there's so many people
waiting so whatever
i don't know these ones are all turned
off because of you know what
they turned them all off for like over a
year in japan
very very considerate this game is
manipulating me though it's not fair
it's wrapping on your pants yeah 36
okay uh yeah this is also something they
don't do in my country but they do this
in japan uh
yeah wait let me let me wait in case
some
nah i wanted to keep it open in case one
more one more person wanted to get on
it was too quick oh okay uh training
with my girlfriend she must sit on the
window side so let me
uh sit here
it's like blocked or something you
change it's pretty fast
ah let me just put it on this one
on the tray
no no no i'm not gonna give you my hand
[\h__\h] you
oh what's this line up hey
my hands my hands i can't do it
[Music]
[Applause]
me
i will not have this
stupid
i will not tolerate that
inconsiderate game yeah i turn i
plugged in my control but i wonder if i
have to uh restart the game does it even
work with a controller
does it even work with the controller
i wonder if i can even play with the
control do you have to restart the game
probably yeah right
but um it's safe up to this point so let
me
say uh yes okay one second
[Music]
yes i am indeed using a controller thank
you thank you very much
let's play the game again because this
is so
unbelievable it makes the controller
works okay but now i'm not sure
what the what i'm just guessing it's
probably you know
the buttons and and this one should be
about
it no oh [\h__\h] uh
no
okay well
i guess we'll continue because we've
already made it pretty far
what do you guys say should we continue
our start from the beginning again
continue new continue continue okay but
but the final result we have to consider
the fact consider
the fact that they they manipulated me
many times okay
um yeah 49 okay
so let's see line up yeah
what hello
hello
[Music]
why is it only in certain situations
still
what game is rigged
paul is not i don't know it should be
true
i'm i'm a doll made of wood my whole
body is made out of metal
i went on the group date with some idols
i invented the light bulb
and mario oh wait i don't know
i was one of the sexiest mother kings
crazy mickey oh no
i was just i insured my legs
[Music]
depending on the on the perspective i
had to go different directions
the nose hey hey we see that the top
left it's like peeping out of there his
nose is
made of left turn in the downturn
okay the game is not being considerate
but whatever we'll take it we'll take it
by the way are you seeing the game
anyway yeah okay
oh are we poop or jellies
[Music]
wait hold on we want him to fight us
kill me nice i think that's what we
wanted to do i think we were slimes yeah
he was gonna fight
i have a date with my boyfriend today oh
out there i don't know maybe he wants to
go there
but i think
i think we did the right thing
oh
he's a deer yeah but maybe he doesn't
want to be in the prairie because he
might be killed or something
oh that's me that's me
oh that and that's me i'm not a smoker
okay give me
give me some fire give me some fire
thanks
dude oh but i'm not allowed to smoke
here
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
you got a light bro
that's not me anyway i was the torch
okay i didn't have anything to do with
that
not sure which button to press on the
controller though but sure okay
yeah but he said ready right now
boring uh i'm not falling for that
being not falling for that
wait ready no he said
didn't he say when he says ready then
i'm supposed to cut right
no he said cut on ready
huh
there was a misunderstanding here why am
i only considering hitting it
that must be the highest score i'm being
considerate no extra words necessary i'm
just being considerate
46 uh
one died that's okay
that's okay at least one survived
okay we're in the train again i love
train situations
[Music]
my leg i wanted to put out my leg
nothing moves
nothing moves yeah
just nothing works okay what
thank you for waiting when i say begin
press the button okay which button
though
why are we pressing buttons we're
supposed to cut ribbons no
no but press the button
hey that's weird though also what i
wasn't even
i mean i'm so confused
[Music]
that hurt a little bit but okay
but but isn't that isn't that kind of
phrased wrong
[Music]
okay
oh what who am i
that one okay who will you mean on your
bicycle this is the final stretch
oh oh that's cool let's go back
okay there's a camera i'm gonna stop no
okay i'm fine
you go you go do your best
nice one i think i
made me figure the controls i'm not sure
let's see if it happens again the weird
thing
51 we're halfway through the co-worker
recently got engaged what i couldn't
read all of that what the hell
inconsiderate game honestly where am i
though who am i in this wedding ceremony
am i someone important or do i sit in
the audience
[Music]
okay i think i got it right ladies and
gentlemen
mm-hmm please stand for the bride stand
look to the right okay i think stuff now
works
[Music]
where's she where's she let me see her
never mind
whoa now you yeah not me swell i got the
red roses i'm way
cooler than you guys nice
i'm not sticky oh that's sticky
no that was the right finger shut up
you girls take it
[Music]
i'm not supposed to catch that am i
yeah i think in inconsiderate mode i
should catch it
considerably consider it [\h__\h]
that sounds the best out of everything
okay okay 56.
guys we're getting better now are you
scared
don't let go of course not you better
not go off uh
[Music]
i don't even know how to let go i
couldn't no i know i couldn't do
anything hmm
weird
it's so amazing let's take a summer
vacation yay
you ah i guess i'll get one day
nice yep yeah that's that's that's all i
can take
yeah cause boss and the other worker are
being [\h__\h] and being [\h__\h] douche
bags
unbelievable so inconsiderate 58.
oh that's i love that i love that um
curry you're done with that white dress
that's a japanese traditional wedding
dress
oh kooky yummy store let's get uh this
one
and
let's see let's see let's see okay i
want to see the other ones
no i don't want to get the other ones
should i have gotten all of them
[Music]
oh she dead what's he doing no way i'm
kissing you
no way no no no no no no
i guess i guess that was the right way
to do it to wake up
right
moderately consider it okay i mean i
feel like
i feel like
that was sexual harassment but okay i'll
take it
it's just a game
cancel him 61.
oh you okay buddy what what is it
am i too hot for you what is it what is
it
am i so sexy i mean i know but oh he has
to get up i was trying to move but he
wouldn't let me
i was trying to see what i can do but
nothing happened
oh yay
it's i don't know what's going on what's
going on here
how are we happy okay ah wait i'm the
small
great no no
yeah not into their faces i'm just smoke
and smoke
i want to do barbecue that would be nice
cold sake press the button to stop
it shouldn't be so much in there right i
think
about this much i don't know how much
i'm not an alcohol
drinker i don't know how much you
usually have there i suppose this much
i still use i'm so sleepy i gotta take a
nap
uh but i think you can probably recline
the seat but i don't want to do it
because someone's behind me
no i'm not going to lean back
we'll start with a urine test please
fill us up
yeah um i guess i gotta fill it up like
all the way
oh this should be enough though no i'm
gonna stop here oh my god
i don't i don't know this that's enough
no
in some way or another consider it nice
66.
let's get our tickets to soccer game
grandma really and where we have you
only four tickets left
oh but no i'm going with my grandma
[\h__\h]
i'm going with my grandma
but wait there were only two people in
line i could have not gotten free
tickets anyway right
it's kelly the cowboy yeehaw
huh
ah i guess i'll land on your finger
you don't need them you're not scared of
me right here let me land on your finger
oh no you're gonna bite it
no way where's that
am i getting more inconsiderate yeah
oh are we gonna shoot each other
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
you have to have the umbrella i'll see
you my girlfriend so why not what's this
what are you looking at
oh she's happy ah
that's that's very considerate very
sweet
in some way are never considerate
that makes me very happy i don't know
about the i guess yeah i should have
looked over to
that side not sure how i would have done
that
71 taking
taking to the night what
here's your free spots to kiss yep
have some safe distance in between the
other kissers
that's so great the family's calling
amelia's calling cool
where's your hat though let's go too
let's go to amelia
amelia let me look under your skirt
yes give me a treat
from japanese make little one inch
bigger with the magic mullet
how big how big you want to be this big
wow that was too big [\h__\h] one less i
guess
damn it 74
i think i'm in the wrong section oh
make yourself a goal yeah bye bye
sorry sorry let me pass through
awkward 75
oh i said that the wave again
perfect diamond again
oh oh we start us down now okay
oh i already did that the second
the next movement too early damn it
that got the michael jackson molds yeah
[Music]
look at those moves progress update the
previous five questions
moderately considered too bad oh
man i can do better a lot of this
a lot of this was messed up by the game
i gotta say i knew what to do i knew
what to do in those situations
i want to take those classes
so i just just leave oh yeah cause uh
they're
already cleaning up i guess
shouldn't that yeah i needed to leave
i left in time okay oh my god wake up
listen to it sorry oh i always feel so
sorry like
when i drive with someone in the car and
he's telling stories and
uh-huh okay okay okay and i feel so
tired
of you gotta pay attention and talk to
them but
sometimes they say it's okay you'll just
sleep it makes me worry i feel sorry for
them
let's cross at the crosswalk
what the [\h__\h] is the matter with you
[Music]
noodles no
that's it
i don't know i don't know eddie
[Music]
bro look at the sea turtle around for
real oh
cute she's here to lay her eggs let's
watch over them absolutely
oh exo
is she gonna steal the eggs
she wants to become a hero
[Music]
are they supposed to make a sound like
dun dun
dun very vaguely i don't get it
no one understands
i think did i do it right
don't bully the turtle on what i guess
i'll take the
ah dad's dvds uh
there might be something in there that
we don't want the girls to see right
[Applause]
even though the books are heavier but ah
they need to see what i'm writing right
oh wait but where do i go that's how you
solve these formulas
this will be on the test make sure to
take notes there we go okay they can see
it now
write it down write it down
okay
83 they were packed yeah but the box was
open
the other box was closed completely okay
dude
you stupid go away
we should have the best would have been
if we stand on the same side
though like both on the same side would
have been better
but he waited too long
one two three extra extra
ah that's when i go out ah that's when i
go out oh yeah
yeah yeah cause i'm i'm some kind of i
don't know demon or something
supposed to leave the house on second
february
the evil mr rogue was cast down into
hell
okay however since he once saved the
spider in the past it would have lowered
the afraid of spider-sick down and onto
him down to him
what seeing it he went climbing the
thread
but others also crowded around seeking
to
climb up as well mr rogue
everybody stay calm the friend will snap
if we all try to climb with one so smart
so it's mine
so personal okay
make a line and we'll climb at one at a
time
when you raise the top call down for the
next person so smart so persuasive
okay oh
should i have what
should i have caught it but then they
die did they want to
die
not sure was that
helen they tried to get out of it but
i'm not sure you walk around
okay well that was fair i didn't
understand the situation so that's okay
86 oh shake shake
i have those two i have the same things
yes mine can even be eaten
my raw guys i have chicken maracas oh
what's going on
what's going on here
what's
i can't even do anything i couldn't do
anything
i wanted to protect her and stand like
all right that was his turn
nice
give me another one no okay i hit one
89 not until you ask me for my
daughter's hand
ah i tried
i tried
look at this look isn't it nice no don't
go back
[Music]
i tried to stay there
no this is taught this is manipulating
me
i i know what to do i know what to do
i couldn't even move it was moving on
its own
oh wow it makes me cry dude
91 we're almost done i'm not gonna trust
that evaluation oh no
it's zombies close close close
oh [\h__\h] that was open [\h__\h]
that was opening i said giraffe is so
cute hello
[Music]
let me put it down for you oh eat it
come on
eat it oh good
yeah it's cute
very considerate for the zombie i guess
so what's going on oh
what
what 94.
there's so many situations i don't
understand here we go
new year five four three two
one happy new year
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
wow how exciting
new years were was always more fun when
i was younger somehow
um recent years i don't know haven't
been doing
such special things in the recent years
oh let's keep it green let's keep it
green oh no no no no no red no way
downward
run away from the buoys
we have to protect him 97. press button
to clap hands
i'm just gonna no no
[\h__\h] anyway
[Music]
it's you guys and me oh i'm gonna crack
let me crack
oh crack went no no i'm not gonna crack
in front of you gonna crack into in
front of my mama
no no
mama come back mama
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
yep
[Music]
where wait are your names on here yeah
okay
okay there we go
graphics are uh miho nakazuno
[Music]
what that's not correct what you skipped
someone i think
okay and finally you oh that's me that's
me that's me
that's me after that you will be you
will each begin
walking your own path from time to time
you will find yourselves
in situations where you will need to be
considerate of others
however being considerate all the time
isn't always a good thing
yeah you need to also think of yourself
exactly that is true
being considerate of others and knowing
when to take care of yourself or both
vital skills
i want you all to become strong adults
who can do both yeah that's really wise
yes
nice beautiful
now then class representative stand
ball good night
what is it what is it is mama garden
where's your mama i've realized how to
walk oh i just know it oh but we
shouldn't walk until them
until they take to come near my laptop
no
ha ha wait
look at me yes yes
now i walk yes he's taking a video now
yay
he stood up yeah why are you taking a
[Music]
video
do a flip
very baby
i was very considerate okay
okay well this is not this is not a
correct result this is manipulated
[Music]
and understanding middle manager i'm the
top manager okay
i'm detentio i'm the freaking tencho
okay
detailed results with tab
all right
where am i
what you don't get the long text anyway
i'm pressing tab but it doesn't go
[Music]
start on the controller nothing
there we go i don't know what i pressed
okay
uh common sense and specif
specified specified knowledge commonly
understood social management etiquette
this is the first step
in becoming more considerate specialized
know-how that isn't commonly known
having a lot of knowledge is an
essential weapon for being more
considerate
sharpness for sense of direction and
maintaining the right amount of distance
oh knowing your place helps them perhaps
in being more considerate of others
okay okay group dynamics the knowledge
to understand the role others expect you
to play in a group
the cooperative nature leads to smooth
teamwork yeah
i know sympathy whether or not you can
put yourself in our nervous shoes and
understand how they feel
and at the adult thing of the ability to
step back and take in a situation then
assume the rules
others don't want to do that was for
example the one that's like
or maybe not exactly because that was
more like comedy but like the one where
you say i'll do it i'll do it
uh information integration the power to
instantly find the right meaning from
fragmented hints with no context
speed 38
well he won't let me do [\h__\h] the ability
to immediately make decisions in any
situation
the speed to understand and react to
rhythm and interval ribbon the town of
following the woman is instructed
being flexible with the ability to go
with the flow will be useful in being
considerate
and good and bad intervals disappointing
whether or not you understand the best
timing when acting in a series of events
shut up disappointing above average
hey there's a lot of above average even
though i was manipulated you know
okay i think that's that's it
roll comprehension inside
i think that's all i can see
do you guys wanna inconsiderate mode
or uh or not do you want me to be a
little bit
inconsiderate
[Music]
what's b k y
allah
i'll try my best it's gonna be really
hard though
maybe the controls will be fair to me
this time
i think it's probably going to be 50 50
uh
things this time
[Music]
only gonna show you half of it the
or not at all
you will never know what year it is
number two
i don't know i still don't know what the
right thing was to do here but
anyway number three
[Music]
okay so i guess i'll just stand right in
the middle
here
stop moving stop moving e
right right here
[Music]
i don't think they liked it
i don't think they're like yeah i
asserted my dominance
thanks for the meal
those were can i actually move this time
no i still can't oh well i guess i'll
stay in considerate
it's not like i want it to do that
originally here we have kiana and
natural have to shut up
i still can't give him any mints though
makes me sad
nope i can't i can't i pressed every
button
that i have a castle just not get mints
but hey
i feel like we could get full points in
the inconsiderate mode
moderately book it shut up i'm perfectly
bogey
now there's no motion controls
now use the d-pad and the analog sticks
all of them
uh
i can't raise my hands i cannot okay
okay should be easier to be
inconsiderate
than being considerate
hello hello i'll take the ball yeah
my belt my ball my ball i got the ball
[Music]
okay and now i'll just no
because you just i guess yeah yeah
i wanted him to fall down as well when
it would have been difficult
would have had to go all the way down
here right away
[Music]
he did
player isn't much different from the
last one oh come on
still can't do anything here even
with the controller you work part-time
for a moving company okay i'll take the
clothes
oh i'll take nothing you know what i'll
take nothing
you do the work you do it
attach your name
i don't think nothing
i don't care i don't want this job
anyway this job sucks
i don't want to do heavy lifting okay
also i won't even move at all
this is where i want to be i was here
first
i'm gonna stay here now i'm gonna stay
i'm gonna stay
stay do my dance
okay everyone's gonna get off oh it says
um
that's why you guys said that before
didn't you and i'm gonna stay right here
because i don't care and you're sleeping
anyway
so it's okay right i can stay next day i
can cover with you right
number 13.
it's on steam and switch yes the game
let's watch this uh uh you know what i
prefer watching girls though let's watch
[Music]
girls
i'll already open up now or maybe not
you know what i'll close
did i ruin it sorry i'm so sorry
number 15.
this is a natural sense it's not
something that can be trained
looks like oh my god i didn't i didn't
know that was possible
oh my god
[Music]
what is that good or is that bad
is that the inconsiderate way i was
trying to press down and this is what
happens
yeah he's collecting all those
sunglasses
in his hair nice he's got a whole stock
of sunglasses he's selling them to
people probably
it's like you know you like this glasses
you like these ones what about these
ones these are gucci
take these why is she crying don't cry
girl
unlimited shades
okay this is uh i know what happens here
i guess i'm gonna stay
i was thinking that too that his upper
is just made out of sunglasses
he's actually bald yeah
[Music]
just hang on a bit long i'm a big
brother we'll go get some money
ah ah
oh i understand now okay
consider way would have been to let him
uh answer
first but wait am i
but still he doesn't move so am i
supposed to get it for him
oh well red fighter
are you sleepy yeah y'all so boring
y'all so boring
i don't give a [\h__\h] boring
boo boo boo
sleepy oh should i have a dark thumb
i don't know it's my night okay
[Music]
but i'm really sorry but yeah
it's a pleasure to meet you too hey
what's up
you you you looking very
full full today very um
i don't know did you try a new cream or
something your skin looks great
[Laughter]
nice oh the zombies are coming
the ollies are coming the ollies are
coming guys
get yourself into some safe house or
something
i wish i had a bike leave it to big bro
road race competition the winner of the
race will get a brand new bicycle
ah okay okay anyway
anyway the final stretch
yes
knock him i wondered that would have
been possible so yeah don't let go
oh oh wait i don't know
finally i know how to let go of her but
i won't i won't let go of you because
you
you probably want me i probably should
have let go if i wanted to be
considerate but if i want to be
inconsiderate
you know all right here let me help you
or not yeah it's all mine you'll never
grow telling me that me because i'm the
biggest giraffe in town and i'll always
stay the biggest giraffe
understand little child name
oh my stomach this one i really don't
know what happened before yeah what the
hell she's just zooming
i don't i don't know
how can you move so fast if you got his
stomach ache
impressive um
i don't you want to come in smack snap
i don't know what do we want him in or
not
hi hey what's up i want to talk
the third floor please no wait we didn't
get this far before he didn't actually
talk to me did he
oh wait i was being polite huh
oh it's the forbidden word on screen
right now
the forbidden word
i feel like
i was an maybe yeah your coworker got
engaged
okay anyway i'm going to uh uh no wait
no go back no [\h__\h] i was i was
i was i want to be consistent but i
first
i couldn't go back anymore mine
[Music]
mine did i catch it
did i count it
stop being good i'm trying i'm trying
oops [\h__\h] okay
i bonked him
die i can't maybe not yeah there we go
nice one
okay are you running i'm wrong oh i'm
off bye-bye
gotta run see ya
does someone have a piece of toast that
i can put into my mouth
and run together with and all the way
all the way back come on i can't i can't
do it no i want to go all the way back
i can't move
i won't let me take nine
yeah that's a decorative night
but you know it's the thought that
counts yes yes yes
31 taking in the night scenery with your
girlfriend
yes that's so take it take it in
[Music]
what we joined them
yep
i like rain rain is nice
rain is so refreshing it's a free shower
stop complaining
come on you don't need an umbrella
you don't need it i if anyone anyone
needs it and i need it
free shower not until you ask me okay so
we did something wrong here
okay good
not sure what happened i was hiding
behind her because i was scared i guess
what is it no no
no no no i don't hear you
i can't hear you la la la la
[Music]
the only physical exam today we'll start
with a urine test
please fill us up can i overfill it
let's never press the button to stop
is that how you fill up sake so it fills
up even in the
in the on that part oh he drank a lot
didn't he
so guy
that's pretty impressive i guess
blather wow
ah now that was p that was not sake
i think they cut out the socket one for
this one
[Music]
grandma yeah but like
no no because
what if my grandma dies huh then
tomorrow
and she didn't see the freaking game
well i'm just spy i don't want to date
you anymore i guess
i guess i'm good
how did that happen i guess we're
sitting on them now yeah i'm sure
they're happy about that
we're saving some space you know
hatch goes by
i don't want to be here anymore
cards you and me i challenge you to a
battle
go away dude it's not your fight to
fight it's my fight
i walk over you like a [\h__\h]
i dance on you i i'll make you my [\h__\h]
my karna no shake no stop shaking
don't stop sicking stop saying no no
i know you love the mustache but stop
shaking
resist the transformation yes i know it
feels good to have a mustache
amelia must be so happy with hers
i wish i wish i could have a mustache
maybe in another world in another
dimension
[Music]
forty-one
nice nice one i was looking for a way to
be extra inconsiderate there you go
celebrate let's take a summer vacation
on this day
and this day and this day and this and
this day
and here no one's gonna work no wait i'm
not wait oh that's not high works i'm
taking this day and this day and also
this day and i was taking that day
and that didn't what do you mean tonight
that's my stamp that's not your stamp to
use
you denied the one that i stamped on
someone else
okay i'm controlling pretty well no
yep yep it's not happening at all
not even for a second not giving you
that pleasure
[Music]
oh dude come on let me show you my sexy
body there we go i'm a baby
i'm i'm hot congratulations on hatching
members
oh i'm baby i triggered so many people
and now they're the real babies ah what
to do
everyone's so sensitive because i'm a
baby and i said baby things
let me just leave real quick
can i leave i want to leave
[Music]
i want to leave let me leave i want to
be free baby i don't give a [\h__\h] about
you i don't need you mom or dad i don't
need you
i'm gonna leave i wanna leave this
you're just gonna make me work for you
anyway
in some way or another bouquet nice
hands you got there
46.
[Music]
uh how do we how do we how do we do this
right here wake up already wait wait
wait
[Music]
i couldn't do anything i didn't wanna be
kissed
your change is three thousand twenty one
again let's give it to the other person
yeah
no no no no no no
[Music]
is the considerate way to do it
i don't know i don't know [\h__\h] it went
it
got smaller again
damn it have you tried turning it off
and on again that could make it work as
intended
but i don't know if you effing around
with me but yes i did
yes i did actually
you are not growing at all you're
staying small forever
number 50 i think this is the last one
i'm in charge of the paper ball
decorations the closer the timing the
better
thank you for waiting i just skipped
i just press the buttons and that's what
happened
i guess that was nice okay
i am officially better at being
inconsiderate than being
considerate so many slip-ups a delicious
broadcast writer
yeah you got but me knowing how to be
inconsiderate means that i also know how
to be considerate okay
[Music]
[Applause]
yes success i would say
thank you thank you thank you very much
for watching
we're going to read super chats now
[Music]
are you guys ready i don't even need it
i don't even need a break but um
let's take a one minute break
if you want to stay you're welcome to
stay we usually do some chili telly
while we read super chats we're gonna
catch up on the super chats that we
didn't read yesterday
so it might take a while we might have a
lot of stuff to talk about
so if you want to stay you're welcome to
stay give me one minute and i'll be back
[Music]
you're hearing the music right
okay
[Music]
do
uh raspberries
almost at 880k or only whoever is here
not subscribed subscribe now to win uh
your chance
of being a subscriber
your time only if you subscribe now you
can be subscriber
isn't that a huge offer i think that's
that's a once in a lifetime opportunity
if you're if you become a subscriber now
you
you can actually be a subscriber forever
if you become one now
i don't know if you can do the same
thing tomorrow i don't know might only
be today
might only be today it's a super deal
it's a 10 out of 10 deal
i'm just gonna tell you now it's
actually a secret i only tell people
this
in the super chat reading because i i
only want
to cool people to know and the cool
people stay
until the super chat reading which
actually means the cool people are
already subscribed anyway if you're here
right now that means you're one of the
cool people
and that means you're already subscribed
because only the cool people know
what the cool people do so
i think all of you are subscribed anyway
makes sense right um
we'll start reading the ones from
yesterday which are i think
quite a lot actually um
yesterday was near automata and tomorrow
is new automata two i'm a bit addicted
right now
we finished route b yesterday which was
amazing i'm excited for route c
really excited um
this was the thumbnail let me just put
it there so people know what we're
reading
now reading the super chats from that
stream
you mustn't
welcome to all the new members by the
way
yeah i finished root a and root b
amazing we're already at root c
we had we just played uh the stream we
just had five ah no busy me thank you
how about now we just had five streams
and progressing quite nicely i would say
oh ritzy is pretty long really
i thought root a was the longest from
what i've heard from my
viewers bgm good now okay
thank you for the membership thank you
we've only got like 20 inch endings left
to get
well i don't really like plan on getting
all the small ones i don't care about
them
just the main ones you know the main
routes
although i really don't know how many
there really are
but i guess it's abcd you know we're
gonna end it after that and i might just
do the rest privately if i'm really
curious
but otherwise i feel like it might go on
forever and ever
so
i guess i bet kelly would be into the
small ones
of course she likes small people yeah
yes okay um
[Music]
did we read them did we read the silver
chats in the members only stream
oh yes we did yes we did okay
yes okay starting now super chat reading
federal ministry of health federal
ministry of have done
two times
starting up nicely uh
i guess i'll read your super chat
i'm gonna be considerate because i know
you have a funny super chat
so i'm gonna be considerate and read it
even though it's
to be problematic for me flying
quiet we received reports of pests such
as flies and scrolling okay
pests around the food pose a risk to the
safety of customers
we require access to all rooms in kfp to
inspect the clean
cleanliness of the business unless the
ceo can explain the reports
it's a federal offensive line you know
what actually i don't mind you coming
over and checking out
the situation because i would like to
know the reason and the cause
myself but i've noticed in the past
two days way less of those stupid little
flies
than usual way less of them
uh but it's not like the fly trap
actually worked
it didn't work at all but i'm not sure
maybe i really
finally killed enough of them
not sure not sure chunkers must have
eaten them
i don't think so maybe i accidentally
ate them
well i fell for you you've heard me
killing a lot of them
on stream
oh well well thank you for the
membership welcome chris dobbs thank you
soon
i'm trying to be more safer these days
so can you tell mama rooney to cut it
out
no i want more of that i want her i want
her to draw me
as much as she wants in any kind of
position
that she wants i i'm
she's a free artist i'm not in a
position to tell her what to draw and
what not to draw
although she does uh often take requests
from me
but i would not tell her to stop drawing
something no
i want to see more looking for the top
down
looking for the top again hey can i
realize today is yeah i know i said too
today's your first month since your
return to australia australia yeah i
keep track i'm weird
the beginning has been boozled but do
you think things are finally starting to
look up now
being back of the caddos and i irl
friends ukelele friend mvp
is better than 2020 i imagine also is
there anything you want to share with or
ask from your friend fans
don't chicken away from the doctor
um well
um it's hard to say it's better than
2020 because it's so hard to compare
those two years
because i was in japan most of the time
in 2020
uh
and so i think it's uh not really
comparable
um but
it's the year is off to a good start and
it's
better than before i went to japan
i guess maybe in some ways
looking forward to getting my own
apartment again like being able to
afford it again finally
and uh filling it out with furniture
that i like
and will be nice and
i don't know about the doctor i'm
getting
stuff done and i'm getting uh
all kinds of stuff done right now and
like
i uh my brother found a
tax person for me
and then that tax person is gonna get me
an insurance and
all that kind of stuff so i'll probably
be able to go to the doctor
as soon as that person signed me up for
my insurance
yeah just waiting for that but we're
working on everything
yeah thank you and yeah i know this too
it's been one month already and it's
kind of fast
it's one month already since i left
japan
after my one year i don't know
it still makes me kind of sad i wish i
could have
used that one year better
i wish i could have made better use of
it but i guess
um once
the the p is over
then there's still a lot of time to go
travel
and check out the places that i wanted
to check out in that one year i can
still fly around and
travel so but the other things that i
wanted to do in that one year
i'll probably never ever get to do i
definitely missed out on that
which is a bit sad but that's okay
[Music]
thank you oh my god congratulations on
your kidney transplant
felix dao thank you for a double red
super chat
morning tanjo it's nice to be back again
for another new stream i absolutely
enjoy watching you play one of my
favorite games ever and glad you're
enjoying it as well
also one small question where did you
hide your beautiful tail when you
transformed to the current form
i don't have a tail currently oh
it's just i'm not hiding anything it's
just not there
i'm mostly human form right now as you
can see
the only real thing that stayed is uh
see
my my my feathers what
ma maloney found the tail what what do
you mean
what do you mean mama only found the
tail what are you talking about
huh
[Music]
you mean the 3d
oh who has danced forever you mean the
three
w which i think i think the cat won
you mean the cat arts
they're just talking about the booty
not sure what you're talking about i
don't
there is a knob back there shut up there
is no what the hell
what
that's [\h__\h] what
no that's [\h__\h] just talking [\h__\h]
let me take a look
what notch are you talking about
it's black panties nothing wrong here i
see
a complete human looking person
i don't see a tail where are you looking
where are you seeing a freaking tail
throw it to me look
look i'm looking very close at this
picture but i
just can't find anything
um
thank you though thank you felix
once again thank you for your support
and i'm enjoying near very much so i'm
glad you're enjoying it too
let's let's enjoy it together until the
end
the end if it will ever come
david attenborough and soon i've once
again climbed the great tree to observe
the igneous album in her native habitat
we shall see how her and the flock
behave today
and green wilder or wilder sent
uh 102 grand two and a half red super
chats thank you
ignore this if you don't want the
critics issue brought up
okay look i don't know you
wrote so much i i'm gonna read it anyway
uh hot wings you're sexy like a
chocolate covered strawberry
i want to tell you how awesome you are
it seems you fell down lately of some
critics and
i know because of some critics and i
know that no matter how many employees
reassure you
that we love you those comments still
sting but i'll try to overwrite them
anyway
you're so charming and cute you just
seeing your smile bright and smart day
oh my god where's my person
i love how sassy you are you're so fun
and entertaining i love you too
i mean you didn't say you love me but i
love you too
you're singing is beautiful i love your
voice i could listen to you all day
you've heard from some of us that you've
helped us for tough times
inspired us or helped us feel good put
smiles on our faces
and one of those people and i guarantee
that i think about you more every day
than any hater could
so it breaks my heart imagining that you
might spend more time thinking about a
handful of jerks
than about the hundreds of thousands of
us who love you to the moon and back
some of the comments maybe from fans who
only disliked one little thing
i'm sure they still love you too kids
just sometimes fail to realize
how sensitive their mamas are and say
hurtful things about meaning too
that's true yeah thanks for reading viva
la quinaga
i want to give you a hug thank you so
much for that
thank you
love you thank you that means a lot to
me
that's so sweet i'm going to leave it at
that i don't want to discuss the topic
but thank you
nick finlandson donkey shin tassie josh
duncan thank you for the pinky
hey mom did you see dad said she love
you on the german language stream
totally not out of context also love all
your streams and please keep being the
awesome you me loyal kfb members are
behind you as
are the deadbeats thank you i i saw the
clip showing up
in my um recommended recommendations and
i watched
uh a lot of the beginning of her german
uh
study stream but no i didn't see that
part and i didn't watch the clip
it keeps on showing up in my
recommendations i i didn't i didn't
click it though
is it very out of context you guys seem
to say
it's very much out of context but why
did she say it
obviously because she loves me okay let
me see maybe it shows up in my
recommendations now
let's let's type the kelly
says she loves kiara
one month ago three months ago she said
it many times
one day ago okay from unicocoon let's
listen
you don't hear ah you don't hear it oh
[\h__\h] but
i've been repeating it
no we don't need context
very convinced still i don't like your
or something
i don't know something wow
or something she said it she obviously
said it's very clear it's very clear
that's all i needed to hear thank you
very much that's all i wanted to hear
that's all i needed to hear
thank you okay let me turn back on uh
the music
uh story corner thank you thank you
and congrats also for everything you've
been doing your talent energy positivity
are admirable i love how in the collapse
you're the leader
coordinator and director it's not easy
but you do it greatly love from a
fangirl of yours
thank you thank you very much
[Applause]
that is very nice of you to say thank
you
i appreciate it i don't know i don't
know the currency so i'm not sure if
it's a red one or a pink one or whatever
but thank you thank you very much for
your support thank you soon
very kind and uh
you know 22
is
[Music]
i'm also one of the members of the
discord 2500 kfp group
to tell you one thing the group owner
nini kfb we actually do not
want to stab him but she is 2d we cannot
help
it okay that was
that's something that you guys have to
you know discuss in your group
i i'm not gonna
be able to help you with that i think
but i understand
the owner likes is one of those people
who likes every everyone not only kiara
but likes everyone so
the owner is not following the hashtag
worldcasterkilk standards
maybe maybe he you should
put him into the usual room maybe i
should put him into the usual room
touch
[Music]
thank you thank you
thank you the helpful thing thank you
in the silver tongue slacker dan
alexander you are now at the same part
of the game i was when xander was first
born
oh yes i liked the video
alexander was a chicken
very cute did you did
did xander start walking yet did you
also
try to get it on camera but you didn't
what did it was santa like no
i'm not gonna show you how i work nah
nah no i don't want a video of me
walking
and then you show it to everyone years
and years later and gonna embarrass me
i mean he's probably already thinking
that no
because he dressed him up like a chicken
and make him react to my videos and put
it online
for everyone to see and then when he's
like 20 years old
older and he's gonna see that and it's
gonna be like dad what the [\h__\h] did you
do to me
why won't you upload that to the
internet dad
i hate you it's gonna be funny it's
gonna be very
funny
ah looking forward to that
keep me updated uh
he's probably not gonna say that at 20.
he's probably already gonna say it when
he's like a teenager
i mean i i i think you're gonna
get into a really big fight
unless you delete all the evidence
but his name will forever be xander
there's not not so many
sanders that i know that's the only
standard that i know
travis knight thank you nick the killer
thank you thank you for two pinkies
which makes one red super chat
ah but only because i miss identified
your first pink one as a red one
apparently
thank you again why am i doing this what
is my motivation
and giving the speech about money yeah
we read this one before on stream
well as i said before i think i think
your motivation is just
because you love me and that's okay
uh
[Music]
for red super job
this is already the most efficient and
fast super chat reading well there were
a lot of
uh smaller super chats up until now
that's why i can zoom through them
i'm leaving you here you're nearly good
at the game
thank you yeah i feel like uh
probably people who play near
a lot are probably still a bit
frustrated watching me but i would say
it's still one of the games where
i'm uh better
at like good at compared to other games
uh like super my reception like i i had
enough time to get used to the
fighting system the combat system and
i'm playing in the normal mode okay i
know people are playing it in easy i'm
playing in the normal i'm not running
away
and uh i feel like the the
the the heart of her heart hurt
hurdle by
the bar is pretty high in this game from
the get-go
it's like i wouldn't say it's an easy
game
um you improved in hacking a lot yeah i
think so too
it was really horrible in the beginning
sunshine's camera can be rough that is
true too yeah
but oh i am
i'm glad that uh
i'm not being
how to say not beings
[Music]
um
can't find the right words today not
being stopped or like
held back that's what i'm looking for
not being held back
by the combat system as much it was only
like the
the game crashing and stuff like that
that was a problem but now we're fine
now it's all good
yeah pretty pretty cool to finally play
the game normally and be able to enjoy
it normally
it's a lot of fun i love the game it's
so beautiful too
[Music]
everyone post some milk for the baby
everyone put some milk in the comments
yeah
will ya so sweet of you guys you are so
cooperative so consider it
drink it drink it baby it's our dead
baby that we've been
hanging out with since a long time now
like
how long has the baby been around it was
alive when we met the baby now it's a
dead baby
it's like forever part of a family i
love it
what do you see wait waiting for
the baby to reply i'm sure i'm sure it
will
ghost baby november
so sweet i'm so glad it came back after
being dead
ah i chose july 6th because that's the
day of uh
national fried chicken day in in america
no other reason than that
baby you okay maybe now it's like
drowned in milk maybe it can't breathe
anymore maybe we kill it all over again
slide down lord oh there we go oh
it's so happy that's the biggest
donation that the baby ever sent i think
wow it's like
overlapped with milka
why does the baby have so much money
i'm worried now is the baby stealing
money from
from his mom
in his diaper life insurance
[Music]
would you be up to playing new replicant
version
1.224 744-87139 is that the full title
why the hell is there so many numbers
after this comes out in april obviously
after getting the rise to play on stream
is that that's not that's not that's a
port right or is it like a
remastered version that's the whole
title oh my god
it's a remake i would i would love to
play it
yeah i would love to
if it comes out in april then uh
we we're getting done with niro adamata
pretty soon too
although i did want to get a free
i guess we're playing rhino right now
when it comes to rpgs so i guess ryza
can be
replaced by yakuza once we're done with
raiza and then near automotive and we
will replace by near
uh replicant if i get the permission
frame rate isn't so bad
it's not bad although i feel like i
noticed it while i was playing too
uh that it was pretty low
stupid [\h__\h] internet
sorry about that guys also i'm moving a
lot today somehow my body is moving so
much i don't know why
i ate too much chocolate
where was i out there uh daisy thank you
broken loop duncan
tv oh these are the flush shots i'm
going to skip those
pretty sure these are flush chances
someone i know you still don't care
daisy duncan's right cactus
[Music]
i don't like to compare games and stuff
especially while i'm playing that
specific game
but those that that that those bullets
that's just
all i can think of is total total is
just
traumatizing with bullets so whenever i
see bullets all i think of is tall
and i think it's also because i was
singing the the torah song
while i was uh one touhou song while i
was
playing was having a lot of fun i just
love toe songs so much all the
arrangements
i love like touhou arrangement music
circles
why
[Music]
there's such weird comments in the chat
what
god damn it kiara why is your taste this
good
what
what explain yourself
explain yourself
and then the other one was asking me
what cali's belly button looks like
what what stop invading my privacy mine
and and callus privacy
i have stuff to do and you keep
distracting me with your good
taste what wait do you mean
taste as in good taste because of touhou
and stuff like that
or what what what
oh my god
i'll taste the music okay okay oh okay
then it's not that weird okay
okay thank god
i was getting really confused in games
not meant to be weird okay
i really misunderstood you there
thank god okay
oh my god where was i
out there random kai guy nikki duncan
alexander
bryan sanji shandang the fuzzy ducky
duncan doctor helghas
what
your hacking is moving shooting half
speed probably need to turn off these
sync and graphics
oh really
but what was it before someone told me
like we sync
on when full screen and resync off or
not
or the other way around
we sink on is it is that is it only done
no
don't touch near-sightings anymore at
this point yes i will not
yeah do you think we think i'm on the
full screen not for nobody okay
i guess
have you a look on the whole second gen
edition and no no
i have no idea who's auditioning i do
not have any input in it
i don't have any control over it
i don't get to know until the members
are
decided i'm as clueless as you guys are
uh philip matthews thank you for reading
[Music]
please can you say aya i said this one
already
hope you got your clip phillip hope
you're happy
drive 789 thank you thank you
uh not sure about the currency so i
don't know if this is a red one or not
uh but i'll read it hello camera i hope
you're okay
on australia and thank you for playing
this game this is my favorite one and i
enjoy seeing you playing it the root c
is hard to watch but gumball
everything's from chile yeah i already
heard uh from some people that root c is
gonna be very painful
root c the next one that we're playing
interesting i'm intrigued
yeah but i don't want to get spoiled i
mean
i mean up until now it also hasn't been
that happy anyway
but you know what something got me
thinking someone told me
pink in the super chat or someone on
twitter reply
that they played the game but only they
they only played route a
because they didn't wanna they didn't
care about 9s so they didn't continue
playing afterwards and
i felt like
i i kind of get it because then you i
guess you don't know
what what what you're missing out on
and what happens afterwards if you don't
know if you're playing on your own
then you could be like okay oh i guess
that's just the most interesting part
because even if you start the second
route
then you're like hmm everything seems
basically the same
just from a different kind of
perspective so
no need to play this right i feel like
some people might really do it like that
and then miss out on so much content
unfortunately so
i don't know like i wonder how many
people
just stopped there and did didn't
continue playing even though they liked
the game but yeah
they got turned off by root beer or so
kind of a loss it's a bit yeah because
also yeah
it was a bit misleading to me too
because from what i read like
at the end of the game the way that the
game
told me about the next route it made it
feel to me
as if root a was like the main thing
and everything afterwards is just small
extras that's how it sounded to
me so i can understand if people stop
playing there
but in reality it's way more after that
huh
miko did abcde wait what she got so far
already
what
what she already finished it
what ah she was yeah i know she was
playing uneasy yeah
but did she do side quests and stuff or
did you just
just zoom through it
damn the speed she zoomed
elite speed run she zoomed through on
easy ah
i wonder how long it took her hey
seems so fast because i didn't even
notice she already finished it
she already she finished everything
before your second episode
what what yeah i mean yeah it took me a
month before i did the second episode
because i moved
but still what wow she finished in like
two weeks oh my god
wow whole week
wow okay um
bam
anyway there's a lot of uh flush super
chats here again so i'm gonna skip those
two
ah amazed
there's another comment telling you turn
off these things too so your hacking
will move faster
is that for real
well maybe i would not say that you
willingly run into those balls but i
would merely imply that it makes an
impression i wasn't trying to
and good night too everyone who wants to
sleep
but anyway uh thank you you need to chat
but i wish i would try my best okay
they were following me the bullets are
following me
i can't do much about it
kiana can't dodge balls i'm gonna stay
back in
school in a
pe class i was really bad at shooting
balls
so bad that was the worst that's why no
one wanted me in the team
but i was one of like actually
so good at dodging the ball so i would
always be
on the field until the end so i don't
know
i don't understand why they never like
realized
that they need me in the team because
i'll stay in the
on the field until the end because i'm
just so good at dodging i
i can't but then every time i would be
on the field in the end
um like like you guys probably play it
differently than we do but we have this
specific kind of dodgeball um
where everyone who is out gets to stand
on the on around the enemy's
side field outside and then shoot
the approach about yeah think of that
and then shoot the people in the enemies
field
we call it folk about and if you got to
shoot someone you're allowed to get back
in
anyway so when i was last
when i was last in the field then
i would usually be surrounded by
like 20 20 people
trying to shoot me and uh
the only way for me to get
uh to win in that situation is getting
my teammates who are on the other side
surrounding the so hard to explain
surrounding the opposite team
for them to shoot someone from
the enemies so that they can get back
into my field
but that would mean that i would have to
catch the ball
that their the enemies are shooting at
me and then shoot it
into my team so that they can shoot
someone but i couldn't even i was so
scared of catching the ball
that it mostly didn't work out i can't i
could dance perfectly but
catching and and throwing i was so bad
at
and and whenever i was the last in the
field it was just
everyone was trying to kill me
the struggle yeah i mean throwing yes
it was fun though it gave me a little
bit of an adrenaline
thrill whenever i was the last one
standing i felt so cool i felt like wow
they must be proud of me for
for me standing there still
i i thought they would think i'm cool
but every other game
they would always choose me last in the
team
they would never appreciate me and my
dodging skill
defense zero speed hundred
i'm getting for the prologue
oh my god being told that that was the
prologue i i hope it's a joke
but
cause i mean in some way i'm happy
because that means i can still play so
much more
but in another way it scares me i'm like
what was all that for then
what was all of that for then up until
now
i mean is it officially related prologue
no it isn't right
but you take it as a prologue because
everything after that is so much more
important i guess
i really want to play a replicant too
now because uh
basically does it mean that in
replicants there are still humans
if it's the if it's the prequel does it
mean that there are still humans
that's so interesting so don't ask okay
okay reading super chat thank you daisy
lubiak
[Music]
can't i see you're just starting near
automata it's one of my favorite games i
hope you will like it
no i've already played for hours and
hours and hours
gd cafe thank you for the pinkie root be
done congrats
thank you i'm proud of myself
for going through these super long jrpgs
because i like them rather than forcing
myself to play
other games which give me more viewers
um just because i love japanese so much
and i i think i want to enjoy
the games i play rather than playing
games that i don't like just because
they get more viewers
if if those were if the games that get
more viewers were games that i would
also like and enjoy then okay no problem
but most most of them aren't like i
don't like shooter games
i'm also fascinated by the fact that
shooter games like fps games get so many
uh so many viewers like
i don't quite understand because it's
just like boom boom boom boom
i personally don't get it like what's
it's just people shooting each other
there's like no story and
no no nothing i don't get it
it's i just i got i don't understand the
charm
the charm of it i don't know i know so
many people enjoy it so much
watching it and playing it but i don't
get it at all nothing against people who
enjoy it like
good for you
but i don't get it
i mean i understand that it must be fun
to play
but why is it fun to watch
[Music]
but i guess i can ask the same question
why is it fun to watch someone play an
rpg rather than play it yourself
but at least at least an rpg has a story
it's like watching an anime or something
like that watching a movie
to me
it's like sports but like in sports i
feel like sports are
more interesting than fps games like
there's more happening in most sports
like
soccer like to me
watching soccer is at least somewhat
interesting
but oh well um
it's fun to watch scale
i mean really no problem with people who
enjoy it i just don't get it
got so much cat hair everywhere again it
feels so tingly
[Music]
thank you thank you everyone
congratulating on on finishing the route
thank you guys except for
kitten dancing for the yard ninja
postman
thank you sir
i don't feel so comfortable saying your
name
even though it's totally fine but the
way that i will pronounce it
makes me think of a german word and it
makes me feel very uncomfortable saying
it like that
damn it sir
sir t-h-i-c-c
okay if you don't speak german you don't
understand why i don't like i don't want
to say it
in that combination of words
that's totally fine in english it's
totally fine in english
s-a-l-o-t
there's a lot a lot of thickness but
anyway so what this is what does this
say fun fact to me his name is obviously
supposed to sound like to be
oh it's supposed to sound like that i
thought they were just putting
random numbers and letters together
unless unknown is 9s
name sounds like the latin phrase non-s
which means non-existent
so together to be in that srt or not to
be
brain explosion
wow so smart but i wonder like
because the rents are like the queries
of the game are mostly japanese right
and then it was made in japan and like
how do these things translate though
like obviously
probably not they don't probably they
don't
probably they just had it in english but
i wonder how it translated to the
audience
like did they miss out on a lot of these
things like also on the on the jokes
with the with the ending
letters like b and c they had some jokes
going on there didn't they
so what what was there for the japanese
viewer players i wonder
was it just the same in english
gosh
english is used casually throughout
japan right not sure
um no no no no no they learn it in
school but
no
[Music]
i mean if you're really into the game
i'm sure that they
wanted to learn more about those
those hints
but i wonder if they translated it to
japanese and made it like kind of sound
the same
way like 2b like at the end of the route
b
it says to be or not to be or something
like that
i wonder if they translated that witch
uh thank you for the pinky comments i'm
beating the prologue thank you i guess
leo rico 86 thank you and felix style
thank you for red super chat
congratulations on getting the b ending
dental feel free to get some rest before
starting the next part i was going to
say a bit more about the game but just
in case i'm gonna shut up
probably better that way if you think
you can't hold back spoilers
thank you no felix i'm looking forward
to the other endings thank you very much
but no no time to rest next stream on
near
is tomorrow the next near stream is very
tyson thank you for the pinky
and now to the now the root bee pinky
you're starting to fly through this but
now the real game begins getting ready
for the trip tension and get ready for
the trip tangible
route c is a trip thanks for playing
this watching you take the ride that is
near is amazing thank you
it's amazing for me too i like like
really
deep games that have a lot of meaning so
this is one of the best games i could
have ever played on stream i guess
and uh one of the
deepest deepest content and
the most beautiful content
very glad to be able to play with you
guys
i'm glad i didn't play it privately
before
it was it was good that i failed so many
times
in the tutorial because i didn't know
how to dodge
and then gave up after trying and trying
and trying
thank god otherwise i would have
probably already played it
if i figured out how to dodge
check it out felix sal thank you for
another red zipper
wow also when you think you should save
in a separate slot and don't look into
the next part yet
why did everyone not want me to look
like i was going to look anyway tomorrow
why why was everyone like no don't look
don't look i don't get it
why not why not
but thank you yeah we didn't know how
far you would go now i really only
wanted to
see who i would play
[Music]
spoilers but why spoilers when i'm
playing the game
at that moment i
how how would i spoil myself like i
would
play it anyway and like like
i don't get it
[Music]
congrats on finishing ruby thank you
every time i say root bee i feel like
i'm saying root beer
pronunciation problems
thank you tai chi cosplay spells thank
you so much
thank you for the pinky converts on
finishing route b
now that you are done with the tutorial
it is time to start the real game
it scares me that everyone says that
scary scary
razzie dancing
that's it for the new automatic super
chats we got through them quite quickly
it was a lot but a lot of smaller ones
so i
didn't have to read all the text
and uh thank you for
being so considerate and accepting that
because
it is past midnight here and i don't
wanna
read too long on these super chats
sorry but now we read the super chats
from today's stream
looking for the top down patrick chen
p125
traveled i just want to send in a little
love for the stream title i didn't
expect it
so it really cracked me up why what's so
funny about the stream title
what's what's so funny about it
[Music]
such a good title
how to not be a douchebag
i originally wanted to write how to not
be an [\h__\h] when i was like okay maybe
i shouldn't use that word in the title
hey you think douchebag is just a funny
word
it's really straightforward i was going
to be even more straightforward but i
went for douchebag
you just like the words douchebag oh
okay
cool
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you attention my new iphone 12
mini screen was accidentally broken by
me
can you comfort me
why did you not put
a cover on top of it huh
so that it wouldn't break why why sleeka
why iphones are expensive aren't they
it's like
i cannot comfort you that was
not very smart how did you break it
did you just drop it iphones do um break
very easily don't they
i've been using um privately i've been
using a smartphone
from all of my life and i dropped it a
million times
every phone i had dropped it a lot but
never had any screen break ever
meanwhile you drop an
iphone and it instantly breaks
honestly like 50
maybe 70 of the people who i see with an
iphone have a broken screen
[Music]
funny
damn i feel cold out
so sorry now i have i have an iphone too
uh but it's like i don't i don't take it
outside i don't ever move it
so it's safe
i think but i'm i'm very careful
with it my phone cracked when someone
stabbed on it but the screen is still
usable because it didn't shatter
completely
damn who stepped on your phone
arrest that person you should make that
person pay for a new screen what the
hell
anyway thank you hope you're not too sad
about the broken
screen i don't know if this is a joke or
if it's for real but damn
if you if you spend actually just the
money you spend on this those these red
super chats
you could spend them on repairing your
phone screen
okay you do you obvious
priorities i see i see kiara is more
important than uh
than a phone nice
nice
and razz thank you mr cat
taking on the past canada has given me
plenty of good idol songs to jam to
but i'm still nervous do you have any
recommendations for me
but i thought i already gave you plenty
eh recommendations for idol songs well i
mean
did you go through all of betty's kobu
and juice
juice and smell it and and morning music
and cute did you go through all of them
did you also go for a bono
not yet but then there you [\h__\h] go
wasn't that obvious that you have to go
through everything in a hello project
geez
have fun once you start
there's so much hello project stuff i
mean you
no matter how big you deep it's
it's not even a rabbit hole it's like a
rabbit loop you'll never get out of it
did you say that
oops that's that's that's how
how devastating that loop is
randall thank you yeah yeah laser guide
i'll do some magic thank you
dr helgens thank you guys thank you
felix thank you for a red super chat
good evening nintendo i missed the first
half of the last cookie yum and i'm not
missing it again why did you not watch
dark god
also i have a feeling that near tomorrow
is gonna be as long as usual so make
sure you get enough rest tonight
yeah i mean no i mean not necessarily
because yesterday i was just like i
really wanted to finish it so tomorrow
i'm not going to
force myself i'm just go i'm just going
to end it at a point where
it fits nicely and when i feel like
that's enough
i'm not going to stress myself but yeah
yes thank you
[Music]
danny godfrey thank you afternoon afghan
mobs
thank you thank you for using a
translator and not making me translate
by myself
it's really annoying to switch tabs and
open google translate
hello from russia kiara spazziba
hello have a good stream i thought you
were a kfc chicken but you were phoenix
oops that was awkward
now i would have preferred you to keep
that in russian so i would have skipped
it
russia says you're not stupid
the russians have come to my stream to
insult me
am i not i'm not wearing enough adidas
for you huh
sorry you're picking a fight with me
let's fight let's fight come on come on
come on
yeah i guess he defended my intelligence
but but i don't know
i don't know i feel like he's i feel
like he's challenging me he's to feel
like he wants to fight
she called me a chicken after all
need to get the trip yeah let me buy
some adidas
real quick
uh crunchy three four nine times thank
you mr casper
nexus thank you fred
[Music]
monkey i've been a member for a while
started watching it more often again
since last week i don't regret it a bit
kiara is sweet chad this whole song me
is sold i might be ky every so often
though
thank you i'm happy to hear that thank
you del star kf
it has come to my attention that officer
subato has enough evidence for a train
you mean trial it is a time to call
it is time to call the kfp lawyers to
prove your innocence and find those
responsible for the false leaks
you did what you had for to for the good
of kfp and loyalty kfp
well i know that uh i know some of you
have leaked my stuff i know i know some
of you i know
i know exactly who here was reporting me
i know for example where bear was
reporting me
yep hello i see you
i see you
but it's okay because i said myself i
wanted to be arrested
i want to be on subaru's police
trial thingy let's see what happens
let's see what happens
uh try to arrest me try
come on come on super senpai give it a
try
i want to see you try
it demonic sixty-three times
stop going
what are you doing here my cat is just
sitting down on the
ground on the floor next to my chair and
staring into nothingness
okay
oh
no that was smoothie i i brushed them
uh a lot today both of them there's like
uh i had this uh they said there's this
kind of weird brush that's like just a
uh a glove with some
nip knots on it and when you
when you brush your cat with that
glove yeah a blue glove yeah
it like gets a lot of a lot of hair
uh off of them it's really good
it's better than that yeah stupid
painful brush because they like
the glove somewhat especially jonker she
really
likes the other club but she just feels
like she's being
uh petted
and she's not she likes being brushed
too normally but not with the you know
the new brush that i got recently she
doesn't like the new brush
because it goes in too deep but anyway
the glove is really nice
and uh i've
brushed so much hair off of them today
that i could probably make a new cat
out of it yeah
i think it's time for them to shed start
chatting for the summer
that will be fun so much hair everywhere
already
no i threw the cat hair away
yeah my cats are long-haired um
yeah then the brush pulled out too much
for i have a normal brush which is
mostly um
which doesn't go that deep but i got
this like
undercoat brush and they didn't like it
at all
i love your earrings yeah that looks
awesome are you are you trying
those are not earrings look look
you're there i have one earring see it
you see it but the freaking spiders come
from behind they grow out of my head
okay
how often do i have to say it never else
how often do you want me to say it
i got one stop yeah not on that side i
don't have it on that side i only have
it on that side
remember it artists artists and everyone
[Music]
yes
did you know people make puppets out of
cat hair yeah i know and you know what i
don't think it's weird
i like the idea of it
i love your popsicle can it looks
awesome you suck you suck
worked for me on the hand raising part
weird why did it not work for me i
really wonder
that's so weird seth please thank you
soon thank you for the pinky
kiana you're my favorite video wherever
i think you're pretty wholesome
i've never met a phoenix so that's so
awesome yay thank you
i'm obviously you never met a fakes
before because i'm the only phoenix here
thank you i'm glad i'm glad i'm your
favorite that's really nice to hear
thank you very much hope you enjoyed the
content from now on as well
nonyx81
looking looking for the top function
[Music]
magic mango 99 thank you sean nielsen
time to thank you for the red super chat
with ky well thank you but actually does
the super chat before that niels mh says
he had the same issues on the pc version
what is it what the steam version of
games what is it
what is the issue hmm
foreign
[Music]
hey boss ever heard of a future musical
called wicked i encourage you to listen
to
the soundtrack sometime at least a song
for good on it and you'd understand it
very well
also i encourage you to look into the
drop co-op game
deep rock galactic never heard of
any of those
thank you thank you i might look into it
thank you for your recommendations
people seem to be reacting to wicked oh
i think you'd like wicked
you would really like wicked eh why do
you all know wicked
is it so famous i never heard of it
you guys like deep rock too wow
so many recommendations so many people
who know the recommendation and i don't
know it
hmm
oh happy birthday to you
it's his birthday herbalist rendang
chen flynn pierce sanchez ocean man
thank you little smith
hello from russia we love you really
really okay then i love you too
i i i prefer to have a lovey-dovey
relationship
with you guys so just stop calling me
chicken
and then we're good
okay i'm refreshing oh
and scrolling there we go
[Music]
pauldron golem thank you also happy
birthday
it's been a long time since your last
kadogan i was wondering if he would
consider a song called bonnie and clyde
by the total host and have a great day
i'm not sure i'm not a fan of the
tottenham
i might sing more german songs again in
the future but
probably not that one i'm sorry but i
wish you happy happy birthday
and um yeah it's been a little while
since my last color okay but did you did
you miss the one where i sang whole live
songs
i practiced so hard for that one i hope
you all saw that one
as a cakes cooked and frustrating now
what's the best monster
that's making
[Music]
um you sounded so good thank you
thank you i want to re-challenge some of
the songs
because i i didn't i didn't um
sang them perfectly
after all but suspect was godly thank
you i can do that one better too though
if i had more time to practice
maybe i'll recharge some in uh 800k
right now 900k
the next next one is 900k right
hmm wait how many what you doing
yeah 900. i
i wanted to do another kind of look at a
celebration at 900k
because it has been a while
not sure if it's going to be archived
and not archived style
preferably preferably archived
so let's do soon it soon
i'm going to practice some songs for you
guys and we can sing
sing again rosie dances dance in
carefree ranger wolf dankeshan justin
graham duncan
did you see the shout out to you and
cordon and super chat
reading during her chicken game stream
earlier no i didn't but
recently i have noticed especially
because everyone has been playing this
harvest moon game
um and everyone's been getting chickens
in their games and everyone has been
naming those freaking chickens kiara
i mean that's sweet and all but you guys
realize that i
am not a chicken right every freaking
whole live member that has been playing
that game
or any other game where there's a
chicken they've been calling the chicken
kiana but i'm not a chicken
i don't know what to do about this
they're just they're just spreading
these rumors with their
with their games in their streams
they're just
spreading and spreading it and i can't
do anything about it because no one will
listen to me
but it's nice to be mentioned over and
over and over again
by inatan
yay it's pretty sweet yeah
daisy danke sin chris dobbs donkey
shooting crunchy three four nine donkey
shin pudding duncan
iron heart thank you you know how we
like to affectionately call you our
rainbow chicken
you know what other birds are commonly
called rainbow chickens
sun canoes
[Music]
what why why i don't understand you're
not a chicken you're a rainbow what the
[\h__\h] iron heart
what why am i rainbow chicken
i don't understand
[Music]
that says hello
she wants to cuddle you gotta end this
quickly
thank you to pinky i do love the german
phoenix as botan
and ancient german of ordinal father
i do have to say you have the greatest
five meat
of all the nine realms
thank you i mean he called me a phoenix
interesting what's going on
what's going on in these super jets
thank you very much i
i know i have the greatest fight
thank you
tre tracing thank you chimi by dan
kashan looking for the top
uh grant thompson's function
your twitter link in the description
isn't working oh my god it's so annoying
like uh
like the links sometimes stop working
in the description even though i'm just
copying or like reusing the settings
from the previous stream
duh well i really don't have the time to
check each link every freaking stream
damn that's annoying why does it always
stop working
i fixed it once but i guess i don't know
ah anyway thanks for letting me know
that it's still not working good to know
chris dubs duncan brady and crimson
games are like sports it's a competition
and you want to root for your team
and you get to watch your strategies in
action okay i see
motivational reminder rpg streams are
peak vod content and a lot of us watch
them
that way due to the time cluster i agree
with that like
i like to watch rpg streams and archives
uh as well
whenever i need something to watch
because i run out of shows on netflix
and stuff
i do enjoy that a lot myself lexington
the lion dancer
i like that you play jrpgs i don't see
anyone else streaming them
i've never played any before thank you
for introducing me what you never played
on
yourself well then get started
what you better get started
maybe you'll find one you like by
watching me
hippity hopperty you are now it cuts off
there but thank you soon crunchy349
thank you soon matthew easter duncan
jacqueline duncan missed with
thanksgiving
for an idle recommendation have you
heard of the really talented one who
started making music recently
takanasi kiana
thank you for that amazing
recommendation best fist
you got good taste
[Music]
right right
thank you for the pinky um
i feel like that's kind of a spoiler the
fact
is actually like a little bit kind of
low-key
accidentally spoiled myself on that
already
the the the phrase
with uh you're thinking about
how how much you wanna it to be
and now you're telling me about it in
super chat well i already kind of
know i guess but um
that it has a different meaning
apparently
um and i will i will kind of get to it
later in the game i guess it kind of
sucks okay so
i'm not i'm not gonna read the super
chat but thank you thank you
i'm going to continue thinking that 9s
wants to to be
that's what i want to think that's more
wholesome
than the other thing that it's probably
supposed to mean
it's more hold i mean of course it's
more wholesome
it is more handsome
magnificent eyes oh small skeletons
inside
molten fairy sight mama and the boss
adorable
cute chicken whoops i mean phoenix hope
you like the haiku i made this
homage well thank you we haven't gotten
a haiku or like
wraps or or poems in a long time now
what happened we got so many before why
did it why did it stop why did you guys
stop i want to hear more
thank you for the thinking to us zero
okay very sweet of you
black friction ducation dress and
reinhardt function falsely thank you
i just wanted to thank you from the
bottom of the heart of my heart for
being one of the
bright lights in this cruel and
depressing world being able to listen in
on your streams has been an immense help
from my depression so thank you
happy to hear that thank you
well then please continue watching my
streams if that makes you happy then i
want nothing else just
keep on watching thank you i'm glad i
could help
dakomadankashin iron heart thank you
extra live stream lord
[Music]
one more question do you have to cut
shorten your hair every month
uh it kind of stays like that what are
you doing
oh yeah it doesn't really grow much
unfortunately
yeah so i don't cut it no
also thank you liaori oliore
wonder why someone might have stopped
sending high cause i don't know why you
should
wha are you are you working on your
hikers and your new poems dealer67 as i
told you
to practice
thank you for the pinky for the cutest
movie and suckers
meow trunk is my aussie one of those
movies movie is hella soft
i know you would like this movie as well
thank you thank you sean eyre thank you
for pinky too
my name is sean iron and i'm here to say
i love kiara's dreams in a major way ah
there we go with the poets
thank you i thought you were
yeah i thought you were gonna say and
i'm here to stay
that would have worked too but okay
thank you that's it for the super chats
we have managed to read them all sorry
for not reading so many messages today
there were a lot of short ones
so and my freaking nose is so itchy
i'm gonna go and eat sandwich now and
then go to bed
and tomorrow near automata i don't know
if you guys saw the
the schedule but if you haven't it's on
twitter and it's on the community board
um it's up there if you haven't seen it
yet this week is pretty exciting
and oh yeah there's a special collab on
uh first of april
we are planning to play
jackpots games but there is also
an announcement
maybe maybe plural
i don't know i don't know
there might be something in that stream
that you want to see
i don't know who cares
who cares about announcements who cares
about
collabs who cares about streams now
don't come don't come you
you're not gonna like uh by the way
it's not gonna i don't think it's gonna
be streamed on all channels it's uh
plans to be only streamed on cali's
channel
she's uh hosting it this time
because jackpot's game doesn't need uh
everyone's perspective
so we're just gonna go with one
perspective and we were asking her out
who wants to
who wants to host and callie hasn't
toasted in a while so there we go
hmm you'll want to you'll be in the
stream you want to see that
trying to produce very psychology on me
no no no no no no
why would you want to see
[Music]
it's not going to be interesting at all
it's not going to be fun
no it's going to be boring boring collab
nothing to see don't come
nothing to look forward to nothing to be
insanely hyped about no
nope thank you for the super chat
yesterday laser guy and skye
danke ah that's it for today
i'll see you tomorrow and in
near automata thanks for watching and
enjoy when we say
auf wiedersehen also come to hollow talk
thank you nero for the membership come
to hallo talk on the weekend
me
bye bye had fun today thanks
[Music]
you