[Music]
so
okay
okay i could have been here much earlier
but i had the cardboard disease once
again
so it took me [\h__\h] 40 minutes to set
this [\h__\h] up
and i still didn't find a real solution
so [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] i'm so mad
first it was funny i was getting up and
was like oh oh my god and when i looked
at my phone and i realized what time it
is i woke up because like
first of all my neighbor was like was
like bonking some carpets or something
and that noise woke me up but then i was
like um
i'm actually not that tired anymore
let's check the time
and then i saw it's like 11 40.
no was it 11 4 i think it was something
like that
yeah so i should have already started
and i was like
i don't know it was 12 already i think
but my my alarm
well i don't know that i'm so confused
but anyway i checked my alarms but
my alarms were turned off i set them
last night
but i think maybe i did a mistake with
setting the alarms when i changed the
time it probably turned them off
you know i'm so proud of the fact that i
usually
don't don't have pro yeah i know
everyone was like even my papa
retweeted my old tweet i'm
so freaking mad
but it's not like i it's
you know the people who oversleep even
though they have an alarm on
okay those are the bad people just
kidding not they're not bad people but
but that's that's that's a problem but
my alarm
i didn't have an alarm to begin with
okay
anyway first i was like wow this is
funny
because you guys are making fun of me i
was laughing okay i was embarrassed and
laughing and
this was i was doing like this kind of
like walk of shame thing
and i started getting ready but then
nothing worked for [\h__\h] sake
[Music]
um
but the problem is i don't have much
[\h__\h] time
i'm gonna be reading super chats by now
i don't know
i don't have time
i don't have [\h__\h] time so i'm still a
few races
i don't have time
now that's what's really pissing me off
is i don't have [\h__\h] time
ah
[Music]
i need to be doing [\h__\h] which one do i
go for again
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h] all of this
i think it's online play
if you i'm not i don't want to read it
read it take it now
okay here's the code okay okay i don't
want to write it down
i don't want to write it down
i'm done okay let's go
i don't have time for this
all right let's turn on the bgmo
let's turn it back up
no i can't cancel it cause i barely i
can barely stream
what i can barely stream for the rest of
the
week so what the [\h__\h]
let me join
no [\h__\h] you
sorry i'm mad
hurry up
hurry up out of time
i'm really on the need for speed now
i'm really i really have a need for
speed
what the [\h__\h] are you talking about
what what
what
let's try this one i'll open it up we're
going to open it up
on there
what's what's going on oh this one works
oh hello
what the hell how the [\h__\h] did you
wow oh did you guys get the number
can i check it again and how do i check
it again
uh you guys did you guys get the number
how the hell is you guys good job
okay one second oh my god
i don't have the number does some does
someone have the number
i need to take my medicine one second
who ha anyone who has the number write
it in the chat so i can
no i don't want to do this one oh
someone posted the number he's not
really in
i'm gonna try to pin it i don't know if
it is
did i pin the rap message come on
come on
[Music]
um
all of you are stealing my number one
what the hell was that why did i stop
for a moment
how do i use items again
[Music]
[Laughter]
are you playing yoshi i love yoshi
[Music]
oh oh oh hi hi honestly i think we
turned it
off last time what no maybe we turn it
off
i need to win right now guys i need to
win
i i cried okay first time at first i was
like
haha this is funny i overslept this is
gonna be funny
and then i tried setting up things and
it didn't work so i got mad
and then i started crying because then i
was just really really sad
because nothing was working i don't have
time it stressed me out
oh my gosh bowser you look scary
i need a win guys
[Music]
conley you're so close to me are you
trying to cheer me up or could you do
better
do that judas
judas i know you're not that bad you
must be here
to bully me or something i just i
i ground pounded that rock
[Music]
damn it i'm still 12. what the hell is
going on
i wasn't even saying that bad
story they don't do anything thank you
oh do you just wanna
wait what was that what is that why did
i do that i don't understand
it doesn't make any sense it's not like
i'm actually
[Music]
come on come on
oh a nice one for once
i almost got you there
wait dude what was that that that was
third place had some kind of
uh medal what was that
two dollars did you give me a win
because
because i said i need to win
oh is that what happened thank you guys
please leave the race and
thank you please leave the race and then
give someone else is that really the
real code guys test it out and try to
get in
is that really the right code eighth
place yeah it's not that bad don't you
write one of the cheerios so you can
take the w this time
will you what i'd win ah
thank you sweet it's real okay
it works okay okay cool cool cuckoo cool
in the words of abbott cuckoo cool
okay electro dome one i know there's so
many
i don't think i've played either of
these two before i want this one looks
crazy
i want this one
everyone welcome i feel like one
or two people didn't leave
i feel like
[Music]
cool
let's do another one i don't know if i
can do a full hour maybe 40 minutes i
don't know
because i gotta read some super chats
otherwise i'll be behind
so far so far
alexander wasn't he in the last row all
right too
god damn it why did i have to
why was my alarm off i don't get it
why was it off goddammit
oh now what about my my
awesome record of never over sleeping no
people are never going to take me
seriously again never
[Music]
it's not cool it's not fair
my lung my freaking alarm
i don't know what happened i don't know
it's not my fault
[Music]
we need someone like uh like fugu
in our whole life english team who would
in such
situations do a like you know um
waiting until she wakes up stream
[\h__\h] you who is that
maybe ina maybe enough should do it
enough was awake actually so ena
actually tried to help me
ah you [\h__\h] faster
nina was awake to help me i didn't even
i didn't even tell anyone that i went
like that i was that i uh
was having specific issues i didn't tell
anyone in in our discord
marina showed up with my dms and she was
like
hey what's up how can i help you what's
what's the problem what seems to be the
issue
let me guess is it is it the capture
card it was not the capture card but
um it was sweet of her to assume that
that was it
because it is often to capture what it
used to be
after the capture card these days the
capture card does not give me any issues
why am i fifth right now what what
[Music]
why is everyone stopping you don't they
usually continue to drive
how did i get fifth what are people
being nice to me again
oh no rainbow road but i have all this
uh auto steering on so i shouldn't be a
problem okay everyone's leaving
thank you thank you please leave thank
you for driving with me
thank you thank you i hope you guys had
some fun
are you new
yoshi let's go for yoshi yoshi is a
classic please let me go on yoshi
circuit
please please i want to drive on the
yoshi road
who's the nosaki this time no sagi-san
ta-da
the chances were low but we did it who's
the
nice drive i feel like i've maybe seen
that before
that's freaking down
told him to respect me because i'm the
most famous
out there i am it's the freaking item
wait you know what we do oh damn it all
the steering i want to stop
we're gonna do the aqua i got senpai
technique because i learned that from
here so we go all the way back so
they're doing it they're doing it
they're doing the awkward technique
come on i need an item to do this do i
still have a chance
the problem does this even work when
everyone's doing it
when like three people are doing it
okay okay okay good and now of course i
waited quite a long time to use them
oh good items good items
i'm just going to use it now because i'm
way way behind anyway
damn it wait
what at least one of the people who did
that in the beginning is number one now
maybe i shouldn't have chosen this road
because that's where akko senpai did the
thing oh hello
oh hello and uh i guess it's the easiest
road to do that damn it
[Music]
i don't need that you almost got me with
that one hello
that was at the perfect timing thank you
for that thunder
it was a little bit too early
[Music]
you're the winner yeah where am i right
now
hello what the hell no i don't want to
start
glass this is stupid what is this race
what oh what happened here and i'm
catching up to some people
okay ready okay go go go go go go go go
thank you
thank you i needed to win
i needed it yeah now can i get number
one please
technique wasn't working hundred percent
could have could have worked better
thank you guys thank you
next up please next people come in
please please
you look good in the crown thank you i
agree with that
amazing recovery are you are you saying
that in irony wait where is everyone
don't let me drive with two people there
we go
oh god the alien i've seen that alien
before i think
that a cute nosaki
no sake is for the people who don't know
why would you not know i
have um that it's a fan name of piccolos
and by fans
leave drx what
are you telling him to leave because he
was in the uh ride before yeah what the
hell
why'd you not leave why
next time you better leave imagine it he
has been in there for three games really
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
okay guys i haven't been clear about the
about the rules
and you leave at pekka yeah
you leave after you have played one
right with me so
i don't know how to kick him though
you guys have got to tell me how to do
it
oh wait rainbow road but it looks so
easy wait since when is rainbow road
looking when
when i think of rainbow road i actually
think of uh the other one
oh i actually got one i just randomly
threw it out there
i actually got [\h__\h] you
yay this is actually not that bad
hey the other one is whoa the other one
that's so colorful is way more difficult
i think
the other one it's not officially called
rainbow road yeah
[Music]
oh my god what the [\h__\h] is going on why
is it so crowded
[Music]
oh the goat has fallen i repeat the goat
has fallen down the rainbow road
the goat has fallen the gold is back in
front of me
how are you right in front of me again
you just fell down you're cheating
there you go you should be behind me
that's right that's right
yo
[Applause]
getting those good items wow did you see
that
that that that the drift did you see my
voice
thunder can't get me finder can't get me
yeah i double item oh what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] was that
hey
[Music]
oh i'm getting really good items but i'm
still number 10 what the hell
what now get that back to me
that back to me no [\h__\h] hell
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Laughter]
why are they so good why are they so
freaking good
why are we on this screen oh yeah
hello why are we on this screen
and the coco what
am i gonna get an error message oh yeah
i know there we go
okay has he left oh no
no there's free no sakes
it's free
who's the other one say something
say something i'm giving up on
one two three four five six seven eight
nine
ten eleven actually we are i just didn't
choose okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
last minute solution i'm talking to my
nose aggies in japanese hoping that they
will understand me but
they don't seem to acknowledge me as
their queen
what do i need to do to have them
acknowledge me as
at least one of their queens what do i
need to do
hello hello no one here no one here
telling me oh
almost got that
i got some quite the distance oh [\h__\h]
i got quite the distance um between the
people back
i think at least
i can't use the green challenge
[Music]
last second he
he ran past me it's not fair
it's not fair
[Laughter]
like why did the did he die drop out
because he'd suddenly changed into
a different avatar i'm confused
animal crossing animal crossing okay
everyone leave thank you
thank you
yeah by you i don't have time ah
how much more maybe we do like three or
four more rides and then we're gonna
read super chat
i know i can't read all of them but
i gotta read only some of them oh my god
what a weird face
what do you do to right oh you're
supposed are you supposed to be a burger
she does look like a burger
that's fascinating the pin code is wrong
really really
really really can someone
confirm that it's not wrong i changed
zombies um
i guess yeah that one time when it was
loading so long i probably changed
yeah because it usually it creates like
two lobbies and you gotta be lucky to
get into the one where i am in
is that kelly no i've seen her before
that looks like that anime character
i know that sounds dakuma i know it
sounds super generic but it does look
like that one anime
character that that did the one that did
the dance
[Music]
oh my god look at the villagers oh [\h__\h]
i'm too late
get it okay
this is just a chill ride for the animal
crossing
world
what a good start dakuma
bakuma you know what's going to happen
if you don't let me win if you're doing
better than me you know what's going to
happen right that come on
don't get cocky document just because
you got in don't get cocky because of
that you still have a job to do which is
letting me win
are you aware of that sometimes it might
be hard
to let me win because i'm just so so
bad already it's hard to do worse than
me
i understand i understand that
but the user room is waiting for you
[Music]
and for all of you all of you who are
not letting me win you know where you're
going after this ride you know where are
you going
you know why everyone's been real quiet
after they had uh
the chance to ride with me you know why
everyone is so quiet after that
[\h__\h] hell what's this what's going on
i'm not driving like that it's weird
with the [\h__\h] coins it's not that
hard
nice nice one nice one nice one and the
star right after
nicely
star star star star star star star star
star
woohoo yeah
yeah that banana ain't got nothing on me
come on give me give me already oh no
wait i thought that was the goal for
some reason
ghost and girls boo hoo
boo oh nice
i wonder who we sold out from let's go
still am close no more angle
that was close that was extremely close
that was so close
what the [\h__\h] just passed by me last
second who was that
who was that daddy
who was that tell me john
okay john john you are going into the
usual room
dakoma you can stay where you are
you can keep on working where you
usually work at but john you are going
into the usual room that was
so unnecessary
thank you everyone thank you burger wait
i'm so proud of the burger dough because
you know we gotta love we gotta stand
the burgers we gotta
support the burgers congratulations on
getting number one burger i'm proud of
you
i'm proud of you and i will eat you
after this
winner win a chicken dinner wait that
makes so much sense that
just makes so much sense you're the
winner but you'll be calling my dinner
okay are people coming in wait burger
you need to leave and the one with the
spiky hair i think too
what wait we're not enough people what
the [\h__\h] is our face
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] now
now what happened here did you guys not
try to get in
i think three people didn't leave but i
guess since we didn't get enough new
people anyway it's okay
because otherwise i would be driving
against what four people
i was gonna say he looks like colonel
i'm trying like hacked again uh
that's weird did you guys only get into
the
the the second lobby
okay we have a overseeable
um amount of participants
so i would like you guys to coordinate
yourselves
in a way that i would win understand
it can't be that hard because we're just
like what six people
it's it it cannot be that hard to let me
win
okay what's happening let's have a nice
and and and and calm i wanted to use
that
let's be fair okay follow follow the
rules
of the kiara kingdom
okay before it's going well okay i think
everyone is agreeing to the
plan let me go there let me go there let
me go
[Music]
hey could i [\h__\h] all the steering is
pissing me off right now because i
wanted to go here while i was flying
he wouldn't let me why am doing so bad
no item item item item
all are mine all of them are mine
stupid buses stupid stupid buses get get
rid of them
[\h__\h] me [\h__\h] [\h__\h] those bosses
wait wait wait um ghost wait no someone
stole that from me oh i thought i was
gonna be the ghost damn it
got bamboozled
what the hell is it what do you want
from me peach peach point
2.0 what do you want from me
what is this what's going on colonel
colonel
[Music]
huh oh
well i mean that's not i don't see that
much uh as a big win
oh wow oh well i'll take it i'll take it
number three is pretty damn good okay
everyone leave
okay don't be a dick
burger leave spiky hair leave i think
the one with the glasses leave
all of you leave the one with the pink
uh with the blonde hair leaf
thank you thank you thank you thank you
very much
thank you but please leave okay how do i
kick people
chiana no toe
kiara's toe wait oh my god you do look
like a toad with lots of
um with a lot of imagination like that
the blonde guy
was there before no why why are there no
new people coming in either wasn't the
blonde guy get here before
my toe
wrong room code no it's just two lobbies
i think
[Music]
thank you guys for the super jets by the
way
i want to read them but i'll try to read
as many as possible
today yeah
schnitzel from australia
janna is in the yeah yeah i'm in the
kusatori tournament because the speed
one didn't let me
i'm in the kusatoni tournament
that's the first time it looks like
hokkaido to me what the hell
wait what happens if we drop down there
on our ice getting so cute
[Music]
wait this is unfair there's this guy
from norway korok wait is that the
norwegian flag it's unfair because
that's like
his natural inhabitant
it's not fair
[Music]
i hope that really was the norwegians
but i'm gonna go there what is there
oh oh
oh home field advantage unfair
what the [\h__\h] f all of you
go away
nick i hate this i hate this i hate this
i hate this i hate this
i hate this
hit the steering i need to turn it off
god damn it
it helps me sometimes but it [\h__\h] me
over so many times now i didn't get a
freaking item
damn it oh my i almost got myself into
that explosion
everyone's so close to each other except
that that uh
rosalina and is that her name
in the very front why am i so slow too
[Music]
oh wait this is new to me
all right he's gone he's gone he's gone
let's go on
[Music]
give me something good give me something
good give me something good
i hate this wait for me
for me
yes i see you sweet sweet sweet potatoes
i love you
thank you
this is how you do it you can't you
can't drive
like a crazy person until you reach the
goal
but then you're gonna stop that's where
you're gonna stop right in front of the
goal okay
and then then you for yourself you can
still tell yourself that you could have
been number one
if you wouldn't have stopped so that
that must you know help your ego
more than enough but then at that point
you have to stop
you have to stop there and wait for me
ah mount wario isn't that the one that
was on the
super mario mario kart
uh smartphone app
i want to go for the dk jungle though
wait are these new people i think i see
mostly new faces are we full though
i spent five years from sexy mouth and
after yeah okay
okay
okay thank you guys thank you for the
super chat wow wow wow
you all send super jets at the same time
okay um this i think this is going to be
the last road because i honestly have no
time
um russia boing
[Music]
i hope you don't join lucia's races with
that name
lucia mariota
[Music]
where i got where i had my accident am i
going to have an accident now too
oh it's so small
hey oh yeah give me those drifts boy
i'm number two i'm number two i'm number
two i would like to announce it i'm
number two
i'm number two
where's number one i need to get a bit
closer to him because i don't trust my
shell if i throw it up now
but i have to okay let's go
[Music]
how long oh yes yes
yes yes yes
wait is everyone just waiting behind me
what's going on why am i still number
two
no courtney don't take it away from me i
was so happy okay let's just wait there
just wait no no no no no i was so happy
you take my happiness what else do i
have left nothing
nothing nothing why is everyone in front
of me
give it back to me give it back to me
i got nothing left i got nothing
i got nothing i'm leaving my wife
and turning it into a long distance
relationship
what do i have left nothing
i just need some mario kart wings to
cheer myself up please
[Music]
okay that doesn't do anything quick
quick quick quick quick
[Music]
the japanese people are at the top why
why
okay one more that's the next one is the
last one everyone leave
[Laughter]
i need my people come on guys join doing
doing and i see
uh at least two people who have been in
here before
and two people i think is this person
yeah this one isn't here
hasn't he been in here before
wait wait wait wait there we go there we
go okay i'll cook it
that small one is cute is that amelia
is that amelia amelia
watson are you driving against me
the one with the curly hair though he
has been in here before definitely why
am i going crazy
[Music]
is is that us right
one of the japanese names was please
come to japan again
oh you're going to make me cry
[Music]
okay who said that it's me and you it's
between me and you
all these others we can't ignore because
they all suck at mario kart
it's only me and you now the best
players in the world
[Music]
i'm leaving him behind even though he
had such a sweet message but
it definitely reached me
okay no that's him okay okay he hit the
start
[Music]
but he had a star right now so i i i
didn't
i didn't um i didn't get to
damage him either way so that's okay
[Applause]
sorry sorry i gained some weight damn it
no item
sorry move move [\h__\h] get out of the way
get out the way [\h__\h]
your spikes don't hurt me number two
what the hell
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
that would have been so dope okay
foreign
wait if anyone's gonna okay here we go
[\h__\h] you yeah
[Laughter]
[Applause]
thank you very much everyone
i i was able to cheer up a little bit uh
from the stress
that ah nothing was working and i have
slept
i'm going tr i'm going to try to read
some super chats
and wait a second
well you shouldn't have seen that
i'm trying to fix some things
okay okay we will read some super chats
but
wait the the most recent ones that i
have to read
the the most the oldest ones i mean
are they from the takamuni stream then i
think i would skip those for now because
those take too long i want to read like
a whole section you know what i mean
so i would say so i need to read
takamoni
and then the nina stream and then mario
kart right
so i think for now i skipped takamuni
and maybe read them
the nanny ones and if possible also the
the mario kart ones and then keep the
tatamini ones for later because those
were
way too many just read the current
um i guess i could do that too
and i'll read though i'll read
[Music]
uh ones from yesterday but there's
nothing before takamori right
as far as i know
[Music]
also
the art is so cute actually for
for both uh the takamori stream and
the orenzo stream i reached out to mama
luni
and asked her if she could draw
something and for for the orlando one
she i told her about this um fan night
that she did of me and nana before
which i was so happy about because it
was so cute but
she she was so kind to
um because it was originally that fan
art
had and then his old outfit in it and
she was so kind
to um redo the whole art
not the whole thing she only redid her
outfit
so she used the same artwork but she did
nana's outfit which
which which was really really really
really really kind of hair but she did
also the tacoma art
the taco boy art horny [\h__\h] that one
it's just so freaking good
it's like it might have been
that might have been one of the best
artworks she has ever done like
including me
including me in the art uh her previous
works are great too but
that might have been one of the best
ones like she even made like an
original outfit because she asked me if
it's okay to draw
um original outfits instead of the usual
one i was like yes yes there's something
i don't i don't like
um and she did such a good job because i
the the kind of idol outfit that she
drew
reminds me um a bit of macras
but also of that one fandom that she has
um from the visuals it kind of reminds
me of that
what was that i actually don't really
i'm not really familiar with that but
there's this one thing that
uh one girl band a bun is a bundle
yeah yeah it does give me some vandaly
vibes too
yeah yeah did you guys get those vibes
too from those outfits
that she drew us in
you know this one
yeah i love it i love that kind of style
of uh just clothing design i love it
yoga
okay we got no time to spare um
i might be rushing through this a little
bit of course as per usual i'll be
reading every name
and every text of pink and red super
chats
and i will try to uh squeeze some
um smaller messages in there as well
from
a smaller super chat i will try but
generally i have to
be a bit quick today so i hope that's
okay for you guys
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is your name praying kara
has a safe trip home she's a wonderful
spirit of beauty
see this is not a red super chat i'm
going to read it anyway beauty with an
admirable love for the japanese culture
it must be heartbreaking to go though
she has a has priceless memories to
cherish now and there's always hope in
tomorrow
it is kind of heartbreaking yeah because
i i didn't really
accomplish any of the things that i
wanted to accomplish in this year
so if i think about it too much it makes
me cry
but it's okay because i got something
else thankfully
i talked about this before but you know
i would be devastated otherwise
what's wrong with my name pian
it's okay it's okay thanks for being
here
i'm always happy when the people whose
super chats i read are in the chat even
though it's a different stream
so that you can actually pick it up and
i'm i always really wonder how many
of the people who send super chats
are actually like going to the super
chat reading to hear
their name i always wonder
[Music]
i'm one of those people sometimes
many do i'm sure i usually
sometimes i catch you saying my name and
i totally forgot i said this
[Music]
is
thank you guys i'm glad to hear that
because you know when i read these super
chats i want you guys to
to obviously hear that i'm thankful for
you
i don't want it to be unheard so yeah
thank you
nicolas torres danke
oh kiara mother of chickens haven't you
heard the unsettling gossip that has
spread among the kfp workers about the
nefarious secrets that lie beneath the
cold and
bloodstained floor of the ur israel room
i feel compelled to unravel them
oh kiara on a side note i haven't
mustered enough strength to watch the
takamori concert we know how much you
love cali and how disheartened
heartening all this has been for you
girls stay strong on sunday take care
with you thank you thank you
nicolas i mean
i have to say for the oh let me open the
comment by the way
for the takamoni stream
[Music]
i didn't even cry as much as i thought i
would and i think i know the reason
it's because um at the point of doing
that stream
my departure was still quite far away
so um i think i'll cry once i'm on the
plane
as as far as i know myself i will cry
when i'm on the plane
yeah but up until then i'll probably be
fine
because it's just that's when that's
when i'm finally alone with my thoughts
and i'm really
like actually leaving yeah but i don't
want to cry on the plane people gonna
feel it
be like what the hell is wrong with that
girl
can you play rhizo on the plane what why
not i played on steam
i will bring my gosh i'm like oh i'm
like almost done with packing though
but today we actually have something
there there's something happening for me
like like a farewell
family dinner actually yeah
that's why i gotta leave earlier and and
tomorrow
um tomorrow is not the day when i'm
leaving
but tomorrow is the day when i'm like um
moving my things um
with a truck and i'm still gonna
um store some things in japan
because it's just too much stuff like
like um furniture stuff you know um
i'm storing those at a friend's place so
that's what's happening tomorrow
um it shouldn't take that long actually
though
so for until tomorrow i should be done
with packing everything
that's why i'm a bit stressed out
but i'm pretty pretty much done
the pink gamer girl said yeah i wish i
could bring it along with me
but it will be stored for i don't know
when
i don't know what purpose it's going to
be stored for but yeah
um unfortunately the pink gamer girl
chair cannot be sent
to australia because well
well it's too heavy and too big i'm
already sending like
10 10 boxes back to my home
which will be already expensive enough
like 10 boxes that i sent home
and then one uh one big pc box that i
will try
to and it should work honestly because i
mean people do that all the time no
like i have i have two big suitcases
that i can give up for luggage
then one small hand luggage suitcase
that i will bring in
um but besides that i will go to the
airport with like
my pc in a in a box
um and ask them to let me pay for extra
luggage
uh now i really hope it works like that
because i didn't
i didn't i didn't um uh like
reserve anything but it's
probably going to work right because i
want that i don't want to send that pc
for normal post because i feel like
it might get delayed and you never know
when it actually
um arrives um
pc as a carry that's impossible because
my pc
is too big for carry-on it doesn't
have the right size and um yeah that's
not gonna work out
but i am bringing my microphone and and
some other stuff as carry on
yeah i know pc is fragile i'm trying i'm
going to try my best to
pack it properly but i'm very worried
about that um
uh so yeah that's gonna be my my third
piece of luggage i really hope that
works out anyway
i usually take the graphics card as a
carry-on because everything else is
pretty stable
a graphics card
maybe i'll do that too
be careful with the pc heat sinks what
and gpu super heavy can cause and can
cause problems
probably just better to pack them
separately i thought about that too but
then
there was some arguments that that was
that would be a bad idea too like both
has like good points and bad points
like if i if i pack it all like if i un
unravel everything and then
i don't know i don't know it i'll just
i'll just uh yeah i'll try to take out
the graphics card maybe
that in my hand luggage and the rest gpu
always always taking that wait is the
gpu the graphics card
does gpu equal graphics card
if you have an electrostatic back to
story i don't i don't have that
where do i get that what does it look
like what's it called in japanese
an electrostatic bag where do i get that
what's it called in japanese tell me so
that i can look it up
[Music]
on
if you don't have the bag leave it alone
it's it's the bag with like metal
crisscross over it
no no can i leave the pc as it is if you
touch it you might have that's what i
thought too
damn it anti-static or electronic safe
might work as search
terms
back
oh
it i'll buy it because now i have the
japanese term for it
and then
do you guys haven't have a an idea
what i should stuff the the inside
of the pc with because i got for example
i got some
um air filled bags like tiny bags that
are connected to each other you know
what i'm talking about
like air filled plastic bags
no styrofoam or bubble wrap oh
air fill baths are okay
air filled bags should be fine
those will have a lot of static uh beans
what kind of beans are you talking about
you mean those you mean those styro
foam beans
no plastic okay what about what about
um newspaper
is newspaper okay
i don't know where to get those beans
from now
newspaper is good okay okay
gosh i'm so worried i'm so [\h__\h]
worried
worst case i do have another pc when i
go back
um which is good enough to stream it's
better than like
it should be my my pc that i have in
australia
should be better than the pc that i
first had in
in japan it's i think it's better than
that one
just ask of stanford who actually knows
no there's no time i really don't have
time
i don't have time to meet anyone right
now and i think that
that um botanzappa for example also
can't suddenly
make some time to help him with my
stupid pc
i doubt it i don't wanna and it's just
too much it's just too much too much to
think of i already
i should have called my [\h__\h] uh i
didn't
call my i i was gonna wake up early
before the stream and i was gonna call
the gas company and the water company
and uh that i like electric's company
and was gonna call them and tell them
i'm leaving
but i couldn't do it because i was late
and then nothing worked out
[Music]
sorry two stressed out
i need to read super chats pudding
duncan
dominique duncan kfp window thank you
soon looking for the top down kitchen so
let's keep playing thank you
this is a thank you to all i love to
write but never did anything with my
skills until now and i was inspired by
both
you and the community i made a takamura
fan version and managed to complete
today with over 15 000 words wow i feel
so fulfilled so i want to say thank you
to callie for motivating me to start
the kfp employees will encourage me to
keep going and of course your attention
who inspires me every single day to try
my best things thank you so let's keep
lying
good job on finishing it i hope a lot of
people
will read it good job thank you
thank you for the super chat thank you
thank you for the red super chat
congrats on the new song cover of king
i bamboozled you guys didn't i
use instapack to pack the inside of the
pc google
but can i find that in in japan
can i even find them
what is that
i don't have time
i don't know what that is
i didn't know thank
[Music]
soon
see now someone says just take out their
hd and cpu only those are valuable in
fragile but the others say
take out the gpu i don't even know i
[\h__\h] know
i don't know
[Music]
i don't want to read super chats like
that
i feel too stressed out
what if i if i don't write down it's
gonna be way too much
sorry guys
oh i think i'll end it here because i
i have to finish packing and then get
ready for
something
sorry for the bad stream i was late
and
and now i'm ending it like this
kind of sucks
sorry guys
on a on a happy note
last night casper was really noisy so
he seems to be
quite energetic again
he's alive thanks to eating all my
chocolate
and so it's it's not it's nice to know
that he's
he's he's happy
okay guys
um i really appreciate all of you
staying here to
to be with me i i i'm not sure about
what to do for the rest of i'll have to
see how how early i finish tomorrow
tomorrow might be quite gorilla but it
should be in the evening time of japan
even in time japan i'll probably be
streaming
um
it's okay once that once all my [\h__\h] is
being taken away tomorrow
it should mostly be
no us actually that's where the whole
stress starts
okay it's so hard to like
keep keep my keep my [\h__\h] together right
now because there's so much
so much oh my god when i look at my
schedule i want to throw up
i want to throw up looking at my
schedule
oh well okay guys
i'll see you tomorrow thank you
i love you all you
thank you sorry for this
horrible stream sorry
um i'll go and go get
some stuff done um
bye bye see you guys super chats another
time
don't wait for it to wait for me because
i don't know if i will tweet
bye bye and in german we say
alvina's in
bye bye
[Music]
you