the rise of chiara de phoenix
once upon a time when there were no
humans yet on earth
and sightings of mythical creatures were
nothing
uncommon there was a young phoenix with
feathers
burning like the golden sun
this phoenix's name was
kiara over thousands of years
kiara would travel over the world
go on adventures like fighting giants
visiting the moon becoming an idol
and many other things however
every couple of hundred years chiara's
lifespan would come to an
end going up in flames but
soon rising from her own ashes again
every time she would rise she would be
reborn in another dimension
discovering completely new worlds
nowadays there are no more phoenixes
left on this earth
and in most other dimensions
[Music]
started feeling lonely and decided to
take human form for her next lifetime
and do what humans do fiera decided
she would come to this world and conquer
it in a different
new way today is that day
today kiara the phoenix is reborn
foreign