a
[Applause]
[Music]
the
[Applause]
[Music]
n
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n n
[Applause]
K oh my my shirt is a little
bit too high there we
go how you doing
guys how you doing
okay okay okay
okay I woke up good morning I'm still
half asleep
same no I wouldn't say I'm half asleep
but I'd love to be
sleeping
yeah hello although for once I'm I can't
I'm not even going to blame smovie that
much yeah she woke me up for food I care
for food but then
then it was just my brain that kept me
awake when I was trying to sleep again
but it's okay low energy stream no I
have a Red Bull watermelon flavor here
oh
smooy smooy just jumped up the table and
his walking behind the
monitors what why you what why why
what's wrong why are
you is this going to be our thing now oh
no she's leaving
no no what are you
doing
[Music]
baby I thought she was going to come
maybe she will maybe she will you always
welcome baby
girl she came she came running over hi
you can go behind the monitor if you
want just like yesterday
today yeah oh where she's going I think
is she no what are you
doing cute
baby she's so
soft me and junky
wonky we were
enjoying the nice weather
outside more than smoovie surprisingly
smoovie is kind of freaked out by the
wind chunkers also sometimes when the
wind is like too strong she's
like and she runs away it looks so funny
because their fur she's so she's
especially chunky wonky is like extra
furry and when when the wind blows
through her fur wow it looks it's it
looks
amazing okay
cat with bonus fur yeah so much fur oh
my God everywhere I look is fur I think
I should not drink the energy drink
yet but I'll pour myself some
water m n show wasn't smoothie I was
trying to be a gymnast yeah it was
smothie but nowadays movie is kind of
spooked the roles have changed the turns
have tabled we're about to head into
shedding
season you're right
[\h__\h]
oh on a scale of one to get the [\h__\h] all
out how bad is it for me to follow along
given that I haven't watched yet if you
want to that's no problem yesterday
basically uh what we did is we started
with
kidu uh we what did we
do
we I don't
know what did we do what did we do there
was a huge plot twist yesterday a yeah K
met with d who showed him his son in a
cabaret Club hanging with the girls but
kidu tried his best to not you know be
seen by him and then there was a fight
because the boy was hogging all the
girls and then he was knocked out and
then that's how he was like okay maybe I
didn't see K you because I got knocked
out H and then D was like okay I'll I'll
call you up again and you know uh see
you later and then
did something else happen with
Kio uh a tatara Tatar the vtuber we
didn't see I don't know if something
happened in between but we we watched a
video of Tatar the vtuber exposing us to
the whole world that kidu is still alive
which was supposed to be your secret and
then we
realize that she was yeah we we've been
filmed and also they show a video from
like the S Clan from the the dudes um
you know talking about us directly to
the
vtuber oh my God backstab no we have
been
bamboozled and then we switch over to
Ichiban again in Hawaii where uh we
finally managed to uh make way to
someone in an informant who knows where
our mommy and lannie are and uh the well
we have to give them some money but
that's okay they give it back to us
eventually but we go with a boat out in
the ocean and we find another boat that
has our mom and Lonnie and with that
boat we go back to yamay yam's
headquarters because now apparently
we're we bestes forever which was
destined since the beginning let's be
honest and we thought we were safe there
and and then we go to our own
headquarters with the help of
yamay and uh you know in our
headquarters there's this this guy who
looks pretty cool Hanah Hana hanaava Han
Hana uh Hana not
hanakawa and and then there's a the the
guy in the wheelchair right remember him
and the and the the Wong guy or Tong
what was his name Wong I
think and they were waiting for us and
we brought uh the mommy and the little
girl over and then we were getting ready
to fly to Japan and then
bam something happens because sheo said
this whole time she's been acting kind
of like sussy and Wiggly and and she
notices that AG is about to make a call
on his phone and she goes over and she's
like no you're not going to make a call
and he's like what the [\h__\h] is wrong
with you no
no battery
level and and then and then and then um
uh wait so uh and then and then and then
everybody's like what's going on and
then she's like actually I've been
deceiving you and he's been deceiving
you too but I'm being blackmailed so
it's okay that I deceived you um and
then it turns out he wasn't the really
in the wheelchair and the wheelchair was
alive and and and big shock big big
shock and and and then we realized oh my
God it's already too late because this
whole time he was in a zoom call with
those dudes the Y other yaku SIU and
what no savido actually no no not savido
he was in a zoom call with one of those
[\h__\h] and Dwight yeah Dwight that's
the one and uh and it's like oh [\h__\h]
it's too late they already know where
she is the mommy and Lonnie and so they
sent a whole crew over to knock the [\h__\h]
out of us and they steal Lani and they
kill uh Hana and they kill Wong uh and
it was really shocking they died so
suddenly and yeah it's just really
messed up because now the child is gone
that we worked so hard for to get a hold
of and mommy is
injured and Ichiban is like [\h__\h] I
failed you all and Chito say is like
[\h__\h] I failed you all too and yeah so
and now on the other side in Japan they
just had a call about this situation and
Kio is like okay so what we're going to
do is we're going to go to the Salo Clan
and talk to savido and ask him because
kidu doubts it no K not kid kidu
believes it after ichan says it but the
others are like what the [\h__\h] really do
we really trust him but Ichiban says no
savido really probably doesn't really
know what's going on oh yeah tat yeah
the vtuber is
chto and yeah uh so now we're like oh we
we we have to check with to sa to go to
Sao and see if he's maybe actually uh on
our
side what do you what do you mean van
were you not watching yesterday I mean
maybe you were only watching a part cuz
you had to go at the
end in that case that's understanding
your time zone
is bro was
sleeping okay yeah okay then I thought
you were listening and then still you
like
what okay okay no that makes a lot of
sense that's okay I left halfway that's
also okay she was blackmailed yeah I
think we don't know yet what she was
blackmailed with so that will be
interesting too um I think it will
be uh something very spicy not I mean
spicy as in just like something shocking
as well maybe something with a
family or so yeah uh I'm going to get a
longer USB C cable to
[Music]
oops I just uh automatically connected
my phone to the USBC cable instead of
the controller
there we
go
[Music]
automatic okay so uh I need to get up
early tomorrow so we're not going to go
until
midnight but let's see how far we get H
uh unfortunately this time I didn't have
time to do like grinding beforehand
I didn't do any grinding so we might
have to do on screen on stream
grinding no stream tomorrow yes stream I
I I want
to I want to that's the plan
probably 3 members
test
probably m
in the evening in
the uh before noon I need to do
something and then in the in the
evening in the even uhuh we have to go
there all
right in the
evening probably
stream so we're getting a 7 hour and a
half stream as opposed to an 8 Hour
stream now a little bit less
yes so I kind of have to
cook I have to I wonder how how long my
pork is
good oh my God
He's So
Co he's
really can't believe they're actually
joining the team too again
damn did I like him
[Music]
before
Oh ohes
[Music]
they're characters from a different game
that's a funny
com what it's happening too fast too
much information
but who uh who's takab
again uh
what every is the the the smooth uh skin
smooth like
smaller smaller compared to the other
one dude right and takab B was is that
one that was the one that was just
sitting next to him wait I I need to
look up pictures I just don't remember
the
faces um
Yak is
uh yeah yeah that's
[Music]
him
uh that face was unexpected to me
he's in jail he was sent to prison e
yeah yeah yeah because EA is the the new
one in town yeah yeah yeah yeah so so
takabe was there before and okay is his
position okay okay okay okay
okay fore
the way he talks is so [\h__\h] too
[Music]
I mean I'll be honest like fashion and
all that like not really like something
I I would like you know be interested in
orl but he's still really cool I don't
know okay it's the glasses it's the
glasses but other than that it's just
it's too flashy and too uh too much for
me you know but but still like wow he's
got something yeah no not not my type
but he's just um cool okay now my
time I mean
it I mean
[Music]
it not my time no no no no trust
me no for real though for real I mean
it no no clothing clothing wise way more
like what kidu is wearing
okay why are you flustered because
because what if you com combined
them well I mean oh
no you mean him wearing those clothes I
mean sure he would look great than
anything whatever oh my God
what what
hey oh yeah let's
go wait a
[Music]
second
for you don't
[Music]
get we need to
talk buying sunglasses
in
no
[Music]
for
foree Fore
so we're going to get
attacked
okay look how sensitive his skin
looks on the inside it's the skin of a
55y old
man would be
more I think
yeah yeah
yeah you think he want us to save him
rescue
him he wants to be
rescued
[Music]
foree ah
okay I mean is that not not what you
came here
for thank
you
[Music]
foree
for but now it's hard for me to make a
decision who to put in my
team
yeah too many people
to choose
from
number well I just gave number new
[Music]
weapons
no no I keep the team I just is this why
you guys meant I
shouldn't keep the same team for
now you did not just say that say
what he's left out wait why wait why is
he not coming
along let's take uh text you to S Clan
Warehouse I know how to get there
okay you know Z did just join up with us
again we sure you we want to jump in
like that maybe we do a little training
just to be safe probably a good idea in
the long
run yeah I mean she's literally breaking
the fourth wall right now I think she's
saying what you guys are trying to tell
me true yeah recently a building on the
construction here in ento CAU fire once
it was put out they basically left the
place to rot these days there's talk of
some strange Group H up inside
supposedly it's now their
Hideout a brand new gang un scene well
then I can't imagine you're just going
to ignore him huh exactly I want to
investigate figure out who they are and
get rid of them if need
be
right yeah what better way to sh up more
[Music]
skills not only that but it'll save me
much trouble too whenn win far as un
concerned okay west of carriage Highway
I've sent in one of my officers there
already he can fill us
in membership thank
you yeah I know there yeah because a new
member just joined so we have to
practice well we want to be prepared
sure
whatever yeah
uh uh don't we have drink lings
fore
foree
[Music]
e for
I don't really I don't really know how
he would be helping uh what what is he
even thinking
[Music]
of
foree she's over the moon
[Music]
fore
speee fore
I didn't see that before that they wore
that
[Music]
he's breaking NDA
break fore
[Music]
how does she keep her
cool when she's actually like such a fan
girl how does she do
it do we have one with you no okay then
you get a present here um
and a present for
you oh go 21 oh wait I to totally didn't
see
Satan Satan want some flowers
here ah so close to level
18 uh not sure about you dude wait a
freaking minute they took sat out of my
team ah never mind yeah yeah yeah what I
was thinking about when I said I gave
Namba new weapons is I gave Tommy new
weapons I gave this side of the team new
weapons recently so yeah I could change
up this team a little bit I guess did I
like fighting with z
did I even enjoy that was
that
number uh how do I
here I mean I'm definitely keeping Sony
M
numbero and the side quest only party
member well I mean that combination
isn't even possible so can't really take
it as a
reference I'll do maybe this combo for
now and I have to look at the cloes
again oh dear
[Music]
because we took it all off of
them need to
sell uh these shitty equipment things I
don't
need and we're switching some stuff
around uh
hat oh oh at least Dow came with his own
equipment
[Music]
Satan wearing itun shoes now
ooh that looks pretty nice MP
increase attack
increase uh
H the dirty
[Music]
Underpants
um items Namba Namba is not on the team
now he's not going to he's going to
sit
out mouth guard on anyone mouth guard
H sure you can have
it uh
hat uh yours
maybe
and your jacket
and your
shoes
and I know you're going to have the
fighter spelled
and the Dow he at least has all of this
nice and an Artisan's
saber does he have generally low HP no
right not
[Music]
necessarily but this is pretty epic I
would give it to Kido though I think
maybe
or I could do this which decreases HP P
by 100 plus this which increases HP by
oh oh big
brain just so that I get the highly
increased
exp is it
smart why because of the
XP it's just math
yeah how does my bucket list look
like
uh
uh-huh
uhuh
uhuh well I don't really have to do all
of these
right not a hold Okay so
does he even need more XP the
same don't question my
ways wait where can I can I
sell
uh my things in any store I forgot
let's
go for a pawn
shop oopsie
ah expensive as [\h__\h] these five
stars we got to work on Z's pawns pawn
shop pawn shop
Bon
pawn pawn
shop can I walk no too
far next
time these school girls by the way I saw
them when I was rocking around here off
stream I was like they they look so
sus when you tell ah I start from the
head wait that has nothing to do with
the T thing
right it was interrupted right
[Music]
kayaki is that wait what happened to my
thing do I have to activate it again
yeah it's the fish shaped
waffle with some cream in
side I like
inside wait now they didn't ask
me they didn't ask me this time what
little
[\h__\h] you are so
weird we're just so
weird damn
it you think he remembered
okay
oh what he ran away I see like a special
one that I could have maybe gotten
a good amount of money or so
from I wish that was a like a speed up
button so at least for the enemy's turns
I could speed
[Music]
through there's not right
there it
[Music]
is you need to be a high enough level
what I'm already at the end of the game
or do you mean speed through when when
I'm high like significantly higher than
the enemies when they're like
blue ah that does mean yeah yeah that's
not what I mean that's not what I mean I
just want to speed through
like speed up their
turns not skipping it or anything I just
want to speed it
up Auto Battle is kind of slow too I
still have to look at
a okay
[Music]
d
h
M let's see what he has in
store
[Music]
wow
yes if I ever get murdered I want to be
murdered by her
[Music]
me
too
true wait I know I I don't want to go
here I know I know I just want to pick
it up uh pwn
shop haven't been here in a long long
time selling
ah equipment specifically
oh I have to switch out his hat why is
he wearing this why is ky wearing the
madame's
visor oh
[\h__\h]
K it's about time we're selling
this just talking everything
I honestly don't care much about the am
amulets going to sell
them don't need to many
briefs what's
this a
weapon yo good
prices just going to sell the extra ones
and
that's it
[Music]
what's
this oh don't
care don't
care boom box boom box boom
box Chef we're not going to give anyone
Chef
right the business card is the attack
item for
hosts what's that going to look
like
Desperados use antique
coins get swiped no it's not even a
credit card it's a it's a business card
the one that you introduce yourself from
you're barely getting money that's okay
I just want to clean up my inventory I'm
not going to keep all this in my
inventory I don't need this old bat
anymore
right is this yam's
crowbar did he just leave it with
us is he going to need it
again
uh yeah the rest I don't
know you're just doing some spring
[Music]
and what are you sell uh buying selling
what are you
[Music]
selling yeah too low levels sorry thanks
for taking my
[\h__\h]
um called
medicine okay and now this thing where
you
train is here apparently and there's
also some nice conversations we can have
or so
many but I can't go over to this side of
the uh City yet I guess it's h this this
is is this where the factory is probably
I'm going to go the taxi I'm going to go
maybe actually maybe here oh or here I
want to get all these
conversations just want to get the bonds
up I can walk along the
river please do the that missions where
where are
they how do I do
them are the D missions the things that
you guys said oh please at least do this
for K you
maybe that's what you guys meant in the
beginning near survive they're at a bar
near the survive
bar okay can we do it after the fight
the dungeon
thingy oh my God the Bingo is near
I can't put my finger on what it is
exactly but this building doesn't seem
very Japanese to
me yeah looks more like something i' I'd
see overseas
instead Yumi would probably like this
sort of thing
though one time she said that the best
place to hold a wedding ceremony would
be Hawai huh H I'm sure there's better
places if only I could have made that
happen for her Hana must have pulled
some strings and sent me on a mission to
Hawai out of concern but I I should be
grateful thanks to him I finally got
some of the closure I needed by bringing
her ring with me I felt like I was
taking her to the place she'd always
dreamed of
myself
a I wonder if she'd be shocked by how
foolish I've been or maybe she'd be
pleased at least I would hope so it's
like his ex-wife is dead wife or
what a he brought her to
Hawaii
[Music]
man or were they they not they were not
wedded they were
engaged mother of his adoptive
daughter let's go manliest of manicures
okay I want to
go this and this and these okay maybe
just this one maybe just this way maybe
just
straight ow and we got a Satan Bond
conversation
wait what's in
here fancy
restaurant
Bingo or does the same thing whenever he
goes
[Music]
out I wouldn't say the same thing about
me
necessarily oh
expensive I
mean not too
bad but not something I would put my
money into right
now it to be
classy
scalpers s disappointed that the walk he
wanted sold out says he blames scalpers
they're definitely annoying us for sure
oh he likes to cook he wants to be a
cook is that his real Destiny should we
change his job to
cooking m' can I please go play soccer
uh-huh you broke your promise with me
the other day please I promise I'll be
better this time heartwarming sight that
is I wonder if how will grow up like
that har sa Haruka and UT's child and
something like a grandson to me H guess
that makes me a grandpa never thought
I'd be able to see the faces of my
grandchildren before I die if only Lady
Luck was on my side huh now I'm starting
to feel sorry for myself I do anything
to see how hard it those future and we
humans sure are
greedy
baby can we not
see
him s s
szy hello Mr Hero wait I want to go uh
which way
oh we can go this way
first oh wait no this will it
activate after after after first here
speed running the
bondy wind
sneakers
congratulations
yeah good for
you good for you
girl
bingo
bingo bingo I never played
for Bingo Ira or maybe once I'm a
grandma maybe that's what I'll be
playing W nice I didn't think there'd be
a cafe here I'd like to order a short
cake to go with some strong black coffee
that make for a per perfect PR K if you
want to order something you you can't
just think it you have to say
it the sweetness of the cake balances
out with the bitter bitterness of the
coffee two complimentary flavor profiles
but if we're talking about the best
combination ever I'd say it'd have to be
but that's such a random connection to
make daisan and
helicopters going from coffee and donuts
to daisan and
helicopters every time I get involved in
a crazy accident incident yeah maybe
also accident that is an almost always
shows up to bail me out of the
helicopter really is that what was this
like very GTA like
maybe that's why whenever I see daddy in
the chopper I double down
and guys I thought movie wasn't here I
just realized under the monitor I saw
some fluff she is here wa I'm going to
cry is this going to be
like normal from now on that she's going
to pay me company
again she's right there I can poke her
if I wanted to she was here the whole
time
is this the new Norm you know this makes
me really happy I mean I don't I was not
like
feeling sad or anything when they
started leaving my room when I first
came back to Austria after joining Hol
and at first they were clinky and stay
with me and then they started like
leaving the room whenever I
streamed but I was like yeah I mean sure
makes sense because I'm noisy and I talk
so much and I don't I don't tend to them
when I
stream you know so the past years
they've always left the room every time
I would stream and then they would come
into the room especially smoothie when I
would stop streaming but now she's here
what the
hell why why does she why does she want
to be with me so
badly she's accepted my career so
late oh man that's so sweet so maybe
I've just been conditioned to think that
way maybe maybe he's been conditioned to
think that she wants to leave the room
but now she has made up her mind and
changed it and she's like I want to be
with Mommy no matter
what oh oh I can buy them directly for
[Music]
someone
yummy smothie Bond leveled up yeah
she said she would start voice
training before going to karal
girl it's not so like
serious you don't have to take voice
lessons that's his name that's such a
cute
name
for probably really
[Music]
sweet for
save
them oh my
God what we've never seen the side of
her before even in the previous
foree
[Music]
oh apparently yeah this is a a person
that exists IRL and he's a
rapper but a really funny
one she's just not stopping this is just
fan service for him
taking M dungeon time okay rescue people
it's just like with the other dungeon
then
I don't want to fight I'm I'm
scared I
mean I
will oh
all
right it's like jumping into C
water I hesitate a little
bit stop moving guys thank
you keep on
missing not so
[Music]
hard
for
nice CH
board right where's the pun is that is
that supposed to be a
punting no
[Music]
yay guys
today you may already know but I fill
the
[Music]
table yesterday I made four chairs okay
I assembled them I don't mean I built it
from scratch obviously I assembled it
and today I assembl chair the table
[Music]
res
this using a power cable as a whip is
new I like the
idea and it really wasn't that difficult
building the table there's just like one
thing I was struggling with at the end
but I don't think it was
like me not understanding something or
so no it's just the screw didn't go in
properly where it should when I did the
same thing on the opposite side of the
table it worked just fine so I think it
was
some something wrong with like the screw
just not going in properly well besides
that I did everything correctly and it
was um
oh oh that's the end already is there no
one to rescue here
though anyway it was really satisfying
and and it was like Lego for
adults and I was like oh my God I can do
it
yeah once where they forgot the drill a
hole it for a chaos St they normally
don't forget to drill holes like I don't
think that's really what happens
usually but
maybe maybe sometimes maybe the I don't
know something's like a millimeter off
because the wood is maybe an open could
that be or just because I didn't screw
something strong enough on one side and
then it's not as tight as it should be
but then
again I don't think that was the
issue we enjoy building stuff as long as
it's something as like small and
unchallenging as uh like a chair and and
the
table I don't think I'd want to build
like a whole closet with drawers with
soft closing mechanism and [\h__\h] like
that um hell no no thank you I'll leave
that to other people thank
you that's where I start yeah maybe one
day I'll be making more intricate
things who
knows you got
[Music]
easy stuff yeah but even though it's
considered more on the easy side I was
still very proud because normally like
just because of the amount of things
that I
built I would normally um ask someone to
come over and help
me but this time I just you know gave it
a try did it all on my
own and it wasn't so hard actually
especially with the chairs it just got
easier
got to build myself a house yeah
probably not but uh that goes a little
bit too
far but I could build
myself a lake by a house not a house by
a
lake you know what I mean I could just
make a hole in the ground I can buy a
house and then just make the
lake all you got to do is make a hole on
the
ground and pour in some
water
genius free Lake for the
house obviously it's not that
simple obviously
did I miss something in the previous
level or is the first one just
empty trash let's
[Music]
go oh no
items I did go into every room I think
I'm sure
why do I always miss this
now and then and then and then when I
put the the the table
out and the chairs next to the table I
was like sitting there enjoying the
sunshine drinking a chill string
drinking and
then and then I showed chky wonky
how nice the chairs are because I was
sure she would like to lie on the chair
while it's tucked into the table I'm
sure she would have enjoyed that so I
brought her over and she loved it and
then because the table has
like the surface of it it has
like like holes so to
say space in between
like
the surface I don't know how to say
how it's not just one one yeah it has
gaps thank you the words gaps so I put
my finger in between the gaps and she
was attacking from underneath the table
and we were fighting and she was jumping
from one chair to another
chair she's having so much fun
[Music]
we were
playing with the chair and table chy
wonky so much
fun then I wanted to show smoovie that
it's fun too and I brought her out but
she was like no too windy I don't want
to even though Smo is always the the
more brain
[Music]
one oh she do be brave but wind no that
[\h__\h] scares
me that's
terrifying oh
[\h__\h] hey yo
huh yeah
honestly
cat the way their fur moves and and how
small they are it makes me sometimes
feel like they're they're light enough
to be just taken away by the wind even I
sometimes have to to like put a lot of
strength in my body when the wind is
really strong to stand up against
it then how must it be for little kitty
cat where is this what he says treasure
but where is this
treasure ah I didn't see that these are
really easy to
miss at least somebody says something
[Music]
something is that it is there something
on the other
side think
so I'm taking Windy what the
hell 100
discs and
he
di
this where did I I hate it when I find
the exit
first eat it
here oh I saw that
already this is
[Music]
connected okay and then there's this
this map is
big oh there's enemies there didn't I
already fight them and these are just
some
more ah wait he needs to be res
okay okay okay
okay yeah I have to explore everything
especially especially because as you can
see I need to rescue someone has no MP
M and needs some HP too
[Music]
so maybe just a light one is this for
now
Gucci always be
ex you're joking
right
[Music]
Gucci mhm the Twister guy looks strong
oh nice follow
up these follow-ups only happen because
of their bond right or is it because of
their position I think it's because of
their
bomb what
[Music]
maybe these
days Ming at night these past couple of
days we haven't been falling asleep um
cuddled up together that often anymore
because of where she decides to fall
asleep is in a difficult position for me
to
reach so maybe her sitting here while
I'm
working it's her way to make up for the
Lost hudle Time makes
sense I'll take
it dance
off 590 HP are you for real dude
[Music]
didn't he have full HP ho sh
can you
move that might just be
it maybe
maybe you see what I was doing there
carefully laying out my plan
and manipulating them to stand where I
want them
to you [\h__\h]
bastard I'm going to destroy you whoa
whoa
what more and more get up I can't barely
hit
you no it's already over
you could hear
[Music]
thear woo good good
timing
yeah e e oh [\h__\h] strong
this ends
[Music]
now 200 thanks oh he's wearing the
mask that we were talking about in the
bond
conversation uh the other fight we don't
have to do right there's not going to be
a person to rescue in there I don't
think so
not worth it
right feel now
yeah true
[Music]
um goodbye hot dog it was nice having
you
K the auto heal button doesn't work
when I'm with Kio I think is it because
I'm with Kio but I I already noticed it
doesn't work when I'm on the Kio
side
okay I have no healing skills he's
okay this way this way works too
and then I have control over what items
I use
up uh down here is also
something
[Music]
items oh just some servy data okay we
can buy stuff with that I think that
was I
hope now we can move on
to the next
floor
uh why must it be so in the middle of
the okay those cases are easy to miss
surprisingly huh I already have
that I don't need that
[Music]
mhm level
three wait
ah a man
it's a [\h__\h] creep in a
safe oh I like his get UPS though I like
it looks cute the drawing on the tummy
classic
okay I'm sure that belly makes a nice
wobble when I whip you with
my
cable the power of
[Music]
electricity yeah he has the that rainbow
move that's the one you mean
right I'm I'm aware it's there
[Music]
H
man and now he needs a grapple I don't
have a
grapple I cannot offer you grapple
how about a rap
rapid not rapid rapid crane
kick I was his
back countered
me
need you want me to change their
job maybe not hers I like her
but I guess the the class that she has
now is already ranked so high that I can
take the attack that I like with
me I suppose
[Music]
I I need goofy outfit that is so true
oh well an idol for some reason
yeah is that the only one I can choose
for
[Music]
healing I don't S no no don't waste her
potential he's a
fighter shouldn't be
[Music]
I the only move you use with this Jak
while don't worry
I I don't want to waste too much MP
that's why I go with the lower MP skills
the
time I don't think
I'm her
potential by doing that in boss fights I
I can go
more
flashy I don't want to fight you
guys oh what the [\h__\h]
Transcendence
trans
trans you
say what is
he what is
he what are you
[Music]
does he have he doesn't have a shield up
right it's just his defense is generally
high right
now let's
[Music]
see
um okay that's really not much
WoW but it's not going to be like this
forever so oh wait I thought this was a
only one person battle okay
[Music]
the dude in the back is it just
like don't I have like
one mayele lower the
defense that like one that ignores
everything
ignores the enemy's guard this one for
example but wait never mind that also
doesn't necessarily help much H doesn't
ignore his
defense oh there we go
finally pyro
b e ew ew e
[Music]
stiny he's so
cool so what's his
weakness nothing I
[Music]
have nothing I have really
okay did he get burnt no he didn't get
burnt he was supposed to get
burnt oh that's
big that was
big no
I was about to kill
him I wonder if he would have given me a
lot of
money if I'd have killed
him cuz also he was gold maybe that
indicates that he was like a big money
dropping enemy
[Music]
can I get them
all two of them
[Music]
nice
move yes take it harder take it
harder sh party sh yeah waste all those
bottles like you could make so much
money
from your workplace
waste them
all I
supported ah
[Music]
resist he almost God damn it
oh oh oh got some guards out of
that okay at least he even though he
stayed alive he couldn't do
[Music]
anything some he needs
healing the helicop speed speed
oh Mrs Ka P
Mor streaming rest
right CR old CR
times long long time
ago hey thank you for the raid damn R in
20 24 yeah I also didn't really expect
to see a come back from rast
anymore was rust a long time ago oh
yeah how you guys doing de what well I
mean yeah I'm getting kind of tired but
maybe I should drink my energy
drink without a
trace I have Red Bull watermelon
flavor and then also from Hello be
hell
fresh I got some free
samples of
uh do it no I had a
feeling of like a red B kind of
fun two bottles of that it's not bad but
it has
no caffeine
uh or anything like that [\h__\h] I should
have
healed it's just like the little Little
Red Bull
made little
sparkling orange juice but it tastes a
little
[Music]
bit
bitter yeah cuz they have I think they
have some blood or stuff in there too
not my favorite
I don't know if it's because it's new
and that's why they put it in there to
promote
it king of
[Music]
beast you would think because of the
brand that all the Red Bull things in
one way or another have caffeine in it
because also the the cola from Red Bull
that one's I drank it before it's pretty
good that one also has C
obviously oh he's weak against
guns I have found your weakness and I
will make full use of
[Music]
it I holy
[\h__\h] I had no idea they made stuff like
that there's Red Bull you don't
know it's
good but maybe cuz Red Bull is from
Austria maybe we get more variety than
other people for once in
products
maybe just like how
Japan makes so much oh [\h__\h] I should
have healed
Kitt so much Variety in in other
products where I'm like why don't we
have this in Austria
[Music]
what what how does he do
it how does he do it wait we need to do
something kind to debuff him with
something I could try to Blind him
[Music]
decreases
team yes K is very very big healing
effect can
confirm okay wait but
[Music]
please don't
miss thank
God can confirm
if oh
Sho please please please
please oh wait somehow I thought he had
a gun attack he doesn't
[Music]
whatever trry
again this time it
hits okay do you think will happen this
yeah it's Sunday today so I have to to
make the schedule especially cuz I want
to stream
tomorrow um so I'm thinking about it I I
I might do with
this there is a
chance that that look kind of crazy holy
[\h__\h] yeah the truck simulator K might
happen next week
already and you know we're going to have
the finale of
Yakuza as
well why is this floor so short I went
into every
room but okay I'm pretty sure I went
into every room
M you think he'll finish finish yosa
next weekend
yeah I think so maybe not one but two
more streams I don't
know either either way we're going to
finish
it don't doubt
my you guys have made the mistake before
of doubting that I could finish a
game
early and then you have regretted
it should I again I
don't two out of two cases by now it was
an enemy inside is there ever not an
enemy
inside do it
ah for
once wait is this the rescue thing
yeah need some
MP they might be a little bit
drunk for
great time was a charm mhm he better
never be coming
back flash grenade that I always miss
somehow
ooh
champag that's exactly how
[Music]
I like I jump with them
sometimes just because of the
intensity that I feel is
necessary okay I never use these fist
attacks I want to see them like once
essence of
sweeping let's see how this
works
whoa
okay that was
[Music]
okay she just like jumped into it and
landed dramatically On the
Floor
[Music]
Care don't worry we're going to kill you
either way you don't have to ask for it
[Music]
I was hoping the right one would get a
little bit more damage too but at least
something essence of sleeping brings out
a big room
[Music]
yes now there's only one left I didn't
see it I was no my eyes are like
tire so tired
man okay okay we weak against water
has no
water drowning you in pain how
[Music]
luxurious
strong it is so Red Bull
time it is so time
this is this whole thing even optional
or is you have to come here first you
have to right you have to do this whole
thing
first or could you skip it if you wanted
to it sounded like it was optional but
then looking at how the map made you go
there I guess it wasn't
it oh really no going do the whole thing
though I think I need
[Music]
it ah you can do one floor at least and
then leave to progress story oh okay
that's how it
is see in case you already leveled super
high
[Music]
[Applause]
not
[Music]
bad good opportunity to clean up all
my
items that I never use
no extra damage for real I press so
hard damn this dude is
chunky why so
chunky you have a license for that chunk
[Music]
I'm just going to shoot
him the last one is very
strong there's even stronger ones you
[Music]
say oh I got a
trophy oh
uh might need again some
MP okay they drink those coffees and
stuff I shall drink my Red Bull
wow and that's my first time I'm
drinking this
one actually really like
it not
bad uh what the [\h__\h]
what who put this musroom Farm in here
so
randomly
what it looks like
pretty normal mushrooms
too I would not want to eat those the
other day you know when I made um
something with mushrooms and I didn't
actually throw them away actually used
them to hopefully give the sauce some
flavor I don't know if it actually
worked but I so disgusted I I washed the
mushrooms I don't know what it was
champos I think it might have been
Champion or so but I washed them and I I
really don't like how when you make them
wet the
surface the skin gets like so it gets a
really weird texture
texture like what's up with
this and then it's so creepy like a it's
like the vegetable out of horror movies
like when you cut it open and then it's
like it has these Frills that are dark
and
disgusting it's just weird what a weird
vegetable oh
smoothie
to you're going to toilet or
so she's
hesitating what do you even know where
you want to
go she probably doesn't
know you can come back later if you
want mushrooms aren't veggies they're
fungus
well I think they're
[Music]
consider because they're they they just
you know
they because they
suck I don't like
them they're
[Music]
weird yeah the veggies in The Culinary
sense
yeah yeah yeah
yeah I would agree with that that makes
sense what did these called
people what are they
doing W what's wrong with me what's
wrong with
me we will never know
man more
please that's not even in the big
picture it like it feels strong it feels
like you're doing a lot but when you
look at the total damage like it's not
even that
good was it just me what do you think
why did you move over there it could
have been a perfect line
stop stop moving guys what's
wrong uh why did she move why did she
move to the
[Music]
side these dudes are very tanky I guess
yeah I guess
so true
I hate when they just like run further
to start the attack start the attack
where I'm telling you to start the
attack you you know I'm trying to get
the line perfectly aligned with as many
enemies as possible nobody responds
yeah
surprise need to build up
[Music]
momentum
momentum is a
lie just like this cult you're following
[Music]
what they they worship The Cult of a
chicken how do you know
that back up wait there you go
okay it is indeed a MAA nugget Messiah
matumoto
you weren't even lying
[Music]
what let's slice up that chicken filet
charie why was I making fun of this when
it's so similar to
ours Here Comes
Matsumoto profane
Revelation you little
[\h__\h] that's what he
said honestly not so far off really
the same same Vibe as you little
[Music]
[\h__\h] A come
on one HP and a dream
up see I can do it I can actually hit
the triangle at the right
[Music]
time pray for the chicken this s and
then beat them
up Soni remains unfaced she does not
like
chickens guys
what do we
do what do you
do no matter what I do what do you
do she hates you
let me go behind you no he's he's got
his eyes on me he won't let me
[Music]
go [\h__\h] I knew I I was like mentally
ready for it cuz I already know it's
like really fast The
Prompt but still I miss it even when I'm
ready ay
there break
[Music]
dance oh T follow
up break and relationship this can't go
on like this if she hates
[Music]
chicken but I have a feeling she lies
nice so I we were healed right before
that is that
[Music]
because wow wow wow wow
can I go back to heal
again oh wait I
can well three of them healed oh oh okay
it was that's it already
Okay next floor clap clap next
[Music]
floor
yes
on oh wait I wanted to give kill you a
new uh head equipment anyway I should
totally do that now before I
forget cuz he's still wearing the three
star madame's
risor here take this oh it's even it's
both a four star but this one's like
double the amount better and it Buffs
evasion nice
too bad the kfp hat isn't in the
game did you guys see like I've been
seeing a lot of really cute kfp merch
that's made by fans recently o ice cream
a cats
hi hi cats you guys
see like for example the bucket hat
looks really
cute somebody was selling a bucket hat
that's
like the the edges are
orange I think and the main part is
white and then there's a chicken
face and then there's this awesome ITA
bag that you guys
funded it looks so dope if I was a fan
of myself and not
myself biker boss
Mory Mor C you have a biker
brother what was I
[Music]
saying you
say in the shape and in the looks and
the designs of my
beautiful Shield it looks so awesome as
a bag and it has like these transparent
parts
put you know typical ether B stuff and
that one so goes F it's so cool like I
really want to steal your idea and
making my own merch but they would
probably I don't think they would even
make it as beautiful as yours I think
our merch Department Design This designs
some pretty cool
stuff in
general but I don't think if I had this
idea before I don't think they would
have come this close
to an amazing design as
yours I can just really sense the the
passion and the
love for me in your product
design it's just different when a fan
makes it I
think when a real fan makes
it it's so
good so I hope everybody who ordered one
will'll be happy with their bag and
bring it to every every Holo event
because that bag will be such a cool
Flex I
think be like damn is this official
merch or what and you'll be like
no but it's amazing isn't it yeah oh my
God so cool let's
go and in the preview the material also
looks really high quality ordered one
got to bring it to every yeah you should
I've been collecting pins and cards and
key from the back you're going to make
your first maybe I was thinking by the
way for a member stream maybe next week
next next week then to do a kada merch
collection AKA K
Shrine um
review where you guys send me pictures
of your collections of waa
merch and I look at what you got
maybe would you like me to do
this I feel like I would like to do
[Music]
this why not for everyone I know I do
weekly member
streams this is like particularly
something about my fans so why not I
want to do it as a member
stream there I have a lot to
unbox I just moved need to build my
shine ah hurry hurry hurry you have like
maybe two weeks I don't know one and a
half weeks go go go build
it I don't have anything to show but it
would be interesting to see what you
guys what you guys got yeah right it's
okay if you don't have your own shine or
whatever not
necessary but I think it will be fun to
look at what other people have collected
maybe some really old nostalgic stuff
maybe some fan-made
stuff nice
[Music]
block your entire room is
Shrine that happens when you lose
control no no no no no yes yes
yes I didn't hit the boss in the back
damn
it damn it
what let's try this one oh
oh when you get my FMA you're going to
put me with your F
figures you want to die step
up oh I don't even have to press
anything
wo oh
Bo
fish stinky fish feet
hot yeah 400 that's not even that good
for Dad cut scene but
okay okay come on crit give me a
crit yes I got it see that is 10 damage
less than what we just saw from
kidu but way less
[Music]
the fish was for
n Cy does the same amount of damage
forut
exactly and she doesn't make such a big
deal about it
either oh wait he actually does have
healing I didn't like have it in my
brain I could have just waited for his
turn he also can heal the others
actually H so much far we don't have
healing we actually do have
[Music]
healing wait a second
sh whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa triple oh I
only got one but I still did 420 damage
sick yeah right cuz he's a chef she
didn't yeah okay okay okay makes a lot
of
sense can we kill him can we do
it so close don't give him another
turn MVP
cycle
this can we make it until the end I mean
we weren't close to dying or anything
but
[Music]
that's all I
think oh just empty
room yeah they get really tanky
I might switch out s with
numble I don't know I don't know if it
makes that much of a difference I was
thinking we such actually no no she did
have good damage output
wait before I go let me try to find one
more group of enemies if there was
another one because I do need the
EXP as we
know
him uh this is the one that ran away at
the end right so we have to kill him
[Music]
faster yay yay
yay
eat potato chip
okay all the shitty food is
gone good bit of exp but yeah okay give
me those yummy yummy
exp we have
to do it fast but the first few rounds
we cannot really do much damage
so we can do kill his minions and also
maybe try to buff ourselves I don't
know let's get
started I was so close to killing him
last
time I would have just needed one more
turn I
think really unfortunate
[Music]
is there any way to break I think so at
least I don't have a way
[Music]
number
one number two this move is really nice
for cleaning up two like almost dead
enemies really quickly with
kidu oh he's done he's
done he's getting
serious oh no he's going to get both of
us [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah I don't know what to do about this
small one should
[Music]
I I'll try to take him
down what's your
weakness I don't think I have
anything I don't know what his weakness
is
Dragon
exension
okay that's a lot of
[Music]
MP I got two I got
two okay okay okay
okay okay got to go all
in son's deadliest series of CQC strikes
damaging an enemy with a high chance of
a critical hit power
extreme probably really
fast or do I have wait this this one I
don't have to do anything right right
right right right these ones the rainbow
ones have no input
this essence of Bone
Breaker how much damage are we talking B
27 is stream to you
um
nah that's um not worth
it compared to what damage we can do
otherwise should do this
again yeah maybe it's his
defense go for
it she doesn't
have uh oh no it's dead uh hers is a
Reviving
skill High chance of a critical
hit do
succeeding in the action BMP guarantees
the crial
hit I don't know if I should really go
for that one but I I'll
try she will break her is broken
[Music]
okay now it's
the what I barely had time I feel like
you ran away faster than before
ha
ha that sucks
nice just shaped I is not
bad all of this for What Turn Down for
What
man so disappointing
that tends to happen if a guy gets
kicked yeah maybe I shouldn't have
kicked him in his
balls that was like for him I was like
oh [\h__\h] that's it I need to go to the
hospital right [\h__\h]
now understandable I
guess shell shatter
okay after this dungeon I need to bring
over my
cookies from my
bedroom it's cookie
time the Cookie
Monster is going to be
Unleashed okay A Room of nothing
[Music]
I I I don't want to run away anywhere I
need to
find what cookies they are lifeit
cookies covered in chocolate milk
chocolate I don't get those very often
for
myself
but I felt like having them randomly
[Music]
I wonder so if it's
AOE in a situation like this cuz they're
weak to it but I choose the middle one
for the sake of the AOE making
sense uh do they get less damage then
when I then if when I if I would have
selected them you know what I
mean wonder I mean that's real science
maybe you I don't know yeah I mean
they're still weak to it but but do they
get more damage when they're the ones
that are selected that it's focused on
because like this they're like standing
on the edge of the whole AOE maybe they
get less damage because of
that you run the risk of not hitting
their side gun yeah cuz the AOE
sometimes W yeah that that is a existing
risk
yeah let's see I wonder if the primary
target gets more
[Music]
well they're already lower
on but they still get the weak from
they're already lower on HP so it's fine
oh one of them survived though
[Music]
dead end
no it's like a weird
Supermarket electric
geod I think that's
it unless I I'm missing something this
is actually like those rust abandoned
supermarkets in Rust ah I always miss
this
one actually this looks exactly like
we're in
Rust rest Bud oh in a little bit better
graphics actually not just a little bit
so many better graphics right wouldn't
you
agree I me rust isn't too bad either
though it's all
right nice
hair o
the Barb
Wire yeah it keeps on tangling in my
hair M the crown and the it's okay I
want to do them
all
because better than no
XP no
Satan why Satan why why why must you
hurt me like this it was supposed to be
free people free not
one why why does she do this to me does
she hate
[Music]
me does she hate me
what chill the [\h__\h]
out nice one hit
wow
okay y we already have 11 million
million again yes I think when I started
I had way less when I started
todaying good morning and then it's so
easy to spend all your money right away
again cuz equipment is so
[Music]
expensive make money spend money The
Circle of
Life make money spend money make more
money spend more
money make more more money spend more
and more
money become
depressed circle of
life brce and
repeat this is the last Flor
there probably not second to last
third to
last but that means there's healing
coming
soon my problem
is no I guess I still have enough stuff
[Music]
let's
go these fights can be a little bit
tough
so I expect it to be a long fight the
last one is the boss for so second to
last okay okay see that way okay ooh o
this one's kind of weird cuz it starts
before the enemy you choose and it also
continues
afterward so hopefully yeah this work
well he even went a step closer to his
buddy nice this is
perfect resist water I
see what about your
actually maybe a normal hit is good
know n no follow up please no yeah thank
you there we go that's what I was hoping
for guys today I I no yesterday
yesterday
I saw the lady in the
store forgot to tell
you I saw the
lady I noticed her before she noticed me
because she had a
line of
people uh at the what do you call
register
register so I I took my time picking out
my things and then I looked looked over
my shoulder and she was just looking
right at me and she waved with a big
smile an open mouth
smile like this she waved at me and I'm
like same waving back with big smile you
take my time and I line up and I
thankfully lined up in a way so that
nobody else was behind me
anymore and then we had some time to Chi
we talked
about uh I I told her that
on the day that her colleague told me
that she had a broken toe was the day
where I then proceeded to almost break
my own toe and then a week later or so I
almost broke my other foot
so we were joking about
how some for some reason I
was just trying to copy her trying to
maybe maybe maybe was trying to go for
the same pain as her you know share the
[Music]
pain she found it quite funny and she
asked me how you doing these things she
asked me that question like three times
you know when you ask someone how how
you how are you and then they answer and
then you're like okay so so so how are
you do you just forget you already asked
the same exact question and then you ask
it again and again she really really
wanted to know how I am I
guess so I'm like oh okay what she asked
me again what do I tell her
now what do I tell her now I told her
that I built some
furniture I told her about my broken
foot and I asked her about that calling
just to make sure you know that grumpy
calling I told her told you guys about I
felt like he was bringing down the mood
and always [\h__\h] on his
colleagues to to the
customers oh holy
[\h__\h] I asked if he quit or so and
apparently know he's just on a break oh
for [\h__\h] sake man it's going to be
back I thought I noticed like everything
was so much more brighter the atmosphere
was so much more better ever since he
was gone
you telling me he coming back oh
man oh
man wait actually s San come
closer oh wait is gradually oh [\h__\h] ah
yummy ah I thought it was right away ah
yummy ah yumy ah uh please go attack K
you if you
can he shouldn't be working he does good
they should future Endeavor him for the
sake of the
custom looks like you have to make sure
to brighten their day with her
presents yeah I I'll continue to
brighten her
day like she brightens
mine she that stupid colie was like
teasing me about
her probably told her because like she
was like oh I heard you were asking
about me and I'm like yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah that little
[\h__\h] I'm just going to hope that he
attacks kidu or don't he yeah I think he
does I think it's time for me to get
into
[Music]
baseball we need a like a like a cute
cheerful Pop
remix that song like a uplifting
cheerful version
can I take him down can I can I can I
can
I come on
yeah yeah was about to end go you
go he was
Unstoppable oh he also got a rainbow
skill okay
you said those are not so worth it huh
maybe this time I'll skip
them oh damn it where does it continue
ah down
here in the
[Music]
beginning empty room empty room
next room next
room where
oh place your
bets enemy or treasure what do you
think if you walk ah you mean if I don't
run treasure treasure enemy treasure oh
lot
ah it's like
50/50 I say
treasure not the biker
boss
[Music]
no
you what your weakness
I'm going to poison you a
try oh yeah I did
it where's my
earnings no just because you said it
right that just
means you're getting the enemy that's
what you asked for
[Music]
no misunderstanding
I was just asking you what you guys want
just giving you what you guys want
except for the ones who asked for a
treasure because that's not I can't give
you everything
guys you can't have it
all that's today's life
lesson good good poison damage
good not bad
actually we're getting every
[Music]
round this reduces accuracy
nice I'm hitting everything the way I
want
to we don't now that I've been watching
The
Witcher I I somehow happen to have a lot
of Cosplay friends so when I look
through their social media these
days in their stories or whatever I
notice way more they're all like
cosplaying The Witcher yesterday I was
going through my friend Social Media
stuff and then I saw I saw one uh Tris
cosplayer sir and then just the other
day I also saw uh one was uh cosplaying
Siri like uploading a picture of her
cosplaying
Siri like everybody's everybody's
cosplaying them H CH is rad yeah game or
TV show I'm not sure cuz all the all the
Siri cosplays I've been seeing look like
Siri as geralt where I thought it was
just gender bent geralt as you
know so uh I don't know if that's yeah
actually no I'm at the end of the whole
show so she never showed up like that so
it's probably from the
game probably from the game I never I
met the last episode of season 3 of The
Witcher and she still looks like the
usual Siri she doesn't look like geralt
yet she's getting there though I think
she's getting
[Music]
there so I must be from the
game she's a kid in the
show but I wonder because I mean it's
just kind of hard to make an actor grow
that much over like Seasons so I wonder
the time frame that the show
covers how much how long is that time
frame actually is it like 5 years is it
years I think it must be at least like
maybe 10
years from season 1 to season 3 for for
just her of course we're like jumping
over different
timelines not timelines but like yeah
you know what I
mean the time frame that is covered for
Geral is obviously much
longer maybe they will do a Bizarro
gimly film the actress make special
effects please
[Music]
don't they like
it when the books end even which one I
imagine she's a kid
though she
did but when she's like training I
wonder how old she's supposed to be when
she was like training to become a
Wier
stop and just generally when she like
like around
14 here's an adult at the end of the
book
interesting very
interesting
518 for such a low MP skill see that's
why I like using my low MP skills cuz
they can be really strong too I mean
yeah they just maybe had less defense
and less HP and whatever but still it's
definitely not a week one not a week
skill wait The Witcher free game you
guys said it plays after the show or
before the
show before didn't you
say all
right after
oh so can you kind of like feel the
aftermath though of series
existence just wait wait she shows up
obviously
right because all the cosplays I see of
her are from The Witcher maybe not from
The Witcher
free she's in the game oh oh okay
okay way after but she's still alive
maybe she has
gained eternal life as well or like I
mean she looks like she became a Witcher
in the end honestly you don't have to
tell me but she looks like she became a
Witcher just like geralt following his
wot footsteps so then I guess just like
The Witcher geralt she would be able to
live longer than she would normally
anyway m
you'll see her fate I'm so
[Music]
excited I'm actually so excited
water hey you
guys time to
bounce just don't spoil
me do we want to see tag team
I'm just going to go aim for him cuz he
looks the strongest and I am scared
we'll miss
him
not he's got a crazy billboard on
him it's like
a look at that picture
frame that's not wa don't spin with that
that's
dangerous very very dangerous oh he's
weak to
fire yeah burn
[Music]
burn not that way I wish you could
control which way he froze them in the
end
or is that like always the opposite
direction from where you're facing when
you attack them it
didn't it felt like that before to me
but not
always this time was also not
opposite anyway we killed
him resist
and I
missed it should be in the direction in
which you're
facing
stop oh he's weak against like almost
every element I
think
invulnerable I just I just get it now
this way
no this
way I mean I
missed is a walking
blender is yep he really is weak against
everything
so strong no he's getting healed no I
should have oh [\h__\h] I should killed that
dude guys why' you not warn
me yeah he got some collateral
damage over a th000 heal yo oh all my
work for nothing
but let's try to lower his attack
[Music]
again this time it
worked nice and he's got a cold from
before
so a
[Music]
man readying an
attack what am I going to do all my
attacks are us
[Music]
up oh wait actually not so bad I thought
it would do way less
damage he's a
[Music]
turtle it isn't the amazing
fun oh wait that's crazy damage what the
hell
POS it comes out of hiding didn't do
much for you in the first
place is that all you can
do
[Music]
for
spee foreign
[Music]
sweep does attacking from the side do
anything no I think generally the
generally the only like effect in terms
of position is when someone's on the
ground or when when you're attacking
them from the
back correct me if I'm wrong
[Music]
no thanks for the membership renal damn
it
Miss need some
[Music]
here it has high Attack
Base someon I mean yeah we could um even
use Al weapons if we do
that then I don't have to use so much
money instead
doing great thank you I can't believe
we're we're almost free hours in and I'm
still in the doing the first thing that
we're doing today the
dungeon
o I didn't have to do the whole thing
but I think we all agree we need
it we need to grind a little bit and
this is our our way of grinding
[Music]
a tiny tiny little
bit oh yeah
nice think future battle e
here I hope so I hope we'll have an
effect from this and hopefully we don't
have to go into the dungeon again for
more
grinding I hope this is possibly all the
grinding I'll have to do until the end
wouldn't that be
[Music]
great otherwise I'll do more grinding
off screen until next
time uh so We rescued the person just
now right so I'm not going to go into
that room that one's
empty that's also empty
[Music]
you think I'll need to grind even more
oh
man well the layout of this map
is very straightforward
I'm using so many
[Music]
items we'll see we'll see
rafan rafian are on the uprise again now
that the dougles are seemingly back
Ruffians are on the
loose Who let that dog out who who who
[Music]
who
wow Lu knocker
indeed oh that's it already for this
level I skipped one fight
whatever combat sword four star probably
don't need
it do we get healing now
yes oh
finally finally finally the
[Music]
finale ah uh
yes can't be so
bad
right so
who is it what
freak
cigarette
cigarette and some Massacre mascots
nicotine Lich and Massacre
mascots well this Arena feels
familiar know why it looks like the old
arena we were
in he
he like
whatever oh
no nice my guards are on point
today we got to sweep
those H cigarett butd away or whatever
you call
when they're on the ground like trash
sweep
sweep if only Kio could be the mid class
but I'm guessing he can't be can you
guys stop that that is really
strong kind of mean even when I block it
it's so strong oh they're weak to water
please walk over
no then I'd rather go over here
then I get a little bit of an
AOE yeah
nice nice follow up I love
you girl Power Girl Power Girl BS girl
power he smokes out his
hour why did you poison your
ally
why what
did that what positive thing did that do
for
him but why
[Music]
H get out of there bubonic smoke he
smokes out his ally he's not even
gaining anything from that is
he do we have
someone H is a metaphor for smoking as
it damages everyone regardless of
intention a health hazard for everybody
involved can you guys stay away from the
dude who already has cancer
though the
[\h__\h] yeah they kind of became like
zombies
him not yet though he stayed away stayed
in
safety oh he's right for his thing no no
no no not the
r yeah home run
girl you can finish
it not like that you would have had to
use a
skill is it random would he like ever go
for us too or and we're just lucky right
now or does he always go for his allies
to make a
point oh he's
next he's just finish him nor
random
then random within really random I guess
we're
lucky sat almost died
[Music]
nice
400 uhoh oh oh [\h__\h] I should have heing
a t
on okay it's like a debuff so no damage
for
now just got to heal
[Music]
her I just have to make use of the
perfect
position that son he was in
m h what do I
[Music]
do use K should I do I have
to is she going to die otherwise next
turn I have to use this
turn I think I have
to uh what
is she
poisoned we can't just heal 50 we need
to heal way more
anyway that's not even that much
no
okay
y Yamada smoking is not good for
you I mean you are a cigarette literally
but still
[Music]
let boost my agility little bit a little
bit more oh wa there was some lag for a
moment it threw me
up but I still got the
buff we got R to stop but did she
actually stop though like for real for
real
forever if as if it was that simple
joins Holo stops her chain smoking
Behavior no
way like did she really
do I'll have to meet her in person to
find out I'll be able to tell by her
smell I have a very sensitive nose
nobody wanted to follow
up yeah if you're not a smoker you can
tell
easily please don't attack up please
don't attack them oh okay
[Music]
oo I blocked it
though well I'm running out of MP
[Music]
so I'll just ra it a bit more and then
maybe
somebody else can heal my
[Music]
mp you smell ashy because of a bonfire
yesterday take a
shower ashy little [\h__\h] you smoked
chicken you don't get rid of that smell
when I eat you up cuz you smell like a
smoked grilled chicken so tasty M that
Aroma can't get enough of
it that's Grill
[Music]
Aroma I mean he's almost dead I'm not
going to heal our impo
nah instead we'll do this send st's
enemies out for lunch with a high chance
of inflicting burn if they
survive what how what how does this work
what it better be good it's
uh cooking a cigarette
that's not going to turn out so yummy
but okay
oh wait he turned
[Music]
black we're
silverish s
me who straight into the
pl no please no I just have the veggies
the P Choy please thank you what how
much was that that didn't look like that
much
yummy thanks that would there's surely
other enemies where this makes more
sense 350
only I say only but it's probably
plenty don't
die don't
get tools
in o is almost
dead finish
it down we
go the cigarette
has burnt too long it
has become nothing
vaporized quit smoking
everybody if you talk with the Bal again
he'll give you a reward for the lost
people y survival
Foods o o wasn't that five
stars I did it the last guy was one of
their big play well done I heard there's
an even strong enemy for
done thank you who
ana
oops what wait I want to go back in yo
that's probably enough training no no no
I have to go back inside d
d
oh take me
in Ana has come to see
me
wow dragon's Dragon God's amulet uh for
the dragon of Doon old Amulet the purply
channels blessing okay what does it
do what does it actually do
also
yeah just so we
know the these things are
here I
happy he looks good as a chef
change of scene
guys
cute
no we could make her a kunoichi as well
but no no no no it it yeah probably we
should do Idol I don't even think I made
her an idol in the previous game did I
because I don't remember having this
outfit on
her cute I like the red
one very strong
here I did oh is this a new outfit
then I don't remember this
outfit I was like isn't she already a
you know that's Cheetos said they're
like very similar
Vibes um but should I keep her the
same I I feel like she might even do a
good job as a koni as
well cute answerer I made son
my and attack cres enemies to paste but
then if I do this you guys are like just
L horny in my
chat maybe I just keep the OG outfit no
no I can't give her this outfit
constantly
no I don't like it on her anyway I don't
even think the outfit looks
good m
not about the outfit though this one's
so
cute actually with her pink hair she
would look so cute in this outfit but
man we'll try it just because we just
didn't have a chance to try this one out
yet but I don't even like any of the
colors I'll
give and for
you we should give him chef
right cuz he likes to
cook but is he done more of a ma Mage
class
Chef let him
cook I think this one looks the
best let him cook that is a
mage look at
him okay but what about yeah skill
inheritance I'll take these with me and
these with
me which else would be
good I don't know I didn't use the other
ones that often but game master Maybe
maybe I don't know
grapple not true a they're both
grapple yeah one lower one Higher
MP
um one of the champagne
skills the thing is they work in a
different line like this is the the
triangle one so I'm not sure which one's
better for General use maybe the
stronger
one could bring the fire skill depends
on what other skills she gets but I I
guess I'll bring the fire one maybe for
now okay
okay and then for you
her boosting
agility skill might be useful I don't
know the I like the whip a lot
too I like a lot of her
skills she even has a stronger Whip too
but it's really a lot of
MP the electric one for
sure and then I wonder does she have any
gun or knife skills in her other
in the in the current class that I gave
[Music]
her she does or both of
them oopsie uh yeah Grenade might be
good too
he can't bring
much the the cooking class you guys said
has no healing right but we already have
our Idol healer so I don't think he
needs to bring any healing
skill reduces accuracy lowers
attack boost his own defense May boost
his own attack
lower their
defense reduces their accuracy I don't
know they're all
[Music]
okay I'll bring this
one okay
why did they not just heal me
automatically when I left Place
huh okay let's do the freaking
story It
[Music]
Go ah wait
equipment well they get they get like a
basic one first right oh wait he
automatically equipped the Megalodon
sword nice she has this cute magic girl
stick
[Music]
cute temptress
whip does she neat agility
still actually
class exp would be great but I don't
think I have anything
good hey the Whisk
oh n right he's not wearing anything cuz
he's not really
partaking uh I think I need to
go make some stuff
consider my party's arch
support what what are you what are you
trying to say
what what does that
mean I think I understand what we
talking about
Oli thank you for the way
thank you I appreciate it ooh two raids
today from Hol
members I'm
honored let's go everybody have you been
streaming Chima my new
[Music]
song
please stream Chimera on Spotify Amazon
music Apple music Etc and of course
YouTube every single day thank you ollie
you're so sweet you're the best I love
you I love
you taking the crown now you're calling
me King you going to hear him all
sing oh did you guys see
coefficient so coefficient um um bought
my
cosplay and then he did like a wheelie
thing so he didn't like write to me on
Twitter on out of his own will uh it was
kind of decided by a
wheel and then he wrote to me and asked
what he should do and I saw it when I
woke up today and I was
like
oh well the first thing I can think of
is the Chima dance but I I felt really
bad because like I don't think he has
any dancing experience really properly
so for people who don't have dancing
experience it might be a little bit
difficult to learn a dance like that but
it's not even honestly the chor is it's
not even so bad it's not even it's not
even that
difficult can you retweet his tweet
which one the one he tweeted at me
asking what to do I don't think there's
a need for it but yeah um now it seems
like like hisz reaction was so
funny it was a reaction to me asking him
to do that while apologizing I'm like
I'm sorry you don't have to do it
because I feel really
bad um I already feel like he's going to
start hating me for kind of pushing him
into this whole thing I was kind of the
one that was like M you should cosplay
me and my default
outfit for a guy to wear is kind
of
rough big tummy
Expos big fire
Expos everything exposed it's like a big
expose it's just uh rough so it's not it
might be very uh
embarrassing um so yeah I hope I hope
he's not mad at me for put pushing him
even further
down
yeah but uh he's he's taking the
hopefully he's taking it like an
Entertainer and thinking well all for
the content it's all for the
content now good luck with the dance
challenge it doesn't have to be perfect
just uh try to try your
best I would
say really doesn't have to be perfect
looking forward to
it coefficients
journey
of w becoming as
Wawa what if Cod Dan better than you now
[\h__\h]
way
try give it a try challenge me dance off
it
is got to make use of my ex
suit let him cook he's going to surf I
hope he will surf
me all the CU and he
has in himself okay so
um the thing that we would
make for our Chef is
what we have the
Whisk Would we not be able to
obtain a wooden spatula and make this
damn that's a lot of rainbow geod though
I don't know is it worth should we make
uh the Armament
spatula I would need wait I don't know
where I would even get beautiful
seashells maybe I didn't phrase it so
well buy a five star weapon or six star
if we can afford no no no no oh no I
don't I don't know I mean yeah I gained
a lot of money now but I would have to
do that for
everybody otherwise you're going to be
like wow why are you not buying big
items for us
too we can just make this but then okay
write it on the shopping list oh by the
beach is it hard to get the beautiful
seash shells though I I can imagine
they're a bit more difficult okay ride
it down wooden
spatula and four beautiful seashells
put it on the shopping
list this is what we're going to do now
um for
her whip of
disappointment uh it would even be the
whing Whip or the burning Rose but damn
this one also
needs beautiful
seashells and three more lava
geod and a for new whip I wonder if we
can get all these
things in my opinion let's see what next
requirements we'll need a good equipment
eventually oh yeah right we're not even
we couldn't even get the shells cuz
we're not in
Hawaii oh never mind then
he's
fine wait what about
SAT but is there no idle weapon to make
oh why
not why
not
why you think they'll ask for five stars
okay
okay cuz I don't have an idol ah so
because I don't have anything to craft
it from it's not going to show me what
really
what that's why you think that's
weird
H okay if we're not crafting
anything um
no
no I was walking and he looked at me
anyway with a mean
face I'm actually just trying to get
over here you can buy a good item just
to focus on your
healing rather than attacking
no still to think that the former Tojo
Clan headquarters is now the S Clan's
Tokyo branch
as a supporter of the great Sol
dissolution I might not have any right
to say this but it pains me to realize
that the too Clan is no more H they were
the top of the under the world society
would be better off without the Yakuza
this much I
know Dao must have struggled with this
decision whenever I think of his
suffering the loneliness I feel seems
trivial in comparison d v and the others
made the right decision I want to be
proud to say that that's why I have to
do whatever I can to help
okay well then we can
um go do some work oh we have to go to
the
station both sides or is it like
either a store for some weapons right
next to you it's a shop yeah yeah I know
that shop yeah I was thinking they might
have something but yeah I guess we'll
just wait to see if the game wants me to
get five star
weapons also I need to shop I need to go
to the
supermarket okay I can I can handle a
little bit longer
prob no no no don't don't don't
don't I just want
there we
go doesn't
work level 34 imp patience o okay let's
look at these new
attacks tough love heel stomp candle
Rush some assault leg wow wow wow
he set the
mood it's good for
[Music]
me oh there's one behind us too
wait there's a Red Bull advertisement
right there wait that was so disected wa
there's actual like little these things
are like fake and
[\h__\h] wait that red pool advertisement
right next to me is so
[Music]
real e just so happen I have a red bu
right next to me too on my right side
just like this advertisement is on my
right
side wow
it says get some energy from a Red Bull
then for one uh station you might be
able to just run
instead putting this at a train station
is keeping like motivating people to not
take the train is that okay
Sashimi slice pepper mil
blow medium
well I love these attack
names
impatient
oh I didn't
realize patients are often impatient
aren't they
huh oh my God they're impatient
[Music]
stations I wonder what the pun is in
Japanese
who did both die you both died even
though the other one was just the impact
from him FL
Uber advertisement in the back let's
go
wow how do I kill
[Music]
you maybe a normal
step I missed that was
weak onto the streets we go
episode on U wait how how old is it I
probably saw like every
episode in the
past four or five
years unless it's like from yesterday or
so but I don't think there was a new one
I would have seen it
already oh get going game doesn't tell
me
to do anything with my
equipment that was 11
[Music]
levels we have a lot of
I forgot to take
my I forgot such weapon what what do you
mean she has no weapon at all no she has
a weapon she has the basic weapon what
do you mean I forgot I didn't have a
plan on doing anything
the most basic
weapon you mean like not even how many
stars do you
have that's why she did so little
damage
well that's that's why I wanted to
upgrade everything
[Music]
maybe
you want to move no not
there
no
yeah sexy
ow no wake up I need
you why are they all going for
her see it's her sexy outfit everybody
can't take her eyes off of her damn
it look
away oh there
we not all of them but a lot of them
yeah the damage is kind of
sad yeah
but he's
okay
ow she'll just focus on healing
FS an enemy greatly decreasing a random
stat if the enemy was
leeding tenderize an enemy and season
them to
Perfection
um this job promotes a
lifestyle that you really don't want to
promote out there to the
world this is very
cannibalistic non-stick coating ensures
their teeth will slide right off you
mean you mean the teeth of the humans
you're cooking oh how
convenient wielding the most expertly
crafted Yanagi knives damage an enemy
have a high chance of making them
pleased
[Music]
you
ble
alive something that doesn't happen in
KF would love to
what what wait I think
[Music]
you think I can do
it nah damn
it
fu fu f f f f f [\h__\h] the other enemy I
could have
done
ow what do you think can I do this no I
just heal I'm going to heal um
are they
close oh wait it looks like this to oh
they're close to each
[Music]
other yeah thanks
whatever now get out of here with your
cutesy dress and your cutesy idle stick
I was hoping for that did you see what I
just did with a normal attack I got some
AOE to kill
both she did yeah I'm a tactician you
know where I got that from I learned it
all in Age of Vampires
yeah oo interesting two birds with one
[Music]
stone oh
sexy I love it double
kill
oh wow two
weaknesses
covered by one
dude can you do
it little Stone all
right oh but wait there's
more they are taking stretching exercise
very
seriously want to move a little bit
closer to your
friend so funny that you can kind of
kind of manipulate them but no he
doesn't want go there oh but oh CH he
did move once I stopped bothering
him I am controlling his mind and he
doesn't even know it he thinks that was
his own choice but no no
no I play you like a
[Music]
puppet that weapon hits really hard that
attack on stage are throw when once they
throw it I'm going to heal
K where is he
[Music]
there mm AI manipulation I like that you
can do it cuz
like they only move a little bit but it
can often make a big
impact he's weak to fire who would have
thought cannibalism
[Music]
B AB really [\h__\h] up what I just
say 600 gun
you know that Melody that song
right from
D it changed the lyrics
too very very
tasty nice
block he's I didn't change aane uh he
does sing very tasty about
something no wait he doesn't does he no
he sings to
dauki normally not oi so almost complete
original
[Music]
song you don't care about fire oh he
does
though
ohal you
please oh he's he's freaked out
oh 100 burning
damage sea is
fine
nice sea it may be in the middle of the
night for you but you're
winning how's it feel
[Music]
extra damage to enemies if a status
element the more elements the more
damage he does have a status element
[\h__\h] English language
mukashi
yeah I know Wawa's Tang is powerful and
it lags in an entire
country truer words have never been
spoken ah he could have died why did you
not
die wait there was a ah I didn't expect
another hit that's why I didn't block
but FY I blocked it all everything that
I expected oh hly
macaroni aome close to break
this almost
[Music]
perfect me with my new kitchen knives
they're really
awesome take
cutting
those cutting those those those herbs I
told you already but it feels so good
also cutting for tomatoes M man it's
just
amazing really good worth I need to buy
like a what's it called Wet Wet
Stone Wet Stone con
Shadow
slash oh I see I
see Shear you
got oh oh oh oh there oh embarrassing
what do you mean you bought chicken Shar
what does that
mean chicken have to be shared like
sheep yeah I need something to sharpen
my
whip service lip
service no not caramic ones but I might
still end up using the caramic ones
together with the new ones um because
the keramic ones the good thing about
them is they just don't have a
reflection H cuz they are pastel colored
um but I can't sharpen them again cuz
they're caramic and or
ceramic and and uh yeah shut up and but
I I looked at the reflection of the new
ones there is like some reflection going
on there but it's like like it's just a
general vague reflection of something
some object but it's not really like you
can't see anything in particular I would
say yeah but that's why generally those
keramic knives are better okay
I might
stay with keramic
cuz in German we
say she's really into kicking these days
[Music]
so can I go back now and get a weapon
or
[Music]
oh could you not have told them to
stop nobody
wins I had to like waste my time and my
energy to fight
right and your Fighters now can't do
their
work what was the point I know you said
you can't stop them because you know
whatever no no you could have totally
stopped them what the [\h__\h] so
unnecessary nobody
wins they're not going to be able to
[Music]
work bargain
barrel all
this on
shoot looks so
good for
[Music]
pron huh ironic
H well if you want to
see poetic
way
true do you mean that literally
though yeah he thinks that's
oh
only as long as I don't have to
[Music]
fight he's in fighting stance
a few more than
four good
everybody Welcome to The Fight Factory
we do talk about the fight factory oh oh
duck duck goose oh
yeah weapons for
[Music]
everybody as if he had all that in his
Kaku soundtrack
guys hear it
well so far
away that could hit Free
People a we didn't get healed e I'm on
low MP
well will be handling these
things I think this will be a longer
fight so it might be worth healing those
EMP there you
go she's just a support character
now good and see once again they
immedately go for
who my sexy
lady an eye from
her
[Music]
okay and to Mak him
bleed and he does
bleed nice extra damage and Status
ailment should be helpful uh any
weaknesses ahuh he's weak to water are
you weak to fire not
necessarily okay but uh you know what
this means a okay they're not all the
same o OOTS oh
wow I'm going to turn this
up just a little bit because the sfx
will be
louder oh
oo greatly if they're bleeding that is
actually great collaboration between him
and our
Chef cuz like right now this dude's weak
to water and he's
bleeding oh
my a I would have almost expected a kill
but 700 damage is
sick okay
expect they'll be hard to take down in
general so
ow tyrant's
displeasure
okay switches to dagger ah ah he gets to
use all those weapons that he picked up
in the cut
scene Hotline Miami music was freaking
dope she's pretty low on HP already
[Music]
but I don't know if I should focus
everybody on a different enemy ideally
we want to take one down
now the bleeding one perhaps
wow okay healing
[Music]
time that's will be good I'm going to
run over two I'm going to get healing to
for
sat uh Z should be
okay
oh considering how close close you are
and how directly into my face you shoot
that really doesn't do much
damage okay now anybody we to fire
ah should I do it or should I do a
different one to give him a
debuff I might leave him
burn okay no burning okay
absolutely fine with that Arrow or
whatever it is in my
face weak
not well I'll do a shadow slash then
although I mean can't hurt to do a
little damage the ones on the side
line yeah even even though he resists
200 f is not something to pass out on oh
vile skin col wo whoo
wo oh wowo
[Applause]
[Music]
sick oh even that heal is kind of weak
even though it's a single Target
heal yeah it's honestly not not
necessary to have a good weapon for her
right now because yeah as a as a
dedicated healer is actually exactly
what we need her for right now I don't
know if normally we would need her if we
would want her to attack anything anyone
at all to be
honest what do mean he does he change
his things depending on the weapon he
carries it seems like
it nice
it's like a
stance what what what how do you block
all of
[Music]
these resists the knife so
o what funny attack I didn't expect that
that was the first time I used it Dam
it grapp it's time for a
grapp do I have a different grapple too
yeah I'll use this actually or no maybe
[Music]
Overkill yeah this was fine was enough
he resisted the resisted the weapon but
it was too
strong
okay
um wait what no no no no
uh uh I think I'm going to do T team she
still has the same healing skill right
yeah kind feel
her I mean it's mostly just necessary
from her for the girls
but
needing it's okay I it's still pretty
chill I have it all under
control
although
saos HP maybe just because I didn't work
much on him yet
but he's like a freaking Ellen ring boss
holy [\h__\h] that HP bar is a little bit
too long for my
taste oh
yeah
okay pretty much only Sav next at left
um
kind of don't want to I I'll try to get
him down with S joh I hope that will be
enough and focus on you
now making him bleed would be nice or
blind great they cre in a random St of
that enemy was bleeding moving bleed we
need to make him bleed
oh you know what let's do this one
now oh nice okay we lowered their attack
and it was pretty good
damage you see what time it
is this is the time of all times
I kind of want to put one one hit on the
other
dude so I can kill him okay nice nice
nice nice nice nice then I don't have to
waste sat turn big
brain woohoo
okay t t that's a lot 143 for burning
damage
girl recovers you're
I wish it would also remove
El I really need to do
this so
[Music]
lame or
uh do I not have a cure burn
oh and 50 I mean should I do this yeah
an
item why not she's not that low on
HP we want to get rid of the burn 100
plus oh damage is not nice to lose each
round especially when her own heal isn't
even that strong dagger
time what's your weakness now fire okay
wonderful wonderful I'm so happy about
this let me show you how my heart burns
for
you not that
strong okay
more more
[Music]
fire phoenix
fire it's okay it's okay he has high
defense more fire I need to use this
weakness cuz everybody has a fire attack
Amazing Just when I need
it what kind of attack was this again o
dages enemies greatly if the action from
is successful okay heavy
attack oh this one easy
thousand oh he probably learned this
lesson never
oh how did I know he's never going to
switch to daggers ever again after
this I pressed that one really fast
didn't I honestly I kind of pressed by
accident I was lucky it was Circle
they really don't give you that much
time for these
PRS why are you fighting me sa
why
why oh he's fighting the fists
now no that
so what's your weakness
then doesn't matter I'm going
to maybe do a little bit of uh I was
thinking of group healing too but maybe
it's a bit uh too early and I can maybe
do a de buff Charming an enemy laring
their
attacking their resist electricity very
probably going to give them a
cold I think I'll try
this I like Charming a boss is nearly
impossible
though I want the attack
de
ah but okay see that's all I wanted I
didn't care about the charm I did think
that would not work out
anyway I you still wait to fire guys oh
big mistake sa big mistake big mistake
you should have switched to one of those
other weapons not to your face oh salido
you poor poor baby
boy the only problem would be if I don't
have enough MP with Kido how much how
much MP was that attack surely not like
50 right under 50 right
right I hope
so oh he's next he might switch weapons
next before it's K's turn
I hope
not I hope he gives me one more
turn oh okay he's not switching is he no
he's
switching
oh okay I mean was that 50% special
attack like he only did that cuz he was
at 50% cuz then okay okay
okay uh what's it
now
uh I don't whatever it is in this stance
I don't have
it
yeah I need a a big heal and Satan is
not going to able to do all of that I
think I maybe even it's should I maybe
even call
someone this is like upward 100 HP 100
base damage pretty weak at this point in
time I think I need to help with the
healing
do I have what do I have that works for
all people I think I have an MP heal for
[Music]
everybody iup
it ah uh P to the entire
party pretty
good I might do this and then try to
heal uh HP with
saan it should be
okay
yeah although I should have walked over
closer with K [\h__\h] ah now they are so
scar oh actually fine everybody's coming
closer everybody's coming closer as if
they knew ah kind of far no no
oh wait is she how far is she H it's
okay okay I
think
okay so it's probably electricity
right w why don't I have this with
electric I don't have a good electric
one I only have the 150 one
which sometimes is then more than 150
but still kind of low I don't know
should I use that N I
think yeah let me put out my rocket
uh even with without
weakness only have
one okay but it would be even better
when to use this when he's on fire we
let's wait guys guys think what if he
goes back to fire weakness I should has
it down that
[Music]
potential I have to lower the attack
also 300 is really
[Music]
good so is it electric yes it
is all right he's next by the way but I
should be able to withstand whatever
he's got in
store sick at least I'm nailing most of
my
prompts that was
crazy okay uh wait you did you is this
so
electricity I think so yeah yeah it is
um
he's next again after
[Music]
this hoping he won't go for the
girls at least not for son I don't think
he will
I need
[Music]
to yeah 482 oh oh good good good good
yeah he's probally going
for oh dagger time which means rocket
launcher time but holy
[\h__\h] oh holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] that's
fine that's
fine H let me think who would I want to
use the rocket launcher with maybe
him po the
872 that was big that was
me good stuff good
stuff uhoh yeah it was that right
decision to heal
[Music]
her yeah he's got his eyes wait let's
not attack with her she's
weak more heal more heal just heal
forever heal every freaking turn we need
it we can't keep up with the
healing vile demon Ripper again on her
oh she's the official punching bag look
at her triple lowered agility oh man
poor
girl it's going to be over soon don't
worry wait did he switch he switch water
water Shadow clean time I think
[Music]
yeah greatly he's not bleeding any more
was he have a bleeding
m
[Laughter]
okay
ah low his [\h__\h] attack please please
please I missed I focused too
hard
AOE it was son he was in the back
Hallelujah
[Music]
um K are you cuz I'm going to heal
her no
hey when do you blocked this after he's
through or [\h__\h] she's burned you know
that does a lot of
damage uh are we in in electricity
stance I think so
yeah
[Music]
those oh yeah this is the one where I
only had a weak item for okay we can do
this one again I pretty
[Music]
good M
650 Lori awaits on son oh I I look at it
again
okay let's try the lower attack one more
time or yeah
[Music]
good very very good we are at the end of
the tunnel oh what is he
charging you cannot let him do whatever
he wants to
do o hurts hurts
hurts and yeah no
MP what should I do with her wait he
switched his stance he's uh in this
stance he's still fire fire fire
fire he's still sensitive against fire I
could throw uh the normal rocket
launcher at
him go go go sh she almost finished him
that would have been so sick rocket
launcher finish with freaking San who's
so useless right now besides her
healing
okay it's time to die or please actually
don't die I know you good guy I
believe I do not press X to
doubt press y
to give him
hug cuz the why the why looks like a
person with open arms just like tea
actually okay for the upcoming cut scene
I'm going to very
quickly bring over my cookies
PE I think that fight went really
well don't you think so too it was
actually not a bad
fight I don't think I was struggling
much and even if we had a better weapon
for Satan I think we would have still
used her to heal
constantly and I think having to heal up
constantly is not because I was
low-leveled or so it's just that kind of
fight
yeah that's good I had it all under
control woohoo oh he got the pine bamboo
Plum rank
up level up rank
up
LEL looks like a [\h__\h] egg
Yol no
[Music]
wow we have to help him
oh no please let me I don't take me
[Music]
no
swim kind of cute
[Laughter]
oh cute nice Fe
okay stop watching he has to dive up
he's trying to stay
down yeah it was all scripted by
sairo was just acting it out
me too I'm looking forward to it that's
what she said
[Music]
okay before we
go should I buy her weapon here we need
to go here
anyway I should have checked what they
have oh
well I think I I remember now that store
was indeed the best place to buy Idol
weapons ah wasn't it just like stupid
[\h__\h] like
vibrators
a I remember it's coming back to
me a
no
okay okay this is looking very
say a Flor microphone a twinkle
microphone and the wings
microphone wait this is not bad at
all very tame might even buy her the
five star one might as well we have
enough money and we're we need it
eventually right should I buy the five
star
one this one's Five Star Plus
116 not going to get this
one mhm
okay
mhm Twinkle Twinkle Little
Star oh this doesn't look like a whip
anymore this is just a sword okay we can
I can get her the five star one too
wait I hope that's worth it instead of
crafting
it it's fine
right the other ones are
craft I
think cute
[Music]
whoa no wonder they all get so much more
stats that's what seven
star wait the
price 29 29 29 29 n n n
n yeah the the other things are
that what we need right now okay awesome
um we're happy with
that I thought they would sell some MP
items
wait H
okay what is he going to look like what
is he going to dress up as oh he's
already here
I just dressed as like a
worker
normal pretty
normal I love
her
no
for bana
too
for
[Music]
foree
for curry flavor
wow you can't always rely on it like
that okay
fore
[Music]
foree for
a very realistic
[Music]
problem
MH we saw this already
yeah
[Music]
problem man that's so disappointing when
you think you're the chosen one to go to
the nice Island is all nuclear
waste wow
yeah cuz it's in a different country
then
[Music]
you're just hoping they'll change the
love
[Music]
for
this time
I script it
fore
[Music]
h
foree
for oh
backlash oh
oh that's it I moved myself out of the
way for a cool
scene that's the dagle guy
right it was a back flash right d That's
a back flash
right pretty cool though could have been
longer uh oh maybe there's there's going
to be more after this chapter as we have
just finished a chapter let's
go go next sua
chapter 11 H devil in the
skies oh it's supposed to be
he's having a zoom call
wait is he predicting the future
pretending to do
so and the Yakuza dudes are buying ity
he's just summarizing oh but it still
feels like he's trying to predict the
future cuz I still think all of that is
like just how you wish things to happen
you don't know that
that's that that
law he is talking to politicians there I
think
he probably struck the deal
already but don't people have to
vote isn't there democracy they can just
decide this
right what about
democracy Gaslight Gau reactor
boss if you like them
whatever
[\h__\h] his
flock what are they
Birds good news overseer what is
it we've secured the girl she's coming
in on the next
boat and am I supposed to be impressed
by
this why is you sooner I wouldn't have
relied on ev's
help if there ever comes a day where he
uses this against
us it will be your last to right uh
there won't I
swear it's so weird cuz like
he's like the person he talks to is
literally speaking proper English hey
yo public ex [\h__\h] in ction with children
and guns what the
[\h__\h]
the
whoa what the [\h__\h] is going on what the
[\h__\h] is
happening you have all been chosen
father Bryce has granted you the right
of
fire no now forsake yourself to the flam
and D that came back
oncap what
the keep going their impurities have not
been fully purged they are to be
unspoiled nothing
less
what you good bro he's smiling you have
made me barely plot my children of
par even if the world were to collapse
Into Darkness I'm confident you frames
Who Lies
away what they're they're teenagers
right I saw like
doubles what the are those two dudes
that they shot
um dudes who came back from the L
take over thingy or just random
dudes they look
familiar
mama you can't die no Mommy
Mommy s you
say it's really sentimental right now
don't be like this what the
[\h__\h] I thought you were nice
now you can do that with a I don't know
little little stick from a tree or so no
we have a [\h__\h]
crowbar that's not the normal kind of
pipt dude I know like a it's cool to
like punch him or whatever to like get
him to realize or just I don't slap him
use your hands don't use a [\h__\h]
crowbar you're supposed to be buddies
now and you see he's in front of his
[\h__\h] dying
mom what the
[\h__\h] this all [\h__\h] up why is there so
much violence
never been hit by a crowbar but I just
imagine
it's [\h__\h]
painful come
on I don't accept
this it's [\h__\h]
up also what the [\h__\h] was that scene
with the teenagers
I I what am I supposed to
just do stuff
now
what heyo where is the girl I guess we
have to get her
back is it you no that's the the
lady a that's see my dude actually first
I'll talk to Tommy because I feel like
me and the DUI
have deeper
[\h__\h] when we found aan and Lonnie I
thought we were finally good then they
took it all away from us can't stop
thinking about Han was and Wong
for this whole time we've been playing
right into the bad guys
hands
yep hurts oh I know we we've been Thanks
for the
pinky oh hey D what the
[\h__\h] you mean you mean not like they
don't work on you as in someone's like
using it on you uh some you using it but
the other way around like ena's using
the Crowbar to do pep talk to you or
so and it's not working for you and
you're not feeling pepped up or do you
mean you're the one using it that's also
concerning what who do you need to pep
talk
HH I should be pep talking you
if anything he said what he said I think
it can be interpreted both
ways tacos poor
Tacos yeah X is more efficient no what
the [\h__\h] baseball bat made out of
plastic uh soft plastic is
best yeah pain but not too much okay I
know we've been very deep in [\h__\h] before
c but this time feels like to this I I
literally said that before I talk to him
we got some deep
[\h__\h] but there's no use wallowing in it
we have to go up the Lani we have got to
go move while she might still be alive
very Maddy back
scratcher has similarities yeah where do
we even start looking we haven't got a
clue got clue [\h__\h] one but
what we haven't got clue [\h__\h] one
wouldn't you say one [\h__\h]
clue is he okay are you having like a
heart attack not a heart ATT a stroke
you
okay what a
clue that's legit
phrasing mumble jumble that's mumble
jumble for
me Yama is kind of the new majima isn't
he uh the vibe I got people tracking the
barracudas and the
gunu if we're lucky someone might cough
up some info on the
girl okay it's really sweet how he's on
our side now and I feel like he can be
very passionate about what he does and
who he
supports um but please stop hitting me
in my back with a crowbar I am what how
old is he 50 45 please don't do this
anymore endure too much pain already day
to
day
oh she probably feels really [\h__\h] bad
about what she
did
for we have to consider that we're not
mad
for real she waited until the last
moment to change her mind on which side
she
stands or she's currently facing
the what's the
word
the
uh consequences
of the blackmailing because she went
against them and maybe they did whatever
they were blackmailing her
with yeah she'll be around
right
[Music]
Che cheah
thank you
HL I'm happy to hear
that
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
for I wonder if she wants to go to
Japan to fix something but I don't know
if she could fix more in
Japan then she could here in Hawai hm
listen listen before we act rley we need
a plan right okay then uh I say we talk
to the tattoo lady
again son s yep I bet if anyone else
knows what she turns his headed it's
hurt that's not much of a plan but it'll
have to do let's
go a we only free people
now she wouldn't have stolen a gun if
she planed on leave the
country
a never know if
Yakuza never
know oh
no well now that I'm only free people
surely
they
adjusted the difficulty of the
enemies oh it's right over
there what you got a problem what you
got a problem what you got a problem
what you got a problem you got a you got
a you got a problem what you got a
problem what you got a problem you got a
you got a you got a
problem what you got a problem what you
got a problem you got a you got a you
got a problem
what
[Music]
it's the energy drink
sorry true I guess maybe
fore spee
maybe he's at the
beach what you mean he's going for a
swim cuz he's out of the
wheelchair I can't believe they're still
calling him
a i she's so
cute we should head to the dini safe
house okay let's go
where is
it
far what you got a problem what you got
a problem you got to you got to you got
a problem what you got a problem what
you got a problem you got a you got a
you got a problem what you got a problem
what you got a problem you got a you got
a you got a problem well you got a
problem what you got a problem you got a
you got a you got a
problem rock and roll I was going to go
here
actually
yeah yeah
[Music]
can you
see on the
street some time
ago with a big fancy
[Music]
show she
the melody
anymore
she even
know I am not
even I just wish she come back what you
looking at because take want her to give
me a heart attack
and when she comes to
me I'll be
truly
free what what's going
on a [\h__\h] my gear
I have no
gear oh still good
damage man
the
man trying to tell I was busy stinging
you know it
what it's not decaffinated Red Bull no
no no no no that's not the thing I drank
I'm drinking proper Red Bull watermelon
but then before that I was
drinking like a Fanta Red Bull kind of
thing what are he doing ow what the [\h__\h]
was
that
watermelon yeah we were busy listening
to the new you say and
[Music]
the come
stop for not having any armor is not so
bad what the hell is Ali
Charmed well I thought Ali was no homo
but okay let's go love everywhere
[Music]
Love Is in the
Air that's it
honestly such a
bro where is the this where ah is this
what is this it is this the the the
speech
bubble
oh equ it
ice that syrup or fruit look old man
I've heard from other shops are you
going around buying ice and covering
your face in it
whatever wait didn't we yeah didn't we
have this before in one of the early
streams I take pride in what I sell or
did why am I hting so I'm not going to
let you get your jollies off on my
product no we did we did we did you need
to cool down take a swim or if you're
angling for some we weird lawsuit
against us you should just give up what
the hell you talking about Jolly I'm
being serious here please
he custom damn the old man's gotten
himself black baled from every shaved
eyes place around here guess that's no
surprise have to admit I'm curious what
the guy's goal
is
uh yeah I'll talk to him but I need to
put on my
armor hey old man are you going come to
laugh at me now that I can't keep
chucking ice into the sky like the damn
fool I am I wouldn't do that I'm just
curious what you were trying to
accomplish you seem pretty serious about
it you mentioned turning down into snow
right mhm ain't like I was trying to
quench my first on straight eyes it's
for my wife to show her some fresh fall
St you know why you'd have had better
odds taking a trip you know I don't know
Alaska or somewhere don't you think
don't you think we would have if we
could have is she
dying yeah my wife's sick he want you
able to get out of bed anymore she could
you could go anytime now so I've been
asking for something anything I could do
for her most of the time she's not all
there when we talk but I damn well hear
her say I want to see the snare with you
again we have some good memories in the
snow went to Japan on our honeymoon you
know I was the first time we saw stuff
we both felt like we had been
whiskeyed away into the other world I
always promised here her we'd go again
someday but what what well you know how
life can be hard to take time off work
or for something a silly yes S I never
made much money so I've always worked
doubly hard for my family all this time
I'm not sure how she felt about that
what's this
accent and now it's too late to ask ask
ask all I know is she's always been
there for me without a word of complaint
funny it was only after I retired I
could start making plans again now we
realized how sick she was we m all the
warning signs huh what warning sign what
who am
I it it was too late by then I'm so
sorry she gave me everything she had to
give it this life and I can't provide
her this one damn thing godamn thing in
return and to think I was excited when
she first said she wanted to see snow
again figured it beasy I could make her
happy for all I know she'd be too out of
it to even realize but maybe I just need
to feel like I did something
for I was thinking maybe I could have
some air lifted in from another cut
that's crazy there is no
time so all you could think of was to
shave I shave shave Shave Ice you were
trying to save maybe it'll fall down
like
[Music]
snow let's see how
about
using cotton candy or um you know just
like the kind of cotton filling
for uh or even confetti if she's so out
of it that you think she wouldn't notice
buy white confetti don't even buy white
confet buy a paper snippy snip make it
into it just yeah it doesn't have to be
doesn't have to be snow put it in a room
with really really really good air
conditioning turn it
freezing and then any of these things
there's so many more materials that you
could use
and you could probably buy fake snow you
don't have to airlift
it yeah there's so many the Apple
headset yeah the Apple Vision or
whatever so many
ways hell I might have tried something
just as crazy in your sh but in this
heat there's no way it would ever build
up of a melting and now I can't even buy
more if I want to what do I do it can't
end like this can it
it looks like winter
lisu winter
ISU I appreciate you telling me your
story but now there's no way I can just
wish you luck and head off together let
me try to think of something we should
go home and be with your
wife name is
Orlando Oh orando Bloom by chance no I
heard of this guy orand
Bloom he's qu charming and you're
charming so you might be the same
guy and maybe be in this
fate um is there going to be a
fight I don't see how this could lead to
a
fight or maybe the the the me getting
the snow will somehow lead to a
fight but okay for
now don't worry I got it guys
storm board class okay here
[Music]
um
nice
uhhuh I wish you could just like have a
sharing
function man
o probably not really what he needs but
whatever cuz you constantly switch
between these two game teams it's not
like they're like mixing maybe until the
end game end end end and end and end end
end and end end end
game uh
just buy more armor
no no no no
[Music]
no no no no no no
no no no no no
[Music]
your face your face pisses me
off your we
[Music]
are a baral egg stop
no thanks
okay a not
a it's not a show [\h__\h] head it's not a
show [\h__\h] it's not
a
next okay okay okay
it's not not my fault when they're
repeating themselves like this it's very
inspiring it's very
[Music]
melodical why only
coconuts why do the the coconut trees
only grow
coconuts grow some more
Bingo perhap some more variety in this
day and age in this economy you can't
just only be focusing on one thing
coconut
trees you're so far behind you're
lagging
behind I thought she one shots tea
honestly the the small tiny um te's that
they give you in these kind of places
you can totally onot them and when it's
cold outside [\h__\h] yeah that's that's the
best
what is that a that's a prop right
that's not even supposed to be a really
person it's like a joke right cuz he's
not
breathing is his face on the other
side no they should put his face there I
never saw that before did you guys see
this before
so not a real person I
think give me some good sushi because
only in games I can eat
sushi yeah this is the place with the I
know I know I
[Music]
remember you know the thing is even the
food that I don't like eating it just
looks visually so freaking appealing
a w we have 140,000
bucks everything
please man one day I would to be able to
say everything on the menu please don't
order anything I hope I hope I can eat
the things though I shouldn't be alone
but I'll just say everything you got on
the menu all of
it hopefully it's the small menu cuz
that's kind of crazy what a crazy thing
to say talk to the dude in the back okay
okay okay maybe in a sweet
Place boost
okay thank you very
much do it in
America got do it somewhere and make a
video out of it oh a mukbang video you
guys mean this guy there's another one
of please ha welcome you can order at
your table you want a Hong Kong what I
don't want a Hong
Kong get
honked for 1,000 bucks give me a quick
moment to get ready wait what do you
mean with Hong Kong what's happening is
he touching his manly
chesticles oh I haven't put that much
effort into anything
not say it's plus 30 for
everything not bad for I do say so
myself oh nice thank you what the [\h__\h]
what happened what
happened what did you do to
me I only saw a pink
screen is that that's all I saw I don't
even know what
happened I think his manly chesticles
got tweezed or something maybe he
tweezed his
nipples I mean itan
nipples I just feel like that's what
they it's Yakuza after
all
for they look like Han
people I'm so
sorry foree
[Music]
fore
got finish this job
is that
still
available
people
me what did you just call them
lizard God your face pisses me off your
face pisses me off ah your face pisses
me
off you can't
measure your face pisses me
off your face pisses me
off your face pisses me off
[Music]
okay this is
me let's make a whole album
[Music]
yeah this dude is so sus over there you
think you're being smart hiding there H
although I don't have anything effective
I'm going to work on you instead
jellyfish juice oh
god
wow the game is calling me weak I do 547
damage and they call me weak my my my
manliness is feeling very insulted right
now oh there they're calling me a miss
again I'm even more insulted I guess I
am a miss
first they call me weak then they call
me a Miss I have to accept
it huh oh I did it
again they know that they're getting to
me I don't know what I'm saying help me
guys help
me I I I I I I'm normal okay did I just
do 1,000 damage wow Tommy wow
go
drunk uh I drank almost a whole energy
drink
[Music]
so wait so I can't go there are you
kidding me um oh never mind I don't need
to go there
anymore we are going
here can I go for here so I can get all
the
conversations yeah but like how do I get
around can I go
here like probably could go through
these back at least no
what's with your
face
maybe but is there oh there's no path
here I know I need to go to the pink
Icon but
um actually I should go
here actually yeah I'm just going there
to zoom through them so I can just have
the bond
Bingo it's addicting surprisingly
addicting your
face waterm flavor yeah it really tastes
pretty good it doesn't
um give me this big uh Vibe of I'm
drinking
a what you looking at an energy drink
throw away your life I don't really like
the basic main flavor uh Red Gold that
much because it really givs me this in
your
face red energy drink vibe pretty
flavors if
[Music]
anything Peach
apricot think I'm probably had that one
before
tropical
L ow
[Laughter]
[Music]
I believe in aachi
power I believe that without a skill he
can take him
down oh those are drones they look like
crows CR
[Music]
me oh that's the idea makes sense it's
okay Tommy can suffer because he can
heal himself back up again come up
little
[Music]
wor no why did I
miss viewer is here
mommy wa thank
you
wa I just felt
this voice to me it sound very much like
Satan help me guys I need to be
cleansed let's go to maybe they can save
me maybe they can save me before Satan
takes
me wait this
way just casually hearing demons isn't
normal that's what I thought so I must
go to Pana and ask him to save
me so where are these uh conations I
want over
there what are you looking at
not oh cool
right okay
hi I the dog
handler used to work with police dogs
he's got a pretty Keen sense for what
they're feeling kind of surprised I'm
not
surprised it's like an Adai
thing a BC d e f
[Music]
g how do you sing this in
English froze everything
[Music]
off f
g e y l o p
s
t v I never know the end not even in
German I don't know the
melody
bird bye-bye
bird I don't know the end do you know
the
end open
so many keys and not this
[\h__\h] I take nothing below four stars
from now on
understand volleyball what do you want
what do you want what do you want what
do you want what do you want what do you
want what do you
want this ain't a show dip [\h__\h] hey you
there hey you hey you there hey you
there hey you there hey you there hey
you there hey you there could repeat
that forever oh my God I'm actually
insane
guys and what do insane people do they
run across the streets with no no eyes
on
anything that's just how we
do oh
stop what you looking
at run on home to
mama is not even worth my time but the
gold you making fun of me I'm going to
give you a good show here
[Music]
Now give me your [\h__\h]
car can I
ass they left the car here for real it's
mine now but I don't know how to get in
they should let you have the
car what are you what what is that whole
thing for what why do they show up like
that why do they make such a scene of an
entrance
and then you don't even get the
car what is the meaning of
this what you looking
at you like red
Ki it really brings out the best in
me yeah I'mma go
in I'm going
in p
steal open the freaking door
[Music]
should
have everything in Yakuza
always becomes a big
thing okay have a seat everybody cuz I
can imagine I'll be standing for 5 hours
and 20 minutes now watching my stream as
you're usually following the rule book
and then the rule it says you have to
watch my stream standing until I'm
telling you to sit the [\h__\h] down and now
they told you so I guess just this one
side allow it you may sit down now for
the first time in 5 hours and 20
minutes please take a seat you're
welcome you're welcome just this once
don't get used to it
enjoy feeling the own your own fluffy
butt that you
have it's nice isn't
it I know but I can't have you enjoy and
get used to
this can't be the
norm yeah you're so kind today I know
just today just
today
for
foree
for foree
[Music]
yeah
know yes
and that's already [\h__\h] up on its own
but then you see how they're making
teenagers shoot
people
uh then then the other thing just almost
seems like a very tame normal thing
so that's why you treat them like a
god
stks
for foree
[Music]
really
for
w
[Music]
fore
surprising
fore fore
spee fore
Red
Bull I still have some more but I don't
want to drink
it my brain
uhhuh same he
[Music]
hates
fore fore
[Music]
so a got framed and a things he got
framed
by uh
uh uh the aawa
family but that's not
certain but so he was a
reporter and what's this whole thing
with the car who was driving it what
happened with ag how was AG
involved there was then some Court
thingy and they couldn't prove that the
anakwa family was in involved in the car
accident though right a was the
driver and then there was an
accident somebody jumped in front of the
car right and AG thinks it was on
purpose AG was AF for a hidden
run he was driving and ran over a
pedestrian allegedly placed there by AR
why does he think that why does he think
it was aova
family H because he was already on some
dirt from the alak family maybe yeah and
so he thinks they wanted to get rid of
him I want to watch this discussion
again um okay okay okay we got it we got
it
tomwa emphasizing with ag right
now bleach [\h__\h]
Japan
no not
yeah
damn him like our
best
[Music]
foree spee
fore
[Music]
true
reporter still a
[Music]
reporter
for we don't
[Music]
knowe
spee uh I feeling
is he her trap or she's in trouble and
she couldn't write a proper message so
she just send a picture or AG has her
phone and use that to bait
them say say something
let's go we'll do that and then I'll
probably end it it's already oh my God
10 p.m. I wonder how long this is going
to take is it like a whole
dungeon or just like one big
fight quick just a biger okay okay okay
okay so so the picture it's of a place
called Club Gil
only thing is it's up District 5 that's
Barracuda
territory well then we keep our guard up
right Kasa I to say it but there is a
chance that she does is trying to screw
us over again let's make sure we're
ready for
anything oh don't worry about it don't
worry about it don't don't worry about
it don't worry about it don't worry
about
it don't worry about
it okay we got to
I don't know I don't know don't worry
about it
what don't worry about
it how do I make a more like American
accent don't worry about it no don't
worry about it about it don't worry
about it
word for dirty dirty
[Music]
dirty yeah I boot itot
okay
a let's [\h__\h] him
up let's [\h__\h] this
club
[Music]
for join
us we fck him up
[Music]
but Chan you better fix my reputation
after all this is over and make some
positive
reports about ich the number one
[Music]
yak and then report that K is dead
not because he actually going to be dead
but because we need to fix
this hopefully he won't actually be
dead oh I should have healed ichiban's
MP
[\h__\h] hey it's the hell are you doing
here yeah
it's tell me my
Sor the balls on this guy hey fellas
looks like we got ourselves a new
punching
bags they will come in like a wrecking
ball into your face run on home to
mama let me swing them
around
oopsy at least we have full HP
like a raing
[Music]
ball
yeah
Yahoo let's go
what can I
maybe I wish I could get the other
one all
you he's also walking
away well at least I can get
two
wo I can't see
[\h__\h] we an MP
for say
combo
oh he shoots to kill can't see sh how
what do you shoot
normally shoot to
bir when shoot
[Laughter]
strong
but how many arrows was this
three it's not how it work what do you
mean no
really then
how
come it's okay I know I know I know I
need
[Music]
and please give me a level up or a
heal level up gives PE back
right he only has eyes for
CR i d see in love
again we love to see it
the rainbow skill Tommy got the rainbow
skill we have cruising kfp cruising
KF cruising kfp is better though it's
the other way
around cruising
yaka Mommy can we have Cru in yaka we
have Cru at home Cru at home no Mommy
can we have Cru at
home we have Cruis and Yakuza Cruis and
Yakuza
let's go clubbing
kfp katas R club with
[Music]
K don't worry
Cruz it's not
you a
I am here to
kill what do you mean reliable as
ever
oh the never set up by Cho but I trust
her very GTA
like bastard
I will put you in a wheelchair for real
for
[Music]
real going be
okay dance dance dance
[Music]
why a start okay I think we can get the
free only two okay but they're
dead okay going to be okay
[Music]
there
wa I'm put to hurt on you what do I do
with all this power what do I do we
there's only one choice only one thing I
can do with his power I've got to save
the
world I have to save the
world double power w
maybe I'm saving the world I should
destroy the
[Music]
world the power
feels like power power is
power thank
you
[Music]
fore no don't believe
it proof
speech speee
he like a secret
[Music]
agent shoot
please at least his legs come on
she's so
serious
for spee
foree foreign
[Music]
huh the wheelchair is being
reused it looked like they would cut off
her arm
foreign foreign
don't don't bring up cutting it like
[Music]
that
fore
for Fore fore
but yeah she looks cool with that
hair and
um it's good
[Music]
to close the chapter and move on
to
[Laughter]
C ch ch ch
[Music]
I love it when Tommy hits real hard it
just feels so
good taking your
[Music]
time found one Target
acquired sh
[Music]
attacker the skill is call [\h__\h] him
up teach me teach me that skill maybe I
already know
[Applause]
it oh driple baby oh
triple let's
go a chome is
[Music]
H does she even have her proper
equipment now
though cuz I took stuff uh yeah look at
that weapon that's not normal
right that's the thing like they don't
they bring members back into your team
and they don't let you like they don't
didn't consider that I need to maybe
switch some
equipment yo
what a chicken what a chicken excuse me
who said that which one of you was
that it's okay I'll kill you all anyway
it doesn't
matter I think it
[Music]
was oh that barely did any damage oh cuz
your weapon is so [\h__\h] ah M Mia
oh that's really bad that's really
[Music]
bad it's on someone else too
bad oh perfect
[Music]
line
man it's a perfect wave
[Music]
yeah I get it I get
it get
it
then ack if I can get to Tommy where is
he oh here then I'll
heal revert to
heal even that
120 man
[Music]
you
substitution to give turns to others oh
okay okay
okay it's not already too late I will do
it it
on what a chicken stop it stop saying
that it's very insulting to a phoenix
BR
it
come come
on it says um this one says multiple
enemies but like I can only choose one
so how does this is it just like
random the choosing makes no difference
oh
goded I need to do that more often so
that I am ready for
it
oh that is
perfect shut the [\h__\h]
[Music]
up don't care really who does it
so he gets two turns right this is not
not like we got an extra turn
right
[Music]
a no not
good Grand liner
go here this is May
good chicken water a chicken water a
chicken Oh wait we're back to her let's
just do it
again Let's Do It Let's Do It Let's Do
It Let's Do It Let's Do It Let's Do It
Let's Do
do it do
[Music]
it tonight going to be a good
night tonight
[Music]
be well I mean
I'm it's hard to make this exensions at
this
point I'm so
dumb
[Music]
come the song became a huge meme in
Brazil recently because someone
misremembered hearing it in Spider-Man 2
when octus
sa what else was playing
[Music]
she she keeps on getting her turn though
what
agility wow
now can we please kill a
I hate
him like how didn't become an absolute
ignorant Bastard with no
heart aid you definitely chose to become
like that
I don't get it either
no don't don't don't drop her down the
[Music]
stairs I can't watch this
no it's going to malfunction or
something's going to happen right this
can't that's too [\h__\h]
cruel but he's so [\h__\h] up
[Music]
don't push her now no don't
don't what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
malfunction I swear to God like
end of last
stream and now there's I don't recall
another
game that made me so
genuinely
angry
at uh a fake character that doesn't
exist in real
life I'm
so flabergasted
and angry
at the situation that's that he is
creating whoa
whoa and that
no
whoa uh-huh
okay gas
[Music]
for
no that nose is so
broken oh [\h__\h] oh it was her
head cuz they couldn't like change her
model again to make her broken nose
because done that too much
effort [\h__\h] you from the bottom of my
heart [\h__\h]
you wow wow wow wow wow wow I'm going to
make like uh I'm going to buy a figure
of this dude if exists one or I'm going
to commission one or I'm going to make
it myself maybe I make a [\h__\h] H CH
sock puppet and I'm going to like stab
it
69 times and then I'm going to drown it
and waterboarded and then I'm going to I
don't know I'm going to
freaking throw up all over it and then
I'm going to I'm going to throw it down
into a river and then I'm going to pick
it up and then I'm going to smack it
smack it smack it against the pavement
and then I'm going to rip it apart in
little pieces and I'm going to [\h__\h]
burn it and then the ashes I will I will
I don't freaking know I make a cake and
then I [\h__\h] eat
itam [\h__\h]
what's wrong with
[Music]
him what happened in his
childhood you are literally yifa right
now don't worry
everybody's
y yeah let's make a ag tort doll
okay are we now going to start the
campaign
of you know
improv seven years ago
this is such a real
story
[Music]
fore the 10 nights of t
you got the place
fore
for foree
[Music]
damn oh
that's not really what she said in
Japanese those fre
the English was a bit
extreme so yeah they just she just said
that they just were like oh what are you
saying what what are you talking about
not not like shitty Vibes tonight
like hater
[Music]
comments and does she became a drama
so for
[Music]
her family doesn't know that she's
tatara
right that she's the one like exposing
her family right did I miss
something they don't know
right uh maybe that's what she's being
uh yeah threatened with
I can see
how
for so cute though
I wonder I wonder if the character
designer of her is the same character
designer as all the other Yakuza
characters because like it's a very
different vibe obviously but whoever
designed her should really design a
proper V maybe they did I need to find
out like who's like behind this
character design in
particular and they need to
be actually that I mean maybe that style
looks familiar I don't
know next Hol
mom cute I love her cardig again it
looks so fluffy nice
but that logo looks like the typical
logo I
wonder made that one too
[Music]
yeah trying to make it more
difficult
to get a normal life so that they have
to rely
[Music]
on D she's a
puppet
forening with
doing
m
[Music]
foree
fore foree
[Music]
we got a real trouble
fore
foree
[Music]
Tomy for no it's
okaye for
[Music]
uh yeah sure yeah totally tot
you reading too
much
fore
for
foreign
spee
[Music]
fore
e
for
[Music]
foreign
for
come I'm orange too I'm orange
juice is that the end of a chapter no
probably not too short
yeah wow wow wow so you think L been
yeah that's most like the place of
course nobody seems to know where it is
there's one person we still have ask we
should check on her she's at y right
yeah let's move
okay
P
yep you know it's time to end it you
know it's just as well as
me yeah check your gear yeah yeah yeah
I'm not continuing to play feel free to
remind me at the beginning of next time
time great stream thank you thank the
Red Bull for keeping me
alive and also soon being the death of
me just
kidding
what's next weekend will continue and
hopefully finish it I might do some
grinding off stream because I do want to
finish it so hopefully the grinding will
help and and might do some side stuff if
I find where it
is
yeah and okay uh I don't
[Music]
know
um if I'll get to do the schedule before
I go to sleep but just think of tomorrow
as probably the member stream or a
different shter
normal stream and then a different day
might be the M stream no smoothie didn't
come back after that time she left but
she was here for a
while
um yeah what time yeah just like uh 700
p.m. or so probably the thing is
like yeah my mom's
coming over tomorrow but not to me she's
first staying at my brother's place I
think and then she's going to stay one
night at my place from Tuesday to
Wednesday so I'm going to take Tuesday
off so that I
don't uh have to stream while she's
here put Mama toy in the
suit
no
um yeah got to clean up yeah that's also
true
uh and tomorrow I have something like to
do during the day a small thing and so
during the day I'm going to clean
later are you calling to people stream
no but I'm part of uh a part of her
birthday stream anyway I'm part of a
part of her birthday stream not calling
in though is she doing Callins I didn't
hear anything about Callins
happening should remind you about the PO
oh yes please
do please do feel free to and there
were like
randomly in my replies I saw like maybe
two people on separate occasion telling
me that I forgot their Polaroid
previously please just write it in the
community post of when I delivered the
Valentine's po Awards and uh cuz I might
check there like having it randomly in
the middle of hundreds and hundreds of
replies when I'm not working on the PO
wordss in the moment is a bit difficult
to
um keep note
of or I might I don't know do another
post where I'm like uh whoever I forgot
last time here's your last chance to
remind
me I don't
know um yeah I can't believe how this is
always happen I'm going through the list
one by one one by one don't know how it
happens
still it's so
weird and now I have to think what am I
going to cook or am I going to get a a
PE pizza or
so thinking about it well well
well yeah only the
people yeah anyway when if I do a tweet
like that I'll do it when I'm working on
it so then I can get right to
it no no it's not so exhausting signing
those no no no it was it was not so
bad take some time and some Focus but
it's not so bad we post some tips for
stuff to do it ah thank you yes please
do but maybe maybe
H post
them I mean you can post them in the kfp
hashtag but if you post it now I'm
certainly not getting to it now maybe
take your time do it
like on another day don't do it
now do it on on the day you think I'll
be
playing read my
mind nah maybe do it tomorrow I don't
know
or do it on Tuesday I probably won't
play on Tuesday
though I probably need two days off next
week though just
considering uh all the long streams I'm
doing look my eyes are going
insane need a break in two break days
maybe but I have to see how it works out
actually cuz girls talk is happening too
y girl talk girl talk will be on my
schedule okay in German we
say yeah indeed
oh so
[Music]
true stream
tomorrow is going to
happen about
bye-bye thank you for watching oh my God
this game is so crazy
[Music]