[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
this is
[Music]
foreign
things are not in the right place
there we go
[Music]
hi everybody
hello and welcome to another scuffed
cooking stream is gonna be even more
stuffed than usual because I am in my
office in front of my computer and I'm
currently pointing my hand uh at the
exact opposite of myself
yeah that's that's uh egg I can't get it
like really like perfectly you know
curled for some reason but I only use
the fork but well it works it'll work
this way
um
wait you don't hear the video
there we go now you hear it I think are
the cats only not
the kids are not locked out but they'll
be fine once I talk they usually stay
away
[Music]
too loud yeah I turned it down is it
still too loud
wait
[Music]
the good old cooking medium it's back
yay
[Music]
maybe now now now I think it's good yeah
okay also I'm using um plastic gloves
this time they're very short but I've
got my sleeves on of course and yeah
um
did you wonder why I
um put aluminum foil all over my table
it's uh that one's um you know I was
bringing in some some smaller tables to
have more space everywhere and that
one's um that one's my my my my couch
table is this a round shiny one and it's
kind of reflective so I used the back
side of aluminum it works really well
because the back side is not reflective
and it wraps so nicely around it I don't
know that's the first thing I came up
with I could have probably just done any
kind of clubs but I went with aluminum
foil because why not
yeah
um so this is not my kitchen right now
I'm not not in my kitchen I'm in my work
room
um
[Music]
our boss is so big brain haha
it works it works it works what is an
air fryer well clearly you do not own an
air fryer what an Air France you look on
the left side of the screen you see that
thing here I have the same one but in
white actually
[Music]
I think it's just exact same model and
I've used it once I've seen it like
other people use this one like
especially one Cooking Channel
um you know was using this one and was
praising it so I bought the same one
um
[Music]
white O'Neill stains will show up no why
would you stain this like it's just
white on the outside and you put things
inside I don't know how I would stain it
it's perfectly fine
um anyway
[Music]
basically okay if you really don't know
what an airfryer is you clearly do not
own an airfryer but let me tell you so
basically and if you can if you can fry
something if you can Grill something if
you can bake something I think those
were the free rules
fry it I think
uh yeah I think those were the free
things oh so and the good thing about it
is that supposedly it isn't the same as
an oven
yeah but it's kind of faster because the
size of the Empire I don't know it's
Compact and it contains I think I think
I'm trying to Big Brain here
um it contains the heat better
um and it gets uh hotter faster I think
and the biggest thing about it is that
you use less oil let's say you're making
fried chicken
um in the pan in a lot of hot frying oil
you're gonna use so much oil but the
airfryer needs only a little Spritz of
oil yeah
um so ideally you would get yourself
like one of those oil
um spray fingers I couldn't find any
though so I
this is not gonna work well but it's the
best I could fight
I got a
a simple
um flower
spraying thingy with one tiny tiny hole
there
um I tested it and it does not work well
at all
but it's better than what I did before
um before I just tried my best to like I
don't know dab everything in oil a
little bit and I still felt that
actually works well for me really I
think if I would use the proper
um oil frying device uh or oil spraying
device
um then I would have
less oil
uh
spread over a bigger surface nicely
evenly this will not be very even that's
my problem like I tried and it's just if
it has a missed scrub it doesn't that's
the problem I need that it just comes up
out in one Big Blob kind of
so well
it's not the best no no no the the knot
was it's cheap ass thing it only has
really no there's no difference like
this it's just one thing one one tiny
hole there's no nothing else
unfortunately I rotated it if you've
rotate it it closes itself it closes
itself it's really just that uh I
I know I was in this like little shop
where
um you know they have all kinds of
things it's like a it looks like a one
of those private shops not like a proper
shop it's more like a private shop
really small really Thai and narrow and
and everything is like like randomly
thrown onto the shelves
I was like
I need a spraying thingy so I bought
when I was like where can I buy one
and they didn't have them in the
supermarket so and then my next idea was
I go to this little little kind of
private tiny shop that like one person
runs
Home Depot uh like I guess we have
similar things but like I don't know it
would have been like somewhere else so I
wanted to go somewhere somewhat close
and they have these everywhere it's not
a thrift store but you know
anyway so uh that's what they had and
it's better than nothing I guess
we might still like put quite a bit of
oil on there just because I can't spread
it evenly because every Spritz is quite
the
water fountain action
[Music]
uh I do know that I have to kind of
preheat this thing and
um I I really still don't know how this
[\h__\h] works there's like a couple of
there's a button for preheating and then
there's like a couple of like icons one
is like a steak one is a fish one is a
fried chicken leg one is the
um
prawn not prawn the smaller thing one is
bacon when it's broccoli one is Carrot
one is potato fries
one is bread and one is cake I don't
know which one should go for I've I've
watched several similar recipes trivia I
watched several similar recipes
and they are all say different degrees
but like
roughly I guess like 100 degrees Celsius
to 150 degrees Celsius maybe I don't
know
I don't know no manual sounding no there
is but I don't know how much I would do
so
um maybe more than definitely more than
100 I guess one but one recipe she was
saying 100 and I thought that sounds
like it's really low there is a setting
for fried chicken though and we're
frying but I guess we're not frying
chicken so I don't know what we're
frying is like smaller I guess than what
the frying Fried Chicken would be
uh 20 degrees Celsius are good for most
of the stuff yeah but are we like is it
the same for
it's just like 180 degrees Celsius but
we have to preheat it and I've I've
prepared this stuff oh my camera There
It Is I've prepared this stuff
um so I just have to like you know bread
everything and I'm just gonna bread it
in the same stuff like different recipes
said do this and that and do this blue
but it's like pretty like do whatever
like you can like do whatever really
some people don't even use egg some
people don't even use flour but I'm
using it all as if I'm making schnitzel
um
freestyle yeah I did
um into the plow I turned off all the
focus by the way but I think you can see
it well into the flower I put some
um pepper and some garlic
um
not powder but also not flakes like an
in-between uh and some you can't really
say it at all but I put quite a bit of
paprika powder bell pepper powder in
there as well so because one recipe was
saying to put that stuff in there at
least for
I think for the zucchini but I think it
fits both the mozzarella and the
zucchini
um so I'm kind of nervous about this I'm
very about this
[Music]
it turned itself off I'm really nervous
about this okay branded with Paprika
powder interesting
to have no idea people have been making
these mozzarella sticks with um like
Hot Flaming Cheetos uh powder and [\h__\h]
they buy these Cheetos and and the other
thing I forgot was the other thing was
called and they throw it in the food
processor make a basically a panko a
breading out of it like this and they
use it instead of that
and apparently it's really good and it's
it was a popular airfryer recipe on on
tick tock
good
let's see that sounds disgusting no like
everybody who eats it is like holy [\h__\h]
especially if you like spicy stuff they
have like those Hot Flaming ones right
so you do it with those if you don't
like spicy stuff then you do the less
less flaming ones but anyways yeah they
do a lot of those recipes so basically
that's uh I don't have a tick tock
account but I looked up compilations on
YouTube and looked for some recipes and
the ones I decided to do is number one I
always have to turn around when I look
at this table so my face will not be
moving but number one is zucchini I've
cut up some zucchinis and my mozzarella
sticks are currently in the freezer
because they say
um freeze them before you tease them I'm
just kidding um
they're in the freezer they've been
there for
14 more than 40 15 minutes
um and they said like put them in for
like an hour
um some people put them in before they
bread
um most people put them in after they
bread them but it's important with the
cheese I did my research guys it's
important with the cheese because
otherwise it will
um just melt everywhere in the airfryer
and we do not want that I don't I want I
I'm nervous about air frying stuff
because I haven't used that much yet but
um we want to have as little accidents
as possible Right
yeah well I'm not doing research I did
research yeah she has a book full of
notes no this is all in my head I'm so
proud
and we're gonna coat everything twice by
the way uh also something I normally
don't do because you don't do that but
coding it twice will make it extra
crunchy supposedly and also my breading
is not normal schnitzel breading no it's
um uh panko breading
breading doesn't really go bad right if
it's in the
same
container closed uh because it looks
good
smells like nothing basically because
um my mommy always reuses the prank call
the breading and Paco is basically
Japanese for
um breading and but some like even is it
I think this is so interesting even like
over since
um they sell panko
like Asian Japanese breading
uh under the name Panko and it is
actually different it looks the same on
first glance but it's actually different
because it's just a bit more bigger it's
bigger it's really yeah it's good
breading oh it's bigger nice and
crunchier that's why I always say
um the breading uh from an Austrian
schnitzel compared to a Japanese
tonkatsu is different because the
tonkatsu is just
so much more Crunch and when you just
even look at it you see how the the
little bread pieces they're like much
bigger because
foreign
[Music]
so we're gonna start with the zucchini
and then later we're gonna do the
mozzarella and
yeah I'm nervous but I guess I'm gonna
preheat this thing I have it standing
like I I I also honestly do you think
like it's safe to put on like a kind of
like a more or less wooden table it's
fine right the air for air because like
I I will watch the video of some air fry
tips and they said leave some space
behind the airfryer well it's more than
enough space but also something about
surface but like I don't know well I
mean I think as long as you don't put it
on the carpet right it's fine right yeah
okay okay okay okay okay okay
uh
yeah it's fine this one but yeah in the
back you should keep it
um open as much as you can because
they're the the air fryer needs air
to fry
so you need to keep some space in the
back now everything's open in the back
right now so all good all good
yeah
yeah we'll see you need social
distancing exactly shocking
wow
so we're gonna fry some air
um I'm gonna preheat it
I guess oh when I press preheat it says
205 and five minutes can I change that
oh I can
okay I'm gonna preheat it to 180 degrees
Celsius I don't know how much it is in
Fahrenheit do you think that will work
um the zucchinis I'm not so worried
about the zucchinis I'm worried about
them
cheese if anything I guess
yeah it's fine right friends 50 degrees
Fahrenheit okay
that sounds right
okay and then how do I start
let's start oh
it's loud
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay I think it started okay then we can
um present it says I think it takes four
minutes and it will beep when it's done
so
um I will I will I guess do my zucchinis
I'll turn around okay
okay let's hope this goes well that's
this is really not the best sound but oh
well
[Music]
um I bought some they're in this tonsils
tongs
but for them but I think I'll use my
hands anyway even though I the good
thing is then I'm using gloves I hate
doing this kind of stuff with without
gloves with my normal hands because
um
[Music]
breaded too it's like I'm turning into
Fried Chicken anyway so I haven't done
this in a while but
[Music]
make sure to get the ends yeah listen to
uh
[Music]
chunky monkey don't come here
I hate this
it doesn't even [\h__\h] stick I don't
get it it's like immune
come on
[Music]
come on it's getting nice getting there
it's getting there
[Music]
okay throw it in the brain
and give it a hug give it a squeeze
[Music]
these are plastic gloves I have more of
those way more
don't worry it's not my usual
um fabric gloves
eggs are those
well they're from Frank
yeah friends um Frank volunteers
here comes the second it's cold I hope
I'm doing this right
[Music]
foreign
on there I think
that will be an unhappy zucchini holy
[\h__\h] that is a lot of breading where do
I put this right now I guess I'll put it
I I prepared a plate okay next
is watching me from the
ticket number two
oh my God it's like almost done but free
anything [\h__\h] man I don't know do I
really do I have to do all of them
[Music]
come on
yeah
uh yeah
[Music]
sorry that I called your egg you
pick me like that right I can keep it
like that for a while right
but because it stopped making noise but
it's gonna stay heated right
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
yes but be quick
for real it was saying yes yes okay
[Music]
uh we're gonna do oh God
oh God
[Music]
I hate this process so much
go Checkers please don't come here
there's no space for you here anyway
why are you here you should not be here
I hate this
is disgusting
yeah I'm so glad I got the gloves you
you you you you
[Music]
you you
maybe I'll just do like three now and
then
[Music]
oh put put in a small tank bag oh that's
a good idea
and I'll do one more and then I think
we'll throw it in
this one
[Music]
that's why I never fry things because I
don't like this process
[Music]
it's okay
I have gloves it's not as disgusting
with the gloves
for breakfast or what dinner yeah
I have like a croissant
like an hour ago
foreign
[Music]
do this and imagine it's your breakfast
I Do by the way I really like zucchini
I think as a child I didn't like it so
much but now I'm a huge zucchini fan
what am I before egg later
thank God this would like soak up so
much egg
[Music]
is it preheated or not I don't know man
what does that mean
[Music]
s that mean
it's beeped he's like why am I why don't
you make me wait so long okay I'm ready
I'm ready so some people use
um
parchment paper with holes when they air
fry stuff here it is by the way but I'm
not gonna do that because for these
things nobody used that they just threw
them in there just like that
[Music]
okay uh he likes to go cold oh really
uh okay I'm gonna I don't know
um let me I'm scared to open it also I
have all this [\h__\h] on my hands it's just
one hand though I'm scared to open
oh is it hot
so this is my air fryer yeah okay I'm
gonna like just put it in there
uh I didn't put oil on them
ah [\h__\h] close
let me just try my best here
[Music]
do
you hear it
it doesn't work so well
I mean you know what is it okay if it's
only on the top
I think it's okay
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay so
let me show you here it is I'm throwing
it in okay
I I still I still feel like some kind of
heat radiating out of it so
that's good at least I guess okay now
um
180 degrees
uh yeah four
[Music]
oh should I turn it off
go
oh okay
it's air frying currently
pray emoji and let me I'm gonna take
this glove and switch it out to a fresh
one these are disposable gloves so all
is okay
[Music]
okay
and I'm gonna after this uh bring the
mozzarella sticks it's five minutes
enough we'll see if it's not then we'll
just um
we'll just push
yeah we'll just do it a bit longer it
needs 10 minutes I think
most people had it in for like four to
five minutes so in the videos
[Music]
five minutes sounds low
maybe we can you know flip them at five
minutes
please bless my ocean mistake yes please
airfryer Gods fry me some good zucchini
sticks
yeah then I flipped it into it again
ah
better more to be sure yeah probably
also lost a little bit of heat because I
took so much time to put it in there
um
yeah that's okay
where is where does Victoria also
teleport yeah
[Music]
the mozzarella sticks definitely were I
think the zucchinis too yeah yeah that's
zucchini still yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
um I also I think I made my skin sticks
a little bit thinner than the one in the
video so heat should be going through
faster
you could add one more egg in the
meantime yeah and I'll bring my
mozzarella sticks like this
um all right uh I'll I'll BRB this thing
is on three minutes right now
we'll be back
[Music]
foreign
left over how fresh the parmesan cheese
[Music]
okay so this is Frank's sister Esmeralda
I mean
[Music]
mix them together
nice oh
whoa
pretty
okay
should I start preparing now yes
yes I should oh yeah they're they're
hard I did by the way cut them in half
and yes this is this is string cheese I
was surprised to find it in my
Supermarket actually
[Music]
multitasking
foreign
[Music]
let me look
oh
looks good
uh okay it's kind of like too bright but
uh it's darker than that in reality but
I think we can do a little bit more but
it already looks kind of done
[Music]
um I'm gonna do
oh let me let me turn this first I guess
I don't know if it matters but
what
what good
[Music]
um
this is fun
I feel like I'm playing a game
yeah I'm gonna Brown them a bit more I'm
gonna do like ah I'm gonna keep on
turning it off I'm gonna do maybe three
minutes
[Music]
maybe four okay go
back to my mozzarella
[Music]
foreign
sticks anywhere ever again
I'm gonna make them at home
foreign
[Music]
by the way I'm reaching up my arm quite
a bit
[Music]
far away
this is like
arm workouts low-key
foreign
once now
by the way the packaging was kind of
funny hey
um it was four different sticks like
longer ones
[Music]
and on the back of the packaging they
had like stats like HP stats and attack
stats and two other stats and apparently
you can like like play with your friend
or so and then like fight like compare
which stats are higher and which one
wins
I've never seen something like this
before on on like food packaging
it's like a Pokemon fight oh yeah
speaking of Pokemon I mean I saw Cali
put out the reservation so I think now I
can say
uh tomorrow after whole talk I am
planning on playing Pokemon
Scarlet yeah she's on the whole plane
right now yeah
okay
let's go Pokemon
the things I what they they did not
officially show the evolutions yet right
so I have yet to see it like I looked
them up but I don't know which one are
like fan art and which ones are real
this is so confusing because if you look
up Pokemon Scarlet Violet starts her
evolutions on Google there's so many
different ones that come up so I have no
idea why the [\h__\h] did they not show
anything
if anyone I mean now the game is out so
now there should be official sources so
if anyone could send me the actual
actual evolutions on Twitter and show me
so I can make a decision that would be
very helpful
I would appreciate
[Music]
yo I'm using up all this breaking noise
I don't know if I'm gonna go for the cat
to be honest I like the the Apple Dragon
very much too and the duck just because
you know bird and Shuba Shuba has a
chance to honestly I like them all so
much I don't think I've ever really
liked
all Pokemon starters in the game so
equally
yeah
oh it's done I hope it didn't over
overdo it wait I'm gonna look in a
second baby
[Music]
I feel like the breading is not sticking
as well on these but uh
yeah
here we go are they burnt or are they
not burnt
there's five
[Music]
uh I'm gonna take a picture and then
upload it because you can't see it so
well here I guess
let me place them
carefully
wow
hello
I mean okay they still look very bright
but I think it's fine
it was in there long enough they look
bright they're brighter on the camera
for sure
uh okay okay back to business
[Music]
let me be let me try to be fast with the
mozzarella sticks now I'm just trying to
get off some of this goo-ish
[Music]
should I preheat it again
wow that's quite
chunk uh
[Music]
probably it's so hot yeah I think so too
um
I feel so stressed and pressured but
this is the fastest this is still the
fastest cooking stream I've ever done
because like we're almost done
[Music]
foreign
baby
[Music]
okay
um
the oil sprints
[Music]
it's okay to Spritz them when they're
already in the basket right I keep on
saying this word Spritz it's actually
German but I've I've heard English
people using it while they're speaking
English language so
I assume you guys know what I mean when
I talk about that right you say Spritz
right yeah yeah
[Music]
there's a lot of German words did you
know that
hmm
foreign
[Music]
but we also call for example
um an an apple juice with a bubbly
bubbly water sparkling water we call
that also uh Spritz
yeah interestingly
German one
they feel so soft even though they are
frozen ones this is the Cozy fluffy
breading all right it's in there now let
me try my best to Sprint
I can't
it won't get out because I turn it
around and then
[Music]
I thank you
nobody's coming out
why not you think it's okay without oil
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
now with the cheese I'm really unsure
I'm gonna do
um
I'm gonna do six minutes now
and then we'll see
we'll see we'll see
when we open it if it needs like three
minutes or so more
[Music]
glove I have another one
you can put drops or brush to oil yeah
[Music]
ah whatever
yeah okay can I stop it stop
you guys said I should just try my best
to like Drop It Like It's Hot
[Music]
um wait
I have a brush but um
let me get the brush real quick
spreading
[Music]
so I brought one of these brushes
a plastic
[Music]
I'm gonna try to be smart
oh that works
I'm just having it drop off of the brush
[Music]
yeah that's all right
that's all right okay better than
nothing
[Music]
go
oh oh I want to show you one more thing
guys wait wait I'll be right back I know
I keep on leaving but I leave my bag
[Music]
foreign
it's pretty big
it's pretty big but it's it's okay it
feels okay to hold
[Music]
um
yeah I got it um yesterday I picked it
up basically like I exchanged uh it's
with the person who ordered it for me
because I couldn't order it it was
stupid steam I paid for it but you know
and there were some problems
um
[Music]
I'm trying to steamed like yeah
no no it was too expensive to do that I
got the middle version
with um extra you know saving space but
I didn't want to buy the most expensive
version because I didn't think it was
worth it uh got it faster than my friend
in Brazil did oh
yeah well I guess we had like stock here
in Austria it was in stock
yeah 256 gigabyte yeah I think that's
how much it was glossy screen instead of
mud yeah I've thought the screen was
like
not that worth it for so much money yeah
so I played with it yesterday
I got right into slate Aspire don't
worry I did not
um do the thing I did not play the
actual Spire because I
um
had troubles
um I was trying to recreate the block
deck but I realized I must have been X
lucky really in my stream
[Music]
ever
um like only get no I was mostly only
getting [\h__\h] cards or or I got like [\h__\h]
relics
um that actually ruined everything so I
realized holy [\h__\h] wait I thought it was
so easy when I was streaming it but here
I am alone and I'm really trying my best
with the [\h__\h] cards they give me
um and I just could not make it past the
second stage
I was so pissed off I tried and I tried
and I tried my last run I was doing with
the snack eye Relic because
I don't know uh the other choices were
[\h__\h] and I did not want to go without a
relic
and
as Nick I made it very interesting
um and it every turn took a lot of time
I
sometimes you know at that point my deck
was still [\h__\h] and I still didn't get
good cards either so I was fighting with
that too but
um
yeah it was kind of also the reason of
My Demise in the end I mean I mean
sometimes it can be helpful and
sometimes it's like [\h__\h] up
everything
yeah
yeah and every every turn every turn
takes so long to look at like okay how
much does this cost now do I have
anything that costs zero
um
um makes a little wild run yeah
it's like definitely changing up things
that's for sure
[Music]
could not
I could not slay the Spire I wasn't
planning on it anyway I was gonna like
stop after the third stage
I just wanted to place like the spider
and then after a while I was I was so
pissed off because that I was I was like
stuck at one absolutely normal fight
and they absolutely [\h__\h] wrecked me
because it just it's I just didn't get
any
anywhere oh I just realized I wrote AI
fryer
oh [\h__\h] I didn't know this air fryer
well clearly nobody owns an eye fryer
I do own an air fryer though
oh it's almost done I'm nervous yeah bye
what the favorite things like melted
everywhere
[Laughter]
you think you guys didn't say anything
oh
gosh I'm kind of like tired today I
don't know why I slept enough also I
tried to sleep a bit earlier today and
that worked I slept like uh one to two
hours earlier today
I still woke up at a late time though
[Music]
Moment of Truth
wait why is there
I forgot to put one more in
[Music]
the free one was like left on the side
but uh
no why why don't you well I'll eat them
anyway obviously they're are they
considered finished though because like
they're very bright
[Music]
oh they smell good should I do it longer
of course they Bleed It Out Of course
they did
uh
you can do it faster uh maybe he had a
stronger heat and shorter time or so
I don't know
[Music]
um I'm gonna throw in
you have to try out things this is how
it is oh [\h__\h] let me throw in the last
one and it's just gonna
I'm gonna get rid of uh the other ones
after a couple minutes and then
you know
[Music]
baby trial never yeah
um
foreign
but what about the the stuff that's
already
bled out
[Music]
um
so I'm gonna do 200 now
I'm gonna do
[Music]
six minutes five six six I'm gonna take
out the other ones after like four
minutes maybe
yeah okay in the meantime oh I didn't
even try to do this yet what
let me I'm gonna put some
uh uh parmesan on top of them
[Music]
uh it's not not spreading so nicely but
oh well
[Music]
come on come out here
come out of the package
[Music]
I hope this parmesan is still good
let me just put it on one that's okay
and I'm gonna well just eat it with some
uh tomato ketchup I'm sorry I don't have
like
marinara some people said eat it with
marinara I don't have the marinara but I
bought fresh ketchup
wait it's really fresh so I have to open
the
well
for sure
good job it will be yummy with the
ketchup too
okay stop
here we go I'm gonna eat this one
[Music]
didn't take a picture
hmm
[Music]
maybe they needed more time
I'm not I'm not sure about it that
cheese sticks are fine still
um
they tastes good but very plain
and I don't know like is anyone ever
make these before
are the zucchinis inside also supposed
to be crunchy
foreign
[Music]
I don't know what um zucchini tastes
like raw
it doesn't necessarily taste raw it
tastes like just a little bit cooked I
think
[Music]
this should be a little softer okay well
they are
[Music]
um
but I guess they lacked some some
seasoning
I did add some seasoning to the flower
of Lauren's loud
[Music]
it's not bad it's just a bit boring
in the video they put the seasoning in
the flower so I put it in the flour
[Music]
maybe just needs a bit more cheese
speaking of cheese
[Music]
and good
that's good it's good okay
um
I think it's time to take out the free
that we're already in there
oh cleaning this will be fun
oh we're sticky oh sticky [\h__\h]
[Music]
I should have used like parchment paper
they [\h__\h] hell there's like a big
chunk of
cheese
[Music]
what
trying to rip it up actually works quite
well
[Music]
what a mess
although I've been containing the mess
quite well I would say
uh continue please continue
so
they look similar a little bit shorter
and a bit Browner than the other is
[Music]
not be anything wrong with these like
what can you do it's mozzarella sticks
it can't be bad
put something there
[Music]
comes the this is the most contained one
I guess more or less
miracles
oh it's hot
[Music]
all right that works
mm-hmm
[Music]
did you hear the crunch
um
Cookie Monster
[Music]
wait let me
try to
[Music]
see the cheese
ow
[Music]
um
it's really easy to make so good lunch
and I barely used any oil
[Music]
because when people say it fried stuff
is unhealthy they mean mostly because of
the oil right
[Music]
I have a zucchini with some breading how
can it be unhealthy
I don't know
[Music]
so I wonder how the last mozzarella
stick turned out that one was in theory
longer and hotter uh
it's not long over
[Music]
it's also bursted of course it did
um
foreign
[Music]
this one doesn't look much different
actually
it's a bit too bright actually
oh well
I'm happy
yay I got my lunch baby oh
[Music]
um
they feel a little bit empty now that
they lost so much cheese
and I got my pinky up
[Music]
I'm trying to catch up no
it's not the dad
that one legit looks like a finger
hmm
[Music]
you even saw the Heat going off of it
wow
I could have got even further
no no no no no no
wow it looks like bacon to me because it
has like
it has like yeah you definitely can't
see that but maybe from here you see
that it looks like bacon like the white
part of bacon
[Music]
please separate separate please please
foreign
[Music]
I'm not playing with my food
mm-hmm
foreign
[Music]
cooking stream very very easy
maybe I need an air fry out
I'm gonna be honest
I think everybody can live without an
air fryer
it's like
I barely use it this is like the second
time of her time
[Music]
no this one still had a lot of cheese in
it wow
[Music]
um
wow zucchini with the mozzarella in the
same mouth
adds more taste to the zucchini
[Music]
very good
yeah it has its uses but basically
everything you can make with it you can
make with an oven or so so
the question is
do you really want to get yourself an
air fryer just for the memes hmm
[Music]
it saves oil yeah
I think
um
good for reheating stuff yeah but I also
have a microwave um
foreign
for example reheat potato fries french
fries
um
even from like McDonald's
Dad they taste actually really good if
you put them in the airfryer
but
hmm I don't know if I would want to
really do that
um I don't trust them
although there are many times in my life
where I felt like when I left had some
leftover
um fries not left over but they were
already cold and then they don't taste
anymore and I want to eat them but you
know
um
I didn't have a moment like this for a
long time where I had leftover fries
though so if that ever happens maybe
I'll use my air fryer but
no I would definitely not put them into
the microwave though
yeah I'm making your own fries yeah I
need to try that with the airfryer I
haven't tried that yet but that
apparently is one of the best uses for
it
potato fries self made
um who the heck has leftover fries well
I mean there's cases where they're just
left over because
just because they're already uh cold
and I couldn't keep up with eating them
because I had a burger to eat as well
and that one will taste even more
terrible also if it's cold
um
good
foreign
[Music]
for this time just to get used a bit to
the airfryer
I wanted to
um
um I wanted to do something more simple
so this is what we did but maybe we can
do some more a little bit complicated
things or difficult things I wanted to
do that Korean thing
but
um I couldn't find those Korean rice
cakes uh so we're gonna do it another
time
and maybe I'll find something else
that's Korean that I can do in the same
stream in an Africa
maybe I wonder maybe Korean Fried
Chicken but like how do I make it
different from our Fried Chicken
[Music]
brussels sprouts
I don't think I dislike brussels sprouts
foreign
[Music]
to create air pockets
is that really a fact
what
[Music]
beer is commonly used in batters
probably heard of that before but never
a vodka
alcohol vaporizes and makes air pockets
[Music]
how about broccoli or cauliflower I hate
cauliflower but I love broccoli
yum yum yum yum
be a batter in common yeah I heard of
that yeah yeah
sounds crazy to me
foreign
[Music]
that's probably why they used it because
it has no taste
how does that make it worse
if its only purpose is to create the air
pockets and that's perfect
[Music]
last bite
foreign
[Music]
at that yeah
do not like it when I got you
was that enough for lunch yeah I
normally really don't eat lunch
um
so when I do it's usually something
small weenie
[Music]
yeah it was worth sacrificing Frank and
Esmeralda definitely
someone told me that making hot dogs in
the airfryer is highly recommended so I
do want to try that
uh
eventually because I like hot dogs
and I have a feeling that you could make
those
[Music]
um Korean hot dogs as well but
I feel like they would become really
really messy if I tried them
because they have so much stuff on top
of them
the corn dogs corn dogs
I don't know if corn dogs would work
would I mean it's almost the same thing
as the Korean Hot Dogs
Korean corn dogs
so good but like wouldn't the batter be
like
everywhere
I don't know
sounds difficult
but you have to experiment with air
fries and the people try out things just
for you know the sake of
making a fun Tick Tock where people have
their minds blown because they didn't
know you could do that in an air fryer
so I know I I we could
just have to experiment and come up with
something
basically as I said if you can bake it
if you can Grill it if you can fry it
then you can put it in the airfryer does
your if I have a baking option yes
that's probably what the the cake and
the bread icons are for yeah the one
that I have the one on the bottom left
over there is a lot of people use it a
lot of like YouTube cooking people use
this one so it's highly recommended and
that's why I got it
[Music]
um
does you ever have a yogurt makeup but
no and I don't want it anyway because I
don't really like yogurt that much
can I recommend cool sorry yeah I think
a lot of people have cool story
no I have not been watching tick tock
I watched Tick Tock videos that are
compilated in the compilation on YouTube
I don't know how to
go through tick tock
I'm too old for that [\h__\h] thank you
use a Phillips airfryer I think that was
also one of the recommended ones
[Music]
I'm a Zoomer now
no I'm not
I guess I mean maybe maybe I should take
it as a compliment
you Boomers
foreign
[Music]
yeah yeah
honestly oh [\h__\h] what this was one and a
half hours only damn it's good because I
still have to prepare everything for all
to look at
so I don't know
oh I think I'll read some super chats
but definitely not all of them because I
need to
um
still do everything
yeah
foreign
[Music]
makes me even more nervous because
um
[Music]
that was so fast I I like this fast
efficient cooking
we should do this way of efficient
cooking more often yeah baby
[Music]
a bit more usable thank you and I know I
know you guys like missed my cooking
streams I gotta say though like they
stretch
the the real ones
this was also stressful it's also always
a problem with like the camera setting
up the camera like in a way that works
and
captures things like in a good angle
a cult
uh I wish I could do that like perfect
Bird's point of view
uh
yeah position but uh I don't know
[Music]
place it in front of you it's in the way
it's just not so easy because it has to
be quite up high and you can't show too
much in in you know YouTubers cases you
know
only the hands not the body I mean here
you see my body and that's all you'll
get to see
but gotta be careful with the camera
he was a GoPro yeah but then you see
like all the surroundings too
when I turn my head and so on I'm
guessing you mean like put it on your
head
in theory that sounds like cool and
useful but not really in action
[Music]
the time
and where where did I stop last time
I hope you
just watch this around as well if if I
was surrounded by everything green
screen or sound and that would be fine
but yeah
yeah can't do that
entropy finale
how quick is quick very quick
yeah yeah yeah yeah all the reflections
on everything yeah and you can see my
feet is probably
Mr stream thanks to class they'll
probably just watch the archive
are We Done Yet yeah kind of yeah sorry
it was actually really fast but like
that's actually a good thing
I'm scrolling
remember no tangents I don't think I can
really do that but I'll still try to be
fast
spray paint the whole kitchen
oh no no please no my eyes will Court
[Music]
so did I read them or did I not read
them
I don't think I did okay
thank you
[Music]
oh
you meant the super chance oh
recommend wanting a vlog for those who
miss it yay
air fryer Chan did a good job at
providing me with a fast lunch thank you
air fryer John
I patted it
[Music]
foreign
I should have let everything probably in
the airfryer a bunch longer and next
time if I'm gonna do those mozzarella
sticks again I think I would leave the
mozzarella sticks with the breading in
the fridge I guess
not without I mean in the video there
was a lady that did it without the
breading uh
yeah but I guess next time it will
probably be helpful to freeze the whole
thing
and and then put it into the airfryer
and then water and longer maybe
and hopefully then it will not burst but
that
if you want to fry cheese that's just a
problem
but maybe it lost too much heat
in the time when I was waiting I don't
know I really can't tell because I have
I don't have much experience with the
airfryer
I will get there
at least I own an air fryer
clearly you don't own an air fryer
[Music]
okay so let me put up the thumbnails
representer uh wait let me change
these
done cooking
time now
foreign
and you're late and you're late
yeah I'm just gonna stay here please
take
it 47 day out thanks
kwj Duncan
uh
thank you when the moon
thank you
foreign
[Music]
actually even besides whole talk I have
a lot of things to do
I have to record some stuff
um
[Music]
I think I should go to sleep have good
time thank you have fun watching the
stream everyone thank you for coming at
least in the beginning
[Music]
maybe you are here too did you sleep
well did you sleep well dreaming of me
you probably when you woke up were
surprised seeing me still streaming
cause I think that stream was like nine
and a half hours long if you left at the
beginning that's a good chance that you
missed a big part but then woke up to
the end
properly
that's fun
just a regular day
[Music]
my birthday was this week and I just
want to say you're my favorite YouTuber
and you're such a huge inspiration to me
thanks for being you
[Music]
hope you had a great one
stay yourself stay being awesome
and stay being awesome listen
tea awesome properly
continue being awesome and yes they're
healthy I wish you all the best thank
you for supporting me
Dynamic Duncan bunny bunny bunny bunny
again thank you thank you Musashi
captain
[Music]
um
I think those are I don't mean Super
trans but thank you thank you for the
pinky
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
there's so many blue ones these are
early and then I don't know idle meeting
so early I don't think so
but apparently I was gone
[Music]
uh maybe around here it restarts
administrator of Sorrow donkey
I had two adult meetings oh I made tea
[Music]
I have two oh yeah huh I watched a clip
by the way of um
like the idol meeting
between me and fauna
I realized huh that I mean we're doing
it at the same time even though I
totally met her at the idol meeting I
don't know how she didn't notice I was
like right in front of her
foreign
[Music]
yeah medical chocolate is
um like not the like most high quality
chocolate but it's just that here even
our basic chocolate bars are [\h__\h]
good I love milk they also have like so
many different
um flavors
and variations and additions yeah
oh International sections
nice cool what kind of stuff do you have
on the international shells
I didn't
seen one when I was in America but I
didn't look so closely everything felt
International when I was in America
and I guess it wasn't a real Supermarket
where I was that was uh what was it
called again Target
yes I think it was Target I guess the
target is not really a supermarket
it's just a big
mix of everything to make it go crazy
and think you're insane
Walmart Walmart I was a Walmart not a
Target I think never mind
foreign
where we bought the Pop Tarts
[Music]
targets do have supermarkets
they put limbs until black on there so
the American chocolate though in the US
oh yeah I guess those are like really
really International so they're not even
in the international shelf they're so
International that they skipped the
inter and are now National
[Music]
firing
those Pop-Tarts were good are you
[\h__\h] kidding me no they're not
uh I found Pop Tarts in our Supermarket
the other day they started selling them
and
I bought some as a joke for my friend
she did not like them at all
she was forcing herself to eat them I
was like I just bought them as a joke I
know they're terrible like really you
don't have to eat them it's totally okay
I get it don't like feel free to throw
them away but I think she's the kind of
person who
doesn't want to throw things away but
she also was like in a in a real
conundrum because
she really hated them and she also did
not think that anyone else would
appreciate them around her so
[Music]
opinions do not understand you
you grow up
with Tides the only reason I guess why
you like them is because you grow up
with them or why you tolerate them but
even then even then it's crazy think
that this is being fed to children
[Music]
fully
depends on the flavor no they were all
[\h__\h]
somebody likes them
really though
really like
[Music]
liberated them
I think she just tolerated them
[Music]
and I think Japanese people
um they they make great food right but I
also think they
have a big tolerance scale
[Music]
I feel like they
a lot of them grow up to be raised to
eat absolutely everything
like in terms of like vegetables and so
on so they will you know they eat they
eat everything they make also good use
of everything that is part of an animal
they don't throw away [\h__\h] and that's a
good thing obviously like I would say
that I
um
should um
cut off a slice of that bread and
become the bread
um
kind of messed up let's say
yeah but because of their not wasteful
culture I think that's why she's also
able to tolerate something like that
better
even yourself are you snack box oh
a lot of the stuff that you recommend oh
here
oh cool did you get Kinder chocolate
there's so many different ones you need
to try them all you need to try to clean
the country kinda Bueno and kinda
bonbons Kingdom
[Music]
um
the normal one
the the little sticks
I like the card ones I don't like the
card ones actually
oh okay no bueno is [\h__\h] amazing
that's the stick yeah
[Music]
I was I could like
Kindle buns nowadays I would go for like
kinda Bueno Kinder country but when I
was a bit younger kind of bonbons were
like
[Music]
irresistible
absolutely irresistible
kind of penguin not my favorite my
brother it was funny that
um you know they're here you have kinda
Penguins it's like a a cold chocolate
milk sandwich
and then there's
um
which is in theory by description
similar but it's very different and I
was the ministry the type of person and
my brother was the
um kinder penguin type of person so
my mom would have to buy both to make us
both happy but they were both considered
expensive so I didn't get them often
um
versus Mexican yeah Mexican nobody
really I think Master King is the least
popular out of those for me
foreign
simple but good
I like the milkiness
[Music]
salmonella scandal in Kinder chocolate
didn't know of that
[Music]
okay
okay where was I there I went to
attaches but it was super chat related
still
[Music]
thank you
I'm glad to see you Becky one one last
month was my two years and change with
kfp change
last move with my two years and change
with kfp what does that mean
the way you are auto corrected and you
meant something else I hope the next
projects go up about any troubles and
that
can we use in a bit to use and change
means two years and a bit I've never
heard that before
[Music]
like spare change
well I mean again when you say that
that's so songs we hear it
wow I learned something
wow
[Music]
the troubles and that you and the rest
of her life have everything go smoothly
according
thank you
yeah uh next project well well thank you
there are continuously always ongoing
projects and
I'm preparing actually yesterday I
booked my flight ticket
um for
yeah
[Music]
I am treating myself to uh a premium
economy yay
actually that wasn't even a normal
economy available for some reason so
straight went to the premium economy
premium economy actually was a fine
price wise
um
um I'm just uh quite worried about
accommodation because after booking a
ticket I was looking for accommodations
and holy Shinto I have a problem like
so I want to
um stream because I'll be there for a
while
um but I'll be staying for like
a little bit less than a month
it's my plan
[Music]
um so if I want something that is
more or less a little bit soundproof it
will be [\h__\h] expensive because first
of all all the airbnbs they're not
soundproof even if I get my own
apartment I would have to get a whole
house and even the houses are not
um soundproof
and I was just looking for the prices I
know that some of the
better hotels in Japan have
um relatively
okay-ish sound proof rooms
that's what I was thinking Alex but wait
so I was looking for the prices but for
a whole month
it goes from not the whole not even the
whole month like less like maybe three
weeks or so it goes from four thousand
the least and then I'm still not very
sure if it would really be sound proof
to
[Music]
000 total
and I'm like
um
I thought I don't want to spend that
much for that so my idea is
stay in a normal place
and then
do almost only of collapse
visit everyone ask them if it's okay to
stream on my channel do awful lots of
everybody in their Apartments
have basically almost only of collabs
for almost a whole month
um
yeah
I think they would you know
let me in do some off collapse there's
so many members that I have yet to
um meet
and then every once in a while I'll try
to do like a
a solo stream a whisper a quiet solo
stream during the day
if I can yeah
this is the way
staring at the office is also possible
Right
[Music]
no because it's always like full but
I guess they do have like uh
a non you know motion capture
room that I've used before that maybe
would not be
in permanent use
I might
I might ask about it but yeah I will I
will um explore some options I do want
to stay in a nice hotel but holy [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] Tokyo is so expensive that made me
just think once again that Soul really
was not that expensive
[Music]
and
um I guess it's also because
long term if it's that price but only
for a week it's like acceptable but for
almost a month it's crazy
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I could totally go like to the outskirts
of Tokyo is what I was saying because
they were like recommending it on in the
Japanese
call it like the outskirts yeah
yeah before too and
two and all that but I wanna like um you
know do stuff while I'm there and it
would be nicer to be in the central uh
in the center of Tokyo to like be able
to go everywhere from the center and
fast and
um
yeah and then yeah I need to I would
need to take long train rides to go
anywhere
[Music]
I sent
can you buy me souvenirs nah
no
I'll probably will barely have space
force my
[Music]
um
bunk I don't want to sleep over for a
whole month at people's places because I
want my privacy too and I know that they
want their privacy as well
so that's not an option I don't see that
as an option maybe like for one night at
Marlin's place
but besides that
no
I don't I don't want to force myself
until
anyone for a whole month and also I I
want my primary Street too I me
but yeah we can finally do the money
inside my off collab sleep over that was
supposed to happen like two years ago
yay
I'm excited I'm excited
oh yeah I can also visit Cali at her
place again
Joey Kelly might let me do a solo stream
in her place I feel like she would not
mind
she probably would just let me do my
thing
can we can we can we touch Karu
tuscaru can we
this is why why
[Applause]
hi yeah
[Music]
it's not properly finger painting when
you have to use gloves guys
but it would kind of work with those
plastic gloves that I used today but the
the thing about fingerprint finger
painting is that you use your own hands
[Music]
yeah but I'll definitely visit
as many people as I can so that I can do
streams on my channel from someone
else's place because they live there and
they stream there so they must have
um a streaming environment where there
is
a decent soundproofing
[Music]
so yeah
it's genius Strat I know they were
probably therefore be a lot of like chip
Japanese heavy streams though
because most of them don't speak English
you know we can do like Cali Iris Louis
[Music]
oh my God I can meet at tomorrow
but besides them
it's probably mostly nihongo
[Music]
I need to now that I finally booked my
flight ticket running to finally like
start asking hey is this date open can I
reserve that for me please hang out with
me
foreign
so my streaming times will be very
different for a whole month
um but
I think there will be streams during
daytime Japanese time and during evening
time both just not morning time that
will not happen not before I die
[Music]
um
EU friendly streams yeah well for a
while but uh
well Japanese evening is afternoon in
you so
too bad
[Music]
foreign
I mean they probably all will be like
shorter streams since they're off
collabs
yeah yeah yeah generally
um
like maybe I don't know two hours most
of them roughly so it will not be
difficult to catch up on them
anyway let's go back to Super chatos I
was at Doc attacks Super Chat
oh
see the donkeys
so these are flash shots again Tai Chi
thank you for the recipe
good morning good morning titanium
and Tucson Super Chat in the beginning
of the stream too
you didn't sleep in between though did
you
did you
I thought you stayed the whole time
[Music]
well you might interest some new
potential game females to tag along with
a part-time following you
Oh you mean like new viewers well who
knows
I hope my Japanese viewers will remember
that I exist
I will remind them when I stream in
Japanese prime time
um
long tangent even though I said I had no
time
but it's an important thing to say
very important
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you for sharing that thank you
did I forget the Christmas
[Music]
extensions
thank you you guys all those people who
like send money because they got a Bonus
or a raise or it was their birthday or
so
[Music]
you guys need to be more selfish
and it's not even selfish
use that money on yourself but thank you
guys
thank you for inspiring me to do my best
even on rough days you're so very
important to all of us and bring so much
comfort and kindness
[Music]
yeah thank you
it's let's stream to you do you do you
but yeah I hope you had some leftover
for yourself Tara Tara it's important
be be more selfish
I'm having I'm being selfish but having
you read my Super Chat yeah but no no
do you eat tarantula now
[\h__\h] no
hell no
hi happy belated birthday
relations
[Music]
um
I love this music
thank you for the pinky
and thanks for spoiling us with another
long stream boss you're a big brain
gamer lots of fun please buy a check out
dinner with the Super Chat thank you I
don't need to take out dinner doll
because I'm cooking so much for myself
but I did go
um yesterday to a restaurant had some
Japanese food yesterday but generally
um this money is useful anyway for my
subscription because it's quite
expensive
thank you
it's interesting questions
[Music]
that's the last one for entry presenter
thank you guys for watching that long
ass stream
Brio
[Music]
foreign
I should because I won't be running
super chats after Hollow talk
[Music]
and then what do I have to prepare
afterwards
questions I still didn't pick the
questions and then translate the
questions make the graphics
um and my questions
I feel like this there's a bunch more
things I can't think of
ah the thing is like I need to
do the pre-recording but I I can't seem
to do it today because schedules don't
align or like the actually the world is
not ready yet so how to do it tomorrow
night after Pokemon Maybe
foreign
[Music]
I hope it goes well
to put that reading stream next week no
I don't have much time next week
[Music]
because I'm going on a trip next week
Dominican for the pinky I seem to have
revived two years went by fast those
wings make operating to fry away easier
thanks for everything you do for kfp
thank you too happy Revival Day oh two
years thank you for staying remember for
such a long time
and you say operating the fryer
is way easier with the wings but can you
actually grab things properly
I mean I guess the dude behind me is
doing quite well and oh wow that one is
even carrying the the order
you guys are really talented really
skilled you just make it work impressive
those chickens in the in you know normal
people's yards
they can't do stuff like this
so just
definitely
[Music]
below the floor it's too small I don't
know it doesn't have the strength he
doesn't have a thumb that's the problem
it's hard to flip something with a
flipper when you don't have a thumb I
think that's the issue
[Music]
get on our level
proud give me train chicken down you've
evolved beyond the average chicken
yes you did
Evolution that's how Evolution works
[Music]
thank you
that's right it's not like Kotori is
completely gone
soon Mary Pippin thank you soon for the
recipe chat
sometime last year Sparks gave me the
motivation to find a better job I'm
happy to report that I love my current
second job after kfp
enjoy my co-workers and I'm able to
avoid owning my own condo I'm putting
this on your boss next challenge
learning to cook oh wow
damn I'm happy for you
congratulations
but it's not only on me it's on YouTube
you worked hard for this so
congratulations and I'm glad you enjoy
your job so much and that your
co-workers are nice hmm I'm happy to
hear that you're enjoying life and
making the most out of it
keep on doing that
wish you the best
I needed the motivation
that's understandable yeah
it's so worth it right
yeah find out
soon
[Music]
um
thank you for two pinkies I don't think
there's enough space on the Super Chat
nor enough word to describe how much you
mean to us where where
finally come from I don't want to know
you with my messages but I love
supporting you and it makes every single
chicken happy to want your content we
always look forward to another kiwawa
stream I hope you realize that you are
giving us the best time every day I'm
enjoying every single moment with you
and kfb and I wouldn't trade the time I
get with all of you with anything else
I love you guys too but where did that
come from why why are we so so wholesome
what happened I was just slaying the
Spire minding my own Spire business
thank you so much for the sweet words
[Music]
you guys have too much love to give
don't ya me too me too
me too I feel you
can relate
[Music]
I could stretch it
thank you for the ticket you know
recently I wake up every morning with a
[\h__\h] dry as [\h__\h]
dead throat
that feels like like this
is so bad
[Music]
is it worth getting uh not until I get
sponsored until then I will not
recommend it
yeah I need to turn on the humidifier
I guess
[Music]
the season of humidifiers yeah
there was a
it's in there I was wondering is it
because they left out so many letters I
thought like I don't know I didn't want
to point it out in case profile felt
embarrassed about leaving out so many
letters are all the left out letters a
word then
oh my God
okay
do
[Music]
you think you
do
[Music]
bee doobies
boobies
[Music]
I'm gonna say I'm a chicken you little
[\h__\h]
uh
uh I don't know if
chipkin was supposed to be an eye or an
e there because you're already writing
it like
not how it's supposed to be written
I couldn't assume it's an eye so I
[Music]
um
set
Z
foreign
[Music]
like
Bamboozled me like that by making a
hidden message telling me I'm a chicken
nah you're not that type of person of
course it was a sweet message even in
between the lines
it means you are unique or one of a kind
more like one of a kind in that case
[Music]
you're so sweet
I'm happy I thought this was gonna be
you are a chicken so
profile I am
not disappointed
[Music]
good chicken good chicken very good
chicken
very good
travel D thank you for the pinky
[Music]
paint and refund my sneeze chat from the
entropy streams okay sometimes times
four oh why did they do that so
I'll ever have a relevant time to ask is
so flock it if we ever have a bad movie
night like when we watch cats I was
talking about that was a good movie
night can we watch Kung Pow I love the
hell out of the movie but I acknowledge
it's bad so bad and it's humor isn't a
quiet taste to say the least but at
least I saw that it's free on YouTube so
no one will have to waste money oh
I don't know I have never heard of that
movie
I think you'd like Kung Pao really
I love that movie it's fun to watch hey
it doesn't it seems very popular this is
the bad movie night then
[Music]
so so bad that it's good then it's not
bad
so bad it's good they're bubbles
[Music]
uh thank you Trevor G for the idea
not very
convinced at the moment
because I already tried to keep
um movie Wanted Longs at the minimum and
then using one of those
to watch a supposedly bad movie that I'm
not so quite interested in at the moment
yeah
but next time I ask for a movie one to
Long recommendations you guys can tell
me uh and recommend it and then I'll
consider it again
[Music]
um
we didn't have one in a while though so
the next member stream might be
um a one too long
section substitute Junction uh thank you
ribbon thank you soon
eating Mike Tyson's ass concussion it's
the second time you showed up recently
August friends one for everyone
Phoenix fairy shiny Hunter thank you
soon thank you
no I have not
Daniel gold thank you thank you
brand induction is
[Music]
I could compete for Germany
they opened applications
open until 28th of November
thank you
I just think
it's kind of weird
to compete for other countries
because if I was there I want to
represent Austria
even if I made it
I would want to represent my own country
[Music]
it's
um
but don't you have to
apologize apply with an original song
available
[Music]
where's that where where can I find that
yeah you have to send in a song
oh
one that has yet to be published that's
the problem I don't think I can make a
song so fast
[Music]
huh
does it say anything uh usually as far
as I know is you have to apply for
someone that has yet to be published
City random
you guys ridiculous
[Music]
it is a bit
um endearing but as I said I I would
feel weird representing Germany even if
I made it
may have been any day after first of
September 2022
foreign
[Music]
the only problem I have is that do you
is not made for
singing it live really and Eurovision
song contest you always have to sing
live
and the new year is so difficult to sing
alone live
there's like no breaks even worse than
Sparks
tell Kira next time we make a song to
put in some [\h__\h] breaks
[Music]
I mean if I put it do you
even though I'm not from Germany is
German so you know we would be a a
German Austrian Duo which I think kind
of works
foreign
at least it's different than you know
maybe someone from Italy applying for
Germany
someone from Austria playing for Germany
makes a bit more sense
[Music]
are you listening
do do
I'll think about it
[Music]
oh finger point
I already completely gave up on that to
be honest hmm
does you know I feel like Austria
um Austrian
rarely wins rarely does well except for
some you know really rare
uh exceptions
and and I feel like Germany wants to do
generally better
what I'm trying to say is that I think
Austria would be more open to risk
something like that
just for the sake of becoming a topic
um even if they know that the chances of
winning are gonna be low
you know what I mean I think Germany
might want to go for a safe choice but
the thing is
it's it should not be about winning it
should be about the participation that's
it for me and also it should be the same
for the organizers because if you can
put a [\h__\h] 3D YouTuber on your stage
and be like this is how our
representation you you're gonna be the
Hot Topic of Eurovision song contest
and we all know that bad
uh what's the word bad like not um media
not medium but like any way to get
people to talk about you even if it's
not 100 positive it's still good you're
bad press I mean I wouldn't say it's bad
press but you know people have been
gonna be like what is that
but still
if you do something crazy like that
you're gonna get all the eyes on you
yeah no such thing as bad publicity
that's what I wanted to say
[Music]
so Germany should consider it
headlines
and honestly
song and the people who watch Eurovision
I think are generally very open to crazy
things because Eurovision always has
crazy [\h__\h] going on crazy acts and weird
songs and weird people performing it is
a thing that's what your original song
contest is all about
so we would just one-up them with the
craziest thing you could possibly put on
there at the moment
and I do think the audience is quite
open to it
yeah they are known for its weirdness
exactly that's why I feel like
it would be
foreign
[Music]
they would just have to be able to
organize it so that we can do it like a
Hatsune Miku kind of concert you know
[Music]
um
you know with those kind of screens
[Music]
and that would probably uh have to be
like
organized and paid for but uh German
um like the people who are behind the
German team
[Music]
wonder if they wanna
look into that
[Music]
people gonna think I'm an AI
you think so
[Music]
I'm just gonna think oh my God she's an
anime
oh my God there's an anime on stage like
oh my God is that like Sailor Moon or
like Naruto mommy look
it's not Naruto Naruto Naruto
[Music]
yes child I am I am an anime
oh believe it believe it nehruto
[Music]
oh man well thank you for the info on
Title Cross
I think I'll just try applying and see
what happens
maybe that was just ignore me you know
but at least um I tested the waters I
can't say I can't say that I regretted
regret not even trying
oh my oh my oh my
[Music]
squeeze your thumb scars
sorry Austria you're missing out
soon principal flame Duncan Robin thank
you soon Robin thank you soon again
thank you welcome
first time I'd actually vote I also
never voted
hmm
you can only vote inside of Europe
though right
so you all have to come to Europe buy a
throwaway phone and vote for me please
thank you
I'll name your vaults
everyone come on a trip to Europe
now you have any new phone you can't do
it for the internet I think
[Music]
Australia yeah Australia can vote Yes
as far as I know because they also
participate
[Music]
you don't need a phone number
but I guess you need a European IP or so
oh that's like hella
[Music]
oh they should do phones like
have they ever heard of vpns
how Boomer are they have they never
heard of vpns
[Music]
foreign
I'm not gonna say anything
[Music]
that will also be competing this year
what
[Music]
uh Eurovision is uncontained with
Australia and Canada
[Music]
okay
so you guys can also just go to Canada
and vote from Canada
that's an option
crony can represents Canada well
[Music]
do you do you say you do feel the
science fight me
the same oh do you do you
okay that kind of got me in a funny mood
that whole idea
it would be so funny people are gonna be
like what the [\h__\h]
your football club is incredible thank
you
happy birthday in your shoe when's
birthday is it
tick
[Music]
reactions would be Priceless yeah I feel
like even like news programs would pick
it up and be like at um at this year's
Eurovision song contest oh this
incredible thing happened something
called a YouTuber performed uh to
represent Germany let's uh we we got an
exclusive interview with the YouTuber
takanashikiwawa to ask her is she an
anime is she Sailor Moon
[Music]
laughs
breaking news V2 will win two hours
no I don't want to imagine that
oh man
it is in fact Naruto no her sister is
Hatsune Miku
[Music]
oh my God
voiced by Chris Pratt
oh oh no the thing is like if I won it
wouldn't even be us 300 will be hosting
the real real version after that it
would be Germany that's so sad
oh well
sorry Austria
sorry I'm German now
okay so the person
[Music]
thank you
after that stream help
s
Scorpio thank you oh
I don't know you can use any of them
oh yeah yeah have fun with the Ironclad
enjoy
from Australian to Austrian to German
that's how it goes
[Music]
Goku wins your probation
I love you here now but I hope you hear
this happy birthday
not an outcome function thank you
I want to ask what got you into
streaming
[Music]
I think it's uh I was really
um I know
I felt like communicating with people I
didn't have
many friends and I wanted like
specifically
um I want to learn Japanese while
streaming and I wanted Japanese people
to like me I mean that was quite the
weeaboo way of thinking but yeah yeah
that's all I'll say
um but that was a long time ago alcohol
Kiana my birthday is in six days but I
will send this Super Chat since I won't
have six days
someone sat won't have time to send it
for about three weeks since I got a new
job what
good why for about three weeks do you
only have this job for three weeks
thank you so much for every fun moment I
had the pleasure to watch with you and
kfcu you are amazing and I will ask us
about you if you say no
[Music]
if I say no no to what
happy birthday six days is the six days
ago 15 no it's two days ago never mind
not happy birthday yet but early Loki
happy birthday
oh uh if I say I'm not amazing
hey I'm not amazing
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I hope you're only busy for three weeks
and after that you'll settle down
hopefully come back to me
I'm gonna cry I'm gonna put you in my
airfryer
[Music]
thank you
you here forever thank you
[Music]
okay Germans in the chat say hi say
hello say something German's in the chat
Germans in the Chant raise your hands
oh so many would you mind if I
represented your country
in Eurovision song condensed
[Music]
would be good for once I don't know
about that
oh
can't get any worse so no
[Music]
totally totally unbiased sample is
totally it is totally unbiased
okay sounds like a yes
[Music]
rpwnkt Junction for the pinky
oh the super about Alice madness Returns
reminds me it's my second anniversary
watching you oh I'm proud you reached so
many goals this second year I will
continue admiring you and supporting you
as always I love that you are my Aussie
oh my second year so oh you also kind of
found me during that time of Alice
Banner's returns was that two years ago
[Music]
no
that was one year ago ah okay okay so
this one was even one more year okay I
would have felt really weird if it was
two years ago I knew there was something
wrong
I just reminded you of that huh so what
did I do two years ago at this time
rpw nkt are you here also thank you El
Canal wheel did you hear it worked but
do you know what I said
probably not right you're just sending
it in case
fire oh no
didn't I play Fire Emblem like around
January February
at the time
thank you
foreign
[Music]
played that so long
foreign
[Music]
interesting
I don't think that the next Fire Emblem
game will take so long though because
I'm better at
playing long games now
[Music]
I think I would be faster this time
around
[Music]
what there's a special Tick Tock
influencer application this year
foreign
wait but where is that and I'm just
seeing a normal one
[Music]
oh
there's like a questionnaire why do you
want to participate in Eurovision
sounding as 20 23s how long do you make
music were you on TV before was I on TV
before
[Music]
I mean if you if you play YouTube on
your TV
[Music]
I don't think I was on
short TV before right
damn
but there is I'm I'm I'm on a DVD and
that's cooler the third fast DVD
um I'm on there
[Music]
median oh
please upload a photo of yourself
a picture of myself
you know this
[Music]
oh
I'm gonna think I'm [\h__\h] joking
around making fun of them I'm so serious
though
[Music]
haha
spicy fan art no
[Music]
am I just gonna like send a picture like
this
[Music]
just like that
that's just that
this is gonna stand up it's that's the
thing yes it will stand out in their
applications will they take it seriously
depends on who's looking at them I hope
whoever looks through those is not a
complete Boomer
[Music]
for watching me for so long
so happy to have you around please don't
[Music]
thank you soon
I'm done okay I'll end it here
I think I have to do work
[Music]
I'm not gonna I'm gonna write this
application now
[Music]
hey
foreign
[Music]
just right into Genoa first
no it's not Elena board I'm just typing
very aggressively
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
foreign
I have to bring it back
[Music]
whose address do I put in
okay to put
um
like
maybe the fan mail address in
[Music]
I'm so excited
yeah
I guess that should be fun and
[Music]
yeah it's fine
I'm feeling fine and I just can't hide
it
[Music]
okay I have to wait for it
um approval from above from the heavens
first but
say no
I can't
but don't get your hopes up you know I
might not even make it into like their
consideration they might just put me in
the spam folder
and that's okay well you know we just
have to try at least you know hmm
yeah we have to at least try okay
it would be so funny
[Music]
ah okay
uh so I will go now I I need to [\h__\h]
get some [\h__\h] work done so in German
we say Alvin
um
tomorrow I'll see you at whole taco and
then afterwards I am planning to stream
Pokemon
oh
I'll see you there I just woke up sorry
you can watch The Vault though I would
appreciate it
um
you have to hear the crunch that I
created
thank you guys for watching
and go get yourself some lunch get
yourself some mozzarella sticks all
right
yeah
my mind guys
guys
[Music]
send me those Evolutions please the real
ones please someone one person is enough
on Twitter
I'll be waiting bye-bye
[Music]
foreign