[Music]
w
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
it's here I'm not talking to her yet
though hold on
that was obnoxious of me I I did
something kind of strange I I zoomed in
and out way too much sorry I'm going to
go say hi to you
all hold on I'm entering now here I
go tickling me oh sorry was I tickling
you
oh oh
sorry yeah I was just just so you know
you you didn't surprise me at all
because oh yeah I I cannot be surprised
I cannot be pranked back okay well it
wasn't like I pranked you okay well it
wasn't necessarily about surprising you
it was about it was about Annoying You
by making myself really big and then
making myself really small and then
making myself really big again and then
making myself you though oh well I yeah
I'll move you is this okay for you yeah
that's cool okay very distant that's
okay though I understand you know you
know what I'm doing I know what you're
doing I'm going to do the same thing
actually which means w go bye-bye oh
there she go bye-bye by the way did you
watch did you ever happen to watch like
a clip of the prank oh I saw actually I
saw I saw it on Twitter
actually I saw I see you you are I came
in like several times the clips I think
lots of the clips didn't even like put
all the moments in they cut a few even
so I came in and then I waited a while
and then I left and then chat was like
oh k k k and it took you it always took
you a while until you noticed oh
yeah sounds about right and by the time
that you noticed that the chat is saying
something I was already gone and that
repeated like several times oh yeah yeah
it was pretty funny honestly well I kept
looking every time that you showed up I
happened to be looking at
Minecraft yeah even I also look at
Minecraft you know in my middle screen
but I I think I would notice like on my
other screens if something's happening
you know if someone joins the room scre
guess you guys got it covered up they're
too big
there's there's just not enough I don't
have enough eyeball to look at
everything all the time look please
understand yo why is it so
big is your UI also big it's so weird
cuz usually the game is the game screen
oh it's cuz maybe it's cuz I made
jackbox really big oh gosh oh okay okay
I can't control the UI if the Minecraft
UI is big I can tell you how to make it
smaller oh that's okay yeah no I I
figured out how to do it thankfully to
make the UI the UI smaller and it's been
a lifesaver especially when fly
oh oh zombie gone even though I gave him
a [\h__\h] name a that's weird maybe some
an asteroid came from the sky and killed
him or
something what is shame okay we can find
another one easily if we just don't put
torches down somewhere but that's sad I
I used a freaking name tag on that one a
well he was covered too that's all right
these things happen
happened rude rude rude rude or is he
like did he like glitch down what
there's a Golem there's a goem is he is
he with my wait a second Golem
oh okay wait how did I not notice the
Golem before Oh my God probably killed
the zombie wow what the heck do we put
him in a boat wait are my villagers
there were they kill they can't no way
there's no way because there's a fence
okay there's all good all good with my
villagers
oh that's good news ah the Golem spawned
probably because of my villagers but
wouldn't the zombie have to be like is
it because the zombie was relatively
close to the villagers to my villagers
oh and then somehow really the villagers
sensed it and then called for the h Chad
says try to fight
[Music]
him can you leash or boat a a Golem chat
that would be helpful well he's kind of
small he's much smaller than I thought
he would be it's a little guy
a he he feels him please no I don't he's
a small King he's a small short King I
mean short
King you can leash him oh okay cool
Kelly this could be our first Golem I
mean they'll spawn automatically anyway
once the contraption is finished but
nice you got to start building just
literally wait no let's leave him here
because he will protect us whenever some
shitty enemy spawns yeah let's call him
Iron Giant Iron Giant yeah iron GI
should I give him a name we don't have
any more name tags I think actually oh
dang it and those are kind of rare hard
to come by
right we we used to have so many I feel
like but nowadays they're not showing up
anymore
dang it's okay it's okay I guess if if
it spawns once it will spawn twice yeah
oh you know what you know what actually
chat says maybe he killed the zombie
yeah yeah yeah yeah I said that too duh
I'm sorry I just I look it's been a long
day it's been a really long day wait
have you greeted your viewers yet you
can do that if you want oh hi everyone
like I'm so sorry I um I'm just a bit
I'm a bit scatterbrain today I had a 7
hour recording session was standing the
whole time my God yeah and I didn't I
only had like 4 hours of sleep hi
everyone they let you sit don't you feel
like asking for like recording while
sitting or you want to stand oh I want
to stand so I can use my
diaphragm oh for singing Because I I've
heard of some people who just like sit
down while recording because it's more
comfortable for them honestly when I
record stuff from home I sit down too so
that's super normal yeah yeah but I
prefer that yeah I just kind of like
especially for S hours yeah 7 hours long
time really very long not a lot your
voice okay no I did a scream I did a
scream song today
scream yeah screel song it pretty pretty
cool but it was definitely a lot of it
was hard unravel the W unraveling the
wall or something like that and then I
recorded two other songs as well but
there were like features and stuff like
that so it was like half a song kind of
yeah just busy I'm okay though I I
wanted to stream today because I want to
get this iron farm working I just yes
got to put my nose to the grindstone you
know so many am freaking do it yeah wow
and and a skirlington horse oh my god
let's
go call I do want to say um thank you
for being so committed to this I really
appreciate it being here a lot heck yeah
I want to help even if I'm useless I
want to help be a part of everything
here I'm doing my best you're not
useless girl thank you I'm learning the
ropes little by little let's see you're
going to be employee of the day if you
finish that iron farm employee oh cool
okay I want to be employee of the day
that sounds like a high arm yes yeah and
cobbly St all right let me watch I got
to watch that tutorial though and I know
yeah the audio is going to come through
so I need to find a way to not let you
hear that hold on although I don't know
maybe it would be easier for you um
instead of adjusting that tutorial to
less Hoppers finding an actual tutorial
that has only like Hoppers or so yeah
from the getg go that's like built for
that that might be a good idea I wonder
if I can find one let's see Farm
Minecraft
1.15 two
Hoppers it's very specific yeah I wonder
if it comes up like that I hope
so let's
see
um it it's got to be a small one low
effort one missing Hoppers the word
Hoppers is missing from all of these
that's okay I'm going to try and make it
put in the description and maybe I can
do some more Mining and get more iron
blocks or something ah look up look up
um i i n xo4 i
nxo in one word I x04 and then like iron
farm or so Ian
xo4 yeah I A N sorry oh it's okay in
iron
farm you find him iron farm on day one
okay okay I think I did
oh let's see okay I just make sure that
he's doing it for 1.15 but chat it says
1.16 to
1.20 a 1.16 onwards huh does he have
others other ones it does look pretty
simple no Lava needed either no name tag
any zombie will work easy loading
villagers and zombie into Farm ooh I
mean it looks nice it's a 30 minute
tutorial why they why they all got to be
so
long yeah is what it
is
see all right I'm looking I'm looking
I'm looking it should work don't think
they've changed the spawn mechanics in
1.16 okay they think it works okay this
it better be working okay gotcha I'm
going to turn music off really quick so
I can listen to his
speech I hope the base is
similar okay let's see if you need to
mute me to watch that don't worry about
it it's okay you you're fine you're
fine no
problem oh yeah chat little
update uh so there there was indeed a
problem with you know overlap not
overlapping with the Stream but like
overlapping with preparations of gaa's
birthday stream so we got to figure out
a different
time um I'm trying to get everybody's uh
answers soon as possible that we can
maybe do it on the weekend how did you
get out what the
hell hopefully we can do it on the
weekend but then if we do it on the
weekend I was thinking um obviously I'm
taking tomorrow off cuz like I feel
like we won't really have anything to do
uh until the end so I think it's fine if
we all just like chill until the last
stream um so yeah that's probably uh
hopefully what's going to happen and
then everybody can you know do some
other streams if they want until that
point like Kelly's doing Red Dead
Redemption stuff right red dead I'm
going to do my member stream my watch
along and I'm going to do the the
soccer stream and stuff so I think well
it's maybe good that we all have like a
small break and then we can continue
slaying the game yeah yeah that's that
would be the ideal plan at this
point now chat could you do you know the
date and time I guess it's good as usual
streaming time but but do you know the
date what's the actual date for gaa's
birthday stream cuz I don't have her in
my calendar anymore for some
reason and you know
everything
620 so tomorrow okay I mean for me it
will be the day after tomorrow even I
suppose cuz it's going to be like 2 a.m.
in the
night okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay
I want to say sorry for being boring I'm
watching this tutorial but I think the
farm will drop enough for you to craft
okay see this dude is yeah he's
definitely like um he's like f he's like
mining mining um let's
see on a sec trench into a three oh man
he's quick that's okay we'll figure it
out he's like he like goes into the
ground so I I feel like we can't go into
the ground so I'm just gonna all right
calm that chill my dude 3
a 3 a.m. okay okay okay good to know
yeah that makes sense that um that
wouldn't work out and that's fine no
problem I fought I saw a thumbs up but
looking back there was no thumbs up I
must have like mixed something up that's
okay it
happens let me figure out is it a 3X3
let's see one okay he's going down three
three
three okay who focused cie watching
tutorial
focused like a 3X3 in
the there are three beds lined up all
right I think I got it and then there's
like a bunch of trap doors okay here's
what I'm going to do in order to kind of
mimic what's going on here um okay might
as well hey hey hey chat you guys are
mesmerizing wow that's nice cuz I feel
like I'm not very mesmerizing right now
I'm going to build something to dig
into oh yep cuz my peanut brain can't
handle things like this unless they're
exactly as shown in the tutorial you see
okay okay so I'm just going to Fig it
out I'm just going to build ground for
me to dig
into
yeah peanut
brain of you learning like even such
difficult things that even I don't do
like building a fuing iron farm I want
to try well I mean I made the haunted
house work that one time right oh oh
yeah that had a hop wait do you mean
yeah there was like ha house yeah for
Halloween of last year um we did like a
little um haunted house and then I
invited Advent to come check it out and
like people did little contributions and
and I followed a blueprint for most of
that until like maybe the last 10% 15 %
but it was I don't know it was it was
nice to try to actually do something you
know instead of being like ah well this
looks too difficult I guess I won't do
it you know mhm it was cool I'm glad
you're evolving I tried I'm
trying I do be trying so be patient with
me cuz I and Bae made a pumpkin yeah she
made a pumpkin and a pumpkin and a
pumpkin yeah there was some cool stuff
going on it was fun but Halloween I want
to try and do more things
you know I can if I if I really try and
put my nose to the
grindstone dang I couldn't wink because
my eyes were put my nose to the
grindstone don't put your nose to the
grindstone that new nose is precious we
want to keep it don't grind it okay yeah
true I don't want to grind it back down
to a stump that'll be a
way do you like your new nose I do look
look at how so big but it's not like
it's not annoying big it's like just big
enough to make me
happy you know cute good SI nose it
gives you more personality than you
already had wow dang I'm happy was that
a lot was that a lot big nose big big
personality right yeah big
personality all right I'm going to start
using other blocks instead of just
probably should put some torches down
nose energy nose
nosy B no nose yeah big nose team
congrats on your nose thank you my nose
surgery nose surgery went well that's
the actual surgery that you have actual
surgery I had is nose
surgery I don't tell anyone it's a
secret they can tell want we don't want
we don't want people to know the nose
knows though the nose nose the nose
knows that's a you get it it's a dad
it was Father's Day recently felt
appropriate is Father's day like
directly 1 month after Mother's Day oh
kind of like a white day Valentine's Day
kind of thing yeah is it cuz that's the
feeling the feeling I got might be
wrong a no
no it felt like one month apart but I
could be extremely wrong chat's more
knowledgeable on Father's day than I am
to be completely honest Mother's Day is
in March that's pretty much one month
apart oh just about just about a oh I
saw did you see of of course you saw the
height tweet right oh yeah I did that
was Happy Father's Day
K I saw that did you see my reply you
did you wanted to know why they didn't
do one for Mother's Day yeah what the
hell yeah and you know hey's been kind
of teasing me and kfp mhm like the way
they're like replying to me and stuff
and then CB's like oh my God is she
getting a hide case is she getting a
hide case in fact I'm not like so far
there's no no like talks about that at
all but they keep on getting everybody's
hopes up and
teasing ask for one what are you doing
ask forone I don't really I I I I don't
know I I don't want to like
I don't want to do something like that
uh
[Music]
when I I'm not sure like those items I
feel like it's maybe hard
to sell because it's relatively
expensive and big and I see not
everybody wants to buy a new case yeah I
know so I'm not very confident in it
selling so well but it's not really my
decision if they think that I should do
one and they think it would sell well
then they would they would probably hit
me up I gu I makes sense I don't know
when it comes to whether it sells or not
I don't really care about that I'm just
kind of like oh I think some dead beats
wanted PC case and also I want a PC case
so all right so it did you originally
did you go to them and you were like hey
I I can we do also one because who was
first let me see I think it was wasn't
it ba it was Bae and the
croner yeah yeah I'm pretty sure okay so
you actually spoke up about it okay okay
yeah I was like I wanted and then it
turns out that I think um one of the Hy
people I'm like they Oshi or something
like that I I didn't know that I was
like me you I'm your okay yeah it was
cool so they were more than delighted to
do that they're like yeah you w you got
it I was very happy I don't know yet how
it's decided though but I did say yeah
it would be cool if we had a PC case for
the the beats and they're like all right
we'll see if they'll do it and they say
yeah okay okay hold I did that with
something else um so yeah that that does
work sometimes but chat just so you know
that's not how it always works like
usually they they hit us up and they're
like hey we want to do this and do you
want to and we're like oh okay or
not okay or
n oh there's a hole okay got it but if
there's something we specifically want
to do then our management will try to
see if it's possible and if the company
in charge is willing to do it yeah yeah
yeah yeah that's how it goes that's how
it works I'm making a piece of Modern
Art oo piece of Modern Art uh speaking
of piece of Modern
Art I I I look like a look yeah but
Kelly can you send me my can you send me
my art Come Get It Come Get It Come Get
It okay the the the small one I can like
the the most recent one I can go get
yeah easy look look cuz small yeah okay
a box no look at the kfp here oh the
chicken is looking that's what you mean
get off thank you so far is it like an
empty box yeah I haven't started digging
down yet but I'm about to start digging
down I like these like rose patterns on
the Terra cot yeah that's cuz I ran out
of
cobblestone all right now let's take a
little look
the go Stone the gobbly stone going to
take a little look see all right uh
punch Me
Harder kfp o kfp That's Kiara's job not
mine that's y's job let's see I think
I'll do a little
mining he's just really quick so I'm
going to turn this down to like half
speed5 I'll do a little mining yeah go
for it first I do a little
sorting building instruction yo yeah is
that like the stuff that's filling back
up here Chad is that like was that in
the hopper or
what what's happening 1 two
three your son coobo seems to be
betraying you yeah um that little Brett
that absolute kuso gaki KY we need to do
something about her like she sees the
new members and the first thing she says
who's who's my new Mommy right
so because she already has plenty of
mommies I replied to her hey and then
which is very C like actually
hey like a really manlike voice yeah and
then she gave me the brattiest reply
ever she was
like I'm I'm an adult I don't need you
anymore you can't tell me what to do you
know but if you're an adult and you
don't need me anymore then why do you
need any other mommies oh and she did
say like she needs money which implies
that she's not really looking for a
mommy she's looking for a sugar Mommy I
see this is typical child behavior
though from what I know yeah she's crazy
she's crazy yeah I believe it though
that's that sounds very cobal
like yeah she's like whoever can buy her
that pony or that
motorcycle speaking of which I'm
probably going to get her a pony maybe
you can buy her a
motorcycle what yeah we need to we need
to divide up
the O scary we need to divide up um the
responsibilities here huh the the
responsibilities or the
the spending money the what what's the
word wagon what
wagon what's the word for spending money
uh in English yeah div not allowance I
mean oh the budget uh spending oh yeah I
get what you mean um expenses expenses
yeah expenses yeah that's what it
was but I don't no that kusogaki she has
earned enough money to buy that [\h__\h] on
her own a I guess that's true enough
yeah but I mean yeah yeah you don't
really get to choose though when you
have when you have like a baby child and
I don't speak from experience cuz I only
have two cats um but I have a mother and
from from knowing Mama Mory um it's just
kind of a you just you're you know what
um you can't uh parenting is a thankless
job oh yeah they do say that they do say
that mhm maybe at least until your child
reaches a certain adult age when it
realizes uh that it's time to thank your
mommy yeah exactly thank your mommy mhm
and it will happen
eventually you just got to grow up a
little bit just wait for it it'll happen
the time will come just be patient
please wait mommies please don't lose
your minds
yet not yet not yet not yet but that c
so gaki I swear to God
yeah she is
what can you do she is a difficult one
want it's down another block okay how
many more all right so two more layers
all
right jez this is very
deep AFP
please
AFP why he watching are they in the way
I'm sorry he's just watching he likes me
a a a oh we have some ah you were
cooking glass there's nine glass
finished I'll let it
continue
cooking shove him off wait let me get
the C we did have some glass
huh did there a guide say you need glass
in this case and this one no not this
one I don't think oh
okay I'm just trying to dig in the
ground the ground that doesn't ex Lov
her mommy though does she she she she
has barely been saying things to me
she's been like not not giving Mommy any
love there's ghost in you yeah kids are
cruel she doesn't care about her mommy
at all a it's okay
yahwa don't worry about it she hates
me I'm sure she doesn't
she very much loves you
still it's hard to see sometimes that's
all let's see
surely surely this will be enough I mean
it's it looks cool how does he keep
doing
that kids are so cruel get down
[Music]
your kfp chicken keeps coming over to
talk to me what do you want from me
little guy I have nothing to give you
ask Kiara for treats or
whatever okay KY I got something for you
see this one I think so he's going to
try and climb up the stairs
again give him proper love and and
affection it's not climbable anymore
that's sad yeah a he's kill he's so
plump he's yes for
you see stay with
Gua I think we
got all right cool it's one two three
again K be hearing screams of animals in
the neighboring room and are like oh oh
I hope it's not our turn next yby
y wait this cow yeah this cow
can this cow can
go you guys also eat wheat right uh-oh I
don't have any torches in
here damn I really need more wheat all
the
time it's okay I got wheat I got wheat
[Music]
but
wait all right guys I've dug
sufficiently into the ground I think
amazing how far you all come with this
one block awesome work right like this
world is pretty cool I kind of want to
keep this forever I know it's pretty
nice right yeah so nice good stuff good
stuff good times oh no There Goes My
pickaxe all right I'm
coming I'm going to bring a
Whatchamacallit uh
torch torch you need torches yeah that's
okay I think a there's a few I have like
20 in this box let me bring them to you
oh okay thank you hold on I got to make
a weapon new
weapon oh where she I'm I'm over here by
the chest I know that doesn't help when
I say I'm over here this world is so
small and we're still keep on passing
each other yeah we do thank you o more
torches welcome can always use more
there probably more
[Music]
somewhere all right um what am I doing
what is what is the waa doing the
doing yeah someone in chat says kobo's
in the rebellious child
phase I feel like she's in that forever
no she's never getting out of it oh no
no no true surely
not no any more oh wait this one can go
iy
torches hey why do I only have three
that's oh cuz I'm holding them in my
other hand oh my gosh I'm so silly
Perpetual rebellious face it's when she
says it's not a phase Mom it's literally
not a phase like she's just forever
rebellious that's just how goo is from
the face mom yeah that's seems to be the
case
kopan
indeed I'm almost level 40 damn level 40
is the the level of 40 is in
demand that means you've been doing a
really good job uh not dying right yeah
I hope I will not die because with this
level I could do some cool stuff in the
enchanting table I think for
sure okay now we just got to move this
way and then it'll be a
3X3 and then we've got the basic
starting
point for the inner structure then we
got to lay the beds down can I put this
on the pickaxe guys that would be good
right so much gold oh I need the trap
doors that's right
it's good right yeah okay let's go I got
something good out of a chest for my
pickaxe I should make a ladder
honestly I'm not making a
ladder let's go you heard apples oh yeah
good apples we have enough golden apples
actually oh yeah that's side quest is
finished finished side quest Apple
Golden Apple side quest
complete M okay let's see and this
person puts trap doors
there at this point guys if you think
we're doing too much it's just because
now the last stream the end episode will
be a few days later so now we're just
you know we have the excuse of there is
time so why not do more yeah exactly oh
this guy's face is this looks kind of
like a creeper face okay I'm going to
make
ladder uh and then I have beds yeah
ladder it's just really fun to finally
have something to do again in Minecraft
for
me yeah yeah cuz you're you're a pretty
big fan of Minecraft aren't you well
yeah but like I I'm not the biggest fan
of building things so my favorite thing
about Minecraft is adventuring and
finding new biomes and stuff but I've
seen them all that we you know can
see um in our server so for me it's like
I'm waiting for the next Minecraft
update so that I can look at new stuff
look at new animals new enemies and
stuff oh yeah I see but this opportunity
in this one block Minecraft gives me the
chance to start from scratch again and
it's been really cool like having
problems of iron for example getting
iron or getting even the simplest things
that's really rare that that experience
you only have in the beginning when you
play Minecraft for the first time and
right well actually no not not even then
because iron when you play the game
normally even then even if you don't
have an iron farm it's not such
a huge problem
usually but we had a huge problem of
iron yeah we
did yeah we did and I'm kind of we're
fixing it too late but that's okay no no
no no now now is the best time
now actually I can put a ladder here
that's what that was supposed to be for
okay ladder time stop ladder time L
time still in a dream
[Music]
snake the last it's always the
ladder you should eat oh you're
right M yummy time I completely forget
about that and then I see that I have
the eggs and then I remember that
Minecraft doesn't take place in Japan so
you can't just eat the raw
egg yeah that's that's I think tourists
are or not even tourists just generally
foreigners who don't know much about
Japan they might be surprised that
there's so much like raw egg in all the
dishes in Japan super nor yeah it's
pretty normal there and the raw eggs are
super safe there H yeah and it makes
everything tastes like really really
yummier in my opinion like Sukiyaki um
or like I like tamago Kaka which is like
oh yeah RW egg on uh
rice yum yeah can be good can be good
for Sukiyaki when you like dip stuff
into the raw egg mixture which is not a
mixture it's just the raw egg
twir um I I I like that too but I when I
dip it I try to only get like a small
amount of the egg on the meat I don't
want it to be like absolutely dripping
with the egg you know oh yeah there are
definitely some people that like want it
to be drippy for sure M mhm not me not
me yeah you don't seem like that kind of
person that would be in that s
s see um I want to feel like this can go
somewhere okay now hold on
beds you got three beds there you
go kind of boring actually ah what do I
do I was making some actually was going
to make some books but then I was
breeding the
cows and then I wanted more
wheat but the wheat is growing
slowly very slow slowly okay okay that's
fine okay guys look I'm making proog
look I'm making progress dead beats
look did already make the potion no but
uh the books that I'm making I want to
make I'm preparing the books for the the
not the potion maker for the enchanting
table actually yeah the potion maker I
saw I saw it like yesterday
somewhere one of these
chests okay now we got to continue you
ah here it is see guys it didn't break
okay
let's brewing stand is so back where
should we put it let's put it somewhere
else let's put it
here blocks
told
told okay so we're going to hollow out
behind that how many minutes are you
into the video Kelly um four wow four
the first
[Laughter]
let's go you can do it g it it flip it
down flip it back up after it's down and
then I go two in flip it down and then
flip it up and
then go two
in N what is this what is this chest and
then to random crap chest in that part
behind that
okay got
it yeah there are a lot of random crap
chests hanging around sorry I really got
it's okay unoc I'm actually trying to
like sort a little bit as well so just
to help you out a little bit thank
you in the middle wait I have one block
one block that fits in here did I not
see
okay oh well I think they can go in here
too the thing with eggs is that we treat
them in America and it destroys a
membrane on the egg that makes them the
way they are oh a membrane
oh very interesting any raw egg can have
salmonella but that doesn't mean all raw
eggs will if you trust the source of
your eggs go for it if not I wouldn't oh
okay interesting yeah at least like you
don't have to worry about it at all in
Japan it seems that's good yeah I'm a
raw egg fan so if you're the type of
person who loves their protein and stuff
and chugs five raw eggs in the morning
then go live in Japan yeah do
that I've met a person like that and I I
was watching them chug it's it was a
very buff person actually was a need
their protein it was actually a f
relatively famous person that you guys
might know but I'm not going to say the
name
but uh they were chugging yeah it was
Gaston no one eats five billion eggs
like a Stan I know
that they were chugging those eggs in
the morning I was like ew in a it was in
a at at an event so
anyway how how can you at least like put
salt and pepper in that raw egg mixture
and enjoy it a bit more like that I
wonder is that acceptable yeah I mean at
the end of the day I'd still prefer
cooked over raw it really came down to
it
right it was actually Yago
Yago I don't think Yago chugs wrong eggs
in the morning he seems pretty fit but
not like that type of crazy
fit
right this boat really is moving around
a lot it's
[Music]
fine the boat should be fine if it's
right here right guys did you see Kelly
that the uh oh oh beautiful parrot H
Kelly beautiful parrot new color that we
didn't see before Oh red with yellow and
blue red mostly red Red's a good color
that's like the most beautiful typical
parrot ever oh but I was going to say
did you see um the whole life Japan and
I guess Ian to Twitter they changed
their profile pictures uh to the Justice
logo which I don't think they did they
ever do that before I don't think so and
so I literally didn't recognize their
their um account when they were on my
timeline I was like who the [\h__\h] is this
oh nice good job bro who the [\h__\h] is
this yeah I didn't even notice
that it's like new phone H
this uh oh this seems bad okay that's
fine we'll just rebuild around same same
right they they've had the usual cover
logo for
ages so that was oh
oh H let's see how this is going to go
he protect me Golem protect me oh oh
good job M MW I love this Golem he's
just protected me from one of those
flying vexes Skelly what a nice guy he's
kind of useful maybe we shouldn't put
him in the farm yeah yeah I think he
should stay here cuz the it will spawn
anyway in what you're building
automatically EX
exactly so there's one need more
Golems bodyguard and it just walks up
from here I feel like this is going to
encroach on the storage space but it is
what it
is oh no it can't be
helped encroach going to encroach on
itting word oh yeah it means it's going
to get up in its [\h__\h] uh it's going to
it gets in the way
Jama useful uh useless book useless
book
[Music]
here
gu okay hold on uh
[Music]
I'm crouched good I need to be crouched
no please don't do
that
okay
um I know I know I can heal the Golem
but right now he still looks very
fine he's doing well don't think he
needs a heal right
now he's very buff he also chugs those
eggs in the morning yeah and uses
antlers in all of his
decorating did you get that Kiara it's
gastan what never mind it doesn't
freaking matter he's like from a Disney
movie right
stop wait you don't know wait huh oh
he's from a Disney movie right gon yeah
yeah he is do you know which
one uh I think
um oh oh yeah Beauty on the
Beast it is funny to me that it took you
a minute to to remember what he's
from no no no no that's what I I've been
thinking about uh since the first time
we mentioned
him he's just such a a meme I don't know
I watched Beauty and the Beast recently
when I was recovering from surgery so
I'm kind of like a a Disney kick and
like a I remember just the classic one
oh yeah yeah yeah classic of course um
I'm just kind of on a Disney kick where
I'm like thinking about like old Disney
movies and stuff like that and like um
also not just not only that but like
also like funny like Disney like haha
funny funny Disney YouTube videos where
people like edit the characters and make
them do funny things oh there's funny
Disney disne Disney videos yeah YouTube
do YouTube do da
yeah you guys know the videos I'm
talking about right it's the good stuff
right hand me your
mes s him to me I don't think does he
have a different name in
German Gaston probably I guess so this
doesn't sound no not
sure the Aladdin YTP is the this is
pretty good that brings me back to my
school days kids would be like look at
this fun video I found on
YouTube and they play it and like no
don't let the teacher see te going to
get mad that's an inappropriate
video thank you no D than you
Shan
[Music]
D okay let's see
how I wonder let me go ahead and check
oh he's still okay I kept it playing
dang it all right
so who goes up
there I will these chests I will
literally never open the WR
chest I've opened those chest a million
times and I still don't know what is
where oh my
God are you guys losing your minds over
that because I
am I certainly
am seven steps I believe it's too many
chests no no you're
not you're not really 2 3 4
six good good decent
book going to work great guys it's going
to work
awesome you'll
see I put labels on mine yeah those are
unlabeled would probably help to put
labels but even here I don't look at the
labels who knows if they're still ACC
need
to
yeah sorting is visually pleasing
really I'm really running out of blocks
here Lads cat this looks new uh we got a
new music disc
now oh it's new it's
new nice
wait let's listen to it well pump up
them Jams Pump it up while your feet on
the floor Pump Pump It Up PP Pump Up
Pump It Up why your feet on the floor I
don't know oh yeah I love it get down
that one get down
guua
o it's
good wait hold on no it should be
it should be correct never
mind all
right it reminds me of mini
motorways you ever play mini
motorways yeah yeah it reminds me of the
music that plays during many
motorways puts me into a trance want to
sleep it sounds like several Plum Plum
tracks overlapped oh okay now it's
getting better yeah oh did
[Music]
cute
yeah get down
sho I'm about to run out of cob Stone oh
my Lord all right we got to find another
block a block should we do now
guys oh I'm going to die hello
[Music]
Kelly what do you think about JoJo Sia
oh that's a hot opinion thing that
people are talking about
huh oh man yeah my opinion
is I don't have one you don't have
one
no not in
particular oh okay okay not even a top
nine JoJo says chat all right that's
cool cuz I watched a deep dive about her
cuz I had like absolutely no idea who
she was and and what she's all about and
then I found out she's from that uh
dance toddler dancing show dancing Dance
Moms Dance Moms show I do feel for the
people that were on that show I will say
that yeah that's a pretty terrible
shitty ass horrible show yeah I do feel
for them I really do the way the kids
are being treated and how biased that
teacher lady [\h__\h] sorry but like Mama
Mia yeah they see the way she treated
those kids and the dance mom out crap
crap crap crap crap yeah those are oh no
yeah those are those are children and I
get the world is Harsh and it's good to
figure out how to handle criticism early
but um those are children those are
those are little literal babies that
don't their brains aren't ready for that
there's a way to ease them into it and
that's not it way that it's you okay
gell it's going are you really
okay sounds like a battle's going
[Music]
on did she
survive oh
[Music]
boy ow you laying eggs again is what
that's yeah she's laying eggs
again yeah oh my God
Jesus they're really that painful to lay
eggs my
goodness take a
break a break from the
eggling how do you do that birth
breathing is it breathe in twice and
breathe out once or is it breathe in
once and breathe out twice
oh my
God two twice in one long
[Music]
out it's okay it's getting better sounds
like a monkey it's getting
better there thanks for the memberships
oh oh those are the eggs that I just
laid oh my Lord what the
heck thanks thanks live egg laying on
stream my goodness do I need to do I
need to age or my stream not the first
time oh my God the first time is
happening
[Music]
huh yeah
yeah why have you never laid an egg on
stream before key let me
think um
no I haven't I have not ever done that
before in my life but what's it like
tell me tell me about it what's it like
uh it hurts but the relief when it's
gone is so so much bigger than the pain
do you have a choice to not to not do it
well why would I not do it when it when
it comes out it's got to come out you
know okay
but but I mean I don't know is it is it
something that happens no matter what
even if a chicken like doesn't like do
anything put un quote you know
anything even if the chicken doesn't
like meet a nice uh a nice rooster for
example like even if the chicken doesn't
meet a nice rooster does the egg still
like come
out let's say it's only in all world yes
in all world yes if you say
so all right trust me believe me trust
me bro if you have to get rid of them
you have to get rid of them somehow he's
got to go out oh either way mhm better
out than in Shrek always says exactly
that's a that's a wait how did I only oh
never mind I got more
okay
tutoral hold this and lay up fertilized
eggs all the time says
chat okay okay some of those American TV
shows are [\h__\h] up is what I was trying
to say I agree definitely are and chat
might actually be surprised that this
once um I don't like one of these shitty
TV shows oh are you a big fan of shitty
TV shows usually no actually not like on
that level like those are all [\h__\h] like
actual like not not good not good not
good at all oh everybody just suffers
the moms were suffering too partially
but the moms are just basically stage
Moms living vicariously for their kids
and and getting that Fame for TV through
their kids and getting it through drama
and the TV producers are [\h__\h] too
because they they script those things
and they cut those things in a way to
make the kids or the the ladies the moms
look bad and and H it's just all a [\h__\h]
show Showbiz is full of evil people can
you believe it that's crazy I believe it
I believe it
absolutely believe it it's
true Aquarius
break you tell them y
waa I'm telling I'm telling them I'm
telling it how it is waa speaks the
truth always they could do it for the
ratings and that sucks yeah exactly
about them
ratings well I'm rating it Zer out of 10
because it's
[\h__\h] it's not worth like having children
grow up so in such a traumatic way with
such traumatic experiences agree like
imagine like practicing and dancing your
ass off for like 10 hours per day or so
when you're like I don't know8 years old
or so and then you're actually like
really [\h__\h] good like amazing and and
they still like somehow have it out for
you and Target you and they're like oh
you're [\h__\h] you
suck oh my God it's just so not worth it
so sad
their ass off and then get nothing from
it yeah especially cuz when you're a kid
it's like you know that's like the time
of dreams you know like you have dreams
that you want to see come true to a
certain extent that kind of training
surely for some girls uh or boys too for
some of them for some kids it might work
you know some of them might get
motivated from that motivated from that
and and will actually get a a kick out
of it but it doesn't work on every child
you you have to like adjust the way you
treat and teach a child and train them
depending on their personality and all
that it might not work for everybody
like treating them like [\h__\h] doesn't
work for everybody yeah I also but I
also am of the opinion that the opposite
is also not very good so like everybody
gets a golden star kind of thing um I
think that that should not it should not
be that way unless there's like one kid
in the class that isn't getting an award
and every other person oh uhoh you know
it's like maybe let's who did
that agree though oh my God that donkey
is living dangerously on the edge oh we
should sleep because Phantom is out
Phantom yeah sleepy sleep not everybody
needs a gold star though it builds
character to be also that dance mom's
show uh the the reason why they had it
filmed in that one Studio one of the
reasons is also [\h__\h] up it's just
because the location the state or so
where it was located in had really
really loose uh children working labor
laws so that they can have them work
longer hours and stuff like that film
longer hours for the show like that's
the simple reason why they filmed it
there so that they can you know have
them work their ass
off well I'm going to answer a quick
question um in my chat sorry it it
involves a piece of merchandise um yeah
there is a there is a memb only version
of my my new album that's out um someone
was asking how much it is I believe that
it is
$31 it's a it's a special cover that's
drawn by Studio wi so if you want the
physical version grab it it's very cool
um pretty it's for members only that one
is so hope you guys like it sorry I
Wasing members only how does that work
so the way that they do it is it's like
you access it via a QR code or like Link
in community post that's only for
members cuz yeah descriptions are
visible to everyone didn't know that but
mhm members only descriptions are
visible to everyone even if you're not a
member H uh description of a video you
mean yeah or oh okay okay met the
community post I was
like no no no no no those are definitely
a me mems only those are okay oh yeah
just wanted to answer that Q now where
do I go next do we go next from here oh
person who's telling me how to make this
pleas Ian Ian
su
su me the
way we're getting
somewhere okay no don't don't leave come
back come back I built the trench back
yeah okay and then trap doors got them
so ti so put two beds over there or
three three more beds over there
okay more beds I need three more
beds get
out then
sheep get
up okay Mama given birth again no it's
just so much in this chest that I don't
know what oh my God should just make
random chest to just throw things into
even if we don't organize no we will
never find things ever again yeah but
like we don't need them though don't
need those things you have the
shears a yes
H those from
you there you go thank you step by step
step by step even if it's overwhelming
we'll get it step by
step for your w
got to mine some more what am I looking
for right
[Music]
now all right please blocks coal blocks
iron blocks oh thanks for the gift
memberships that's
kind all kinds of
things leather iron yeah
[Music]
yeah basically trying
to wait for those cows to make more
Babble
bubbles
yeah oh
iron enough okay we just need a little
more come on someone quickly grow some
W
true okay let me feed some more of them
wish you could like bone meal on the
animals so that they grow up faster know
I was literally about to say that but I
thought that is
stupid what yeah I was thinking the same
thing bone meal on animals maybe you
give them treats or something you know
an update or something like that a that
would be kind of sick will okay oh what
is this for a new three
beds a lot
of meaning cotton candy in
Japanese have you had that um like uh
you know the what myai had that collab
of that uh lamb Shabu Shabu play
yeah did you ever go to that place
before uh-uh cuz they serve you know
they serve this like plate of raw lamp
meat right and on top of that yeah the
super fluffy cotton candy on top it
looks so nice it look so cute I look
pretty yum but I didn't get a chance to
try it out you ha I actually I I went no
no I liked it I went there with v banai
auki I think there was one more person
maybe um and we ate together uh when it
was like what Senpai collaboration and
we did Shabu shaboo all together and you
know they gave us like a lot of
merchandise from Wai collaboration too
that sounds so fun the heck
cool
yeah good times I got to go there some
I'll find a way to go there at some
point honestly they already had it like
twice maybe they'll do it again at some
point oh fingers crossed what I mean the
collaboration the the lamp with the
cotton candy I think you can have at any
time hey
cool of course they chose wat then for
that makes sense some real Cotton K
that's what her name means after
all oh wait hold on you're not hungry
yet what the hell oh no that's just one
okay never mind I messed up all right
all good Japan collaborations cheese
yeah man I'll get some it's so cool that
in Japan stuff like that is even
possible
mhm yeah I'd really love an Ian Cafe
here
someday I'd love an Cafe yeah didn't we
likeor there we have those anyway
already in nepon in in
Japan haven't had one in Japan maybe not
yeah yeah I want one that I can go to
really easily instead of having to take
a how you going to go to that you got to
go during non-opening hours oh yeah
well of course otherwise that would be
dangerous very very dangerous
night see okay so he makes a
line that oh no oh
God it's like a
trench difficult looks difficult yeah
I'm just going to have to expand
okay going from thetis expand it's a
serious illness that a lot of people in
the world are affected by these days
dongus a lot of people are yeah quite
common from what I've
heard oh no second time I heard about it
in these past in this past week yeah
let's see maybe it's 9
by5 9x5 trench I think
one two four five six
seven8
n and we have to
expand okay we'll make it work I'm not
afraid of anything I'm not afraid of
hard work yeah maybe it'll be more
difficult oh you definitely aren't yeah
hey what's up guys
yeah feeding
time come on eat the breads where you
going why they're hiding from me they're
scared of me what what are you doing
why
what they're discussing how they're best
going to assassinate me what's the best
way to assassinate takanasi Ki stop
their
plotting stop it I'm giving you bread
and beds in a nice fancy house what else
do you want jobs too like hey and and
and the Golem's protecting you like this
is the life so ungrateful this is the
[Music]
life oh my
God
[Music]
beautiful all these random blocks are
hilarious cuz it's so
disorganized think any of these can be
burned oh I could buy bookshelves wait
no we're not using lava anyway so it
doesn't matter
no me baby Mega
baby me
B is there more beds
oh do I have to won't they won't they
make a baby if there's not enough
beds they better remember how much bread
I gave to them yeah be
grateful well that is at least like um
economically smart of them to not make
any more babies if they don't have any
more beds in their home yeah
economically smart no a good economic
decision makes
sense then I shall make more beds
although I might have to make a second
floor for that house but I don't want to
I don't want to make it too big I think
we don't need to go crazy yeah
we don't need a a Trader for
everything it just been until here I'll
check the
tutorial do you will you need beds for
your uh Farm what I already made them
don't worry about it okay
nice
S8 uh-huh
one two can we sleep three four hold on
five it's five gotcha oh yeah we can go
we can sleep let's sleep after I put
down a couple torches hold on it's very
frightening mhm
okay all right and we can
sleep good guys do you want bgm again
should I put bgm on again Chad like we
had before I've just been Oh you mean
like yeah regular yeah we should that'd
be nice
I'm going to put something
no sure yes
no actually that's quite a few
nose yeah I don't know what it is I feel
like for this stream people have been
like no bgm please which is really
interesting okay well then if you need
bgm then I guess
it's bring your own bgm to
[Laughter]
workday is this
normal sleeping on the floor
oh they're definitely bugged let me try
to get them up oh they are up this
version of Minecraft this mod is very
buggy M oh
yes
H you remember that I gave you bread
guys right or do you need more again
they
forgot these [\h__\h]
yeah it looks like we're going to have
to end up leading villagers over to this
you think we can do that to get them
sleep ined easy all right villager
master I feel like you're such a like
master of using or utilizing villagers
from what I've seen well well well I am
the creator of
fixon from yes yes founder the
[Music]
original from the Hol love
yes and this
is
practically uh phix
Stone uh numero yeah uh nice I don't
know what this is French Italian who who
the [\h__\h] know one of
them it's a mix
mix wee we we we peepee we we
ah oh yeah um
well speaking of like uh different
languages and yeah different
languages so now that the girls have
been Unleashed on Twitter Unleashed you
know about them so do we and we see
their designs fully already I'm
surprised the all of the artists from
Justice already put out the full
reference sheets for them did you see oh
yeah I did it took it took me 3 years to
get yeah it seems like they kind of um
decided on all of them putting it out
with like even the same description kind
of seems to be a thing a pattern for
them they have some sick weapons right
mhm I want to fight them with Ricky
fight them but no we will we will watch
Advent and justice fight it out and see
who survives and then we can beat up the
Survivor
yeah survival of the fittest ah all life
English is just Hunger Games oh
yeah it's just Hunger Games yeah in case
you didn't know I feel like there's no
power creep anymore
though what no power creeping yeah
everyone's I it means that I feel like I
can beat up the new people you know
without them being like these miraculous
gods that can defy death right that's
what I was worried about is we just get
more and more powerful people and then
I'm not going to be able to beat up even
my
yeah yeah yeah we want to beat up our
kohai yeah beat them up beat them up
beat them up kohai should not be able to
so easily beat up Senpai I mean they can
it's just like I want a fair fight is
the main thing I want a fair fight you
want a fair fight yeah I want a fair
fight what's oh what you want an
advantage Kiara we already have an
advantage I me I guess that's true true
but fair and square is
good fair and square I'm a phoenix they
can't do nothing about me all right Kar
if you say so if you say
so wait they they have like an official
description out already too right yeah
wait let me see all live English Justice
there was like a press release right
yeah yeah yeah let's see let's see right
we have Elizabeth Rose blood flame code
name the scar Queen oo um so far guys uh
I've been calling her and I would like
people to pick this up because she has a
really long name you're afraid to steal
it from me I've been calling her
herb oh not Liz Rose blood the first no
it's the first three letters of her name
herb yeah I'm just been calling her
herb she's uh her April her April her
birthday's in April she's from great
exard whatever that means uh oh ah some
of is like oh wait it says here uh herb
paves the way for the world and all of
its people she does how she paves away
for the world and all of its people how
all right maybe I was wrong about the
power creep I was wrong uh not only does
she stand at the Forefront during
missions with her physical prowess but
she also captures the hearts of all
around her with a beautiful singing
voice mhm she does have a beautiful
singing voice yeah we heard it we heard
it
we know she gave us actually in our
first meeting she gave us a a beautiful
you know how do you say it she said for
us yeah demo she demoed her voice for us
it was it was crazy
lovely so she's highly self-disciplined
and a bit too hard on herself that
sounds like my
description but perhaps due to her
culture's emphasis on politeness and
manners okay we're hinting at something
here she tends to g a bit soft on those
around her as a result she spends her
days stressed out with her work
coordinating justice but it seems like
there's nothing uh a nice nap in a comfy
bed can't fix ooh
relatable yeah have you guys noticed she
has like uh a flamy a blue flame on her
on her middle chest
o really cool she's flaming yeah you
think it's open like if I put my finger
in there am I like inside of where are
you sticking your finger into K don't
the the blue the blue flame Oh you mean
in the flame yeah blue is the hottest
fire in case you didn't know like really
hot burning stars that blow up burn blue
hey y' that's undermining my fire oh
okay again the power creep I was wrong
about it I'm sorry yeah what the hell
oopsies okay well yeah she looks really
cool she seems to be like the mature of
type out of these four right yeah uh I
like the red and blue combination I
think she will look really really nice
next to narissa yeah red and blue hair
is so
cool that's the best color combo in my
opinion I love that blue next is gigy
murin gig or wait was it g or gig it's
Gigi but I want to call her gig for fun
yeah I might call her giggy too
yeah um it's like how I say Digimon I
say Digimon usually cuz that's how they
say it in German
yeah
diyon yeah awesome so she's the Chaser
apparently I mean she seems fast yeah
mhm um it says born and raised under the
flag of Freedom oh
wait doesn't well that that okay I mean
the the other one was you know in the
polite Clues yeah certain things there
are definitely Clues there uh gigy murin
is I can't I can't help it it's locked
in gigy Moran is a free-spirited Chaser
and mischievous gramlin while she is
proficient in chasing down targets with
pure intuition she struggles with
memorizing directions and making
calculated decisions yeah that's what
she looks
like she states that she'd rather not
spend much time thinking because it
makes her head hurt UHA
understand is it like a pattern like the
smaller uh girls in whole life have like
smaller
brains there but yeah also I think
you're on to something but yeah but I'm
definitely an outlier in that situation
cuz by all if if that's true then I
should be small no no you're just using
up all your brain cells for your work
and then when you you know do other
things sometimes maybe the brain cells
are already used up for the day well
thank you for coping for me
I appreciate coping on my behalf but I
just don't know if I can agree no I I I
agree for you it's very sweet of you it
continues as uh these quirks are also
present in her everyday life where she
tends to prioritize her instinctual
craving for fun and being silly over
anything else she's often the source of
headaches for those around her causing
trouble because she thought it would be
funny a okay cool that sounds I'm
interested in seeing if that will
actually transpire like in reality I
want to see I want to see is she really
a a silly little silly little Gremlin
you know not all Gremlins are meme Lords
though so I'm curious if she's like a m
Lord a little mem Lord so far mem Lord
Gremlin or like I don't know regular old
kusogaki Gremlin that isn't educated on
memes I'm curious I want to know she I
think she is I think she is think she's
educated on memes and her Doodles are so
cute yeah she's a good think I think her
design is my favorite out of the bunch
what do you think I think so too faite
my actually no my favorite is RA oh that
one's really damn good too yeah but I
really like her hoodie and I love the
the hair uh color variation of the light
uh Brown and the dark brown and and and
she's so cute she's so cute the little
the little pigtails are cute and she's
orange and that's nice yeah she's a
cutie more orange I like all of them
but yeah yeah so the next one is
Cecilia green
green Green is to
Shrek emmer in German means ever so this
is like Evergreen oh like an evergreen
tree yeah I think that was on purpose so
it says she is an ancient
automaton with a penchant for flowers
tea and creating music oh tea another
tea
person crafted during ancient times
Cecilia was originally made to be
dedicated to Eternal servitude oh yet in
recent times she began slacking off on
her work o lazily cooking mostly potato
potatoes potato
potatoes potatoes potato I'm feeling
something I'm sensing something with
whatever else she found in the kitchen
she has now all but abandoned her duties
doing the bare minimum and mostly
immersing herself in various crafty
Hobbies with Newfound interests in life
she takes on every new experience with
pure curiosity of a young
girl no she seems like the lighe headed
no
Airhead Airhead yeah and sweet kind of
person kind of aaton that like doesn't
understand like human things like IUS
from Persona 3 that's my favorite
Persona game and there's a character
that's just like but she's not character
this is a real person but still you get
what I'm saying yeah yeah yeah she seems
soft and in her design first of all I
love the the dark green that's going on
is beautiful uh and her design is really
beautiful and she has that um that
violin yeah mhm this dirt okay got it
really interesting looking so far and
people are getting kind of crazy about
her limbs uh which is also a nice get
crazy about them what does that mean
what does that entail
getting crazy I think she'll
actually like she's kind of matching
with oh yeah I get that that idea yeah
but she's not fully a robot automaton is
a little different yeah but they're kind
of all like
yeah cool yeah okay so finally a green a
new green
member exciting or green and the next
one is a pink one yeah and I think her
brain is also very Pink as they like to
say
uh ra ra ra I might just end up saying
it the Japanese way ra ra yeah what do
you can you say it how you want to say
it yeah ra P pan panta I don't know a
difficult name to say um the artist with
the god eyes Raa panta is endowed with
investigative investigative and
descriptive prowers her means of
information gathering are diverse
utilizing not only her agility and
social skills but also various social
media platforms and other dot dot unique
methods what does that mean what are
they implying I don't know what that
meansa what does it mean what does that
mean I don't know actually neither do I
I actually am at a loss I have no clue
is it the the pink stuff
like like flirtiness or so I don't know
guess we'll find
or I don't know the facial Composites
composits composits comp comp comp mug
shots that she draws crime crime
drawings how do you pronounce it
composits composits she draws based on
the information she gathers are renowned
for their accuracy almost as if she was
looking directly at the criminals she as
she draws maybe she was however these
days her gaze is directed towards
finding a new finding new pizza
joints totally not at hand uh and
enjoying the pop culture of the Far
East Mama spicy me the ball of pizza of
Margarita oh we're going to have fun I'm
going to we're going to have so much
fun yeah so her design is super cute she
has that big tail did you guys see my
tweet at her where I drew um I drew a
good fan art of her asking her that's
her was a well drawn composite drawing I
I think she will get that a lot um nice
composite pink P she is literally a pink
panther she is she is there's no no lie
that is what she is M no I really like
the way she looks I like those spiky
fluffy hairs I like those ears I like
the big like chunky tail it's not like
super fluffy right but it's
chunky yeah her tail I read an
interesting uh kind of theory about like
the colors that they have and whatnot in
in like contrast to us so I saw someone
make a point over the fact that like for
example fauna is nature she is of course
nature incarnate and then cilia is like
machine right but they're both green and
then um ra is light and I'm Darkness but
we're both pink so like they show and uh
and Elizabeth is red and so is so is
hakos CH Bales but ba is chaos and
Elizabeth is order so like there's this
kind of like they're reusing how's light
though cuz look at her outfit it's white
and she's light and color yeah she's got
like this brightness to her yeah but
like ba Bae is chaos and then Elizabeth
is kind of you know order right even
though they're both red so it's like
there's no over there's no real overlap
even though the colors are the same I
forget what the what the gig one was I
forget what that one was I forget if it
was yellow or I think that it might
orange I think that what did they say I
forget what it was I forget what it
was h i comparison to you I don't know I
think it's cool though I like that
they're using the same colors but it's
not a total overlap you know yeah
they're both
orange yeah Gigi is small and kiar is
big I guess that
works G's Garfield wow I don't think
it's a stretch I don't think it's a
stretch at all I think it's actually
smart can you imagine if there was
another dark pink lady I'd be like
a uh yeah h i mean eventually it might
happen cha you know there's not you know
it in Hell project the idol company that
I really like um they also give
everybody an image color but they just
have so so so many members not as many
as AKB but still um like for example in
morning mus they have so many members
Sometimes they come and go but uh at
times where they have like 12 15 members
or so they really struggle with giving
out different colors right and then
eventually they had to give someone like
brown and you know those girls are not
really happy about having Brown as their
image color so they call it like macaron
color or so something cute to make it
sound
cuter but that's like the where you end
up at if you give image colors to people
and you try to keep everybody separate
now here in noral life we have some
overlap because can't be helped helped
eventually we're going to hit every
color of the rainbow but at least we can
do like different combinations and stuff
like that well so far we had no Brown
yet though no Brown at all and no do we
have I don't think we ever had black
we've been having white but no black oh
I'm waiting for a black and white that
wait hold on
she is it black and
white she is black wait Brown I am right
oh my God she is yeah oh let's go yeah
TR true true true but her it's like a
how do I say she's so cute I I don't
know it's it's hard to hard to descri I
think Brown is cute brown is cute yeah I
think it's very aesthetically like
furniture and stuff I think H was what
was I just saying uh versatile yeah yeah
if we have a black uh who who did you
say Shi shiot is black and white but not
just sh's image color seems to be purple
when looking at the talent whole life
Talent website oh yeah I guess so
huh no black I think we should get a
black I mean then the question is what
tlight color would they use I think you
can just go for white then you know WR
yeah just like the opposite of it just
give it white I think it's supposed to
be one block deeper oh God black would
be cool would be sick yeah it is one
block deeper oh my God this freaking why
he goes so fast
I'm on two times speed and it's so quick
okay it's
fine
whatever
whatever please make a baby please y
yeah I need to let more of them grow so
I can make more babies instead of
slaughtering
them oh no um oh man sorry guys again
I'm I think I'm more productive than
yesterday cuz I'm more uh awake
but it's still
rough to do so many things at
once taking my time why are these eggs
in here no one will ever
know and you can't like use rabbit hard
for books the same way you can use
leather right even though it looks so
similar I wish you could I wish you
could yeah at least I have CI here from
the start hi that's good I'm just
grinding along trying to
baby's first iron
farm at least I'm doing something kind
of it it seems like it's
working so far well I mean I haven't
tested anything but you know what I mean
like I I'm making it work even though
it's a bit
tough okay well I don't have enough
rabbits rabbit to make I'm pretty sure I
saw some rabbit hide I I have two but
you need four I don't think we have more
do we oh no we do actually we do have
wait is that the one I just put in what
the hell no no we do have four we have
exactly
four all
right okay cool that's at least
something then that's out of the way
MH this enchant is a good idea what this
enchant
what cil's birthday is one day after
mine let me look at their birthdays
again is May 11 which already passed
Cecilia is November 11 which is coming
up
still
uh gigy is October 18 which is coming up
and yeah herb
25 oh my lord it's a good it's a good
day by herb the
herb makes me think of like a like an
herb you know like
a that
plan what do something Golem do
something nah what you looking at like
you got to protect yourself woman
uh uh
uh oh he's doing something now he's
going to die probably this is pretty
rough oh no protect me while I'm getting
a
sword all right I'll spawn a gazillion
more okay uh the the dude is gone now
it's just the
vexus nice sweeping Edge
gooda ah don't don't die Golem come
I want to help him there's
another oh good
job well I have reunion in my head too
these
days yeah I've been using it as the
intro for this these streams oh another
yeah the instrumental I've been using
[Music]
it fix the Golem but okay I guess we can
use
some some iron like one
question says chat you can but I might
not answer cuz I'm collabing with
gaha hey what's up
twins answer it don't
worry okay well no it's just somebody
said can I ask a question oh so I'm like
all right just ask it hey how do you K
the um the soil byebye ah you need a
hole you need a hole I have one I think
this is a hole there's uh there's a hole
in the in the tools chest oh okay I did
it
okay all
right hi guys thanks for joining in one
more
in I'm making an iron farm I
think we'll find out you can do it oh
wait no all the all the hey come back
why is it turning back to dirt stop
that I didn't say you could do that
stopy
[Music]
give
me need some water oh is that what it is
I need water oh now my ho is gone okay
and the the there's a hole in the tools
chest oh thanks let me keep watching
that tutorial let's see place a torch to
spawn
proof out a hole to turn the dirt along
one side into
Farmland
okay
H nobody's taking the
job H
okay I get it all right so I need water
need water bucket
you know how to do it can we maybe go
get that water okay get a bucket and go
to the endless water source yeah you
taught me yeah you plant seeds in the
Tilted ground it won't break them to
become dirt again but you need water to
keep it from going back when you break
the seed freaking Slackers
man all right we'll just we'll just wa
you just got the job
right okay okay okay
just wait I have the bucket oh it's just
it's a little it's
trapped oh
Neil
hi look I'll show you oh is this the
Bodacious boat no this is a regular boat
dudes come on
dudes there's another story
waiting there we go there's the okay
take your time no I'm I meant the the
the for the uh villagers oh okay thank
goodness please don't
[Music]
worry yeah this strange scary
place strange and
scary okay you
guys you know what I'll focus on now
what the
bookcases oh yeah one bookcase needs
okay free books six plags how many many
bookcases do we want
chat
for what version are we playing on it's
1.15.2 if that really matters I don't
think it 15
okay
15 and what's what's the uh enchanting
table let me look up a uh recipe
Minecraft enchanting
[Music]
table m
m o obsidian oh and two diamonds and one
book okay make it too small I think I
made it too small dang it that's fine
how do I take one I will never
know wait two diam [\h__\h] wait one Diamond
two diamonds is it like
no mine under it okay there a lot of me
watching tutorial sorry
guys you can use your ammo Sur B cues
yeah I was thinking so too
yeah I might do that I I'll make a few
myself and then I
see a long ways okay never mind I did it
right was
there no longer nice
rip rip diamonds uh okay we need
four four
obsidian and one book okay so uh
enchanting
table okay I made
it now we need an area for it that
can uh oh actually I'll put it right
here in the
back let me make my hole
so so we're going have to that L here
maybe and around it will be the
bookcases 15 it's like two rows I think
from what I usually
see so this next I need to figure out
where are they plant okay how long will
the stream be today not super super long
uh I want to just finish enchanting
table and iron farm thingy probably
that'll be it cuz I want to get some
stuffed
done uh
IRL understandable I also want to sleep
you too right don't you have you're
going to sleep and then you have redit
Redemption yeah
oh so 5 hours so 12 hours
while no it might not even go up to 5
hours who
knows
Farmland okay let me watch this part of
the tutorial again and half speed even
though it feels like it's going at light
speed well go with the flow chat go with
the
flow um ah okay all blocks
placed and then my do starts digging
XB okay that's fair oopsie what did I
just oh
yeah
um oh wait I got a to dying sick
sick hey no I'm not so mad that that POS
spawned
yeah we have a couple totems of undying
that I was trying to save for the nether
a couple yeah away from the bed yeah
there's like four or something like that
I yeah the torch is away actually the
torch right here here and then ho it oh
my God please don't do that opposite
okay I got it guys I got
it turn it into
Farmland won't save you from the void
well it will save me a death from the
Ender Dragon it's good it's good I will
not fall into the
void I Will
Not Over My Dead
Body no
oh dang it I only had the one water
uh all right hold on it's okay we can
redo that part later go get more water
right back oh my ashes that's right
that's how Phoenix says that thanks for
the
memberships
[Music]
cute
cows what am I going to do about the
cows maybe I don't need
them is there any villager job that
takes laies Luli in exchange for
emeralds cuz we have so
many this ladder needs to
be I forget
where I think right
here okay he did it did what the game
wanted me to do
cleric
really that' be
cool me
out yeah we're making progress we're
making progress everyone clar is the
reverse to emeralds for lap yeah that's
what I mean thank you for gifts that was
nice and the way you're saying it means
that I give them lapies they give me
emeralds that that would be good we
don't need the lapies for anything
okay gotcha that's how you push the
Golems
okay got
it okay the water has to be at the same
height as the farm blocks I needed to
enchant oh okay okay oh well done need
to be up here you mean so I'll need two
more things of water is that why P I
Always was asking na give me give me is
that why
is that what she needed it
for G me G me hey
Ma G me G me a she was
enchanting well she do be an enchanting
woman
lower flirt that's not what they do in
this tutorial hold on a
sec P hey hey Mona
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] I
can't I have like this problem when I'm
like it's like a performance uh
nervousness failure that's okay I think
that's normal also I know you guys say
same level as the farm the water needs
to be same level as the Farmland but in
the tutorial they only do it once I
think they only do one splash of
water I don't think the water goes all
the way up bird CH go away doesn't seem
right they do one in every corner
including this
corner in this
corner tutorial just had them
go and there and there are we out of
buckets
Kelly do you have an empty bucket or you
probably need all your buckets
or huh do you need all the buckets you
have do you have one that you don't need
no no no I'm I'm good I just did it I
just finished the main part now we have
to do villagers I
think oh okay I'll make one anyway you
can't plan if the water is blocking the
crops oh so I needed a plant before cuz
he didn't put any seeds in there whoever
made the tutorial didn't put seeds just
tilled the
Farmland that's weird was I supposed to
put seeds in there hold on a sec I'll
look maybe the villagers do it
themselves not sure yeah cuz there are
no there are definitely no seeds in
there yeah maybe they need some starter
seeds I'm just going to follow
the
see oh no this isn't a normal farm this
is an iron farm this is an iron an iron
farm oh are you starting to say like me
yeah iron iron farm yeah the W way let
see a Farmland is supposed to stop the
Iron Golems from spawning on those spots
no seeds are needed okay
gotcha M I see I see okay understood
smart Minecraft Geniuses who come up
with this stuff
genius cool who's
iron I don't know who that is iron is uh
is actually um the brother of Sauron if
you say
so if you say so they're
related so
relative
see
waha see the water
Cannon it surely sounds like Sauron the
way I say
it
check
bubble hydrated okay now we get all
right now we're getting to villagers so
I might need a little bit of guidance
from Kiara on this one because I don't
know villagers you mean you need free
let's find out at dusk villagers will
sleep wow on the beds that you set up on
the surface surface or at the surface
knock
the beds out from under so that they
will fall into the farm and cover up the
hole when you're done okay so that's
what we do would you like to see kind of
what I'm planning to do yeah I already
ran over there saw the saw the building
it looks pretty colorful yeah so I'll
show you it is going to be Troublesome
getting villagers up here but look let
me show
you so we get them to sleep in here and
then we take the the beds away
I guess we got to make them some normal
stairs cuz I don't think they can use
ladders if we make them normal stairs
they might go to the beds okay on their
own all right I'll make especially now
that it's night okay I'll make you guys
are making
Railway uh suggestions again but I think
I think we can just you know try it
though yeah let's give it a shot easy
way first give it a shot the stairs for
me that's the easy
way a stairway
make stairway I have 12 stairs all right
here we
go we're now constructing the
stairs stairs just just kidding stairs
have been constructed um okay we go get
this out of the way for a moment and I
know this is going to make some
[Music]
trouble
um maybe it it's because the trapo as
long as you break all the other beds so
they don't try to pathfind
them
yeah this may seem complicated but hear
me
out please don't do that please don't
although currently they all have their
own bed right can you birth some
more yeah I'll make I'll make more it
should be possible
okay aw if you could oh my Lord okay
that works
right but then we got to wait for them
to grow up too for a moment cuz they're
going to need a little moment to become
adults yeah all right I need to just use
regular blocks first I get it I get
it the regular blocks for more irregular
blocks bread
partyle
[Music]
qule actually do so I'm the Matchmaker
this is now a Netflix dating show oh my
Lord and I am the I great appreciate it
though I subscribed the the love making
uh yeah or you mean something in your
chat I don't know anymore my brain is
I'm brain dead right now
Kiara oh Babble bab I don't know what's
going
on good morning Babble bab B Bab one
babo has been made need oh two babos
okay hopefully we're running out of bed
wait wait there one one two 3 4 5 6 7 8
9 10 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 damn it it's
exactly the same amount that I have in
beds we will get these we will TR these
villagers don't worry oh I hate to use
this I know I should use an I don't have
an a break
B
[Music]
okay all right and then villagers should
be this one this one they looked
untaken and just get rid of this one and
this
one sorry sheep you're just going have
to deal with this for a
minute oh boy oh my God I I thought I
was hurting him I thought I was hurting
him don't hurt
him Gua you can't
that's why I always switch to like a
different uh non weapon before I touch
them cuz I don't want to hurt them good
idea don't worry a jump scare all good
nothing to worry about here nothing to
see here folks I don't need to play
horror games I can jump scare
myself yeah yeah you
can ah um I'm going
to wait do you have beds over there or I
do they're ready
okay then I'll close up the myth house
cuz otherwise they might go to oh yeah
this place instead here's the staircase
I made Kiara that'll lead them to the
beds wait
uh
what let me see oh nice from here okay
oh oh beautiful C no I did it and then
they just what they stay up here or we
push them in or so they sleep on these
three beds and then we destroy the beds
and they fall
down oh is there holes there
oh yeah okay inter the color combination
yeah used random blocks that were
available he beautiful yeah it'll do the
job never seen a an iron farm so
colorful ever before yeah it's cuz we're
low on
materials we got to let them grow up
though so I'm going to kind of uh peek
at this tutorial see what we do next
after that actual kidnapping actual
torture oh calm down it's not that big
of a
deal only they ate something besides
bread I kind of want to see The Mating
process I'm curious about I mean not the
not that but I want to see how you do
wait I don't need to M them anymore
actually um really I just need to
transport them now you could possibly
help me tell me what to do boss um let's
um okay let's see if n this might not
work okay I have to open
this
up make it a bit
[Music]
wider okay okay thank you for the
sacrifice P I hope somebody will
boat please come on you know you want to
take a ride with
t come on baby no little baby go back
wow whatever I don't care that much
about about the CH maybe it will go to
the bed eventually oh do you want to
take a ride
potential oh yes she oh okay is this one
that I like no not not particularly this
one can actually go but oh I can't sit
in the boat anymore oh he's taking it
over can we put theat close the door the
child went back in on its own good good
child oh good
baby how come it's all stuck it's all
stuck no you can lure them with a job
like a
barrel yeah uh that is true but this one
that I caught now already has a
job is that a bad thing I
wonder well child this may end up oh now
the stupid child is in there no
owab how do I oh man okay okay we're
going to we're going to do a quicky
we're going to get rid of the boat and
then quickly place it
again a child had a taste of freedom and
got scared come come on who wants to go
be tortured forever afraid of a zombie
to make
iron put the boats around the entrance
so no one can escape yeah oh okay
oh no the double again no we like that
no and they're making love in the boat
stop and you think about
this you guys think oh God they became
one oh God this is horrifying just one
just one just
one no where you going well they will go
back for the beds no
worries you say so hey hey hey where the
[\h__\h] is he going
over hey
ah
uh uh wait wait yeah there's not a lot
of room to move sadly
close I just want one of you guys to sit
please one guy oh okay oh wow two dudes
s not to again not quite
optimal come on oh do you like me get in
the boat wait that's actually is that
hey hey hey you have a name come
back he does not have a name currently
he sells iron armor this hurts me so
much oh don't worry we don't need him we
got oh perfect perfect okay let's go
okay off we off we
fly got to make a
turn let's go let's
go get ready for your life of torture my
man it's going to be great but actually
now with our method m although we could
on top of those stairs we could make an
iron card but we might have to wait for
nighttime we'll leave him here for a
moment how many do you need again three
three we can just get two and then make
them have a baby actually but we'll try
um make them have a baby down in the
dark well that I've made the dark trench
okay yeah spicy time oh okay I have
another
boat and Poss the child will go in ch
children are okay too I think yeah we
got a child we got a child let's
go ah the ethics of this I do question
don't worry he grows up fast they grow
up fast these days Kelly me yeah but
yeah ah
whatever kidnapping congratulations who
knows maybe that's maybe that's his
father possibly they're
Daddy he probably doesn't know even who
his father is they all look the same
true
enough they're all sharing they don't
have feelings it's fine it's
fine okay one
[Music]
moreas ideally I would want
him would you like to go on a little
trip it's going to be fun I promise no
no not not Tri no you're valuable oh no
you stay right there
this is messed up not going to lie let's
go to iron Paradise come on oh oh oh oh
he took some job what the hell what what
job did he take what the [\h__\h] cleric
okay cleric's kind of cool I might want
to take someone ah [\h__\h] there was
already someone in there realize ah
sorry oh he hated that Ah
uhoh that's okay does that ruin it
forever no he's more expensive but it
doesn't matter if we end up transporting
him hey hey oh he's he's running away
from me oh where's he going do you want
to go to the iron farm
sir I'm oh oh karma karma uh Hey keep an
eye on him keep an eye on him got it oh
he got in the same boat as the
child oh okay that's fine that's fine
for now um we can force him out of the
boat and get him into the second boat
yeah sounds good or oh no never mind
might not be NE Neary because plan is
now it's it's it's becoming night time
yeah so they will go up themselves there
no other available beds right exactly
I'm hoping that the other villagers are
coming back to their house as Welly come
on guys so I'm going to keep that open
yeah these two can you please go to
sleep or
what go to sleep
please go
go yeah now you're thinking about it
push push push
push okay good good get back in there
options to run what are you doing why
didn't you want to sleep I know you
sleep always so early come on okay
okay want to want to get back
home
push push push push hold on what are you
doing delivering a child pushing a good
yeah there we go okay I there's some
more missing but this is okay um I'm
almost back to you
cie actually that go I'm going to need
to make a zombie come here at some point
we'll get to that in a sec yeah
villagers no go to the beds I'm watching
them go to the
beds destroy desty them and then they
fall into my
trench
okay and then and then I'll cover the
hole just really messed up but
okay okay I'm coming to do step two all
right thank you for the help of the
villagers yeah let's go I hope this
works fingers
crossed oh he's going he's going well oh
sorry no bad well he he might no now
he's his priority now is probably
fleeing but come on he's caling down
it's okay it's okay he's going he's
going child is also going up see see
Chad this is easier than having to make
rails yeah yeah woohoo we got it now
hope fall in fingers crossed okay try
one TR for sure fall
in yeah fall down dummy good job good
job uhoh push push push yeah yeah push
him yeah wo ow oh oh okay he almost died
from the fall but he's alive good job
Kellie got thought thank you we did it
that was the last time that they saw
daylight super over for them wa we did
it you did it Callie y oh there's a
little bit of daylight here huh MH
that's so nice a little bit oh yeah you
know it oh you can go down there what
it's what is it like down there and I
need to see I see what I need to
do I need to get this boat we can visit
them
yeah and let's see don't you need a
captive zombie to threat the zombie is
the next
part Kelly I think you might be might be
the fifth member of Justice with how you
are imprisoning these people what can I
say have a great sense of
Duty okay let's see said the boat is too
far what is the boat for I don't know
how to keep the how to keep the boat
over here though is the
thing not sure what how where the boat
is the boat what captures the zombie cuz
I think the zombie goes down these trap
doors and goes here and then they see
him but I just
don't if we move The
Boat Boat need to be at your side not
near a villager yeah guess cuz if it's
that close it would hurt the Villager
right exactly so what we do is for
example we need to be out of here and
then I guess I'll put the boat yeah so
I'll show you sorry over your head okay
here I think it's it's like
this yeah yeah but what if the zombie
gets close to them you can remove the
boat for now turn off the light for
spawning them I think that that's
what's the zombie once it's in the boat
it will not move don't worry oh really
okay so we just have to lure him down
here then is the thing I think that's do
that I think if we just yeah make a
place with no torches right now yeah
like a dangered Zone and then we he runs
after us anyway so yeah yeah I'm
watching in the video they lure him and
then he fall how do you usually get out
of here do you just mine the block uh
yeah you go up and then you get rid of
it but let's see they trap him okay
first steps he'll go down the steps into
the boat
automatically everything is done right
with your farm you should start in a
moment
just be careful in case you get more
than a zombie yeah all right all right
ready um okay then oh wow okay the video
is really long but the creation part
really actually isn't long at all okay
all right shall we remove some torches
maybe yeah but uh where do you want to
do it up there I wonder what would be
best can zombies climb stairs would be
so
close no he he can't climb the stairs
but
if we spawn him up here I
guess I guess that could
work that would be best we get rid of
the Torches I feel like he might spawn
egg and chest we still have
one oh really
what wait we can climb stairs there's an
egg ooh in the chest really that would
be a perfect usage but which chest boat
needs to be
sideways like I'll make it I don't know
if that's true but I'm just going to to
do it
anyway we the one we had before we used
no bottom chest top right what bottom
chest top bottom top right
what
what I just opened
it that we have a turtle egg
[Music]
that
one me
out fine turtle
egg oh you thought it was a okay you
thought a they thought it was a zombie
egg that's okay yeah that's fine we'll
spawn him now we spawn him now just by
removing these yeah but if we get
something that isn't a zombie we're
going to have to try and kill it
mhm with all of our might Chad will it
Spa in our presence
or let's keep it Clos it's not a zombie
first so that it doesn't fall down and
hurt
them no it will not spawn in our
presents only 16 blocks away okay we
might have to go go away okay and look
from maybe a different uh rooftop okay
sounds good maybe over
there uh Beware of creepers
let's watch from here what a good
idea that should watching
party
okay maybe use fences to stop things
from leaving the roof ooh true he might
jump down once he sees us yeah fence
okay I can make a fence really
quick the villagers won't die if they're
stuck down there will they
uh no they won't die okay cool just
making sure they shouldn't fingers
crossed something go wrong but surely
not right guys
right no
way fence there's a fence it's fine what
where
fence it's on the bottom there is but oh
there okay
okay let's
see I just don't want to make too many
fence
pieces uhoh oh my
God what the
heck what on
Earth are you
good you good I kind of saw that coming
I was climbing up the ladder like not
seeing anything at the moment I reached
the top there was this big spider right
in my
face oh jeez oh my heart hey at least
things are spawning we might need to
wait till tomorrow that's good that's
good spider is dead now we wait for a
zombie yeah oh yeah I was going to make
a fence but I'd rather wait it's
probably F the spider did jump down so
oh it did all right well the sun's
Rising anyway that's fine um oh uhoh the
chat provides various suggestions such
as using a Zombie egg creating a special
zone for spawning monsters and checking
their chest for Zombie egg yeah that is
true Minecraft streamer asked the chat
for help figuring out how to lead a
single zombie without trouble yeah yeah
good I actually decent he's figuring it
out decent
analysis maybe better to create a 24
block Bridge into the void so you can
control the spawn better no
[Music]
no no that
this is the
most horrific how do I say it's hi hi
just really it's
just the different blocks are really
bothering
me even though I'm the one responsible I
did this to myself but
still into the void is kind of scary I'm
going to build that way yeah
I'm short a couple fence
pieces it's looking pretty weird cie not
going to lie we'll wait till you see how
it works
chat and then you'll be proud of
me how many blocks
16 1 2 3 4
5 can't
count 24 it's pretty though that's a
piece of modern artwork one 2 3 three
four 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 it should be
[Music]
here 13
uh
15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 maybe one
more for good
measure okay Kelly yeah jump on the
carpet and come over here although I
guess it will take some more time until
it's night time again okay oh we can
wait nice I see what you did and then we
can come here yeah sounds
good wait all right let's go do other
stuff then while we wait can you sort
the
chest I don't want to but yeah I
will you don't want to anymore nah I've
lost my I
touch no it's okay though I'll do it
just cuz I don't want to doesn't mean I
won't does not mean I
won't also wait I guess I should put
torches on our Bridge otherwise it's
going to spawn on the bridge oh yeah
good
idea and I make it a little bit more oh
it's already pretty
dark are these a
problem I don't want to metal to much
with Callie's
build it's
fine don't you
worry
okay the torches on top of the dirt is
it okay if they're temporarily removed
call I think it should be okay
okay we won't want them there when there
are like Golems well I guess it doesn't
really matter they're not in there in
the original build of the for the
tutorial anyway so just get rid of them
okay we just want a dark for
now oh no no huh oh ah okay I see we can
put that back oh God you're scaring me
so much damn
it ah there's a p out there okay I I I I
need to put some more water back into
your uh
uh okay that's fine no
problem are you good as long as the
Farmland is
tilled am I going to need toes all have
to be tiled all of it yeah it it
prevents them from spawning uh cuz I
don't want Golems to
spawn on those areas oh oh that's the
job he took
up that's ah he went to the potion
thingy okay he brought some water it was
uh right here so that's it
nice it doesn't look tilt though does it
only these these blocks on the side look
tilt yep that's there it's only those
that are supposed to be tiled okay then
all is good in the tutorial but I'll
double check and make sure it's not like
a double that I missed but I don't think
so keelly you being able to build this
kind of inspires me to also build
something like this sometime ah why I
just follow I'm just following the
tutorial but I to try and do something
where's the lava this is a non lava
build it's slower though I think with
the iron but that's okay I don't care if
it's sler
okay I just wanted it to work how our
villagers we don't need like endless
amounts of oh God the Villager why is he
in the boat he shouldn't be allowed to
be the boat is meant to build
underground to make it work you will
have to spawn proof the spawn proof the
area of
7117 with villager at the center in
short it will be very hard to make it
work reli
ibly understand 7 by 13 by 17 oh it have
to be spawn proof you mean you mean
light it up or
the it will work it will work we'll make
it
work 17 1 17 the one in the boat used to
be a baby the small hit box let him get
out of the bed area oh my God otherwise
the Golems will spawn out of the farm ah
you have slabs ah hold on hold on I
think I see what you mean but the area 7
by 13 X 17 I don't really understand
that what what like seven eh what what
does that mean so we should turn the
other areas void is spawn proof already
true like in that direction it should be
okay where there's only
sky this direction towards our island is
the problem maybe we'll fix it at night
time m
freaking babies man I swear to God I
can't let him tutorial first and then
fix yeah we'll just make it work once
and then we'll see if the Golem spawning
elsewhere is a problem for real yeah so
Cy you understood what they're saying
yeah I get it I understand they might
just spawn nearby instead of inside of
here here which is not what we want
yeah got make sure they can't spawn on
the yeah I get
it yeah you need to make everywhere
around not a place things are able to
spawn okay but like how far out when you
say 17 13
17 uh yeah that seems yes compated like
17 blocks in that direction or like
should they be slabs right I feel like
the reason that they did it that that
way in the tutorial is because of the
location of the villagers being exactly
where it is then this is exactly where
they would spawn but oh I don't know
tall oh
yeah it's fine figure it out you can
cover the area with
leaf and remove the beds
nearby yeah their beds are gone well the
ones underground maybe they mean the
maybe they mean the myth beds
too oh these guys can't get out they're
trapped anyway so good luck to them if
they want to get out cuz they
[Music]
can't build one in the sky and cover the
stairs with torches they can only on
that
area um okay they won't spawn in car
okay I'm going to make some carpet
then yeah spawn on carpet right yeah and
slabs but have to be placed correctly
maybe carpet might be
easier okay sheepy come
here hello sheepy
nice we already have things of white
wool cheaper you doing
here they're like all over the place
Shrek Shrek come on go to your bed wait
let me try to lead them back in now that
we what the Shrek doing don't have
this issue anymore we're figuring it out
guys got this oh sorry sorry sorry sorry
why are they trying to leave
why are they trying to
leave come back in it's isn't it night
time the villagers cuz they figured out
what we're doing oh it's not oh my God
come back
in they're done with our
treachery it can't be helped okay it's
not nighttime but soon soon soon soon
yes I'm going to put some carpet
down they wanted the they wanted to use
the Bell they should I use the Bell
ding oh it's genius that I have the Bell
it's actually that was a good
purchase nice when you ring the bell
they go inside their house a oh oh come
on come on come on what are you doing
get yeah my disaster [\h__\h]
coordination is going
oh F that's kind of mean don't you think
no he's so stupid come on let's go let's
go let's should I have bring it again
huh
oh come on time to
go oh why are you so
stupid did you put a hopper in chest no
this isn't one where any Hoppers are
necessary you have to manually go pick
it up but it's okay because um I I saw
what how it works and it's not it's not
like perfect but it works just just
trust me you'll understand it will work
yeah it's like I said it's it's it's
like a very easy one where it's not
about maximum saving up iron out like
whenever you go grab iron there will be
Iron there it's just I think there's a
limit it it'll be like a stack like one
stack you need to go once every 26
minutes or it'll despawn but that's fine
I don't really care about fine it will
despawn yeah just because there's
nothing to collect it the iron that
falls down is the thing you have to go
collect it yourself but every time that
new iron appears it like Stacks up again
and it resets the timer for despawn it's
night time now do you want to come over
to the platform yes okay one sec we can
upgrade it later I think there's an
upgrade option for upgrade later so it's
fine okay I'm coming but first we got to
make sure we got to make sure that uh
the one villager gets back in his bed
cuz the baby grew up Tiara the baby grew
up and he he slipped through um but he
got in the boat he got in the boat oh
okay no problem we can fix that so we
can attempt to fix that a that's funny
you're not
leaving fine just got to let him I might
have to open this up is that okay for
you that's fine yeah try that just
replace it
afterward ah okay ah there we go okay
seems to be here yeah close sorry oh m
okay now boat okay the boat back right
oh I got it I'll place the boat or you
can place it it just needs to be
sideways is what they say yeah and then
jump over
it you know what you're
doing sideways
yeah
Kiara not fair not no not fair not fair
not fair not fair I glitched through it
and I lost my diamond
pickaxe wait oh God
what if the same fate befalls
me Callie not you too this is what we
get for playing God I never should have
entered the boat we should have put the
floor
below because that happens a lot somehow
in this mod there's like a problem where
we glitch through often am also died a
few times by that that's all right you
know the Sword and the picka I'm sure I
wasn't holding anything to to valuable
and my paper I was holding so much paper
that I needed and my lever noing the
[\h__\h] okay we're going to get more
iron glitch it'll be worth it for the
iron it's it's okay can I go into
creative mode and get my things back
that's not fair [\h__\h] glitches are you
allowed to do that in creative mode just
I don't know I don't even know how to go
into creative mode how does it work yes
can I at least like the I I don't know
bu paper bag
oh what do you mean
no who who gives you the right to say no
yeah you don't have the right therefore
you don't have the right I I also think
that the iron farm will help us now get
more and then no o o oi careful Kelly
did you fall again stop I accidentally
entered the boat I didn't want to the
bo that boat is [\h__\h] up what if the
zombie glitches for two we have to make
a floor below
all right well it's not an iron farm yet
but you know what it is it's um
it's yep it's it's an automatic soku
farm so
that's I'll make a floor
below okay because that helped at least
for not
dying ah man here's what I'm going to do
I'm actually going to break death First
Care
okay make it make it taller uh um
where's my stone
color yeah that'll
work St col in here where's my stone
cutter what the cows
H
why all right why see if a zombie spawns
c
c c where it c ah there ah I'm right
because of him
H yeah man that's really [\h__\h] sad we
lost some Co stuff I'm so sad spider
skeleton I don't have any weapons
actually to beat those guys up oh yeah
me neither now because I lost
it okay is there something else I wish a
zombie would go ahead and spawn and I
think one Infinity bow also fu
F were you holding the Bodacious
bow I don't know if it was the Bodacious
bow but it was one of the two Infinity
Bows Oh it might have been the Bodacious
bow dang
it that really [\h__\h] sucked I'm trying
to go get some weapon though so we can
kill them
yeah yeah kill them or at least like
protect ourselves from the others that
our you
know way that's all right fine mine is
fine get a sword or something that
really sucks yeah it does yeah it does
really
suck well these things I guess we have
to make sacrifices with them but it
doesn't mean it's
fun that's a that's a setback that
really pisses me off yeah it's not the
funny kind of setback that's all right
we'll make more bows and we we'll
enchant them with infinity I'm
sure do you want a sword I can make you
one sure I can go sword here iron sword
take it take it behind you all right
cool I'll kill him with
this um pickax I don't
know
maybe make sure no creepers creepers are
the number one thing we need to be
worried about
yeah so true come here stupid skeleton
uh okay ouch ooh ooh they're already
there huh ah he's awaiting you yep
nice we got him the spiders went away oh
he can climb the ladder
yeah hold on our battle will be
legendary okay all right um where are
you oh there on a bridge just praying
for oh there's a zombie down there
Ching he can shoot so far wow what the
heck [\h__\h] he's following you me get this
try try to kill him zomes trying to
shoot me right ah o o
oie hold on sorry the animals are free
close it
here
zomb oh it's a blood bath here why no
zombies why I died oh no at least my
stuff is still here oh no there's
creepers we kind of need a bow to get
rid of those now yeah I have a zombie
though he's chasing me it's a skeleton
can climb a ladder can a zombie climb a
ladder too I wonder oh you can lead him
over the stairs I think so let me try
that but if you wouldn't mind helping me
with the creeper situation oh boy
because yeah if you go up there and
everything explodes that's [\h__\h] um no
oh no stop stop that stop that I'm here
zombie all right he's going to follow me
don't kill my
animals follow me okay chaos chaos chaos
chaos chaos do I wish we could put him
in a boat and drive him but I feel like
he's going to hurt us I'm over here all
right he's following me it's working are
there creepers up there though yeah wait
try try to go in a circle with him for a
moment all right you got it
um uh bow bow bow no bow here okay wait
wait go go keep on going in circles I'm
going to go get a bow you got it please
don't see me creeper please oh he sees
oh the creeper sees me okay it's fine
he's stuck in there the creeper can't do
anything he's stuck cuz he's a
dummy H arrows arrows arrows arrows
arrows arrows arrows arrows arrows I
have 12 oh it's okay I'll I'll probably
I have some okay I got it and now uh I
got to go up from a different
wayse how did you get up there a stairs
that I built okay okay I'm I'm here I'm
here all right the creeper right
there get him beat him o he fell into
that's well I can get him from here
right yeah surely oh he's still alive
okay Gra
okay yeah break the
fence okay anyway
creeper
die
and die Not Dead uh now they're both
dead okay let's go all right come here
zombie he loves you he's following you
so much he wants to have us an autograph
don't go
down okay you think he will go down to
the boat so far he doesn't look
interested it's all right you got to go
this way way we got to line up the
platform now that we have him though
yeah okay come this way cuz he still
wants you oh okay I
think no oh no he's rning
ah no stop
Bing stop no oh okay wow he
lives oh oops well that
works clutch clutch absolute clutch why
supposed to go though let me watch the
tutorial but I feel like you should
go ni safe yeah yeah I don't know maybe
it's hard for TR he falls in the trap
door
okay he falls in the trap door can we
push him some make sure it's on top of
he's going now he's going now oh nice oh
wait now he's yeah he's going towards
our Direction now m
I sense him think he in the boat let's
check if I think he
did he's in the boat H he's standing
next to the boat interesting how he
didn't get into oh
no okay that was dangerous cuz he was
hurting
oh oh no ah the boat moved like into
the uh into the
uh and then he sat in it and destroyed
himself it's okay we can get another one
you think the same thing will happen
again
though um we'll make it work we'll make
it work okay I'm just uh I don't want to
die by this boat again I agre should
work yeah no Dying by boat for any of us
in the mean not sideways though yeah I
feel like the sideways is important so
that he doesn't hurt the villagers maybe
okay I think that's what was getting at
but not totally
sure don't place the boat sideways then
no need to be sideways okay I guess it
was one guy never mind oh okay there was
one guy well what about this place Bo
were so glitchy in this version for real
man make more car you can't attack in
the boat okay
um
okay
[\h__\h] no no
okay I have to uh get rid of this stone
for a
moment
probably it's okay do whatever you got
to do I trust
you why does it move around so much why
is it got to do that that's pretty
Annoying It's buggy
okay that's not a sheep it's a polar
bear oh that cat cats have the Zoomies
look can them
fly um I think the trap doors need to be
open not closed the villages needs line
of side well all of
them
uh
of but then what if the villagers run
into when they wake up what if they run
into the
zombie uh
I
yeah he I he seems like once he sits in
a boat he can't attack them so but they
do say close the trap door but if they
walk into him though that could be
problematic uhoh it's okay I I'm too uh
dramatic it's fine no wait ah oh H close
uh is it open up there close uh okay
it's fine that's fine it's fine it's
they can't go up there come back come
back to bed come back to bed come back
to bed uhoh you
[\h__\h] come back to bed okay we just
need a we just need be night one guy
what the trapo is one
guy TR hard to tell yeah it is how did
it look in the tutorial did they have it
down I'll go check again but I believe
it was the way that I left it let me see
hold on a sec I'll check I feel like it
was several guid not yeah there were
quite a few okay so when this person
leaves so making the steps
up
okay and there's that boat
in there trapo is closed in the tutorial
the boat placement is very specific
there too overall the tutorial has the
instructions there okay the boat does
look like it's sideways but I don't know
how they placed it let me see how they
placed it there's a chance that the trap
door is a little bit too high like one
half of a block or
so
maybe maybe maybe oh I don't think so I
was very careful
it hold it
[Music]
no it's okay I can make some out of
these did you fall it was open I didn't
realize it was open here what the [\h__\h]
wait is this that trap door is please
look at the trapo tutorial person they
go back inside they'll go back inside
open
I'll go back
inside the f is on your
platform okay uh that's a different one
please turn around tutorial
man it looks like it's up he left it
up yeah he left it open that's
okay oh did he leave the Bell hey one of
like they both left because the the oh
the trap door was open oh my gosh those
freaking jerks not uh yeah yeah the trap
door yeah but it's okay uh we can we
still have two so we can birth one more
out of them okay sounds good you know it
just takes just two of us you and
I we can make it if we try I'm going to
go get some bread for them in
advance okay yeah it looks like the trap
door is open okay
well I'm going to trust it
then M Mia M
Mia why are these things not like why
can't
perfect oh what are you doing here oh
what's he do oh he's stuck
there is it a
villager yeah currently they're like in
the water or around the water just don't
worry they will go to their bed okay I'm
just going to prep some bread red they
can't another zombie although that place
is not lit up right now so once it gets
night time it's kind of dangerous for
them so we'll have to be fast for them
to get to bed got and protect them
protect in case something spawns no
problem this is riveting this is
exciting riting ribit ribit ribit like
froggy
waa
Ribbit okay he's planning his escape a
too bad for for him it's not going to
work out this is no sha shank come on
silence if I ring the bell from over
there you think they'll react on the
other side CH wonder the other side of
the
world okay I'm going to ring it see if
they're going to move to Towards the bed
okay probably not right nah they're not
moving they seem like they can't get out
those so I probably need to provide them
with a block or
something uh oh m m i oh they're really
trying to get out let me see okay I got
some bread for them I'm trying that's
one thing put a block down for you wait
how did you I can't get a block I mean
you work they can't climb up
guy shouldn't you be here can you go up
there how did he get there this game is
so glitchy I have to stop the water all
right uh I'm going to need a water
bucket one sec get yourself to safety
please my man please the water is
preventing them from moving oh this is
really hard to break okay just use my
gate oh yeah he was escaping the zombie
but like how did he get over the fences
and stuff come on move
move [\h__\h]
it where's the
bucket I don't know where the bucket is
there was a bucket I was holding a
bucket now it's
gone bucket iron but it's we need use IR
to make iron use iron everything's gone
iron everything's gone everything that's
okay still going to make this
[Music]
work need to collect paper
again carpet on the fence top you can
jump on it yeah but then can others Jump
On It villagers jump on
it it's chaos but you can recover mhm
but you know what I'll never be able to
recover is those pickaxe and
swords I can try to make something
better though come on
yes okay
yes no come on up here what I think
they're figuring out how to
jump they can escape
surely use a smithing table to lure
them that
work they they just want any kind of job
so yeah carpet stopping them oh my gosh
all right
I'll give you a nice path back home by
home I mean your
whole they're learning they want their
freedom too freaking
bad I'm going to light this place up
just because it's getting
dark yeah um only one torch though yeah
we'll light it up so that some the
Villager can get back to bed and then
we'll unlight it again so that we can
spawn enemies AKA zombie
yeah sounds like a plan oh they're
already back in no oh no they're there
oh okay okay
okay they didn't want to go up the the
blocks you placed they were they did for
a second and then they
stopped aren't their beds close right
below yeah their beds are down there
they're trying to go there and they
can't get in there oh oh
maybe
maybe the pathing
I think we're stuck here no we
could uh get rid of them once
[Music]
or or okay idea yeah break the wall I I
guess I could but no wait wait don't do
that yet how about we we make the block
closer to them wait I guess they can't
really go up there and we need to move
the carpet I'll get rid of the carpet
make it easier for
them how about now come
on they're like nah dude the beds are
right
there you
think oh dude I could could buy another
uh uh Bell although no I guess they're
already wanting to go aren't they they
under their feet
knock through the wall just break the
wall okay if it's really right below
yeah do you think it's okay to for your
build like you know what you build like
maybe uh they we just we got to
try is that where it
is maybe I have no
[Music]
clue
wait oh
oh oh is it is is there a hole now uh
maybe we'll find out I see you I don't
see a hole from the from below yet hold
on oh wait you're there oh oh hi come in
here dummies ingrates they can probably
go through there we got to push them
into the
hole pushing we can do oh yeah push them
wait where are they now are they done
with you didn't they follow me oh
there's one of them came
in where's One them went to the bed
what the hell is the other one
uhoh oh no they're both in the bed
they're both but there's one
EMP yeah cuz yeah that's because one of
them just disappeared but now that's why
I made some bread we can just feed them
again
oh wait I want to go for your hole uh I
know that sounds weird but I just mean I
want to go through there weird
thing so I can throw the bread at them
yeah and then we got to close up the
hole
we got to close it you're you're not in
the mood huh okay let's sleep first but
are you sure you're not you feed him
tomorrow
yeah you got to close up this
hole it's a good B bread throwing hole
though not going to lie it is kind of
nice but they'll be able to escape
through
it I don't think so you don't think so
they can't jump up these slabs no no no
really wait we can make one block uh we
can close one block but don't let's not
close we're going but we're going to
need to fill it with water
eventually after we have the third
villager again I think cuz then we can
fill it up again okay we got to go step
by step with fixing this chaos yeah and
we might want to do I have some torches
no I lost all of them oh nowh just stay
there apparently it won't spawn as long
as you're
there let me go grab some okay that was
really dangerous H I'm going going to
quickly go below and make
a uh bottom floor so that the disaster
from previously never happens ever again
good
idea in your version the farm only works
if they have their workstation available
putting it in in the wall behind them
should work your Workstation
none of these guys are assigned to any
work
though an escape attempt gone wrong they
never had a
prayer I don't know I don't think these
guys have assigned
workstations okay okay
a oh how did you how did you get down
here okay building floor below need to
be able to sleep
yeah I see a lot
ofing opinions but that's
okay
[Music]
confusing he use boat hacks too
maybe a [\h__\h] boat man sorry I'm like
so mad at that boat and the
glitch you have the right to be angry
I'm also very upset MH
dang it oh well do we won't spawn there
oh should I like you should build with
bottom up yeah okay
okay uh dude don't go
there you're so close
we are really close to getting it
done
yeah it's too bad the zombie destroyed
himself though I hope that doesn't
happen
again I was saved him clutch from one
situation but I couldn't save him from
all of the situations that's
okay need a boat a
hoe hello villager there's another
villag that wants to come up here oh
don't you just come up
then oh you think you can bring him
up there's a bed for you if you want oh
probably should I don't have any blocks
but yeah he looks he's looking at me
like he wants to come up
here does he have a job I don't know
he's just standing there if he looks
really plain then he doesn't have a job
if he looks like he's wearing some fancy
clothes then
he does have a
job might be my clay guy
oh oh no he I think he's got a bunch of
different items but they're not really
useful
items h no no they useful because we
often we have a lot of clay and we can
uh exchange for emeralds oh yeah mhm
well he's standing right here for some
reason so maybe you should take him away
or tell him to go somewhere else cuz he
wants to go to this bed he's a bit
confused he used to be with the cows now
he's confused because the zombie the the
enemies were like hunting him down oh go
back down
then go back
down as long oh yeah right cuz it's twoo
true [\h__\h] one guide again because
it's not like enough space for him to
spawn
anyway
end just in case I'll try to build below
any
wait oh wooden
ho
okay eight and I want
axe
yeah all right we're going to make this
work I'm telling
you oh it's so much oh
dear which part this
part no he's on the
[Music]
dirt where you got to go
it's all so difficult why so
hard why we don't we can't even really
guarantee the zombie is going to not do
the same thing again but fingers
crossed so all we can do is cross our
fingers and our
toes 2.5 LS might be enough for the
Golem but like the half they he can't
spawn on the half oh my God you guys
yeah this might be tall enough for him
but he can't spawn on the
half
M on the bottom
half nobody actually knows nice deflect
yeah it's
like Bo flip Bo flip Bo
flip you you say something you try to
one guy me and I go Bo Flip boin Flip
that's I think it was a was it a scrubs
thing you know the the guy what's his
name Ted actually like in Scrubs uh the
guy uh who's like sweaty the sweaty
lawyer of the hospital uh he's really
nervous all the time and he has no no
confidence and stuff and people people
make him especially the hospital CEO he
makes him feel so insecure oh that's not
nice and then yeah in order to not be
affected by what his boss says to him he
goes like Bo flip Bo flip I think I
vaguely remember that yeah did you watch
scrubs ever yeah it was always it was on
in the background because Mama Mory was
a fan I think okay is there a really
good show I've rewatched it like a
million times yeah
[Music]
nostalgic right I'll put this
back yeah I think as long as it's where
the uh The Villages and the boat is that
would be helpful but the rest doesn't
necessarily all have to be covered can
you stand where like even if it's not uh
below even if it's just above them can
you stand where the villagers are
roughly
sure is that here okay okay cool
D no problem appreciate it yeah
hopefully we can get another one in here
just for us yeah yeah rip the last
season yeah the last season was bad oh
hate to hear that it's okay we had so
many good Seasons you got to appreciate
the good things you can't always hate on
the bad things just appreciate the good
things you
got Wise Wise
Phoenix wise
words okay okay I think that should be
good hey oh wait
you where did you come from gra door is
to be horizontal how many villagers are
down there right now
two well did he lose his job I guess ah
is it the potion guy but he lost his job
okay he's probably going to die down
there although he would be the perfect
candidate to put up there if I make him
some stairs
it's so complicated I'm just going to
birth another one yeah birth
another they should be fine they can't
actually go in
there okay I'm coming back up and I'll
help you birth the third villager are
they awake right now surely they yeah
they're
awake Mor's
not all right we're close push him off
push him off no o
he's a he's an emergency villager if
we're like really really need if we
really need one we could have one from
there that was Co okay we oh wait I'm
going to the bread throwing Place bread
hole oh
my oh hi I throw the bread so the bread
behind
BRB yeah so we can close the bread
hole I want to put the water
back
yeah also no they don't need
workstations beds should be enough is
what Shad has said a lot so we're going
to see if that works if it doesn't work
then we'll try that I think the
workstations would just be helpful to
get them to where we want them to go cuz
they usually when they have no job they
just move towards the workstation to get
a we trapped them see look there're are
prisoners going to bread
them okay yeah I I only have 16 so this
better be enough for you
guys he's feeding the prisoners oh no no
no don't be so
greedy don't be so greedy why why you
want what do you want from
me make love to each other take
[Music]
bread okay okay what's wrong with that
they not want to do it
anymore what's wrong
with small one can escape from where oh
it's okay from this trapo but it's okay
cuz we just we just let him back inside
I think we we can destroy this platform
and then it'll be
fine we'll let him back in watching them
oh they see it's I saw the hearts oh
okay do it do it do it do it doing
it how am I going to escape oh oh no oh
baby child we just can't let the child
oh okay baby okay okay we can't let him
Escape can't let him free so we'll wait
till it's night time and hopefully he'll
be grown up
and okay yeah thank you they were woohoo
woohoo not confidence H okay we're
getting there we're getting somewh the
Villager the bo the disaster debacle
yeah we should I take the
ladder and brow out through the you
could I can take the ladder and
bu
nice that bad boy okay we can close it
up now doo doo okay missing some dirt do
you have dirt by
chance currently no okay I need another
dirt
block
see the baby still go under the slabs
was trying to so far that's okay we fig
it out it's it's easy to fix it's an
easy
fix and then when it becomes night time
we try to spawn zombie again
FY yeah we'll try again we got this I'm
going to replace the water
now you going to take it from the edges
there yes that was where I placed it
temporar o temporarily oh my
Lord oh
okay
now
that
water now just one more
side come
on there we go don't fight it you got to
be one
water uh maybe you could use the
platform to spawn the zombies a no
here's fine it's fine here's
[Music]
fine
maybe
probably
okay seems good and then we need to try
the boat again need to make a boat but
make sure it's I have a boat in my
inventory oh okay cool you see man the
whole boating thing scares me okay but
now there's a there's a flow below it's
just um so when we fall it's okay but if
we do get a zombie to glitch through
there then it's going to be difficult to
get him up again yeah but he'll just sit
down he'll sit his ass down and he will
stay seated yeah what if we rode the
boat sideways and then we glitched
through the floor on purpose to leave
the boat sideways
we can do that now yeah yeah okay let's
try that I can I can try it if you want
I need to eat though I need to eat now
oh God I'm about to
die oh don't worry you don't don't die
in Minecraft from like no food you just
stop moving fast when you fought
this you were living in in danger and
fear this whole time kind of a look half
a heart it's okay I'm good I'm good
now oh half a heart oh half a hunger
half a heart oh well that will it wasn't
regenerating because I hadn't been
eating yeah yeah okay okay Saks don't
need you you die from Hunger difficulty
was on heart oh you can do that like
make it even more hardcore like that
[Music]
interesting yeah how are the cows
make boat boat made okay okay I'm going
to try glitching through the
floor oh look who's back wait you're
yeah you're the right one oh thank God
he's
there SM smer
cow basically it's a cat
basically but I probably should wait for
the
the baby oh oh they're all sleeping
nice they're sleeping we need to wait
for the child to grow up I think maybe
yeah Yep they're
sleeping suya suya oh that means it's uh
possibly zombie spawning time yeah let
me go get a bow for creeper uh killing I
mean should we put him in here before
the baby grows up though cuz the baby
can get through the the hole right now
true we're going to
uh oh wait as long as there's wool up
there I guess nothing spawns at the
moment anyway yeah smart yeah okay hurry
up baby grow up I wish I could hit you
with some bone meal and you could grow
up how long do they take to grow up I
wonder I think tomorrow like in
Minecraft tomorrow he will be grown
nice okay
then um
TR them thinking time books I need
leather I need
Lea do we really have no more leather
anywhere else I chill
here the instruction for boat placement
is at 15 minutes 44 seconds of the video
minutes wait I can buy ah forget about
it for about
it
okay Smite free actually hey I like that
on a sword right SM SM not the worst
I'll try you're not the one I was
looking
for but I am worried about things
spawning on top of these so I'm just
going to chill here for a little bit and
hopefully baby will be grown
up oh we'll figure it
out close door it's for on that is for
zombie and skeleton only okay yeah I
want him to change his job again then
but oh wait you see what's happening
right now there two of them using
one uh table again for their jobs be
happening should we sleep for the night
because we don't want anything to spawn
right now anyway yeah that sounds fine
to
me all righty I'm on my way we will
financially recover from this yeah o o
Callie I'm so did you fall tired
of no where did you fall where it's my
own fault I deserve that I was again I
wasn't car something cool no okay I made
a boat that I likeed
use that boat it's okay matter boats are
very replaceable there's really kind of
nothing I'm glad that I put other stuff
away though thank goodness for
that okay can't do that anymore anymore
anymore you can't do that
anymore any that's cute I put the
important stuff in here because I was
planning on glitching out anyway it's
fine you will be you will be caught safe
sleep by the under floor I think
yeah that'll be fine we're going to
sleep pleas I don't know why I came all
the way back up here cuz the easy way
was always available right here what a
silly dummy dumb idiot all right sleepy
time what's the fall counter for today
yeah we fell why can't I get few
times did you board up the
doors oh yeah cuz I didn't want the
villagers to go to that house but you
can unboard it now yeah an arrow in my
hand how'd that happen good
morning mon
so
well I guess I might just buy it may
he's blown up
now we'll find
out hello
no he's still
baby but I am going to try can they
please fix this
bug well they won't it's not going it's
too
old who plays
1.5 one block who plays
it Debs
please
de we should make it more exact though
only five versions behind was probably
fix a new version I really don't know
why we have this old version but okay
okay oh hello baby no baby go back no no
no baby yeah go back to your
parents go back to them stay in there
with
them what else could I trade grow
up I kind of just really
but what if wait what will happen if I
lock him in can both of them be locked
in oh wait while I'm at it give me
another Ming book stop dreaming of going
to the outside world stop it won't
happen put These Foolish Ambitions oh
now he lost his job okay and then that
belongs to him so actually I need a
second
one actually want to put this here yeah
you're not getting out
same same guys
same I'm like genuinely Hing along with
them what is outside what is grass touch
some cusa touch some grass and you will
know some
cool think waa think come on baby
child it's time to make
new
pickaxe there Bo not
yet not yet I'm going to make it slip
and slide destroy the ladder but why
they can't climb the
ladder corn only chicken here you eat
corn cornfed chicken oo specifically
cornfed chicken I'm a cornfed phoenix
corn is yum I also like it in ramen even
though it's not like a traditional thing
but yes I to be a Hokkaido Ramen thing
right Mis Ramen mhm and I wish they
would combine my like tonu and Misa
Ramen because they have the favorite
things I want in a Ramen just combine
them and then that's the perfect Ramen
for me yeah I really like the butter and
corn in the whole and Mis it makes me
remember the the RAB that we ate
together in Hokkaido County so yum oh
yeah speaking of that I wanted to ask
you do you have like any plans for
vacations in the next months oh let me
think well I kind of I kind of did but
you know I'm I'm healing slower than I
thought that I would true I don't think
a vacation is a good idea there's some
there's some business that that I have
to do this year that
I kind of promised that I would do um
it's just yeah it's kind
of busy even though I didn't want it to
be and yeah I didn't I don't know mining
is
okay travel more but I have to I have to
um is what it
is it's fine try not to travel as much
these days I'm tired tired of traveling
I'm done with it I think we'll end up
traveling either way even if it's not
for vacation true
enough but yeah I wanted to go to some
places too but the summer is really so
busy I know if I can might have to wait
until like Autumn schedule's all packed
huh mhm can't be helped I'll be in Japan
for most of the
summer y
let's go get some
Ramen Mis don't go to Ramen but they
have so many calories y true which is
why we get we get it once thinking about
calories now same it's okay it's
fine oh to be honest I have not I've had
a really poor appetite since the surgery
Noe can you not do acrobatics to get out
please go back now he won't to go back
you FR it's because the beds are so fun
to jump on oh my
God he wants to be an acrobat when he
grows up is he not grown up yet
no I have to leave him
alone oh where'd he go I don't know if
that's true but yeah maybe maybe you
just leave him maybe go mining or so
he's gone oh he's back what do you mean
he's gone he's back he's slippery this
is a slippery little dude Kiara
for a little D's training to break out
he's going to free his parents I don't
freaking think that's going to happen
sunny boy call him Simo M be working
really nicely over here I am curious
about it look he's waiting for me to
break free he's like yep I'm going to
I'm going to slip through the
hole no you're not you go
back come on come
on okay
oh was pretty good should be enough to
enchant the
pickaxe nice to see M working so good
yeah we're going to make the iron farm
work as good well it takes 20 minutes
for them to grow up
okay go find something else to
do I'd love to take it
out ns are nice
Mary M marry myth mining myth Mary
mining mining Mary myth Mary my Mary
myth
mining wasn't quite the previous name
but I like this name
better okay mending pickaxe has been
restored it's not quite the same because
it had efficiency before but we're
getting there maybe this maybe we have
some
[Music]
efficiency ripping Edge for
sword
efficiency was it efficiency free before
perhaps but this is
fine Mary
Mary okay I had a pickaxes back never
happened it was never
gone strong pickax is back
let's mine a bit together for
efficiency together cuz I wouldn't mind
getting
some specific blocks out of this like I
want some bone blocks and
maybe some Emerald blocks that might be
nice yeah yeah oh why are these animals
always walking all over our stuff you
all well this one just spawned oh sorry
I want to I just want
to get it out of the way oh wait they
dropped
the was that a donkey well then if you
dropped me some
leather sorry
cat oh I didn't realize
cat the cat is fine the cat is
fine
no I'm awake I'm
awake I'm awake key are you okay I'm
good I just I want the child to grow up
now become adult like cobal yeah that's
right it's forever a child even though
it claims to be grown up oh my
god get some sleep no you're so close
can taste
it one of the meals was tamed by Ena
well I don't think she needs it and it's
not like she's showing up to take care
of it is she oh I mean yeah that is true
so I shall murder it she'll probably not
even remember it
probably not even be looking for
it so when it becomes night time
hopefully the baby child will have grown
up and then we'll see if we can make him
go to bed and then we'll begin operation
make the iron farm
work it'll be
sick and then you can go take a
nap and then you can play
the Cowboy game the Cowboy game yeah
yeah
Cowboys is there like is there like
gangster Cowboys because in GTA there's
like you
know outlaws like you know yeah Outlaws
out gangster Cowboys are outlaws okay
I'd say so
yeah makes
sense yeah oh yeah it's tons of fun
they're really awesome story too now
we're in the epilog so if you hate
spoilers don't you're busy red de can
rate can wait I appreciate that guys but
it's okay I want to keep playing happy
fun again you need some coffee or
something I've been drinking Coca-Cola
zero today past my bed if I drink coffee
I won't be able to sleep after the
stream yeah all right let me see surely
true true true
it's night
time maybe instead of coffee just like a
black tea or green tea just a little bit
of just small amount of coffeine yeah
that might might be nice coffee coffeine
coffe cof yes he's an adult now YW up
before my eyes now he's going to bed all
right oh placement
time yes uh what you going to get rid of
the
carpet uh yeah let's do it all right I
placed the boat correctly
it's time for to commence the operation
you place the B correctly all right
that's [\h__\h] go all right o luck
potion and
now actually we can leave these
open
yeah zombie spawning time and creepers
probably too oh boy it's go time took a
while to get back to this point did
that's
okay you think this is is good
enough it uh probably better to get rid
of all the carpet to be honest all of it
yeah we can put it back afterwards
okay all right up it goes we're ripping
out the carpet I'll be I'm putting away
important
items well this one I want to keep
though for shooting I'll be fine there's
floor
underneath I don't know why I would
glitch for the world
now shouldn't
happen there still in the water you got
it yeah I got him all right let's
go it's go time go time operation get a
zombie with
taka yeah takamori get a zombie just be
careful when a skele is shooting at you
it's it might you know shoot you down
the edge and send you into the void
again right so we should be right want
that okay but I got a bow so if I see a
creeper or or anything else that we
don't want I'll shoot him down okay I'll
leave it to
you zombie Operation Zombie take two
come on yeah take two
cut come on let's go got to stay away
got to stay away come on zombie
[Music]
there's a
sington okay oh skirlington
now kind of far zombie there's a zombie
too okay I'll take down the
sring and then we should Place torches
soon as possible some more characters
show up go time let's go zombie zombie
zombie do you want to lead him again
yeah although I think he's on me but
let's see oh yeah now he's on you ah
look at Cy look at Kelly look at look at
she's beautiful look at her 2.0 update
now he really likes me right now Okay no
Okay we're okay okay
okay okay okay okay come on all right
all right all right all right all right
now yeah let's uh lead him towards the
beds and I made sure that the the boat
was properly placed he might be stuck in
the trapo now that's okay he starts
moving eventually right oh
uh now he should he can't go back up
anyway oh he can't come on come on cuz
it's two blocks side oh yeah
true there really is a method to all
this
huh come on know you want to go down
maybe it just gives him a sec it just
takes him a
second push push oh no how am how am I
how am I going get down get down you
bastard y y
I got you get down why are you not
hitting me anyway we friendly now okay
we're chilling get out you can escape
I'll thank you we got to put it back uh
oh okay we got get down we got to put
the block back come here come here y I'm
going go my Wood's gone he ate
it we were friendly for a
moment you have a block you can maybe
place in that oh oh there we ah good
good good good is there a block we can
place see his green head is he staying
there or is he he left he went away
oh H I wonder if he's in the boat it
worked he is he's stuck in the
boat so wait let me let me see this he's
in the boat they're not attacking each
other oh this should be working Ka gen
op Genie genius genius as ingenus op
yeah why is it not sorry sorry I put the
carpet there
okay where wait huh where's the block I
just had uh it fell uh oh did you pick
it up oh maybe block do yeah all right
let's carpet up the whole
area
yeah we might be missing one carpet
maybe that's okay go down and get it
let's pray that this
works fingers crossed everybody pray
prayers please hands in prayer oh boy we
need your we need your help we all got
to pray I'm out of
carpets you me pray pray for
Takami yeah
Takami we did it though maybe now now
we'll see it will take a while maybe for
a Golem to spawn so it's waiting time to
see if it works okay a little bit I'm
going to look at the zombie what do you
think Chad how long would it take name
the tag name tag the zombie we don't
have a name tag right
now oh yeah they're pretty scared it
looks
like they're really F maybe a chest will
it's only two though isn't it there's
only two villagers what happened
to it there
third one in there are you sure it's
only two
mhm are you sure let me see where case
we can birth another one it's only
two wait where the [\h__\h] did he go did he
glitch down I wonder let me
check okay so I'm doing
parkour doing
hardcore that's the second time I went
down there Chad
it's the second time it it works guys it
works and blocks that drop here glitch
glitch and go away forever so oh hey
there's a dude
here is it the same dude no there's
there's um there's one dude down here
that I think has been down here for a
while now that is
unrelated yeah that's a different
dude diamonds it wasn't a baby villager
uh he grew
up Hew
[Music]
I don't
know come on spawn here
Golem I need to see this with my own
eyes you can come look but if you
destroy the block uh that's like sitting
underneath the carpet you need to bring
a replacement
block you'll understand when you try to
get back up and you can't and you can't
replace the block see look
that does look like to oh yeah b d maybe
we should try and lure another one and
just drop them in it might be easier if
he grew near a block they can
suffocate
yeah did you watch the moment when he
grew up yeah he became a full grown
adult and then was he like taking damage
or from something what was he doing he
was just chilling in his
bed hm H maybe they're just
idiots I mean can Golem spawn with just
two or does it have to be
three check the ladder D you think he
climbed up or what wait okay wait wait
wait wait climb up lad we can
check
ow he's not I don't think he's in there
but we can push another one in there or
TR but I I'd prefer to push an adult one
in there at this point think so too
let's do that just check from the roof
yeah uh can we do you remember where you
made the a wait what it's okay there's
free in there he was just probably half
in the wall oh well I freed him then
there is the third one yeah what the
[\h__\h] he just he just walks through the
wall and goes back and don't worry about
it it's so
FY M momy why how dare you worry us like
this
silly Sur even chat is like what the
[\h__\h] dude found he's in hiding in our
room will it not is so cool and so
normal mhm yeah nothing wrong with this
mod incredible a known Viller glitch oh
okay he's just like glitching through
the walls and comes back so he it should
be fine it should be fine name the
zombie we don't have a name tag but wait
the the potion people they make they
sell name tags right if I level him up
then maybe let's do that cuz we yeah we
definitely don't want the zombie to
despawn yeah but there should be no name
it's in a boat it should be it should be
no
need I think it's
fine if there's an existing Golem you
might have to kill it eh that doesn't
sound right that sounds there's
currently no Golem I think that sounds
like not true
it won it's endless amounts of
[Music]
Golems set up lava now no this this one
doesn't need lava he dies because he
suffocates with the
water oh yeah yeah yeah yeah kill the
Golem near oh boy Callie knows what
she's doing I don't know I don't think
we should kill the Golem nearby that's a
good guy is there one I don't see him
anymore what happened to him he probably
died like at some point from all the
shenanigans well if he does still exist
though do you think that interferes with
it
no I spawn below
below oh yeah the place that you built
underneath all of this Kiara don't worry
don't listen to chat oh it's not it's
not going to spawn there oh okay cuz
it's bottom slabs they don't spawn on
bottom
oh I see I see
smart think you need a workstation oh
but yeah it can't it's it can't SP
no yeah I don't see any somebody saying
Golems don't die in water but if the
tutorial says so it will die in water
they died in this water for
sure the farm doesn't work in
1.5.2 you're using a
1.16 yeah but we fought the that would
be fine we came to the conclusion that
surely that will be fine because it's
just one version
difference oh yeah they will die to to
some we'll kill them one way or another
even if I have to kill them by hand with
a bucket of lava I will frecking
freaking do
it or if I have to shoot them if they
fall down there you know we can just
shoot them with our own
hands other first of all we need it to
spawn
another
Golem I'm going to find him if he still
exists somewhere they died to
Suffocation from the blocks okay there
you go it's the block to kill it will
work believe see I'm going to go find
him who theem if he still exists I think
there is no more
Golem I wonder what happened to
him think he died I could have sworn I
saw him walking around
pretty sure that they need workstations
to summon a Golem okay all right let's
say they need a workstation how would I
make that do they have workstations in
the tutorial no then don't do
it it's fine well something went wrong
somewhere you need the villagers to have
jobs for this to work
right I know that's a whole bunch of
guys but well I did my best I really did
try to make it work
but they don't they don't yes they
don't I
[Music]
try 20 minutes to watch 3 hours to
accomplish barrels on the frot of the
bed easy
fix really
[Music]
there's an easy fix add three composters
in the wall next to the beds oh what's a
composter that's uh the the thing where
you get bone meal out of I think wasn't
that let's go take a look see yeah it's
also a job thingy it's for Farmers oh oh
I see it
you need a bunch of
slabs it's a workstation for
Farmers
oh I see bunch of slabs okay it's pretty
simply yeah try that then that seems
manageable you can't do it Callie you
can do it I'm
trying we'll get there I'm not worried
we got 48 slabs which means we can make
compers more
Le and the NOA turtle
egg okay now where shall I put them now
because of the zombie situation I want
to try and put this behind them or enter
from behind Maybe
[Music]
okay so the
bed close by I
remember oh it's a let's play rather
than a tutorial that's why it's so long
not
[Music]
that'll do it hey my guys you're never
going to be
free letting you know right
now Freedom will continue to elude
you evil
laugh sure they can't climb up here and
we'll be how do get up we are so devious
and so evil aren't
we people so terrified and scared of us
all right I need to figure out how many
blocks love we
are by the ladder makes
sense get rid of
that no
freedom but I can climb a ladder wa know
they can climb ladders
too uh these guys make me nervous
serious what I'm going to do the
Villages from what I saw they're not
they don't seem to be able to climb
ladders okay the skeleton however was
able
to I'm going to put these things next to
each
other you're going to need to be
quick they definitely can okay maybe
they can
what the W current go what the W current
go making
books I have to remind myself
sometimes chat do you also forget what
the wa current goal or you never even
know to begin
with the books yes books books but in
order to get the books there's many ways
to get the books such as you know
trading it then I would want more
emeralds and then for emeralds I would
want I would want more of the other
things blah blah blah so many things
involved and maybe
bread to make more villagers I don't
know why I'm doing this I know no I'm
also making wheat to feed
the cows as well many purposes and this
as
well
yeah I need one to be a blast furnace
because one of the villagers already has
a blast furnace related
job
oh yeah he might be locked in I don't
know if he was locked in cuz like if you
never trade with a a villager that has a
job um if you don't trade with him and
you get rid of his workstation and give
him something else he will change his
job but if you already traded with him
once he will not want to change his job
anymore you know okay what's the blast
furnace called in this
game blast furnish but you might not
have the recipe yet I don't and you kind
of need iron for it to okay we have iron
you got to spend iron to make iron
need
[Music]
oven
need oven cobbly
Stone
yes take the existing one no doesn't
someone need
that um yeah the thing is I don't really
really understand why he still has that
job anyway cuz but I think I only locked
in one of
the guys with that job and it wasn't him
it wasn't I don't know
anymore I only made one but normally one
workstation per villager they cannot
share workstations but this game has
been kind of glitchy and it's letting
them share jobs
so it's kind of difficult to know yeah
it's it's but
Ed so he should lose his job but
sometimes sometimes they lose their job
over time and sometimes they lose their
job just because I replaced let me
actually do that really quickly before
you finish making the blast furnace yeah
I don't know what the recipe
is don't worry about it I don't think we
really need it
okay so I replaced it our Blast Furnace
guys ising
he wants his career gone bottom three
smooth Stone
oh we need the smooth
Stone maybe if we just offer him a
different job he might take
it that could work but you're going to
have to get to him to talk to him about
it I'll talk to him about I have a
little talk I'll have a little
conversation with him maybe you should
go around the back you have to deal with
the zombie I don't know oh there's
nothing here don't oh Oh you mean those
it's okay I'm just going to I'm not
actually going to talk with but oh
there's a creeper in the water oh it's
okay it's okay just as long as we don't
get to wait the zombie is gone what that
happened the zombies gone oh wait okay
uh the zombes gone but they turned into
uh
fers it's hard to see what's happening
here there's a be a work station did you
like leave something compost yeah I put
compost there I was going to pick up the
last comp there's a composter that's
just unplaced though yeah I it it got
stuck I had to break it and then it got
stuck there and zombies in boats didn't
stop despawning before
1.16 okay need to give him a name dang
it is it guys is it the potion guide
that I have to
level for a name tag
sorry Cali this is so seemingly endless
of a process it's okay I wanted to make
it
work
somehow I want to go get the compost for
now that they're
sleeping fishing
Works
fishing you mean I you mean I can fish a
name tag but not in our pond
that one is too small can try giving him
armor that should stop him possibly yeah
the but I was trying to do that with a
different zombie and he just didn't take
any of my
items book guy not potion guy oh okay
okay
okay that's good because I got one
already they don't despawn in 1.52 if
they are wearing
equipment yeah I tried that before
giving one equipment but he just
wouldn't take it he just didn't take it
strange
piercing kill the
creep to
kill need wood I guess I could buy a few
lanterns to level them
up eggs too eggs too not all zombies can
only some zombies can pick up things and
depends on difficulty some zombies
only some you'll just need to you need
to find the right one what they don't
even look different they just all like
there's a percentage of zombies of the
same type
that okay name tag would be a sure
version sure way to do it so I I'll I'll
I'll try to work on that I think Callie
if you want to sleep you're um probably
good to go I can try think we tomorrow
we can finish it
tomorrow I mean you wanted to I think
you wanted to rest right yeah I will I
will well we'll make we'll make we'll
get it to
work now I can definitely try like
getting a zombie to spawn up there is
pretty easy and then learning them in is
pretty easy like that shouldn't be too
much of an
issue but I don't know I'm going to work
on a name tag and leveling my
VES m not
depends like we used to have many just
randomly out of the boxes the treasure
chest from mining yeah so if if just
another one shows up that would be
nice
otherwise you know yeah hey to the
yo we'll see if it works we'll figure
out what out
uhoh oh no not powerful
skeleton ah oh boy that's bad that's bad
that's bad that's bad that's bad
that's oh the curse that curse is really
bad I killed him though oh no still
I yeah you can drink milk to fix it but
it will go away on its own oh he cool
he's dead just keep your health up yeah
he's did he drop something just
experience okay some me
XP do you want to help sorting the chest
one more
time throw the chest if you don't mind
getting the creeper that is up
there creeper yeah in the
water I already took him down oh already
dang
quick okay thank you for doing that all
right I'll quickly empty out this and go
to
sleep it was a tough
day it was a really really tough day
K's going to fall asleep someday the
tough days will
end no maybe not don't think it will
that's fine though I'm having a good
time me too sleepy that's I'm not as
like brain empty as I was
yesterday that's good thanks to the
Coca-Cola maybe oh maybe that'll do the
trick
guesss in there as long as the it's like
decently
organized enough it's organized
enough oh finally more
string yay
oh evanel ah he's back you're
right I was wondering these past days
like oh actually I've been missing
some fan boy
tweets something's been missing for
sure thirsty Fanboy tweets oh hello
villager not like we need you now at
this point but welcome thanks villager
for nothing
villager back up
[Music]
villager just going to keep on swimming
keep on swimming keep on swimming I have
the hiccups
why hick
hick oh God it never stops filling we
could use him to replace the one that
already has a drop how are we going we
can drop him going from the back but you
should wait till they're all
asleep there is a back
entrance it works pretty well actually
oh right you're there too um okay I
might try to trap
him
yeah oh boy
well well that's
okay that's okay where did the trap door
go SC
me where it go where it
[Music]
go where did it
go thanks for the memberships sponge it
up it's
okay feel like there was a trapo here
yay yay
yay but I kind of wanted to get rid of
that so that he can walk out
M kind of stuck how about
this
[Music]
oh oh hi guys oh
he's he's hting the gritty look at him
go oh he took he already took a job he
took the farmer job nice
sit use the why the [\h__\h] won't you sit
this is my last
dump final dump
he might actually go to the bed on his
own again that would be kind of awesome
once it is time if we kill the other one
oh good idea yeah like I said go around
the back and maybe and now we still need
another
zombie maybe it'll work oh he wants to
be farming there's nothing to farm here
sir sir please take a seat take a seat
he doesn't believe
you aren't you already tired from
working
huh nah he's a workolic
be a good boy and
sit he has seting
resistance it seems oh yeah okay he's
sitting
now yeah I don't know is it really an
issue of the the one guy how what do we
think is the issue why why is is a job
having existence a problem I think that
I I'm not sure what it was about the
update but I think that it's very
important that like the job situation
kind of it stopped
marry after one 1.16 before that maybe
it did matter so that's the only reason
why we need to have their workstations
next to them that's my
guess okay they need to have access to
their own work to to spawn hold though
okay to spawn Golems they need to have
access
okay oh wait is this what's this
hole find the back okay I'm not sure
where are
you well there's no zombie there right
now either right so we can lead him also
through although I'm kind of scared
about that now I will I guess go ahead
and
kill this one I'll do it I'll do it yeah
I'll do
it [\h__\h] oh
no I think it's time for me to go to bed
I'm going to go to that's okay that's
okay well we we tried real hard and
everything was basically set up
but I'll fix it for you Callie I'll fix
it I'll make it work maybe you are if
it's not fixed by tomorrow no pressure
though no pressure yeah that's
fine
doesn't wait I shouldn't I'm actually I
shouldn't the friends we made along the
way or would matter
right I'll see you guys tomorrow for
cowy yeah for breathing I sh okay cow I
will be more it was it was fun having
you around yeah let's play again at
least once before the ending maybe that
would
be okay I was thinking probably I won't
show up anymore until the end cuz
there's not
really much to do at this point it's
okay
okay that's fine then I'll see you later
um I might just show up like off stream
to do something with the iron if we can
get it working sure same here all right
well then I guess I'll see you guys on
stream for the
finale bye everyone take care
good Ka be uh uh construct more more
iron yeah yeah not quite yet though cuz
it's not working but that's okay I'll
see you guys around you too K
construct Mory Mory construct constru
make sure that you grab my new album
that's all I'm going to go away bye
everyone check the link in the
description check the link in the
description um oh man I'm going to I'll
play the ads yeah play the ads we love
ads see you guys it's your own ads we
love them thanks K I'll see you guys
you're welcome thank you have a good
sleep with the Kito sounds good peace
out dead dead dead houon we have a
problem I'm sleeping
[Music]
h