[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
hello
hello everybody can you hear me
I'm so sad right now everybody
I'm so sad
I can't believe
is dead
[Laughter]
hold on hold on I bet I'm not unloading
it
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I even got to the most dramatic part I
was like Chiara is dead
[Laughter]
okay oh I changed I change okay did I
change I think okay
I can't believe
Kiara is dead and
frog Chihuahua
exists
I miss her so much
you're not crying you're celebrating
um
do you want to come in now
[Music]
[Laughter]
you got this you got this
[Music]
oh
hey
[Music]
thank you oh sorry frog froggy Wawa
sorry sorry
I'll I'll come over to you all my places
right here
nice to meet you
oh it's uh it's following me oh uh go to
get used to this thing here go to Anchor
and like put it set it to world I don't
know oh stuck on that
world yeah and it'll keep it there
okay thank you no it's still following
me well that's okay oh there's like
oh
I don't know
sorry scuff guys I'm sorry guys sorry
guys
so anyway you you were you were crying
about a certain takanasikiana learn too
um I'm really sad about you know her
being turned into a frog and everything
right now she's right there there she
tasted like like gravy great chicken
yummy so now I I took over her channel
so sorry you can't collab with
takanasikara you can collab with me
though
is that okay I think you're so cute I
think it's okay baby
Maybe
[Music]
yes but I'm also slimy I hope you don't
mind that oh I already felt the Slime
very slime yeah
you like you like the Slime the Frog
slime yeah can I is it okay to like a
like a yes yes
laughs
all right all right I guess that was it
uh uh wait wait
let me
read it
ah it felt like the kiss frog hold on
what did I say change right now
uh
was it a kiss it was definitely
something like a kiss Maybe
I'm trying to find my transformation
[Music]
she's a magical girl
magical translation
[Music]
this is
the Sparkles oh wait hold on oh I can't
I can't find it
is
[Music]
almost
hold on everybody
technical magical difference the frog
and the kiss was not good enough yes oh
here come here I'll lay one on yeah
yay
[Music]
she lived she lived Beach yeah thank you
thank you
[Music]
yeah
what are you doing for more I'm just
brushing your hair It's gotta I'm
getting the I'm getting the slime out of
your hair you know
there should be no slime only gravy
please oh sorry sorry I'm still trying
to figure out this camera guys
confusing me it's different ah there we
go that's beautiful so maybe we should
since this is the first first time
special collaboration maybe we should
introduce ourselves okay okay to each
other's viewers okay
you go first you go first okay
[Music]
something's wrong there's something's
all
righty why did you hear that before
sounds familiariki yeah it might be a
secret secret code word
or something but no please please more
please
[Music]
and
I'm really nervous I feel like I'm gonna
throw up oh God
me too
me to die y'all
from did you say did you send Gian did
you say that make it clear yeah
[Music]
we're both we're both first Generations
yeah but like like kickstarters of
chicks are very special something yeah
yeah
revolutionists
revolutionizers something like that yeah
thank you I am
a Phoenix from Hawaii English to love
myth and I'm thank you very much for
Reviving me because this stupid [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] took over my channel
for like a whole week but yeah
she could really just eat a phoenix and
nothing would happen no no no she had
the guns and everything
yeah but did you know that that eating a
phoenix is the only way to really like
like
make them go away forever if you end up
you know going to an idol meeting and
then like getting rid of her but as long
as she's still the Phoenix still in your
tummy then there's still a chance to
revive and I was still in her tummy she
has a really slow like digestion system
so thankfully you came just right on
time I don't think you should tell
people your secret like that I think
it's a little I think it's a little
dangerous
I think you're inviting a lot of ideas
into the world
nah I don't think anyone else would
would attempt such a thing ever again
right yeah surely I think maybe your
fans are different than my fans but I
don't know
you'll thank your fans would attempt to
like you know
destroy you demolish you get rid of you
yeah I think so we kind of have like a
love-hate relationship
I don't have loyal followers yeah you
got you have like you know everybody
working at you know kfp I have my Arch
nemesis's all of them
oh but you're wrong if you think that
KFC chickens are all really loyal and
supportive some of them they want me
gone too they always ask for like raises
and stuff even though
the reasons to me
look at the audacity right now I'm
hearing I I can't believe this that I'm
hearing this oh
you have a special special bomb wow yeah
pop
oh celebration
first let's go yeah
nice do you have another one of those
yeah only one no I have one I have to
share we have it oh
it's a rainbow I'm like stuck on the
ground oh gosh
thank you
all right so uh one thing I wanted to
say that this VR chat VR stream and we
are going to show each other each
other's worlds right now we're in the
Ninja Sanji Ian world
and then later we'll go to the hollow in
many many various ways yeah you know
show each other
and and yeah get to know each other
because actually it's the first time
that we're talking like this
I was so nervous to join the Discord
like oh God
oh my God I was like I I was I was I was
like um you know setting up together
with Amber and then right before you
came in I was like oh God this is the
first time I'm talking to her
but it's okay it's okay we're just two
two girls nothing nothing to be nervous
about we all just human or fairy or
Phoenix I don't think we're we're not
human we're like
we're opposite of that so that that
doesn't really work that thing doesn't
really work unfortunately we're just
Phoenix and fairy after all doesn't
sound like the same the same way but
they both start with us
[Music]
ah oh true Phoenix and fairies pH yeah
yeah
just uh you know ignore that part
all right so you're not gonna show me
around you just send you one first and I
already I saw this before in in some of
your guys's streams a little bit I saw
it and I really like the design of the
train because this is guys maybe you
didn't see it before but uh let me pick
you up
[Music]
is there like I really like the the
shooting stars outside yeah hold on guys
I gotta get my camera let's see let's do
this
all righty
two things yeah where are we located in
right now where is this train right now
um we're in Diamond lights
City almost we're you know
we're going to Diamond Lake City we're
going there yeah yeah yeah yeah
that would imply that later the whole
livian world is Diamond light City
I mean it could be maybe
so pretty so there's like there's
pillows of of your like gen maids and
not gen mates and so on around here huh
yeah
I know her do you want a hug I want to
hug it it's quite soft that's the first
time I'm ever touching a dakimakura wow
that's like physics let's go
down
where is my camera do you think she
doesn't mind if I like punch it
she might enjoy it even I mean I know I
would
the purple I actually I like to call
Pomo Pomeranian what do you think about
that nickname I love it I'll bark for
you really
it's not like dogs are my favorite
animal but I feel like Pomeranian is
nice nickname for you yeah I feel I feel
we
um we both share a great love of cats
together
yes yeah
I'm putting my show me around what do I
need to see what do I need to look at
okay um first if you would like to have
a sip of tea
there's some tea right there oh yes
please feel free to Tuesday and then on
Tuesday
pick it up and drip drink all of it I
just dropped something oh the no milk
that's that's good oh there's like um
your bosses in here
that's cool
did you meet your boss when you were in
Japan recently oh no I don't have a
chance to this time
I said foot into Japan they should be
rolling out the red carpets for you for
princess ball
honored to talk to you can I have an
audience with you and talk with you
please we need to have a moment
we should we should um
go there again
and then talk to him again I'll bust
down his doors
this way if we go this way yeah I will
show you
oh hold on camera uh camera camera okay
um this is it is this stuff actually
also flashing for you this like it is
this is flashing like crazy I'm not sure
why
let's just if you come this way it'll I
think it'll stop flashing
okay yes it's uh somewhere else now
that's good okay there we go okay oh
this is dangerous
fall out there
[Music]
oh God we're in space
you're like you're falling through
you're falling
I don't think we're going anywhere
we're dead this is a dream or something
oh God no it's like
don't worry about it don't worry about
it it's not a trap or anything at all
yeah
I didn't just that's exactly what
someone would say who's kidnapping me
too then we all you you know we can even
like jump off later if you want actually
Romeo and Juliet this
yeah oh we can jump up yeah
so what do we have here the food area
yeah welcome to the cafe
[Music]
um just like uh I'll click on it and you
become oh
oh this is not made for people like us
mama
um my chat's being voyeuristic
but what are they saying what does that
mean voyeuristic do you want it
oh yeah
foreign
really really so they're being nice
yeah they're looking out the window for
me
oh
fix myself my animal my body moves
really weird today oh weird all right
all right so can I order something yeah
what would you like
um something sweet sweet okay I got you
I got you
um what's something sweet you guys hold
on I know what to get her I know exactly
I know exactly this way this way okay
hold on oh sorry you're in the door one
moment
foreign
let's see where's the parfait you guys
where's the parfait
how do I open the fridge oh gosh I'm
stuck
where's the where's the where's the
parfait
[Music]
s
oh gosh okay I'm on the table we have a
magazine
[Music]
yeah where's Millie's she's a project
leader
who's alone
can I learn how to open I want to open
this this is a fake magazine
what we will we don't publish we don't
publish fake news no
no it's real it's legitimate
where's the real thing oh there's a cake
right here
wait it's not even wait it's not even
it's not even new to Sanji it says here
[Music]
some seems pretty suspicious
oh
am I in a made Cafe yeah um okay
put some magic yeah magic okay the magic
okay
okay I'm nervous now okay okay here's
the magic
me
[Music]
open there we go oh uh can I change my
camera
yes
how how many
made outfits do you or did you own
um
you know that's a bit of a loaded
question don't you think I mean
no no you don't think so no no no
there's a reason why I'm asking that
mm-hmm
because I um
I I used to own like um about
um eight different made-ups at a time
oh mates as well and and I wanted to be
one too and I was smaller my mid nakama
yeah
I had like um you know normally they're
like
um normally the really classic ones are
black with a white Iver
well my favorite one was the opposite
because it looked really offensive by
having the the main dress be white and
then the apron was black I like that oh
sounds kind of sexy I can't see oh fancy
yeah sorry wrong wrong word
I have a couple I had also one that was
like light blue with white oh yeah this
one that was like beige I had a light
blue one too yeah yeah
oh good taste
um one or how many
I've had I had like the traditional one
and like black and white
[Music]
on the blue light blue one I've had like
ones that multi-colored
multicolored oh like pastel colors yeah
yeah yeah
takes one to no one
[Music]
right in front of me I was like holy
[\h__\h] this head is Big this isn't that
big you guys isn't that big
where's my body I don't even know
don't worry I'm the same
it's a disease that's called the Chibi
Chibi body at least I have I have
fingers
but my frog model has fingers this one
doesn't some of us have fingers some of
us don't you're one of the lucky ones
you're at least have fingers you're like
a Powerpuff girl I thought you have ears
do I have ears do you have ears you're
right oh my God we're Powerpuff Girls
were chibis
it's a Glee right if you think about it
the Powerpuff Girls are like chibis
who was your favorite Powerpuff girl I
really like buttercup
wait who did you like
yum
it's hard to remember I think probably
was her name Blossom the orange one oh
yeah yeah yeah what's your original
what's your pink
her hair was Orange right but her but
her outfit was pink yeah yeah
as it's mixing up in my head yeah yeah
I'm not surprised I like the orange girl
she just you know you were a young
Chihuahua you just saw yourself in her
right
Maybe
do you have I think I was watching you
stream uh yesterday as you may know
and I heard this no wait let's add that
I think I heard that from sevens
stream wait I'm mixing up this but but
you had like a you both got like a tea
right and then you oh yeah it was like
pouring it and she was like say stop and
you don't want any more tea and
challenges did not say stop and then it
almost overflowed but you you'll respect
for me
they even said they were like they were
like we won't stop if you don't say stop
so and I told her that and probably that
was probably a mistake I understand
wanting to test it out like how far did
they go I get that yeah
she called their Bluff she did call
their Bluff
oh by the way oh my God you're supposed
to show me around and we're just sitting
here oh yeah show me around please okay
the dessert of course
how do you say you're welcome
uh petition
yeah hold on camera come here
[Music]
yeah there is a polymer rice around here
but what is it supposed to be they're
Doritos
but not Doritos they're
you know
they're a copyright free Doritos oh here
they are right here actually oh gosh
[Music]
oh there we go
oh they exist oh my God there's every
product on that on that menu exist in
here I think so oh just about everything
here's my pomerize
oh
nice
oh here at the table oh
my gosh oh is that where what you were
laying underneath to uh show your your
new outfit that's the one this is the
real thing oh yeah yeah that's the real
thing
that's what was used to reveal your
outfit oh she's stuck in the wall or
stuck in the table oh gosh
oh dear
I didn't realize that
oh
no I'm suffocating
help me
long live the king
thank you
I'm gonna have to clean that mess up
later
oh this is really exhausting okay
sorry guys
we got the Dutch angle going on
surprise surprise I am alive yeah
Phoenix after all right
what's next Pomeranian okay I'll take
you to everybody's rooms
oh everybody has rooms everybody yeah
almost everybody
oh my God okay oh my God okay okay
let's go
I Fall Out Boy yes
it gets really laggy here for some
reason
[Music]
started yes this is where we started
there's some darts there
there's a
there's a game thing there
plays Sky dragons yeah the most popular
game in niji Sanji right now
oh you know I thought it was really cool
when I saw
um you know when YouTube Sanji Ian's
second gen was announced and I saw that
you guys have like uh sister designs in
there
[Music]
yeah are sisters
wait
do you want to go to my house or full
sisters they're half sisters because
they you know they don't have the same
last name different different
Papa right because say mama say Mom yeah
oh gosh I can't reach the door oh
this is so small
oh
I think so actually hold on let's go to
oh this is my room here we go
welcome to Myra oh my God I'm taking
Kiara to my room
[Music]
I'm in here
nice
[Music]
coffee Photon on the ground and then
like a coffee and comfy table where's my
camera what unless
oh God
kfp just like where are we
there we go
can I stream on your channel from here
yeah yeah here I'll go to Kmart I'll
give you my stream key wait there's no
keyboard oh
um it's like a really high tech like you
know
I don't need to look at the keys I'm a
gamer
[Music]
um
do you do you see me sitting right here
do you see me sitting right here
yes yes you're you're in under the
covers
no it's a ghost of me
I'm staring at myself
well now you moved yes what
are you seeing a ghost yeah I think I
think my room is I think my room is
haunted
I will see you there I only see you
there
oh what's going on I don't know are you
are you are you okay
I don't think I took my meds today you
see me yeah I think you're mad
I'm worried about you it's probably
hallucinations I'm starting to
hallucinate too because like the headset
is really heavy it's just strangling my
head the first time we collab and I
hallucinate unusual how embarrassing I'm
sorry everybody everything everything is
a hallucination this is all this
hallucination there's a button here
thank you
well actually you know what when you
were saying um you see yourself that was
probably me because I'm Pomo too oh true
this is approved
this is really quiet though but I hear
it
[Laughter]
so you have this button in in reality
too
actually I saw someone make it for real
[Music]
button
scientists
okay
I was trying I was trying to fix my
headset but it's it's just because I
decided to strangle me today oh it's
okay
me too I haven't worn VR in so long oh
gosh
um it's it's a pain in the butt but
we're doing it for this realistic
experience I really like it though like
it really feels like more real than a
normal clamp yeah like I can touch you
um
you know what's missing in your room
what's that
a box
there's box in this thing you need a box
what a box why do I need a box just a
box
[Laughter]
I was thinking it but I was just like
surely surely she's she's not talking
about you know because you know I don't
wanna
I won't shut up I won't shut up I won't
shut up
oh god well well we all know
won't be going to battle gear solid
convention because she's not a real fan
are you a stalker Kiara I'm sorry if I'm
that's a little direct but
no no I'm just up to date
okay I'm ground Point
okay we'll go next oh next go next oh
next places
oh uh hold on Everybody follow me yeah
go to pinana's room
anchor local terms no I do have banana
room parents oh wait hold on oh hold on
I can open up to the side hello oh why
am I what am I fish
there we go a fish
hello everybody
I can't I'm too I'm too thick wait
really
there we go
oh hold on camera
where are you guys oh there you are
fish they're real real fish
well yeah
she has such a nice room
she does she has a button of her own
bubbles bubbles mother Truckers
[Music]
mother trucker
trucker oh
everybody has a button oh maybe I need a
button too what is this oh
[Music]
let me jump on her bed oh
wait yeah yeah
I'm stepping on your clothes finana
I didn't take off my shoes
foreign
oh yeah acting yeah yeah acting
oh man
A's room yeah
it's very cute I really pretty I like
the scale pattern on the wall and then
at the ceiling there's like
there's a wave reflection yeah look chat
wow
I'm so pretty did I remember like the
design like I mean obviously you didn't
design everything probably but did they
like give like a concept of how they
wanted it to look like yeah I think uh
for mine at least they I kind of just
said what stuff I wanted in there
and uh they decided what to put in and
what yeah what not
I think there's one more room actually
one more
there we go
next is uh is it okay to leave the door
open you want all the doors open yeah
it's pretty safe in here don't worry
yeah I guess there's no one else here
who comes into [\h__\h] outer space to
this tree
outer space is a pretty hot destination
I don't know what you're talking about
[Music]
let's see
she has like a fancy round bed I know
I don't know if that's comfortable to
lay on it's really special
I mean I don't think the shape really
like makes it
uncomfortable
would it be a long legs
I don't think she does though
long legs she's probably about the same
size as we are oh she also what is this
what the real Gamers nowadays have they
have all these um laptops that have no
keyboard at all yeah it's actually we
got a sponsorship for it the um what is
this juice
Nate
[Music]
it's like a lemonade
sentence
talking kick ass
[Music]
wait where
[\h__\h] there's a mangle on the drink
I think it's a lemon
mango
it's manga
oh
man I'm very German I'm sorry
in German it's called mango mango and
anime
[Music]
oh my God
people you also have this when like
people who don't know really what
they're talking about
um or what you do they ask you oh are
you like a manga oh yeah
what anime are you from wait I don't
marry you from
are you like you like Naruto that's my
Naruto run
oh yeah like this
oh yeah yeah look at her go yeah yes
I like how she kind of kept her room
like more like
chill and down to earth like it's not
like finana who has freaking fish
everywhere
yeah this is very cozy all of that stuff
up there I don't oh this is
[Music]
yeah someone made a fan game
for Selena
I I think it's kind of like battleship
is there a death course
actually I don't know Chad do you know
she'll never know we were here I'll put
it back it's okay I I come in here
periodically and [\h__\h] up her [\h__\h] you
know
I think red that's all the bedrooms
what about like what what was the maze
we had one that's right that's right oh
gosh you know you know better than I do
oh gosh sorry guys you're in the wall
oh gosh I'm trying to find my camera oh
there we go
all right so it's so pink
it's so pink oh I'm once again too thick
the doors are not made for Wolfie models
like mine wow
[Music]
the t-shirt is so cute yeah Rosemary's
room is really cute
let's put you here with a rose uh carpet
very pink and girly oh my gosh look at
this Dressing Table
cute oh so girly well does she like
hamsters yeah she has a hamster yeah she
has one so
yeah oh okay
Lord King I like it honestly like when I
was um a couple years younger this would
have been my dream room right I tried to
have my room look like something like
this everything super like princess like
okay yeah me too
I love pink so much but just because all
girly things are always pink for some
reason even though I like like purple
pastel purple yeah I think pastel purple
is like underrated with this kind of
aesthetic yes yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah I like I like the wallpaper in here
though with the Roses oh yeah oh yeah
they're they're like not too strong
they're just really faint yeah
you guys see this it's hard to see
Rosie so bright at the bottom there it
is
okay okay beautiful beautiful 10 out of
10. yeah okay
foreign
now this one doesn't work yeah Petra is
still not sure like who has a room yeah
not everyone has one so
it gets a little confusing
let's just did she not have the funds to
buy um a room here for permanent usage I
can imagine it must be really expensive
oh yeah Space Room in a train yeah it's
you know the rent is like breaking my
back but it's okay you know
[Applause]
I like to make sacrifices for some
luxuries exactly I'm a bougie I'm a
bougie girl
IE girl booty
what does that mean it means like um
Boogie
boogie boogie boogie boogie boogie
woogie boogie woogie it's like a
it's like you're really into a like
fancy things like
yeah I like you exactly
Kiara is a boozy [\h__\h]
nice I like the rooms really they're so
nice and I like the whole train idea I
didn't show but up here at the top it
has like a really fancy you need to
Sanji logo pattern
everything has such a nice atmosphere
there's one last thing I have to show
you and then we can move on yeah okay is
it is it is it a made Cafe this is a
shrine
oh is it a box I wish would you get in
the lovebox
no
no you wouldn't get in the love box with
me
to be true I don't know what the lovebox
is
that's exactly what it sounds like
a w box
I've been denied rejected
yeah I have to I I can't make it too
easy for you oh you're playing hard to
get I get too cool I get you
okay where are we going all right but
not least this this way
back to like oh gosh sorry everybody
hold on let me fix my camera everybody's
going through walls
come here come here
okay
um
um this one
this way this way right here
okay you guys stay here
oh can we go ahead yeah
go up go up go up
well how how there you go
okay open okay now I do the thing
oh gosh okay here we go
might
and three two one
happy New Year
Happy New Year
it's true
so we're getting there we're getting
there yeah it's true it's true
that's oh I knew this was outer space
how many stars are there from
right now in the night sky
um
about seven pounding
six
ridiculous this this child cannot count
and about this this is what this is this
is the job that you get guys if you
don't get to school if you don't go to
school and you don't learn how to count
you become like us a YouTuber I'm a
modern day mathematician
yeah
how how
much is
uh three times nine
the question the real answer is
what does three times nine mean in a in
a cosmic sense
I will tell you in a German sense is
that okay yeah yeah
three times nine means
she really
or she really or you're really we really
don't [\h__\h] want to deal with your
[\h__\h] what
what do you mean
reasons then is this a German language
[Music]
hahaha
I learned I learned think about it think
about it that's actually really deep
well thank you for visiting my German
class today
um so at the end of my German lessons
I say
I'll feed us in so am I supposed to jump
now
yeah oh there we go
[Laughter]
yeah we both jumped together
um
safety precautions like that that bring
you back here thank God oh God oh God
it's flashing
Okay so
nice world you got there I like it I
wouldn't mind going on this train a few
times to travel around the world oh
thank you yeah and space anywhere you
want to go to
no space all right all right but next
we're not going to space no we're gonna
go to
[Music]
and you guys you guys should stay until
the very end because we have something
special plans in whole life and world so
come with us we're gonna go in loading
the screen yes
a moment until we get into the world so
we'll stick around stay tuned stick
around stick around
all right I'm going to my loading screen
right now me too one moment everybody
one moment
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
so all the people who get dizzy from VR
are not suffering anymore
all right I'll be showing you around
full moon yeah I'm excited after I
calibrate there we go all right so first
I show you the the first word we have
many more episodes I'll show you the
first one first
I'm spinning into a vortex
yeah
come here come here
this is we keep on like adding on to
this so it's starting to get really
confusing like a like a maze but yeah oh
yeah I guess since it's right there we
can go to the auditorium first is it
safe it says they're zombies it says
here
there's a zombie zombies infesting this
area where too powerful and broke the
local Quantum metrics please exercise
caution to this hallway okay be careful
don't like hold my breath okay okay
you can't
I know I knocked over oh
yeah there's an area with some props
and like bring into the stage cute
yeah two
2022. why is there is there someone
shoot for this it's New Years here too
oh no it's because it's for your eye
oh I love the breadstick okay and then
you go then you go over here and we have
the auditorium like in a school yeah
[Music]
so cute Devin has a basketball court
yeah oh and we would go up here and this
is where we had that that like special
moment where we were hugging each other
up here and we were like oh I'm gonna
meet in real life I remember that
don't cry don't cry right don't remember
you don't I do remember I do
here I got a breadstick since then we
have met plastic
yummy is it garlic I need some garlic on
this please oh you're a garlic girl me
too
[Music]
yeah nice
yummy bread singing if you don't look
close enough
oh life's sick oh yeah you just got a
false enough
it's like some bread guys dirty maybe
yeah
dirty yellow dirty yellow
bread is superior yeah so this is the
auditorium but let's go next time oh
yeah you're right okay okay okay
I'm running I'm running I'm running I'm
like I'm like a really really stressed
out overworked uh tourist uh guide
the zombies
oh God okay okay
I'm Naruto running I'm not returning
oh oh oh yeah I didn't realize this was
a uh there uh we can like turn on
different decorations here like off
season a little myth anniversary
Halloween happy holidays Halloween is
close so I wonder if we can turn on
Halloween yeah
yeah oh my gosh
it's pumpkins everywhere this is about
the size of your head you could fit in
that one
yeah
[Music]
take a screenshot guys take a screenshot
please please
thank you
and here we have a bar you can get two
classes ranks we have for example
oh
wait I can't pick it up I'm on a table
oh there you go here I am I am going to
serve you yes then Dr oopsie oh would
you like some Dr oopsy
well it makes me have a whoopsie Pepsi
or you know yeah oh no doctor oops did
you see it yeah I do
it it makes you uh be able to hack
through the gate oh I'm chugging I'm
chugging
delicious that's um
that's twenty dollars please oh no this
is one of those this is one of those
host clubs that doesn't give you the
name of the or the price of the the
price of what you're paying for
a friend
depending it always depends on how much
you look like you're able to spend until
you look like twenty dollars experience
of drink yeah
no no no no no that's not what I'm
saying you look like a million dollars
all right and next
we go to the lobby right
um from there we can go to all of our
different uh rooms which are not really
rooms they're more like worlds yeah
we have the the crying golden juggle
okay Fountain are his tears drinkable
yes that's what we thrive on that's how
we are able to stream every day by
drinking his tears
delicious yes
wow
do you feel energized I feel like I'm
ready to
dream for 24 hours oh time for a 24-hour
stream oh
look there's a there's a crystal Tony
tension coffee over here I don't think
you can pick it up but you can look at
it from the other side
change your coffee oh my God
guys because you're the boss
yes and the next one is Toki no soda
that's okay
oh I get it I get that reference
all right which which um which myth
members world would you like to see
first
uh should we go in order
okay
yeah okay
it's kind of Japanese style candy
traditional
oh it's so comfy in here it has tatami
mats yeah big big plushies
lots of books science
oh there's so there's a pumpkin Taco I
just noticed it's so cute
she's so cute
oh
I like this one wait first day do you
think he'll be mad if I take it
foreign
unfortunately we don't have the actual
eating mechanism that you guys had over
there that's something we have to look
into
delicious oh it's gone
give me a nose it made me grow a nose
I look like an animal crossing
anyway I'll make myself a cookie nose
too yeah
hooky nose cooking those oh
oh yeah
[Applause]
wait we look like Muppets
oh God
love chocolate chip cookies
so cute so you know Ina Ina is the
artist of the group shows there's a lot
of art here and it's her at Atelier I
think wasn't there like even
a function to draw on it no no no no
that was oh but I guess we have that in
a different world she's artiste in a
different world we have something where
you can draw yeah at least is
we
[Music]
oh then we have a smaller smaller very
small original
I really like this one because it has
like this Atlantic theme it's really
cool you like fish themes don't you
I actually it's not like I'm a big fan
of of fish but uh I like these
Aesthetics
the underwater Aesthetics wow
step step
actually maybe they deserve it
yeah do it yeah
yeah fancy it looks like it's made out
of diamonds yeah you want to hold it
touch
you've got the power I feel like I'm in
Minecraft
on the Minecraft now
oh yeah oh did you did you know that in
Minecraft sorry
um okay
Once Upon a Time was chilling in
Minecraft minding her own business just
going through the water and then
suddenly she gets attacked by this this
thing and I'm like well hey yo so I kill
him you know they really drop rarely
these videos
[Music]
the first time you ever killed one
oh my God
she's cracked
it was it was
it wasn't me she's a gamer oh and say
that
she's okay I bow about you oh
there's there's an archive of that if
you guys are curious look
um wait what is this thing called again
I'm having a brain freeze mode I tried
it tried it tried it
yeah that's right and look for first try
first try that that's what we call the
first try
Minecraft first try I tried and did it
and you'll find it okay okay so yeah
this is under
underwater themes
and speaking of under something there's
also an under on the world themed Cali
world oh under there next yeah
I really thought you were she was about
to underwear me
and
actually no next is omelette I guess oh
is that like uh
oh
how did we get oh
this is oh
we can go there last yes this was the
exit
but on the world is the exit was it
always called exit
all right
our worlds exit no we're not exiting yet
but whoa
oh
what oh God don't trip be careful
how can I trip it's only sad
no actually I have a I have a really bad
relationship with sand
Ito me too me too yes
when you're like
when you you know on vacation don't you
like walk a lot like I walk a lot on
vacation not not even that much but it's
not enough to get like blisters
the problem is you want to go into the
water because that's what you're here
for and then you go there and and then
you get out of the water and all the
sounds
and then you try to wash it out again
but you always have to go through this
freaking sand see I was gonna say it's
in your underwear
you know
it would probably be in my in my size
it's the freaking stupid blisters
so here we have a desert and I don't
know I like this this like
wide
loneliness yeah because there's this bus
bus stop with the
with a small AMA here waiting for
or something who is she waiting for
she looks so peaceful what could she be
waiting for but look her dog Bubba has a
little candy in his in his mouth
cute and then we have here I can look at
you closely with this you can look at me
close oh sweet just kidding it doesn't
actually have like a I don't know I
think it works pretty well
yeah let's just act as if it has a
magnifying effect
oh you have nice nice skin very smooth
really recently I feel like my skin has
been I don't know kind of like
not so good no no no to take care of it
with some gravy it's the stressful
oh but the frog the frog don't you think
the Frog moisture should like slime yeah
you can capitalize on that actually that
sounds like a new business venture for
you
I honestly don't know where she is right
now I don't know what happened with her
after I transformed hold on Chad maybe
it was also just a hallucination oh
let's look at you guys yeah
I'm trying to find it
what are you seeing I'm trying to find
where I give a [\h__\h]
[Music]
um
hmm
I'm glad
hi hi
guys
[Laughter]
before before the sand infiltrates our
um systems let's go to Cali
[Music]
yeah
I'm exhausted
I'll leave you behind now
small Cali next would be Kiara but we go
to Cali first yeah yeah it's very pink
oh it's so cute she's a girly girl oh my
gosh
although she does have a lot of like
surprisingly girly parts around about
her oh oh God
thank you so much
I'm just I'm just and while we're at it
thank you Ahmed for also helping thank
you
for fixing some things and helping and
also ask thank you also for helping
thank you thank you
all right so she has this little moon
stage here
yeah wow wait wait wait it feels so hip
yeah
I'm getting the I'm getting the Boogie
oh yeah
[Music]
oh my God okay Eric can you turn homie
you're twerking does this show up
Kaka
oh my God
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
all right okay sorry sorry my son I'm
not don't be sorry no don't be sorry
or an apology we have some some cool oh
you want to put them on will they fit my
face I take them
yeah they're made for big faces
if you want to be a little bit more like
Cali you can have her save here you put
on the glasses
um hold on ah there we go
[Music]
it's like a guitar
welcome to the crib yeah yeah welcome to
another to MTV oh TV my cribs what's it
called baby cribs yes
so this is our three million dollar home
yeah Oh I thought you shared because we
thought you said free at first I was
like whoa it's free
no no no no no no
I only cost costy huh how much does the
real estate go about here oh okay I'm
ready
where would you like the injection
here I think you need it oh oh okay
I think you need a button Jason okay
it will take up to five days for it to
have effect okay I'm already feeling a
little funny but now yeah
okay
and now
now the best room
although I might be I might be a little
bit biased but uh you know
oh there's mine
what our umbrella so cute ah
wait then I should I want to change you
look around and I I change into my
vampire outfit I won't watch
I won't watch
[Music]
did I change
no
oh no I didn't
something about this I'm not
understanding
hmm
did I change now not yet
you have so many candies
wow
I like I think I I'm a fan of this one
hold on what's your favorite type of
candy
um
what's your favorite
[Music]
um
I like Kinder chocolate they have so
many different colors
[Music]
yeah yeah
Kinder chocolate have you have you eaten
Kinder country before
I don't think so
kinda country it's very very yummy
what's it like how about the egg it has
like yeah yeah kinder eggs but there's
way more Kindle country has like the
cereal cereal inside the chocolate bar
wait maybe I have had it I said no
the whole chocolate bar kind of tastes
like the Kinder Egg but like oh my gosh
that's so good I love Kinder chocolate
[Music]
yes well I'm trying out some Expressions
don't mind me
supposed to be like Austria you know
because we have many mountains yeah
yeah beautiful beautiful nature and yeah
so it's kind of like supposed to look a
little bit like Austria
[Music]
my
my bird Kotori
oh hell above me yes yes
glory Lord
is the closest kfb branch close
instead of me
or like not working but streaming so
they were like ah
it's gone all right let's let's leave
Cafe let's go oh my God they're lazy I
see what you doing guys lazy I will not
forget
you better come back right here it is
instant yeah I want to see your work
open the shop and serve me some burgers
or else yeah you better be ready in
uniform right now
we're guests after all she maybe wants
to eat some burgers what burgers
hey guys
perhaps we have um a phoenix Burger
Phoenix burger and a Jaco burger burger
I've always many other different kinds
of burgers I've always wondered about
the you know the um the ethics of the
Phoenix Burger
effects the ethics yeah yeah like um how
ethical
I don't know it's just called it's just
called Phoenix Burger but it uses
chicken meat oh okay
yeah
I'm a chicken okay
it sounds cool and yeah yeah people want
to buy it oh right right right right but
you're not a chicken no
speed run into a window world
[Music]
beautiful
girl let's go
do you like do you like snow
yes well kind of I don't know I'm not
really good with cold places but I like
snow I think it's pretty
oh well uh snow happens to be very cold
so well it's really cold then the next
World will be suffering for you I'm kind
of really hot because of the VR so
[Music]
let's go there we go
oh hi hello I'm glad you came
where uh oh is she able to follow is she
uh
Maybe not maybe not maybe not
all right let me let me go back yeah
let's go back
ah are you uh
shake your head if you can't if you
can't come to win the world
oh I take I take okay okay grab it okay
there you go oh
look how cute I was in control
Pamela here
we've got it
nice and nicer okay I'm gonna figure it
out oh my God this is um a world that we
got with uh I think last winter last
Christmas
last Christmas oh my God
we have the same brand you guys know
you guys know the song
Christmas I'll give her my heart
and give it away
[Music]
you're special okay
follow me oh you can push these these
balls and they become bigger oh there's
one over there this one this one
this one is so small push
push and push push push push push I push
I think it's getting bigger is it
getting yeah yeah it's getting bigger
yeah
[Music]
can we get much bigger
big how big does it get
yeah I'm not sure I never tried to make
it inside Max we can we'll push it to
the Limit push it oh my God
ah
nice oh you can like dance on top of it
wow
can you look oh there we go I'm like a
monkey in a circus
[Music]
welcome to the circus Hong Kong
oh
let me drink some water and if you look
to the middle you see our Christmas tree
we had decorations up there but it's not
Christmas so we took them down
hmm
understandable sorry I'm drinking water
too
oh YouTube
oh over here over here right in front of
the tree is where I did like a Christmas
karaoke in my Christmas outfit
wow yeah remember it's the pilgrimage is
fun
do you already feel chill down chilled
down actually a little bit
that's good this is this is you can the
immersion come here to warm up again oh
okay
oh gosh we have like a sauna what
oh
and here come here
only girls allowed oh everybody get out
I'm toasty right now hasn't been used in
a while oh yeah real toasty oh yeah it's
okay I'll just brush away the dust a
little bit Yeah bye-bye it's private
time
oh just kidding
oh there's more
grandchild
when I went outside she was she was
trying to she was trying to pick out a
window naughty naughty unbelievable
naughty naughty
quite hot in there and then here here
you can go ice skating oh
wait are you are you okay in there
[Music]
my head is too big my head is too big
for my body
we have another one of those moments
here take my hand yeah okay
now our hands are so short I know
and who if something's working yeah it's
probably working
nice nice
[Music]
I have spooky witch hat
oh
[Music]
I gotta cast a spell on you oh
and now you're in love with us oh
[Music]
my gosh she's a real like a real man
real I do yeah
why are you so cute
right in the kokoro oh no you no you no
you no you okay one more come come over
here okay okay we have a cozy
cozy place oh this is so cute
yeah you can Grill some marshmallows or
grill some sausages oh I love sausage
you want the marshmallow Okay good uh
what do you like you have a marshmallow
though you don't like marshmallows you
want to switch do you like what you do
like more
if you like marshmallows and I like
sausage you know I feed you and you feed
me
we can share oh yeah oh it's like it's
like lady lady in the [\h__\h] but with the
sausage
[Music]
this happens after the stream after this
oh sorry sorry guys no no free show
tonight
[Music]
no no no
no secret secret
is it comes into endings also this hot
dog
thank you thank you
[Music]
I'm melting it's so hot
I have nekojita syndrome oh me too
[Music]
Sports
I think I wasn't there like uh where
where's the drawing area there was a
drawing area I'm not sure if it's like
working right now though
hmm is it here huh where was it
oh
aurora borealis
oh my God localized entirely you can
take a pen and then
when you when you press the button you
can draw
oh when you when you press like the the
equip oh I said yes
and you can draw on your Snowman
okay you make snowmen I make snowman
okay okay oh oh gosh I'm I'm struggling
that's okay
okay oh I'm I'm an artist
um artiste me too
who can make the best snowman
what kind of snowman are you drawing
Mama I'm drawing a really punchable one
right now
yeah
what kind of snowman is that
you know just one that you know I just
look at it and I wanna
I wanna punch it in the face I wanna
bring it I wanna
one problem do you have with
um snowman what did they ever do to you
well wait what is yours
what is this
what
what is yours you say wait I'm not done
okay I won't look
did not recognize this
do you guys chat do you reckon do you
recognize it
well from the side it's like really
kinda
um and you have to look at um up front
oh okay okay
it's ready oh wait no no it's not ready
yet ah that some of the lines disappear
when when time passes oh no oh no oh no
oh no okay
oh it's okay it's so cute oh my God
oh it's oh it's you you oh my God
oh my God oh my wow
okay mama you know what yeah
uh we are starting to make me feel like
absolute [\h__\h] me too we'll go to the
studio next unfortunately we'll we'll
skip the Halloween World
[Applause]
we'll go let's go let's go okay
oh wait I'm gonna sit down oh I don't
blame you yeah it's starting to make my
head hurt a lot
we are we are so exhausted she's zooming
Look at Her Go
what do I look like
um sometimes your legs like come out of
the ground
like you look yeah
to the super special Amit dubbers do I
have to take the the camera yeah yeah
okay okay
okay I returned to Lobby can I press
this
oh are you myself the pen let's see
oh
I got it oh
I think you'll have to hold it again
though right to go to the studio
probably do we
if we go to the studio do we have to no
I'll take it just in case because I'm
confused no okay no okay
oh I think maybe fine maybe guys will
let's go to there
[Music]
yeah wait oh
wow wow wow wow wow
[Music]
oh my gosh we're so tiny in here
oh yeah
but but but it's actually supposed to be
like
um
made for us tiny people because there's
also like instruments and stuff and
they're all made for us
perfect size for your perfect little
hands
I drink some more water
me too me too everybody hydrate hydrate
everybody
oh I think this is the same for the
ninja stands in World probably if I if I
remember correctly but both of these
worlds if I'm not wrong
you guys can visit right
oh well right now the ninja Sandy one uh
I don't know if you can visit at the
moment
oh oh my like wasn't it like visitable
before yeah it was it was it was hmm
ah okay I think our world is always
visitable but not the not the studio I
think maybe the studio might be
different
so actually uh I wanted to show you
um a little game that I um prepared like
before yeah I changed it I changed it up
so that it says Puma's name I just
thought you know it's it's fun to have a
little game and before we do something
else yeah
game again
[Music]
whoa
welcome to the Maldives Maldives
Maldives
I know I know I remember your streams
about it
yes
so I before we went I made this uh I
have the I had this area made with a
little game a gimmick uh oh yeah how do
we start the game it's not here now is
it oh yeah
oh I think oh oh it's right here
yeah okay okay so we're gonna play this
um just just once just one round okay
the rules are and by the way this is
this is um
yeah you see all these items here
various items and you see two suitcases
and his orange one yours is the blue one
okay okay basically I will start by
taking for example this brush and I say
I pack in my suitcase the brush and then
it says
uh your turn my turn you have to
remember the brush that I packed and add
something onto it but you have to put
both both in your suitcase okay yes so
brush okay and we'll do stinky sock
stinky sock which one
we have to have a good memory
the brush and this one suck yeah
and a new iPhone new item I will bring
no bikini top oh
all right yes and we got a brush good
okay stinky sauce yeah for the beautiful
Pomo hair this stinky dog for the
beautiful formal beads oh
yes yes the bikini top it's a little big
on me I think it's I think it's more for
you it's a little
bit start don't worry it has pads it has
pads look bigger than it actually is
okay good again all right all right now
one more grounding let's do that Chucky
do you have one of those I have one in
pink I do I mine and mint
oh man I love mint color yeah it's
pretty
okay brass brush thank you thank you
suck I'm a pro with this game yeah you
have experience yeah
bikini top you can talk and uh
mine's being cute
okay
you know actually I I also have um like
this is really cool you know for
checking camera you're like uh when you
make a mistake then the photos messed up
and you can't save it but I have uh like
a techie printer that can print out any
photo in your phone oh yeah and then it
looks like a real cheeky so that way you
can take a photo with your phone first
make sure that it's actually looks like
something you want to you know say spend
lots of money on check his work because
they are like really expensive they are
really expensive
[Music]
take a camera take a camera
okay yeah flip-flops we call them
flip-flops oh the flip-flops yeah
um
um before that I just um you know I
really wanted to oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah I just you know if you if
you wanted to like you know maybe talk
more like you know about you know how
um you know this just anything you want
to honestly just anything you know you
did you how was how was me yeah how was
these how was it oh oh it was actually
like um terrible timing because we went
when there was like uh constantly uh a
typhoon
the typhoon season yeah yeah
monsoon season wait Monsoon is different
awesome yeah yeah the monsoon is I guess
the season oh
[Laughter]
actually we're doing a really good job
at like confusing ourselves because I am
confused right now
um
okay and Chucky Chucky
and then the flip-flops I think yeah and
and then and then a ticket ticket ticket
ticket
[Music]
oh yeah
yeah I was you made fun of my fanny pack
oh
yes and I I still stand by my statements
actually Kiara I have a I have a bone to
pick with you
a bone I know okay I was not you know
okay I'm gonna fight you right now this
is this is about my gingerbread house
what was it oh
God so if it isn't the consequences
oh my God sticky socks
um
[Music]
wait what was after the stinky sock was
it the sandals
wait no bikini talk anything up there
you messing up there already no no no no
no and then
and then flip-flops
and then Beach the ticket
[Applause]
I don't know what it is
I actually don't know
[Laughter]
give up give up it's my win
it was the sock get on your knees bubble
yes surely it was the stock take it put
it in there no it wasn't it was this
this is the passport it was the passport
one day
[Music]
was it actually the sock
no I I just um took the days here yeah
oh what are those
oh
I was I was just like while you were
talking I was like oh just the moments
click quick while she's talking
because you can't see it oh yeah
I got Bamboozled caught it I got
Bamboozled but this is good this is
exactly all according to keikaku
well next time I'll get you next time
okay so the game is over we can change
to the the like other background now I
think
yeah yeah
let me change
let's see oh
I'm in a void I'm gonna avoid
this one this one yeah
can you play any instruments uh I used
to be able to play the violin
oh what yeah that's so cool
[Music]
here I'll be on the drums oh actually
um
yeah get yourself a microphone
you can even get a banjo there's like
all kinds of cool stuff back here
uh um a gun because we're not here
yes I took microphone I'll take this one
okay
sorry we have no no pommel colored
microphone but we also have light sticks
okay let me get a promo colored light
stick yeah
what for what for what could it be for
oh
you should you're nervous orange colored
light stick too I have
I have
[Music]
um
oh you have some in your in your model
yeah yeah
how do I do it again
uh gestures oh
I don't think I have those
there we go and then I can change the
color oh
so long too I can make it shorter
oh yeah yeah oh yeah
oh wow
[Laughter]
[Music]
Orange
wait do I have orange orange
oh it does not have orange the first one
is the first one look like orange not
that one did the first one the one that
started out with looked kind of orange
that was red wait let me change the
brightness there was a different color
before it was oh
it was right on my screen now when you
first opened it up and was orange oh
well anyway
pick whatever color red is fine too I
think you think we're in okay we'll go
with red
so guys you may wonder why did we bring
out some microphones well well I thought
uh it's a special occasion so we might
as well make the most out of it
so I I asked promo to join me and sing
some songs but first before we sing
together
[Music]
I'm so nervous
I'm a singing person I cheer performance
it's too real it's too real oh gosh okay
I'll do my best tell
us when you're ready all right give me
one second
[Music]
yeah maybe you have to do that too
that's what I just did yeah
okay guys who
op okay are you gonna
kill promo fairy singing no boo no get
her off the stage
[Laughter]
now oh God turn on the music from are
you ready
yes
okay uh free
oh wait uh one second one second hold on
sorry uh I just saw I just saw the
message one moment please yeah yeah one
moment please
um
okay I'm ready I'm ready
get on
um
[Music]
yes
please
[Music]
put it guys
[Applause]
[Music]
he is
if I go around what awaits me in the
dark could you tell me please
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Applause]
shut up
[Music]
I'm so embarrassed oh my God
that was amazing
oh I made a I made a a small mix a small
little call for that one
[Applause]
I was like yeah wait that doesn't that
doesn't sound like the usual one
no I made it just for you
thank you
thank you you're the best oh it's my
original song my my first original song
you know Tony
all right
so maybe it's time for me to sing too
[Music]
what what will koala sing hmm
what will she sing what will she sing
what could she possibly sing I think
I'll be singing
I wonder
where you stand right now by the way is
perfect because I had to cut it cuts off
exactly with your cute ribbon
it I can see that I have an audience
thank you all right I'll sing a song oh
oh please please send while I sing uh
okay okay
uh I'm ready I'm ready anytime
let's check my check one two three
nowaday I opened up memories door
I found something that I could live for
Curt and she'll guess you'll open my
eyes
and Light Came rushing inside
behind my hearts and grips and keys can
you see listen and you might hear a
melody
your fire spy the passion that keeps
burning
magic that helps me to believe
[Music]
I'm learning what it's like to love and
being alive oh there will always
[Music]
behind don't cry look in my eyes
when gray skies take the colors away far
away I'll paint the rainbow lasting for
days and days just like the man take
that you always shared with me maybe now
you need to believe
[Music]
Diamond City foreign
foreign
[Music]
I don't wanna dive into tonight
nice
hi hi
[Music]
in the night there's no need to hide the
joy in your eyes
don't let it shine
thank you
That's So Perfect
[Music]
you're right you're right we finally the
train departed or dropped us off here
I'm kind of lost
[Music]
I tried so hard with the deeper lines
you know I was like I was like I wonder
I was like I wonder if I have time to
learn the dance that you have for
hinotori and I was like trying to do
like the length
oh my God it's like oh my God honestly
honestly even if you were to do it oh
where am I where'd you go I'm here I'm
drinking water sorry even if you were to
do it with these small bodies then you
you can't show it properly yeah I'm
trying
oh God I'm exhausted from that Puma I'm
exhausted don't be exhausted yet we
still have more songs yeah yes
what is missing guys what is missing
what is missing I think a song with both
of us yeah
boy I'm nervous okay I there's let's
Stand Together on the yellow one here
okay okay
uh-huh
oh this Spotlight cool
let's put my light too oh gosh it's down
in the middle okay wow
ah
so um both of us each chose one song
that we want to sing with each other
yeah I haven't gotten the song with the
one yeah the one that you picked it's
been stuck in my head like for for ever
since you sent it to me it's so good
it's so good
yeah I took the chance to sing something
that I I was like hope interesting or
someone
but first we sing well first we sing the
song that you chose okay which I
actually I didn't know before ever but I
I really like it too it's a really chill
song I like it a lot yeah
yeah it has a nice vibe to it and I also
want to say oh my God I love Diamond
City Lights it's stuck in my head
forever
when I was trying to sing the first
couple times uh after like the second
chorus
the moment the third chorus starts at
the latest I would like I would start
crying
[Applause]
there's something about the instrumental
I don't know and the way it goes like it
made me cry man I don't care I know I
remember when I first heard it the like
the the first time we got the demo I was
thinking that way too I was like oh my
God am I gonna cry every time I sing
this just how's that like kind of hurt
s
[Music]
well then I'm gonna get rid of this
oops uh I mean um I think my my
microphone went over here for some
reason okay
oh
okay
um nervous
I hope all goes well
all right
um
I think I'm already maybe if we raise
our hands then the music up Shield [\h__\h]
the music can be killed when when we
both raise our hands okay Alicia all
right hold on
um
let's sing together
[Music]
more
foreign
[Music]
bye
guys
[Music]
foreign
thank you
my opinions died right at the end for
like one second okay are you all right
the street yeah it's it's I noticed when
I heard like the Windows sound kind of
go go like
but it's back it's back oh no no because
you can watch Puma's archive later too
uninterrupted version I don't know if my
archive will be uninterrupted uh-oh oh
but hers definitely will not be
interrupted sorry
[Music]
it was just a tiny bit at the end you
didn't miss much guys don't worry
actually you missed the whole fireworks
hey
okay oh there's one more I'm so excited
about this one
yeah the next one actually has like
harmonies and it's supposed to be a song
that's sang with two people yeah and
choosing songs
yeah and I commissioned an instrumental
just for this occasion so if you guys
really like us saying this maybe who
knows since I commissioned an
instrumental then we can put out an
official song covered
yes the instrumentals made made by
raining marbles the credit will be in
the description afterwards too
sounds awesome
okay
you know you don't have a project right
yeah
yes of course you do so
um this song
this song is is made up of um uh two
members on two different Idol groups one
is from veriscover my favorite animal
group that doesn't exist anymore
and the other one is cute cute dog you
know cute though yes yes yes oh they
also they also don't exist anymore
the Golden Era yeah
yeah but but so these two members they
were put into a unit and they released
literally only one song but it's really
cool so please listen to Lady mermaid
are you ready lady mermaid yeah I'm
ready
yeah okay okay
boys my where's my mouse
where's my mouse
where's my mouse trying to say mama I
hear this okay I'm ready when you are we
raise our hands okay okay when we're
ready raise hand okay okay
lady mermaid version go
one
[Music]
time
that anymore
[Music]
foreign
give me
[Music]
foreign
if there's anyone in the chat yours are
mine who knows who knew this song from
before I honestly want to have a talk
with you a coffee no not really coffee a
tea with you because it's even in the
inside of the Hill Classics bro it's
like you have to really dig really
deeply to get to that song thumbs up
units are yeah yeah yeah
okay um here um I don't I don't
knowledge and so on so this unit wasn't
even just a normal unit you know hello
project had like this weird thing where
it's called like satoyama something
something where the idols they would
like
um do like some some stuff on the
countryside like agriculture kind of
stuff
oh my God
we're not campaign they made like
several units with songs about stuff
like that like this lady mermaid song no
not quite so much about agriculture but
some other songs they made for this
purpose
we love Idols too but then oh yeah
tell me tell me something about about
your favorite your favorite Idols tell
me because I'm too excited I need to
calm down
I really like that you know it's hard to
find sometimes girl fans of Idols I know
we're like basically different sections
you know because you're like really
hello Pro but I I know a little bit
about hello bro I really liked um
I can't
I go thank you
[Music]
I really I like a lot of uh morning
musume songs
um oh and some of them are there's hard
to find sometimes karaoke for them like
I really like the
um
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
yeah I really like that song I've Been
wasn't that wasn't that during the time
but like uh was in the group
Maybe
do you have an ocean I don't think I
knew enough to have an Oshi I really
like the Siam you know because she's
like a idol Legend
you know she would she would she was
such a she was such a cute she was a
booty girl and she was going like
what's up what's up
young he was cute it was really cute
yeah I've heard you know some solo songs
you know that do you yeah yeah yeah I've
listened a little bit to it yeah I've
heard you I've heard you yurushiyan
maybe maybe with our powers together we
can drag people into the rabbit hole
that is it could be and okay little
project
it's okay AKB can you know I'm dying
oh you really became like it's like it's
like this kind of reminds me of shirts
it feels like you're like in sherbet ice
cream yeah yeah yeah yeah like a like a
gelato ice cream
wait I want to be orange floor oh there
we go
that's beautiful
um so I wanted this one to be special
and I think it was special don't you
think but more I think so yeah
so Chad please look forward to lots of
fun collabs from now on yeah
yay
I'm like oh I need a shower me too me
too I need an hour how do you sink into
the floor like that
I literally lied down on my actual floor
oh
gosh I'm tangled and cords
you're not you're not quite ready to
become one with the floor yet
I'll turn Down On My Level
I physically cannot physically
that's cause you're not ready you're not
ready you have so much experience chill
yes floor experience I landed from Ina
no she is she's also one with the floor
yeah floor gang what's up
okay here we go I'm testing I'm testing
my limits
[Music]
oh wow
you're becoming one of the floor again
you just have to you're dead reached the
floor
hey
yeah
you should you should become one with
the yellow floor right next to me all
right all right
[Laughter]
yay
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm turning I'm I'm turning on the floor
I'm getting dizzy
oh my God whoa
[Music]
this is next level floor again yeah
I feel like I'm going into a new
dimension I'm traveling where no one has
traveled before
can we go faster oh God I don't know I
can't go faster
how are you how are you spinning so
smoothly I can only go with free FPS uh
you're oh you were spinning smoothly
before
it's okay I'm happy with this
so I really want to take this headset
off no I can't guys yeah
I hope you enjoyed this oh God yeah
uh yeah thank you very much for watching
this was uh takanasikara from Whole Life
English and Palma rainbow
yeah you can see our channels in each
other's descriptions well thank you for
being so kind I know that my audience um
they are all very very welcoming of home
Wonder oh they all love promo because I
talk about you a lot and they just kind
of like both of our personalities I
don't know about your your promodations
but thank you for
um yeah letting me uh get closer to
Palmer
I'm really glad that we could finally
have this actually happen yeah after so
long yeah finally yeah yeah
it was bound to be we we wanted to do
this for a long time
[Music]
long time yeah and finally the time has
come yeah I know now the gates To Hell
the floodgates
hahaha
we should play Monopoly oh God we just
became we just got closer
[Music]
so thank you guys for watching and uh
yeah please support us and let's have
more fun in the future and be nice to
each other yeah
um yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and in
German we say what what do you say in in
German or in English a German I say uh
uh three times nine three times three
times nine
yeah
thank you
[Music]
I love you Chihuahua wow
oh God time to get up now oh bye-bye
okay bye-bye
[Music]
foreign