[Music]
a
one
[Music]
hell
yay hi
[Music]
I'm why do you guys have
clothes I I got coins why not
sweepy yeah you get like 150 coins in
the beginning and one shirt costs 50
coins it's so expensive I have
coins well the B it's nothing look at
the other prices those are way more
crazy this is the cheapest shirt
yeah or you can get like a little fart
Emoji oh yeah it's so I'm gonna
click okay well uh is it everyone's
first time playing the game
yes can we introduce
ourselves no
[Applause]
[Music]
yes starting from
the player
order okay we can we can introduce
ourselves while doing the volume check
then oh right right
okay I'm not a cat I'm P hello
hello
yeah sounds
good next one the one who says sounds
good
for having me
y just wake up oh no I'm just sick she's
sick
she she sounds a little bit like
M
[Music]
Miss sounds okay and next uh uh my
lovely this running
bird which one uh
w why why did you need to think so long
about that cuz your both are running I
was
choosing
[Music]
okay um I'm the kiaha I uh love ID girls
and I love am this is like the best
party ever let's go let's
go
Loud Let's
[Music]
go next the one this yellow
bird yellow bird
yellow um how to how to introdu
my soul there you go introduction da
okay good day man my name is k from H
third generation D my
soul what we all been waiting
for have you had bricky
yet Brey done bre nice Brey
okay Brey done okay next uh Amy let's go
hello
[Music]
Watson we have a
detective we have a detective and we
have a secret agent very
nice I'm barely a secret agent
you barely misunderstanding of why am is
here oh oh oh should we should we talk
about
it wait can can we talk about it yeah
yeah yeah oh yeah I I I reacted with an
emoji to the invite of this because I
was like oh shoot that sounds like a
cool game so I put a little POG a little
C POG reaction and uh yeah I wasn't
expect you to join but I'm here and I'm
happy to be here anyways we're happy
that you're here we're happy that you're
here didn't sign up but she's still here
even though she didn't sign
up she didn't sign up for this it was
really funny marer yeah it was really
funny cuz I was like uh react if you
want join and I was like I'm imp POG so
I was like let's
go
makes sense sense yeah okay uh
this
H re I'm H reu
[Music]
yay yay next last but not least our
sweepy sleepy bird sleepy
bird oh did you forget about
mea oh
my how even I thought you did
[Music]
intruction I'm
sorry go
attention please thank you for your
attention I miss
you okay now the real last but not
least
any hello it's Ana from Hol Live ID
second
second um how do you change your color
can you change
your oh no yeah yeah yeah yeah you good
perfect yeah okay yeah it looks it looks
good okay yeah you're good
okay okay since we don't have much time
I'm thinking we can do
um maybe one
uham
yeah and then we can try other stuff
like um the hide and seek or The Killing
Spree one I
think sounds good yeah there's many
different modes and stuff sounds gooda
Sensei yes is this um is this game like
a certain impostor game this call oh
yeah yeah something similar but
duck okay and Goose du quack yes wait
which one which one is the Imposter the
duck or the goose I think the is the
okay the goose is the crew mate yeah
okay okay sorry uh I
hav't very I think I haven't played
either one in the
title haven't played either so yeah I
haven't played either I couldn't up my
alarm oops also this is also going to be
my
first sorry just in case I overslept
um yeah okay let's play I think it's
everyone's first time playing anyway so
let's play Let's Play
Play What go wrong okay three two one
I don't know what this
is hello everybody I am
Markiplier I don't do
this
Dusty Dusty hello
water
bye-bye
[Music]
okay
piano how do I get
there
[Music]
okay strange
shello am I a
musician
[Music]
s
it is very early for ID right now but I
hope you can enjoy it though because
apparently only this day that the ID
hello
Mar only only this day that the ID girls
are available because we're going to be
so so very very
busy so hopefully you can
understand
oh
[Music]
wow what he's good oh hello hello
hello hello
[Music]
you hi
hi hi what is
this you're an imposter you're the dock
qu qu I'm a
phoenix okay that's Port
train I like that same
[Music]
portrait that that is the portrait of Mr
goosebird
the um the
[Applause]
third let's portray
again stop
it
huh I
keep
y
[Music]
we were
lovers we were
l no we were L okay okay we need the
wait did no one kill yet no I just
trying to see what
yeah okay it's we can make the task
longer the task
longer sounds good I was looking for
dead bodies cuz I was the vulture I'm
supposed to eat dead bodies but there
were no dead body oh my God what the
heck four um we do have um it's four for
SC right eh
no like two dcks and then two two other
people on the duck
site wait there four people I think the
roll for the um the duck site is only
two so oh wait wait wait wait wait wait
wa wait wait wait yeah only two only two
and I I was I was a vulture which is not
the
duck who's the duck you're not a duck
but a duck is a are you guys supposed to
help the
Ducks means no the vulture is kind of
doing their own thing they just they
don't don't even have to do tasks but
they also don't kill they just eat
corpses and if they get eat corpses they
yeah they're just in for the they're
just in for the
yeah just for the food yeah just I me
dodo as well it's like Jester if they
get folded out they they win alone yeah
I thought supposed to be like anybody
know the um cuz when you're a duck you
get these like unlock this and that like
sabotage unlock blah blah blah do I
could but yeah I've been trying to work
that out but I didn't get it yeah I you
have to kill someone if you want to
sabotage oh it's like
oh okay knowled I will bring Senpai I
was searching for you we were lovers
hey you know you know what's crazy the
lovers role they didn't tell us who the
who the other partner is why you don't
know so we have to look by
ourselves just came out where's my
lover my lover let's try one more
time um um my task I I I set the task
list to be larger so I think it should
be fine can everyone okay let's go press
ready ready up please I'm ready ready
okay again let's
[Music]
go okay okay okay okay
lava
laa fishing oh what are you where am I
[Music]
oh I'm so bad at
uh
dinner dinner
time sorry
sorry no no no we we were at the dinner
table and we didn't know that it means
like
[Music]
emergency oh my God okay scared
wait we can't skip we
can't this is literally a skip ad
moment oh no we
can't the
DU the duck
voted what what what does that mean what
does that mean I don't know what that
means everyone everyone is say for now
want
to I don't know how to do this game
actually but we we we'll learn we'll
learn go to dining room dining
room
[Music]
G
cooking
guys guys guys what what
happen you and Ollie went upstairs right
I went right and then I saw it upstairs
upstairs the room beside
it I was
withous Ella was with me this wait wait
where can you self report in this game I
don't know I don't know I I think wait I
it's
either both Ollie and
Kyla but it wasn't Kyla because she just
got into the
room
I
V you just press the name I think I just
what what yeah I think I press the
name what oh my
God I think we don't know what we're
doing
[Music]
same
how do I get out of here okay C
CA hello
hello what where is leave
[Music]
leaves
that's see
you Mama
[Music]
m
wait
yeah how do you
unclock I click just press click your
M I think I'm
lost
hello am I lost
where's the
map the pond the have
Pond I sneeze where
is can we go to the pond this Mansion is
so
big oh kill me kill me all stand by kill
me kill me can kill anyone right I think
no I'm a sheriff I I only I only kill
Ducks
oh I think it's KY she keeps susing
everyone then can I kill Kyle yeah just
kill me
everybody just kill me make some rooms
no no no K so after witnessing yes
and yeah and then Z going to be
responsible for
my that's so
dramatic no that's so
dramatic
no
um no no one trust
me I said I said don't kill no one trust
me
for she selfreported
was staying low key the entire
time wa did you actually report or
because I was Canadian so like I self I
didn't report it's Auto
report don't kill the Canadian don't
kill the
Canadian I literally said that I saw W
and rainy together before that happened
and but no
one did we hear though I I remember you
saying it yeah
it so wait I who who who was the who was
the who got the lover roll oh yeah I no
not me what I'm not sure was it was it
you no I'm I'm lovers with you oh wow
spicy so we got it correct you're spicy
oh my sorry my alarm keeps ringing on
okay so turn it up
girl this is a lot more faster than
other I have I said alarm every five
minutes I'll turn it off okay so are we
ready how about we switch it up with
different rules
okay let's see
rise and grind Gamers I
think uh I think I think I think
I we can do assassin so basically it's
uh you can kill during meetings by
correctly guessing a role or die
trying your Die
Trying during meetings okay let's
go let's go let's go let's go
let's go I like
healings you scare me
woman I'm ready
that okay let's go safe safe
[Music]
safe
oh
[Music]
hello back
seat hi are you my
lover I love
[Laughter]
you where am
I why is the r so
big love is big I don't
know peish I can fish I don't remember
where to fish you know what let's see
Fish don't know how to do
this that's fish
[Music]
fishing
unil
[Music]
what what
happened self reports us might be self
report no no no reporting can where was
the
body uh the body is in the laboratory in
the top labatory
W well me me and Ella we were we were in
the kitchen I'm in the kitchen I was
trying to find them were we were in The
West Wing yeah we wait where is I
think don't skip it was me I
self-reported don't skip oh it was you
it was me what that's very Su
that's what she's
not what
a probably a
do that's very no so who who
killed I
killed you guys so easily I was like oh
how do I make myself like if I want to
be kicked out as a then I should just
make people think that I'm the suy one I
skip
though I skip I voted
Watson
um how many times did re s by got the
duck
two the do the do I'm voting you next no
I'm inoc we're voting her out first
by okay let's I'm
ready is my evil Aura already been
detected by the game but I'm not evil
though I just like
chaos not evil just chaos
w wow wow w wow
[Music]
hello
water I like
water I draw bath I think I need to wait
for
it
[Music]
what is that why am I look stoned like
what is this on the top and no no on the
bottom
left oh my God it's foggy no I might get
killed
4y hello
happening
P oh clear water pump clear water
pump
oh what is clear water
pump how do I get
there here
I
think did you guys got it I got it oh oh
I got it I got
it does everybody have to do it I think
everybody has to do
it I did it I it already wait wait wait
I think what there is like count
counter counter on
it BL
TR so far
tties I love me making some
tea
one
hello ladies it's it's te
time it's tea time for my l
[Music]
Yay
good Dang
d
no I cannot play the
piano dang dang dang
where is candle hello
candle I need to find candle how do I
get there ish so
[Music]
hard no two people gone two people gone
hm
I shall remember those people in the
piano room I'm voting no matter what
piano room okay it's
reai it's her I mean it's I
guess
recent because she's always it nah it's
just my luck
previously that makes are we voting it's
up to you I vot I voted to be something
but okay
I'm innocent though just
saying goodbye
everybody she
isn't that's why that's why you should
stay with your lover because if M dies
you die oh but you know I thought
actually cuz you can also be lover uh if
your lover is like the other part like
the
impostor so I thought you were imposter
for some Reon I'm not imposter you're
just a lover I can oh I didn't know that
you could
actually eat F mother so did you die
just because I died yeah I
did it
was oh you saw
the
no
oh see I'm
innocent I can't never
trust Rea only died cuz she was a lover
with me I was killed and waya died with
me so romantic a that's so
romantic a wait that's not true I
murdered you
k
yeah you did you did but Rea died with
me because you murdered
me yeah so you
guyses are else and I
died okay let's do something
really stupid let's
go stupid stupid stupid something stupid
something stupid something Dum
something M M
M what about so what about I heard
someone eating oh how about a detective
round I hope I'm what's the detective do
detective you can investigate players to
see if they have killed that round maybe
too op maybe too op okay never mind too
op too
op okay I can we we can go with stalker
basically you can track one player
that's my
[Laughter]
jump again you scare me woman I'm
sorry I'm ready by the
way
okay a that's to
Sweet I don't
know I am in Pursuit Of Love
I shall find My One True Love
what my
love oh
interesting guys are in love huh
yeah I shall
follow I found my one true
love okay okay have tasks right yeah you
can do you can do task I
follow oh this is my
task okay I'm
done okay
fine where where where do you want to I
don't think do I want to go
what I need to reassemble
this okay you go left I go right what
see yay
okay scary I would like to deduct a few
things
deduct deduct Kyla might be a stalker so
she's not a duck what okay I'm the
stalker Ollie and it's kind of useless
oh never mind calling her
useless call it useless what no no I'm
saying the stalker roll is kind of
useless cuz I like I don't get much from
it I feel like does it like do you win
if you successfully suck someone what
does it
do why are you blaming me I'm fing you
no no no no she's protecting you I was
trying to call you no I was trying to
like
nice
deduction wait everyone is safe for only
be the
Doo
Oh
interesting break leaves where is leaves
no I have been separated from my one
true love I shall rake leaves
where is the leaves oh there
okay D it's kind of sad that Ena is not
here
though I kind of want to listen her p
and
everything how do I do
this o
fun okay
fun Cor
[Music]
hone I I can go from here
fine
hello what wait wait wait wait wait wait
what wait what what's going
on I I was cleaning a picture and Raina
ran past me and I heard her and then I
was ding the picture I was going in the
same direction Ollie was going with me
and we both saw the body kind of at the
same time I was like what the what what
it's one thing for sure it's not Amelia
Senpai
it's is is my one true
love oh you guys are
lovers is inde you why would why would
be who where was everybody where was
every
where were you huh I was on in the
hallway where were you you tell me right
nowson tell me where you
were I was with
ol yeah she was with me I was with ol I
was with ol no no before that I was with
her the
time what's
happening oh [\h__\h] no you guys messed up
you messed up big time you guys M up big
time what
Goodbye by public
opinion with the fish
you I told you guys you are so close you
were so close but you were telling the
TRU no fight I knew you were the doo you
were so fast
yeah what do do again they just want to
die needs to be voted out
yeah but but all got the people right
the yeah she
said yeah but I still wanted to win so I
voted for
myself I see crazy that is so
sad and you didn't win I'm so
mad let's try
game okay so instead
unnecessary mhm okay the stalker
roll um yeah this one instead of so I'm
exchanging the lover duck to um Hitman
duck and bodyguard Boose so The
Bodyguard gets a bonus for protecting a
player wow but the Hitman gets a bonus
for killing them wow I don't know what
the bonus entails though how to the same
May when you're
hello the discussion time I feel like
the discussion time is a little bit too
short yeah to be honest okay okay let's
age discussion time that was 30 seconds
how about um how about uh 45 45 yeah
okay what from 30 to
45 yeah and the options are only 30 45
60 60 okay 60 okay let's go 60
[Music]
okay okay I need to write this down
mhm let's go okay so let's go instead of
mimic I'm using the detective so the
detective can investigate players to see
if they have killed that
round okay we can try that one okay
let's go okay let's go
byebye bye
what's going
[Music]
on
where is pillow though I want to see
pillow but I want pillow them I wonder
how I wonder why what is this
[Music]
what wow that's so fast that's so
fast eh is it self report is is is is it
like automatically reporting themselves
no I report it it was at West
Wing um it was at went to West Wing can
you see the map oh you can actually yeah
you can see the map
I I well it wasn't waa waa is safe H
thank you why do you I was righty too so
I'm to it was pretty last time the last
time I saw someone
mhm and The West Wing is actually Ru I
no I haven't I
haven't no I haven't get to the West
Wing I was
inaa and I left I don't I don't think
it's no I was I was from
hway you're from hway yeah I went to the
study library and then hallway I'm about
to go to the sitting room it's a long
way from hallway to West
Wing for L skipping I'm skipping you're
very
quiet
yeah goodbye is
she she still she's still safe
okay why I'm just singing I like singing
no I don't like singing for you guys
goodbye I just like singing for
myself
hi
yeah hi hello hi by I
need want to see me please marry me
okay what the
[\h__\h] okay you know what I'm going to go
around okay
humping the
pillow nice wait what just
say I mean it looks like one it looks
like one it looks like I'm humping the
pillow where's the light
though humping the
pillow it's you it's you people what the
heck we're trying to fix the light I
think oh there oh oh it's fixed
nice almost stack kill I see I see
Howe might be dodo
again what is shrub oh this is shrub
you're saying stuff she's she's yapping
in purpose that girl she's yapping in
purpose kind of sussy huh again kind of
sassy you yapping about no
idea no idea wait can we say our rules I
mean if it's it's it's a good one yeah
sure I think I think Anna is the the
protect the protecting one oh wait wait
wait come here come wait wait wait do
not I think it's I think I think it's
Wawa why because actually
there's
food food
oh I think it's
[Music]
w I was about to report that cuz I I'm
the medium I can see it I see wa going
around and there's a corpse around where
Wawa
left I was with re Senpai yeah the whole
don't no don't stick it on me I'm the
medium I can see the dead bodies I was
about to go back to the dining room to
report because I just looked at what's
the
medium it shows me it shows me uh like
uh there's a countdown every once in a
while I can press shift and then I see
how many ghosts there are and for the
longest time it was just one from the
last round and now I just after my task
refreshed and I saw two so I was in the
studio doing the the base or something
stream connection and then that just
around the corner is a dining room where
you can report right so I don't know
where the body is but I went to the
dining room been going back and for that
was with Ana and no no I saw you going
back and forth as well so don't stick it
on me now you you two were together
you if I kill someone no I'm the medium
oh my God I swe to God why
is I think W wants to be killed again
actually
I hey how how good did I just explain
how the medium
works we get the wrong person it's going
to be bad I'm not sure
God I'm hungry I swear me
too din why would you do that why would
[Laughter]
you wait she oh same okay yeah you
better
[Music]
is it
gone what is this Bell oh no sorry I
pressed
it okay never mind it's not on H sorry I
like b i I see b i i i hi I think it
might be raining yeah I think it's rainy
though cuz K Ki was trying so hard to
defend herself I don't think I don't
think it's than that that
just these dcks are too
clever I don't have the heart to lay a
finger me
meing on
me that was it was so funny Ching run
away from
rain didn't say anything I mean she's a
ghost out a little bit too late she was
silent oh wait you were dead I'm sorry
music
ohing
okay I think
uh how about we try since it's been an
hour how about we Tred different uh
mode okay we can
try okay what about this
hoot okay hoot and seek the owl must
blend in with NC to complete task to win
the game spotters and snipers work
together to identify and kill the owl to
win I don't know how many owl that's so
much
aniy I'm ready Goan what about Goan
Goose Goan might be like better like
hide andek hone the tag Okay Go Okay
want to try Goan yeah yeah
yeah okay let's try
Goan to ruce the timer or choose to hide
oh okay okay there's a similar mode in
um in uh Among Us I mean we can try runs
really fast can try the other
modes yeah yeah I I think we can try the
gohost hunt first and then we try a
different one after this okay should be
a quick round let's
go
ta
tyyy call doy doy boom boom boom boom
chippy chippy choa choa dooy Dooby
call do
do chiy chiy CH cha chubby ch
ch chipp chipp ch
[Music]
ch chipp chippy where is Chippy chippy I
want chippy
chippy boom boom boom boom chippy chippy
choa choa what what what who's
that who's budny is
that how do I do task what
task magic task oh uh I think you press
press
it chiy chiy choa
choa
[Music]
hello
everybody
everybody I didn't manage
[Music]
to chiy chiy choa
choa boom boom boom boom do do
a
hi why is
it oh my God why did she keep getting
the I don't
know the task is too much the task is
too much is too much T was too much okay
for this game yeah Al I spawned where
spawned in the beginning I like
hi
no what are the spawning with the
killer oh we can't adjust the task it's
like
set so the moment Ru immediately came to
chase us I was like oh no
don't zaa is like what what is
TK me no I wasn't talking
about I thought it was I thought it was
Zeta but then Zeta
died why I did that thing okay um
there's this one called Trick and
Treat so villagers complete task to call
meetings and then vote out the monster
to win so it's like we're wolf right the
coun wins when everyone's been converted
to a throw I don't know what a throw is
like vampire I guess okay
I okay basically
we do Tas call meeting vote out the SS
one
okay okay I like the killing though
ready
[Music]
ready killing
time grandfathers no don't come near no
I'm not I'm not doing anything
why why people afraid of me it's
different
mode a grandfather's dust oh no a
Grandfather's
Clock I thought it's like grandfather's
ashes or
something
how
okay get
book uh uh uh uh uh man I kind of want
to kill any everyone
though
Kyla it's
Kyla
k
[Music]
it's oh my God what
the I don't know um I was at the studio
restringing
Theos with my tasks I haven't seen
anyone I haven't seen anyone but wa wa
but she was just I don't think wa or res
anywhere
either I'm going
to okay I'm going to for
myself
goodbye
goodbye it's not me though have an
intervention about
bullying guiled by public
opinion
okay I'm
now hi
waa I'm going to eat
you I'm going to eat
you there's a
SK I can't eat you
though yeah I just want to make waa
anxious or is it
Wawa it was so hard to figure out I
didn't know what I was doing but I guess
I won
[Music]
yay thank you my little vampire babies
you're welcome the one who converted all
of them well not all of them most of
them oh
wow that was
fun
nice wait so what can the
do yeah the vampires turn into like
zombies so they're kind of like yeah
like
zombies but even when I clicked like the
Turning thingy it didn't happen
immediately it takes a while I guess oh
oh did it happen immediately for for the
others for the ones for the fs who
converted other normal people you know
what I
mean I sure let's play let's let's play
one more okay
yeah last one whoever becomes the
vampire good luck just try pushing
everything
everyone Lee not me oh okay
I had enough of
[Music]
killings I supposed to go
oh
spanking
pillow spank spank spank spank spank
spank is that
okay
hello research I
heard oh
[Music]
what
yo what the
[\h__\h]
okay rain I don't think it's Ana either
yeah I don't think it's rainu so it's
either Ru or wa I vote waa I had enough
being
voted I understand okay I wouldn't vote
you either bullying is not
okay i'mna I'm going to be a bully today
inv V
res you're going to regret it
cuz you were you were talking about
spanking something well that's that's my
job I see what it's my
job again no it's not
me that's not me man
damn hello I wanted that
one
[Music]
why why am I the the one that nominated
as the most
sussy I know I'm kind of Psychopathic
but but you
know I'm not I'm not evil I mean kind of
but
see
it's see you got to trust me I'm always
honest I I don't know why it gave me
vampire again see I told
[Laughter]
you spicy
time work for some
reason you knew what was going on
well it's because I need to fluff the
pillow oh me
to Out For Blood one more please please
please please please please please do do
we still want to do the previous one or
new one new new one sounds all right
okay what about this taste like
chicken social deduction Battle Royale
protect your team's chicken and kill
everyone
else
deduction I don't the duck the duck duck
the duck
like I'm not sure try Roy I think yeah I
think it's like it's like Battle Royale
I think you're supposed to protect
yourself one one man for their own
okay okay protect your chicken ready up
protect ready ready protect your
[Music]
chicken who's not ready let's see
everyone's ready everyone's ready why
can't I start the game try again try
again are you ready I'm ready I'm ready
I'm ready
are you
[Music]
ready here okay I'm ready up
again
ah maybe we need a minimum amount of
people to
[Music]
stop okay we can try the um we can try
this one this one
and seek maybe yeah let's go okay let's
try whatever this is let's
go we have to take down M even though
she's not
here I can't start either I wonder why
that's so
weird and then ready maybe we can yeah
I'm ready and ready already um yeah me
too okay I'm ready now I also did
um
weird let me try again sorry let me try
again no
problem maybe if the room is restarted
worst case I think the only like you can
ready um if it's like classic my button
lit up when it was classic but other
molds I don't think I
can
what do you guys want to try
draft dra draft is like the like classic
but like you can pick your rules now
okay that's so
nice let's
[Music]
go
okay oh you get a G oh you get a
oh what what is
[Music]
this to choose
first okay you need to win a vulture why
would you choose vulture out of all
things because I like
eating I mean I'm I'm picking I'm
picking whatever this but can we see
what the what the duck the goose the
duck also chooses then duck yeah I think
we can choose we can choose everything
like we can see everyone's oh
but but I'm not a killer I only eat
G living the life of G does it show a
fake one maybe for the maybe show a fake
one doesn't show people's names or what
player they are yeah so yeah it doesn't
show I guess yeah I guess technically we
can just like guess which one is
it w a lot of people picking
random I was
sheriff
sheriff damn it I wanted to be
Sheriff
[Music]
then eat food a food this does not
satisfy me I want more I want to consume
more yummy
yummy no I'm not s why are
you okay
[Music]
a no I want to eat
n she she just she just ended me who's
about to help her so
she's that's her loss
[Music]
areum is it so silent where where was
the body where's the body I don't know I
didn't see it I think it's selfreported
I'm the sheriff so I can't oh you're the
what r z your Z I just need food Zeta
Zeta give meway by the labor by the okay
I think came from above from the hallway
and
it yeah I think it was it though
yeah you hurt the
high two people did I want food West wi
no way you came to the kitchen
there
was I was in the
wng I no you said hi to us hi one thing
for sure it's not Ona because I was with
her the whole time yeah I was with all
the whole time
so
to
Def
myself goodbye Zeta goodbye
Zeta Zeta it was your
mistake Zeta it was your
[Music]
mistake why did you kill
me you should have not killed me I
actually don't remember saying
hi ially don't remember saying you
should have not killed me Zeta I am your
helper you my
help didn't you hear a hi didn't you
hear someone saying hi maybe it's me no
but I did saw Zeta I don't know oh you
didn't see Zeta I heard hi I mean I said
hi to
everybody she was singing weren't you
dead I was dead Zeta killed me yeah you
were dead yeah I killed my
helper yeah it wasn't you then if you
were dead cuz it was righted before the
body was found
I
oh yeah that was fun though the was
fun can we do it
again okay let's do it let's do it again
let's
go I want to I swear to God someone said
hi Chad you hurt
no I didn't hear a
hi I was so close to killing she was in
front of my eyes
that's so freaked up Pi
vulture you sick sick
being eat
food cores I like this
one then you're a party you win then
that's you Z what's a party wow Zeta
what
do detective nice what is that that
looks
like
Batman
[Music]
Batman give me the m
yum
[Music]
mouse mouse
hi
MH
M wow we're hitting ba
dead
[Music]
I
kle
hello
hello you're not a vulture this time
no the Roa take from me that's
sad
no I like eating
corpses
heyo
[Laughter]
zombas hey
yo damn I'm smart
what' you do did you just kill somebody
no I was I was making a new um word zom
buy
sorry I I don't want to
[Laughter]
know oh humping pillows let's go my
favorite
H is waiting where is
pillow
got humping W my love oh my God finally
I find you they want to hump together on
the
pillow
[Music]
e
oh
spicy all right let's do this
okay you know I don't got to do my task
don't die
[Music]
okay dying is not my specialty God voted
is my
specialty first attack
yes oh you
again
wow get plunger oh I see I see I thought
I was done oh there's another one unclog
toilet
okay there's so many TS okay yeah I got
to do this one the bath oh I hate this
one the
I don't understand how it
works I've never gotten this one
before how does it
work oh no
[Applause]
fire ooh on
fire we'll see fire fire sorry guys I'm
going
toass I think it's
raining coming it's r
what oh this how do
I oh
God oh my God how
how where's you guys did it you
saved I saved the
day I'm assembling the knife it is my
specialty I'm assembling the knife so I
can cut your
teeth assembling the knives so we can go
party I'm assembling the
knives party party party
hi there so many candle
what ingredients
ingredients
[Music]
W I think the the the the the people are
not as oh hello
hi
hi potato salad turn on stuff stuff
mates bath
bath I'll protect
you yeah hell
[Applause]
yeah what the [\h__\h] you were a
vulture she was she was following you
just in case you
di yeah I was hoping I was hoping either
of you you guys will
get it was hard cuz everyone was to get
there the whole
time yeah I I think having only one
imposter is hard it's so
difficult when people just to be like y
be
together to
be I'm not making it better
though I'm going to only accompany me
that's you
yeah okay I actually you know what's
crazy I actually didn't know that party
was an imposter I thought party was just
like a goose just like just like a just
like a useless Ro I was like it's it
only says something like you can give
someone high pitch sound during meetings
I was like sounds cool
hit voice also
kill you can
also I guess it will be hard for
villagers to like discuss with each
other about sound
yeah my Roes like if I'm not alone if I
have like at least I guess if I have at
least two people with me I can't get
killed so that's why I keep asking
people to accompany me
oh
H was together the whole time it was so
difficult okay okay I think we could
possibly end it here maybe yeah it was
fun I want play again
sometime yeah let's play again sometime
sometimes yeah this is so fun thank you
for making the time to play together
thank you for inviting inviting
thank you it was a lot of fun yeah thank
you I'm so excited to see all of you in
Japan soon for
f
y then we can
party take care of everybody take care
everybody good
good byebye byebye
[Music]
byee
po
[Music]