e
e e
[Applause]
[Music]
k
the think
[Music]
[Applause]
trust me
[Music]
I'm
you
[Music]
closer than we ever
take
[Music]
[Applause]
k
[Music]
the heart mind the
count coming you
[Music]
[Applause]
tou
me trust me
[Music]
okay touch my listen list
he
I wanted my over can't that no no
[Music]
a it outle
shout it outout
[Music]
out around
no es
[Music]
it it
hey
it gifted was for
[Music]
man best the best oh
yeah my the next to the each by
bling bum bu bling bum bu bling bum bu
BL bum bu bum bu BL bum bu BL bum bu bu
[Music]
spe
the best oh
yeah me m got to my D to the next to the
by way now
[Music]
singing Bing to the next to the
way he
your
[Music]
[Applause]
kiss me keep those lips from wondering
off tell me every sweet and tender
thought giving me all you have to do and
more fantasies where Futures are born
and You Feel The Beat the r of the tun
your heart and mind the
countdown if you feel something coming
to you believe it and scam it
away I don't think I'll miss you anymore
I you there's so many just like you like
good news inste cuz fashion forming F
only hurts you in the
the said it was all the
pain tomorrow's another
today C calls at show time send the
moment dancing in the moon till your Gat
start swaying with my body keep your
eyes on
me take me somewhere deep into the night
touch me here there anywhere you like
trust me won't you let me look inside
fantasies and future slide it's just a
two of us beneath the stor
SK the only way to keep us living is
keep on living strong then you can keep
the kindness CU of moving on no need to
say goodbye on me I'm more gone just
wipe all your tears
away and then we'll start over
[Music]
[Applause]
someday all your heart your soul your
body you belong to one and only
unconditionally Ying now we know what
will do can you feel the bond between us
real we're closer than we've ever been
for me let your RM to mind and let it
all out from
within I don't think I miss you any than
I did you left I will say I love you I
know I'll take it back I'm us this I'm
not the same
old rning quick C and wind could never
last and bet it a very fast far away the
perfect place where lovers like go to
take a chance there's nothing here to
stop the planing Ro romance and I will
let you leave me alone without it Dan I
don't want to
hearby don't break the illusion
tonight could call that show time St
forever
till the sunrise feel that look with the
lights off stand up till we
drop wow hello
everybody this is my my very very first
3D live concert what do you think about
it so far and this is the hashtag r
member 2024 so rain
and you know the sound I make September
and this year 2024 easy to remember
right so I'm looking forward to your
post and your consoles you know what you
think about it on X okay please do post
a lot I will be
looking and so so the idea behind this
life event uh today is rave
Rave this I want you to see a cool side
of
me super elegant super elegant
elant it's so r boy and there's so many
planets K
Ki and then there's lasers as well you
guys saw right yeah
disco there's also audio Spectrum
everywhere you guys saw it right did
anyone here notice during the
performance well they're not here right
now though the AUD spectrums they move
in sync with the music oo for those who
didn't notice I hope you pay attention
to them in the upcoming songs okay yeah
it's super
cool the songs are very very ra and then
uh and then the song songs I sang it was
show bling bum bum Bor I had the Hat on
now I don't have it anymore but yeah I
had them on and then if you missed it
well sorry they were bangers so please
do check out the archive and also for
illusion KN well it's illusion night you
know you know illusion night for those
of you who don't know I'm stream
illusion night okay and up next we have
many many guests making appearances so
please please please look forward to it
okay
okay but before we go to the next song I
will take a moment to get ready okay
guys
[Music]
again you 1 2 three
for soig
[Music]
for
yeah fore
[Music]
I need
a
no is that
[Music]
ohe
hey
[Music]
foree spee
i s is s
[Music]
what
for on
[Music]
wow that was two more
songs the first song I sang ddy daddy
together with a very very special guest
called r
I would want one rainy Bogel in my home
you would want one too right and
then for this song I've always wanted to
sing this song in like an official live
and I finally can do it so I'm very
happy happy happy about it and for the
second song I
sangaya wait it's passionate
3. sensation yes I did it it's such a
long title but a very very beautiful
song I personally invited uh other Home
members Senpai and not Senpai we have
Lou we have K Senpai we have wa Kiara
and me
[Music]
together yo who thought you that Kiki I
told myself because I'm from Whole Life
Indonesia am I yeah really and I have no
memo in my hand no no the secret Secreto
secret
Secreto so okay well I don't know if she
if it's okay for her to be here is she
is it okay yes
really okay okay well okay well since
she's here anyway so what you think
about the song oh I I always love your
song Choices I feel like you're a genius
in putting the right people together
with the right song cuz I also really
love your beat eater cover that you did
long time ago I always listen to it it's
my favorite yeah and now you get to do a
mature cool song I've always wanted to
do it you know like with like a oo four
people you know spicy right very spicy
always
spicy spicy spicy did you guys miss
pavoni oo pavoni yeah this we've been
together so many times now I know I was
in your live last time right my birthday
and I was first in your fre de oh we
also sing a spicy song then yes so let
collect the spicy tradition let's go
keep it going we like it spicy well I
like it sweet but you it's sweet and
spicy it's a good combo right
y okay
okay what should we say I want to do our
bird mating dance okay okay okay we can
do
yeah yeah it's a long time ago do you
guys know the OG panach do you remember
it do you remember it do it with us yes
do it with usting dance yeah okay so
okay okay okay 3 2
okay happy birthday you remember I was
going to make a bet if she's going to
forget or
not okay
byebye thank
you guys thank you so much even though
she's not supposed to be here thank you
so much k for coming and next up we
still have more songs and more guests
that's right you heard it right so
please stay tuned for the next song
[Music]
speee
for
[Music]
for for
night
foree
[Music]
fore
fore foree
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
foree
for
[Music]
fore for
my
[Music]
dadic for
yay I hope you enjoyed those two songs
[Applause]
wow why do I want to sing
with I wanted to sing with her because I
don't know I just felt like um uh fire
yeah um she was dropped off in front of
my door so I thought it would be nice to
you know babysit while s singing with
her I guess and yeah I thought the song
Fits both our voice very well and we're
both blue you know it's kind of like the
tall blue and the tiny blue so it all it
all makes sense it's nice right I hope
you guys enjoyed our
performance yeah and for night dancer
Our Guest is kop it's
Callie Callie is someone I've always
admired she has such a cool voice such
strong elegant I don't know how to say
it but just you know very cool very cool
person very cool vocals and this time I
want to sing something more chill and
elegant not elegant chill chill with
her how is our how is our
dance I think uh both of us has you know
different indiv idual Styles and it's
really interesting to see them together
in a
performance and then next up
is
the did anybody guess it it's a DJ
segmento DJ part this I'm going to be
changing outfits cuz I think I don't
know maybe if we're going to DJ maybe we
we need something more you know more fit
for
DJ okay so I'm going to get changed okay
see you soon soon
[Music]
fore
make for
[Music]
I
one two
3 4 5 6
7 7 8 9
[Music]
10 are you ready
know shiny
is crazy
[Music]
crazy up
nightly heyl Dolly night let crazy part
night stay
up night hey night crazy night St up do
do do hey do
do St
[Music]
good
[Applause]
[Music]
kiss me keep those lips from wondering
off tell me every sweet and tender
thought give me all you have to give it
more fantasies and Futures are B you
feel the be the r the dun your heart and
mind the
countdown if you feel something coming
to you leave it and scam it
alone I don't think I'll miss you any
like I did the day you left there's so
many just like you like good news in cuz
passion fin hurts you in the end the C
swallow the
pain tomorrow's another
today calls at show time spend our
moment dancing in the moonight till your
G start swaying with my body keep your
eyes on me
[Music]
my must bring the s to the floor I'm BL
a sonic boom i r feel like I'm suring sh
don't need the sound Mak rain the baby
get ready if you want to ride away
[Music]
time
e for
[Music]
the at to your body
back defenses you'll be glad
[Music]
time
again the hand you it's
night
got your
[Music]
[Applause]
again better get me
[Music]
[Applause]
Al you
[Music]
right we the queen tonight
[Applause]
[Music]
love me love me
me and the next song
is sip some tea
[Music]
everything was easy I did it all Al so
effortlessly I spread my wings and make
my magic un fold got all problems so
without any set there is nothing uncont
controlled but there no way I can make
it tream more that I need do it I to
hold these things from into little
pieces I know I a little higher all to
the things
[Music]
iire give up as long as we got that
strength in ourselves we could rise
above the pain walking step by step
trusting my faceing me what i is up to
have me Let It Go bring it down Let It
Go never bring it
down still my royalty and univers
against me I will just let it
go let it
go let's
go let it go
[Music]
let
go I been living Carefree there's no
better was in the world that could
affect me I SP my wings and li My Magic
I'm cold not letting it show things but
I'm bigger than my feelings so be enough
there's no way I can make it that I need
to it I do this things into little
pieces I know I could be better than
ever hope
[Music]
as long as we got the strength in
ourselves we could rise above the
pain walking step by step trusting my
face giving me what I deserve to have me
Let It Go never break me down let it go
it never bring us let there cruelty
still my royalty and the universe
against me I will just let it
go let it
go let's
go let
go let us
go let us go
[Music]
attention please are you somebody
looking for a new experience or are you
by any chance a mocat who just can't
wait for when I'm going to be
implementing a certain
feature or are you simply wanting to get
a head start with flexing using super
amazing Badges and cute
emojis well you're in luck my name is
Folia Raine and I'm going to be here
explaining briefly what is going on with
bolia ring membership that is me by the
way at the royalty our super Advanced
magical technology grants you badge
flexing rights which you can constantly
show off every time you're here with us
we also make sure to provide you with
utmost care and sense of belonging by
granting you a wonderful kind experience
with cute emojis at just the right price
you'll be able to join our exclusive
Royalty Parties which also means
membership exclusive streams in which we
can have various talks play games
together and do other miscellaneous
member involvements like what you might
ask only one way to find out and lastly
safety isn't guaranteed but it's
velopment training in which we aim to
build a community of people who like
living
dangerously we welcome everybody with
open arms to join the
[Music]
royalty
for again
[Music]
spe fore
a
[Applause]
[Music]
I
happy birthday
R me
how was
it that was performance after
performance first up we have the DJ
performance wow for those of you guys
who don't know yet well previously I've
done a little bit of a 45 minute
performance on my channel if you guys
haven't checked it out please do check
it out but you know some people have
been asking where is DJ wayy coming back
so you know what I thought this would be
the perfect opportunity to include it
well even though we were on a bit of a
time constraint so I had to do something
super short you know believe me it's
part of um you know I really really
wanted to include a lot more songs it's
actually you know just a lot of whole
life songs I really really likeed I
think the songs are like super super
dancable and did you notice you know uh
we had like whole lot of songs back to
back I really I really really wanted to
make it work and yeah it did work you
know so yeah maybe next time I will do a
longer one you know so I can
like put just a lot more
songs I thought it's just like fun you
know I want to share share and play all
the whole life songs that I like and
maybe in the future I can do
more also you heard my song sip some tea
but it's a little bit different right
the person who did this beautiful
remix thank you so much red shift
song shft they made it sound really
really cool yes I really really really
like it I hope you guys liked it too and
then my J mates came with me and we sang
and performed sh High Honey together
I've always wanted to do a super super
super fun song with Holo because you
know it's just a Vibe it's just a Vibe
you know we're all like super like w yay
so I thought Shanghai honey was the
perfect fit for the three of us yeah it
was really cool right and look at these
sunglasses very nice
right well today's birthday live concert
is about to reach the final song but
before that I have two announcements to
make the first announcement is birthday
celebration merch taada there's limited
supplies so get yours
ASAP and here it is the merch key
visuals are illustrated by poim Mama yay
so cute
right and the concept of this
merchandise is like oo like neon Street
performance and you see the glowing
tatang too right with the sunglasses so
cute and we can take a look at the items
one by one you
oh my
God oh my
God oh my God oversized t-shirt loose
fit
[Music]
t-shirt this is a big silhouette t-shirt
that can be worn by
everybody can we see can we see the zoom
out version of the shirt
and please don't forget to wear it to
events
okay you can show your oi through your
Shir and then the next
one oh two a tote bag it's a reversible
tote bag zer
it fits A4 size and it's designed with a
zipper for ease of
use you don't need to be afraid when
you're like super hype and finally your
Things fall all over the place because
jump all over the place because you're
too high yeah so I think it's very very
perfect with the zipper of course get to
and you can also attach keychains in the
toe bag so you can show off and what if
you don't have any keychains what do you
do next one we have this this this
this we have Mar of
the cute keychain featuring aora Fabric
and you can hang it like string and show
off your tote bag and show off your
kitchen with the shirt
and then that's not all there is one
more
thing this is the next one a birthday
situational voice
yes it's a secret you have to listen to
know what it's about but it will have
something to do with this whole
performance I will you have to listen
you have to listen to find out and tell
me what you guys think
okay and by the way this voice pack will
be sold separately not as part of the
merchandise set so please do keep that
in mind okay and also here's a special
bonus you get for buying the good set
bonus
special
sign BR
C everybody will get a cart but there's
a limited quantity so
so guys and if you buy the full set you
will receive a card that can be used in
the whole life official card game as a
special
bonus official
store it's a member card to show off
your
favorite
okay guys so keep that in mind whole
life official shop only
and then second
announcement second
announcement second announcement second
announcement done
by it's crafted with a dark yet pop feel
it's mature but also pop it's a nice mix
of Both Worlds it will be released on
September 10 0000 so please be sure to
listen to it there might be a time zone
difference and stuff like that but yeah
please do keep your eyes peeled okay and
of course this time we will be ending
the live concert with this song okayo So
guys please enjoy okay yummy yumu
yummy ymy ymy YY ymy yummy yummy
[Music]
[Applause]
to y YY
[Music]
yyyy
YY y
y
[Music]
bab baby
baby y
y
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
for what
yummy yummmy do do yummy yummy do yummy
yummy
do
e
e e