[music]
[laughter]
Yes, happy new year everyone
Until just before
My stomach hurts
Something like that
You said you were nervous and your stomach hurts.
I feel bad but thank you
I will introduce myself
I agree
Let me introduce myself.
yes
This is how it is done
As expected
thank you
That's right
Mario Kart since Door debuted
Last year I said I wanted to do a tournament.
I've been saying it for a long time, so I'm going to come out and say it.
I will do it again this year
This total number of people is quite large, even 40
Yes, it's a burning 40, so today it's probably 43, 3 people.
There was a great number of participants.
thank you
Thank you in advance. Hello Holo.
live staff friend
I'm A and I'm a little assistant MC today.
as
Next to Towa again
2 years in a row
stomach
I'm glad to be
I also have a strange sense of distance
thank you
Thank you very much.
If there's anything, let me know
Supplement
That's amazing
on second thoughts
tension
That's why when I explain it to everyone
Something
On the contrary, I got nervous
What should I do?
We were doing it together.
Just today
Please look forward to it. Thank you everyone.
Today's hashtag Hane Follow New Year's Day
Ako's live at Cup 2022
Yes painted in New Year Cup 2022
Please tweet, thank you
Thank you very much.Okay then.
If I do that, I'll do it right away.
Let's start by explaining the rules.Yes.
Please explain the rules.Yes, this time.
Each group has 6 courses.
Last time there were 4 courses, but this time there were a lot of people, so
Since that ordinary cup is gone
The number of courses for each group has been increased by 26
It is a course
It seems like the volume has increased.
that's why
On the other hand, I might be able to do it many times since my ability will be a little more powerful.
There are so many 6 courses.
I want you to do your best.
I'll do my best and Towa-san will be there too, so I'll do my best.
150cc without assist
Yes, the items are not all items dynamic, but all items are normal characters and
It is OK to use all vehicles.
You can express your individuality in any way you like, yes.
There are some people with the same character, but I don't know why.
Hey, just say you're a gorilla
Some people use gorillas
There are people who use various characters,
This is where things get a little interesting.
If it was this kid, this
I think there is a possibility that I will choose it.
Thank you very much. Yes, please follow the instructions.
Although it is available for use 6
During the course
So that the same map does not overlap
The same course
Please do not cover it
That being said, yes.
For example, 18 points in case of a tie.
When there are two people with 18 points
For example, 1st and 2nd place
If there is a person with 18 points in 1st place and 18 points in 2nd place,
Because 1st place is the highest rank
The person who took that expensive gun will be ranked higher.
Yes, this is about the company.
I can participate in this part way, but until now
I thought
A little bit of score
I got 0 points.
Yes, your previous scores will be invalidated.
oh dear
I wouldn't go so far as to disqualify you, though.
that
0 points
I will only give you the points for the course you ran from the beginning.
Umo in the form of ability
I hope that young people will do their best based on their perspective.
I understand, though.
It's really unexpected
There was a bug.
Seafood falls as it is
I did it like 3 times a little later, but oh well.
But you can still take what you can get.
Yeah
I will certainly do my best to the end without giving up.
Okay then
Explanation of the timetable
I wonder if I can have Ei-chan do it for me?
got it
yes
From that 13:01 o'clock now
Now at the opening ceremony
This lasted until about 1:30.
A
Block qualifying
It will start at 1:30 p.m.
And even if I say every 30 minutes
I think there may be some fluctuation in time.
I'm just looking at the match situation.
I would like to adjust the block
B block
There are d block and 4 qualifying rounds.
And then add small fish back
ABCD
The top three players in each block are heavily favored.
and
Kai
3 people each are small fry
It will be shaped like a back
Until this year
Ordinary
There is no cup.
small fry
Only the range for placement
and after that
closing ceremony
There are also some, so please watch till the end.
yes
who
Will it be awarded?
Because it's going up
I don't know, but the other day
Deciding on the block
It became a lottery competition.
Let's take a look at the members.
Illustrations like this are cute
Matt's explanation is amazing
ABCD 11 people each AD
Shion-chan is the only block this time
I'm a little unwell
Unfortunately, it will be in a form other than that 143.
P block abc has 11 people and d
Blocks are made up of 10 people.
yes
thank you
Look at this a lot
That time when I was collecting paper...
B block
Sui-chan and Aqua-chan are definitely
You came out of Japan in 1st place last year.
I'm sure they will end up together
I wonder what will happen
[music]
en and ID
ID
I was the last one to lose the lottery.
I just went to watch the stream and it was terrible.
It's definitely a pretty magical bee group
Maybe, but we're still strong people
There's a possibility that we might end up collapsing, so
A little careless
Because someone will move in and move in.
Ina drew the lottery for me, Gura-chan.
I kept saying I was sorry.
It's definitely a battle from now on
It's already started, and what's more, it's just like that last time.
The size of wandering
It means you're in Block B.
Moreover,
BBB
Let's meet
Mr.
I wonder
He's my senior teacher, so I guess he's a teacher.
small fry
I wonder who it will be?
A little bit this year
enIDGPS
I think it's a bit of a concern because the level is a little high, so what are the top 3 people?
3 people
It looks like this
I think there are images available.
yes
Let's go
This is it
It's the final
Really
Well, looking at it this way
I wonder what it is hmmmm B
I have a feeling that it won't happen, but I guess that's what it is.
B is amazing
It is said that
Reebok is also today.
fine
Behind the scenes
It is said to be delicious
Moreover,
marine
Probably the store manager.
The captain said, "Yesterday, the day before yesterday,
Something like that
Holomain
I called him and we played Mario Kart.
Marie with hidden status
The captain uses it
poultice
What would you say?
It's like that though
Looks like I'll be on a boat or something.
the boat is in the water
It seems like it's a little stronger due to a hidden element.
Hey everyone
What do you think?
Who do you think is the dark horse?
Something like that
What is
I personally apologize
It gets personal though.
Amane
Kanata-san is showing rapid growth, so
I'm already pretty weak
Before, I had the image of being weak.
I'm weak but what should I do?
shape like
You may be spending a lot of money, but if you practice, you'll get better.
Proceed as follows.
You said something
That's right
no
Something
Sometimes I accumulate
I'm getting really good and messed up
You were practicing
My grip strength has also improved tremendously.
death
proper character
I really don't want to use Moa-chan and the gorilla.
It's going up though
yes
Thank you very much
really selfish
personal story
What is it?
Miyo-chan last year
a little bit
Is the tournament good?
It was something like that, but Yuru does it well.
Holo Team Ka
Let's form a team and laugh.
Is it quite a bit too much?
He thought it might be interesting
I'm learning a lot from you for participating this time.
Nintendo was happy
Thank you very much
Thank you, I can go to the tournament too.
I'm glad to receive it
No, thank you very much.
Today is really
Naga-chan is also like that, but
The staff are also in the studio today.
Actually, last year, last year.
Last year I was alone too
I was doing it, but thank you for doing it.
But even so, it was quite difficult.
Can I ask you a favor this year?
In that sense, various materials are used.
Then there are quite a lot
I'm sorry for the large number of people.As expected.
Large group tournament
Thank you very much because it is really difficult
Towa-san is fun
thank you
And then
yes
Oh my God
I can't believe it was that way
Should I shake it?
A super beautiful girl
Mine
That idol and the best
It's no exaggeration to say that I'm receiving comments from someone who is considered an idol.
no
That's right
I'm a little happier
I'm happy
Maybe I should watch it alone for a little while.
Thank you for thinking about it. Let's all take a look.
It's impossible
Well then, please
Happy new year
It has been held
practice until today
What font size?
Something
My father is receiving
I tried my best to make it sound as good as it was.
Today, let's determine the results of your practice.
Let's do our best
This concludes my greetings for the conference.
Good luck everyone
thank you
interesting
I've been working with some interesting characters lately.
What do you mean?
Looks like a book
It's like a book
It's amazing when I get replies like "Congratulations after all."
I want to play around with it
It came out again
Congratulations
It appeared like
I always want to play around with things like this.
I'm sure there are some
Rather than that.
that
Please play with it
It's better to feel like
It's helpful because it's a good idea for that project.
yes
thank you
I will do my best
yes
Let's do our best
I think everyone will be very excited about the comments.
thank you
I really asked him to do it on short notice, but he's also willing to model for me.
Also a model
Let's ask next time
Is it true?
Can I ask you a favor?
I agree
I'm sure you'll do it. I'm sure you'll be fine.
Yes yes
So then
Well then
So many cute cute illustrations
It's happening this time, isn't it?
That's right
This time a little
Participation award
Something like that
The shape of the three parts is like a door that was a present from my father, and I'll give you a little illustration of the shape.
that
Here are some illustrations of the characters.
I was asked to draw an illustration of the number of participants.
Yes then
I would like to introduce some illustrations.Yes
This is cute first
Written by Futaba Sensei
thank you
It looks really cute
All I want to worry about is as it is
It's cute. Isn't this cute?
That's nice
The New Year's costumes are also very gorgeous and cute.
that
She made an original New Year's costume for me.
Thank you for making it
Next
quickly
I have my teacher write it
This is also cute
Everything is already cute, but that's right.
Something
become brain dead
It would be nice to have Kou-chan and the items together for each character.
is
Thank you, next time
So, next time, in the next puzzle,
yes
This is it
feeling
Mr. Rin came back.
Five cute Misses
Ride in your favorite cart
It's so cute to see the banana slipping in the rain.Happy Birthday!
What is an idol?
That's what I mean
Makes me think
It's a philosophical video
But it's like that after all
I really like the sharp feel.
I agree
Everyone must be amazing
It's interesting
I always wish I had that idea.
As expected
thank you
yes next
The 1st generation students seem to be having fun here.
Porridge that seems to appeal to gamers
It looks like it's going to be a lot of fun, and there are quite a few moms too
There are so many dark horses today.
It was written that it is not a dark horse.
That's right, Subaru is really strong and quite a lot.
I've been practicing and it's stable.
As expected
I still have a strong lazy mentality today, so I made sure to save money.
Yes, I would like to take a look.
Thank you very much. Next
Yes 2nd generation illustration
Written by the teacher
Thank you, your New Year's costume is new and cute.
2nd generation
That's good
Everyone
2nd generation
It's nothing.
Yes yes
I'll go next
Okay then
0th graders and 6th graders
I heard you drew it for me.
It's cute!
There is a point where it happens, isn't it?
Certainly a little
I'd like you to show me
With 6th generation students
I'm sure someone is trying their best to ID.
There's something about me that makes me happy when I touch it.
Thank you for your presence.
Yes, the last one is the 3rd and 4th generation.
Nanao
Written by the teacher
Thank you
this time
I think I just don't have enough practice.
I have some practice songs, but I want to give it my all.
I'm rooting for you
seafood
Splash
Isn't it perfect?
Because
studio
So if you do that
I don't know the door today.
That is certainly true.
It should be okay, but yeah
A little strange magic
I asked many teachers to write to me so they wouldn't get angry.
Thank you for your cooperation
logo
Splash
Mr. Hiiragi joined us.
amazing
thank you
Talking about various things and being gorgeous
It's gorgeous though
It seems to be organized
I received
As expected
Moreover,
It is written properly in English and there is also an English logo, which is helpful. Thank you very much.
If we continue,
The frame of A block is gradually increasing.
It looks like he's standing.
Looks like it's really true in the comments
A block, right?
[music]
I just made a mistake in the wrong race.
What started?
I wonder if someone pushed it
I feel like I'm pushing it all the time
It's not just the frame, it's the amazing momentum.
As expected, Hololive is unstoppable.
A
block later
It will start after this.
Click here to see who should go to A block.
Roboko-san Yozora Mel-san Hi Ayame-san
I don't know about Nekomata Okayu, but I don't know about Flare.
Kanata-san Yukihana Lamy-san Amelia-san
Iris and Chloe Sakamoto
There are 11 people participating, so I'm nervous even for the first shot.
I agree
I just don't understand how everyone is acting like this.
on second thoughts
Well, I guess I'm nervous.
There is an interview.
each block
1 person and 1 person first, 11 people will be the next winner
I would like to hear about your enthusiasm for the preliminaries and finals.
a little bit
en
Those who are
I would be a little nervous if I came in first place.
Surely he'll make us sleep
It's fashion
Fashion shows what's underneath, and everyone seems to believe that it's warm and that it's okay.
iris
I ran with him yesterday and it was great.
[music]
No, but Ayame-chan is Ayame-chan
Um, what's that? I took off the training wheels.
I want to remove the upstream part of this place where I missed the dance.
I'll debut, what will happen, will I fall?
I hope you don't want to fall. I wonder if you'll be okay now.
I definitely want it
But maybe even with those training wheels...
Maybe with or without training wheels
I think I'm good at it, so I guess it's okay
I don't think it will change, but it's a bit
A
I'm sure BCD will be
I think the way it comes out will also change.
First of all, everyone is working hard.
While supporting salt
other deaths
All the other holomemos are working hard
I hope everyone will kindly support me.
yes
By all means, please
And this
that
You can also see other people's screens during the broadcast.
that's right
find another screen
A little bit of commentary and commentary, etc.
a little bit
while talking
I hope to see it with everyone.
Yes, thank you very much
I would also like to call it Fukuma.
It's also on this screen, so it's a good situation.
It looks like it is. Yes, it looks like it.
Thank you very much.
It's about time for Han
The screen will be divided into 4 parts after that.
That voice
If you put everything in a little
Because it becomes incomprehensible
Only the audio on the upper left screen will be played.
You will be able to hear the audio on the top left screen and our conversation.
I agree
thank you
It's about time
It will be half
I wonder if the screen will change soon everyone?
Hey everyone, let's have a tournament.
There are some people who are not used to it.
Whether I go into that room or not,
We are also doing wacha wacha right now.
Please wait a moment.
By the way, is it okay for me to ask Towa-san about your tactics?
I don't know how I want to go.
Will you run away and go first?
Or like this
I want to catch up later.
Or something
Are you thinking that?
Who do you want to be careful of?
oh dear
That's right
no
yesterday
It was really fast.
After all properly
You've been working hard without letting your guard down.
What I'm a bit worried about is this
Procon
is getting a little weak
It's getting weaker
I'm doing it a little too much
I went a little too far
I'm getting tired so I'm a little absent-minded
I'm worried
hand
Yes yes
Yes, but ok
Even if it's all, it's too much of an item.
I want to use it a little, but I want to think about it carefully. Are there times when it would be a waste if you don't use it at the right time?
I'm so nervous that I'm crazy
a
Now
Have you been contacted?
A call came to A's room.
[music]
Nice to meet you
now
We're meeting up in the lobby.
Yes yes
By the way
In my father's way
like this
Are you able to escape?
That being said, who is catching up?
I get excited
I hate getting excited.
first thing in the morning
Oh, I got 1st place
child
If I can escape
When it happened
absolute
You can't be number 1
I can go!
perhaps
I feel nervous inside
With a sense of tension
Maybe that mistake often ends up costing me a lot of money.
If anything, maybe
It's a little better to extract it
Sweet
first half
oh dear
Go to the front of the middle and pull out
He's like that
Looks like you have a good mentality
The most beautiful thing is when you hit it and then use a mushroom to remove it.
Yes, yes, yes
that
At the very end, it's pretty
There are some courses that have a lot of shortcuts, but I'm sure they are such courses.
It makes me want to take it out
I don't want you to chase me too much.
I'm definitely not coming and I'm nervous, but ok.
Anyone who runs in front of you will be chased by everyone.
That's right, I see. I'm so excited.
By the way
Other than that Sui-chan, that...
This girl is fine
Is there anything I should pay attention to?
Eh, what group is it?B
If it's a group
B
That's a group, right?
I mean, except for the baby and Sei-chan.
Pecola
I think Aki-chan is pretty fast too, but Aki-senpai.
do
[music]
I wonder what's going on
But I've heard that Gura is also good.
But look a bit
a little bit
The unknown is
Fafner
Laplace
That's a bit amazing considering how much that [ __ ] turned out.
I agree
A little bit of freedom
Wandering around 11 etc.
commander
I remember asking for that sauce.
Mr. Choco too
chocolate teacher
please don't laugh
Just a little bit
that
At the last tournament, the blonde group changed.
I guess they line up a little lower down.
There is a little bit of that itself.
ASMR
She's strong, but Marika seems like she lacks confidence.
Choco-sensei, please stop.
Yeah yeah
Coming soon
Looks like it's over
I hope it will be over soon
I guess it's okay
I would appreciate it if you could show me the screen.
Yes, that's amazing
that
Tell me I can't come in.
Kanata-san is amazing, but I'm sure it's okay.
yes once
It's okay if you cover it, though.
Both are fine
Oh, it looks like I can display the screen now, so I guess that's it.
Well then
Let's just change the screen a little.
Ainbien
That's right
It's looking good. It's coming out.
It's New Year's Day for Mel-chan, and it's New Year's Day for everyone.
New Year's Day for sure
cup
That's why everyone is wearing New Year's costumes.
It's like Hawaii
Looks cute
a
I think I'll put it in after the 6 people I've put in for a while.
Yes, the screen seems to proceed like this
It's interesting to write it yourself
Mr. Kuroi
Extremely simple screen
I'm sure it's good or bad
unexpectedly
It seems like a refreshing type.
fine
Because it's refreshing
Airi
Mr.
I always wear a hat
Looks cute and cute
That
From inside
Yes, my hands are fine too.
I like this style fully opened in the front.
I'm getting a lot of support from comments like this.
I'm looking forward to it
Ayame-san
I wonder what's going on with the tournament, Ame-chan.
Ame-chan is so enthusiastic
I'm sure you wrote it
album
I'll do my best, Sanyo. Are you saying I'll do my best?
[Laughter]
Only a little more left, yes yes
It's just a little bit more
I am entering the room.
Well, what do you think? Well, there's a tournament.
That's what it feels like, isn't it?
Fair enough
Each person has their own character.
The character make-up is interesting.
It has a unique personality and is on the bottom right.
Momoko-san
kana
They look very similar in nose
amazing
It certainly stands out here
There may be someone who posts the settings here.
It's me
It's like that.
We have provided it to you.
on the right
white
demon
Who is it?
Mr. Ayabe
I'm about to quit
But that's true.
I'm sure something is wrong
I really like it
Everyone is doing their own peels.
This is a win for Mel
I agree
Get fired up this year
I can see that flame
Messed up
It's burning, but I'm here.
what happened
Hey that black guy
who is it
Who is that? He doesn't have a face like that one with a slightly evil look in his eyes.
It seems to be reflected in the center of Ayame's screen.
Judging by the color, it's probably anonymous.
A huge race is coming
start
It's almost time
Looks like the race is about to start
Grand 150cc individual race
Normal item starts me
It's all right, it's all right, I'm doing 6 chains.
As expected, it has begun. Important
[music]
I agree
There are random people too Wow Ribbon Road and wait
a
I wonder if Anonymous is random?
Maybe
There is a random selection
By the way
Tournaments etc.
Not every time
fine
I think it's super bullish, but it might be the other way around.
[music]
Fuutan chooses
cheese cheese land
Yes yes yes yes
Very
weak point
What is
It seems difficult
cheese
I'll choose
It has been decided
Here
Top left audio
Are you out?
What do you think?
The audio on the top left screen is coming out.
That's right, isn't it?
[music]
Yes, it has gone up.
Should I go out with my father, who may have been out of date?
Are you going to Kyoto? That's right here.
It's fine to take in-course.
You're good at doors, Kuroi-san, and you're number one right now.
There was currently 1st and 2nd place
Thank you for saying that.
Iris is chasing me in second place
It might be good
Good luck Ramy, right now.
10th place is top 3 and bottom 3 only
Next one
[laughter]
Let's do it together
I see.
I'm in good spirits
I'm pretty fired up
twice as many people
It's in there.
I'm looking forward to it
I'm pretty sure who's number 1
Looks like it's black
[laughter]
a
But I feel like I'm watching
I agree
amazing
First shot yes yes yes
whole lace
The first place is
Takahata
black yes
black
It was black - it was amazing!
Other people may be faster, but the cleaners are faster.
I agree
I appreciate your efforts, but there is still a lot to do.
There are five races left.
Mr. Mukai is always wondering where he will go next.
It's random, it's strong.
Yes, the course has been decided
It's only 6 o'clock left.
After all, Kanta-san
After all, it was a department.
peach country
The cow is bothering me
If you hit it, you'll slow down considerably.
What's so special about Momo Country?
I don't know if I don't like it though.
[music]
It's interesting to hear some comments.
Ari-san is number 1, because he was number 2 earlier.
As expected, as expected
Apparently it's delicious
I've improved quite a bit, but I'm number 1.
here we go
I'm starting to look forward to it
What do you think, Kanata?
Just now
6th place
Even though I was in 6th place, personally
The part where Futan uses this squid is something I want him to do really well.
It seems like it is, I hope you do your best.
I wonder if the two of them are using Yoshi?
Yes, I'm sure, but what about the management?
[music]
Even if we bump into each other, we won't be blown away.
But
now
The red color is coming out quickly.
There are quite a lot
Good luck, I got wet with mushrooms.
That's frustrating
Should I remove it?
-I didn't expect that.
It's starting to develop
Well, what's next? That's interesting.
This is amazing lol
no
Mr. Black
It was so strong!
Seriously?
I don't know what will happen if I run into another person, though.
A
Currently in the block
I mean, it's been ranked first in a row or so.
No, but it seems like you're getting excited.
That's nice
but
It's pretty tough that only three people can go up.
fine
It's narrow, so on the other hand, the people who have already risen are really strong.
I agree
surely
big blue blue
fine
I have a distinct stage image.
There are places where you can take shortcuts.
there
whether to go or not
shortcut
If you fail at that, you'll fall.
It's a bit difficult if you can't get some items here.
first
Here
Collecting coins at the edges is quite important.
Come on everyone
fine
[applause]
It's 10 coins.
On the screen
Ta
the law of nature
a
mother
It's number 1
1st place
The green one here is a little faster.
It's really the strongest on the inside.
I agree
Yes, that's true.
Well, Crow-san, you're in second place again this time.
Maybe it's because I'm in 2nd place and I have 3 red colas.
Hold down one more item and get a golden mushroom.
Quite considerable
It means you're far away.
I'm wearing it.
-
[music]
Just a little bit
As a spectator now
It's so much fun
sorry
Thank you for letting me have fun!
That's amazing
I added a lot.
now
The total score is
1st place is 3, and 2nd place is mom, I think.
There are still 3 races left.
gradually
It will be confirmed
I'm a little concerned about this
A little above the point
I want to go
There are things like that.
Yes, there is.
Next time, I'll be totally nervous, but it's okay.
I'm the type of person who forgets once it starts.
Now it's the 4th race.
Where will the fourth race be?
Here are the courses that many people have chosen.
It's a bit different so I don't know.
where will it be
Ah, I don't know everyone's ranking, but it's slow.
surely
Hey, it's a music park.
music park
YouTube
This note
It's a big deal when we collide
You'll be blown away.
How about now?
Somehow
What everyone is practicing behind the scenes
Maybe that's true.
fine
It's getting more and more holohigh
I think my level is improving, but I'm a little less like a gorilla.
Try
Victory, victory!
let go
I'm crying, but the gorilla is also crying.
Gao-san
It's gone down a bit
Are you okay?
oh dear
but
1st lap
why
The souvenir
Because there are no items
So basically everyone
I was playing it a bit yesterday and I thought it was strong so it went up a lot
It feels like it's going down all at once.
After all, shortcuts are important, but we are disbanding.
[music]
I'm usually lucky if my burden is kiwi.
If it's just one time, it's a little
Tough but no problems
I'm here, Kuroi-san, even though I've been wearing it lately.
Lamy is in 4th place.
That's right, don't worry
There are also mushrooms that you should go to without running.
Oh, even if it's from behind, you're coming at my back.
The killer is also coming, it's a little scary
That really drives me crazy.
[music]
It's amazing how tan is catching up.
Wow, now is a good time to move up.
[laughter]
There was a distance
[music]
Maybe Mr. Kuroi is now in Mr. Fuu.
I see, I see.
It's some kind of storage.
And from the race point of view
already
gradually
I'm starting to get a little confirmed
I think it will be a bit of a change.
I hope you keep your spirits up.
this team
Now, which team will I be on?
I want it to stop, but to each their own.
I have my specialty, so it's definitely cheese.
There's a splash of cheese, I don't like it here.
That's right, Bone Bone Desert, it's definitely seasonal.
The stage is taken, isn't it?
[music]
A little more lag
You became Chloe's representative.
Delivery lag
The chain setting is down to that black guy.
That's right, I can do that bass properly.
it's okay
It's Iris
Ainu-san
It's delicious
It's stable and awesome
It's pretty stable.
As expected of you.
When Subaru-chan is practicing
Sounds like it's really interesting
That's nice
It's done!
That's not what I mean though
It's scary. Yes, this is how I feel now.
So who is it?
Stop it
Teano
I'm still going
Mel-chan
I'm a serious person who hides things, so I can understand why it's so difficult to hide things.
There was a first place where A1 came out.
1st place
Oh, just in case
variety
keep it up
It's like that until the end of Futan
[music]
[applause]
Good luck, but this is amazing
I agree
Porridge
[music]
These three people are not the best.
If you go down a little
There is a possibility that it will be removed
I agree
a little bit
I think it's still possible for someone in 4th place to make it through.
[music]
What will happen to Iris this time?
It was my second time, so I'll decide next time.
The next one will be decided next 4 and
I mean, the last stage of 3 is important.
Where will the last stage be?
I can't duplicate it so it's a bit
It's a matter of which one to choose.
The cheese that everyone hated
Now
last
Cheeseland
[laughter]
I chose rain and rain.
It's the final
Everyone, even more
Please support me
As expected
It's a quiet place
It's getting better
I definitely really hate losing
Quite a few of you are hard workers and hate to lose.
I'm getting compliments while I'm being praised.
I'm praising Oita for making it so easy.
Good for Ayami who remembers me.
Even 4th place is pretty good
You're pretty high up there, Mr. Well, as I said earlier.
The huge squares on the screen look amazing.
I can barely see the minimap.
It's a bit interesting, isn't it?
It's true that the eel is hiding behind the flames.
Be careful
You said you're not good at this place.
Mr. Kurotani
I might be a little weak here.
Maybe this is really bad
This looks a little unsettling
Oh, just a disguiser
and
3rd place Kanata
now
someone
I came in second place.
It feels like you're quite far ahead.
11th
keep it up
Why don't you let it go for a while?
It's so messed up
I don't really understand though
I don't know
Is this sign porridge and number 8?
Maybe
How is it? 1st place is
That means
What does that mean, Mr.
and
Mr. Lamy
Anonymous becomes a small fry cup
It has become
That's right, yes, yes, yes.
I will ask Mr.
It feels like
Shall I have you come as well?
separately
It's not because of makeup that we're tied for the higher rank.
In case of the final
That's the person who got that top ranking.
But maybe
Sakamoto might be number 1, if that's the case.
If it was the final
This is a battle that could have turned out that way.
No way
Next is Towa-san's call, but I hope it's okay.
Now
The results of that announcement
I'm putting it all together, so please wait a little while.
It's number 4, what do you think?
fine
It was a heated battle.
from the beginning
If it's a good match, it's definitely 6
It's a bit different when it comes to racing
That's true.
surely
4th place
point in time
The ranking was different from the one at the time of the race.
The excitement of the 6th race continues until the end
fine
I think it's important to try hard and not give up.
I agree
And Mr. Towa is next.
not at all
I'm not ready for something
not ready
I have an interview to do.
I still have interviews to do, so what is your strategy now?
Sushi is number one, which is kind of disgusting as it looks right now.
I thought it would be better to aim for it.
to me
That blue
Where cola is flying
I didn't see much
No, but
blue
cola
collide with
rank
I didn't see much
That's what I thought, so surprisingly I don't know what will happen in the future.
I thought it might be better to get out of 1 and get away with stability.
Did you get paid in the end?
a
That's right
So that changed.
I see, I see.
last
Were you awake?
That part is a little difficult, but everyone is basically good at it.
After all on the map
Getting to the top of the map after all
Which map is this?
Is it okay if two people come?
That means it's okay just the two of us.
Yes it's okay
Now let's look at the scores.
Let's take a look okay
Thank you, from the top
Nekomata porridge 55 Sakamoto 55 Iris 47
Anarchy iris 44 degrees Mel 33
It looks like you can read it, that's amazing
Amelia 31 Prison Senpai 207 Limey 27
futa 26 fate 22
So, I see, Loka and Rami
It was the same level, the same level, the same score.
Oh, I see it's true, but it's not like that.
The difference is huge
I don't think it's open.
In this case, the group is small fry.
The one who will be on the back is Roboco-san and Rami-san.
I was ranked low so I joined the small fry.
[music]
I want Mumei to fight so that he doesn't turn into a small fry.
For the most minor fish, there will be a little interview typhoon at the end.
I would like to share your thoughts on that.
thank you
Here's the winner's interview
Just a little bit
I want to do it
I'll be going with Okayu-san and Kuroi-san, so come on over.
What do you think?
Just a little bit
that
Are you curious?
A little Chloe's impressions
I thought I could do something
Is it?
Did you say it was a surprise?
That is something I am a bit concerned about.
No, I want to hear it
The feedback was probably pretty stable.
Yeah
Maybe a little bit
The prediction is
There were a lot of things going on, so it was quite a bit.
I feel like the winner will be able to answer the interview at his leisure.
Honestly, the porridge is amazing
As expected
Let's run together
There's something about it that's stable.
The black one
Sturdy
I was surprised that it seemed to bite me.
I'll contact you shortly
Interview Hello.
[music]
-Thank you for your hard work
It was strong I'm glad
Thank you, Chloe-chan
It was crazy, but that's true.1
times
It's really amazing to win 1st place in a row even though there's probably a lot of pressure.
I think everyone is surprised
I agree
Actually
It's true, isn't it?
I'll do my best
In the future as well
Please give me a word for the next final.Yes.
Supporting the high-value class so that they can show off their practice skills
I'll do my best while listening.
[music]
Good luck in the finals too.
thank you
Thank you very much. I'm sorry.
yes and then
It's Towa-san's turn though.
If it's my dad, I'll wear a suit
That Twitter disappeared for a while.
I will be doing a live broadcast, so please watch Sowa-san.
That's the form
Thank you very much
That screen ends up becoming the main feature.
If it's my father's screen, then that other screen is also there.
Because it is reflected
That other ranking
If you want to know, check out this channel.
wait a minute
This person is okay, right?
I know this so-and-so from this strange person.
Something like this
It's true that everyone has changed their names.
who's who
The lobby of Block B is being built.
[laughter]
If you think it's a strange person, I want you to add a little bit of your own characteristics to the start and preach.
This is okay
Block B is ready.
What do you think? I can watch the tea.
Because it is so
I'll go live, so please do your best.
I'll do my best, but your appeal is amazing.
Is it okay for the first time?
Let's start with the individual competition.
150 normal CPU
Well then, I want to do my best.
[music]
There's a Grand Prix 150.
Everyone is here, there are 11 of us, all rainbow colored.
11 Okay, I'm nervous.
What is the best place to say er?
Let's go deeper into chocolate
There is no such thing as
I think you want to choose a stable course.
I really like Wario Mines
I wonder where everyone will choose to go
big blue really
It seems like he likes it because he's pushing it. This is scary.
thank you
I've finished choosing, this is it.
Who is this?
It's the same map as Akoyori or Thisyori.
-
Big blue for the first shot?
By the way, today
I haven't been running at all because I've been preparing, but I guess it's okay.
Oh no
[music]
I want to do my best
Thank you in advance.I will concentrate.
The monitor
Oh no, I'm talking, I'm not talking
I don't talk.''
this
Oh no, I wanted to go outside.
Oh no, I was really nervous at first.
Oh no
[music]
I see.
I want to take this in-course, but I know it's not a good idea to push it too hard.
Sorry, it's okay, I'll give you ten.
Just go on
[music]
He is
So scary
Isn't it okay to do this job?
I'm worried
already fish
Cut it backwards
I was brought back here
Throw an item
The more I get the more I get
I see.
Wait, the monitor is lit and it's hard to see.
[music]
This is terrible
I feel like I want to be at the top, but wow.
Now
Wow, lucky I accelerated.
[music]
Do your best, do your best
Who did that, Sally? Wow, that's terrible.
[music]
Sorry
5th place or 5th place is not stable.
[music]
Well, who is it?
Well, who?
picture
Tomorrow, it's Aqua-chan.
Wow oh well oh well oh well
It's okay to bow, right?
I'm nervous that this will happen 5 more times.
Saga baby Saga baby thank you
Don't panic, don't rush, don't give up 3 Oh no.
I feel calm after seeing Aki-senpai's text.
[music]
Yay, Sunshine Airport?
crow
Mushi's Karasmith is awesome, isn't it?
There's only one thing that looks a little like a baby.
Even if Mr. Left doesn't understand, it's the same thing.
Yes, I would like to tell you
Stay stable
He said he got the coin.
It's not that it bounces back.
I would like to concentrate only when I am running.
The incostria here is delicious.
Everyone please look
That's impossible, that's impossible, that's impossible
Okay
I can't get over this, but I won't panic here.
Don't panic, don't panic, don't panic
I'm impatient
I'm going to the front
I still can't use the item properly.
that's right
Please help me
I said I'd stop doing encores.
It's going to become a flag, everyone.
Thank you for everything
Yes yes
Hey
Wow Kuro-chan
If only the banana in the back was holding a banana.
OK OK OK
[music]
Here it comes
items here
[music]
Item
No, this is bad
Please stop doing that
No, that's tough
It's so good, it's so bad
Are you okay
that banana
scared
That banana is terrible
terrible
It's dangerous, it's really tight
I'm Tokoyami and my mouth is dry from excitement.
Wow, Yasui-chan is strong.
We and Polly, wait, baby
Is that it?
Is it bad handwriting?
I just realized that there are no dangerous items.
blue
cola
kids
Stop saying there was no blue cola.
Only that ribbon road
That's it
That's right
Just stop at the water part.
Ai, mustard is good
I also really like Apekoro-chan's Excite Bike.
What I hate is Ribbon Road.
That's where the water is over there.
Even if you enter it's crazy. Sui-chan is amazing.
Danger
I was able to get rid of my tension here and enjoy the snow.
[music]
It's dangerous, it's dangerous
This is the third race and once this is over
It's a turnaround
1 time
I also feel like I want to be at the top.
I want to be around 123
You're heavy, heavy, you're here, everyone's body is heavy.
Everyone says their body is heavy
Let's all be kind to each other when it hurts. Be kind to others.
Yes yes
[music]
My heart gets excited just by being in front of my seniors.
It's dangerous
[music]
Not everyone is strong, so I'm strong.
I want that to stop
Don't be in a hurry
It's bad if you don't stand up after someone from behind.
Someone, someone, someone behind someone, which one is behind?
Either is OK
[music]
Scary Scary Scary Scary Scary Scary Scary
scary scary worst worst
No, take these two.
[music]
Use the mushroom here and wait.
I guess it's a switcher
It's too far removed from Aqua-chan.
Minimap, wow, it's so close!
I used something.
with voice
[music]
wait baby
Baby let's stop that baby
Who is going to take first place?
Then only take 1st place, you're too strong.
It's signed by Gra
Nice even
turn around here
I'm so frantic about myself right now that I can't really read what's going on around me, so that's what everyone is saying.
Sorry
2 points difference?
I want to calm down a bit here.
[music]
It's just too strong
So it's all about me
It's going to be full
[music]
No, this Mario Kart tournament is quite good.
The level is really high
[music]
I want to get out
I hate it
I don't want to be the first to be number one.
There are so many bad handwriting, who is this?
I don't know about that.
[applause]
I'm sorry, let me throw that away.
Wow, that was a bad contact.
I threw a request again
Slow down, slow down
Magical things slowly
why are you scared
stomach
Not
I can't get angry anymore
Someone please understand how I feel
I just don't understand why you're coming so much.
Let's calm down and take photos on the in-course.
Ugh.
Sorry, I'm seriously concentrating, I'm seriously concentrating on this one
It's quite important
[music]
No really.
There's no one in second place again.
[music]
[applause]
Seriously though
Thank you for watching
P
Oh my, its come, its come, its this big!
No, I was shaking
[music]
Danger
This is it
I see it next time too
How many responses
I can't see it, are you serious?
I don't know what's next, wait a minute.
Do your best, do your best, calm down
I understand this for the next 5 years.
Is Yabai Chocotentei okay with the same map?
No, wait, stop that spinning.
80% of that comes from lectures and 2 from synchronized Kong.
[music]
It's so nice here
I haven't been running much. Is it okay?
[music]
Akiro's line is fixed at 78.
Isn't it great? It's growing.
As a happy teacher
[music]
Yeah
Here it is
There is a long jump, but how can I never do it?
Probably at the store normally
Is that enough?
No, Grabo is so good it's seriously dangerous
Because we're talking
Where should I use it?
hang on
Akira-chan's
Aqua-chan in red
I can't handle the difference in red butts.
Seriously
[music]
I can't use it much.
stomach
[music]
someone corner someone
When I'm really angry, I play Nico Boxer.
Why isn't the corner coming?
[music]
Where is it?
[applause]
[music]
It will fall out
Maybe wow
Was it a bad idea to throw it?
[music]
This is a race for 2 year olds, this is the 5th race.
I guess so
If yes, then okay.
[music]
Yes, here we are, up to 2nd place.Here's to 2nd place.
voice
The only difference is that
[applause]
[music]
Is it really okay here?
hang on
It's like when you close your chest and come to your chest
It has a slight effect on the chest
where is
rank
Can I do anything else? Wait.
No, but I'll do it here
An unshakeable heart and unwavering feelings
That's dangerous
It's terrible, but it's okay, my heart won't break, and my feelings won't waver
Aki-senpai's screen with a heart that doesn't rush
Don't panic about the screen, don't panic, don't panic
It looks like you won't give up, don't panic, don't panic
terrible
no
Sponsored by
That's why I don't care about that, I'll do it seriously.
Seriously
No, here
[music]
It's the final
The first shot is good here.
At first, no matter how you think about it, the coins are important.
If there is a difference in coins, the acceleration will also change.
Okay here
Perm's red cola
I'll go when I'm done throwing, it's dangerous.
No, not here.
I don't really want to go here.
here
No way
[music]
Stop it, that's good, Sei-chan
Don't leave me unplugged, call me at the door
[music]
No, it's amazing because it's a competition.
I think my face is showing
[music]
That's dangerous
Banana when consciousness is too weak
banana
[music]
It only appears in this
No, I want to peel it off.
[music]
A miracle happened, but a miracle begat another miracle, and another miracle happened.
Oh, you've done this 4 times now.
[music]
terrible
Ah Ako-chan
Hit
Let's do it, it's a really naughty bomb
I've seen
There is this, there is this
I'm sorry, I was really happy.
I'm very sorry, but what is Tokoyami?
I'm really happy
[music]
Wow, that's great, I'm seriously taking 1st place.
What is 74?
Oh.
yes
thank you
Thank you 2
I thought it was so dangerous that I shouldn't do it.
Thank you sorry
You've got graphics too, Switch-chan.
Then come back to Ei-chan.
Can I have it?
screen
get it back
By saying yes
thank you for your hard work
It was interesting
show me
As expected
tomatoes twice
After all, that Sui-chan is a little soothing
It's powering up
this year
too strong
Too much power up
That's amazing
What about Sui-chan?
Gura-san
but
existence
It has been decided that I will participate.
Aren't you happy?
Definitely great delivery
I'm curious.
I agree
It's definitely a train
It was really packed and
Small fry, Mr. Laplace
Mr. and Choco Sensei.
I'll harass you, I'm number 4. I'm sure you're a small fry.
As a teacher, I'm really happy to escape.
I'm happy as a teacher, that's amazing!
Well, it's a bit of a ranking.
thank you
As expected, let's bring it out.
yes
This is it
Comet and as
Rumor has it that
girl
Gura-san
That's a lie
Mr. Picola
And everyone and Aqua-san
crazy
Mr. Olly
Ceres
Fanna-san
Kokoa
awesome game
It's growth
this is
and
Koyori-san
Laplace
pacific saury
Crow
Insect
And it's shaped like Mr. Choco.
I hope you enjoy it
It was good
Oh no, already
aqua
was also ranked quite high in the rankings.
My mom will be in 5th place.
fine
It was a surprising development.
amazing
I think everyone was surprised too.
Well then
When I'm running, the file is strangely behind me.
throw the item
That's right, you
I feel like I'm going to hit it, but for some reason I end up in the back.
It was interesting though
I carefully avoided it
Shine
It was interesting. 74 points is a bit abnormal.
Because it's outstanding
Because they said you can win even if you don't play.
last match
That's amazing
That's amazing, it's a switcher.
[music]
It's out
The king is better
That's it today
It's not cutesy.
I'm sure
I'm sleepy
He still showed that he had some leeway.
this person
I'm still sleepy
no
It was a door.
picture
How was it?
I was really trembling when I saw it. No, not at all.
I don't really know what's going to happen
really at the very end
I'm fighting against the possibility of the line going down.
Still this follow up
new year
A cup or rather
That Mario Kart
2nd consecutive victory in the tournament
I don't think there is one yet.
I don't know though
that's why
I want to aim for a second consecutive victory.
Wow
I'm looking forward to it and want to beat it.
Same here
It's a bit serious, it's overtaken forever
Without
It felt like tsutsu, and it was really amazing.
There's no such thing
By the way
Switch was so nervous that his heart was pounding and the chair was shaking.
[music]
It was outstanding
It was a little unusually amazing.
It's amazing how they only get 1st place.
Two consecutive victories with momentum
Say you're aiming for it
but
Someone stop this
There might be someone to call.
[applause]
I don't know, cute
I asked Ano Matsuri to turn off his screen and it's that big.
The manager is amazing
I feel like crying now
Don't plan foolishly
It won't collapse
that
It's a day to celebrate something like that.
surely
Everyone
the goal
I wonder if you're listening a lot
I'm already crying
There are a lot of people who are very opinionated and have something in their head.
surely
Noel
Moreover,
I guess I got the time wrong
It seems like he's been nervous since 1 o'clock.
1 hour
So cute, so cute. Isn't he riding in a beetle car?
Is that so?
I wonder if Sea Group is ready yet?
fine
Everyone has gathered together.
everyone
It's quite interesting because they put a lot of effort into it.
[music]
Nekosenpai Leader Watome Polka Calliopeanya
Sana Kuro Ni Iroha is at 11 o'clock
Yes please, it will start soon.
I wonder what Calliope is doing too.
jump king
I've been doing it for a long time so it's happening recently.
definitely jump
Apparently it appears in King
[laughter]
I think it depends on whether you run it or not.
I'm sure it will match
CPU
none
All 6 races
no
It's really today
Thank you for setting up that race.
There's someone who makes Robin, but I think everyone is calling out the rules properly.
I read a lot during my time.
I'm doing it without
thank you
Thank you everyone
Mr. Matsui's
All those people
I'm used to it, but it's still a bit scary
Oh, I thought, who is this?
OL
Like
It looks a bit like Yuu-chan too.
I agree
festival
Mr. Miss.
You're fine
I think Matsuri-chan's screen doesn't have to be on the top left.
alone
child
It's mixed though
I agree
I can't give up
There's no whale
Messed up
It might be a little off because I've been practicing, but I'm definitely growing.
Oh yeah
I wrote notes analogically.
As expected
Last year was really good
[music]
Matsui-chan is also quite competitive, and...
Iroha is number 11 on the top left.
I want you to do your best.I'll do my best.
Yo
Who is it?
As expected
I also realized that I shouldn't look at the comments.
I'm really excited about the comments
[music]
Looks good
character
As expected, I'll do it when it's time to do it.
He may be in the ranking
It's in the top right corner, but that's it.
Now look at the arbitrary
It would be nice if you could raise it a little bit.
I guess I got hooked on it.
Isn't it pretty amazing when everyone gets hooked on it?
Certainly, that may be the case.
here we go
Remains 2nd place
fine
[laughter]
The ranking is unexpected.
Is it showing now?
I don't think everyone understands
BGM
I see.
I wonder if that's happening
oh dear
But.
The first game was a little ok.
That's after that, isn't it?
no
Gradually from there
Just a little bit
Everyone is feeling nervous.
You'll have to be careful, too.
One scary time when I was 2 years old, I went through the door and let my older brother in.
That's what I get.
after that
If there are two games, if you fail here, it will be over.
There's a lot of pressure, right?
[music]
I'm curious.
here we go
2 game goals
Pretty much everyone tends to hate it.
a little bit
everyone chooses someone
I'm wandering around while I have a tendency
This was #1 a while ago, but now it's a bit more common.
oh dear
not at all
full bloom
Since it is possible to use it, Kaoriki seems to be a surprisingly good runner, which is good because there are surprisingly few people who use it in the first place.
Currently, my hearing loss is 9.
[music]
It was still a dumpling
What should I do with the shell?
Crony is number 1 right now.
I'm waiting with the red shell, but Crony will fall on my butt.
Now I can dance in a flash
And the festival
kana
There was a comment about how successful beetles are, I guess that's it.
perhaps
I might have said it at the sports day.
There's something
That kind of thing
I said something, but I can't tell anyone.
I can't speak Japanese but I came
Thank you for coming
Maybe a little
Did you study? That's amazing.
I'm happy
Huh?
I'm happy because I want to learn English.
calliope
I'll always be waiting for your English class, in English.
It would be nice if you could give me a little commentary.
Yes, as expected
Do your best!
I couldn't concentrate or talk anymore
No matter what, I can't speak anymore.
It's pretty easy to get a reaction, but I keep forgetting, so I put it in the male and female category.
This is it
[music]
This time 1
yes
A come-from-behind victory has arrived, I see.
It seems that everyone tends to not want to give names properly.
Something
I wonder why
elite
Mikochi
I agree
type that suddenly explodes
Ah, I agree that you might have something in common with Mail-san.
I guess that's mostly the same with his personality.
The people forming the team decide based on their ranking during the Yuruhodo team card last time.
At that time, 1st place and 12th place etc.
Miko
My senior
Maybe when I got to the top in the first round, when I teamed up, suddenly
earn points
It's true that she's strong once she awakens, but she's mostly a shrine maiden.
For some reason I feel like I'm going to lose
I'm sure there are quite a few.
what happens after this
I'm a little concerned
Sunshine airports are increasing, but beetles
Looks like those three got honey.
Looks like it's a little sweeter
Now it's begun
Is this the third game?
It's the third week
It's sunshine airport.
Sunshine is easy to run
Because it's easy to run
Certainly quite a bit
There are many people who want to choose
I see
I really like this place
In course
I didn't want to go here if I could get it.
I guess it's pretty easy for everyone to choose here.
Look, he's following me pretty closely behind me.
I don't really understand.
[music]
I don't want to be talked about.
There are a lot of items
Very
Looks like he's practicing
Ah
the news is strong
Apparently One Eye is practicing, so he said,
I understand it well
As expected
Amazing with no sticky residue
It's been chosen
I noticed though
It's just military tactics
It's called a bike.
The one that suits me is the best.
Wasn't there?
ah
If an item becomes number one, it's a bit...
It will get bitter
Was this good?
Even if I wonder if it was good or not, I can't stop.
Mr. Abe
thunder
dropped
a
I'm feeling a little bit right now, but is it okay?
The shadow
Now
I thought I saw it, though.
But it's not far apart at all.
[music]
If I can get something to protect here
Yes, the amazing shrine maiden is in second place.
[music]
Maybe it's good
You just have to not do it at your worst.
here we go
What will happen?
fine
Because it's a dumpling
for now
[music]
race
This is what I see when I look at it
Overwhelmingly
I don't feel like going out.
I agree
The screen is a little
insect
It's better if you're not good at it
I'm sure I'll be a bit surprised
It increases with the number of races so I don't forget.
It will increase to 6
This is interesting
It's funny, you're really smiling
kind
TRUE
The leader's
here we go
1st place
It's a summary
Rainbow road for everyone inside
Everyone loves everyone, everyone hates everyone.
but
That's quite a bit.
Timing is also very important
[music]
Please concentrate
I agree
[music]
I'm sorry, but I'd like you to come back again.
Mr. Watanabe
Still in 1st place
I'm listening now
Hearing loss.
It happened a while ago.
[music]
I can still go
As expected, there is no one who can go yet.
Well, someone seemed tired.
But where is this killer going to be dropped off?
I agree
[music]
Dark Horse Erika is amazing, Watanabe-san.
And Miko and Cunnilingus
Clay is also Mine
[music]
I wonder if Mio-san will be able to come back.
That seems to be the point.
[music]
That's a little bit
The score will change
Iroha-san is a little crying.
I'm talking, but everyone is fine.
We're talking here too.
A little bit
I
I wonder if I can do it?
What do you think? Can you all bring it?
It's really strong
[music]
Please come back for a while
I wonder if I guess this?
Now, can you stay on the bus?
What happens when the gyro is turned on?
[music]
Unfortunately
oh dear
The line is also a bit
Because it happens sometimes
After all, I want to cherish it.
I was having a bit of a fight with the bad handwriting.
Oh, it's Crony.
I'm competing with Mr. Crony and I'm currently in first place.
It's a bit strong when you have cola.
The first week is good
[music]
You're up there.
But I've been there quite a while ago.
Miko-san is amazing! 1st place last lap
Miko is really good at catching up.
Whose is this?
I was in Kuro-chan, and I was ranked 1st in Pro.
Just like this
As expected, there is
It's elite
Yes, that's what it looks like
[music]
Mr. Black
The shrine maiden is Wakame-san.
I see
[music]
Well, it's time for the goal after all.
Everyone
After all, it's decided
Like I said earlier
It's okay at first
It seems like it seems like
[music]
I had the impression that I had a pretty good score and a good ranking.
Mio-san, please do your best even if it's just for the last race.
enjoy big
Miho-chan hates me again
No no no
Mio has that kind of mentality
It won't leak
I'm sure it'll be fine, it'll be fine
[applause]
[music]
here we go
A shady shrine maiden who can't give up
Will it be the second one?
Well, it ended up being Miko-senpai's choice.
It's like I'm having some luck.
[music]
C
block or cotton
eyes
final
It's definitely going to come together
I'm getting bloodshot
How about this?
Mr. Watanabe, Miko, and Crony are now
My name is Joy, but it's in the second season.
Yes, that seems like it
Counsel who is a completed member
I keep buying it.
I think the shareholder ratio is good.I think it is good.
I think I can still get the message across.
Watabe-san is currently in 3rd place.
a
If it's a shrine maiden, it feels like she's going to the front and fighting.
I can't find Florin.
Cranny
Splash
is in 5th place
Oh, I see.
10 using coins
It's important to put it in coins and wear it in pajamas. It's very important.
important
here
It's quite important.
And later
Do this properly with shortcuts
If you ride well with mushrooms, you won't get stuck in the mud.
Decide on dark action properly
After
Yes
You were the leader, as expected.
[music]
I got into
this hurts
I put a lot of beetles on the back, and there's more sound in 1st place.
It's the finish
No, but it was amazing. Just a normal race.
[music]
I wish I could participate
It's a pretty nice place.
[music]
Just a little bit about that
Quite
Mr. Gura is here too.
That means yes.
It's pretty hot at every game though.
C
The block resulted in something like this
Kuroneko-san
I never thought it would come in like this.
It's definitely very good, you did a good job
Looks like Miko-senpai is going to come over now.
Shrine maiden
Miko was so good
You must have been practicing, right?
It's delicious and amazing
That's a lot better than what I did last year.
Has it changed since last year?
There are quite a few people who think this is about it.
I think I'm getting better at it.
As expected of 1st place
I think it was Mr. Sankanao Trial.
Wow, I'm really happy about the 4th generation.
pylori
You're getting better at it, aren't you?
Everyone in the store as a whole was like, well, Miyo-chan went for a delivery for a while, but that's right.
It looks really good.
Certainly this
I'm looking forward to it, so I'd like to see it.
Is that how the points are collected?
Aggregating points
in
now
Yes
still
Shrine maiden
good
However
that
live
Most of the body
He'll tell you.
point
Points that seem to be coming out
Please introduce the points, yes.
See you 60 points Miko-senpai is 56
Points to black 42 points 40 points
It's 2 points, 7. It's a shame, Iroha 37.
Point Matsuri has 33 points
32 Ajaga and 30 points for Polka
27 points for fairly monotonous words
Miyo-chan asked me to borrow 11 points.
Yes, it's 10 points.
3 people in black are 3 people
I went high
I see, I borrow Noel and go.
It will take shape.Okay, I understand.
You're an interviewer.
Cotton Me, who passed the 1st place with Yes, is calling.
It's possible
[music]
Sorry to bother you
Very
I was nervous
But
Watame
It's really been a long time
Seriously
I worked hard every day
The effort really pays off
I'm sorry now.
I'm nervous and I can taste it
Everyone looks strong, but is it worth it?
in
I would like to go to Joy somehow.
Yes together
Actually, Canada is still here after this.
I agree
what will happen
That's right
Let's have a little fight
Thank you very much
Thank you very much for your hard work
By saying yes
It's early.
Qualifying
1 more place left
budget
Has it been a while?
That's right.
It's 3 o'clock now
Although it's a little too late, it's mostly in the form of time.
Because it's on time
I think so
I'm looking forward to the next match
The next one is the next one
That's 10 people.
Yes, that seems like it
Fubu-chan
Subaru-chan
I always wonder about Mr. Rui the captain.
I'm not sure what to call you, but I feel like I want to call you by my full name, so it's easy to say.
[laughter]
I'm looking forward to that Marie.
Yes choose a course with water Well
It depends on whether you get selected or not.
donut hair and summer
Oh no, why is there a place like that water park today?
Maybe the captain is amazing. I see. Maybe I'll choose.
I think so, and
Okayu-san was strong just now.
Subaru has been practicing with Mr. Okaya for a long time.
Yes, Subaru-chan does too.
d block is also pretty good, b block is amazing
I heard you were that conspicuous.
b block is also pretty amazing
Yeah, it's a bit strong.
I'm sure everyone is like this.
I'm sure he won the en cup or something.
I agree
Gura is in 3rd place and that gura
Crony came in 3rd place.
Rice is
than that
Well then
I did win, but that's true.
Inaris-san, you don't really like it.
He's not one to show his fighting spirit, but he says he's really good at it.
surely
perhaps
I'm working on it behind the scenes
surely
Also, personally, Rene
I want you to try your best and come up.
Please do your best
idea
Originally there were only those three people.
I want it
Now, I'm Fubuki, and I have a real baby.
Something
Viewed by people of all ages
That's strong!
It's huge, it's huge
It's noisy, it's noisy, Auntie.
That's a daddy gag
Because you'll have to react
It's here, stop it, dad, no gag
Seal it, you're a motto
But I guess it's nothing
Come on, captain
I feel a little uneasy.
Nice that you made it 6 races.
That's where I keep Poppy
I'm collaborating with you.
GO with Bowsership on YouTube
and
everyone
individuality
It's strong
You care.
I guess it's because I apologized for growing up.
Actually, it's okay
I guess it's Fubuki-san.
What do you think?
What is this pushing the baby bottle? What is this?
Yes, that's amazing.
Are you punching me?
That's why I have something for now.
And Subaru-san
But you don't seem nervous at all
It sure looks dangerous
Teasing
So it's over
Is that true?
[music]
Maybe now
I can't believe they are being watched at the same time
grandpa
don't know
Does anyone think that everyone can hear the voice of mom?
But for now it's a little long
There is more
1st place
What about other courses?
Really
item
important mess
It changes, right?
I don't understand this
There are a lot of people who choose it quite late.
I'm saying that because you said so.
I'm so focused that my face hurts
underwater
It's a little sad because it's not buffed.
Might be
but
1st place
As expected, it's a mess
I'm concentrating
But I'm doing it without having time to worry about facial expressions.
everyone
I will gradually increase
As expected, I came in 3rd place
By the way, I'm probably running with this one hand.
One hand is pretty easy to bend, which is nice.
[applause]
It's here, wow, wow
As expected of a little bit
It's hard to read the rankings for this course.
I agree
Since this second game, I've been looking at his ability a little bit.
Yes, it is in the form of
I would like to fold it.
There are races like this, so the rankings are quite high.
I think it will change
Mr. Luigi
As expected of Nee-chan, that's what she is.
I got some jerseys
It kind of feels like an old biker gang.
Does he look like a Yankee? Is he wearing a proper rider suit?
Is it a rider suit or something like a helmet?
That might be because he's carrying it under his arm
How was it, Mr.?
At my current age, I'm at the bottom.
Yes, I'm sorry, I'm over there.
And a little
I'm wearing it
But it's okay because he's running.
I agree
I certainly can't see how many races there are.
I'm in the second row for now.
I'm practicing today. I'm angry.
Luna-san
12 is pretty good around here.
beach circuit
Mone
Easy course to run
What is it?
Narration
Waiting for a face
Mr. Subaru
and
My uncle was the first
I couldn't do it, everyone, you're number 1.
It's huge.
From behind
good
That's what I expected. That's really sly.
This is a suspicious person scam, this is a veterinarian.
is the lowest, so there is no 11th place.
Is the back flower okay?
I was skipping over and over, 1st place
I'm kind of growling, Mel-chan.
I'll do my best
Even Airda-san has a pretty good ranking.
Baby is doing his best today, so cute
Luna is also amazing
Note very early
It's dangerous, mixer.
Will I be attacked?
I agree
It's called a battle between babies.
There's Lawson
Is Louis there at all?
[music]
[laughter]
No, just a little more
If it had been earlier, I probably would have bought it, so someone pulled it out.
It's amazing that Luna hasn't left out.
Oh, it's Reina, Reina-san.
Although it is still number 1
Subaru and Luna are now in the overall results
I'm 23.
I'm a little worried about whether it's okay or not.
Engine from now on
I wonder if it will be that way.It's amazing.
It was hot! Ranking based on when you throw coke
maybe things have changed
Next is the 3rd race.Next is the 3rd race.
a little bit
Now which course will I take?
Change
I guess everyone has the same favorite courses.
I mean.
It's quite popular as I'm aiming for it.
I wonder why from now on?
I like it, I like it
Don't you like it?
Not much
Something like that
Surprisingly, I'm curious why Mario Circuit or a fairly normal course isn't chosen because I'm particular about it.
I've been practicing a lot
That's a troublesome thing, I guess.
I think I overcame that by practicing.
You can collect it.
I'll give you the coin first
first
hey
1 is also like this
I wish I could escape.
That's cool
I'll be waiting for you at the finals
cool
Louis, it's wine.
[music]
There is a possibility that there is
How can I say this?
It goes up and down
Mr. Louis
Still in 2nd place
and 1st place
Subaru-san keep
Sorry to bother you, but the manager will give you a shortcut.
[music]
Looks like it's okay
As expected of you
Let's go somewhere now
school
The cup is coming soon
Ah, there it is
That's what makes it so interesting
Looks like a club
ok to have fun
The most important thing is that I want you to do your best and have fun.
I think that's really important
no
Inagi
It's fine if you just expand your belly a little.
I'm surprised.
2 blocks basically
average value
It's expensive, isn't it?
I agree
That's it
What happens when dew and small fish come together?
Where is it?
I don't remember, after all, Subaru-san.
Cape Dolphin, that's right.
Ah for the buff buffs I want to come
It's big blue
Who decides which shortcuts to take?
I agree
I guess that's going to be pretty important
and 4
race
eye
The point here is quite important.
It starts to get a little tense from here on out.
If you have ID, please come
[music]
Looks like a lot of fun
I'm sure I'm busy
This block is
I had heard about it by reputation.
As expected, it's amazing.
Sakamoto is waiting.
I agree
no one
No one takes shortcuts and strives for stability.
The captain came up a while ago.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good
strong
It's already the third week.
coming from behind
[music]
Well, it's true that there's quite a conflict here.
Mr. He a little too
This is where I want you to do your best.
It's an accident so
This is it, yes
I think everyone is getting anxious about this, especially the person who is in first place.
On the other hand, 1st place too
Do jump action
Very good
I agree
But it's a little difficult, isn't it?
But that is
It's really amazing
It's done
I think the level of smoothness is high.
I want you to come in
I will definitely wear it this year.
Buff water hole in the 5th race
amazing
I've always been in the 1st position
It's just an item
I'm dropping it now
2nd place
We've been talking a lot about who's in third place.
[music]
What will the captain do?
Wow
That's how it will be
And everyone who became Mr. Benz
It's a place I want to be in.
very concentrated very concentrated
Good luck!
And the docile
Mr. He
kiwi
a
fine
It's a dumpling.
I want to use Kira in a good place to move up.
The captain is almost at the goal
Oops, that's it
yellow
san came in second to second place.
everyone
There is an underwater buff
Asbar here
a little bit
I don't understand at all
It seems like it all happens all at once.
I couldn't see it though.
What happens after this?
Not the best
It's crazy
I think you've entered now?
long
Looks like you were able to go all the way to the end with Killer.
here we go
This is the last race
Qualifying
It's the last time, but it's decided.
strong
I'm looking forward to it
What will the race be like?
yes
I think the rails are quite high.
Now the final is here.This is here.
I think Ruhl liked it here.
Luna I really liked this place, but then
Maybe I'm happy
Bowser Castle, right?
[music]
now
The person who came in 4th, 5th, or 6th place is 1st
If there is, it will probably fit on top, so there is a possibility of it slipping in.
Everyone is so focused on the screen
Let's do our best until the end
It was good
As expected
I'm in 1st place
Oops, here comes Reine and Marin
After all, strong people go far ahead.
Good from the beginning
It's amazing that I was able to demonstrate my skills in the actual performance.
2 laps in 2 races now
It's the eyes, it depends on the item.
But the captain
It's like this
I feel like I'm concentrating to the point where I can't talk anymore.
no
Even if I keep 1st place in this last race
Messed up
I'm under pressure
It seems like Mr. Rain and Mr. Sit Down are changing quite a bit.
That's right
As expected
It feels kind, doesn't it?
But then Lede and Lele...
Rayne and
I think Runo came in 3rd place.
There it was, Subaru-chan came in.
Marie and Subaru in love
will be participating in a strong defeat.
Marisa is amazing, after all.
last time
It's 3rd place, isn't it?
As expected
terrible
Direct
time to talk to the captain
I will certainly apologize directly
I heard there was an underwater buff.
So there it was.
All qualifying rounds have ended.
It's time to anti
It's about halfway there.
Well, yes, I guess that's true.
One game was so short
That's what I thought. Amazing progress.
That's right, on time
At this time, I was able to go almost on time.
I really want to go to the bathroom
I'll take a break for a while
Please take time to use the restroom.
I feel like I'm getting a little hungry.
Doors were a little quick to get in.
I said yes, so it was smooth.
It is currently in progress
No, it's strong, it's strong, I'm looking forward to it, yes, yes.
The results are out, so let's go! 1st place radiation
The end is wonderful
Strong background of Aboria Rayne
High price Louis Himemori Luna in worship
Until now Inari-san Shirakami
Fuuki-san and Momo Suzune-san Hacos
Bales-san Takanashi Chiara-san
And Kai
The eyes are now shaped like a sakohai.
Yes yes
[music]
[laughter]
icon
This is it too
Ah
But that
I'm sure Fumu-chan has 26 points.
unexpected
Maybe
Because it's true
I agree
Because
Because there's no difference
a
Pretty much here
5 points for sure
1st place and 2nd place are also 3 points, and even 2nd place is only 3 points different.
I agree
outside
I think they were competing at a similar level.
I agree
I guess that close battle continued for quite some time.
This is amazing
I'm looking forward to it
Marie, I wonder what you're going to say.
If the captain is ready, I would like to connect you here.
yes
extend
Even Mr.
I'm a small fry, but I feel like I wasn't weak at all.
I agree
I'm also curious about the engineering department's small fry.
I wonder who he is, Mitsuo Za
Small fish are also a bit of a concern.
certainly certainly
Yes, stable strength, that's a surprising result.
There are some people who say yes, that's true.
For some reason, there are a lot of birds on this block.
There were a lot of birds, right?
The birds are just gathering together, I think it's a crowbug.
I don't know who the crow beetle is
I think that's why people think
Mr. Yamada, well, Mr. Laplace.
Yes, is this the captain?
Yes yes yes yes
Captain maybe
Maybe I'm basking in the afterglow now
Thank you for your hard work, Captain.
Can I say something first? Yes.
[music]
Can I just say that one word?
underwater
Buff is
I'm sorry for calling you that trick.
Most people expect it to be about twice as fast underwater because it has a debuff.
On the contrary
That impermanence
There's a place where there's no gravity, right?
It's weak and compared to something
2x
It seems to be about 3 times slower.
[music]
What do you think?
Try running
Certainly
I thought it ended normally.
that
I don't really listen to that at all.
The beginning was over
Pretend you didn't hear it at all
That's what I said, but in my heart I was already
Usually when I do live commentary,
They said he was the captain, but actually he had a smiling face pasted on, but the sales were amazing.
Please give us a word for the final.
Please don't put any more pressure on me
Yes, everyone, thank you
thank you
Ah, so
Looks like it was pasted on a bit.
That's right.
It's something after all
Everyone after all
You're nervous, aren't you?
This is true even for strong people.
Because
Shin-chan
in
Sadou's Kouno is definitely
Messed up
He said his hands were shaking, so no.
strong
I'm looking forward to it.
and
What about small fry? Small fish
white chuhai
I can go
It's a tally of people who went.
who said it
Let's take a look at the juniors first.
yes
plus
It's dark
yes
I see, I see.
No, but
Among these
The leader and Bales are totally the same.
fine
I think it will come out
I'm curious about stage selection.
Personally, I think there are a lot of random people, yes.
This is Chiyohai
My junior who became a member of Tsuyohane.
Yes, please force me to do so.
Looks pretty strong here
I'm reading out the winning and losing members, but yes.
Nekomata porridge-san Sakamoto Chloe-san Amane
Kanata-san Oshimachi Mercury-san Tokoyami Towa-san
Gaurugura-san and Makiwatabe-san Sakura
Miko-san Aurochrony-san King General
Marie-san Ozora Subaru-san Favorite
Reina-san came in. The two of you are amazing.
ID
It entered normally and properly.
As expected
That's right.
Personally, I'm definitely happy about that.
Then, here are the new members
Like this
I think it's fun to come in like this and play an active role like this.
And Towa-san is also very nice.
I'm glad I got something in there.
I'm looking forward to it.Okay, here we go.
I was looking at a lot of things, so it looks like the next one will be at 4 o'clock.
that's right
After 30 minutes, I took a break for about 30 minutes.
Yes, we will resume recording from around 16:00.
Yes, it's 4 o'clock. From 4pm
I would like to start from my juniors.
Yes, then wait a little while.
I will take a break as follows.
Everyone please take a break
Thank you very much.See you soon.
Bye bye
[music]
[laughter]
yes
I went
Sorry for the wait, everyone.
I ate rice
I went to the toilet
Go to the toilet and eat some food
After this
Although I am a small fry,
Well, once
Can you prepare an image, small fry?
go on the back
Shall we review the members?
Okay then
This is for rice
12 people
yes
I will go on a business trip
Who will be the real bastards?
first
The battle to decide the small fry begins here.
No way
An unpleasant battle is about to begin
lastly
worst
As for Zako
During the closing ceremony
I would be grateful if you could say something to me.
That sounds like a nice position.
yes
I'm looking forward to it. Well, let's get started.
Well then, let's start delivering for my juniors.
This too
I feel like it's just a flag, but it's fine.
The strongest of the small fry
character
Splash
I agree
You've been at this store for a long time.
all
6 races
Ramin
thank you
Let's go
That's more likely
It looks like it's a hat
I feel like I'll never lose
The stage
A little selection of courses
Maybe
It might be different from before, so it looks interesting.
Will Choco Sensei be able to avoid blonde hair this year?
Good luck for the blonde
Good start
I was so lucky that I didn't even know it.
It's totally safe and okay
Is there anyone who looks like this?
I have failed
[music]
The cooking is elaborate.
This is happening all of a sudden, but I'd like you to turn around a bit.
Certainly a mistake
from where
Choco
Where are you going to go from here?
It's fun but stop
I'm transfixed though
I agree
I'd like you to take some coins.
Something
Personally, it's true
You are participating.
I agree
but
rule
Why can't I do that?
oh dear
I agree
Come from behind
You can also take revenge
Yes, let's do it sometime
How about it, shrimp?
I'm sure you've been following along quite steadily.
As a characteristic of small fry, everyone is quite good.
He talks a lot, he's definitely a mess.
talking
That's why
Mr. Flair
And Bell is 123
After all, this course
You're good at it, aren't you?
certainly certainly
but
After this course
I'm not sure which one to choose.
What are other people choosing?
I wonder what Choco-sensei likes about Neko?
no
Where can I do it?
perhaps
handle
The system is probably
I worked hard for a long time
skinny
Maybe my expectations are that the car is gone.
That's what it feels like
Just a little bit of that character
Wouldn't a splash map be better?
Well, I guess here too.
There are quite a few items, so I'll grab some coins.
Well, it's a bit of a dumpling, it's interesting.
I broke through and found Abel in 1st position.
Yes, that face is really concentrated.
Look at this serious face
[music]
Right.
As expected, it is stable and at the top.
It's okay
But there are 10 coins there, right?
Well, it's depressing to cut it down
It's okay to be easy-going
Isn't it?
Just a little bit, those two years are also a little bit older sister.
It's a little suspicious.It's a little suspicious.
I see
What happened?
that
I guess that's because it was deleted.
Noel's beetles are amazing right now.
Hercules
[music]
It's going up.
I wrote this in this moment.
Let's go, let's go
What will happen?
I feel sorry for you here.
I guess you don't know drifting last time
There were some people who didn't know how to do drifting.
certain
Now it's begun
[music]
Sunday
It's like TEPCO.
Koyori-san Koya-san
This is just the beginning
[music]
[applause]
If you look at the frame where you scream all the time, you probably won't be able to stop that tsukkomi.
I agree
I want to do this and that.
This is it
As expected, Mr. Ikeda
That's nice
As expected
It's quite early.
insect
I wonder why
[music]
Stop crying with the same face angle
I want to win, so I'm about to wear it
Looks like I'll let it go
Let me take it out or let me take it out
Did you avoid two in a row?
now
2 in a row
red cola is
The seafood was cut
All my painful feelings here
Let's hit it
I agree
There may be some points where I would like you to vent.
That being said,
Two times in a row
I remember talking about something like that.
Seafood
I was a small fry.
Normally
I spoke because I was in the third place.
Not fashionable
Yes, there is.
You talked
By saying yes
Member
I didn't really care.
It's true that we have no choice but to go up from here.
That's what
I can't help but feel like I was there last year too.
[laughter]
Koyori is amazing
A little bit
Let's move on, it's a slightly different course.
hey
I'm really curious about that thing in the back though.
[music]
It certainly can't be stopped, it can't be stopped
It's Dragon Ball
I was hosting my first major event.
Certainly there is
[music]
Messed up
twice as many people
Are you concentrating?
The leader is in front of me, but he's probably pretty good.
You may be driving the recommended car, but it looks quite heavy.
I agree
After all, this heart with bad handwriting is heavy and difficult.
That's quite difficult
There is
That's good, Furuya.
Do your best, try your best, move with that body
Maybe this
Even mushrooms came out.
[music]
But I don't know, but you're saying something.
It feels like something is falling
There it was earlier
Not much in the preliminaries
I couldn't improve my ranking, but after all
I thought it might be somewhere above.
[music]
on second thoughts
Everyone please take a look
Please take a look
[laughter]
[applause]
Everyone thinks you're always behind me for some reason.
Maybe so.
Certainly, it varies depending on the ally.
Hey Choco Sensei
Come watch the broadcast
I want to comment I want to comment
Guarantee using Drift that you want to comment on
Yes, but I'm trying my best, so I'd like to watch it until the end.
You can still make up for it
[music]
I think I probably won't come in last place, but in the small fry cup.
yes
want to go up
Just once
It seems like you want to see where you cross the finish line.
200cc
Who found the shortcut?
[laughter]
It's normal operation, yes.
So nice
shortcut
Mio will use it
It's amazing that I can use it again.
[music]
I'm going home in first place.
Looks quite a bit ahead
Can I just go on? From behind.
a little bit
Watching the game earlier
The length of that one game
I'm sure the explosion is over.
But it's not over yet.
final
Not everyone is that far away, so Machoco-sensei is a little behind.
I think you should take a picture of the upper part.
Let's drift
I wanted to teach
I lost my head
Very good
hug
Because it's high
This is it, yes
Invisible bangs
I can't help but say it lightly and it's beautiful.
I was able to create a beautiful waveform.
Yes, I'm in 4th place.
[music]
It may be something that has already been decided, but within that, I also ask my juniors to
I think that if there is a story, there will be various emotional stories.
Some impressions
I also wanted to ask
As expected
Where will you go in the end?
Does it go as the clerk wants?
Wow, this must be my first time.
mario kart
stadium
unexpectedly
Even though it's normal, everyone
Courses you don't choose
Hey, that's the point
Choose and go get it
I think it's good though.
I'm sure everyone was interested in something.
It's a surprising choice
Because everyone can take it
a
I agree
Not much teacher
I will continue to watch and support you until the end.
Certainly yes
But the small fish cup is probably
All the interesting parts
There aren't too many characters
I like the fact that they don't overlap
I can see that you are choosing what you like.
I think it's great that you came here looking forward to it.
It's pretty good, because in bad times there are only three of us.
It's too bad that no one chooses it in the first place.
Maybe it's in the air
I feel that way, but it's not that much.
[music]
Yes.
1st place
Rummy
It's Mr.
Lamy and the rest
Hey Ho
And again Peach and my meat
Ah, that's right
that's right
Toad and the structure of Toad
There are variety shows
fine
I think it's interesting to see all the different characters.
It's fun to watch
The atmosphere is also quite good.
It has a loose feel and is quite whistling.
Messed up
I'm concentrating
Die
I'm coming to the top
Just a moment here
I want to earn points
Ah, thank you for making me realize that this is the right place.
It's intense
It has a cute place name
rapun crow
I have eaten it.
The intestine transection is also going well.
Anonymous is also doing his best.
It's not restarting now
I ended up in Asahikawa
ah
One person came last
Yes, so it's not a tournament.
That means it's at the bottom
Choco Sensei is a small fry
Even though I am the tallest, I am still number 1 among my juniors.
Everyone was strong
75 talking
As expected
Good thing it was strong
Hey, just a little bit
There were storms and storms
That's right
I said that because I came to work with a junior who had a problem with seafood.
Everyone is like that
It's strong after all
Because
I haven't lost.
I think you were able to show some pretty good results as it was your first time participating in the tournament.
and
The correct answer is
As Choco Sensei
You'll understand if you watch it run.
After this, I would like to go directly to the stronghold, but I will be participating.
I
Twitter
I will report back to you again so please look forward to it.
So a little bit
Johan from 5 o'clock
But seriously, is it okay?
Or
Yes yes
Well, I think I'm going to lose a bit, so hurry up.
From that 4:30 p.m.
Maybe we can start like this
Around 4:45 p.m.
I think it would be okay to wrap it.
I'll make some adjustments now, so please take a look.
Please check it out
I agree
It was quite like that.
By the way, have you seen the small fish?
It feels like it's interesting.It's interesting.
It is true that even among the top 4 people, the top 4 people are small-sized.
What is it? For example, ordinary
It feels like if there was a cup or something, it would have been there at all.
oh dear
Honestly, I guess it's just a matter of luck.
I went to join the small fry, but I'm not a small fry.
There is also a thing called
The people around me are strong, so I guess so.
Yes, you can certainly display the points.
That's right, yes
Well then, let's get the score, small fry.
Here are the back score results.
Oh, then, shall I read it out?
I'm reading it.Okay then, Wolf Mio-san.
Hakosu Wales-san Takanashi Chiara-san Yukka
Rami interview Nene white coat
Koyori-san and Riyope-san
Unknown Infla-san Laplace
Darkness-san Shimumei-san Shirokane
Noel and Yuzuki
It took the form of Mr. Choco.
Thank you for your hard work, it was a tie.
Oh it's true
good friends
Isn't it?
45 maybe
There are quite a lot of people who score in the 40s.
Looks like Iketa no Choco-san.
Noel was surprisingly good.
No, leader
[music]
That
birth
I think I could have gone a little further
What?
I just thought about it
Things like item turn still fall.
I think that's also true
beetle
Wear it a lot
I guess I put on too much.
I had become macho.
Moreover,
Distribution screen
It was interesting
but
no
I think it was interesting
Here it is
The results of the small fish cup were as follows.
For Mr. Choco, it was during that closing ceremony.
Umm
One word
I would like to have it
If you are interested in all the running, please check it out.
Please give it a try
Please take a look
I'm also curious
Was there ever a time when you didn't feel skinny?
That's what it sounds like
Were you able to drive in a straight line?
look
I can't aim for 9 points.
Maybe so
It's not 6 races or 4 races.
Even in 6 races
I see, but that's it
I guess that's not the best part of chatting.
Miyo-chan definitely has a lot of Miu-chan
Oh yeah
A word with Noel
I want to ask, is it possible?
Miyo-chan
Are you listening?
That seafood
He failed, but he said he was serious about it.
I'm commenting
Sorry
I'd love to hear it in your own words.
Yes, I'm sorry
Why at the closing ceremony?
Only Choco Sensei
If everyone is okay with it
It seems that he was ranked 1st by far.
Oh everyone
Mysterious and subtle yes small fish back small fish container
It was a close call, small fry cup.
MVP, right?
No, I'll be forever grateful for that invitation
Learn about the fun of Marika at Marika.
Almost every day since I got addicted to it
[applause]
I was watching videos of strong people.
Line dropped
[music]
Haneah
completely
seafood
As a small fry
miscellaneous poems
I put it on
All the effort
I left the company last year, so as a friend, I guess.
Yes, next year, Tsuyoyo
So that I can get out
I'm thinking of training myself again.
No, that's fine, let's play, yes.
I'm looking forward to it again
thank you
Thank you Thank you
Bye bye
Yes, I thought everyone would come out again.
I'm happy, I'm happy.
It was so good
I'm glad it wasn't dented.
Okay, I'll take a look at the contact.
Yes, and the next one is a strong member.
Should I display it?Yes members
Let's take a look
Ah then the next Tsuyohan
I started at work at 45 minutes and the race will start at 4:50.
Reply in 50 minutes
About 45 minutes after starting
Distribution has started!
I agree
From about 45 minutes
I would like to start again
Yes, I understand
Looks like you're just explaining
Yes, that seems like it
strong
Here we are again, welcome back
Also, broadcasting
It was originally said to be strong.
With Chloe
There are quite a few shrine maidens.
I'm surprised it's going up like this
That's it, everything else is fine.
but
For example, number 3
[music]
So, black is the color.
oh dear
Even if Shibaoka is with me.
The rest is pretty ok
I'm sure there will be some convincing men.
It seems like there were quite a few people who thought so.
If it was 4 courses
oh dear
Sometimes luck comes into play too.
Well, a little Mario Kart
There's a bit of luck involved, though.
His ability is also guts.
Looks like it will
I feel satisfied because they are joining in.
Yeah, yeah, I'm glad I did that.
Chloe
And then there's Canada.
Apart from production
Mr. Watanabe
Miko
Mr. Crony
Mr. Marin
Mr. Subaru
And it looks like Rene-san.
Yes, then double it and manage standby again.
So shall we resume the meeting from about 45 minutes later? Thank you.
Yes, then for now
See you in about 10 minutes, okay?
See you soon
[music]
[laughter]
Yes, sorry for keeping you waiting. Stop it.
I'm nervous, but the final is the final.
It's the final and we've done it.
The one who made it to the finals changed Nekomata.
Yumou this is already a cat video
About Sakamoto Amane Kanata Hoshicho Comet Tokoyami
What is Garding's winding department?
Sakurami has been registered, Hosho Marie, Ozora Subaru
12 people from Fabria Reina advance
Thank you
I can only say the same thing
Even if the previous person bought it, Mr.
It doesn't seem like he fought bravely.
Let's all celebrate and praise each other even if we buy it.
Well then, without further ado
Please do your best
Are you going to say I'm coming?
Alright everyone
Should I say let's go now?
Wait a minute, the captain did it.
Everyone, wait a minute, Mr. Spall
I've been asking you to wait a while.
It's said on the game screen
Maybe I should wait a little while
Can I just say we're starting?
Please give me a shout
Well, everyone, who do you think will win?
Please try to make a prediction.
Sui-chan is aiming for a second title.
But I want to stop it Maybe it's another 11 o'clock
It looks like everyone is taking pictures of it.
I'm doing my best, yes, and
Also from en and id
We are also participating from
It looks like it's going to be a bit of a heated battle.
It's the host, so it's a bit
It's a little awkward to be here.
I have feelings though
I seriously want to aim for first place.
No, it has nothing to do with the interview at all.
It's a battle to do it seriously.
Definitely do it seriously
It's the hottest thing to see, so that's right.
After that, it's all down to luck and ability.
Yes, if you enjoy it, that's it.
But it's okay
Yes, can we start now?
Okay, then that's it.
When it started I was a little
Twitter
I'll be doing a live commentary on it.
Please support us.We are all about you.
yes
Okay then.
Follow New Year's Cup Final Strong
let's go let's go
Please change the screen Yes, 150cc
Individual battle normal item machine without CPU
I would like to go to all 6 races.
Let's start the final race
I'm a little nervous about whether it's going to be a par though.
Sometimes I wonder where I should run.
Warishita looks good, Warishita 1st place
It's scary if it goes down too much because I took it.
I hate Cape Dolphin, stop it Captain.
I chose the same stage as Reine.
the door looks nice
Oops, the odds are going up, Dolphy.
There are two capes
That captain has an underwater buff from splashing water.
Wow that's nice though
I'm not saying that I can get 1st place.
[music]
No, is this really true?
I want to do my best to all the streamers.
I hope you will support me
no
seriously concentrate
It's seriously a joke
Let me tell you one thing: It's really scary. Are you okay?
No way
What does Gra-chan do with hanging bananas?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, wait.
Everyone is in a hurry, it's impossible, impossible, impossible here.
It's dangerous
No, this
If there's an accident, it's all over. That's really bad.
terrible
I guess it's impossible if I don't get rid of this
Gura-chan
I didn't stand in line because my mom told me I shouldn't put on a cute face and do that kind of thing.
terrible
or
times
The worst is, my mom is crying and I don't have any coins.
I don't have any coins I want some coins
Even if it's just one item, I'll take it.
Items are seriously important
Deko
I wanted to get these coins, but all of them were taken and I ended up falling.
Yes thank you very much
But I still saw it on the second week when I was about to give up.
Chau mental mental
Slowly mental mental
Yukkuri Mentary
that's dangerous
No, no, no, Sakamoto-chan
Don't do that, it's dangerous
I wonder if porridge and gura are served before this?
Looks like it's in front
I wonder how long that will last?
No, Chloe
You should never throw it behind you.
Thank you everyone so far
No, it's not the end, it's the end
[music]
money is the best
No, money that you don't know what's going to happen is number one.
No, but Sui-chan is in 8th place.
Yes, yes, yes, don't give up just yet
Thank you for your warm comments
I can't give up, I'm not a loser
I can't give up, I can't give up
Where am I?
I'm waiting to see if I'm going to go to the Mario course, the tower just came in first place.
I don't remember any courses I took.
It's still only the first race
5 more games left
Porridge
You're strong, you're strong, everyone is strong.
Dangerously strong Adosu ruins
Surprisingly, I don't even remember the course.
It's no good even if you say ``fuu''.
What should I do?
Ah, I'm a little late, okay.
Because from now on
It's okay from now on
Everyone go to the right
What is
here
I'm not good at that shortcut. I had a big close call.
I'm so scared
Here
It's dangerous here
No, it's just as it looked a long time ago
Okay, that me-chan
Watabe-chan with her sister and that too
I'll see that
I don't want to go to the same course as you somehow
It's dangerous, it's bad, it's bad if you tease me about it
Abune yoshi
[music]
Stop it, I'm going away
Matome-chan, thats what you throw in front of you.
Yes, it comes with a switch.
Isn't it better not to take it so seriously?
It's dangerous
It's dangerous, what's wrong with that?
There are some naughty bananas
OK
No way
I really remember this gear
Who's Sui-chan? That's the one. It's no wonder.
No, I thought
mental meter
mental mental mental mental
4th place is good, 4th place is good, good
It's okay, it's okay, it's still okay, get up from here
It's going to go up
Masui-chan 1 Kakaketsu
-Sui-chan porridge Subaru
Wow
Very strong, nice mental
Mentality is important in this game.
I'll soon forget where I just ran.
Let's go to Wario Lecture 3rd lap with a popular battle.
What is Ecoresato?
Now, I feel like I have to keep talking.
I had a great feeling of wanting to take a break.
Please drink lots of water
It's the worst
Is this the worst? Is this place okay? I hate this place.
Understood silently
Items are a bit important here.
I really hope it doesn't hit me
Hey, this is scary, don't come forward.
Wow
But it looks good
No matter what, in-course
It's nice to have a red shell
There are times when this doesn't work out.
[music]
Oh no, I really don't like this red, please stop it.
too far-fetched
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
Damn it, calm down
I'm terrible at updating too much
Okay, okay
[music]
Sorry, let me throw it here.
I was avoiding it
I can do it as long as I calm down here.
Climb to the top
Sorry Sakamoto
terrible
This place is inevitable
Win course wow
compassion
too much
thank you
It's over.
No, it's over. This is no good.
[music]
Yes, no, no, no
Sunday
Hmm.
Water around the polka dots
There are three of them.
Like that
Thank you for not needing it
sorry
I just got a new one.
Another new one has arrived.
Takana's mouth was dry
No, it's from here, it's from here
galio mine
Please, it's just a normal course
If you look at it, it's mental
Runny nose
I didn't look at the rankings.
I wonder whose team and who came first?
Let's go eat some porridge that I don't understand at all.
Wow Dragon Lord?
4th race?
mental
That's crazy!
It's weird to hear
Don't hit it like that, it's dangerous here.
Because it really expands
How much will you lose if you make this one mistake?
That's right
Let's get along well
I don't think that's good
Cold wind wind nice
No, this reversal is really strong
If you hit too hard
Wow banana, who is that naughty banana?
Anyway, who is this?
It's over, so pitiful
I don't care, sorry Canada.
No more.
There's no love, but there's no voice, but it's coming out.
believe it
It makes me nervous, I can do it at all, I can do it at all.
I recently learned the word ``run,'' so I want to use it.
terrible
That's too bad, please stop it, that's nice
No, ok, ok, it's big.
Tissue with a runny nose brought me a tissue.
Watanabe
1 late
I was about to get some rice in the box.
Sorry everyone
Let's allocate it.
1st place is terrible I wonder how many points they got for 1st place
Did you touch it?
No, seriously, everyone is strong.
Seichanko F
I really like the 0 part so where is it?
That's it!
I chose Nature Road.
That's unusual.
Ah go excite bike
Let's get 1st place once, Toma
It's not that easy, I'm trying my best.
I want to take first place
I will do my best
item
Oh, I saw it fall.
Not red cola
I want coins I really want coins
Mamaman can't run on the inside
[music]
No, it's finally here
What is it?
I used it in a strange place, but it doesn't matter anymore.
Wow
No, that's dangerous
Oh no
The pronunciation stinks
The porridge is terrible and the captain is missing.
That's scary
It's okay, it's dangerous, it's serious, it's true.
I'm sorry
There is no such thing.
thank you
What is Tokoyami who falls into the 6 yen diary?
Next is
The next last one is amazing. Isn't it the last one?
Not a big promotion
Porridge and Sui-chan duel
I wonder what's going on now
Emo last
Curry, 2 more games?
The fifth time, the next one, OK
sunshine airport
Mario Circuit F0
I don't like the wobbly volcano.
Ah, it's still okay, it's still okay, it's still okay
final rest
Isn't it the final final?
I want to take first place with this
What is Nemoto?
Are you done with mental health?
Someone please tell me nice
No, it's true, it's not true at all.
It's good because Incoaster is delicious here.
Stop here for a second
I can't help but feel like I won first place here.
No, it's okay, this is firewood.
That's a little scary
You're so right
Stop that, seriously, stop this.
That's dangerous
Save this turbo, nice
2 is for now
I can see before I can see before I can see before
It's a fish
[music]
From a while ago
Sakamoto Kuroe guy and black guy bumped into each other forever
I don't think this will change
That's terrible, I'm sorry
I used it so much that I was so scared of it.
This isn't Sui-chan. Who is this?
Someone was so scared that they used it.
[music]
This is definitely not the time to ask for items to be thrown.
I don't need that
No, I don't need it anymore, I don't need it anymore
I can't do anything anymore
Wow
-
Osechi is number one
Wow
It has been decided
Wow 6 onwards
It was interesting
So that's it
Here are the finals: 6 games
thank you for your hard work
thank you for your hard work"
Yes yes
thank you for your hard work
It was quite pitiful.
I agree
It feels nice and heavy
character
At least once
If you hit it, you'll go quite far backwards.
on second thoughts
Everyone is strong
He's also good at running, so maybe even if he doesn't have the same item.
I'm in the same position all the time, so I'll just do it once.
It felt like I was about to die.
No, but it was a very heated battle, and instead of winning two championships, we might have won a new porridge.
No problem
first time
Are you okay with being a champion?
Why am I always looking outside?
on the other side
That's also why I'm anxious about my thoughts outside.
I would be happy if someone could fix it.
Thank you for your understanding.
Well, what do you think?
for now
Please tell me what you think
No way
It's okay if the level is too high
It really only took a moment, but it's already over
I also raced after that.
I was wondering if there were any left.
Over there
final
It was as fast as a fish.
The level was high everyone.
No way
It was amazing! I'd like to watch the champion's stream again in a little while.
What kind of mentality would you normally be in?
yes
I'm a little curious
But I was smiling so much that I took a picture of it on the way.
I wonder if that person had fun doing it.
That's what I was thinking, but somehow
Qualifying
than
It seems like you're doing well
Kaya-san has an amazing mental health
Don't do it.
With that voice
It's mental
There was a bit of a bug, so
I understand, messed up
I keep getting hit by the same person
I'm so sorry about Chloe.
I was aiming for it, so I was waiting.
Okay then
Let's take a look at the score. I can also give it, so please give me the score.
Yes, here it is everyone points
It seems like it's usually expensive
What can I really say?
There is no such thing as Qoo10. Yes, my child.
That wonderful follow-up New Year's with 69 points
Champion of Cup 2022
Congratulations!
And Sui-chan and
3rd place goes to Marie and Gaulgura
The shrine maiden, the shrine maiden, is also quite high-ranking.
Amazing and Watame-san and
Mr. Door is tied for 1st place.
I feel like I took it, so it's above.
And Subaru-san and Rain-san
Kanata-san Kuroni-san Kuroi-san
That's the form
It came out a lot
Really stop it
something
I thought maybe he had some kind of personal grudge against me.
That's right
Yes, that's pretty much it.
that
Smoother than originally planned
Or rather
I guess it was early.
I'm sure it will develop like that.
yes
Listen to the explanation
Thank you for reading
Follow me smoothly
Everyone cooperated, including Moe-chan's cooperation.
It went smoothly
Amazing already
enj and ID
The force is coming
And as expected
you know what
There's also a staff member who can translate for you.
It was amazing
thank you
Yes, now
vigilance
Because I can go to the ceremony
Yes, that's how I want to appear.
Yes, but
yes
a little bit
I'll change the color though.
here is
Yeah
If you say yes, the closing ceremony will come.
Well, chu-hi too, after all.
Due to the large number of people, there is also a strong handout.
JP with a small fry
It means that he was a member of
Yeah, but Gura-san was pretty strong too.
The bear was pretty strong too lol
A sign that looks like it's about to come in
It seemed like it would be in the top cell though.
At first I got a result like this
Now let's move on to the closing ceremony.
Let's move to
Please be sure to watch till the end.
Something a little
There's also an announcement at the end.
I'm listening, so
Thank you very much.Yes
Will the screen change?
It changed every day
In winter
closing ceremony
Shall we start right away?
yes
It seems like there are some people who haven't been able to come yet.
It seems like there isn't any, but Choco Sensei
Ma
first that
How can I say it?
Worst at the closing ceremony
small fry
my worst
Stop at the strong 3
It's 3
I agree
I would like to interview someone who
Yes, please come here.
I got 9 points in both the preliminaries and the main match.
It's not great, on the contrary, wait, wait.
12 races
That's 18 points for running.
It's a picture. What do you think?
Since he's a small fry, he's not going to get any better.
That's true, but on the contrary, it's amazing.
Choco thinks it's a bit of a problem that Hololive doesn't have anyone worse than Choco, but first of all,
The problem is that it's been 3 years and I haven't gotten any better in 3 years.
[music]
Aki-senpai still doesn't think it's because he was rejected.
Chocolate theme even if it can be fixed
It's all about this and that.
Please try a little drift on this one
I would like you to remember the number that hit the mark.
I want to hear that. How many times have you fallen?
How many times have you shaved your car?
I was a bit curious.
Before I knew it, I had reached a point where I couldn't turn.
I noticed it, noticed it, and a little later, Choco-sensei.
I've always been curious about Choco-sensei.
that
Twitter
If you look at his profile, he's always new.
I'm a vtuber
[music]
I'm working on a new employee.
Forever
I was thinking
sky
I want people to watch this really interesting race, even if it means they're probably going to tell the police.
Thank you very much.
I did it seriously this year too.
I hope to see you again next year
I have high hopes for this.
next year
I'm looking forward to it
Thank you for the chocolate too.
no
But.
Both hosts
Thank you for your hard work, Mr.
thank you
Thank you very much
I'm looking forward to it in many ways.
thank you
Bye bye
Well then
It's refreshing not to worry about it at all
No, but not yet
On the contrary, next year
It would be interesting if Choco-sensei became damn good.
That's already
I can only run SS
If you say that
It's a lie, right?
That's it
By all means, please
About 1 month
I would like special training
I have a chance to do that
By saying yes
yes
It's an award
Yes, I want to move.
It seems that there are still some people who have not come yet.
So let's start by asking about number three.
I agree
Okay, now to the third place
Marine to Captain
[music]
I would like to ask
That's amazing
no
Matata-san
more
became even stronger
Yeah, I guess so.
Being able to get the signature itself
first
It was really amazing, but there was also a moment when the captain was totally in 11th place, which seems like it was at the end.
[music]
Something
coincidence
Blue
I'm lucky that the cola didn't come flying at me.
I practiced even though I got 1st place.
I wonder what this is?
My rate was 4500 before I started practicing.
Isn't she a hardworking woman?
That's amazing, well done
I tried my best, just a little more
Because I haven't been able to show much of what I'm trying to do in the current situation.
He might have run away even though he didn't do anything.
not at all
No, but
The result is this rhinoceros.
perhaps
Listeners and all
admit
I think it's the result
That's right
I felt like a demon, thinking that I could never do it on my own.
I wanted to lower the hurdle.
This is it
a little bit
Because they come at me with a stance like this
Messed up
I wanted to lower the hurdle.
This is it
It looks like you jumped over that hurdle
It feels good
As expected, yes
thank you
Excuse me, I'm 3rd out of 43 people.
jp
Not only that
That's really true
[music]
I really think that all the hard work behind the scenes has paid off.
how long does it take
It took quite a while. It took quite a while.
That's amazing, she's a hardworking woman after all.
I'm a captain, so I've grown a lot.
I'm serious if I don't show it to the public.
As expected, second place
Let's get ready, this is really Sui-chan
thank you
No way
Something
Me and Arata became virgins around the 4th match, right?
Is that really true?
It's not funny even if it gets all over the place.
However, even if I roll it up all the time, it still ends up being a mess.
Really
Moderately
Seriously, I lost.
I wonder if it's servant
I think we were able to deliver some hot drama to everyone.
I guess I like porridge.
Okaya
If Kasui-chan is like that, it's really entertainment, so I hope people will really enjoy it.
It's frustrating
that
over there
Mushroom on that Teresa
Did someone take the mushroom because you said it wasn't taken?
But what exactly is it?
With that luck as well
After all, you have to rely on your luck.
I thought Okayu-chan was really strong in the beginning because she covered it well.
Picked up last time
I think it came in 4th place.
I'm sure from there
I hope you clear up your insults.
I think he came
I'm thinking
Then I'll try harder next time
Good luck and become champion again
I want to get it back
yes
thank you
[music]
Thank you very much
last last
How
Last year
Award
Not true
Just barely
The rice porridge that rose to 74th place is now 2022.
I got off to a good start
This is Nekomata porridge.
congratulations
Thank you for being number 1
Apparently not
No, it's quite like this
During the performance, I was able to run as usual, and when I wondered why, before the performance,
Mess with Subaru-chan
We run together every day, every course.
That's what I was talking about, that's what I was talking about at this time.
As I was thinking about this, I was able to run as usual.
Only for me
I thought it wasn't a victory.
[laughter]
Insanely
I can say that I was able to win thanks to Subaru-chan.
yes
By the way, female
There was also Kimocino. The look in his eyes is hot.
I couldn't afford it
that's powder
That's so messed up
Looks similar
no
Maybe in production
Mone
When I said ``Ahan'', there was ``Sensitive''.
Maybe, but it's not like that anymore.
Because I didn't go that far
As expected, I couldn't see it for a while.
With Shin-chan
Look
Shin-chan too
I told you earlier
There was a time when we were tied for 1st place.
At that time
How was your mood?
surely
Apparently it was a tie.
There was definitely some tension.
It certainly may have been
I
Something
I practiced yesterday until about 4 o'clock.
I just noticed it a little bit
Because I knew you were practicing.
Sui-chan is much better
It's going to be painful now
I thought so
Eh, I'm kind of considerate.
It's nice that it fits
You could see that the champion was in a slump.
effort meeting
What is it?
That's what I've been told
Congratulations!
43 people
Junior high school 1
I agree
I'm really happy
Award
I received the image because it seems that they were able to use it.
I want to ride
I want to ride please
[music]
So amazing
It's elaborate
As expected
This one
Umm
cup
The teacher holding the banner remains.
yes
this year
It's amazing that it's exclusive.
It's serious
That's amazing
Wow that's amazing
There were really 3 people
And certainly
No, no, no
But really
I'm standing here for this kind of award.
Thanks to the management and others for planning it.
So thank you very much
please
As expected
Thank you very much
If I were to do it next year, I would like to ride it.
By all means, please
I'm looking forward to it, okay?
So that's it
At the end
Marie Hai Comet
1st place goes to hunched back and porridge.
Well then
Excuse me
thank you
Yes, that seems like it
Mentally strong after all
It's important, isn't it?
It's called rewinding
The power to never give up
important
You can win anything with your mentality.
It was seriously mental.
somehow
It's a wall that I want to overcome every year.
Well well well, but from now on
It's only my second time.
tournament
Well if it continues
My dad too
While hosting
Victory
There may be something like that.
It was Hardy
yes
Thank you for watching
Yes, Dad too, and that plan.
Thank you very much for your hard work
Thank you very much for that.
Thank you very much and
It seems that there is one announcement.
Announcement Mongolia Thank you for the announcement.
The mouth is here. Hololive
Free version of error horror game today
It looks like distribution will start.
It seems to be the position, but if it's true today, it will start at 8 p.m.
Download from official website
I'll see how it can be done, so here it is
Please check it out and have fun too
It won't get sticky
Thank you very much for your support, no competitions or anything.
fine
I really like any tournament, and I think it's really important to be able to get excited about something.
That inside the cat
At first, I couldn't really see him practicing.
I'm a little lonely
[music]
Are you okay
Better
I wonder if they are doing it?
I was a little worried about that, but everyone.
The chase and the chase were amazing.
Probably all like Marican
homework
perhaps
I'm the type of person who does summer vacation homework last.
I realized it again
I guess so
That's what I thought, but it's true
yes
terrible
To be honest, it was really difficult to prepare.
That's right
They gave me support through streaming like this.
With the staff
Only one more person left
would not have been recommended
To
Naga-chan also helped me.
Thank you very much
Listen to the story with follower Mone-chan
Various things smoothly
Thank you very much for your response today
I am filled with the feeling of being glad that everything went well.
that's right
And later
Please comment
translation
Thank you very much to everyone who did it at the same time.
Really
We all made it together, and Tona-san
Because you hosted it
It was a great tournament
I would definitely like to do it again
I want to do it again
Okay, I look forward to seeing you live in 2022.
Thank you very much.
yes
of course
We appreciate your cooperation in making this event even more exciting.
Thank you everyone
thank you
Bye bye bye, I look forward to working with you again this year.
[music]