[Music]
not listening
uh
[Music]
meow
oh game is too big
the size is weird what the hell that's
not 16 to nine is
everybody maybe i cut off the side
ah a little bit yeah
so this next
[Music]
yeah
okay
okay okay i'll cook okay
i'm small today because i'm weak
today is the last day of the rust
server thingy
well
before it gets reset let's play a little
jazz bossa nova before
things go
crazy i don't know if it will go crazy
though because apparently most people
are kind of like fighting
um far away
uh
actually let me
i think somewhere in in the in the west
like currently like
piccolo senpai i saw his stream a little
bit i saw i saw there's some alliances
currently with mikko senpai matsuri
senpai nuna senpai puruka senpai are
together and then gura roboku kanata
senpai and
they're all also all together though i
see them in the voice chat in in discord
um but those are all pretty strong i
like even
i don't think i could um really um help
out much but
uh
well well
um i have made some improvements for my
base to at least um protect myself a
little bit
uh in the past one to two hours i've
done some upgrades
i've tried my best but this is all i can
do
so i upgraded the walls there's
basically no wood left
but
it's a mix it's a hot mix of stone and
metal and some high quality metal too
as you can see
yeah yeah
that's something
all right there's some stuff here left
i'll do that too eventually
um
i was like
scrambling with my last few ingredients
and like ingredients materials to get
something going here
uh up here as well second floor i tried
not everything couldn't do everything
also this side doesn't really matter
like who's gonna shoot me from that side
yeah
and uh
[Music]
i heard a sound
i feel like i'm hearing sounds
this is this is the day to be paranoid
on it doesn't need more wood i've been
like i realized today that out of metal
ore you can make these things and then
the metal fragments i was always
wondering what to use them for besides
some some of the few items but aha there
you go the walls the walls can be
improved with the metal fragments and
you need a lot of them so i've been
trying to
um
where's the rest of my wood i've been
trying to
damn it
i'm trying to
to
get as many metal fragments as possible
welcome welcome i think i ran out of
wood
doshiel
oh well
oh well or 200 that's that's enough for
one piece of floor
let's go with uh this one ta-da
okay
now um i do have some weapons from
uh
like you know finding a few random
boxes
uh uh
like crates
i hear a deer i think
and also
i hope that's there also i uh uh i
opened
one of the hacking craters uh last
night or so i'm not sure when i did it
recently and there i found a little bit
more stuff but uh yeah i have a few
weapons um
uh but i don't want to take them all at
once you know i might die
um
so that's that sorry we're late now i
started early so that's that
now you think that's the only thing i
did huh no no no no no i tried
with you know my tech tree is still
not that far so i tried
with what i have to improve something
so now
uh
i tried creating a barricade
look at that
yeah behind are some of those spiky ones
too spiky boys a few ones i learned that
recipe just now
and um then i went
i went to the convenience store
just to recycle some last things for
some scraps and you you will not believe
what i found in one of the
boxes a [\h__\h] watchtower
a [\h__\h] watchtower
[Music]
oopsie
like perfect oops [\h__\h] exactly what i
need uh maybe i don't know will it help
us maybe it's out of wood can you like
improve this one too
no
can you can you add anything to this i
wonder like more more
wood
like a wall no
so we have to work with this but
it's it's it's something but there's not
much cover
ghetto actually the the placement is bad
too i guess because this is a big
opening
uh
i don't know how to turn it though um it
was really hard to place it i had to get
rid of my my planters
janky fort yeah
um
but
this took me a lot of materials
upgrading my house and upgrad like doing
this stuff this already took me like
everything watchtowers aren't known for
their sturdiness
but this is the best i can do okay this
is this is something there's something
although i have a feeling maybe people
won't even come here i don't know
there's quite a lot of houses here
um but
i heard people are fighting like
somewhere else maybe around here or
around here
um
i don't know if it's a smart decision to
go there people might just snipe me to
death
my effort is cute thank you question
mark
[Music]
i'm meeting up with alma i don't know
she has she made a huge tower
that
her goal is to snipe everyone she sees
so even if i'm friendly when i go there
she will
she might not even realize who i am and
then kill me or she will realize who i
am and then kill me
i don't know how to get down properly
wow
yeah um so
i i want you guys to recognize my
efforts here
[Laughter]
yeah but now i don't know what to do
um
we can go out to try to
oh [\h__\h] i hear shooting
but it's probably pretty far
if it sounds that distant probably
pretty far
oh
i i i already did some scrapping but
uh
because i really wanted to get the tech
tree a bit further
i think i can learn
your deer i know i left the door open
no open oh yeah
can i do something learn something
useful
maybe on this workbench
i have 30 scraps
give me something
something useful
long sword
yeah i can't afford that either
i can't afford [\h__\h]
a rough neighborhood no everything's
pretty peaceful here right now
um
i wish i could like leave all the
streams open to see what they're all up
to to keep myself safe to be warned if
you guys have the windows open and you
see someone coming i guess that's
stream sniping
so tell me when someone's coming
i'm not that's considered fair but
there's no rules today so if you want to
tell me about it and you're welcome to
tell me you know just just as a side
note you know
oh
i'll just unlock this whatever
ah ten scraps left
i kind of wanted to pick up these things
and bring them to the um recycling but i
don't know how to pick them up do you
guys know
is that possible
chad already handles that i thought so
i know i know they're online
[Music]
are you asking us to snitch
possibly
[Music]
shrek is coming you mean cali
towards me but she's uh she's for peace
right she's not gonna try to kill anyone
right i was asking for you like five
minutes ago oh
i mean do you need me
let's just make sure
kylie and i'm gonna chill yeah can we uh
no i'm gonna isn't gonna go out to hunt
anyone i think she's just chilling in
her sniping tower as far as i know
kelly is gambling
they're all coming for you don't make me
paranoid that's a lie no one's coming
for me
please please don't i sh you know now ah
i wish i could see
why i should go up on my watchtower meet
me
where
better to probably save that [\h__\h]
i don't even know where her thing is
but if she rides it casino
[Music]
why would i go there
no no she wants me to go to the casino
because she shoots everybody who's in
the casino
sounds like lies
yeah i know
i was watching you stream for two hours
and i know what
what you are
up to
i know exactly what her plan is
don't gamble with me
i don't have much to gamble though
um
the cali seems genuine
but i'm not sure because she said uh
like uh she
i asked her if she can protect me and
she said
[Music]
casino
was here right if we stop at the
supermarket scrap something
and we have a few more scraps to work
with i don't wait wait i have 24. i
don't want as many as possible because
uh
i want to
get some stuff in my tech tree so wait
can i pick this stuff up
[Music]
i don't want to give a clear
confirmation that i'm going because
maybe someone will come and get me
[Music]
equip hammer press e
oh okay
let's pick this up okay
[Music]
huh
it doesn't work
why not
[Music]
ah i picked up the chair why can't i not
pick up this one
i know i'll keep the fridge
empty oh there's something inside ah the
coal i guess
ah what
is there any way of using the coal
i wonder oh then we can recycle this one
too
oh can
we
no no i can't pick that one up okay
um
then i'll i'll bring the mixing table
too because i'm not using that anymore
or i've never actually used it
and this thing
can i
[Music]
no
ah cold cold cocoa
call himself of a gun powder oh
nah i can't even like make any ammo
anyway i don't have the recipes it's
okay i do have some ammo like from
other places uh what was i doing okay
oh yeah
so let me let me get that
let me let me get it i'm getting it
okay
um repair a bench maybe i'll leave that
for now but the table
[Music]
maybe this one too
ah maybe not
those you
yeah i don't think
i don't think i'll be researching
anything
to be honest um
but i'll leave it
and become a neutral commentary
commentator
juan magillius [\h__\h]
[Music]
tell tell kelly i'm coming in her chat i
just don't want to write it in this chat
because i don't want to be stalked
uh
it's okay to bring weapons right you
just shouldn't put them in your hot bar
i just just one for protection
just just one
just one
oh
okay
i'll put the wood here
and then i can i can go i'm scared to
leave my house alone
house will you protect yourself please
it doesn't like chat spoiling
but this is me spoiling not chad
spoiling
but okay whatever
just just
i just don't want to arrive when she
already left like like what happened to
me last time
okay okay
man you can hear people from so far away
it's freaky
[Music]
reyna is not protecting her base either
is she
selena gonna stream
[Music]
that may just be giving too many fake
spoilers
yeah so that was fake right that someone
said someone will be coming for me
that was most likely fake they're busy
elsewhere
[Music]
which is good gives us more time to
scrap some stuff
reyna's gonna stream minecraft soon
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah i don't know what
pekuda is doing right now but last time
i saw her she was like destroying
coyotes base
um with like missiles or whatever
no i don't don't know what they
no
don't know what exactly that was but
oh great
oh baby
oh so many crates
what do we have
what's this
igniter neighborhood
supplies the construction service
yeah one might call it that
yeah
it's just you know moving service moving
to the near server won't be helping you
building anything back up but uh you
know
i have a yes
oh i heard something explode
people are getting serious
by the
minute you like the jazz guys you like
jess
you're like jess like it was a serious
question though
you like the gems
i'm inside my oh god dammit
oh you told me to come to the
[Music]
chicken
she told me to come
to the casino
don't run chicken
did you come to kill me
is she is she like um
being
fascinated by the super
um strong base that i've built
that i've put together it's like
damn girl oh
oh i want to learn how to build that i
wonder how many scraps that would take
me
cctv
she'll meet you at kelly okay okay
so
um
no no i'll keep that
[Music]
turn on hope we got a lot of stuff from
this
she jumped over the fence
well i had to leave some openings for
myself
thank you
thank you thank you thank you all for
the red super chat
oh
yeah yeah i'm on my way i just need some
scraps to to you know bet on [\h__\h]
igniter
this and that and this
and that
and this
and this i'll keep hopefully
um until i'm back
to learn the
recipe for it
i'm
trying nice many scraps
scrap the camera camera um
i'm hoping to learn it but okay
um we might get up to oh
200 scraps
yes how much does this one give the
mixing table
it doesn't give any scraps
okay
it was worth it yeah
these ones are they they must be better
than mine no
oh interesting
okay
next stop
casino
[Music]
um okay
scared i'm scared
i hope no one's like close by the casino
literally waiting for people to go there
[Music]
i thought she was gonna shoot me
i'm gonna pick me up
okay okay you're not gonna do anything
weird in my basement no no no no no no
hey i wanna go to the casino wait wait
you didn't you didn't pick me up i just
get it
i mean what about the carnival i thought
you got oh come on oh wait i can't get
in
oh
oh maybe
okay sounds hot i'll give you my key but
give it back okay
[Music]
got it wait i gotta get back on the road
actually wait
when i play card derby later i got
scared because i saw you
you look you look interesting today
everybody's gonna be interested maybe
oh i look interesting you look
interesting yeah
uh
mikko senpai's armor
oh nice
looks cute
what are you doing what you been up to
yeah i you saw my face right
sorry i thought i i upgraded it
mommy mommy mommy i'll be faster
oh this arm what i mean this arm i have
nothing
yeah i i i tried my best to upgrade my
base
but it's not as good as yours
can i
wait can i leave that was the casino
what oh that's your base
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah ah this is my
base all right you can go thank you
uh don't shoot me when i walk to the
casino i know your plans
oh wait you key you're a car key your
car key
okay
huh yeah i'm parking
[Music]
there you go
see you later gonna make big cash money
nice taxi service friendly didn't even
have to pay for that
very nice
you know they even saw the pickaxe as a
fret better put it away
yeah
i'm coming back
she's gonna give me something
i'm coming i may i'm here where's the
entrance
don't shoot me
i know you have a
a trap somewhere here i want to step on
it
[Music]
no i don't have any traps i didn't have
the time to set out of the thing get
here oh the phone's not you can call me
if there's an emergency oh
it's so sweet i don't know how to use it
but we'll figure it out nice
she gave me a phone
oh
she'll protect me when i need her oh
dude i'm gonna cry it's so sweet
i made i made a friend
[Music]
i don't
do you need scrap i mean i'll always
take scraps you're going to need more
than that for this
okay
here let me give you
here you can have some more i got a
present from fubuki so you can have half
of what you gave me
just keep my weightings
[Music]
is
[Applause]
very aggressive today
towards the casino
yeah
i'm i'm betting on one then cause you
said so
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
how do you know
so many people
[Music]
i know it god told me
[Laughter]
[Applause]
come back come back go back go back come
back i can give you scrap okay
we're just having fun here yeah come
here
damn nice nice here from fubuki senpai
she gave me like so i can give you your
name
[Music]
let's go
what's next
[Music]
oh my god
nice
tunes that's just beautiful
thanks
yeah i'd like to shove this horn
directly onto your wolf snout
[Music]
oh
give me one
[Music]
we already made a lot of scraps
thanks to valley
whatever yeah you're
welcome yeah do whatever you want
they're from fubuki senpai to share the
world
[Music]
uh
nice
[Music]
gamble on the last day game for scramble
shut the [\h__\h] up out there shut your ass
shut the [\h__\h] up
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah give me this
yeah thanks to gambling and drinking
together
even if you have some iced tea and water
food and pineapple are getting lit
though
[Music]
crazy girls
damn three please this is what gambling
does to you
yeah assert your dominance on that wheel
try hitting it
yes
[Music]
yeah
it's the dancing
i believe
yeah my god if i hear another goddamn
shot out of all of you i swear to god
[Music]
um
everybody's turn five
[Applause]
[Music]
it's scary it gives me anxiety
your audio is way lagging yeah i know
you know the european thing europa no
oh so imagine that
bro no way that's insane
oh my god hey we would hello you get a
call yeah i got a call hello
hi
hello are you shooting at the casino can
you stop please
oh no
no it wasn't okay but someone's shooting
at us please kill that person peaceful
time here
yeah kill him
thanks thanks girl you're the best
[Music]
thank you
um i'll be i'll be right back guys uh
you keep on gambling
[Music]
scary though it's so dark
is she gonna pick me up though because
it's kind of scary
they're so funny
but it's so funny and this is in the
combination of cali is very interesting
right now
where do i go
and maybe i shouldn't go in the middle
of the night
how do i
i might call her back did i just call la
taxi
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i i
i don't know how to use the phone
properly
what the heck
it's kind of scary outside can you like
pick me up or like pick up the rope from
some entrance of the
[Music]
okay casino
okay
oh
wait where which direction
[Music]
is she in like l9 i think that was
approx
oh wait that's polka mental clinic
what
i wonder how my house is doing by the
way
p7 p7
what that's here no no i don't mean i'm
dope in our house i mean her her tower
that's where she wants me to go right
because she said she won't shoot me so
that's like saying
wait i must see it i should be able to
see it
maybe
[Music]
e10
oh shut up
[\h__\h]
i think you're funny
okay at least it's getting brighter now
how does she know i have a rope by the
way with me
how did she know
[Music]
she didn't know and oh god no
if i attack the
boar they will attack me because it's a
safe zone i think i'm
wrong direction probably
this is not how i entered either
she just needs a ladder
this is like a maze
oh wait i know i know where i came from
[Music]
okay okay that's it that's it you see a
big tower in the distance that's on the
tower
albert tower yeah fukushima is so kind
but i don't know maybe she's really far
in her tech tree i really need those
scraps i should oh hi hello hi
and here you can have
all of it i actually had uh some rope of
me how did you know
oh thank you i'm going to casino now
okay
[Music]
oh no no problem then no problem that's
a cheap cost
i just want us all to have fun together
this is the real peace party right here
what what
oh this kind of
ten yeah
[Music]
strawberry
we only have a few hours left on this
server
hi ohio
oh
[Music]
easy
foreign
let me check
is this not blackjack what is this
broken i don't know what it is
[Music]
yeah yeah
i want the blackjack how much how many
people do we need for blackjack oh wait
a blackjack is up there
i don't know how to worry i wonder
here's the question is this really black
okay i can teach you if you want
more players with four
let's see how to play
more players needed add more strap to
your tablespoon
[Music]
how
not all caps hold on i'll just invite
people we're trying to
play cards here do we need six people
one
let
[Music]
how do you dance
uh with bean b
oh
i don't see a dance action
the cat got smaller
the wheel keeps spinning
i'm sure if you are
what
[Music]
um
she's been drafted that's like her
problem i'm having fun gambling
gambling
[Music]
number one
okay but now number one now no it's one
yeah no number one yes
i shall try to protect you too if she
does dead
i can try thanks appreciate that
don't you have some cards to count
sheriff
actually
roaster roaster too busy getting rich
yeah hell yeah
oh
[Music]
yes you're welcome to use it
[Laughter]
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
get down get down
a close one
enough
we're kicking ass today guys
[Music]
[Laughter]
let me know
[Applause]
or will do
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
this is the cursed instrument
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah well that's that's sick callie
you got the two thought machines
yeah it's awesome isn't it cool
[Music]
let's go
let's go let's go let's go
[Laughter]
i made it myself
oh it's gorgeous it's so amazing
come on
[Applause]
[Music]
wake up it's gambling time
oh no
[Music]
yeah sounds good
is
[Music]
oh
of like the terrible war happening and
then it cuts to them
[Music]
i think this is important bonding
also i need the scraps i need them
urgently
[Music]
do you need some more i can give you
some
only if you don't need that i'm just
still trying to build my tech tree
yeah yeah sure i'm like obviously i can
throw you a couple of these
a few tech trees
i'm almost done with workbench one but
that's it oh
no keep some for workbench too right
next to our recycling plant
oh yeah i'll do that next season here
you go
here you go
thanks
so sweet
i just want you to keep gambling with us
yes i just i immediately got them back
anyway
nice
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
traps my original plan was to like leave
bear traps around and then play an
instrument and lure people to come and
die but i think i'd rather gamble
[Laughter]
yeah
especially girom oh sorry mostly gura i
wanted to lure today do
[Music]
ah
wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice
oh how could this game be so silly but
also so brutal oh
yeah
yes
big brain hey oh my god
she's just drinking tea
yeah
[Music]
foreign
i'm not drinking as much alcohol because
i don't want to get fat
so only special nights
[Music]
this is a special night kung kai
ba
i did five i think except for the
apocalypse
[Music]
please
let's
[Music]
horn oh i won't lose it
sorry
yeah
[Music]
you drink a lot of beer that happens
unstoppable
unstoppable gamble foxy senpai for
example
oh
[Music]
get out of here
leave
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
get out
get out the person who shot probably
doesn't even know that you're talking to
them
yeah
i
was
talking
to
ass
pools
outside the casino
oh
censored aka
east palace
yeah this is a peace palace
yeah it is a peace palace right i'm
gonna make my own someday but for now
this is perfect hey can you make your
own gamble please
um
[Music]
i'm only talking [\h__\h] about them because
they can't hurt us in here
[Music]
energy
peace palace big peace palace
[Music]
come on give me something else
uh yeah it's pretty rare for anything
besides one and three
these instruments are awesome
maybe next time at the end of a season
we can build a stage and make a big
oh concert i like that idea let's start
a band kiara hell yeah
look at the band i'll play the trumpet i
didn't know it was so easy to play an
instrument
finally i learned
like a stage of the peace
palace we'll make a stage at the peace
palace
are there is there like a piano too
there's a piano
ah cause no one ever chooses ten except
me sometimes but not this time let's see
yeah mo
not this time you know you can split
your winnings yeah i didn't know but
when i did that last time everybody told
me that's a stupid idea
didn't really win much yeah it isn't the
smartest
it's better to bet it all in one yeah i
think
[Music]
i'll leave at night
okay
i didn't mean to send you a friend uh
team invite anymore i mean that
i would i don't know how to accept it
but i would um
[Music]
it's okay you don't have to i don't know
how that's it it's not good
oh oh oh no no no no no stop it stop it
stupid
i still have way more dynamics
really
sugoi yeah well fubuki senpai gave me a
thousand but then i gave away
707 of it so technically
holy macaroni
so generous
[Music]
gambling means peace in this game
gambling is the only piece
is
[Music]
that's why she didn't pick up
there is a table back here with four
seats oh but uh anything besides
blackjack
i don't really know anything besides
blackjack in terms of cards i don't know
it's tough blackjack needs a dealer so
like
both of them need a dealer i don't know
what game is here god damn it
let's see
[Music]
oh i i think i should i should not
gamble anymore i think i have to stop
myself
[Music]
okay all right chiara
senpai and i will just gamble here
or
[Music]
don't lose your horn okay i will company
i'll keep it safe
until the server resets
maybe winning baby winning
yeah
okay
that was fun
that was fun oh i should be quiet though
with my horn
and so we're gonna go back and learn
some tech tree stuff and hope that my
house still stands
i wish
they're like who's she talking to i'm
talking to my chat
oh fubuki senpai's so cute and cali's so
generous they're both so generous what
the hell
where's my home again oh that's dead
i'm in a
this way
she's so funny so funny i want to collab
with her i haven't collabed with her
since sweat total talk
yeah
has it really been that long
also this it's been way too peaceful so
far
where's the action
do i want some action
let's see if there's people around my
area
um
now i want to use my scraps
[Music]
i'm good outside
i i you know they're all like so heavily
armed i have the feeling that like
it would be
foolish to even
think i can pull off anything if i could
[Music]
whose house was that again
one of them
[Music]
could challenge
that one she's not there right now is
she
[Music]
team up with ame oh i i wouldn't mind
but she's not really
planning on going on
a rampage or anything as far as i know
here we are let's see everything still
looks very peaceful here
[Music]
better put
my gun in my hand
yeah if she's done with her sandwich
i'll call her
oh maybe if we would send by kelly and
me and emma can do the car derby
we ain't got nothing better to do
besides gambling anyway
it's too peaceful what the hell
yeah i wanted to do the car there
because i you know i i helped i'm a
builder and then
only callie and nama used it so
i want i want it to be used
shortcut
thirsty
[Music]
okay it's porn
corner girl
oh sh
did she take the workbench or did she
only use it oh it's still there okay
good let's see
800 scraps
okay one more would have been nice but
let's see let's see what can we do
which way should i go um probably this
way hewing is important huh
unlock unlock
unlock very good very good that's that's
very important and then i guess for like
ammo we go this way
but i'm not gonna make it until there
huh
ah
hey i unlocked one oh two two different
kinds of ammo
nice
should i go back gambling
[Music]
that was
a good progress hallelujah that amount
of scraps normally i would
i would never be able to
make
oh yeah
why not
yeah
nice
[Music]
um
propose to derby okay i'll kill game
shall do
uh
gee
and we'll go back again
at least you know i didn't lose the
scraps they were invested nicely safely
how do you turn on the light again of
the of a gun was it r
or f
okay for flashlight there you go
gambling wasn't my favorite not really
we just got all of it from cali and
bubuki senpai
but yeah let's just say that was totally
me
are all the cars still there yeah that's
also something i wonder
what
i think they're probably fine
probably daijubu
you know i prepared some battle music
and stuff and some
some nervous
music
in case we get in those kind of
situations but so far
callie drove one out of the ring
uh where is it now
[Music]
oopsie i was by accident
there's probably no one there anyway
it was actually not an accident
no one there right
[Music]
can't go into the casino what do you
mean
of course i can
if i want to go into a casino i'll walk
into the casino
oh crait
scraps
oh
hi external one i shall add that to my
barricade
not that it will
do much
probably
[Music]
no one's shooting me right someone
shooting me
maybe that
gives away where i am
[Music]
okay i'm back
i'm back
hello
where is the campbell place don't fall
into the water
it's so dark
i can't see [\h__\h]
follow the voices
follow the voices and i don't hear
[Music]
hello
hello i think it's there
oh
everyone left
no
where did they go what are they doing
now
huh
that's okay we we we got um you know
we had some company before where did
they go maybe i should just
[Music]
how do i ask them
use my phone i don't know if i don't
have their number right
these are just random numbers and then i
have miku senpai and what
[Music]
there's like uh
uh some numbers written down
in our discord but fubuki doesn't have
one apparently
check ah there's more pages
does she have a phone though
oh wait nothing else
oh it's a matter of employee
and that's that's
pretty much it
yeah
[Music]
i saw one night
i asked them if they want to play and
i'm his place with the cars
but i don't do you guys know where the
where the
on the map what where it is because i
don't remember i think it was
somewhere up here
i think
derby i don't know i'll just say derby
in japanese but it might be um
is that new
wait i never joined the team before what
does that do does she hear me now
[Music]
oh
oh she
always there from before
now i see her on the map
oh
[Music]
i wanna play
card derby
i still from the invite from earlier
nice well now now i can
talk to her directly
uh where are my scraps here
[Music]
what was it now free oh
come on
kyle says derby yeah yeah yeah somebody
on twitter told me i
wrote it
incorrectly so i
i'm aware now it's d-e-r-b-y
[Music]
ah
did football simply not see my message
i'll go with you
yay
means need
one
more person
assuming ame will
drive too
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
since she built it i think we should use
it
ah
oh yeah oh yeah she's asking it publicly
okay okay
derby doco derby dunka also i was
shocked i woke up today um
and i saw amma streamed
in total including the rust stream four
times in the past
what five no ten hours
she had the the one stream about the 90s
text that i was watching and then she
had two other ones and then she was
doing rust and i was like what
is she ever gonna sleep
why did she just
um oopsie
i fourteen
let's go
oh that's team okay
i will go there now
we don't need to
do any more
gambling
okay
sorry i'm mixing up all the keys right
now ah
[Music]
did you say 13
where's routine what
i was down here yeah yeah close to cali
i remember i remember
oh no wait not this way
i wish i had a taxi that could pick me
up
should i ask i mean where she is
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
i need around
gotta wait
[Music]
i'll ask the important question amedoko
wait can you pick me up
where are you
uh gambling please
do you have a car
okay
i got a ride but wait she's probably
gonna come from the other side right
oh should we show where the where her
tower is
shortcut guys
[Music]
explosion but i don't care
this this phone is really useful we need
to learn how to build one for next
season
and let's wait here until my uber picks
me up
yay
[Music]
just need to find one more person who
wants to play
um they're busy fighting huh but [\h__\h]
senpai probably isn't
fighting
how do i get your attention
let's see
maybe anya
seems like she
has
although that was like 40 minutes ago
[Music]
[\h__\h]
that sounded so close
maybe i shouldn't stand up
there he's coming
i am we are going to start her stream uh
now
oh [\h__\h]
oh sh who is that
who's that who is that spooky
yes
no
no no no no no oh
[Music]
she says
she says that um
she can't because she has a meeting with
her manager now
yeah
[Music]
yo
we'll find someone else
but she gave me a
pumpkin head she looks like wait i feel
like
wait the way she looked right now
that reminds me of
like some uh spooky halloween dance
video with like
with some some dude dancing completely
dressed in black i think
and some yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you know what i mean
[Laughter]
was that person wearing a
a pumpkin head hey where's my uber yo
[Music]
spooky scary skeletons
oh
is it on purpose is the cosplay of that
mission accomplished
i'm just having difficulties
that's a boar we're close by
[Music]
ellie's like uh
still down there
died twice
how could you die to a boy it's a
[\h__\h] bore
just kidding i died to a board before
too i think
definitely died from a wolf before i
want to get that stone
if i bring out my pickaxe they're gonna
shoot me
ooh
snacks
and chocolate
what are we streaming tomorrow by the
way i forgot
why are we streaming what are we doing
oh hello
who is this
ah
oh anya
[Music]
yeah it was other yes hello hello anya
do you want to join the demolition derby
hello what you doing
the what the malaysian derby is like we
have four cars at amma's place and
everybody gets into a car and then we're
like like bunk each other with the cars
there's someone naked coming said that
oh got it
[Music]
sexy
so sexy
[Music]
sounds like she's
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay we'll do it just three people it's
fine
do you know me
am i coming here now let them call let
me call
[Music]
should i go there directly or are you
you're not coming
[Music]
okay
i offered to anya and porque senpai to
come but
i don't think they are in for it
it's fine
bales will join us surely
i hear a chainsaw
oh you keep on hurting yourself there
you have do you have any health
[Music]
uh any what
don't worry about it all done
i only have corn
oh [\h__\h] my base is too good
[Music]
it's too good to let yourself in huh
it looks very strong
[Music]
yeah healing items i don't have any
healing items with me show me my story
yeah i can use the car
what
you're easy ow ow what the [\h__\h]
it sounds like someone's licking
me
because it sounded like slurp shrub
i mean you know
you know
[Music]
how else am i supposed to say that
i think you're looking good yeah yeah
okay
okay i need the key again to get in i
guess
[Music]
let me get it first um
that's your way of backing up huh
where's the key where's the key where's
the key where's the key stand behind the
car oh don't stand
where's the key
oh there you go
uh
we're gonna run out of fuel soon hold on
let me mark it on the map really quick
how's the radio you like this music
oh yeah i like it it's really nice
from cali
um really fast i know uh trumpet not
trumpet what is this
speedrun rta
how fast can you learn an instrument oh
that's a tuba tuba yeah
some deep doo doots
looks really cool yeah
sick
v tuba
i left something on the ground i gotta
pick it up uh okay
it takes one minute
by the way our fourth ow
wow
our fourth person could be um uh bales
fourth person oh for the derby yeah
i wonder what she's up to she i think
she's just starting to stream rest right
now
so it's a good timing to get her reeled
into the derby
[Music]
how do i know do you have any metal
scrap or not scrap do you have any uh
metal fragments uh wait uh perhaps
yeah i don't need them anymore
[Music]
anytime how do i get how do i
oh i'm so confused okay
metal scraps a metal metal whatever
where did it go
you see it did you get it
wood
got it i'm not
[Music]
confused
wanna join
[Music]
kelly
for
demolition baby
know
callie's wondering high quality metal
and
i don't have all that with me but
actually surprisingly i do have 12 high
quality metal with me
i do
you're lucky
okay i can give it all back when we stop
nah don't worry okay we're ready don't
need it
that's true
they woke up immediately dead oh dear
did she spawn in the ward zone
[Music]
dangerous
this sound dangerous
same happened to cali oh spawned on the
beach oh
well
it do be like that in the middle of a
war
yeah
although i think they wouldn't shoot
like uh
people that are naked or something
you think so
some of those uh japanese members are a
little bit too
crazy right now like
senpai
she's uh
hungry for
violence
oh
going backwards
nice
whoa
oh she's just trying to get wood
it probably based on their attack right
now
ah piccolo's base too strong can't bring
that one down
oh we have arrived kind of
[Music]
i just got to get down this hill
careful
oh
it's like skiing
oh whoa
whoa
bounce
bounce out
sorry
okay we're here
kelly are you here
okay
kelly doco
kelly died yeah that's it
what is music
oh
and look at those cars yeah
well that one's a little bit longer than
the other ones
oh
[Music]
okay i'm gonna go grab my body okay get
your body
oh funky music oh my god a dance floor
what is that dlc
oh it's like fever night
baby
underneath the dance floor
i don't need no drinks tonight give me
weight
[Music]
you can actually record it you can
record it and play it no no no no no
it's fine i'm i'm the recorder i'm i'm
the music
i'm bouncing
i put my life today on the on the dance
floor it looks so realistic so immersive
[Music]
oh
look at her she's dancing
wow
oh yeah dance dance collab with amen
sick can you can you do this though what
is this no that's just standing can you
do this again like right here
yeah i'm right there
on my stream i'm right there
i forgot my song
favorite night toku
what's with what's with kalin
no
she's she lost her instruments
thanks for century turret nearby
doko why did she die
[Music]
let me just
get back into position
wow
[\h__\h]
i made myself too big
[Music]
where am i
where
where did i go
age 14.
you're going to ramen i'm here you want
to come yeah wait one second one second
um
oh [\h__\h] you saw that
i thought i hid it
i didn't see it
okay
[Music]
yeah i gave it back to you
before there it is
[Music]
safe
steph cali
have to step kelly
embody her instruments
oh yeah i can't actually can you uh
[Music]
oh okay
i'll just switch over again there
oh
[Music]
guys i'll just switch aside again
nice why are we bringing two cars
[Music]
so what where what where did she say it
was just gonna follow me
[Music]
ah
not enough space true that
oops
[Music]
got my sunglasses home
okay
look at my driving skills can't be
demolition derby has already started i i
i'm stuck
straight just go straight just go
straight
where'd she go
oh where'd she go
what did she say
what number did you say
[Music]
oh what'd you say
age 14
age 14.
oh where is that
here
oh
am i am i safe if there's turret here
am i gonna be safe
[Music]
oh i'm gonna i'm just gonna be there i'm
just gonna be safe
[\h__\h]
i'm lost
immediately lost who's whose house was
this
[\h__\h] i'm breaking the car
um i'll just i'll just drive back um
emma has a seat in her car that will fit
cali
[Music]
don't forget
maybe maybe they're already back anyway
uh
and the car was like this when i
got into it remember that
okay
yeah yeah the car was like this all
right oh god i remember
stop stop stop
moving moving
it's perfect parking skills
[Music]
hello
i got lost so i drove back because i
don't know
where you're going
oh wait what's
which coordinates again
oh
did imma go somewhere else
whoosh okay we go to h14 again
if the car doesn't break down till then
age 14 right oh wait
yeah it's 14.
oh
okay okay
and now we go
in here
[Music]
where
is that her body no that's a stone
it was like uh this was age 14 right
stop stop stop moving am i here no wait
i'm pretty far
i was reading the map wrong
[Music]
almost there
i'm better driving through the woods
than i am driving for a road apparently
wait wait wait wait wait
it's like um
i'm like on a
some kind of bouncy castle
okay somewhere here no
age 14 even though she says edge 14
that's like a big area wait is it this
one
yeah
i found it
i'm gonna just grab some sad six to
seven okay
i found it but i don't know if i can
pick up everything
hold up hold on
my car has a storage so you can bring it
over here oh yeah
[Music]
okay
i found that quickly after all
uh fuel storage
there you go
uh
one of those was callie's
oh
a watchtower this is callie's
[Music]
but kelly told me to lose it says if you
lose this body you will be cursed for
the next month
but she told me to loot it
this is probably hers this is her
i don't hear you
is this hers
[Music]
oh some of the car
okay
[Music]
we're cursed yeah cursed until what next
year
well
i do it for the cali
do it for her
the meme
is this place where am i right now
[Music]
an outpost oh
oh this is uh the area where i think i
spawned
and i walked through here and i got
really paranoid i remember
good old memories oh yeah
[Music]
okay
uh
what that i can't
pick up
cali stuff oh i can't open the thingy
but i'll just keep what i have now
in my inventory
that's cute
[Music]
that's cute a water pistol
does it even do damage
there's no water inside
baby pistol
i'm are you still streaming
okay
yeah
are you not tired
not really i have like the super power
whenever i scream
uh
sometimes like i don't i just don't feel
tired
damn
uh you drive the other car i'll drive
this car
going back to the derby
go down the road
okay
oh i don't know how to turn on the
lights probably uh
yep
yes
[Music]
hope she doesn't notice the damage on
the car
it wasn't wasn't me
it was a bear it jumped in front of the
car
wait
are we going there oh yeah oh it's so so
close
[Music]
thank you
can we thank you thank you can we can we
i appreciate you guys no problem got
this
you guys got a lot of stuff yeah how do
you have so much in your inventory if
you loot this body you will be cursed
yeah i do i do have a couple things you
told me
but now i'm encouraged
no no that wasn't for you
i promise
it's different you were actually helping
me you were helping me okay so you're
good you're good thank you though
gunpowder no it only counts if you kill
me like if it's a guru or something okay
good good
now i'll keep these in here what are
those footsteps i'm gonna take this cap
though cute
oh yeah i found a horse by the way his
name is pinto i brought him over what
where
where is he yes
he's uh right where all the cars should
be oh
we can use him as a car too for the car
derby
do you mind
yeah yeah
i want to be nice to him though if it
hurts the horse maybe not
he's pretty
okay he shall beat us he'll be the
commentator he'll look at us
crashing each other's cars
yeah
that's right good pinto pinto yeah this
place is
i know right
what people need to see
yeah what
hey check this out oh yeah one water
pistol
why can't i shoot you with it
because we're on the same team
oh
but now it's just not working
yeah just broken
oh well let me see maybe i can put some
water
this is really i-14 to come hang out
reload smell like let's see
here we go yay
is that water in your
gun yeah it's water
yeah that's just water are you sure it's
not milk because this piece this is how
peace should be
why would it be milk what the heck
because it's why
on my screen
[Music]
okay hold on hold on let me upload it
okay okay hold on i got you
are you stuck i'm gonna get you oh whoa
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
apparently there's a big war happening
against piccolo oh
nice i have a gun
i have a gun too i've got some bear
traps i was gonna set him around myself
oh yeah i have a pistol oh
i have some boxes here if you want to
drop not anymore
okay
[Music]
okay you can take a car uh just back it
up
[Music]
it was just a regular pistol oh the
pistol itself yeah yeah ah i got the
bullets sorry i got the bullets from you
i think oh 69 bullets
of nice
[Music]
it was like that
oh
wait i think these are these from you
too the
100 pieces of high quality metal
yes those are mine okay
maybe that's yours too yeah
i'll just go make another one
is this yours
let's see
bit bandana mask nope that's not mine oh
okay i wouldn't i haven't held any of
those
i'm gonna go grab something
right here you just have to back it up
okay sure um
question uh what's the chords what are
the chords for the big war that's
happening is it where they live
you're in peccara
oh yeah sure
one sec and let me get out of here um
you know this car is super nice and
whatnot i think i'm gonna take pinto
i think i'm gonna take pimp toe yeah
just cuz you know i'm a cowboy riding
on in with a pistol can i ride with you
almost i don't want to break another car
all right here's your key
there's your gear right there and i'm
gonna go grab some weapons and uh what's
what are the cords can you remind me one
more time
uh i don't know actually chad where's
the award you know
yeah
yeah revolver it's here
oh yeah we're both there the revolver
yeah it's on the floor by all this stuff
oh thank you hold on a second how do we
invite ahmed to the team
oh you can just click on her uh if you
hover over her it says like invite to
team and it's got like a plus sign
i think that's how it should be but the
horse is stuck
in the room
oh maybe
maybe
the leader can do it maybe let me do it
oh yeah i'm the leader so let me invite
you you have a gun
i have one with five shots
all right i sent you an invite
oh here's my spell it's a
shotgun yes
you said this oh here's the way i drop
some more bullets for it and then i have
some of cali's elbow yeah i i put the 69
ammo into the box into the
into the box in here
so it's in the box gotcha
and then let's see i got a roadside kill
water jug is this the pistol yeah i got
more guns at home so if i die i'm just
gonna pick them up there
oh there it is i see it thank you
thank you guys
can i get into your car
all right i'll see you guys soon yeah
okay
we'll type the coordinates you can chat
when you're ready all right cool that's
fine you guys are on my team so i'll
just follow you okay
apparently close to horse
uh
uh well what is peculiar's house they're
actually apparently at piccolo's house
but i don't even know where that is
you know
okay
i like your sign by the way the watson
derby sign is cute
thank you
it's gonna follow on her horse or
yeah
that's dangerous but
she wants to use the horse
rabbit season
yeah
it needs it needs like 20 people to take
pickled down so
is it really eaten or did you get
trolled you uh what
are you sure
oh [\h__\h] that was me sorry
[Laughter]
oh yeah
i'm sorry i tapped i tapped and then
i thought someone shot us
i'm sorry
can you repair it
it was an accident
[Music]
i still have some car parts in my home
did she leave
[\h__\h] i'm sorry
i'm sorry
i tried to repair it
hey but at least i already donated a lot
of like metal fragments and [\h__\h] to
ahmed to repair her stuff and do stuff
yeah yeah
i said it's not broken anymore
i fixed it with my mental stability
anyway
finally it's time for my music for my
nervous music
oh
okay i'll
be back okay
oh it's gone
e10
e10 is
see obviously it's not eaten
what even almond omega trolls didn't she
it's not eaten
unless it's like here
be gym a bit low
but now
or now
oh it is oh yeah let's see it was kind
of in the water true i guess
[Music]
damn
everybody against like what i said bye
stop falling for it well i can't
actually it seems like it's true
she does pick what i know
she definitely doesn't know right
a joke
yeah she's just gonna like shoot
everybody from her
eh
basin raider tooth
howdy oh howdy
i'm here
hey howdy i'm here i absolutely broke
your head i'm in my car
oh dang it yeah how'd you do that i
accidentally shot the car while i was
sitting inside
oh that's okay it happens to the best of
us yeah it's fine you got a gun
yes
i have a license voice
she's telling you because she
accidentally shot
yeah
i won't shoot anymore
okay we're on the move again
all right let's go let's ride
don't
hold on
i left the horn on you okay
that's from
[Music]
road trip
oh yeah to be honest
i'm sorry i'm in your way now excuse me
i don't know you don't want to hurt me
we're [\h__\h]
i had to name him pinto
didn't know they had names already
oh we're back
i hear explosions in the background
or is that in my bgm yeah we're going
toward them
oh god
i'm
[Music]
scared scared
i'm scared you go you go first i take
cover behind you
you can put your stuff if you have stuff
you don't want to lose you can put it in
here okay
it's locked
by the way i'm gonna put spikes around
the cars you guys so if anything run
around the car to the back
and it's a safe area okay and i'm
putting spikes around it
i can't put don't forget
i'll wait until you guys leave before i
put it okay
oh yeah it's locked in there you're
gonna go in and fire no
oh go ahead
come in
do a few shots
okay
yeah take a few shots
all right i'm going right in front of
the cars
is that the house
is that her house
turn on the flashlight uh
okay
there's like no cover here who's that
stuff over there
where does that belong to
ally will pick what up
let me see what's going on on discord
oh she's
oh she's not she's all alone isn't she
there's like there's a lot of groups in
in discord together
no one's of her
she's almost like she's not even in this
good
i didn't bring my binoculars i think
yeah
i don't think she would even let me in
oh she's all alone she's still she's the
last boss final boss
i think she wants to do this alone
she
she wants to impress by being the last
buzz
i'm going to shoot a few shots i'm not
going to survive anyway
it's fine
i don't know who i'm going against
though
final boss of rest
the game needed a final boss anyway
it had none
i should um
you know what i can build myself uh
i just need some wood
what is this dropping wood
is it
i feel like i'm not getting any wood
from this
maybe even the pickaxe
you know i need an axe actually but no
axe actually
[\h__\h] doesn't work
i don't think i can build an axe now
can i use the hammer
no
okay i i have you know my blueprint and
[\h__\h] here so i was gonna
put some where where are the others
oh they're coming
they're coming
i think maybe they can build me a
barricade
tactical sense of a goldfish excuse me
it sounds like a firework
girls can you build
me one barricade oh they're already here
oh [\h__\h] was that team um
[Music]
but i can't farm trees you guys need
wood
yeah let's see i got a high quality
metal i got high quality metal
metal fragments some bars
um that's about it to be honest
oh
yeah
bear trap if we wait here first if we
bait people to come over here bear trap
will kill him instantly
oh yeah you can just break down the tree
but it wasn't giving me any resources
when i was breaking it down because i
don't have an axe
if you have a rock it should still work
i don't even have a rock
sorry
beetle
there's a wolf over there some some wood
galley
i don't have any wood on me right now
actually sadly no okay
i thought i did yeah
traps
you go use that thank you put it on like
a hill or something though so we have to
yeah
nice idea
maybe one of these higher ones up
here oh
be careful i made three barricades but
maybe ama wants to
place them
where did you go
right here wherever you place or
wherever we place the barricades i'll
put bear traps in front of them
[Music]
oh there she is over here over here okay
over here by this tree locating the base
oh
who was that
um like uh
wait i'll give you the barricades
because maybe you know how to place them
there's one there's more coming
another one okay
and
what's happening
oh okay get that can drop it did you
drop it already yeah okay i'll pick it
up wait does so
all right over here over here
this is scary
okay okay
maybe
one more
it's just leather
now in this little this patch of grass
right here i'm putting a bear trap guys
don't run into it
okay
it sounds so close
but my my shotgun won't even reach that
far will it i don't know anything about
guns
i just have to go in
[Music]
a beautiful calming music
oh i see someone running there
oh yeah
no
[Laughter]
oh yo they're all walking oh
oh
my god that is insane what is going on
down there
i want to try oh geez but it will take
me ages to come back if i die i'm
curious
yeah we'll definitely die if we go down
there but
find quads we can make a bed true
go grab some actually come back okay you
live closer i live life i'm gonna come
back million miles away
i do
no friendly fire please
who's this is that someone's face to
shoot at piccolo
who's that
you guys see it
oh they disappeared in the water
holy [\h__\h]
becca must be having a lot of fun today
i'm trying to make the screen bigger
yeah i don't have materials for bed but
[Music]
that sounded close
wait that should be smaller too huh
all right
now you guys can see the action a little
bit better
bae is flanking pekko's fortress oh was
that bae
she has a lot of traps and anti-missiles
and we just have to die on them often
enough to um
you know make them not usable anymore
who's this
who is swimming
they're all going in there naked
run run run run oh there's someone there
too run run
oh okay that person is probably
dead oh there's someone there right
there
oh two people there
oh
we're getting a good view here i wish i
had my binoculars sorry guys if i die
and then
spawn in my home i could bring them but
what was that did someone just
yoni
it's burning though
it's burning
nicole is in no position to snipe you
and she's probably busy with all the
people who are like in the water
also i'm not afraid i can't even reach
her from here
i'm the reporter yeah coulda just got hs
biased pick what is that
hs hypersniped or
and of course and there's a person going
in there's a person going in
and then french or full
why is the door just open like that
are we back are we back are we back i
think we're back
are we back
sorry obs is being a little [\h__\h] today
i want to go in
who's that
what is that
we're back sorry
sorry
run run run
is this
i wish i could see your names from here
oh oh
oh emma's coming
[Music]
here kiara you want to use this sleeping
bag yes
this one here just
just make sure you name it okay
use that
um
there you go
okay now i can go
what if i die once i won't have any
weapons left
do i stand up with my pumpkin head
prop probably
it's better it's a little bit better
i'll be in selfie store it's not
record i have a friend i'm a new
soggy should we really try maybe
convincing her i'm her friend
[Music]
oh
so
uh
ah
[Laughter]
coming up
oh i heard something beeping i was
wondering what that was
[\h__\h] i chose the wrong bag
i think oh but i'm close by
where am i
no wait am i
am i there
where am i
can i respawn in my other bag holy [\h__\h]
i took down santa and and
now should i choose the rubber band just
the wrong one again
is my house still good here
oh everything's chill here i wish i
could take something with me
um
it doesn't work like that
i just wanted to kill somebody
wait hold it
there you go
do it
why can't i not do it
is that like a time timer
did she even say my name maybe she
didn't see my name because i didn't see
her name
oh i'mma died
[Laughter]
i want to do that again that's fun
she's she sucks
oh chad told her
mama
i wanted to protect you
she was wondering why i was there
oh sweet i wanted to have a nice job you
know
i tells her anyway that's true ah see
okay that has a cool down but i wanna uh
revive uh what where is it
wait it doesn't give me the option
where is the is huh
eat ten
eight ten it's not there
did it not work
i didn't i named it i thought that was
enough i reclaimed it ah
oh [\h__\h] well
then
what
let me let me
wait how do i there you go
ah [\h__\h]
i can't use the other one okay then
in that case i'll bring my other guns
no why am i here
because i can't use
my it doesn't like
i'm pressing keys
bedtimer a [\h__\h] hell
oh yeah i can take it in his horse she
probably doesn't mind
there's a lot of japanese comments
telling me that tekora is angry
uh
[Laughter]
try to protect her you know
i mean me me killing um
isn't that a sign that i'm helping her
i'm on her side
yeah yeah yeah yeah
before andori two packs without sent by
only
let me wake up what the [\h__\h] is it
broken
there you go
where the [\h__\h] am i
no there okay that's at least closer
though
we'll we'll walk in we'll see if we can
find some weapons
uh
this way oh dear
at least that's closer to
the base
if i just walk around the ocean for a
while
two minutes still white and brilliant
so cease fire
well there's no such thing as cease i
haven't heard of that
no we don't do ceasefire here no no
extension extension
the yeah the wipe still takes some time
why won't we cease fire it's fun right
now because it was kind of late man
is all the same with gouda so they're
all rivals
like she i guess she assumes we're all
all together no no no no no i'm a no
sake
in my heart you know
you know i can't i can't do anything
about it labu piccolo forever
i shot my oc my father was someone else
awali
oh versus pepper no
peculiar doesn't even need my help
probably but
damn
11 p.m
what time is it down japan isn't it 11
p.m now
your neighbor
they're arguing
aqua is calling for us he's helping for
ceasefire
because they said 11 p.m oh and then and
then porka is like no no no
this is a rain
she's saying ah let's stop it
all these lives it's a waste to kill
them all let's let's look at uh
fireworks together
and then pick what i was like who's
saying all these lives are being wasted
i don't want to hear that from you
see i'm a translator again
you killed golda so many times
and they're having fun
watano at least i got two kills yo and a
big kill who else was able to take
piccolo down besides me huh huh
in the end you know
love is war
and my love for pekura
killed her
isn't that romantic
it's beautiful
oh ah have i arrived i should probably
turn off mine
i'll kill her with a stone
no i'll protect her with a stone
your there's too many people now there
though
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
it's probably dangerous to walk around
here
[Music]
is
holy [\h__\h]
oh my god
is
[Music]
what's going on
what is that
whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
oh
where the [\h__\h] is your food
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'll give it back to here
[Music]
oh
she will show it now
huh
oh [\h__\h]
wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
open up the door to the tc
what
this scary place
i said i'm sorry for killing you
oh
nice
why do i not hear people anymore are
they not talking
am i dead in reality
well they're breaking the wall for the
tc
i hear people outside
whoa
ah they're they're in this corn
huh
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
foreign
i'm continuing the parties
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
desperation
oh she had some car parts
[Music]
[Laughter]
barbecue for all food only
[Music]
tabletop
hey
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
yay
foreign
[Music]
hey
foreign
[Music]
okay
picture time
[Music]
foreign
is
[Applause]
a little bit of these
[Music]
oh
it
[Music]
foreign
oh
here's food
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
foreign
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
is
[Music]
foreign
i don't know how
[Music]
you guys hear me does anybody hear me
yeah we hear you oh and with my chest
[Music]
[Applause]
emma welcome back
[Music]
cute
on an empty picture
[Music]
later
foreign
[Music]
again
foreign
[Music]
and they should have used the derby oh
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
iris answered one
[Music]
a lot of people are talking
i should probably just chop the house
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
scrubs
that looks like fun
[Music]
oh my god
[Applause]
[Music]
nice
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
okay i'm leaving the voice chat because
they're also they're saying uh whoever
oh [\h__\h]
whoever wants to
whoever wants the gamble should go in a
different voice set
and portugal took
four thousand scraps from piccolo's home
apparently but lost them again
but
yeah
tell them about the derby i tried but
i'm just gone now too right so
[Music]
it's sad
oh callie went to the wheel
doing gambling again
i huh really know
this house very well so hmm
where could the
good more scrap what is inside here oh
can i take this
it's the end of the season piccolo
doesn't need her tech tree right
i mean it's not even that much actually
it's not even that much
if you think about it
oh wait who's that is that i'm it
right my boyfriend is up i'm inside you
i'm i'm in
oh my mommy has the keys right
i'm in i'm i'm in
is this
this is what this is mikko jeez i can't
take this
maybe i can give them
back
[Music]
a
foreign
[Music]
i told her my tech tree is too far
behind and that we can maybe do half
because she stole it anyway
she said no no keep it keep it what a
chad
i was just checking if it's her own you
know but no she took it anyway
now i just gotta go back home safely
and then i can do all the stuff in my
in my ah nicer
yay
oh my
god
somewhere
thank you pornography 40 minutes left oh
god um wait
i get home quick um get rid of that
because otherwise someone will attack me
maybe
um
yeah yeah yeah okay just get get home
safely get home safely with the 4 000
scraps
don't let anyone
kill me
there's still scraps in there it's okay
4000 is holy [\h__\h] that's that's more
than i could ever ask for
let's go
going home
bears exist oh [\h__\h] i'll kill them with
my
with my
uh instruments
but yeah you actually ride [\h__\h] wait for
you is it 30 minutes really
i think in favor that's possible i need
i do actually need a weapon to protect
myself though
yeah uh
i do have some ammo still
don't know what ammo exactly that is
beware bear yeah through that
where did i
put those weapons no mind if we find the
same body again we can
take a weapon from that body
you know i i wasn't sure like overall
about oh oh look at that
if uh looting is really fine now i
wasn't sure but like it's the end of the
[Music]
it's the end
anyway so whatever right what is this
this is a rifle rifle is fine right this
is rifle ammo yeah okay good now i'm
protected
uh
yeah but you know i i really didn't want
to look too much
would feel bad would feel like uh
anyway we gotta get home fast
b speed we're like
on the complete opposite of the map
um
but it should be possible there's a wolf
there
i saw you i dare you to attack me
[Music]
run away okay good good good good
i also have no more food left [\h__\h]
[Music]
keep running don't stop don't stop
make what you can't give nothing back
yeah but honestly though like uh
they seem to like especially japanese
members because they all played season
one too i assume
then
damn very far with the tech tree i just
started okay this is what my third
stream
is
oh can i use that horse
i was told horses spawned with a saddle
can i use
that would be lucky
oh
nice horse i wonder whose horse that
go was
oh no go horse
bring me lead me to victory
this arm i think wait no this is water
plant right
hey there's a crate here if anybody
wants
go horsey
good horse
apple
back to jazz bossa nova music by the way
because
no more action you know what
if if pequod is serious about wanting
teammates i might want to join her
but she's not shy not like she needs
anyone i mean up until the end she was
like her tc was still safe
her house
her fortress was still standing
[\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah i'll ask her
i mean i'm not really good but maybe
maybe my progress so far
um has been decent enough
yeah i guess they were trying to find
her tc
said they kept on asking where is utc
why are you hiding here to see you and
then turns out she
like
[Music]
i don't know you should
i don't see
did it kill it i almost died
[Music]
okay i didn't see it
it's so dark
[Music]
[\h__\h] bear
my corn
where's the horse
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
oh my shrimps we're back to mushrooms
guys just like on
day one
okay whatever i'm walking the rest am i
it's it's uh
for
25 minutes left where's the where's
where am i where is my
path
i'm wrong direction okay
[Music]
yes how do you know i got a new keyboard
cookie declarative
i'm using the keyboard that elena made
me which is like a really
fancy keyboard
oh ammo is playing rust again
according to my steam notification
[Music]
join gambling buddy no i'm going to use
it on my tech tree
and whatever is left with that i could
maybe go there maybe it depends on
oh
did i just hear a bear
i feel like i heard a bear
okay we're in a safe zone
[Music]
we could go through it once check what's
up but i don't really have
time i ain't got time for it i need to
go home we're getting closer
[\h__\h] that's water
obama is okay i hope so too i really
wanted to play the derby yo i was asking
for people to come
but they were too busy shooting down
ahmed's home
oh let me get back some instruments too
kelly
okay
[Music]
i'm recycling everything
instruments
[Music]
three three three three three three
swedish
[Music]
you guys heard me though right what the
[\h__\h] is going on i don't have my ps5
microphone connected
what did she see the instruments
whatever it doesn't matter
[Music]
no i turned it on i'm i'm muted now but
i i turned it on i pressed me
[Music]
weird
looking weird
okay
get home
oh
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
okay we can make it we can make it we
can make it
oh
we're almost there
[Music]
that's probably not the lyrics but
did my health actually go up a little
bit i think it was on six or so no
back on 25.
[Music]
i'm almost there
and
i think we will see that my
home
is still intact which means
[Music]
that my home was stronger than piccola's
home
have a gun ready why
someone there
oh
[Music]
we're
almost there oh
running from a bear
[Music]
it was better hidden it's not even
hidden i didn't attempt to hide it
[Music]
but yeah everything's
chill
out here
i don't see any damages
we made it guys
we made it out with over 4 000 scraps
guys
i would say a big success
[Music]
oh god
for a second my game lagged
[Music]
how to get inside my home
without being killed there you go i'm
starving
but i'm here oh
okay
[Music]
food is in the fridge
oh yum
oh look at all that food
oh that's the good stuff nice steak
after
a day of hard work not so much actually
i didn't do that much
in game
okay
now let's
look at
the tech tree
um
[Music]
and i also before that i already had
like what 800 or so thanks to fukushima
and kelly
ah where which way do we go should we go
down that way get some good weapons
homemade landmine
oh my god we can get so much stuff
and this is the level two tech tree this
is the workbench too
a flashbang
revolver
flamethrower
ammo
some mammal
smoke grenade rifle ammo okay okay
[Music]
research table first for level three
recipe huh
[Music]
what's that ooh mega polo site
rocket launcher oh
we can get to the rocket launcher
oh my god
[Music]
what's that thing next to the muzzle
boost i don't know what is the muzzle
boost
this one muscle brake do we need this
[Music]
no bullet puff blably blue don't
understand
[Music]
what else looks good to me
elevator
[Music]
should i go down this way maybe
still have three thousand
would it form what should i do the
thumbs up ah
okay
medium damage machine gun okay okay
all the car stuff um true
could be nice workbench one
can you make a level three workbench uh
can i
don't know how
um
work bench level three white finish
needs
oh
[Music]
but should i really use 1250 scraps on
that now
the game's ending
i mean yeah i can unlock some stuff but
no
i'd rather just unlock stuff here then
then
[Music]
i think it will be smarter
yeah
[Music]
is there anything important here that i
didn't get yet
like these things i don't know what
they're used for to be honest oh
telephone
oh we want a telephone right do we
oh we're getting it
shotgun trap
[Music]
flame turret spinning with spinning
wheel that's for the
the wheel the casino wheel
demolition derby
yeah i think you know
if it's like planned like announced
earlier and planned at a time where more
people have time because i'm originally
planned at a time where no japanese
members had time and then for today she
never like
wrote a new message in discord or so for
everyone to know that we're doing it
again
so
unfortunately
um
look at the bear trap
it is
flame turret
where is it
fire arrow why not kill this
and this one is that good actually i had
one
i have one here
somewhere
car stuff
yeah it would be nice to have some
carvings so i can build a car next time
oopsie
[Music]
flame turret and satchel
where do i start
is this for a car too
charge you better
[Music]
this is stuff oh
auto turret oh computer station what i
can become a streamer
batteries electricity storage oh
okay okay
unlock
uh
just unlock everything
[Music]
unlock
oh the camper i can go on the camping
trip
[Music]
okay i don't have so much left anymore
don't you
i can do this
i don't know if it's useful
for electricity i guess when if we ever
need it
[Music]
unlock all the weapons
or molotov cocktail fun flashbang
and this ammo pistol bullets
a rocket
and a torpedo
for the submarine i don't really need
that it's not so important is it
right what is this by the way prison
stuff locker
[Music]
oh
ooh
that stuff would be cool for
like building an impressive
home
i'll continue here though because
elevator sounds good too
smart alarm
send notifications to your phone when
powered on
tesla coil
laser detector
while i'm playing a gate which allows
power to flow while a player is in the
beam
not exactly sure what that does but
say now we got an elevator
to shoot helicopter what's the sam
what is that
this one
okay
500 scraps left running low now
[Music]
cloves don't look that impressive to me
surface to air missile
[Music]
sounds dangerous
i think piccolo was using this for
taking down the helicopter i think
what is this stuff rf pager transmitter
broadcaster
on the turret
sounds nice
that vision goggles
too bad helicopter distress yeah
should i go to the other turrets i don't
know if i can make it
oh actually it's so cheap
this one i already researched before
i can't afford it but okay 500
eventually i'll get there
just do this stuff
this
and this
[Music]
whatever this is a heartbeat breathing
community footsteps sensor ooh password
is equal to the number of humans taking
a 10
meter radius
extended mag
yes
ah
for the 42 scraps left
[Music]
strength i want this
i should have gotten that
[Music]
and learn about electricity next season
perhaps yeah i can take a look at it i
don't know if i can wrap my brain around
it though it's kind of like the
the red
red stone
stone of minecraft
[Music]
can i do something here
unlock don't need that stuff
fluid switch and pump
kind of lame these things here
lame
well i wouldn't even know how to build a
large wooden sign we want to learn that
don't win
[Music]
one last
a furnace
point is furnace finish this one oh yeah
no why not
[Music]
unless there's something more important
for twenty
there we go
oh
has there been something going on here
[Music]
bandits gamble reward yes what
we want i will gamble it all the way
huh
oh that's what does cali have some stuff
[Music]
does kelly have some stuff from gouda
oh wait that's pretty old already no one
typed since then i thought that was new
kelly as good as loot
nice
well
[Music]
what do we do there's eight minutes
seven minutes left really are they gonna
like
automatically
uh
wipe the server i'm gonna be kicked out
but it's over
gamble the final bits what final bits
there's two scraps
i didn't use my tower
admire my fortress yeah
i'm in not bad you know
for a first time house i didn't even
think i would
actually like
use this house
until the end
next time we can participate a bit more
in the war when i'm not weak as [\h__\h]
but
you don't even have to be strong or
anything
i mean so many people walked in there
naked trying to do something
i mean
in the end they weren't able to do
anything but
yeah well that was for me the first
season but for everybody the second
season of
rest
[Music]
and
um
i hope you guys enjoyed it
i
i don't know it was nice to
interact a little bit with people i
didn't do so many streams on it but
maybe we can
interact some more next time
yeah
[Music]
he's killing my oc
what
no no it wasn't on purpose
it wasn't now let's shoot my house
wow
easy
that house
thanks for the restrooms thank you guys
for
and watching them i know like for some
reason some of you guys are like
i don't like while i'm playing arrest
but when i don't play it people are
going to be like
i don't like her not playing rest
so
uh
just um let it happen
there's always going to be some people
who don't like certain kind of games
who do like certain kind of games
i'm just going to have a feast
so
you know not not everything
is like
made for you
[Music]
it do be like that
the world isn't
world isn't made to please
you with everything
unfortunately
cafe i love you
i love you
but you know me and my european time
zone i gotta take what i can get so
i
i wanna be involved too somehow a little
bit you know so let me
let me do my thing thank you
mm-hmm
yeah that's it
this is it
this beautiful picture can i look at it
how do you look at it
i don't know how to look at it is it
because i already like copy pasted it
onto the the wall
smokey lava
yeah it's monkey what i want today
i just enjoyed kiwa thank you
[Music]
ah here okay okay am i on this picture
or is that a moment where i was uh
somewhere else for a second i wonder
maybe maybe that's me drawing on the
on the heart sign
maybe i don't know what i looked like in
that moment
spacesuit
uh maybe maybe that
on the edge
ah sweet
rest season two
i wish i could take that to season three
kind of sad that there's no way of
keeping
some at least some important stuff it's
not like a photo gives you any advantage
over others
it would just be a memory
[Music]
i was the only astronaut that was oh
that oh that's an ass wait why aren't
there astronaut suits can you go to just
can you go to space and rest i doubt it
why does this exist to begin with
[Music]
why does this exist
is it like considered a hazmat
suit spacesuit built for harsh
conditions
radiation does this help
i see
wow wow
oh
is it is it gonna end
is it ending now it's come out there
[Music]
ah
can i shoot venus horse before it ends
i don't want the horse to be killed by
the wife that's kind of sad i wanted to
have an
some kind of afterlife
if it's still there
ah
it's sad that elena wasn't there
maybe next time
yeah i'll put him down like
fast you know quick and easy
if he's still there he probably might
not even be there oh no horse
course i didn't take it right
probably just ran out of food
yeah no food
emma house let's shoot the star
nice
i'm a house
i'm a lesbian
what's in shop
how do i buy something hello
oh
out of stock
stock up your shop
this is cute is that the wheel
it's cute maybe i can make a shop too
but do people even use other people's
shops
[Music]
i'm gonna build herself a nice place
i'll i'll try to build a nicer place too
next time because now i have more of an
idea of what
what is good
what is necessary scraps
a bed
an actual bed
instead of a sleeping bag nice
and the servers
server's still going
i don't know
no no
do i have to leave
is it can't they reset it if i'm still
in there
i'll buy something from you amen
[Music]
wow did i get it
was it added to my
pork that i already had
[Music]
oh a bear trap right there
why don't you put that right next to the
convenience store
[Music]
eat almond meat and cooked for me
basically
oh hello
[Music]
wait you're still alive
okay but it runs away
i'm out of ammo thank god that you
decide to run away instead
wait we have some some rifle ammo is
this a rifle
it is a
[Music]
a rifle bit of three more hours
oh
monty
three
three more hours
lucille can we get some more scraps
[Music]
time zones um
congrats on beating rust did i beat rust
i hear a helicopter oh but it's just one
of those
okay
well next time i might want to you know
try stuff like um
[Music]
like uh like i don't know what do they
call it the oil rake and stuff like that
could be fun
oh
what's going on
hello bear was that you did you lose did
you did you kill
it
someone must have been here recently
i ate scraps
[Music]
don't be scared
i got a gun
[\h__\h] almost killed me
how about
there any like bandages in here ever no
right it's just normal food gancho
i know
god damn it
[Music]
well we have 15 scraps
we can go
to
the campbell place
or or we just ended here i don't know
and read super chats
20. is anybody there i wonder
hey did i open that one already
maybe i can um
throw that in
oh someone left some stuff
oh
i can throw those in
this woman will give me some scraps
right
that's a thompson
ah
no scrubs
most crabs
the [\h__\h]
i don't need this stuff
[Music]
i'll keep
what for i don't know
dying
next stop casino
there's six people at the casino about
japanese people right
like sushi senpai and so on
[Music]
maybe cali too
yeah i do okay okay
i mean i mean not that i'm mine you know
but
last time i went there
nobody heard me
[Music]
okay
safe zone
oh i can tell folks
thank you
i got so many recipes thanks to her
generosity
hey yo what's up
what's up in this village
this is the right path
up
all in
no i lose
[Music]
oh horsey
let's go it's very kind of you thanks a
lot
where are you going
[Music]
oh huh
oh
that's a familiar voice oh it's just me
i see i see i see what's going on here
hello hello hi
nice i understand i understand
i can't live here what pork is such a
shiny skin
why is she dead
uh she's asleep she just logged off i
think oh i'll feel good she has like
super oily skin nice
[Music]
it does look kind of wet over there
i i understand everything
i just came here for some last second
last minute uh
gambling with uh 20
scraps you want some more i can give you
more i already got so many donations
i can't take anymore
there you go
no that's fun
she like she went crazy and started
throwing all her scraps everywhere it
was very scary
okay
[Music]
okay okay thank you so much
thank you so much i love you so
much holy [\h__\h]
oh hello
this is how you gamble guys
big reward gambling
[Music]
oh did she did she kill got out right
now what just happened because i i
walked in i just saw that and someone
else crouching there
and i was like i see i see she's um
waiting for callie right
waiting for kelly to come out to kill
her
i didn't say anything but maybe kelly
already knew that she was there
[Music]
yeah show up after someone else wins big
and they're in a good mood yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
you wanna fight
oh [\h__\h] oh sorry sir no no no no no no
[Music]
was that a safe place i was already out
of the safe zone
thank god i'm i'm good i'm good i'm good
number one strategy in gambling don't
play at all exactly
and apparently kelly said she got that
from cersei senpai right
so i got a lot of scraps from puberty
senpai from ponokaan senpai and cersei
senpai indirectly
no wait that wasn't political senpai's
scraps it was actually pickles crap so
swissy senpai and piccolo simply and
who book your senpai
[Music]
what are you doing
why do i keep on fighting
what's going on
be nice
[Music]
i was good at asking to get a scraps
back from cali maybe i have them now
[Music]
economic singularity
oh like subscribes eventually come to me
[Music]
wait what did i do with these crabs 1
000 scrubs
[Music]
maybe i can research the rifle i have in
my hand right now
maybe
[Music]
i don't think i have that one yet
gamble i'm not gonna gamble no
i already gambled
and i won
this is the gambling
[Music]
c4 oh
right because i still have to see four
guys
i still have it i think it's upstairs
[Music]
let's see is that like pretty
uh late
um
pretty downwards on the on the on the
tree
i can research it
[Music]
research the chainsaw too
oh yeah i might um not have that one yet
either
why did i put i had like a broken
chainsaw
put it here yeah
[Music]
how much is the chainsaw
too broken to research okay okay what do
i need to repair
you don't know i can't repair it because
i don't know the blueprint
oh [\h__\h]
monty
ah
[Music]
[\h__\h] there's no wood left anywhere
where are my lights i don't see the
lights
workbench two has it
oh really
i didn't see it
[Music]
wrestle
chainsaw
i have all the weapons here pretty much
um
large furnace
that is
600 total required ah
i have like 500 left
ah
getting any 39
but we can get close enough that it
won't be so tough to get it next time
we can get wait what do you mean ah wait
jotomata i left the money in here
[Music]
i mean
what i didn't know it could break
i don't see anything
i didn't know that could break
[Music]
er oh here i go now on
why did i get so shooken
[Music]
all right let's see um
this one
i want the strength from the glass
don't really want the garage door but
okay whatever
freezing so long
[Music]
i want the chainsaw
door is good
really
[Music]
whatever let's just do all of this
will i ever need it i don't know
i got the money
ah now i'm out of money
[Music]
25 left
so go back to the gambling place
uh
i want to but i um
anything
[Music]
uh
i lost my rifle huh the one with the
flashlight on it
i think i have night vision goggles
or no
i'm not did i lose them
[Music]
i can recycle some more guns though
so many guns
[Music]
i recycled them
oh [\h__\h] okay well i mean what else am i
supposed to do with it huh
it's the smartest thing to do
i wish i could throw this whole house
into a recycler
already don't even give uh
please don't give anything
okay
oh well
please don't give scraps
huh
i put the scraps in the box ah
good eye good eye
[Music]
yeah
no
25 scraps i need every scrap now
i don't i don't think i'll get any more
though
from
the generous people
which box was it
this one
i could do i get scraps from this
maybe
[Music]
doesn't hurt to try what i'm trying to
get more scraps out of people
everybody's so nice to me now it's not
like callie has her whole texturie done
yo she's so nice getting five thousand
yeah
i got like six thousand i think in total
man what
[Music]
loot some faces oh
i don't want to lose senpai's base but
she's not gonna use it anymore
you think maybe there's some scraps in
here let me see
[Music]
just like a little little garden in
there
[Music]
but where
is this how you break a window
is it doing damage
[Music]
window very strong
c4 the one c4 i have no wait that was
used for a blueprint i don't have the
there you go
stability isn't going down at all
[Music]
oh do i have ammo for any of these
i do
[Music]
i'm doing no damage what the [\h__\h]
my chainsaw is broken i can't repair it
plenty of sea for an explosive new pick
was his house go grab the phone
i guess so
and
i feel so bad about doing it but
nobody's playing anymore here
you're right if only i could get a horse
or a house because
it's very far away
[Music]
um
did i say a horse or a house i mean a
car or a horse
okay we'll walk for now maybe we'll find
a horse somewhere
horsey
i guess that is our mission now
destroying everything that's here
for some more scraps
as if i didn't already get enough
[Music]
can never get enough scraps
never enough
never enough scraps which way
what
or or a hot air balloon would be nice
too
[Music]
one of amaz
i could probably
ah but almost cars are here but if i
pick one up there
um somewhere here right
and then drive with that to piccolo's
place and then drive back to my place
and i will be
faster
in the end
than walking all the way back
great now whatever
don't need a crate
oh there won't be something so big in
there
the good stuff is at pekuda's house
you have keys no not all of her cars
needed keys right only
like the one that she was
using to drive over to piccolo's place
but
the other cars were unlocked
as far as i remember
[Music]
yeah it is a real loot crate
yeah i shouldn't stop for the loot
crates here
did you see did you guys see what she
had in her chest
did you guys see all that
[Music]
i hear
steps
[Music]
was it
my fourteen or thirteen
i'll probably see it
if i don't break the car that is
upper floor the most unlimited section
okay okay
i couldn't find my way
up
higher
man i need to
check the votes from gurus and that good
as a
piccolo's rust streams
oh
your helicopter
[Music]
that's fire fire
it's designed for crouch jumping that's
why everything's so small
okay okay
i'll try that
for bunnies because they jump so much
i want to see how she did all of that
in such a short amount of time but i
guess i i need to consider the fact that
she played season one too right
i haven't been up to date with fake
gorazian five
well i'm assuming
her house is a maze
just have to take everything down then
but it took a lot of
ammo to take down
those walls when behind where the tc was
behind
[Music]
a hobby what do you mean wait what oh oh
no when i was asking or not really
asking when i was talking about
needing
um a hobby on twitter last night i kind
of meant you know
something where i can go outside too
preferably
not something where i have to work out
really hard but i was thinking horse
riding because i did that once when i
was a tiny tiny baby wawa
and
yeah it was like you know horse camp
for
a week or so
a week or two and i did really well but
that's ages ago and i could never afford
to go horse riding again but no no i can
and it's kind of a little bit of a
workout i think
you use some muscles i think and
i think it's nice
[Music]
i wonder maybe someone stole cars i
wonder
oh i hope not
[Music]
you guys see cards
yeah but uh horse riding hmm
i wonder i look into it
but i just i just felt like i was
thinking about my routine
and i realized that it's like every day
it's always the same and
there you go i might be going crazy
because of it
ah wait those are some scraps from
previously when i left some stuff here i
think there were callies though
there you go
[Music]
ah it gives fuel
ah
wait is there any fuel
ah wait is that fuel can i use that
crude oil now that that's not what it
needs right
fuel
there's some field with 12 is really not
much i have like a [\h__\h] ton of fuel in
my vase but
oh wait there's 59 in there
wait what
isn't that the car i got in
did i do it wrong i don't have to go
backwards but how does this work
do i have to push a button here
how does this work
how do i get the car out
engine
oh
did you take the stuff out
maybe different one
oh wait that's a few uh
all right i'm confused
my helicopter closed
no not really
ah this is the only one that has
something left
okay let's put the
for [\h__\h] sake
wait i'm scared
let's put the fuel in here then
wait i have car parts
[Music]
i brought some to recycle them
for gore
okay
uh this one right
uh uh e
no
x yeah
okay i'm sorry
dude maybe that was not the right way
why is so fast why is this car so fast
well where can i get out of here
[Music]
[\h__\h]
well i'm playing demolition derby on my
own guys
so honor amen
[\h__\h]
for the back
wait
[Music]
i'll try to get over that ramp and
wait
here
[Music]
the car's fine the car is fine
okay
let's go
that's fine
yeah
[Music]
nice
nice and steady
am i going the right way
not really
uh
no way
and
nice turn
let's go
[Music]
oh
straight towards the goal
you guys getting dizzy yet
oh this is so much faster than
while i walking hallelujah that was a
smart idea
thanks evan for the car
whose house is this
isaac goodell's house
house i think you can call it a house oh
[\h__\h] no no no all those are traps are
is she home
oh god
[Music]
okay
okay okay okay okay
ruin the swamp yeah
oh
where am i
i'm like there okay okay
oh i kind of need to go to the idol
meeting everybody please leave
just
kidding
cool
yeah
huh where is it did it um decay nah
oh that's still a sleeping bag
[Music]
the barricades didn't do anything in the
end
we built some barricades but like for
what
gosh
i wonder if anybody else had the idea
that i had
i wonder
i don't think anybody is as desperate as
me to finish their tech tree
okay so here i couldn't jump so well
okay
but here the problem is that this bunks
so
[Music]
oh oh
oh nice
this is just that room okay and how do i
get any higher than this
how do i get
up there
[Music]
it was sure
it's free real estate baby
ah here
[Music]
isn't there something missing here
so is that gonna shoot me that thing
no but how do i get there
i feel like i need a ladder that would
be nice it doesn't have a ladder
like a ladder how can i take it
i take this ladder
uh don't i need a hammer for that
they broke it
[Music]
he broke it
anything useful here
[Music]
this is insane
[Laughter]
well let me let me read that
[Music]
no no not close though i want to reach
the chest
maybe i can craft with um didn't you
have wood in there
[Music]
[\h__\h] i'm so bad at climbing these things
there's rope why didn't i
build a
oh there you go
um
a ladder
rope that was rope
yeah
[Music]
infiltration is happening guys
i learned oh [\h__\h] i need a workbench
uh does the workbench need scraps
metal fragments
100 oh i can do this i have enough
scraps i guess 146 okay good metal
fragments metal fragments
[Music]
all righty
this is my base now
find a hatch the first hat she mean like
an opening
see i should have watched her streams
and i would have known at least roughly
how this place is built
but
i'm ashamed i didn't
[Music]
oh
okay let's let's put my
workbench here
and then we build
a ladder
[Music]
and a hammer i guess would be nice huh
hammer
[Music]
there you go
i can't be face now
my my my home now where was this again
oh yeah
no more cool stuff in there
are we done
yup
come on
where did my ladder grow there you go
okay
[Music]
so this ladder with that one i guess
we should place it there
oh can i not
why
i'm gonna put it anywhere here i could
put it here ah i can put it here
a bit higher please
cool
i see i understand
that uh has like a trap there
i should
i should touch a bed or something
are you
[Music]
a sleeping bag what i need for a
sleeping
i can make a normal bed with a soon kit
and cloth
cloth we do have what about a sleeping
bed though sleeping bag anyway we'll
make a bed i guess it's my my house now
[Music]
so a lot of traps left [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] well will the no saggies be mad at
me for doing this
and just trying to bring
pekudan's things to safety
why am i not just making a sleeping bag
oh well
okay so i placed the bed right
it's my bed
kiana bed
[Music]
okay so now if i die i can use this
right
[Music]
was there some
healing items in here i can't reach that
one
can i hey i'm stuck
what
[\h__\h] i'm stuck
i'm stuck
oh never mind
can i get in there
nice what's in here
rockets
[Music]
was this shotgun rounds
oh
cool stuff
i didn't see any healing items
the bodies on the bottom are left right
you're gone right what am i saying
the bodies are gone right all the all
the dead bodies they're cleaned up
nicely
hi
get up higher
when there's this trap there
[Music]
there you go
or is it somewhere else
[Music]
sorry sorry sorry sorry
[Laughter]
wait
oh
ah
there's no stuff here
no chests
[Music]
should i shoot the door
should i throw a rocket at the door
can i destroy it like that
[Music]
what so i can get through
destroy the
want it i don't even know what the
turret looks like but
[Music]
all right um
is a rocket a little bit overkill
[Music]
i feel like a rocket is overkill
how do i
what's the right weapon for that that's
a
grenade launcher that won't work with it
right here's some healing syringes
shotgun around
[Music]
nothing here looks like a rocket
launcher
[Music]
and no rocket launches here
chainsaw maybe chain no
it will shoot me
we'll just we'll just um
[Music]
the ones are there for the millimeters
right
search research with chainsaw don't have
enough
i think
it's okay
[Music]
what'd you say see
what did you say
40 40 millimeters
are these ones
those work with the grenade thingy with
this one holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
but shouldn't i be like at a safe
distance i feel like if i shoot when i'm
too close it will um kill me
[Music]
yes
okay
what is this by the way
um amount to branch this one doesn't
help me does it
it bounce two
what the what's the point i don't know i
feel like look i guess this is the same
door
i guess this doesn't really lead to
anything does it
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
it doesn't dad doesn't
where'd i go
you guys said there's more stuff here
where
what am i not seeing what am i missing
[Music]
i'm just back here again
go down
[Music]
maybe some
something here
because she did hide something like
behind the wall
so perhaps there's a secret entrance
this is where the tc was i think
[Music]
it's a lot of fun stories okay well
look at this sound
sounds so weak
who is this
[Music]
i don't know where to go why'd you shoot
at
[Music]
wait i just reloaded with oh yeah
i mean this one i'm gonna reload this
one
[Music]
the trap session was one of the most
unlimited part
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] does this do any damage
i hope we're sad if it wouldn't be doing
any damage
come on
[Music]
is it
no
[Laughter]
i don't even know if this is a good door
to choose but probably
not here
[Music]
this is
meaningless
will take forever
[Music]
rocket launcher
if i can
i have
[Music]
behind the face recycle everything
true
what but not everything gives scraps
better just load and recycle okay
where's the next supermarket
oh over there not so far
i can't ever get up here
okay just open from here um
well the guns don't give scraps right
does the ammo give scrams
stack of gears
ones
they give scraps
maybe just the coat lock no
don't need this don't need this
[Music]
the chainsaw
gears are a good source of gears
[Music]
sheesh
subscribes okay
i don't see him
[Music]
look
i'm crouched
i am crouched
[\h__\h] i'm too stupid for this
also it's getting dark i don't like it
let me out
[\h__\h] i'm stuck
i'm really stuck though i'm okay i'm
good
there you go
[Music]
these are so cute
how do you get them to be colored like
this is this a dlc
smoke grenade
maybe there's something behind here
do you see it
it's so cute
damn
guys tell me what should i bring
anything else here that could
be useful
this is so adorable oh my god
maybe this one
[Music]
i thought i could get more
maybe okay we'll bring this
[Music]
this one so i can use two right
the small grenades do these just make
smoke and no damage
the next richest person on the server
mikko senpai and seriously senpai i
would say
but
i don't see anything okay i'll
i'll go
is it really safe to try to leave this
space without seeing anything
no
it's not
[Music]
all their bases still have active
turrets oh yeah
where am i
[Music]
i need some light
where am i
[Music]
there we go
the gun
which one
oh this one has a flashlight yeah
what's in here
ah
rocket launcher but i don't have rockets
right
cowbell
what
[Music]
there are rockets
in the base
magic
so why don't we blow up with those
what should we blow up with that
should we go back to kiwa house and just
blow up all the houses that are in that
area
[Music]
my house we can do that too yeah
ah these are the rockets can i can you
only stack them in free
[Music]
is it loaded though
if i um
oh god
wait how do you load it
we only load one each
i'm assuming yeah
i'm not no loading is not left click i'm
not stupid
one shot at a time
okay i mean with the with the rocket we
might get a little bit deeper but
i'm not sure if there's really anything
left in here
[Music]
so
car should be somewhere up there let me
try to get up
[Music]
i already researched as much as i could
with like 6 000 scrubs yeah
here is the car
[Music]
there we go
where are we going
[Music]
could shoot a rocket at gooda's base is
she still playing
she's still streaming i guess that's the
real question she's always playing
not streaming
oh god
what is that
oh sleeping bag
oh
is there something in here
nope what is this oh
does that work with my rocket launcher
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
is that like suicide samples or mikko
senpai's base like
temporary base no it doesn't work
different type
ah
i'll take it anyway maybe i get some
scraps out of it
all right i don't i don't really want to
go that way
cuda's house will shoot me again
ow
was that it that was it right oh god i
don't
the place is not safe
around
i can't control myself
[Music]
okay
that was just some wood don't worry guys
[Music]
don't eat though
out
am i in the on low fuel [\h__\h] should have
taken some fuel from gooda's house uh
not go to
town's house
don't attack me boy that would be
foolish
what's your
foolish ambitions to rest willia
[Music]
oh oh no no ah
you're coyote i think coyote is also
pretty
[Music]
good in rust
i think she uh
might have some good stuff too
does she
what did you say hers is i got space at
normal space near your supermarket
i i saw piccolo was destroying her house
so maybe that's uh
what was she looting at
her entire world got destroyed by the
rabbit
[Music]
f5 had polka teams raid house not sure
f5
a rate house though would that have any
scraps
f5
that's so far
[Music]
my superhero house i don't know where
anybody's houses are
sucking it's hold
[Music]
well if you guys give me some cords then
i can check some stuff out
g7 iris uh-huh
she's um
she's still in discord
she's still streaming
she's still
we can get revenge is she still
playing you guys know
i will shoot down her house with a
rocket
explain cards okay
hmm
[Music]
oh no streaming i was only bail
streaming a lit how do you know she's
playing cards then
only fails streaming i guess
mob
what the [\h__\h] that's not really a treat
goddammit
is that a cliff
yeah
they do be snitching probably
oh god oh god
i love the turning mechanism um how did
you do that how did you put that into
this car
for demolition derby
holy [\h__\h] it feels like it's falling
apart
it drives like it's falling apart
oh dear
it's so wobbly
[Music]
oh
it's the right way yeah kind of
[Music]
i think we have
pretty much arrived
let's chill on this road
uh
and find
remember it's
uh at the crossing to the dome
the car is at the crossing to the dome
how long will the car hold out this
torture
hopefully a little bit longer until i
can make my way home
[Music]
here
oh
what was this once
[Music]
was this part of iris's house
is that her it's decaying this stuff is
decaying
[Music]
is this iris place
i don't remember
did it look like this
[Music]
it was rated
yeah well then she probably doesn't give
a [\h__\h]
if i go in there's probably nothing left
then
[Music]
interesting
eh that's pig with a secret face
wait then what's the other thing that
was decaying uh
from iris
no way
i don't remember anymore
no wasn't it more higher like an f
something
iris's stuff
yeah yeah yeah somebody told me the
wrong coordinates then
[Music]
i'm not getting so much stuff anymore
as i did before we're less effective
than before
no no no no
oh
oh it's an npc
oh that's the first time i see like an
aggressive npc in the game
we survived whose place is that
[Music]
that looks like some kind of vacation
home you well that looks uh looted
[Music]
wow never mind whose place is this
it what's what's that
what it could
grab that peel ah it could maybe need it
where was it
[Music]
real estate
no scraps or maybe upstairs
well if anyone rated this they wouldn't
leave the scraps would they
[Music]
i can't really see
oh what did they have so many horses
all right who is this can i walk in is
this safe
[Music]
oh
s
no scraps
cute clothes
and some dope weapons
nice
yeah i'll give you these and i'll take
these
those are more useful to me right now
[Music]
and if you already have some fuel
i'm gonna do with that much fuel
i got like 500 right now
[Music]
what
mace
[Music]
is that maybe a secret wall too oh look
at that
oh where was this one is that photo from
oh
all this memory is sweet
[Music]
my chat told me to take the fuel
what do i leave maybe this
no scraps left here
i like the trash tech trash
one brings 20 scraps really
[Music]
is there tech trash in here
no
yeah one bunch of fuel is enough
[Music]
you know these are all rated we should
just go to the houses that are not
raided which means we should go to waba
home although i know how
um
rich all the people in my area where
there's another house over there i'll
check that one out
[Music]
that that one looks like it's been
decaying or broken into as well though
yeah
who was that from
you guys know
oh wait we just looked at that already
didn't we oh yeah yeah
we didn't go very far with the car did
we
i see i see
okay okay
uh car
i didn't expect to be doing this
for so long
[Music]
but okay i'll take what i can get here
my car over there
[Music]
is it that thing that's burning is that
my car
wait no it's not burning thank god
or is it
sound like a little spark
[Music]
you good car
can i help you somehow
[Music]
well should be fine for a while longer
one more gold before we go somewhere
else
i can't drive
i'm drunk hi chunky monkey
you're here to distract me
junkers saying hello gives me the
feeling i need to
not go meow for that much longer
i'm gonna go left now
[Music]
hmm
is is that it
was that it
iris house
eh
[Music]
said
it was already like so falling apart
[Music]
it was her house and there's not much
left i'm sad
that's not realistic the rocket not
opening that up that's not realistic
[Music]
come on
you [\h__\h] kidding me
[Music]
unrealistic immersion broken
lock dancing
[Music]
what
i don't have that many rockets yo
[Music]
huh
all hp
[Music]
[\h__\h]
and
is that small
[Music]
stash i don't trust this place you know
i got shot here to death once
[Music]
i didn't bring c4 i only have one anyway
at home
yeah okay whatever she probably doesn't
have anything good left in here anyway
[Music]
oh shh
break the roof from the top okay
you have convinced me
but now with the rocket should i
do it with the wrong end
that's not the smartest thing
[Music]
wait who's that wait someone's on my
roof
someone's on my road
[Music]
scream yes let me hear your screams
it's my face now
[Music]
i will spare you for some scraps
oh how much
everything i need to finish my tech tree
everything yeah
well how much do you have
[Music]
don't lie to me iris
why would you gamble iris
i was playing poker and having fun
bluffing what is that really setting a
good example as someone who represents
hope huh
it's good to have hope in
open your card
well aren't you naked right now what did
gambling bring you
um
i mean callie gave me some scraps yeah
she's a nice nice woman
yeah she she shared some of her savings
with me so how much do you have now bae
and
nanya
um i
i lost a lot and i originally got 500
from cali you sound broke
that's half of it i only have
oh god
i only have 228 now uh
i see
well
you know i kind of feel sorry for you
sound you sound so broken
i only have 228.
um
well
there's some unfinished business i have
you know
[Music]
[Laughter]
are you are you
are you um
remember my
my hot air balloon business it's
unfinished
[Music]
ah i paid you back
um
you paid me a good amount that made me
quite happy but then you took it back
again
it kind of confused me
after you killed me another time
remember notice that i paid you
i didn't i didn't notice i i didn't
notice i paid you 600 that time i think
that was an appropriate amount though
[Music]
no no no no no you said 100 and it was a
mistake on my part i i feel bad about
that but that's why i decided to fix
that mistake you
see don't mess with me
don't mess with me
[Laughter]
[Music]
who is chopstick
is that bales
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
ah
oh [\h__\h] who's blowing up things there
oh god oh god no no no no no
sorry car
i don't want to talk too much when i'm
too close
she might hear me
oh seems like they came back home early
from gambling
[Music]
i only have guns i have like no normal
weapon
[Music]
oh wait
maybe there's ah at least some food
that's good
[Music]
nice
okay i'm gonna go home now
see what damage i can do at home i
didn't loot them yeah because i didn't
really want to it's okay
[Music]
see i
i'm nice
i'm nice i'm too nice
i left fuel yeah
why not i'm not gonna use the car i
still have fuel but
let's show what it
can reload there you go
[Music]
yeah just to kill was like satisfying
enough for me
i'm walking the wrong way
whose house is that's just a stone
just a big ass stone
[Music]
it moves the fuel is like
i really don't need it why do i keep on
walking the wrong way here and this way
this way
yeah i wasn't in it for this crap for
that one that one was simply
for reasons
[Music]
revenge
is sweet
[Music]
it was about sending a message
yeah how to pay miss
i thought she was gonna kill me
mama mia scary scary
sweat and she um
she crumbled she fell apart like i
usually do
aim doko
my aim wasn't good either
just keep on panicking don't know how to
use these weapons you know
but yeah how many kills did i get today
one two
three four
four or five kills
not bad bad
[Music]
some good kills iris spells zetta and
piccolo
[Music]
okay well i used to intimidate it was
super effective
i want iris to recognize i didn't take
those last couple of scraps that she had
[Music]
no one said she
yeah had left over from gambling her
hope away
there's a new reaper in town
[Applause]
what is this place
abandoned milk oh [\h__\h] is that dangerous
[Music]
i'll walk around here
never went there before
she lied about the amount yeah i figured
i knew she wouldn't be honest with me
[Music]
how much did she actually have
she said like half of 500 so 250.
is that the military base
[Music]
one of those footsteps
just an animal
i hope you are not the one shooting at
me nice shot still
nice shots stressed now
turned around immediately killed it
yeah i can't die now i mean it's not
like i carry that many
um scraps with me just 91.
let's
see
can't do much with that
[Music]
oh is that what you call it 360 no scope
oh
[Music]
is that what that is
no oh
what is
what is that did i do a 180 no scope
[Music]
that's also impressive
there's no scope mean that i didn't look
at like this thing
is that a scope this thing
ah
and now i understand that finally
[Music]
i have learned something new finally the
meaning of 360 no scope like so 360 no
slip is what you do like a
like a flip and then shoot
[Music]
and then still
uh
hit correctly
or full spin
you wanna do you wanna fight you wanna
fight huh
i'll give you a 180 no scope
[Music]
one-handed card where you let them build
people
it's not even following me it's scared
of my gaming skills
oh while shooting from the hip is also
necessary
damn
[Music]
reload i don't have
do we have ammo left i don't think so
i have these left
wait but
ah
that's what i have left
oh [\h__\h] what was that
[Music]
should have used gels on them the
grenades
[Music]
i'm starving
is there some
[\h__\h] it's also getting so dark because
i'm
not feeling so good oh sh wait i'm
actually
i'm actually falling apart right now
uh
[Music]
berries please
can't die here
oh thank god
that's not much but it stops me a little
bit from starving no
oh god where am i am i close i'm close
to the supermarket but
i don't know if i won't actually die on
the way
[\h__\h]
[Music]
i don't see any food
can i make it to the supermarket
[Music]
where's the phone
i could make it
maybe oh
oh god oh god
oh god
once no once i make it i probably die
right in front of the supermarket
no
oh wait i have one more berry
oh
i can survive
[Music]
i thought i already ate that but still
it's still
dangerous
oh come on come on it's right there it's
right there it's right there it's right
there
get some food from the supermarket
everything's turning dark
who's that
what is that
wait
maybe um
okay okay
oh my god
i see the light guys
i see you too now though
oh
oh salvation
that was a close one
oh no not that
chocolate
crunchy butter
[Music]
oh hallelujah
hallelujah
i'm feeling
much better now
an apple
get those vitamins
i wish you
got it
okay
so much better and i wanted to go
recycle anyway so this is great
[Music]
the last couple of scraps i can get
okay
oh i'd like to destroy that but with
what
chainsaw
oh yeah wait
ah
i have the fuel for the chainsaw
how do you use this thing again
do it come on
did i pick it up oh there you go
maybe i should have killed iris with a
chainsaw that would have
that would have felt lovely
wait why is
why is it so oh [\h__\h] oh that was an
accident
i thought i had to change so
why is my my sight so
bloody
[Music]
is it did i get myself as a chainsaw
um
don't need any of this now
[Music]
this
the gears the gears the gears get the
gears
a pig killed her who
iris
this the grenades
these ones no these ones no wait what
smoke i don't know i didn't bring any
but you mean like
any of these
are we done fighting
yo the gears bring a lot holy [\h__\h]
wow
that's pretty good i'm happy with that
come on come on that there
it's gonna take a while let me look
upstairs
the pipes the the broken pipes did they
uh give something
[Music]
anya demolishing her house
everyone is like
taking their things apart now
it's kind of emotional
isn't it
[Music]
researched a chainsaw
okay if if we get enough
uh to research chainsaw i shall do that
oh you're right the problem was that i
uh my
chainsaw was broken so i couldn't
research it but this one's not broken oh
so i can research this one
yeah
nice
a good amount of scraps look at that
guys
let's just throw everything in now
or should i
yeah whatever it's fine
i'm assuming the people around me are
not um rich enough that the effort is
worth it breaking into their house
at least 500 okay we got that
love me some chain sauce
[Music]
oh
maybe i can research that too
so much gunpowder well
[Music]
no no more scraps though this stuff
gives no scraps what the hell
research hand grenades okay
okay i'll just try to research these
things wait what where did those crabs
just come from from the pipes maybe
oh
yeah not bad
we could get to uh 700 scrap
700 scraps if not even more
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
hmm
oh
i am happy with that
let's go
one last time
tsukiwawa home
rifle body yeah
doesn't matter
rich joe
take items recycling wait what
[Music]
someone is rating iris well that was me
you mean someone else riding iris now
what is there left to read
don't
don't you dare
onion
go anya go
there's nothing left there though
literally i should rate like there's so
many unrated houses here yo
we could break into amma's place
in theory
[Music]
cookies rich funky already gave me so
much
[Music]
a new attempt
does this work
[\h__\h] that
maybe the door is better
wait open door
what
[Music]
no chance off of
unless
maybe she has a chance
let me in
[Music]
it's unbelievable
what is this stability
i
i can't
[Music]
what
i have i have some grenades but i want
to research them let me research them
first
[Music]
i didn't think it would break so fast
oh c4
the one and only c4 are we sure we want
to use that on noida senpai's house
i don't think she even played that much
rest
she
[Music]
did she have that much stuff
oh did i already research the grenades
[Music]
one item at a time oh yeah
already researched
true that
what this
already researched
oh
[Music]
oh this
cannot
oh this one you can find only
i [\h__\h] i want this one i want the
chainsaw
[Music]
the component used for crafting c4 and
rockets is that worth it guys so should
i use it on something else
[Music]
i
mean
seems worth it
[Music]
i can reach the chains on the tech tree
was it on workbench level two
yeah wasn't it relatively close
[Music]
wasn't it
no
was that the other one
[Music]
uh
wait i don't see it
chainsaw
slight binoculars shotgun drop center
it is level two
[Music]
in the middle
is this thing there it is
totally required 450.
okay i have to go this one this one this
one and then this one right not this one
this one this one this one this one
[Music]
okay
oh and we can get a lunch furnace that's
nice too ah
yay
now i can prepare my chainsaw
[Laughter]
now that i know how to make it easy
okay okay
[Music]
beautiful i still have a few more 224
hmm
[Music]
easy step for next season yeah we can
get so much wood so fast
what else do we want to get
[Music]
i'll just go down here
searchlight wow
okay
i think that's the last piece of um
uh scraps that i could use
that's it pretty much
and where's my seat i used it i used it
already [\h__\h]
i remembered
[Music]
i want to blow something on
blow something up
i used to see
foreign please and they have a lot of
items in the house you can take
supermarket and make more scraps rocco
where are they where is fujiki's house
where is it
it's probably like super far again and i
left the car
[Music]
can't no
shut up
i haven't read it's like on the other
side
i don't know
if i can break it open though cause like
ah
what should i use to break it open wait
can i make the c4
can i make this before no no can i
let me in let me in
emergency
[Music]
this
20 of them
so for uh
i have like a lot of like um
[Music]
untouched sulfur
this one right
i have to first like burn it
mamma mia
and eleven three oh okay that ain't
happening then
because that caused so many scraps
any other way i could
break it open
[Music]
no
i can't just use her password
it's satchel bump
[Music]
i could ask her though
if she's online
[Music]
senpai
i think she's probably sleeping
[Music]
might be decaying
yeah really let's take a look let's take
a look
i mean
we could assume that i made a c4 and
was able to break into her house that
way
[Music]
previously she said she had a meeting
but i mean she would be done by now but
i don't know how healthy senpai's sleep
schedule is
[Music]
tell me
if you see the house because i don't
know what it looks like
is it where the the lights are the shiny
tower
does she have traps though
is it that one
that thing up there oregano
um she won't play anymore today but i
still find it kind of like
i don't know is it
using the password it's like cheating
but she didn't use a very difficult
password i could just have tried to hack
it
honestly i probably would have been able
to do it if i didn't know it was one one
one one
what is this called
it's open wait is that her house
[Music]
it's just open
i did on this giggle
didn't she take all of her scraps to
give them away for gambling though
wouldn't that make a lot of sense
whoa
i'm just sideseeing just just
sightseeing
[Music]
nothing here i hear helicopter
coming soon helicopter
gonna check those
yeah probably
pickle house
that's a lie this is not pickles house
that could be good
it's right there i don't want to walk by
a window right now
next trash oh i didn't see tactics i
always take twice
okay
commissioned art gone wrong ah
this place is so nice it's so
spacious she has really high ceilings
i might want to do that too
oh
where is it
it's still in the area
i i can't see any scraps she must have
taken them all to go gambling
she gave away so many
oh
it's right there it's right
there you can probably hear me talk
behind me was another room oh wait that
oh
[Music]
he's just sleeping
how did i miss that well that one's
locked ooh i said for dancing by like
room that they live together
[Music]
with the body
no
[Music]
she only has free scraps anyway
[Laughter]
bye good night sleep well
have sweet dreams
break the chest
[Music]
that one
i feel so evil
[Music]
oh
broke again there was a chainsaw
somewhere
ah
lucky
why don't these break so fast
[Music]
huh
no scraps what is that
rock oh it looked like a burger
rocket launcher
um
jackhammer
ah the jackhammer
sick
does that need fuel too
[Music]
i still have rockets
it's it's fine it's fun
coming this way again holy [\h__\h] go away
not safe to go outside right now
should i take the rocket launcher and
what am i going to do with it
can i use these ones yeah
when am i going to launch it at
whose house am i going to launch it at
[Music]
the helicopter
that would take maybe a bit more
preparation don't you think
[Music]
oh shoot the helicopter how many how
many shots does it take to get it down
[Music]
this is so cute
it's adorable
[Music]
all right
too many don't bother
yeah yeah it's not worth it it's only
like
to prove that you're strong
and we don't need proof of that
i've got kfp
it might help to beat the mighty door
window if we actually make it into noise
empire's house and then there's nothing
really there
i'm gonna be so disappointed
we should i guess go to the supermarket
first
[Music]
i don't
she said she's like in her
um
in her sleeping
thingy
was that wrist um like something i could
recycle
properly
[Music]
a bed
she said of course you can enter pretty
much
yeah that's um
it's good good to know we we didn't do
anything bad
you're so cheap
[Music]
who is shooting at what
good night and um i would like to collab
again sometime
ah she was so cute today
she's so cute why is she such a cute
picture
[Music]
who cares
i'm the revolver and what is this a
laser detector maybe i can research that
should i research that is that worth it
[Music]
oh hello
uh you don't want to attack me believe
me believe me
but just in case you try it
you will probably try i don't want you
um
[Music]
this thing is so hard to use like
turning it on you have to like do this
several times
just give me the scraps don't care
good night pinkie piggy in a blanket
sleep well
uh okay gears
and this stuff
should i recycle this
it's realistic that is realistic yeah
i'm still here collecting scraps
unbelievable
[Music]
absolute scrap addicted
i researched it already okay good how do
you know
you have like a real overview
look at those scraps beautiful
mmm
mama mia
and we look up something spawned on the
roof
[Music]
one hour left yeah i don't think i'll
play until the end though
they didn't despawn because i didn't
loot it completely
goddammit
i should have loaded it completely oh
wow
now
[Music]
what is this thing door controller
and then what else did i pick up this
thing a revolver h-shot
revolver what do i get from that
now the jackhammer should be useful
though right to break into people's
homes
if that doesn't work well then i'll know
what to do
[Music]
i don't need any of this
chainsaw for rocks ah
i was wondering if there was like a
equivalent i see maybe i can research
that one then
[Music]
okay
okay let's go
going home
last time the second or the third
and then and then i think i'll really
end it
maybe thank you jay swagberg thank you
[Music]
who should we
have an alliance with next time guys i'm
not sure if peckwood i was really
serious about that so maybe we should
consider other options
[Music]
you see
no one's following me
a pig is following me
[Music]
is super good at rush though
go away
[Music]
oh
explosion
fail stop streaming huh
[Music]
am i the only ian left that's just
streaming rest right now
oh wait what am i doing
oh yeah
[Music]
i cannot create this item out of scrap
what do you mean
[Music]
but i could research a chainsaw what
about why not why not the jackhammer
anya
oh no are they coming for my home
only id remains
we're the last people standing yeah
noise
[Music]
high level tech tree for that one really
damn
damn i didn't think that was so
luxurious all right then
uh
what do we have left
stone gate oil refinery
which can make low-grade fuel from crude
oil
[Music]
i had the bed with callie and from
looking out that was nice that was fun
[Music]
important and that one is important for
cars
that one
[Music]
wind turbine
like when i was using those wasn't she
wait i can get i'm going to get that one
amount generator will vary depending on
wind speed higher
electricity
nice okay
i would say
that's it for real now
unless there's anything i can get for 20
[Music]
20 scraps here the rug perhaps
yeah
all red
danzo
[Music]
thank you very much
everybody
[Music]
i hope
that's fine
hope you enjoyed
the stream guys
underestimated the grenades
oops
that's okay that's okay
i've learned a lot in this season one of
rest
i am prepared mentally
for one more season but definitely not
season four
one more season and that's it i just
wanna
play
in the big league you know once
i want to do some damage in the next
finale
perhaps maybe maybe
so this was kind of just a preparation
arc
and we kind of started very late too for
this season so
and we were behind in many ways
but we'll do one more season and
then we'll graduate from rest
grass situation
what
[Music]
um
i was just a small bug in this season
that couldn't hurt anybody
[Music]
all right guys are you ready for some
super chatos
[Music]
cause i am
didn't even get to use all my battle
music you know i had i had this one
oh yeah
pretty cool right
battling the super chats
yeah should i keep this one on
the quest of the super chats
hell yeah
yeah intense super chats
will she finish them today will she
catch up with them today or will they
take
the crown once again and win over
takanashikiyada
will she finally be able to prove her
strength
and show him who's the boss
oh well the super chats
once again
have the upper hand bono
we cannot let that happen
and with that
we start reading the super chats from
the summer festival
[Music]
is it too loud by the way or is it fine
it's perfect okay
oh my god
what
[Music]
what is his name
papako
my dad
[Music]
oh this person went to the meet and
greet that's all popcorn oh
it was fun meeting great at some poke
and it was a precious experience thank
you for coming
yeah
i'm glad you made it in
hopefully you will stay okay for chicken
forever
yeah
miniature pinch of junk thank you for
two pink super chats
oh this is interesting the whole lines
are now shows like when someone super
chatted twice or three times or so per
stream
uh it shows it now under the name
interesting
miniature pinch of junk sent two pieces
of chats thank you a kiss for you
it was a great opportunity to see
attention bae on the stage with a lot of
people even though i couldn't get a
chance to do the meet and greet and
that's unfortunate
it was nice to be able to see to cheer
you on from the seat in front of the
stage ah right in the front nice did you
have to like
camp outside a little bit to do that or
like i guess inside like apparently the
halls were open but i mean were you
camping before
the opening
to get a good seat
because i think our panel was pretty
much in the beginning of the day
anyway
and there were not many seats so if you
were able to get a seat i feel like you
waited a long time i took off my glasses
yeah
wait why am i here i have a small office
i remember it was kind of a mess
i didn't clean
it
off
yeah perfect
[Music]
i haven't used this one in a while
small office
so small it couldn't get any smaller
than this guys
look how i don't know
okay so we're looking at these super
chats
i love it
okay so continuing i don't know what
makes sense you'll have nightmares but
if tantru falls asleep and dreams i hope
tantra has a happy dream all right wow
well good luck take care and take it
easy thank you
actually last night i again i i dreamt
of something when i was being chased
again
but it wasn't too bad
it wasn't so bad i think
it's okay froggy she's a bit dizzy she's
chilling now
this is i think it's fine
i'm fine
it's just nightmares just gotta keep on
telling yourself that those are just
dreams just dreams
just like you know
games are just games dreams are just
dreams
yeah but thank you for worrying about me
let's hope i can get to another korean
convention
in the near future
thank you so much for your support you
made it possible you and the many other
korean bros
you made it possible
[Music]
yesterday i was so happy to see you
there popcorn event was so fun and nice
and i had a great day thank you so much
tanjo
finally
wait there's some korean
oh
[Music]
thank you thank you
have this all over the world yeah
my beloved chimpkins thank you
i love you too
that wasn't the red super chat but i
still give you kisses because you guys
are so cute
thank you
hope you enjoyed popcorn
don't think you came to the meet and
greet right but maybe another time
ultimo mk 203 thank you for the pinky
i went to gamescom on saturday and i
have to say going to a convention is way
less exciting with them without the
anticipation of seeing your oshie there
so on the plus side on my way back i
took a stop at dusseldorf to enjoy some
delicious tonkatsu
[Applause]
[Music]
me
i'm sad i'm not jealous about gamescom
but i'm jealous about the tonkatsu
[Music]
i hope it was delicious
hope it was tasty hope it filled your
tummy nicely
donkey shouldn't foreign support
i will i will use this pink super chat
to eventually eat some tonkatsu again
i'll put it aside for a high quality
tonkatsu
thank you
thank you thank you
down bed for tonkatsu hell yeah i am not
tonkotsu tonkotsu is like a ramen type i
love that one too that's actually my
favorite ramen type tonkotsu ramen
tonkatsu
oh god stop it diet
unknown thanks for the rest of it
actually that looks like
no not quite a rainbow but like a
ransomware chat and a pinky
and an orange one thank you
my classes are starting this week so i
won't be able to stay up until 8 a.m
every day
what
unknown
oh you can't miss my streams you never
miss my streams
and watch all these streams from start
to finish anymore but i will still try
catching
as much live as possible and i watch all
the parts i missed on the boards
i'm sad that my streak of never missing
any of your streams won't reach two
years but i will still try my absolute
best to support you as much as possible
oh no
i'm sad
love you all isn't forever kiana i
wasn't gonna make this rainbow but i
changed my mind because kfb is too cute
and i love kiwawa too much
oh they're finishing your rainbow
oh
i mean you're not leaving right you just
can't watch the streams anymore that go
throughout the night
but you still watch the vods
i hope that the classes don't um
[Music]
don't take up too much of your time
you're sad you were there for so long
[Music]
don't forget to say hi every once in a
while okay
no you can't become walking eventually
not all of you
might be in the same situation no
no no
no
no don't leave me guys
no vodka for me let's go
i'll stick for you to the end thank you
love love love
i mean you know i get it you can't do
anything about it if you have to
like if you don't have time for it for
whatever reason work or school or
whatever there's not really much
you can do about it and you know what
the right thing to do is but
i mean i'm sad i don't want to see you
guys go
but thank you unknown for letting me
know
and it's not unknown haha
just don't forget kiwa i know you can't
forget anyway
and say hello
as often as you can
thank you so much for your support so
far
[Music]
i do miss minecraft not gonna lie i hope
you all have fun at the festival
yo
i thought you know minecraft every time
i came back to minecraft after a while
the controls and all that it came easy
to me it came back easy to me but this
time it was kind of weird because of
me being like used to the rest controls
messed everything up it was funny
but yeah
um
i think for a while we'll be um
replacing minecrafter frost but when i'm
done with that season i think there's a
high chance so we might go back to
minecraft again
every once in a while some minecrafting
i really hope mangrove makes a big
comeback i hope so too i i definitely
prefer it over rest
there's just so much more to do i mean
the maps are literally
like endless
there's
compared to the rust maps rust map
[\h__\h] tiny
man
yeah
at least yeah id members seem to still
play relatively actively
um
reverse reverse rainbow thank you
funds for horse betting
excuse to continue the reverse ring
thank you i did bet on horses and i won
one time
or two times i went two turns
one or two times
don't remember anymore but it went quite
well
i liked that idea that was
pretty exciting could actually reuse
that for another sports festival if they
wanted to make another one
you um ask someone for a tour yeah i was
thinking about that
i wouldn't ask kobo i think because
she's still new
um i don't think she would know
everything about the server i could be
wrong but i would ask someone else as
much as i love cool book john
i would ask someone else
anyway thank you mike for finishing the
reverse rainbow
and supporting the horse betting
addiction i want more
it was exciting i want to participate
myself though another time
thank you no no mike
and jayvon thanks for the pinky once
again thank you tanza for participating
in popcorn it was my first convention oh
really
and surely a precious and happy
experience in my life also thank you for
always doing your best in for korean
fans i'll keep supporting you
and then oh there's some easy
easy korean but i'm gonna throw it into
papa go anyway
oh
i'm curious what the conventions are
like in korea
if they're very different from western
ones i wonder
curious
when am i streaming tomorrow by the way
what day is it tomorrow is today friday
no today's first day okay
let me do a poll right now
okay so um i mean me were thinking about
you know some games but
she made some suggestions and i was like
i don't know so i was like how about we
let you guys um
decide
what
fbs game so i'mma was like
um
hamilton's or
overwatch or
team fortress 2.
choose
the thing is with overwatch i guess if i
play that one
some other um collapse could be possible
even though i would be [\h__\h] probably
but then a lot of people seem to like
team fortress 2
but i feel like overwatch might make the
most sense
for like other collaborations
tf2 too hard for you
okay my influence is working people are
voting for overwatch nice niceness
i think that might be the best choice
yeah because i could
i see more
members playing overwatch than team
fortress 2.
but is it difficult i wonder i'm kind of
intimidated
kind of worried about it
because i'll be mixed into teams of like
randoms right and then
people will probably hate me for being
so shitty and they'll be like why are
you in my team you suck
way too much trolling
[Music]
not friendly with you guys oh mama
i don't think all the watch is free
i'll have fun with you
but even with paladins it's not like
i was just like
shooting randomly and didn't know what i
was doing
i
didn't know what my attacks are so
really did
okay well that's that thanks for
participating in the poll
paul
i already know about it froggy we talked
about it yesterday too
it's just um
you know
[Music]
the result is overwatch congratulations
i mean it could still change last minute
maybe
um but in general it's probably going to
be that
thanks for participating
in the order from
general overwatch palettes oh really oh
much more friendly than paladins really
chill
chill out
we can do team fortress 2 maybe another
day and sometime in the far far future
chill
yeah i do not understand
i don't really is it easy to stream
snipe in overwatch
i feel like it has so many players that
it's
hard to
stream style
wait when you say no not really it means
it's not easy to stream side
stream stopping isn't the thing
there's no point in stream stamping
overwatch
why
one of new friendly characters for every
role
[Music]
diva is attack
she looked like a damage dealer to me
hey the mourinho
hey wait there's so much one and two
what
i thought there was just one overwatch i
gotta ask amma which one we're playing
a two isn't out yet okay somebody said
two is more populated right now it's not
even out
okay okay here there's a new one coming
why
anyway vengeance thanks for the pinky
hello there is this where we place our
vets i'm all in on schubert
thank you for betting you better at the
wrong place but i will take your bets
i'll use them elsewhere
betting on life
thank you
thank you and then dance
hope you enjoyed the stream
a miniature pinch of zhang kishin
wow fireworks was that already at the
end
oh wow
let me take a froat candy my throat hot
[Music]
but
it's so sticky
to the paper
yeah i will help to make it happen
maybe better to have the car that we not
on the last day but like maybe just
somewhere in between or so
hmm
i see no reason for why the car derby
would have to be on the last day
hmm
yeah yeah yeah
i see thank you
fruit candy sticky kisses
again
[Music]
thank you for the rainbow
rainbow uh for the for the fireworks
sticker the pinky
thank you
thank you and jim tracy duncan this was
so much fun thanks for streaming it
she's always great together and the
festival is so cool thank you i'm glad
you enjoyed the pabunashi
festival date jackson of b
apple thanks for the pinkie and
publishing cute indeed i agree
okay i don't want this music anymore
bossa nova again
oh thanks for the membership gifting
ah
so generous
thank you soon even porchy mama i
enjoyed pabunashi yeah she's so sweet
[Music]
next up we have
called up the lamp from yesterday
that was also quite something who's so
busy and cut off the lamp all the time
the grind mean
oi it's not loading the window is not
loading
come on
it doesn't work
side can't be reached is this side down
[Music]
does whole eliza work for you guys
wow
[Music]
yeah it's down
first timing
okay
okay i'll go back to the usual
reading place the one that youtube
offers to me
why aren't you there
why
yeah okay these ones are not so far
behind so it's fine
[Music]
hey boss your plushie is cute ooh not as
cute as you want it can do unarchived
karaoke oh
but i'm satisfied you clearly charged a
lit too little for it so here's a red to
make up the difference did i oh no how
expensive was it i don't remember
i'll be teaching during this stream oh
so be please dedicate my kids to cats
frog
ah
it's a cute frog trust me you won't
regret it
miss you plus a missy boss sorry i've
been stuck in the vodka oh it's okay
you're tuning and doing stream was
amazing thank you it wasn't quite
supposed to be enduring stream
officially it wasn't an endurance stream
it was just
no a normal gaming stream it just ended
up being pretty long
thank you very much for the support i'm
glad the plushie arrived recently a lot
of you guys have been telling me about
the plushie
which one is it though
is it the one that looks like me
because before we had a kotori plushie
which one is this one you guys ah the
tsukumo one ah
finally
what do i say finally but
how long did it take
um
[Music]
oh there's some interesting talks going
on about going on about the season three
in the discord
what to do how to do
uh
six months
four months a month
well that seems okay i mean ideally you
would want it within one month but you
know how it is
thank you dark hood and the kiss for
casp
casper's frog yeah franco
is it gonna turn
into a human
[Music]
surprise
did something happen
no yeah
[Music]
2nd of september marks the second
birthday i've spent with you on kfb ooh
that's like uh tomorrow
and you're still the greatest gift ever
bestowed upon me did you think i
wouldn't read this until after your
birthday
well look at you now
you're full
i've caught up
i'm reading it before your birthday
[Music]
you underestimated my power
hey
you're still the greatest gift ever
bestowed upon me kiana since i joined
kfe i've begun to change while i've
messed up some stuff along the way i
still see this as a year of rebirth oh
a second chance fitting that you a
phoenix would be at the center of it
your smile music and personal growth
inspire me to do better your kind soul
and love for that softens me
and your adventures abroad motivate me
to see the world oh as they should all
are such wonderful gifts ones that i
can't ever repay i'm no great artist
right a cooker musician but as i
continue this journey of renewal i want
to be here for you and give back in any
way i can and if a bit of that makes you
happy that's more than i could ever ask
for you mean the world to me here you're
so special i don't often say it but
today i'll go a little nuts
i love you tanto and i love kfc i wish i
wish you nothing but the best i'm happy
you've graced my life thank you for
inspiring me and thank you for another
wonderful year
ah oh what do i do now i can't say happy
birthday yet
it's not your birthday yet
only
like an asian time zone
thank you for the sweet message
it's really really nice to hear these
things i'm glad i can like motivate you
and make you happy
i think especially
traveling i can recommend to everybody
if you are able to travel around the
world do it
don't let your dreams be dreams don't be
stuck in your city or forever or in your
country go go go go see the world
make some connections get to know some
people
the world is beautiful it's such a waste
if you don't
go look at it
a little bit more
um
but yeah thank you so much gerard don't
don't say you're not good at cooking
did i destroy your confidence towards
cooking you say i'm no great artist
right to cook a musician of course
you're a great cook i don't know about
the other things but
of course you're a great cook
i'm sorry before roasting you so bad
i'll i'll be nicer from now on
baby
see
no don't let my like roasts uh like
reduce your confidence i haven't even
gotten to taste your cooking i was just
judging it by the looks of it and the
lack of lettuce uh that's that's all
there is so maybe it tasted amazing even
without the lettuce so
[Music]
don't take the opinion from someone who
hasn't even tried your food
[Music]
i'm just roasting you
oh
thank you so much i think that was a red
one and come like if all is put together
so a kiss for you
and
early happy birthday to you
congratulations
enjoy
the next year
make the most of it
thank you
oh
hello yesterday was my birthday due to
this i'm going on vacation today so i
won't be able to watch a stream live but
i'll make sure to watch the vlog thank
you for always making me smile
oh
vacation where are you going
[Music]
also they probably already gone by now
couldn't see you off
can we come yeah please
i'll have a great time there please
get some relaxation going
enjoy
yeah thank you so much for
being here for another birthday
me congratulations you for the pink
super chat
boss i feel like i'm still dreaming
although i didn't win a meet and greet
event i was happy to see it nonetheless
are you going to travel again next time
what do you mean
travel again next time you mean to korea
yeah i want to
next year
my goal is
korea japan
maybe one more america trip
um
maybe i want to go to greece again
it was actually kind of nice
or uh since i went to the maldives this
year this year and next year i could go
to what's up uh they say
say
say shannon uh say how do you say it in
english say shells whatever something
like that
oh bali could be nice too yeah true
it's a nice place in bali
yeah
so quiet a few places that i want to go
to but america you know if i go there
then i want to visit some girls probably
and japan would probably be you know
more of a work trip for like recording
some 3d stuff probably
and meeting some other members and all
that
but in terms of like vacation
yeah bali
greece
korea
[Music]
stuff like that
and kind of i talked about it with amit
um you know i asked her you know when we
weren't streaming and i was talking with
her i did ask her about you know hey why
you are you ever going to come to europe
girl and she was like yeah
passport blah blah blah
but she did say that
she she said i wanna go see like some
some
northern countries and i'm like okay and
then she's like oh yeah like switzerland
and like it
north
[Music]
okay
switzerland is not quite the north but
then i reminded her of some other
countries in the north and yeah some
scandinavian places i don't know where
she really wants to go
but i'll show her around a little bit
she was like ah sorry i don't know
where everything is
switzerland is more like central
maybe she makes something up yeah sweden
and switzerland maybe
maybe yeah
[Music]
you might have been thinking of sweden
um
yeah i wanted to go to some scandinavian
countries as well so that's actually
perfect
just what i was thinking
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah
anyway continuing navy diesel oh dear is
that a rainbow ah
thank you
[Music]
i'm home safely at first i don't expect
my korea trip would be the one best trip
in my life my plan was just to go to
visit annapolis cafe nice
just like me
even though my merch at that time oh no
enjoy popcorn and see my friends it was
a rough plan because i don't know much
about korea yeah same same same but
every korean rose were very welcoming to
me oh
they tried to eventually talk to me in
english or japanese and told me a lot of
things i don't know about korea
maybe you ended up finding out more
things than i did
while you were there we had nice time
together because of you and whole life
kfb is the best and thank you for the
meet and greet i'm so glad that you know
some basic thai and your accent was
lovely hey
yeah she taught me some some thai
while she was talking to me in the meet
and greet it was very sweet
sorry that i didn't tell my name clearly
and make you confused don't worry about
it i i was hearing so so badly like the
audio was so bad that could have been a
reason it was really hard to understand
anyone um
but it was nice talk hope i can see you
in our convention someday i forgot to
tell you that if you wanna do it for
something what if you want to do
something please don't worry we will
love it or not okay if we're always
supporting you and be with you thank you
for carrying us a lot by the way this is
my first rainbow and it goes for you
thank you love you too
it was lovely talking to you thank you
so much we're so sweet
um
i'm glad you could enjoy korea
yeah you were like i think the only
pretty much the only non-korean person
at the meet and greet
and i hope you are not like too
intimidated in a country where you don't
understand the language just like me
but i'm sure everybody was really sweet
and nice to you once again we see
how sweet kfp is always ready to help
always ready to like support and
help each other
very nice
thank you
for sharing your memories and your
thoughts with me
thanks for the rainbow
[Music]
yeah
maybe if you still want some merchandise
from adam plus
some korean rose can help you with that
too
juan carlos rodriguez
thank you
yo this stream has a lot of um
super chats from korean bros who went to
the convention because it was the first
stream after that
um
[Music]
thank you so much for coming to seoul
popcorn with bay i had so much fun on
the 28th and i was so happy it's my
first concert in my life eh but thank
you so much for making me so happy that
i
well that wasn't really a proper concert
i hope i can deliver
a proper concert for you guys
at some point and i hope that at that
moment you will be there too
okay
but so far
popcorn was amazing i agree and i'm glad
you weren't there to share it with
everybody
thank you very much meera
come san miguel
[Music]
thank you
and we have uh
ribbon
ribbon thank you for the pink super chat
popcorn meet and greet was so much fun
oh you weren't part of it i'm so happy
to hear that you're going to be my oshi
we mean going to be i always was right
i will also be the kfp potentio
oh only kiara only tensile
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh i like the attitude thank you very
much
i hope you enjoyed the meet and greet
even though there might have been some
communication problems
i hope you enjoyed it and didn't regret
it
never forget and treasure that photo
thank you you're here right now too and
chad hello i'm yong i'm young
there's already information about
tomorrow you mean the stream tomorrow oh
yeah well we're gonna stream um
overwatch
probably
and stream time will probably be like um
9 or 10 p.m my time
time
cest
yo
[Music]
bubba
song
[Music]
thank
you crown trick game is cute fun to
learn fun to play not too long
crown trick
[Music]
broke like rpg
with cute graphics
hello
the girl looks cute
oh my god she has a similar crown to
the the one from
our cult
oh i like the looks of it
thank you
interesting
[Music]
kind of cute
did anybody here play it before
[Music]
it's turn based what
and the name is crown trick
[Music]
long doesn't seem very well-known
to
[Music]
name
it was nice to see you in seoul popcorn
it must have been hard because the time
is so different from korea
well thank you for coming thanks to you
i was happy that day um i hope you will
always be happy too
thank you
thank you so much i'm guessing you
didn't make it to the meet and greet
probably but at least you made it to
popcorn thank you
the time difference is really tough on
that one yeah um
i think we were a pretty early panel if
the pack would have been a bit later in
the day that would have actually been
pretty
amazing that would have been so much
better
because i think it was like 12 30
in korea
could have just done it at like 4 30 or
so and it would have been a much more
decent time for me
but i had no choice
yeah that's the
time that they assigned to us
[Music]
of conventions um your program before
noon yeah what the hell it's
i
i don't know if there's like a
a good like logical advantage to having
a panel from the most popular guests
i don't know if that was the case with
popcorn but it was the case with dokomi
in the very beginning i guess
so the only reason i can think of is
they wanted to fill up the halls early
because usually
the best panels are at the end
of the day and then all the panels
before that are like now very well
visited in most conventions
we probably tried to like
get some of the
people who go to the panel from us to
stay
to watch the following panels
[Music]
but that didn't quite happen
so just put us at the end
anyway let me turn on the lights in my
room it's really dark and i'll you know
what i'll go to an idol meeting to the
took
[Music]
oh
tell you one secret guys
listen come here
listen
listen listen
small
small quiver
smoky well and no more pewa
actually
i just say in person
[Music]
[Applause]
what the [\h__\h]
no [\h__\h] way
yes it's true guys
it's true
we shared the same soul the same body
this is just an optical illusion
i'm so much smaller how it's an optical
illusion have you guys seen one of the
rings yes you have
[Music]
you know the all those optical illusions
they did there while i've learned from
it
[Music]
i've learned from that and i'm using the
same techniques
what is even real anymore
unbelievable
[Music]
so
you don't have to change your oc with
the same person
now you can just love me even more
[Music]
okay no
no fried squirt no
no
no no no no what would happen to me if i
take off the belt is something way more
majestic not this i mean indeed it is
suspicious that you can't see a belt on
this outfit which would maybe imply that
indeed this is a form i take when i take
off the belt but no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
no i'm
[Music]
hope you like the fan art yes
we prepared for you it is great to be a
part of a cult like kfb i was one of the
people up front cheering you and popcorn
i knew it of course they were in the
front it was so funny and i would wait
in line for 11 hours again wait
you waited online for 11 hours
pong
[Music]
crazy
you probably did that for aniplus too
didn't ya
i can imagine
oh mamma mia
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't do that not good for you but yeah
and now i understand what you had to do
to get into the front line
thank you so much for your dedication
and yeah i thought the advertisements
were so cool i really wish i could have
seen them in person but the timing was
off by like a few days or like a week or
so
uh
but the the illustrations they looked so
nice
and they were so big
but this place was so big
really impressive
yeah
they're not there anymore right they
were probably just uh until the end of
popcorn
i assume
thank you so much i hope it wasn't too
expensive
but i can imagine them must be expensive
[Music]
if you need some help always ask other
kfp okay to help you
please
yeah they look so good they were like
specifically for that purpose some new
art with like kiwawa
kiwawa and like korean clothing and all
that
it looked really nice
uh one day for the big one oh
and that one was probably expensive damn
thank you so much
thank you let's do it again
next time hopefully i can see it in
person
that would be so cool
no
thank you for your kindness always comes
on
[Music]
please check on your wii u i heard that
the eshop overview will stop accepting
purchases of games soon if there are
anything you like there better buy it
read download of course this game will
be
when is soon
oh so i did hear
something about
oh maybe that was a leak maybe that
wasn't supposed to be public yet but i
heard something about something
releasing on the switch
soon perhaps
um but one of those games i already
played anyway
but interesting
[Music]
was it next year march next year
well then chill
chill the [\h__\h] out about buying games on
the wii u
i heard something about something at
some time some point something
[Music]
language again remember guys when people
kept on saying language kiwawa language
kiara
where did that come from again it
disappeared now nobody says that anymore
they got used to it they they noticed it
has it's it's
it has no meaning to say that to me
[Music]
i kept making fun of it
got used to it
other youngs have worse mouths sometimes
people say that but i i don't i don't
believe it although cali was pretty um
aggressive today when she was shouting
at the people who were shooting
oh
oh no i saw that tweet
i did see that tweet i think but i like
that idea
but it would be nice to not do that
alone but do it with someone
like some classes where i can learn [\h__\h]
that actually sounds like fun yeah
um
i like the idea
pottery class imagine kiwawa in pottery
class i wish i could do that then like
um on stream in a handcam stream but i
don't think you can do that with gloves
although
although if i did that my hands would be
so covered in um what's up material
called again
you know the thing boom the
brownish gray brownish stuff
that you wouldn't see my hands anyway
clay yeah clay you wouldn't see my hands
like you know
so it's basically the same as wearing
gloves if you think about it
[Music]
yeah
from what i've seen like it gets really
really really messy though
yeah i still have some ideas for handcam
streams so for now i'm fine but in the
future
oh yeah already origami stream for
example yeah
and um
uh ironing stream
ironing stream and we can do some more
crafting i still want to do the hot glue
crafting stream
you know make some shoes out of hot glue
cross stitching is like man if i start
doing stuff like cross stitching
and and knitting and [\h__\h] i'm sorry but
i would start feeling like a grandma
those you can make so much cute stuff
with that i'm aware of it but first of
all i hate knitting
i hate knitting with a passion
and
um
second of all it takes a lot of time
[Music]
yeah i know that's kind of kibaba kibaba
kind of stuff yeah i guess it could be a
kibaba stream i could be like all right
everybody
that's all
yeah
knit little scarf for my sweet sweet
cold john yeah my child she's um
she's pretty old by now but still every
winter i make a nice scarf for her
so that she doesn't catch a cold she has
to take care of her throat you know yeah
i hope she's doing well she hasn't
visited me in a long time
[Music]
yeah i'm gonna make use from that kibaba
model
anyway
thanks for sneeze chats skipping those
though
thank you for the little pink super chat
it was so much fun to meet attention
bales and many kfp fans at silver
popcorn thank you thank you by the way i
want to make a diorama with a paper
model what is the most memorable moment
for you for two years
oh that's what you want to make into a
diorama
or is that unrelated are you here about
cody
are you asking that because you want to
make the most memorable moment for me
into a diorama
are you here
[Music]
most memorable moment
oh
yeah
i could it could be the hidden toy
performance
in um
but if i think of actual streams there's
so many it's just almost every [\h__\h]
day
it's so hard when people ask stuff like
that like what's your most memorable
stream
since you joined those kind of questions
are so tough holy [\h__\h]
how i can't my memory is so weak how can
i think back on that
[Music]
i would have to look at my streams but
then
let me look at my streams
all of my streams
most memorable stream in two years
this could take a while i've streamed a
lot how many streams have i done
[Music]
memorable memorable
memorable as in the one that i enjoyed
the most i wonder
[Music]
secondary debut was nice see that's so
far away so long ago and i don't
remember that one at all
i don't remember it at all
[Music]
oh no
i don't know
[Music]
i'm looking at them
the crafting stream
where i was doing like stuff with hot
glue or trying to do it was pretty
fun and memorable
actually all of my crafting and cooking
streams
are pretty memorable to me and pretty
special to me
um
wait i do have a category
for special streams what's in there
is that category
special streams
oopsie
[Music]
there's
outfit reviews sparks
endurance
new year's coral get christmas cracker
oh the mountain shrine
love debut streams
hard challenger announcement fashion
review
kibaba easter egg decorating ah that was
nice to
watch a long dance school
dance school was also
even though things was were really
exhausting and didn't go perfectly well
that one was also very special
bag review too that is one of my recent
best streams i would say
yeah i wish i
had another
perfect idea like that i mean we talked
about what else we could show off but i
don't think anything's as genius as the
whole bags one
[Music]
yeah that's okay don't need any
suggestions now
and anyway
yeah for now bulgaria i would say
any of the moments i just mentioned but
probably the one that worked best for
making a diorama out of would probably
be the hirototi performance maybe
or
[Music]
even though it sucked my debut stream
was obviously still one of the most
memorable ones
[Music]
obviously
hokkaido
thank you
thank you so sweet
johnny j thanks for the recipe
it wasn't my fault from the eye
from the very first time that why so was
it really him
i'm still so confused guys but it was
donated in korean one
[Music]
i'm so confused
was it really him
the guy from the meet and greet that i
interrupted to go to an idol meeting
oh if it was really you i'm so sorry
about the confusion
[Music]
so sorry
thank you for coming
thank you
[Music]
guys i'm actually really running out of
energy so i'm just gonna finish the cult
ones i think
because i i have breakfast like two
small pieces of like bread
bread rolls
and now it's seven no 8 p.m i'm really
low on energy
oh it has been six and a half hours and
before that i did
play a little bit rest as well
actually i did run out of energy
yeah i started early today
my eyes are tired
and my my hunger is
making me suffer
[Music]
home stretch yeah i'm getting there
i could stream like for 12 or 24 hours
if i if i had like snacks in between you
know if i had like a dinner and lunch
and all that in between
totally manageable
like smaller breaks
i guess that's what twitch streamers do
right the ones that stream so long
they do take like some breaks in between
and then they also don't always do the
same thing right
they have like a
variety of things they do in a stream
yeah but we're on youtube we're gonna do
it youtube style
although you know fona doing a 12-hour
marathon for her
uh anniversary made me think should i do
one too
but i actually already have like an idea
of what to do on my anniversary
i guess i probably won't be doing a
marathon
[Music]
you mean i did one for um 1 million
subscribers i did a 12 hour marathon
so maybe for 1.5 if that ever happens
i'll be doing another marathon i'll keep
it for for that probably and oh maybe i
could make it a 15 hour marathon because
1.5
a million
because at the end of the 12 hour
marathon last time i was like oh i could
go on even longer
just end it at 12 hours and then have
like an unaircraft karaoke or so like
fauna
for like three hours
although karaoke at the very end after
12 hours
is uh
challenging
[Music]
it would be risky
maybe something else
or maybe cut out at the beginning for
three hours and then 12 hour marathon
coming to 15 hours detective did 15
hours a day
was it 15 hours total holy [\h__\h]
yeah ahmed went crazy today i hope she
is
tight stuck in her bed sleeping now
in
the middle of the day right it's like
daytime there
i hope she's sleeping
oh my god
let me look
okay holy [\h__\h] her rust stream was six
hours 44 minutes
oh my let me calculate i'm gonna get a
calculator
[Music]
tonight
it was probably the adrenaline
six point wait this doesn't really
calculate it like hours i'll round it up
to
seven hours plus
[Music]
uh
plus
one plus
or i'll count it like that
oh my god it really was like 15 hours
how old did she do it
what the [\h__\h]
damn girl
[Music]
damn
and see one of those streams was even a
workout stream of nintendo switch sports
which i want to play at some point
because you can collab no not not that
one i guess wait was that the one that
people collab with
was that the one
and i wanna
do that for a collab sometime holy [\h__\h]
she was on a roll today
oh
damn
it tweeted she's gonna sleep for 12
hours yeah she should she deserves it
man
crazy
[Music]
i hope she wasn't sad about but she's
she's really easy going so she probably
doesn't mind but
i really i was excited for the derby i
was really like like interested in
participating and the first time i
couldn't because it was late at night so
i was hoping we could do it anyway today
but then nobody came
and then we just went to the war because
when we were trying to do the derby the
important war was going on
i hope she's not like sad about it
[Music]
but i think she at least felt
like the the interest
from me
as like
appreciation that she that she like
built it in the first place
yeah
[Music]
i just don't want her to
like feel upset about it i hope she
doesn't
yeah i'll help her build it next time
[Music]
i'll do
at least at least 50 percent of the work
the job
okay where was i
where was i
the [\h__\h] where was i
[Music]
um check up 47 out thank you tiny dog
thank you for participating in seoul
popcorn at dawn you did a good job
always thank you for sharing your
memories as the last participant
from the meet and greet idle meeting is
really important you come first
thank you
hope you enjoyed
the popcorn
had a great time it's a really really
nice event
i want to do more
i'm in super awesome she is
kind of playing with it by the spring
multiple cars yeah yeah yeah i used her
cars that's at least something hey
[Music]
living in my head and heart friend free
check
your meds space waterfall
my son jensen thank you soon
[Music]
um
oh yeah official with the moves and
chants i want to make them but yeah
maybe i should be the one making
them i'm not the best at it
but
thank you unknown thanks for the pinky
for fate all mortal possessions to the
kiwama
thank you
leave some stuff to buy yourself some
lunch money okay
or school
commission
her chants are so aggressive
any thoughts or plans of collab with
whole stars em members watch some of
their streams and fought you and tempos
would have lots of fun collabing
together
i
really don't have any plans right now
um
i don't know really i didn't give it
much spot yet
oh
they're i'm sure they're nice
but
um
currently
no offense but i'm not that interested
maybe
at some point but
yeah
i have like
a lot of other things in my mind
currently that my brain is occupied with
and a lot of stress and bleed blue and i
don't need any more stress that we know
will happen
um
yeah i honestly don't know i haven't
really thought that much about it
[Music]
yeah
but you guys should support them you
guys should watch their streams too i've
heard that their streams are really
entertaining
i haven't gotten to watch anything
besides like some parts of the debuts
um
and some sneak peeks here and there but
i heard they're really funny
really good at streaming
so go check them out they're also
apparently much better gamers than all
of us are
goddammit
yeah
um
[Music]
yeah
cracked oh man
oh
[Music]
a manager at like i always dreamt that i
was at work and it was incredibly
realistic so i would wake up at the
point in the dream i would be going home
at
oh and realize my work day hasn't even
started
and
dreaming about work so much there's
definitely some meaning there you
probably are just like overworked i
guess
and too stressed out
and like i guess this is a
from the past and not really accurate
anymore now but
[Music]
i'm so
i'm tired
tired
[Music]
oh
that's nice
that's very sweet do you see
i think that's very important
because it's good if they have a nice
bond
that'll make everything a lot more fun
panopticon danke soon
thank you for watching
leonardo m thank you for the rest of
jack hi i have been here since your
debut always broken and mostly a lurker
that's fine you're my first aussie and
youtuber and one of the reasons i turned
my life around wow
i got a job and i study now apparently
any time to enjoy youtubers but happier
than ever
oh
thank you so much kiwamo you're welcome
i guess
oh
wow i hope you still make some time for
kiwawa please i'm doing my best here
please give some of your precious time
to qiwa
[Music]
please
yeah but besides that
good luck at your job and your uh
whatever you're studying
thank you
fuzzy chaos 511
[Music]
feeling dank
i went to collaboration cafe on monday
miff's projects were sold out so i
couldn't buy all of them but i think i
already read this one but i ate tantrums
chicken and juice deliciously filming
dante's signature oh it wasn't a long
time but it was a fun day for me thank
you thank you for going there
for supporting it
i saw that now the post-it is in a safe
place
still visible to people but in a frame
and like probably very close to where
the staff always have an eye on it
so that's very good
very good
all of kiwawa's signature are
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
my
wait i'm invader
i just read that now
no super chat
interesting
what
[Music]
interesting
i'm a lime
and a lime
[Music]
anyway thank you so much
i'm glad you were able to go to the
annapolis cafe i think the one in in
seoul
has reached the last um
one or two weeks
right
so it might be closing soon
um
or like not closing but like they'll do
something else afterwards
they should extend it
ah it's been so successful they should
extend it
[Music]
captain
you know me being like a little edition
i always wanted to do that
so there are baka tala toriyo
jesus morales thank you looks thank you
thank you i want to collab with all of
them
with all of them i was three of them
i really want to
swan employee of the year thank you for
the red super chat happy late birthday
kiara
don't remember the last time i super
chat but i don't have to
i wish i could be here more but i have
my merch to remind me of my time with
kfb and you
and to represent camping public proudly
and love you all viva la february
[Music]
why so late
oh yeah what happened
did you forget
until now
what
[Music]
did you have to save money to send that
super chat
i wanted to send a red oh
so you waited until you had enough for
that okay well thank you thank you thank
you i didn't forget
and what are you busy with you need to
watch kibawa why is everybody so busy
stop being so busy
stop
still waiting on the german eofy collab
you don't have to wait much longer ahead
just saying that
[Music]
and thank you swan
thank you so much
[Music]
i demand of you to come to my streams
more often
yeah
are we waiting promise
thank you sean for your support
yeah thank you
soon
drowsy cat thanks for two pinkies before
popcorn started i was tired of long
travel times and long plates but now
it's a wonderful memory including all of
it really
i really enjoyed the stage it wasn't
empty words it was really really fun and
an hour and a half went by in a flash
and i was so happy that kian and girls
enjoyed it together you guys were the
best i love you my [\h__\h]
thank you
it was a really good panel
[Music]
i'm glad we all had a great time
together
thank you drowsy cat for being there
it's really nice to see like all of my
korean bros made it except for some who
you know got the the sifing
but most of my korean bros made it to
the event
it's so nice to see that thank you for
coming for this special occasion
thank you
and a kiss for you papa
[Music]
eat food now i think i'll make some
toast
um just want to eat some toast
some
ham and cheese toast my my mouth is so
tired i can't move it anymore
[Music]
thank you so much guys
members only super chats
i don't know did i read them what what
members stream
what was the last memory stream
[Music]
oh the anime one
oh
did i not read them
maybe i can oh dear if they're still
there when was that
[Music]
maybe i can read them at the next
members only stream
let me see let me scroll down because i
guess they don't show up and in
hololyzer
[Music]
hand cam
yeah not now but i just want to make
sure that i can still reach them oh yeah
i can reach them
[Music]
should be fine for still quite some time
i remember that it saved up like i don't
know 20k or so
worth of super chats
at least
in youtube
[Music]
that's probably fine
okay
thank you so much for today guys i hope
it wasn't boring i know and there was
maybe some time wasting here and there
and not too much action honestly i
expected a bit more action too but
yeah yeah well you know
um
maybe next finale there will be more
action from what i've seen so far it
seems like next time they'll be
organizing like really actual teams you
know i just saw it on discord they were
discussing it
that instead of everybody just like
going against piccolo that next time we
will try to have some actual teams and
that that i think will be more action
for everybody everybody will be more
involved
[Music]
and then i can be
part of that too
and then as a team together we'll be
stronger than you know just some
randalls running against
and especially like still
like newcomers like me
will be able to pull off more i think as
well
[Music]
so i'll keep an eye out on like how that
goes
[Music]
yeah that's a piccolo's team thought
before one rocket rocket took them all
out
[Music]
they're still warming up yeah
capture the black thing so it's not just
shooting explosives
everyone can take part interesting
interesting it seems like most of the
discussions are being done by japanese
members but um i might make a suggestion
i don't know
she deserved all her life going against
her
yeah yeah surely i mean she stood her
ground until the very end so
big respect on that
[Music]
uh
what a crazy rabbit huh
all right guys
[Music]
um i'll see you tomorrow in america
yay
[Music]
yay let's learn how to play overwatch
what a weird choice
i just wanted to collab with her and
want to play something that she'll enjoy
as well so i offered fps
what time and like yeah i think like 9
p.m or so okay what time
[Music]
hopefully she'll be
fully awake
i'll see you there and in germany
thank you
[Music]
thank you guys for watching and for the
love and support
[Music]
bye
bye bye
[Music]
it's oh wait what the [\h__\h] we are today
is the first of september i'll be
uploading
uh the new
members only wallpaper and guys you will
[\h__\h] love it it's gorgeous it's
[\h__\h] gorgeous
so
yeah check out the community board i'm
going to upload it live now i think
[Music]
again
good stuff
[Music]
you