foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
hey everybody
nice hairpins thank you do you like them
do you like them
hey everybody Welcome to oh wait you
can't I'm just gonna be down here
welcome everybody to the Among Us
about this collab with Ian and Ivy uh we
we're doing among us today because
we have a collab
it bends it blends perfectly with your
hair thank you so much
thank you so much
hide the coffee energetic rat has
appeared I have so much coffee right now
it's so early I am so tired
but it's okay
when you said you wanted to decorate
your Christmas tree I didn't know you
meant yourself bruh
bruh do I look pretty
do I look pretty
um so today is a uh promotion stream to
celebrate Among Us the sex Hollow live
yeah and then we gotta do some
uh you know we're gonna do some
mandatory
um
promotion of the merch everybody if you
look at this
just Minify the rat for a little second
hold on so if you have a look over here
you see the amazing amazing merch that
is available until tonight 23 59 jst the
sale will end today today is the very
last day you can get the merch you've
got the acrylic diorama stab the plushie
set an amazing keychains and then you've
also got
um inner spots merch as well that you
can grab
do you want to be sassy in chin
now for the keychains you can see that I
have Council races ones displayed
beautifully on your hair put it on your
bag put it on your on your ear put it on
your keys doesn't matter it's a chain
for everyone everyone has a purpose
everyone can enjoy
um and for the keychains there is one
special keychain for every single hollow
life member so if you have Oshi or
oshie's
you can just get that keychain but I
know you guys will be definitely getting
the bells hey Coast one correct correct
look how cute it is they've all got
cheeky little characters it's the
emergency meeting
keychain you can't see it
I'll move over here look at that oh
beautiful
absolutely beautiful
there's Belle tacos I'm gonna slap you
oh sorry sorry this is in the in the
middle of a promotion uh announcement up
get yours today
for
a steal price of
I'm really sure
um
be sassy in fashion uh
I don't know what I'm doing guys it's
pretty good it's really cute look I got
a little wait can I enhance myself hold
on look at this look at this King Kate
is so cute it says who is the Imposter
I got different colors and look it's me
winking that's me being cute I've got
half of an XD face
look
I have half an XD face
load the bgm
duh what other bgm did you think I was
gonna play
come on you have to play the sneaky
snitch for among us should I just leave
sneaky snitch on through the entire
stream is that allowed
is that loud bro
am I allowed to do that
like head it's just background music
right
bro let's do it
and we're not using proximity today so
she
bruh
snitches get stitches so true
there's a tiny Mr squeaks too yeah there
is so get it today oh we're supposed to
meet up soon but
um yeah make sure to catch everyone's uh
perspectives as well
um but just stay on mine don't exit
don't go please don't go please don't go
uh please don't go
I can only buy two keychains so I bought
yours in irises thank you very much
thank you and also look Santa has one
too
we got the gang all together
um so
we're just gonna be playing among us
today yeah
um
you can unlock the Cosmic Cube which I
shall show
like wait hold on do I need to show it
now how do you do promotion again hold
on
wow amazing okay so we have uh the
Holland live Cosmic Cube here if you
look at it wow it's like a map the more
you play the more you unlock for those
who are not familiar and as you can see
I have played zilch
I have not played any oh my gosh
uh praise the cube everybody
so
foreign
fake Among Us fan
I never said out ah I mean I love ours
is this time limited oh you have another
23 days to unlock the entire map
look
there's goodies
essential
Caillou
Super Key fake hollow life and I'm so
sorry
hey
was my was my shield not believable I
feel like my shield was very believable
was it not get your keychain and your
merch today
what a deal
oh I gotta go gotta go late okay anyway
um there's no chat on the screen for you
know just for reasons but we're gonna
keep the bgm okay and I'm gonna rejoin
the rest of the girls okay
remote work hello
hello hello
[Music]
wow everybody's really tired huh
the third hellos
[Music]
do we want to do like uh you know a
classic introduction of everyone yeah
yeah soundtrack let's start by the top
hello everyone hello it's on your mouth
is second generation how how's my voice
thank you
[Applause]
I really love that it's still fancy
okay Advanced next what's up it's me the
red I'm tired
um the rat I'm gonna Channel my
sleepiness into being the best rat that
I can
hello
oh no you silly
let's go
oh
okay it's bails in the room yet I don't
sit here in the room no I'm not isn't
that gonna timeout
yeah
okay okay
next we are hiding what are you hiding
Kofa now I'm shy do you want to hide
with me yeah
[Music]
oh
you're naked compared to everyone else
oh you know what beauty beauty is is
you're just beautiful fauna you don't
need yeah
the natural beauty you know you were
born naked the natural beauty why why
was that done
foreign
you've convinced me
when you're turning to Nature
clothes I don't have any clothes yeah I
don't I don't have full of life
okay crony next all oh
kuronnichiwa hello it's me
orocroni from Halloween live English
I'm going to kill everyone
[Music]
[Laughter]
but I have her on Max I can't do
anything else
louder or something
yeah enunciate speak from the stomach
crony
be tired
I said you're too low
yeah
well I think that needed a bottoms but
then nothing happened I was really
expecting Harry uh yeah all right
okay oh my god oh yeah say again crony
this is this loud enough now yeah you
sound good yeah
okay yeah thank you
[Applause]
so crazy
let's have a fun promoting theme
everybody whoa
wow yeah I'm ready amazing
thank you for bringing the energy that
we need I feel like I just got
electrocuted by your energy I felt that
in my eyeballs I know so did I whoa how
do you feel living here get better at
feeling in your eyeballs uh
[Music]
we did not only
[Applause]
amazing wow
thank you for waking up so early I love
you
[Music]
hello oh hi I'm a nice movie I'm Paul
Live English I have a stuffy nose
and then registered to me that you were
saying oh hi I thought you were saying
Ohio but then he just cut it halfway
because you couldn't be bothered to say
the rest
and that's fine
I also heard nashimum instead of Nana
she's just saving letters I am saving
time here come on
I mean it would take too long the room
is going to describe
[Music]
oh no I'm the
nice bait Ollie nice try
it's not gonna work
interesting okay we got to go
why am I running so slowly question mark
how to play this game
right
ah
whoa why are that why am I running so
slow
bro
hi Kiara
uh I was stuck by the wall
is the speed set to slow oh fixed it
nice
anyway
we are just a normal crew member today
just a normal crew member nothing oh
I forgot the game had audio
there we go
doing fine
downloading just the normal crew member
time for Bay to die first excuse you
excuse you
like
[Music]
there's also not many tasks yo this is
not that hard uh
that's right
who was that that was that was Muna
senpa wasn't it
interesting interesting interesting
interesting
um
okay maybe
Senpai is safe
she's safe
oh
crony seems safe too oh who's missing I
haven't seen
was that a diamond in the shoot
yeah we just lost so much fun
oh my God
oh
no oh wow where's the body okay
oh two buddies yeah yeah I found a lion
where was everyone at
uh I
just arrived on the shield
sorry
hold on
it should be muted never mind
um
I have discovered the body
at the map okay
sir I was in storage and
there was a hallway to the left you know
the whole way that leads to electrical
and then the you know yeah
and I actually saw a member
and then go in that direction
I discovered the body
oh
crony would you like to explain why you
were there right right before I
discovered the body
what wait but like I've been traveling
like everywhere else like I've been
traveling the right side of the section
so I didn't really notice anything like
I was checking sampling when you were
there three seconds before that I when I
found the body why did you not report
the body if you were there
[Applause]
there was something there I didn't even
go to the right side the whole time
yeah
since we've already lost two crew
members
um
I was on the map sorry
oh yeah
[Applause]
foreign
I feel like I'm gonna die everybody I
feel like I literally feel like I'm
gonna die
I know I should be doing them
okay I still got
there were people there
with everyone
whoa I saw Anya instead of being in the
same room
where are you guys
look so fast is it because you're still
near to the body because you just killed
her
[Music]
you know what happens to snitches
I'm gonna give this the Innocence the
win so
um
no I'm not
Confessions of a killer
oh that's hilarious
one imposter remains
my gorb
anyway
I just have one more actually two more
electrical electrical electrical
oh no
oxygen
come on guys
are we gonna die
are they gonna die
why do I feel like they're gonna die
yo can someone fix the oxygen
no what
no
hey why did no one fix the oxygen what
I just want to say if someone if uh
someone is being choosing as imposer and
the Imposter said that the next imposter
is someone don't believe it
[Music]
which means that they're gonna be
innocent the only two people remaining
were Kiara
choose between the two
uh
I'm
here
information I love it yeah but thank you
for not voting me out appreciate it
there's one person missing in the room
thank you Ollie like when I was about to
walk over and Anya was there and I was
like crony you just got me in so much
trouble
it worked out though I'm also sorry to
everyone in advance but hey that's the
game
like
Courtney was like no it was like people
were there and then everyone else seemed
not convinced and I'm like she killed
man for
[Laughter]
that was so funny
yeah
I couldn't see it because I was doing
like tasks
um
were the ones in the room yeah and like
I was like I was hoping I was hoping
that Zeta would say something so that
people would like me I didn't see it
was very lucky that run the funny thing
is that I was like I was about to go out
from that room so if only you had waited
for like a few more seconds I probably
wouldn't have thought that
oh crony learned her lesson for next
round right yeah
I can't believe it
what
man Ollie every time again we are but
a normal crewmate
just doing our tasks
they're kind of weird
Ollie Ollie a bit sus she didn't even go
up to the lights
okay
wait what
what
what am I meant to do
what the
heater
it's very dangerous
or two times in a row right yeah yeah
and I was trying my best trying to turn
it on but people kept turning it off
I was at there at the scene too but if
you wouldn't have just admitted
immediately that it was you then I
wouldn't have known because there was so
much going on
[Music]
I was I was in there I was in there
because electrical was out and everyone
else was right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah how could we know it was her
we don't know if it was her
too much
just incriminated herself by the way I
mean you can try
best of luck yeah
everything Tony thanks
[Music]
you it's you who exactly who knows
I am more than displeased
I am extremely displeased
I cannot believe this Revenge art it has
begun
can someone please
can we stop throw
I cannot believe this
just because she sucked at being
stealthy now I am
suffering I'm subjected
to have Revenge because she sucked and
wasn't good
at getting rid of her tracks
what
this is preposterous who is the other
imposter though I wonder
oxygen again
foreign do people just not want oxygen
please
hello
okay nice
is Ollie safe
okay interesting Ollie a little bit suss
why'd it take her that long to fix the
oxygen she was the first one there
why was she the first one there oh
questions
questions questions
Nani
oh did you see that it took us so long
to empty to to to fix the oxygen
what
oh look at all of this oh my God how far
how
oh goodness
I was like how far can I Venture all
right we're done
let's examine oh
it's happening
Mommy Mommy
chasing me and then she went off to the
right side of the map okay now you're
running around yeah
I thought that he was the Imposter
because she was chasing me but she sorry
it sounds so suspicious right now I know
I do but you look so used to me and
chasing me around the table but I almost
called a meeting because I was like
that's kind of susp and I was like oh
it's movie so it's just probably just
being normal yeah it's probably
yeah
why did Ollie called a meeting just to
check
actually I wanted to do a little
promotion
and among uses collaborations
yeah sure could they
um why did you go to the electrical for
like one second and then you went out
immediately
oh I was just checking to see what's
inside
why won't you check who's inside why
can't I check who's inside I can be like
oh someone's there why won't I don't
know
yeah yeah if you don't have any tasks
like and inside the electrical then why
would you go inside because I didn't
want to see who's inside and see if I
could stick to anyone
I mean Ollie and me were like going out
of the room why why didn't you like go
with us instead I'm sorry where is this
intense
going out but like you you like you you
were like going inside for like one
second and then you came out immediately
yeah
someone then why didn't you go with us
well because I don't want to get killed
there
last time last time we were all in
electrical we got somebody got killed
but
[Music]
I was not paying attention what happened
okay somebody what happened to me then
[Music]
um
hit two people for that okay
observing observating we are observing
the first specimen
that we are observing
is
seems awfully attached to throw up
interesting
we are observating the observation
Muna is throttling very happily on her
way where is she going they are but
alone
is she gonna do it
she's gonna do it oh
escaped with her life
oh you do seem very very soft
oh he is
gonna do it
she can do it
oh
unless that wasn't him it was at a point
the trust in the ollie foreign
interesting interesting
set up set up
was that you
did said close the doors right behind
her
what what was happening we have just
witnessed something marveling in the
natural world
foreign
my little friend
it's gonna be okay my little friend are
you scared don't be scared
mommy will be back okay
is that a sister where is that at
where'd she go
foreign
when we were all in the admin room and
then I saw someone teleporting from
storage to the to the main lobby
teleportation wasn't the three of us who
were in the admin room and it wasn't
yeah it wasn't me phone and Kiana you
know what what's interesting is that
Zeta came off the Dead
yeah I came from yeah but I wasn't I was
like it came from the office walking I
was walking I don't know I didn't see
anyone teleporting though but that uh
Zeta was like yeah I said I came to
admin I came to America because I saw
you guys
yeah you were doing stuff
interesting sounds interesting I'm I'm
suspicious interesting
to arrive at your destination
but um I'm just gonna say I finished my
tasks
I want I I have one left the wire does
it go again
[Music]
yeah let's let's pick up for those who
finishes
those who haven't who haven't finished
the task
s
yeah sure sure
[Music]
I can
are we voting Anya we need Anya to vote
oh yeah I'm sorry you're just skipping I
I voted
no I hope you like space accidents
[Laughter]
let's see what happens
we want game over
who was it
wait who was it it was
um okay
yeah cause that was so sad I didn't
teleport by the way
is that loud
maybe that was lag I don't know
did you not actually get it I thought
you were just ignoring me on purpose
I have no idea how that song goes I
didn't even know that was a song until
later oh my God jump
Ed
do you want to try a different map or
stay in the same map girls
um
[Music]
I left
all right
um
[Music]
is that the winter one the snowy one
yeah
okay let's try let's try paulus I guess
I don't like it that much but sure it
might be fun okay
okay
um
cold there you go
thank you thank you
thank you y'all see nothing one second
one second
skills that they don't know the map well
so they didn't know where to go oh I'm
in exactly
I never know where to go I also don't
know where to go so like we got lost a
lot yeah oh yeah
bye-bye everyone
oh finally I'm
huh Ollie
good old Ollie
oh no I actually
oh this is a really easy map to get lost
in
it's fine
ah
no imposter
maybe maybe we're not suspect today
maybe we're just good citizen today
you know because we're doing a promotion
stream
I'll just be good yeah
good rap today not says not sauce at all
oh I saw a little fubuki looking a bit
and
Senpai looking sus
oh that kind of scared me
not crony again well she's not the
impossible
unless I saw it in the in the near
office near office where is that
oh office oh right right I'm sorry but
laugh on the office
didn't you report oh
yeah you said you saw it but you didn't
reply
nearby I think
no I was from the office and then it was
on the left room right left from the
office I think so I was in the office no
no you went into the right person you
were in the right room Anya you know
yeah so you go first and then you saw it
it was like it was dark so like
interesting interesting you know I was
right behind you you seemed a bit sus
I was right behind her
she was like acting a bit sus in that
hallway right before she entered the
right office so
in front of me it's Anya yeah but I was
behind you
so I was watching them
was actually on the left left issue yeah
of the office yeah I saw her I was in
the office I was in the office and then
I saw going away
I saw you I went I didn't go in the
office yeah
I saw you I think go towards the office
I passed by you and said I think yeah I
think mommy is near Communications or
something yeah I passed by mermaid as
well yeah I don't know midnight looking
at myself
I was like around there but I don't know
because I didn't see it first yeah they
and Anya are kind of teaming up against
Muna
oh
God are we folding well I don't I don't
know I don't know if there's enough
information keep your eye on Myna
[Music]
I'm gonna choose whatever you want
that's fine oh also I don't know you're
picking fights here interesting oh
no
The Impossible
partner said nothing in this meeting
[Music]
foreign
I'll keep my eye on fauna
she's extremely sauce
is only doing a task let's see if the
taskbar increases
okay yes it does okay
interesting
resting
oh we need lights
can't see
I can't see
ah
nice I don't know how to do that light
thing
I needed
where am I going
oh
hi hi hi hi
[Music]
whoa
oh
clicking simulator okay
oh oh oh oh
right
right I can't go in here
I can't go in here
okay
where's fauna I haven't seen her around
kind of sauce
[Music]
kind of very sauce
ah
a
[Music]
wow wow
wow
[Music]
please someone notice me
foreign
[Music]
yeah we were from the specimen oh wait
he was and we met up with Zetta yeah yep
on the way to the Bay was suspicious of
Muna and I didn't see her the whole
round no I was with Mommy before but uh
I go with Mommy before yeah I didn't see
but I know wait what I was in the boiler
room still doing my task
um
I was in the in the with Walnut and only
before fauna only and Zeta we made right
with these three imposes like standing
there yeah
in the emergency room yeah
the three imposters now wait what room
and then we met at all yeah
I was mostly on the right side of the
map the whole time yeah me too so I
can't be on the left side of the map
um where are you I thought I saw you oh
yeah I guess I just wait you said right
side right
yeah oh wait never mind never mind I
guess I don't believe this
wait what I don't have any imposters
voted out yet right that's kind of bad
yeah yeah this is kind of bad I mean
there's two people left right I don't
know man I'm gonna come with left Luna
Senpai cause yeah
and barely sussing her
and and I mean if you die you can do
your I'm so confused faster so it's a
win-win
um
I'm already done with my test so I'll
just follow people around I'm only I
have like one more I have one more I
have like one more nice
whoop okay
is that getting trolled
wait
there's no such thing as friendly fire
is there
what what
you squatty
who is it
it was moomy she was chasing me at the
end
[Laughter]
foreign
[Applause]
excuse me
yeah it's a new mode I'm scared to
explain wow okay why did you miss it you
should have prepared and you wouldn't
have you wouldn't have missed it uh-huh
oh yeah this is all my fault right
gaslighting is the victim's fault okay I
got you
head yeah who intense I'm missing one
person
who is it
uh get in here
maybe one more sorry oh that's okay I am
learning the game you're doing great
yeah
all right well I think we can only
squeeze in one more round maybe we can
do one more and then we can play hide
and seek okay let's yeah
all right turn around bye wait this one
is
the next one okay well I never
never imposter
man all I've been doing is getting
bullied this this entire freaking game
uh
okay
how do I oh
goodness gracious me I'll get in
I'll get in here
oh there's a door oh
door's locked
that's nice
okay Zeta you seem safe
all right
interesting okay okay okay okay
let's have a look shall we
um
that was not that was that was ah
where's
where is that
where's the report button where's the
report but where is it where is it where
is it where is it where is it where is
it where is it where is it where is it
how do you how do you
it's not crony guys
[Music]
you've done it why did you not record it
then no I was on the security cameras I
saw
how could you
what
okay I will say in in the um
[Music]
I saw her on the security cameras it was
mermaid standing over crony's dead body
and also Luna running away
[Music]
right then and there what what wait wait
that was her natural state
[Laughter]
poster you will have reported
I didn't see her body you were on top of
her body
leaving the lights out
um also keep an eye on Luna because she
was running she was like there and then
she went the opposite direction so I
don't know if she really didn't see it
or she's also in kahoot I don't know
another double m just keep it just keep
it you know just keep an eye out on her
and he dies so I they honestly but okay
whoa yeah okay yeah then it'll be it'll
be all okay
I
cannot believe I saw that on camera
[Laughter]
[Music]
my dear
okay now I gotta be careful because if I
die
if I die
that means I was right I'm gonna stay
away from Muna I gotta stay away from
everyone
okay
how do I
watch I no I'm staying with people
[Music]
we're going this way we're going this
way okay
[Music]
okay
so Kiara is also safe I don't trust Anya
either I don't trust anyone oh my God I
have never felt this heightened level
of anxiety
oh my goodness
oh my goodness I don't want to be alone
oh someone's here uh
oh okay people are here we're good we're
fine
oh nice
okay are you safe
uh-oh
uh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh wait a second someone else will
get it right
oh no
Anya
on your kind of sauce uh
let's go together let's go together you
and me
no one kill me no one kill me no one
kill me
okay okay okay
everyone kind of sauce oh Anya
oh okay
I don't know what that was
[Music]
come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on come on
come on come on come on come on nice
okay it's got to be either Anya or
Moon
it's either Anya or Muna because
everyone else we're traveling in packs
if mooner is dead it means it's Anya if
Anya is dead it means it's Muna
oh moon is alive
it's Anya oh my God wait a second
wait question mark
nanny
okay never mind
do my tasks yeah hold on I'm a bit lost
at the moment
I am just a little bit lost
please return in a minute oh I have to
be a oh my God I have to be alive for a
minute
oh my God this is so scary
foreign
this is so scary
hey
okay okay
okay
all right you guys seem safe
um
interesting
very interesting
foreign
I feel like the Imposter is scared now
who would be scared it would it would
have to be Muna because
right
it would have to be Muna
nice
good job
good job again
[Music]
people I didn't kill anybody
you did walk over my I'm the one who's
ridiculous but there's like Avatar
moving after moving uh get out
everything's like this is so hard to
kill everyone yeah
that was like uh that was like a scene
from like a movie dude I saw it on the
camera and I was like bro this can't be
real
[Music]
you can see people's names when they're
watching somebody no I just saw your
your character your colors
yeah yeah oh yeah oh yeah yeah
see the colors
um
well why are you looking on a camera
babe that's creepy you're the one who
likes watching I don't want to hear it
when you guys in fact but but you guys
instead not in like one step but have
like a different style so I just like oh
this is hard even though I do it
I think everybody should be off on their
own and isolated at all times honestly
oh wow yeah maybe because does that make
that does it make it impossible for me
can we just maybe do one more round and
in case someone gets imposter who
already got impossible before we restart
or just gonna try but it feels like bugs
or snow okay
I'm going to kill all of you
again
okay yeah if someone gets it like okay
narrow down doesn't that narrow down
oh yeah oh yeah okay maybe do you want
to play one more round it doesn't matter
who imposter is just one more time
let's do that yeah well like if we get
an imposter again either Muno or me we
could just do the emergency meeting and
cast okay yeah I found an imposter I'll
be throwing it
oh
well
why
what why now why
I can't even do a Revenge Rock because
Courtney is also the Imposter bro
[Music]
wait how do I get in oh it's over here
oh
ah Frank
Nani no wait are we going to happen
what I I saw someone but I don't know
who it was because I wasn't looking at
the screen but there was someone running
Rockets right oh yeah yeah by the
Rockets
I I was stalking fauna and then it got
dark and I lost sight of her but then I
saw crony come from the opposite
direction
and I started stalking her wait where's
the body again nothing yeah
where is the rocket oh uh it's nearby
the laboratory oh okay okay oh that's so
far
I've just been in weapons all I'm saying
is that like on the left side of the map
did whoever was did they cross paths
with you or did you see them to the left
interesting left
from the right to the left interesting
oh I did see crony run however I don't
know I huh I don't know
[Music]
so okay I will fess up
I I did get it again what
what but like
should you cast me out now
[Applause]
but I didn't kill anyone so I don't know
what happened
Boston we'll just continue like that
what happened oh imaginary kill people I
will just act as if I did it
so like if I'm in pause for a good
should I just out myself and just
everything we have too many people doing
like it narrows it down too much so I'm
not sure we can really do that I mean we
could just keep crony around
well I'll just not kill anyone I'll just
do sabotage
[Music]
oh oh that was close oh man oh close
but at least she's honest she's very
honest that's true that's true
oh my goodness gracious me oh when you
fix the lights right
um where are the lights
I'm gonna walk into the wall you know
you start uh up here no up here
oh oh it's already fixed nope
foreign
wait I keep walking into walls bro
huh
[Music]
okay
um okay I need to go up into there
huh
up here oh
oh
come on other person
we have to go where was it in the
hallway on the left side of the map like
but it was like like a tree yeah
it oh was anyone there I was at the pad
that like on she's in like the middle
okay who was with someone was with me at
stabilizer so they're also safe
um
but then I went to the left
she was coming from that area but I
guess she didn't she didn't touch it
yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
I won't fly
it's okay yeah anything can happen it
must be the other imposter
Fisher friends not food God I I have no
idea are you girls skipping
I I don't know does anyone have any
leads I don't know who to choose
[Music]
honestly I choose bonna at this point
have you been voting fauna every single
round
herself immediately
that's
okay
okay nice sabotage
okay I need to start walking into some
walls okay
because I can't see
okay
my blood pressure bro my blood pressure
okay blood pressure
okay
walking into that freaking wall okay I'm
good
oh good
[Music]
come with me for uh
foreign
[Music]
nice
okay
Ollie I'm safe look Ollie I'm safe Ollie
I'm safe
thanks Ollie what's up Ollie he was safe
uh where am I all right
oh oh I shouldn't have done that
I'll go down my heart is beating so
quick bro oh gosh where am I am I oh I'm
lost down here okay
okay
wait what
oh the lights are out
the lights are out
um
my hands are shaking bro
hands are shaking bro
[Music]
oh
uh oh I have I have a theory like Romeo
and Juliet wait what what romantic
I have I have a very big Theory so I
will discussing uh Zeta
ume and fauna at the very start because
they were the nearest people after I saw
Muna senpai
and since crony came out I felt like oh
oh it has to be someone that didn't came
out after meeting Anya
um any isn't the type that would be
um going on herself doing duties just to
get in anyone's dress if she's an
imposter so it couldn't be heard it
couldn't be me it's inside a car Senpai
or Bang
I could have killed you right
I was walking with you for so long down
was not done yet
oh okay but I don't know I feel like I I
really because we're kind of dwindling
to the final people so if you waste a if
you waste the thing we're gonna we're
gonna lose by the way the body was that
um beside the weapons is that weapons
like you better choose somewhere like
between weapons and admin
wait why is Courtney still here
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I mean I don't know why I'm still here
[Music]
I appreciate the disc thanks Courtney
but like really big props to like the
other imposter doing a very nice job but
Let's Stay Together and finished us I'm
done by the way yeah
[Music]
wait what this is not electrical bro we
gotta get Electric
wait a second
[Music]
I feel safe
I feel safe here
[Music]
you stabbed me where in the back
you know you're killing spree
[Music]
honestly I was dead and had to finish
the tasks I think it was me himself but
I did man wait I read it I was so
surprised you didn't see me when I read
lost
in red I wasn't looking at my screen
oh yeah but is it possible to do one
more since like that that one round it
was just pretty much one imposter
um
oh do you guys just want to do hide and
seek hide and seek is fun
[Music]
we should remake the room though
actually you can just um hide and seek
is you've got one imposter and the
killing time is like 10 like the lowest
10 seconds and pretty much they have to
try and kill every everyone before they
finish the tasks do you know who the you
know who the sneaker is yeah yeah so you
have to you have to say that you're the
Imposter when you get it
um and you've set the the running speed
to the fastest whoever's making the room
and then you just okay you count to ten
if you're the Imposter and then well
yeah
okay I have the player speed on Max oh
my God that is so fast yeah wow
[Applause]
yeah I'm not reporting the body yeah no
reporting the bodies no report okay 10
seconds 10 seconds yeah it doesn't get
any lower okay do we have to do tasks
yeah yeah yeah yeah so the point is to
finish all the tasks before you get
killed
[Music]
so wait so how many should I do
should be good or two to four
yes
um
no reporting um and also what do you
want to do do you want to do the normal
one for now
okay
[Music]
they're screaming yeah
let's go let's go
[Music]
who is it who is it who is it oh we can
stay on music I
[Music]
you're not supposed to do it
okay I'm just giving you a head start
here I come okay okay
[Music]
oh my God okay okay
all right
it's impossible I'm meant to die in this
I have no idea
[Music]
oh God
yes
[Laughter]
I wanted to die it's even more scary
because she's silent you guys you got
the division
[Music]
body's everywhere
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God
play the elevator music oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my god let's go
you don't need to wait what do you mean
I haven't killed anyone in a while
come on come on come on
everybody oh okay nowhere
is a dangerous place
thanks everybody
where's everybody
wait is it only is it only me and Bay
now what
what yeah wait
um
shoot
go grab a coffee
there's like two imposters
I don't think so we can haunt her oh
your sins full enough
oh
wait what
oh yeah
[Music]
we can just give us another 10 seconds
I thought
I think it's good I think I think it's
well balanced
challenge yo this gets the hot pumping
hide again four three
two
okay
thank you
whose task is left
[Music]
possible
wow amazing
I think I would work so that we would
win what what good time
okay this is fun
okay
but I'll change should I change
something any Improvement advice it was
actually okay I think it was good I
I think
it's nice shoes all right to play well
if you want to win it's possible
who's it
I don't actually don't I don't actually
want to be it so please no thank you
wait we should restart okay okay okay
well we could just do an emergency
um yeah yeah you can kick her out okay
all right goodbye
what's your defense
why don't we just you know doing the
marketing yeah
[Music]
let's do it
just
do it let's do it do it
the car really fast of us saying do it
is incredible
invited me
all right will it be fun again or help
no we weren't easy this game is so easy
oh yeah
who is over there
oh
it's not me
we're actually gonna die we do tasks
during the countdown no no we wait we
wait wait okay
something okay I'm counting please wait
what
do we do the task
somebody died already
killed me already okay
okay
I started
oh man
I have no idea what should I do but
um
the Keystone is broken
oh
she's very
careful now well this is pizza
I'm definitely meeting the cafeteria
right now you don't need to go looking
for me
[Music]
I can't do the card
I know
oh
she ignores me
so sad oh I feel the view so small nope
not in the cafeteria at all
every time I'm just doing a white thingy
moment
one more time and boom finally
[Laughter]
oh my God
all my faults my hands are shaking bro
if we lose it's my fault
um yeah
oh it gets hard when
there's only a few people left okay
I already mentally gave up on that thing
[Music]
um
wow you are scary oh my god
oh you've got the terrifying yes
[Music]
I'm so sorry
that was fun
did anyone besides me never get imposter
I mean I never I never got one only an
onion me we have cursed
yeah
it's not fair
I'm going to sue someone I don't know
who but I'm going to school
just like hello
this actually means milk in Indonesia
please give me
how do I say please give me uh it
depends that you can at least give you
can always just say
uh something dong
mama
oh
my God
only I'm surprised
I will marry you or something like that
sorry
anyway guys go purchase some Holo live
mode it's your main meal and uh yeah
right now it's gonna end soon it's gonna
end I'm gonna show you yeah in like 12
hours I think so make sure to grab the
merch guys
acrylic stand oh yeah
cool t-shirt
mm-hmm
[Music]
you got the moon yeah
yeah very nice that was fun thanks guys
[Applause]
I'm finding so spontaneously especially
for the IG members who already did their
homework thank you
thank you
and thank you everyone for watching hope
it was fun for you guys too thank you
yeah it was really fun thank you nice to
see myself
bye
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
thank you