[Music]
for
la
[Music]
n
la
[Music]
Ki the again yay
y hello do you hear us everybody can you
hear us can you hear
us
yay yes I guess see hello we are very
rich CEOs and today we are playing or
it's not playing it's not a game serious
business we're doing shark tank with
some people but the CEO next to me let's
introduce her what what CE are you
what's your name yay hello everyone my
name is
l Kai positive genius I'm from Legos
nice to meet you guys kpg kpg k k it's
so fitting kpg KF K KF KF KP KF k k yes
nice welcome to the Shark Tank CL
Li yes I'm Lio CEO yay and I am CEO of
kfp K fried Phoenix as you know I am the
owner of the fast food Empire all over
the world and your your company is uh a
general Trading Company yeah yes what
what is
that it's pretty diff spray yeah but um
for example some people want to sell
something yeah and something person who
want to buy something yeah connect
together oh matching
app business business Tinder business
Tinder
yes stop saying Ming up
please it's it's a serious business
matching uh company you could say it
like that it's interesting oh I forgot
to uh loop this one too loop
loop H so we are here in Japan uh this
is off collab off cab this off cab this
is my first time off cab with
English and we had Yak yes right
before Yak Ori very it was so tasty
thank you oh yeah this time for once
like normally I get invited for uh F but
this time iot I I paid for her thank you
part two so so so delicious yeah now
it's my turn cuz I am stand
by yeah so Shark Tank just to
explain shark tank is the name of I
think most English speaking people know
but it's the name of a uh I think it's
American but also British uh in English
speaking television they have a program
[Music]
so it's like rich people Rich
CEOs and they sit in their fancy
seats entrepreneurs enter and they say I
have this product from my company and I
want you to invest because I need your
money and then they make some
deals I don't know how to
[Music]
say to to yeah I think so
yeah to give money ah yes yes
man yeah that's one of
like YouTuber
doing oh in Japanese it's not shark in
Japanese it's a a tiger tiger yeah why
is it always an
animal so you understand okay Mina
understand and uh I have some members
who are participating live and some
members who have you know time problem
time zone so they sent in a video music
a bit loud okay no problem okay okay and
so yeah our budget is yes5 million us
yay so many money of course we have more
oh but you know we have to be smart you
can't use all our
money million
[Music]
us sen may I go to some to eat some like
Yak more Yak by this budget no no no no
no no no no we have to
invest but you know we have to think cuz
there's many applications many many
entrepreneurs we cannot use all at once
okay and maybe maybe we have to fight
over someone okay let's fight let's
fight I not sure uh okay I think
currently there is not any live
participant here yet I think unless I
mean let me tell them that just in case
uh we are ready and you can come in if
there is not a presentation going on at
the moment
[Music]
yay I'm so looking forward to yes what
kind of product are you looking for oh
ideally what what you what are you
expecting today oh I want to pay for
things like that like um enrich my life
enrich your life yes oh wow yes that
would be great but you know you I think
you shouldn't only look for things that
you want but you have to look for things
that everybody wants yeah or maybe
something fun something fun yes yes yes
something that makes you think I will
get all my money back yeah no way oh how
about how about
you hi I
am I I hope to find a diamond in the
rough is that how you say it some
something where I I see like just a like
a pebble just a small Stone but I can
see oh it's a
[Music]
diamond I understand diamond in the
r i want to find a Genius Like Us yes we
genius I think maybe maybe many of the
entrepreneurs they don't know it
themselves so we will help them bring
out their geniusness yes together okay
okay so my orange haired friend until
now it was friendly but maybe we have to
fight orange hair orang orange ha orange
orange double orange double orangee okay
so we'll start with a pre-recorded one
um the only problem is or is is their
problem they cannot negotiate they will
have to accept the offer
[Music]
anyway
who do we start with M speaking of
stones and Pebbles and diamonds yes
let's start with Mrs uh beu from Advent
y whole life Advent yay Senpai oh
Senai that sounds so
weird okay I hope this works uh tell me
guys if it's too quiet or so let's look
at her presentation
Doo hello
shark hi my name is
co I am the founder CEO and president of
rock hard constructions rock hard
construction rock hard constructions
would like to present you for the first
time to the world our brand new
Innovative product
called
T the get good box a get good for a
bajillion
for
0.1% of our company now before
you we are asking for a bajillion
dollars a
0.1 oh small that's very small comp now
before you think wow that's a lot of
money for such a small percent wait till
you have heard our pitch because it's
about to blow your
mind
bra now judges first of all I have a few
questions for you have you ever been so
bad at a video game and wanted to get
good yes yeah yes have you been stuck on
a boss before have you been on a lost
streak yeah have you yeah have you just
died died so many times yeah yes and
just couldn't get
good getting good did you lose the
motivation or while you were trying to
get good have you ever raged quit
have
you questions then the get good box is
perfect for you now can you help us
wonder what exactly is the get good box
me well I have answers for you oh Mario
64 oh yeah the get good box is an
Innovative lock box where you can put
your prize possession inside and it will
not open until you beat sad goal that
you put into our get good software the
software is compatible with any game
that you are trying to beat be it you
know you got a 10 loss kill streak in
League of Legends that's compatible with
that you want to fight a certain uh
Souls boss that you haven't been able to
beat it's compatible with that too oh
what do you mean you know you aim to get
10 kills at I don't know League of
Legends wait I said that already
valerant yeah you put your valuables in
there at Apex Legend yeah that works too
connect it to any softare what does she
it to make it easier will not open the
box with your precious prize possession
inside until you have beaten okay so
it's just a safe Vu it's just a safe for
motivation it's just a save easy to use
software that connects to any game that
you're playing wow it is both USB and
Bluetooth compatible wow so efficient
and is also indestructible as an
indestructible Rock myself I have tested
this many times and I have gotten good
you cannot break it the only way to get
your prize position out is to
win to get
[Music]
good it comes in
medium large can fit a variety of
things can fit
jewelry sental value Jewel in there it
can fit some candy maybe you just wanted
to prize to get good as a medium box can
fitum cell phone that's always important
you don't want to lose your cell phone
oh you got a text well you can't check
the text unless you beat the boss yeah
what if you're hungry you can plant a
box of chicken nuggets or your dinner
chicken nugget speaking to me directly
for the L boxes they can fit like bigger
Electronics like laptops or game
consoles or even small animal yeah put
your pet hostage that's the motivation
uh don't worry um you know it won't it
won't suffocate cuz uh the large box
comes with air vent
air vents yeah so your pet
will probably still starvation or thirst
though so you should probably beat that
bot yeah whatever you want it fits it
comes in three sizes wow
amazing
threez and not only that but rock hard
constructions is also developing get
good box plus now with motivational
voice lines every time you die or don't
get closer to getting good uh a voice
voiced by Ki beu president of rock hard
constructions herself will mock you
you
ha get good
or but that's PR me is
uh you hungry you might want to beat
this boss soon because uh it's going to
starve if you don't that one is a large
box uh exclusive what it's going to
start isn't that amazing even more
motivation be your voice special version
special right now in production what I
hope you will invest in the get good B
so we will all get good
[Music]
together
y thank you for listening and you both
look beautiful oh thank beautiful thank
you oh God okay I I want to pay for you
but the problem is she wants a bajillion
dollars that's not even real it's
like thousands thousands of Millions for
0.00001% of her company it's not a good
deal no
[Music]
um wow I understand no um the good thing
is she's not here to uh discuss it so we
can make our
own proposal of budget uh and she will
have to accept
it so okay so what do you think but I
have a question about this yes content M
like see means like the books don't get
like give us some any good like special
[Music]
good no but no we cannot open the the
box so you cannot it's a box you put you
put for example you put your phone in
and everything that you want to use then
you close it and it connects with the
game that you're playing
so uh you cannot open it because it's
connected with the game until you get
good
[Music]
hostage so it doesn't really improve
your
skill yeah so it's it's like for for
controlling yourself
maybe if you don't have your
[Music]
phone what do you think do you think
this will be popular with the general
public the gamer
[Music]
public bad question but she said we are
beautiful so I want to pay for her how
much how much about paying 10,000 10,000
is that too much yeah well I mean if you
stay with
0.1% or so what she
said yeah we can we can invest small
amount and she has to say yes she has no
choice so you want a 10,000 yeah 10,000
10,000 oh she's investing yay we just
say by because I want to hear how cutie
boys
oh okay wait there
is
here yeah I think so this is 5 million
minus 10,000 right yeah oh meth wow y
congratulations shark
congratulations she has uh gotten her
first uh thing but investment but it's
not like it was hard because she wasn't
[Laughter]
here good job you have one one
investment in the Rock what was
it lock
construction no Lo
construction
yeah you can you can discuss further
with but how about
you but if you already investing I guess
we could
collaborate maybe okay because I think
she's asking for too much money but it's
not it's not a a useless
idea um okay I will I will join okay
same same same same so you get 20,000 B
yay
Y and maybe for her that is one vilon in
her
mind okay thank
[Music]
you good luck in your journey as an
entrepreneur maybe one day you'll be
like
[Music]
us okay okay okay so oh okay and let's
see Ollie said she would be ready soon
Ollie I'm ready for you if you're ready
doie doie doie or if she still needs
time we can
uh ladies good
evening wait wait wait wait I have way
too loud okay okay
okay okay welcome
Arie
Senai Hello nice to meet you thank you
for having me welcome welcome I lost my
voice because I was practicing the
presentation so
hard so
serious wow what is this okay okay I
will show you a presentation on the
screen
and I think like this
T oh wait I should show you probably as
well on Discord let me show you pleas so
you can you can guide us through your
presentation are you feeling
nervous honestly I kind of
am I kind of wish I had like a
whiteboard so I can actually pull it
down for you guys to invest that would
be nice too yeah maybe maybe next time
you can do it should I make her more
quiet guys chat chat chat still a bit
loud okay okay I will make her more
quiet and sorry it's I'm in the studio I
have different settings for me usual so
test test Ollie hello hello hello how
about now guys D make her louder
h no yeah it's fine okay okay let's go
Ali please impress the sharks with
your invention or so yes all right well
uh first of all thank you for having me
my name is crazy Ali from H life
Indonesia Second Generation and I am
here to bring you guys the verer 3000 so
let's go to the next slide for the
introduction verer
so you know what we've been in this um
we've had like a lockdown before and
everyone's kind of like working from
home now and you know with people being
so comfortable in their own homes they
don't really feed themselves that often
sometimes you would forget like do you
guys sometimes forget to eat when you
guys are working so hard on a project oh
not forget but I just I I just don't eat
yeah yeah no time no time exactly that
is uh and that is uh according to
scientist and according to studies not
good for you you're not supposed to skip
meals because it could actually lead to
so many other complications for your
health which is why you should not skip
them right I always skip my really my
dinner
dinner really I already eat lunch but no
dinner and no breakfast no breakfast
that's not good no that's not good good
because your body actually needs all of
the calories to go through your day
right because if you don't eat you don't
get the calories and you won't have the
calories to actually work
right yes yes yes which is why today I
bring you next slide please the verer
cute it looks like a toaster radio yeah
like
radio yeah so this is an invention that
I made so what happens you see the
really big tube on the right yeah so
you'll put your food inside whatever
food it is even if it's soupy even if
it's hot even if whatever it is it'll
convert it into bite-sized pieces and
then you see the little Nodge on the
left it will shoot and aim to your mouth
also we just open our
mouth
yeah but that still means we have to
like prepare something though it's it's
not all automatic so we still have to
think about it we have to buy oh no no
let me uh allow you guys to go to the
next slide
okay so you see uh one of the many many
Excellence about this product is that
first of all it can adjust bite sizes
and when you're thinking about bite
sizes that also includes soup so let's
say that you put soup inside what you do
what happens inside the machine is that
it will wrap it inside this edible wrap
and then it'll shoot to your mouth
wow what in a in an edible ah you mean
like ah like um like I I've seen it
before like edible paper or
plastic like that yeah oh so it doesn't
come out just as a
liquid no it won't spray your face
because everything is going to be bite
size and you can adjust it if you want
to maybe have like a bigger bite size
then you can just crank up that um Nodge
okay what are the the choking levels yes
so the joking levels actually means that
yeah there's a um it goes how fast the
food goes into your mouth oh speed speed
of okay so speed size and
temperature yeah because some LS people
like choking on hot pizza or maybe cold
pizza right yeah so it'll help you if
you actually want to choke on your food
I never choke on my food only I never
choke on my food but maybe some other
people guys do you have choke on your
food but I guess if you eat so
fast Japanese people eat so fast so
maybe they should slow down but they
couldn't they could make it fast too if
they wanted to with this machine speed
maximum speed
maximum exactly and it also has smart
aims so you just need to open your you
see that little red thing on the left
that is the sensor it will look for your
mouth whenever you open it for at least
two second and it will start aiming and
firing the food what if I don't want to
eat what if I'm just
talking what if I'm just having a
conversation with my dinner partner and
senses that my mouth is open for more
than two seconds and then it shoots in
my
mouth that is called a you problem a you
problem you didn't think of that you
didn't think of
that no no no it's it's just that you
see there there's an on and off button
so if you are going to stream then you
will naturally turn it off right okay
okay yeah yeah yeah and of course uh it
will tell you to eat it'll beep really
loud and it'll actually tell you hey
it's time for uh dinner or lunch and
then once you open your mouth then it'll
shoot okay it'll usually only feed you
during times like dinner time or
lunchtime or breakfast okay I see okay
is it
tasty it's tasty tast y because it
preserves the C uh the food's uh
temperature and it makes sure that you
have like the perfect bite size because
you know sometimes when you're eating uh
there's only like one perfect bite size
and everything else is just mid right
this machine make sure that every bite
is perfect okay but I still have to cook
no yeah
oh or like or like order
something and then put it in there right
oh yeah but you can like stock them up
so you will never have to forget okay
okay so you're saying is there also like
a a a refrigeration feature inside yeah
of of course there is of course there is
we can we can adjust the food
temperature so it has to have that cold
and hot feature inside okay okay okay
okay I see okay I see should I go to
next slide yes please oh
yeah this is just an introduction to our
team our team really thought about this
like super hard yeah you did mhm I
did ever nice team nice team could you
introduce your team to me yeah so let me
introduce you to CRA Ali the business
manager hello I am CRA Ali and I am the
business manager and next is CRA Ali the
head of
marketing hi I'm cra Ali the head of
marketing so crazy Oli the food
production
manager hi crazy
olly are you going to die I don't know
if I can trust a person with a voice
like that don't worry they're fine
they're working so hard on the project
that they lost their voice oh like Jia
wait which one are
you I'm of course the head of the
marketing oh okay sorry I couldn't tell
the difference I'm
sorry they look the same to me I hope
that's not insulting I'm so sorry it's
okay we get that a lot
okay okay next next side so it's weird
because I actually put a real um a real
graphic on here but when I sent it to
you it suddenly disappeared so I'll just
have to like uh explain it to you guys
it's a real graphic yeah we imagine the
real
graphic yeah so um uh are is the money
that you guys holding like USD or Yen
USD USD oh gosh uh I I'll have to
recalculate this because I actually
calculated
it that's okay that's okay yeah okay uh
if we're going by um Yen uh I'll have to
convert the yen to USD later but what
I'm asking from you guys is 800,000 Yen
which if converted to ID would be 83
million rupia and what we're trying to
do is that we're going to try and
distribute 20 units first we're going to
like test Waters and we want to sell it
out as quick as possible and just get
the word around first and then for um so
what we're going to do is that we're
going to use the 80 million to create 20
units and then we're going to sell every
single wait how much is that I need to
know now how much that is in US
Dollars uh wait uh 800,000
8,000 somebody says to
USD wait uh she did the math
$5,000 oh for 20 units okay okay that
sounds yeah but we can actually increase
it we can actually go for like let's say
uh 100 units that's also okay because we
will get the profit because how many
vtubers are there that actually
remembers to eat their food me and how
many YouTubers are there in the world a
lot so many yeah yeah so we will surely
get a profit with this one miss uh Miss
K only uh it's seems like you are just
aiming for a YouTuber audience but there
would be a much bigger Market I think
even outside of that market yeah there's
the streamer Market there's a work from
home Community also like you can
actually go for a lot of markets which
is why I'm very confident that
everything will sell out have you
perhaps uh because it seems like you
haven't even created the first product
yet but have you at least had like maybe
some polling uh between some people if
if they would be interested in a product
like this oh I actually have the
testimony already we had like one uh
product done uh unfortunately I cannot
send it over to you guys because we are
digital but if we move on to the next
slide I think we have the testimony
oh I think these look familiar to me
yeah so we have Miss Ki Oe that says
that you know what the aim is really
good for the Vater
[Music]
3000 looks
familiar no no no they're completely
different people there's also miss kigi
oi she says this machine chokes me to
Dreamland five stars what
wow wow kinky
lady she likes
exactly okay well it seems like they
really like it the product yeah seems to
have good good reviews but um if they
are verifiable or not I might have to
check behind the
scenes well I mean may maybe we can send
you a product um but it will take a few
business business days as we are uh
different countries
apart yeah that's that's okay well next
slide
yeah I believe is the ending I think
okay yes is this like scum s
[Applause]
SC would you like me to actually run
through with the with the uh what is it
called the statistic of the money the
money statistics oh you have money
statistics really yeah go like I said
we're going for like an 8 uh
800,000 Yen right which is if converted
to like Indonesian money it'll be 83
million and so the 3 million will use
for the marketing strategy and also like
uh the wrappings and whatnot and the
rest of the 80 million will put to
making like 20 units which we will be
making each unit will cost about uh 4
million to make in rupia Ria but we'll
be selling them for like five million
which makes it that if we did sold that
then we'll have like at least at least
okay at least at least we'll have like
uh 10% or maybe even 20% of profit and
revenue oh that's that's pretty low so
you're not you're not considering uh
shipping costs yet are you and like what
about returns when there's a failure in
the machine and you
know there's more to consider for
sure well um which is why you know the
bigger the uh investment I feel that we
can achieve a lot more so let's say that
I ask for like 800 uh thousand yen we
can just multiply that by five and then
we'll have more uh Bon uh you see most
of the money will go into like the
making of the machine right but the rest
of the extra money that will come from
it will be using it for like uh the
shipping the
marketing I guess it's acceptable 20% is
acceptable I
guess well uh I however there is
no you know you haven't tested the
waters yet with the production so I
cannot
immediately invest too much perhaps we
can start with the 20 units that you
have
requested right yeah wait what how how
much do you you wanted uh 5,000 Us doll
or so yeah uh 5,200 yeah okay 5,200 okay
it's not expensive at all that's not
expensive that's I guess even if it is a
scam I could get rid of that quickly
because that's how much I spend on on um
my daily dinner anyway holy
[\h__\h] well I am a rich CEO so of
course
what do you think yeah actually for me
if it's not scam if it's not
scam I be to pay for it because some I
always forget to eat some like food so
but to be honest it's just to like
developing items yes yes of course I
think most items that we're going to see
today are still under development though
yeah but which is don't you guys want to
like invest in an item that would
develop the fastest that would give you
guys the uh what is it called the
H what is
h the the the the the the you would see
the end card pretty quick with it you
know like you can see the well Ollie
results that's the one that I was
looking for I can I can quickly right
now make a poll with the literal
literally the whole
world in the chat and they can tell me
if if they want to buy this if we get
more than 50% I will invest whatever you
want maybe really
oh not whatever you want not whatever
you want a good amount a good amount
maybe well it's looking pretty good for
you oh oh co is raiding let's go oh
let's go hello co Raiders do you want to
invest in feeder 3,000 they're not
investing we're investors they're going
to be the future purchasers for buyers
bye bye bye okay where's my poll I can't
see it anymore there it is okay 69%
pretty high 69% is quite High 70 wow can
I get a 72 can we get up to 72% 7
auction
now oh yeah we got oh wait the one
it went down
no it was 72 just a minute ago okay oh w
w all the votes are not stopping oh [\h__\h]
there's so many 72
okay I will close the poll so how
much how much do you want only how much
do you really want so you know if we
actually let's say we create like about
um maybe we time it by five if we make
about like a hundred then we can just
maybe get about um I would I would ask
for
26,000 which isn't too much I would what
what what
currency uh in in USD I already
calculated Google
$26,000 mhm and maybe maybe if we round
it up make it like 30,000 so that we're
safe with the marketing and the sh do I
get a share of your company in
percentage yes about I would say I am
I'm very confident I would say about 30%
how would you
say okay wait wait wait wait wait
uh 30 what
30% yeah what of the of your 30% no of
the sales of the sales so so obviously
we're going to get profit right like
usually people would always go for like
10% but because I'm being nice and
because I want you guys to invest for
the better the future I'll give you guys
a 30% profit I would go for this yeah me
too 30% of profits yeah good only if you
can calculate for me how much I will
have left
over Mrs Math Genius 26 right 26 yeah
yeah yeah calculate but actually let's
just round it up to like
30,000 she's going up no no no no no no
no no no 26
but but the share would be 30% shut
up shut
up that's it it but how much is the 4
million n what what what is this minus
26k four uh help it's wor the no no it's
going to it's going to uh wait what all
right the 26 will be going for the
production cost and the selling and then
if we get like profit that means we'll
get about uh 50,000
is ah uh what no near 49 six uh
yeah9
64 okay I I'm buying it oh 49 64 okay I
think yeah I'm buying oh you you're
calculating that oh Oh I thought you
were calculating on how much profit
you'll be getting
oh
[\h__\h] yeah actually I want to pay more if
you if you improve this item like are
cooking system too yes yes yeah Cooking
System yes free I don't want to cook
anymore anymore yes no more that would
be a good uh addition in the future it
would be but it would really cost a lot
because the making of the product is
already pretty pretty costly I would say
okay how about I will pay
50,000 50,000 yes wait it should be
possible no I pay I pay
60,000
60,000 60,000 no okay 90 90,000
90,000 okay I oh but please give me 50%
over your company please
of the company all the profit
yeah how about
40%
45 45 for
90,000 how about how about
this this is last
chance cuz I already retracted my off I
already retracted I already retracted
because she's going for high amount I
cannot keep up with
it 45 sounds doable
45% wow okay okay it's a lot but I feel
like we would be able to feed a lot of
people 50,000 50,000 yeah 50,000 so 44
wait wasn't it 90,000 oh
yeah it's
90 yeah 4 z z z no I think 49 yeah
49 yeah I think
so oh no no no no 490 yeah 49
H one two three
okay okay we have a
deal okay thank you so
much congratulations
Oli thank you I I'm looking forward to
your future in this world in this
business World Good Luck Good Luck thank
you so much I appreciate it welcome best
of health see you guys okay okay see you
byebye
bye now I can finally buy all
of what is she buying what is she
buying we have a
[Music]
surprise wait I have
pictures guess who's
here okay sit
we have more chairs more
[Music]
chairs we have some baby
entrepreneurs yeah we're baby
entrepreneurs you have something to
offer uh yeah I send you email on
Discord what do these babies
have explain
explain what is
this our business name is
m
[Music]
don't we already
have
robot so it's a baby translation support
so you guys you guys want the baby
want that
means
nice
wow bye bye bye bye bye but uh uh I have
no I have no this this pacifier yet but
as a baby I understand it other baby
language but uh for Otona like
you you you cannot understand baby
language right yeah yeah yeah it's a big
problem right there so we yeah we make
this specifier so when your baby Google
gaga
gaga babab yeah for for example Google
gaga Hi how are
you yeah yeah it's a a artificial
intence right there yes yes and you can
you can modify your uh like uh your your
names here yeah it's very uh we're also
thinking about fashion too
[Music]
yeah this is what we over what how is
the um like how are you sharing the
company
50 5050 okay
50 ddy both 50 you 50 she
[Music]
50 fair fair fair business okay and have
you already produced any or is it not
created yet at all
m
okay because we don't have money to to
make of course of course that's fine
money no problem how much do you want
how
[Laughter]
much how much is
I
well how many do you want to create in
the first uh production
[Music]
round
many we need to
[Laughter]
discuss
oh it's
lagy
[Music]
baby they will understand YouTube what
the [\h__\h]
YouTu is it for
everybody is it
everybody come back I'm not not
investing in
YouTube YouTube
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh oh yes it's laging but they
understand what we're saying personally
good for
now okay
well I will
[Music]
invest
one what
100 100
90,000 US dollars so
[Music]
many please go with
me do you have an offer
about in my team lios there is also one
baby hor
baby don't understand what she's saying
yeah so can um adult babies can they
also use it or just real babies what
about adult baby
[Music]
like
[Laughter]
oh super ultra technology then that's
like worth a lot of money to then I want
to pay 200
[Applause]
no
200 200
20,000 mom I can't
pay I'm I'm top offer top offer
top uh 200 what 220 220,000 can you
convert it to Yen I don't
understand 220 wait wait wait I think
it's
[Music]
around I think I don't know maybe
maybe
[Applause]
so
[Music]
handshake we can shake hands Wow real
business nice business nice
business okay
byebye
[Music]
y nice investment for me um but very
expensive but I think worth the money
because this is a important product for
understanding babies so normal audience
but
also baby yeah so wait 20 I said 220,000
right so um
seven seven seven right yeah
[Music]
okay nice I am happy with this
investment might be the best today who
knows produced five babies four
babies they know what they're doing they
know what they want what they
need okay very useful very useful I
wonder I think oh Callie kimori CEO
might be next waku waku waku wak you're
open welcome to enter c if you're
listening welcome to enter now oh but
she gave me a f FY
Tech do you do you have just the gift
for me because I don't have fugie Tech
set up right
now wa wait k I have to make you a lot
more quiet because this is so loud
everything's so
loud okay say
something oh hello that's too quiet
hi hi can you hear me I can hear you can
you hear me my my dear my my good man my
dear my women my ladies can you hear me
we are your sharks hello H sharks yes I
almost called you
dragons I uh I I recently presented my
my products to um the dragons from
Dragon's Den uh they they didn't really
like my products very much they just
can't see my vision um that's okay
what's up with that well maybe see your
vision I know I don't know very strange
that they that they would reject them um
but I have a vision I'm so nervous I'm
shaking okay of course you would be
nervous in front of such successful
business people like us it's just noral
it's you guys are Inspirations to me h
wow yeah I worked really hard on on
these
inventions um and I'm hoping I'm hoping
that you guys will see uh my vision my
vision as well as as I do um these
products have they have I have the
patents for all of them by the way so no
stealing from anyone in the chat No
Stealing I will I will show it on screen
now this is your presentation right yes
yes please go ahead and impress us
otherwise we might not invest okay I'm
quite sure I'm quite sure that my my
inventions will tickle your fancy one of
your fancies
yes yes because I'm I'm quite dead
serious about this I'm quite finished
with reaping okay and I would like to um
invest in the the future of new
technology so first I have but a very
simple question for you ladies do you
love
sweets sweet sweet swe yes H that's the
answer that I I wanted to hear
okay we can do this yesy yes yes I I too
indulge in in a sweet here and there all
of that delicious sugar is so uh
tantalizing it it really is um it really
is the spice of life or rather the
sweetness of life so true next slide
however do you find that when you
indulge in too many sweets your teeth
begin to take on a strange color a bit
of a taint suddenly your friends don't
want to speak with you because your
mouth it's it doesn't smell very
good okay okay okay the the sugar has
has found its way to co your
te no no no my my good women no no this
is much much more than simple Dentures
you see I provide a solution unlike any
other next slide because if you don't if
you don't take care of of your pearly
whites after indulging in sweets you
could end up like this child or your
child could lose their teeth and you
could wonder where did I go
wrong as a parent go wrong yes exactly
that's why you've got to take good care
of your teeth and so next slide where'd
you get that background
from love I pay for a
subscription I'm glad that you like it I
put a lot into my presentations the next
slide says introducing
the neverbe seen life-changing product
that will have you smiling for more next
slide introducing the smile
scrubber patented property of myy kop
this looks like sushi sushi it does it
doesn't it it's quite a cute design it's
shut up sh shut up shut up chat shut up
no no no no no no next next slide let me
introduce to you why this product is so
is so important you use it twice a day
once in the morning and once in the
evening and what you do is you you take
the the smile scrubber and you put it on
your teeth and you move it back and
forth and back and
forth it it that sounds oddly familiar
to a product
that the
world I don't know what you could be
just go to the next slide please I don't
know what you could be talking
about see exhibit a exhibit a look I'm
sure I can change your mind about this
this is never a never before seen
project nasty teeth next slide what do
you do with a smile scrubber you rub it
back and forth back and forth yes and
then next slide next slide wow would you
look at that I love my smile scrubber
look at that clean teeth Callie yes Mrs
Cali entrepreneur isn't this hard to
hold wouldn't it be nice to have
something attached to it to hold it
I'm up for negotiation I have patents on
this design so this is the design that I
am pitching to you next slide please so
we can read the testimonials the
testimonials amazing it cleans my teeth
like no other product ever has my
manager wrote that um then there's you'd
be a damn fool to turn this product of
the future down that was me um okay
check this out from cover staff
themselves hella economical lasting
product my everything why did they why
did they C capitalize it like that I
don't understand why they did that help
me help me help help
[Music]
me check this out Anonymous deadbeat
says nothing else like it on the market
it it does what it's designed to
do just don't worry about
it wait is the is the the the rice
looking part is it made out of rice
bristles they are bristles made out
bristles and plastic okay plastic let
see yes plastic for the the main body
and then bristles so that they are
designed to get in between your teeth
when you rub it back and forth it does
look like they're like a katar like
they're struck together how are they
going to get between the
team that is true I I have another look
all right A lot of people are saying
it's a toothbrush I have another
I don't know what they mean I have
another product that may tickle your
fancy oh yes is it also in here yes it
is I I came with backups oh there a
backup okay okay okay okay okay all
right I backup if unlikely okay next
next
one unlikely I'm sure that they thought
it was great okay next slide next slide
next do you have do you have too many
papers yes I [\h__\h] do I see I can WR
you know me too well I do are you are
you
unorganized I try not to be but I guess
I am yes
yes yes I can relate also stressed out
from too many
papers yeah CEOs have that problem
indeed if you go to the next slide you
may see very
relable how can I keep all of them
together a product that no one has seen
before
product how can I keep them all together
if you go to the next slide
introducing see I'm sure you don't I'm
sure you've never seen it before if you
go to the next it's the paper taper
patented P property of moric kopy only
the brand new all new brand brand new
product if you go to the next slide
you'll see how it works uhoh
unorganized what shall we do about that
oh man well if you go to the next slide
you see how the paper taper works it
puts it
together
she how did it do
that stop putting paper clips in the
Chad shut up R this for me genius idea
well it took a lot of time brainstorming
you know if you go to the next slide
you'll see actually the scientists at
Mor Labs were working tirelessly um
putting together you know this the
science behind holding papers and
we can see there is a direct correlation
between papers held together improving
quality of life brilliant Chad you're
correct so so what are we thinking what
are we thinking about the about the uh
the paper taper can you go back to home
now no listen my dear sharks listen my
home is where I develop my inventions
I'm sure you're asking me to go work on
some more inventions surely oh
I have another I have something
else okay I get I have another okay all
right all right this is I have I have
one more invention okay look if you
don't want the paper tape or Last Resort
if they don't like the first two it's
very low chance all right well it seems
we're here now so we just have to roll
with
it all right next slide are you
thirsty yes I am yes me too well who
isn't mean yeah who doesn't need a
little H2O next slide please do you want
to go outside and communicate with
society and contribute to humanity but
going outside means being separated from
your only water
source my only water source yes yes at
home is where you get your
water true the water bottle KY want on
the water bottle I've never heard of
that word in my life go to the next
slide sources say that if you don't
drink water you
die do you want to die Kara you're
little [\h__\h] cie you little [\h__\h] do you
want to die Kiara I'm ask it's okay if I
die I'm a phoenix you know that you know
that you played Final Fantasy 16 that is
true well all of this can be avoided
with the help of a brand new patented
product that is origin toy K only
introducing introducing what could it be
what could it be is it a container to
hold water just go for the next
slide H introducing what's the next
Slide the hydro holder patented by me no
one else owns this no one else owns this
it's the hydro holder the is much better
than okay oh anyway anyway anyway never
go to the next slide please
let me finish explaining my invention
enjoy sports take it anywhere okay it
holds your water and get this it keeps
it from falling out
so pretty great right so so thought of
it all myself what material is this well
if you go to the next slide you'll see
that the plastic material it's it's
durable but it's easy to mass produce
okay so water goes in the economical
Square shaped entrance look at staying
inside
and the closed bottom assures that the
water doesn't fall out what about the
square opening
I look I'm working on a on a plug to put
in the Square we don't I mean look it's
a work in progress the scientists have
been very busy working on the other
inventions okay there's just a lot
there's a lot that goes into
this yeah there an opening no no no but
we can we can all we can if I just need
I really need money to fin to finish
this invention I just don't have enough
I spent it on the other two that you
guys didn't
like is there more to this another SL no
no this is this was it this was it this
was my last this was my last
shot okay what do you think um I can pay
for you three
doll one each no no no no no for
everything yeah one okay yeah okay well
what what about percentage of my company
because you know if you do give me a
dollar to produce these things you know
I'm sure you want a percentage of my
company what do you think because this
will make money no what I think is I am
not paying anything for any of your
products but I do happen to own a a a
television
um uh Broadcasting Service uh that is
called ki's Comedy Central and I thought
instead of selling these products I will
buy this presentation and your your
person off of you and are you making a
fool out of me no no I'm making a
comedian out of you are you laughing at
me at my but I produced very seriously I
was thinking no listen this is my my my
Giga Ultra uh uh Universe brain that's
speaking here um but I think all this
whole presentation could make an insane
amount of money as comedy
material so I would buy these
presentations just the presentation not
the products just the presentation and
your services as a comedian for um per
let's say per
broadcast uh I I can pay you $1,000 US
dollar oh that's
good
yes
do you hear
this everyone
okay if Mor Pie singing for me no I will
pay
20,000 one
song you know that you will you will
this business will fail right she's
trying to create so you will lose all
your money for nothing love serious
thing okay for me everyone either 10,000
per episode on the on the KF uh kfp
Comedy Central Broadcasting Service or
you get 20,000 from
L um and you have to sing for her but
obviously your products are doomed I
will stream it streaming yeah not just
for me but streaming oh so basically
you're making a contract with the devil
which Isa sh she's the devil because she
will make you sing forever for the rest
of your life ah okay here's an idea how
about this final offer ditch the comedy
angle three bus tokens a paper clip and
some pocket lint can we can we close on
that one more time what did you just
offer us three bus tokens a paper clip
and some pocket
L wait the paperclip could basically
replace uh your paper taper I don't know
what you're talking about paper cool
than a paper clip way cooler than a
paper
clip wait for for how much money oh we
are we giving it to you yes three bus
tokens of pocket lint and a paper clip
okay I'll take
it what but but no comedy and no making
fun of me no
but I'm buying it she she wants no money
no money I'm buying it I buy okay all
right final offer deal yeah but you
promis me to not produce these products
at all absolutely
not oh it's okay cuz they call just so
Mrs entrepreneur these products already
exist did you know what no no I have a
patent on them that can't be
possible I I have they're
copyright no I have the rights I have
the rights you might have been scared
but let's you can do what you want as
long as I'm not losing money on it and
just paper clips and paper lint and
whatever well I I just I really need a
bus token to go home is the main thing I
just I need to catch the bus to go home
and I don't have a bus token
so ever breath her teeth because she
doesn't know the teeth breath
right I don't know what it what that is
she she does she F I only used the smile
scrubber are new yes all
new yeah smile scrubber I've been using
the smile scrubber for five trillion
years many billion years yes I came up
with it and I've been using it for many
many many years then they might have
stolen your idea smile is perfect
oh well yes I okay I'm I'm I'm fine with
giving you what you need uh it seems
like you have done pretty badly in
Monopoly uh so okay well you g you're
making my bad day
worse please just give me my bus token
so I can go home okay okay I'll I'll
I'll do you uh one better I'll send you
an Uber okay thank
you yes please okay Uber is coming to
you Miss entreprene Miss cal cal preneur
thank you you're going to need to take
about 20 bucks off of your budget
though oh I think I have those things
lying around you know but the Uber yeah
I'll take I'll take uh the the 20 bucks
for the Uber oops out of there just
letting you know just letting you know
okay thank you thank you for your time
ladies I'll go I guess I'll go talk to
the dragons next month again I'll try
with the dragons again good luck I wish
you the best on your journey um but I
still recomend and you becoming a
comedian keep it in mind just keep it in
mind well I take offense to that but
thank you anyway and have a lovely
evening thank you very much for your
time freeze please
[Music]
please please hire me to make my
products
could now go home go bye bye thank
you oh my God so good that was so
a lot that was a
lot so funny
nice wow I love it I'm impressed I am
stunned I am amazed uh if there's
someone waiting to call in uh please uh
come in otherwise I will just go for uh
one that we have
[Music]
prepared oh
oopsy no anything I don't
know
hello well hello
hello hello
welcome
[Music]
hello welcome
entrepreneur John yes I am I am meisa
from the mie Corp here to presentate
about my
Pro okay um just so we clear this up B
since you are a whole life Japan member
you Excuse
me yes you are I mean I mean what I
don't know what you're talking about
what else is your explanation for making
the presentation in Japanese even though
I said it should be English sorry I
thought the room was going to be in
Japanese cuz you were collect no y she
is she is fluent in English so we are
doing
English it's okay I added I I I added
English pointers thank minute thank okay
what do you have for us Mrs entreprene
Ana entrepr okay um let's get to the
point already you guys can already see
what's the concept of the product it's
called a h slim H man
slime what
this
cuz cuz it's cute it's it will be a
slime but Holo Holo life members themed
oh you know okay yeah let's see what
this is all about okay okay so h m
slimes twist about it it's actually
eatable
what N I never eat slime yeah is it
sweet um I never ate one too but I think
I think there's going to be yeah there's
going to be flavors and stuff there's
going to be different flavors you know
like yeah yeah that's just that's just
uh that's just slime there yeah yeah
yeah
okay okay it's eatable and then my
appeal point and why I'm I'm choosing
this concept for my product is
that yeah um so for example like um
objects like the other people have been
presentating they can actually be a hit
or miss but food food is something that
humans need food will not lose its
Market food will always have its Market
everyone will buy food cuz like humans
need them to stay alive you know but
tell you get my point not very like you
know it doesn't f me much you know like
it's just
like yes I love
yes we
love yeah they're good to eat yeah yeah
people can just eat like you know heavy
food people people also eat like snacks
okay but how are they whole Al members
is their face on there yeah it's going
to be it's going to be there's going to
be their faces and there's going to be
there's going to be their color
responding to our colors so for example
Kias will be orange you
[Music]
what is
this yeah if you eat this you're gonna
you're going to be very very motivated
to live your life oh my God I feel so
motivated I'm going to work out I'm
going to I'm going to run for like how
many meters today I'm going to work out
oh my God I'm I'm so
today at work I'm going to finish this
work and then and then go home early oh
my God maybe even even you'll you'll
find like your love life will exist too
oh my gosh you can Bond you can bond
with other people who who eat like the
whole life slimes
[Laughter]
still want to support that but
no explode explode all all dating
couples oh my
God mar mar s because you said if you
eat like this jery I mean horror man dri
the people like go crazy right no did
you put any like going crazy getting
motivated does not equal to being crazy
yeah no is something positive in your
life
Mar I want a mar
too
okay next
slide what this okay oh my God and so
cute they're cute so they can be they
can be used for
selfies but get sticky when I hold it on
my head and on my hands sticky sticky no
you're not going to hold it in your hand
you're going to have it like above your
head it's going to be more more you know
more pose you're going to be more posing
with the
slime a t from girl
[Laughter]
a she got she got how many 100,000
followers from uh taking a selfie with
this jelly
yeah 100 thousands followers more than 1
million followers from taking a cute
selfie with the cute Hol
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
life
more more English
go I'll go then I'll explain after
that spook that's good for us because
hor will come to our Dream right it seem
do scary things or my but you don't want
to waste food right you don't want to
waste food oh what is Callie saying yeah
they should actually taste like the
members oh my God oh my God will they
taste like the members Anya well only
one way to find out and that is you need
to find this
product yeah and so there's like there's
people who are like but it's a food of
my oan I I can't eat it like you see you
usually see it with like for example
latte art latte art of your ooshi and oh
my gosh I I can't drink this but you're
supposed to eat your food
yes really quickly have to put our heads
together so right now right now we
barely spent any of our money so um just
for the sake of making the stream more
interesting I don't want to invest in
this but can you invest like three
million into this product just so that
we can get the numbers down you know
that will be more interesting okay okay
okay okay but I know it's it's not
interesting the product not interesting
but we need to spend money okay we're
back we back
back no I think we have black company
moment for a second what do you think
what do you think they was speaking
opportunity for you Ana big
investment but let me let me explain and
so please you're supposed to eat this
slime if you don't it will appear in
your dream it's okay you don't have to
convince us anymore because L is very
convinced yes I love it what about you K
what about
theond um it's because shato is going
for such a huge offer that I could not
possibly top it she she's offering a big
money right right please don't be
surprised okay I will paid 1
million 1 million I said I said 3
million I said 3
million
million just 1 million okay okay milon
million million 3 million finally yeah
but okay can
I can I have but but please please
promise me please make Lily slime more
than the other hor man slime
okay my color yeah yeah this is going to
be this is going to be so successful you
know cuz cuz Okay
um yeah it will and make black box black
so I mean like a secret box like let's
put it The Rock Bo from box made us a
box we put the jelly into the box okay
and okay I mean I'm open with
collaborating with other companies ni
that's that's
good okay you get free million that's
almost all of her fre million mhm US
[Laughter]
dollars
we already
have you don't need how can you be so
greedy you already get three million
that's the biggest
ever actually I didn't want to buy it
but K
said so yeah you have to take what you
can get you know I'm helping you out
here I'm supporting you with the Senai
PR so
[Music]
scared you'll regret not investing in
we'll see about that take your free
milon and go I love
you I love you
too go go go byebye take your for
million okay
oh my God I love anai I love her too
but she wanted more than we shouldn't
have started so high we started too high
so she thinks it's low but it's really
high yes it's it's very high very high
but I don't want slime no slime no slime
no slime okay we have uh two more
present
but they are uh pre-recorded ones so I
think no more no more Callin I think
okay okay okay
okay and I still have a lot of
money well I hope something good is GNA
show up
[Music]
now I'm F St I'm here sticking
7 and
Shar
t Okay Okay Okay
restart hi fellas I'm fesia St I'm here
seeking
$700,000 for 7% equity in this product
called zamin Believe It or Not s by I'm
really smart am I right girls oh my God
my
God and it's all thanks to this product
called zamin this product makes you 100%
smarter prove it to you I can answer all
these questions really fast 99% of the
human population have trouble answering
these questions maybe you should try and
see if you're part of that 1% let's see
728 - 79 + 468 * 0
23 answer questions really really fast
all right now it's sent by T's turn to
see if you are indeed in need of some
zamin urgently all right let's test our
IQ together 2 +
2 we don't need time the answer is fish
what about 1 +
1 the answer is
23 * 2 -
65 63 the answer is 23 don't worry if
you have trouble answering these very
difficult questions in by that's why I'm
here to offer you this product zamin
with this you can answer the questions
within 5 seconds or even less people all
around the world would be amazed by you
so what are you waiting for what are you
let's go click this link for more
information on this product scam scam
scam scam scam scam
scam
um I think everything like because 200
IQ right IQ 200 become 200 IQ place of
scam scam yeah scam yeah because 2 plus
two is not fish no no was the 20 the
free 23 answer was that even correct you
guys got to tell us but did I mean that
was a a high quality production video
advertisement
video but yeah I love the
[Laughter]
video would you would you invest in
this um if I drink Zeta me then if I can
speak English more fluently I will drink
it oh but we would have to test it right
ideally I want to drink but you have so
many money yes too much money why don't
you use it I guess not a big deal throw
out some stuff for a scam yeah no
problem because
okay okay I can go what I pay 1
million
because that Senpai is so
cute I okay I will pay I will make a
bigger offer I will pay 2 million can
you have 2 million hey I don't have I
don't have enough money to one oh no no
way oh no I guess it's it I mean it's
[Music]
mine you said hey you three three
million No 3 million doll for it well
you know why okay because we we are not
friends we are enemy in the business
World
enemy I will become the biggest oil
Baron in the whole wide world and you
will not stop me okay but we have one
last investment to do thank you da
entrepreneur I'm looking forward to
being scammed for2 million us do let's
go I I protected
you that's true yeah it's better it's
better to buy slimes than the yeah
that's true believe trust
me okay you're welcome welcome I have
one last investment opportunity okay we
might as well spend it all but uh it
better be a good one I think the audio
is not correct on it though so
it's it's a good item I hope so I hope
it will be useful for a wide br
audience okay the tuning fork a musical
Delight with every bite we all live such
busy lives that it's sometimes hard to
take a break and get some food and when
you do want to eat your choices in
utensils aren't that neat aren't you
tired of your forks having four prongs
when did something so simple feel so
wrong don't you wish your fork could do
more what if we could make eating fun
well do I have the perfect product for
you hia Darlings my name is nerissa
Raven craftt and I would like to
introduce you
to the tuning fork made with proprietary
demon Magic The Tuning Fork allows you
to listen to my voice while you eat to
your voice with the tuning fork every
bite you take sends my dlet tone
straight to your brain so you'll want to
eat lots to hear everything I have to
say imagine being able to hear me cheer
you on while you finish your plate a
gate with your green congrats with your
carrots or a song with your soup eat
wouldn't that be amazing never want to
use any dull Cutlery again or maybe you
don't just want to hear me at home well
no worries because every tuning fork
comes with a cute carrying case so that
you can take it along wherever go you
can even show off your fork to your
friends and family and let them know you
hear your osi's voice in your
head buy the narissa Raven cross for the
low low price of $19.99 plus shipping
and handling however if you're one of
the first 50 buyers you will also get
the narissa suon so don't delay order
now to get your very own tuning fork
today there will be a spoon yeah a spoon
too that's nice oh she gone now she's on
byee she's just
[Music]
okay oh no let's show this okay
okay what do you think what is your
impression actually I think it's good
for just
interior I mean decoration yeah
decoration stuff oh yeah
um you know the the interesting thing
though is she is um very
um strongly passionately selling it as a
eating utensil uh as a fork but she says
that the music that you hear and the
voices that you hear they're only in
your
head so maybe the focus shouldn't be on
using it as a eating utensil the focus
should more be on having a device like
headphones that only you hear and there
is no no way for any uh noise
to because it's only in your
[Music]
brain unique yeah I
agree this YouTube channel yeah
subscribe
I think if we're doing if we're going to
do if if we could do a little bit of a
rebranding uh obviously you're gonna say
yes to everything I ask of
you okay then I want to pay everything
everything
yeah so 1 million
n 1.9 million 1.9 million no it seems
like you and you go last on this program
um you get the biggest or or not
necessarily you get the the remaining
money if it's much then you're lucky if
we already spend a lot of money then
it's not much may I bring it back to
home the money if I li the
budget may I use it for
y no uh we we must maybe invest in more
things off screen oh yeah we make more
Investments but I will invest in this
but I want uh narissa I want 90% of your
company 90% 90% 90 90 90 oh my God yes H
but I will um give you uh 2.76
n980
million US
dollar so you get all all of my money
but I get 90% of your company so I get
like pretty much all of the decision
making and uh just give it to me and and
oh yeah uh I I guess I'll take um your
hand in marriage too maybe my
[Applause]
God so I I I'm taking it
[Music]
um okay 1% for 1.9
million s not good
oh I need more than 10% more than 10 but
I already have 90% you can okay how
about I 90 you 10 n a zero a zero okay
that's that's
great good deal goodal can't
can't no we friend
[Applause]
not we W
narissa yay narissa can now go
bankrupt
bankrupt bankrupt oh how to say I
[Music]
will well we had some lovely
entrepreneurs here today I didn't forget
one hope so yes yes yes should be fine
should be fine thank you very much for
participating in the Hol of CEO shark
tank thank you and uh from now on I I
know I said we're not friends but only
during this U program we're not friends
but in reality we're friends
okay I love I love I love I
love we we will go on many business
Endeavors from now on together yes
I don't even
understand no no don't understand Mor is
fuming
what she is she are you in the Uber
Kelly Uber I've been waiting for you
for Kelly it was so funny
Best comedian uh ever like my God you
should you should be on Saturday Night
Live Cy that's your new career path I
would say forget being an
entrepreneur maybe this show can also
help people realize that they shouldn't
be making anything any products ever you
know I don't know about Ana to be honest
um I thought she was going to maybe um
suggest
shoes
it was slime I thought it would be shoes
for her yeah because she's Barefoot I
would have been interested in in buying
her shoes or or or you know what she
could have done she could have created
like Souls that because I've seen that
actually before in real life like SS
that you put on on under your feet so
you can walk
barefoot yeah that would have been good
but of course such genius ideas only
come to Geniuses like us like you know
that's why you need to get us involved
so that we can help you make better
decisions in your life so that one day
you can become rich CEOs like us yes
like us it's not easy it's not easy not
easy not
easy okay thank you everybody thank
you thank you very
much on sorry sorry everyone my English
is poor but still it was so fun thank
you so much good English more
more I want to study more in the morning
the street more thank you she also took
so many notes yeah I took
many oh I was looking forward to
delivering the fun project with K yes
that's my Meo to
say
[Music]
I am I a chip skate so I don't things
oh yes me too me too I also cheap skate
I don't even use that word chip skate
chips skate chips K chips k k k in
Japanese me too me too yes okay so these
uh CEO cheap skates we'll leave you guys
now thank you for watching and in German
we say
[Music]
yay byebye
byebye deal deal
deal
[Music]