[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [
Music]
no  de
[Music]
Hum
さえ
[Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music]
hi [Music] o y [Music
]
[  Music]
y
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [
Applause] [Applause] [
Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
w
finally
3D
how anime is really not noisy
y'all put it  first,
it's
hard OK then that's how it is
on my small island, it's
just a small hut, there
's a boat there, yes, there's a boat.
The thing is, Kobo usually moves from island to island,
because there's a lot of Kobo in Merciswar,
not just on this island, look at
it, it's really high, but yeah  Yes,
you saw it at the beginning, but
what is it, it's
really tall, so it's a bit of a chili there,
so I'll just show it to
you later, okay, okay, then outfit check
OTD, check okay, that's shoes shoes shoes Look
at my shoes Look at my shoes uh  the
details uh uh there are details uh uh you
can see
[Music]
no e then the usual yes then there are
uh jackets yes gocap get three at the
night market Just modify it a little, give the
brand name the Shan range, it's really cool,
so it looks like it's expensive too.  You know, it looks
expensive all the time. Yes, the rest is just trifting.
sor Soror sor hang on a minute I have to go to
school first ah Cilus Please
help Cilus I Cilus help me ah father's motto
I'm afraid I don't want to be late Ah Quickly paint
my father's eyes draw a picture Ah I'm afraid of being
late hurry up hopefully I'll have time
uh finally get to class there's
something for you guys  Is there a Ril who
feels that falling in love feels like it's
blooming?
How does it feel
like it's not tickling
my heart when
your scent passes through my nose,
my eyes water when I see you pass in
front of me? Just an ordinary person. Is it appropriate to
be
with you overing but I don't want to
bother?  because I'm not you, it's
better to win Oh
Asmara,
I'm close to you Oh
Asmara, hear the whispers of love,
your eyes hit
my heart
[Music]
Asmara
feels that these
days, she still can't get close to you,
uh
How to melt
your frozen heart, it's better to give up Oh, of course
not, for the sake of our dreams, we have to keep
learning  learn to understand your
love language Oh
Asmara I'm trying to
feel like I'm near you Oh
Asmara hear the whispers of love in
your eyes Oh
Asmara respond to the signal of
my wishes just once
Oh
Asmara is there no room in your heart
H left
[Music]
for me that afternoon
you were the first to come
to me, come to me  Oh
Asmara
feels like I'm near you Oh
Asmara hears the whisper of self-love
[Music] in
your eyes Oh
Asmara
feels like I'm near you Oh
Asmara hears the whisper of Love Five
Oh
[Music]
Asmara Oh
Asmara has answered it all already
[Music]
your words because now I have
become  what
[Music] is
mine
yours
[Music] is
hii congratulations r congratulations R hang on
that's why there's why there's this cardboard board what are you
doing? Meet your
new boyfriend what's his name
Eh who is this? No, I don't know, but he's
handsome, isn't he?  I really know, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, bro, it's
not like that, but it's normal for
guys to be like this. Hello, guys who
are like this usually have something to do, what do
you want, don't listen to
him, Ayang, don't listen to him, no, no, no,
no, no, no  Ayang nah
Ay are you listening to me or not eh ay
what Eh
I can't do it anymore A I don't
want to
G
nah that's better to listen I'm
better off listening I used to not be
able to be like this El that's why it's better for
you to be flattened so it's the same ah it's
hard-  It's hard to wait for Rid's debut, eh, it's still
flat again, that's all, that's all, there's no need,
there's no need to make a fuss when it's cardboard like this, it's
not cardboard, that's enough, that's enough, that's enough, that's enough, that's all, I'm sorry,
for your sake,
it's better for you to focus on Rimu, I'll take this with you
first, OK, bye
bye cheer up
R no don't girlfriend I aniani
suisui
[Applause]
[Music]
て
k
[Music]
Yi
iss Yeah
[Music]
Yeah I love you love love love love love love love love
love you  love love love love love
[Music] [
Music]
love love baby love baby
[Music]
loveab love [Music
]
for [Music] [Music] [
Clapping] [Music
]
love you love you love you Love Love Love Love Love
Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love
Love
[Music]
[Applause]
Love I love
you
[Music]
yeah
oh ah so son son What's going on why are
you crying are you so sad We just sang a
great song  together come
on your heart Hurts but why my boyfriend
sit it on me he goes for zetta wait wait
hold on a moment you have a you have a
boyfriend tell me who He is tell me
where He is and I will take care of
everything Dad will  take care of
everything for you coule I don't know I
don't know his name but I love him Um
What Um I don't really think I
understand but it's okay it's okay son
looks sometimes things in life Just They
just don'  t go your way but it's all
right You'll be okay I promise no no no
I I can't I can't take this
anymore here Kids Man
here Gun K I can't I can't do that I
can't do that  you're my
sonak all right right Well it's my job
after all So I guess I'll do it if you
insistobo pick a place where you want to
perish I think I will maybe here all
right stand really still say your
prayers
to me SH  me that rest in
peace doing my
job What happened here KY What did you
do Oh I mean I I didn't do anything all
right look all right Hold on I know what
it looks like Look I shot I shot her
with a water Gun all right  with with a
water Gun Look it's not Lethal or
anything she De She just
playing You should be teaching her stuff
like this you know Kids kar look
only Come
on we fail his parents I wonder Come on
[Music]
live come on Yes come back to  me
come Mommy yes yes yes sorry mommy It's
Okay It's okay oh Kobo it Took you long
enough Come on get up before Dady Gets
in
trouble Oh my
God I'm back mother
father well thank God what happened Kobo
What happened My boyfriend on
me Who's  your boyfriend Where is he I
Said Uh I don't know his name but I love
him listen here you little [ __ ] forget
about him Mommy is here Let's just have
fun together Okay have fun let's
go yeah let's go Sounds like fun you
guys Um I  'm coming too right i'm invited
right you go buy milk milk really for
breakfast milk yeah again we need it
yeah byebye by
whatever co come on
[Music]
I want to be
president so I don't get php guys
[Music]
anymore
[Music  ]
[Music]
[
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [
Music]
ST
SH p p
[Music]
p thank
you
yay I'm good now Thank you oh oh I'm
happy to  hear that but you know Mommy
has to go home now and rest but I will
sleep and dream about
you let's go
so I you I you
bye Okay she now So m does know that I'm
not home yet Ok I w show you guys
something Aku  I want to show you something that's
really cool, really cool, really cool, a trick
using my R
power at
this
ah uh ah am am
am Wow
H Weh it's raining, really crazy, really cool,
lenanoarata. That's really cool, isn't the water
like that, then it starts to
rain, ah, this is also the first  time you
guys see my jelly fish Umbrella
right By the way
every time you send a super
chat It
will give more power to the ya  It adds power
like an amplifier like that. Yes, that's how
you understand. Yes, it's only the power of the
sound of a kobok, right, that can
make rain like this, eh. We thank
you for the super chat. I've arrived, I've
arrived. It's a calf, it's quite a while,
guys, I haven't showered yet,
bar.  at the same time wash your face nice thank
you
aatoah
eh why add a lot yes yes
thank you thank you But I can't swim
Eh I can't
swim just a moment slowly send super
chat Okay relax
frogs like kok
[Music]
k
Thank you Thank you
for Thank you for this love thank you okay thank you
[Music]
you
my P
hur finally went
home ah luckily wearing Jan luckily my
outfit is waterproof oh by the way
welcome welcome to my
light this is inside Mer suar aku
ih me  a little bit OK, let's go do a
quick room tour OK, so there are
stairs here because MIRC my voice is
really high, actually, that's all, OK, never mind, just
here, L, just on this floor,
we'll go upstairs later, okay,
then usually  After school I went
straight to bed and went straight down, but yes,
because I brought guests here,
I'll just do a room tour, right?
Oh, this is called ayamaadas, right?
OK, continue, this is the usual place where
lots of food is taken.
So, if you want to relax, I'll go with my
friends who I usually loot with, well,
what else is there, there are these dolls,
lots of dolls. Sorry, yes, then there's this,
there's Fajri Kipli Kupli, let's be absent for now.
Yes, there's Rio, there's Rai, there's Ryu, yes, there's lots,
bro.  really, guys, then there are several
instruments in my collection, like
one of them is a piano, a keyboard, the keyboard is the same, and
there's e. Where I usually stream
here, what's there? There's a monitor,
but I was just using the TV, so I was
relaxing for a while and then A, I see there's a
catfish and the same thing.  Then there's the same refrigerator, there are
two instruments that I often play,
namely the electric guitar and the acoustic guitar,
don't you think I play the acoustic guitar more often? Well, the one
I played earlier was the
electric guitar, yeah. And then there's the violin, this is
rare and rare, right? S  here's
this plant Hm the pitcher plant has already
reproduced a lot H this is
OK, you guys. Look what the
ceiling is, ah, the ceiling I have
cute lights on top,
wow, the lights keep going on. What's wrong with
the ceiling, it's really cute, isn't it?
How is it? How beautiful is my room like
the owner is not? Yes, I saw Kak
Kobo. Please try playing the
[music]
instrument. I'm kind and not
overbearing. Fortunately, I'm not loud.
I'm good. I'm good. OK, that's fine, you're
here, okay, let's go to the design, I want to
Take that guitar, OK, I'll just play the guitar
and take off my jacket.
Wait a minute OK, wait here for a moment
OK
OK, OK, I'll request buculbucul k
play the guitar k guitar,
this is a melodious song,
OK, what do you think about it? Yes, you
definitely know how to sing.  together yeah who knows
the song we bang together okay
[Music]
bir h
h
[Music]
me
せ
[Music]
men [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music]
si
mこ 忘
[  Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
て
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
та
to
Han
[Music]
Kim
k
[Music]
n
a little wrong it's okay l
yeah a little  wrong sorry sorry I Made some
mistakes because I'm so nervous This is
my first time in 3D life singing singing
with actic guitar the pressure is
different from from the US karaoke you
know you know sorry sorry I'm
nervous,
that's it Yes never mind don't worry-
Come on, let's get confused, OK, I'll put this down for a
moment, OK, I'll put the chair down for
a moment, put on my jacket first, C
Matin,
I'm
back, okay, okay, okay, that's it, come on,
have fun with me, okay, so earlier I
showed you how my room is
and what's in it  but there's still one
there's one more thing you guys don't
know and I want to show you guys
now now right here Yes there's still one
thing you don't know yet look yeah
eh eh how come Woi is it broken or not
Wii
leave my private Le di verobo Okay  e
just a minute I have something I
have to
use [Music] Now ready let's go to the
[Music]
sky
W how cool is my new merchar feature
Wow It's really scary eh cameraman here
cameraman look here it's
really high so high
[Music]
ah the cameraman is flying  guys, it's
really cool, even though it's really small,
we have to cross there first, okay?
Yes, you know, later you'll
know what you're going to do. But
I don't know if the rainbow can be
stepped on or not, like I'm afraid
of falling through, it's not funny, guys, so
we'll just jump.  okay I will jump long Fri
okay okay
[Music]
bismillak one two
three
Yes scam you guys I'm a scam Wi okay okay for
real this one for real okay this time for real
one two
three
Wow wuh wuh
Crazy really cool I let's
[Music]
gomite there's a rainbow  It's really funny, there are three
1 2 3 and then there are clouds, it's cloudy, yes
it's raining, but yes, it can change
again later, right, I think it's raining. Yes, it's easy
. This problem is the weather, there are
balloons, there are stars, I think it's
really funny. There's a floor, there's a bird.
do you see who the bird is
[Music]
let me go hi
I come on
[Music]
when with me
any to
[Music]
goodp
thep
the
[Music]
thep of
the
best
[Music]
time I'm the one Who you've been waiting
for
[Music]
me sen
k
[Music]
h
込
[Music]
sung
hau top of the top top of the world to
the
Topp
[  Music]
the
[Music]
[Applause]
ina
you
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] music [Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
hah How cool or not set not cool
or
not?  but don't you know what's
cooler
like the stage? It's crazy cool, isn't it crazy, when
will you see Kowo
Idoro
Gituar wait a minute?
[Applause]
[Music]
cameraera this is
you guys
[Laughs]
OK, yeah, they're already here, so let's
invite something  times yes wan take the stage
for
Spin
okay
that's perform together Okay perform per okay okay okay
okay first sit down Please
OK
sit
I
have to put on your head
Okay
here don't move don't move
okay
[Applause]
girl
[Music]
[  Applause]
group Okay let's
go position post position okay
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music]
所
[Music]
йй
[Music] [Applause
]
W J bye
bye go go go away go go go go  go away go
away go go fly
F go go next next next Go What's that Bye
Bye byee Bye Bye by
by by Thank you
very much, I've been away from earlier too
[Music]
okay, I can't believe it's already at the end of the
event, are we?  Maybe someone is
interested, yes,
rice field fishing modding agencies, I want to
show you something
OK, that is,
Cang my business card, so that's
really possible, ladies and gentlemen, if you're interested, you can
contact me via here, OK, here
you go, hm, what is this, what is Kobo, what is this? Oh
Yes, this is a card case, this is a card
case, so that's why Kobo keeps your
business cards in that card case, OK? Oh, you guys
want one too because it's really cool. Ah Sumpil,
yes, that's really cool, right? That's it, that's it, that's it, I've
brushed it, that's it, that's it, but you
only have one  just one H but It's OK
It's Ok because you guys can purchase It
online okay okay okay So you can
find everything Yes, I've bought it. This is
really cool, it can protect your KTP card,
student card, sim card, STNK card, ee
card, all card a, basically it's okay,
okay, great  then next I want to
inform you tomorrow hello
Hero is funny isn't he Crazy really cool okay not
note down the date alright note down the
date Okay you take notes okay okay Nice Nice
Iko Iko Iko Iko okay last but not
least I still have another important announcement.
What's up?
Yes Yes, let's just look at
the video together,
what is
universal, what does that mean, Mom,
Ouch, I don't
know either, I don't know what is that, just
be patient Ok, coming soon really really
soon,
OK, hah,
eyes, yes, that's it, thank you  yeah guys,
if that's the case, finally I want to show
my teeth
[Music]
I'm having a hard time, I'm having a hard time, that's it, then that's it,
bye bye guys, bye bye KBU has to
leave you now bye Bye
Bye
everyone bye bye miss me
okay
but
it's a lie Thank you everybody for here
tonight yo spell rain  Ladies and
gentlemen, brothers and sisters, anyone at any age,
let's be together
Minak mantra
glimmerahay
sungi world It's lonely in a vacuum,
problems come and go, it's
normal to be alone, I'm reluctant to
take a step, I open my eyes, look up at the sky, the
raindrops echo, puddle, the clouds seem
to whisper, Come on, explore
the world is dreamy
and various dreams will not solve
problems. Have the courage to step
through all
obstacles, even though the rain won't
stop. I'll accompany you here.
Recite the Mandra to bring light
to your days.
Eliminate all the doubts that
cover your heart, thoughts and emotions, recite
mtra, bring light.  Open a new bar,
everyone's still enthusiastic.
It's okay, type one if you're enthusiastic,
huh, one one, one, one, one,
ready for another one, let's go,
what's the mantra? Sparkling light shines on
the world, hah, I had a hard time sleeping
all night, my heart was pounding until I got
excited. Can't wait to
have fun on stage  Maga
together with
you who are sad here and there
Happy sunset gives
warmth to win the hearts of friends
I paint the beautiful smile of
your night various dreams will not
Solve
problems dare to break
through whatever
[Music]
obstacles' if the rain doesn't
stop it's still there I'll accompany you here
send a mantra bring a succinct light
[Music] of
your days Remove all the doubts
that cover your heart, thoughts and emotions,
cast a spell, bring a spell, open a
new page
[Music]
I Remove all
doubts that cover your heart,
think about it, come Jan, not a
new Pronouncement, isn't it
New prohibitions are not
new Wow, congratulations,
congratulations,
congratul JAT
Oh, don't
do it, you can't do it at this height, you can't do it at this
height, you don't have to be
arrogant, darling, you can do it, it's easy,
hold on, hold on. Yes, you don't have to
talk about it, okay, okay, let's just
mute it later, okay?  let's show it, come on, let's do it
[Applause]
napain Oh my
God nice to be in the mood cuy nice oh
okay okay okay
okay
Go eh Hello Boss don't be shy
Sinia
[Music]
Okay okay then [Music]
S
guys sungkemngkem first
ah okay okay
so be it  polite Bi
polite
[Music]
take bye
[Laughs]
muah