[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
sorry give me one moment please i need
to i need to quickly uh sort something
wait
[Music]
[\h__\h] internet right
unbelievable
inconceivable
[Music]
so
i'm getting there
oh
[Music]
uh
shhh
[Music]
okay
push
[Music]
ago
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
or something like that that's life
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh i can't speak uh
french
[Music]
salute
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
m
[Music]
[Laughter]
welcome sorry for the little hiccups in
the beginning
my internet apparently didn't realize
that i'm coming back today
and that it uh has to work starting from
today again
now
i thought i i
i have no leg works for me okay it's
fine okay thank you thank you man i was
worried i restarted the router and
hopefully we have no more hiccups
yeah yeah i wanted to do that anyway
because recently we always had hiccups
only in the beginning of the streams
and yeah
i cleaned up my office
because we're gonna have a watch party
i'm gonna talk to you guys about my
little trip that i went on on the
weekend it was just um a little tiny
trip that's why
uh
my last week it's not like i took the
whole week off or something like that no
just two days so as if it's like a
normal week
um
you know
uh
just two days off so everything as per
usual today i came back today in the
afternoon
yes i will have a slideshow why are you
saying i'm the slideshow
am i a slideshow
i would be a pretty
hot slideshow no
[Music]
no i'm not the slideshow okay i'll go
okay okay okay
well well i took so many photos for you
guys and i checked them all with uh
my manager so they're all good and also
the new schedule is up i guess maybe you
know what i'll show you that first so
after that we talk about pear party
perry
and so
we have a new schedule
here it is so today right now we're
having the paris trip report
and tomorrow we're gonna do super chat
written catch up i
will uh not really read them today or if
i willed and not many i think
because i am actually uh quite uh tired
or at least i was i thought i was tired
and uh
today i came back but i was kind of
stressed out today i was a little bit
close to missing my flight
but everything's still all good all good
and
yeah so i don't i don't want to stream
too much today
and i just came back so it will be my
little report and then i think tomorrow
we will
tackle the super chats because we got a
lot and left over um
[Music]
actually i put
in my schedule i put um
we have a google calendar that we share
like
we see
kind of like what the others plan and i
that they see what i plan
and uh i i just like to as much as
possible plan ahead at least a week or
two and then i put
a week ago i put the in this time slot
as a
collaboration someone please
uh trying to remind myself that i should
ask someone for a collab eventually
on this day
and uh yesterday when i was still in
paris i got a dm from inna she was like
yo yo i saw that you want to do
something
i completely forgot or like i didn't
have the time to follow up on me trying
to remind myself but ina
ina
ina slid into my dms and so we're
playing she she suggested that we will
play animal crossing um i've been
working on my island recently and
getting quite far for the first time
ever in animal crossing so
i guess i will show you the update and
then we will check out each other's
islands i don't know how far you know
it's like she never streamed animal
crossing right
but apparently she has an island
i wonder
what it looks like so we're gonna
exchange islands and then i don't know
what we're gonna do maybe uh if she
wants
some of my cool items i can give her
some she's off stream player she did one
ages ago oh really she did like a year
ah
i don't remember that at all yeah okay
okay now let's see how far she got since
then
and which villagers she has
and we will be streaming on both
channels i think and then uh we got
first day day off alice's uh and ending
final stream should be
uh on friday and on sunday's tales of
talk
with rosie matisse
and um this is a bit special
because
uh partially this will be uh
well
pre-recorded partially not all of it
but partially because there will be
subtitles
actually uh
my channel of course yes yes and we have
tales of talk one time before with the
tales of the rise producer and this time
we're having it with suicide because
uh
bandai namco reached out to me and said
yo your shift is not over takanashiki
wawa you are still official ambassador
to the english region so we want you to
do some more
and i was like hell yeah let's do it so
we got to say to come over to my tales
of talk studio which is the same studios
horoscope
and this is also the same time slot and
same day as holodog
so yeah that will uh happen and it's
like it's not really an interview it's
really just both of us answering the
same questions and
talking about tales of verizon tails off
games uh in general so
look forward to that please
er
if you didn't play tesla rise then you
might get a little bit spoiler there but
you might want to watch it anyway
because we were
chit-chatting quite a lot it is i think
nice to see
i know
i don't know
and then minecraft on sunday because we
haven't played minecraft in a while
yes
[Music]
so let's have a fun week guys yeah did
you finish
and i really i really didn't have the
time maybe this week i will finish maybe
you know what on thursday
on first day i will i will i don't know
if i will finish it but i will play more
then on first day
no i legit didn't have the time i almost
wanted to schedule it in my google
calendar but like legit then at the time
last week was so busy now i was in paris
and uh here i am back again i'll turn
into pieces can't deny it can't pretend
just follow everyone working out deep
inside
[Music]
for losing you i hate myself
anyway
yes i love this illustration it's so
cute look at you guys in the background
and don't look at the panties perhaps
should i put my logo on top of that
we will talk about
paris my trip to paris
so first of all
i
decided to do this pretty spontaneously
um
i wanted to go somewhere
because
i was feeling like
i didn't have like
interactions with the real world and
real people anymore
and um
then i was thinking where to go and i
was specifically thinking about going
somewhere where i maybe know someone who
could then meet me there and show me
around rather than going all alone or
rather than
paying for my bff
to travel with me again
so
i realized i know someone in paris who
um could possibly perhaps show me around
and so we decided on a date and
you guys are real but i know i mean the
real world like going outside of my
apartment you know what i mean
yeah very old friend of not
to be honest we weren't even really
friends we were just acquaintances
before that
and didn't know her much at all i just
knew that there is this girl who lives
somewhere in the area and
um
had a few
online conversations
uh until now years ago
and
oh yeah so i felt like maybe if she
wants to and then i messaged her and she
was like yes let's do it let's do it i
would love to do
it yeah and she speaks fluent english so
mind you tascado because not
uh
not many uh
in france
uh not everyone speaks fluent english
and even if they do then they often
don't want to
it's
uh according also according to my friend
this is true this is not just a myth
it's really true careful what you say
now
hey it's true it's true yeah
i am
but this girl she speaks very good
english so yeah she saved my life
and yeah um
where do i where do i start uh
so okay so i i actually
went to france
paris
to i think two or three times
before
uh one time was
i think
two thousand
uh
i think 2020
before
i went to japan for a year
and that was also extremely spontaneous
and i went to disneyland paris because
disneyland paris is the only disneyland
in europe and uh
i i went there with a friend but i was
super spontaneous on doing that and
actually did not check out the city i
just went there i think yeah i arrived
in the morning time i went to disneyland
uh i met there with my friend and then
we spent the day at disneyland and then
i uh went to a hotel in the evening
that's really close to disneyland which
is not really in paris city center um
and then i on the next morning i went
back so i did not see paris and then
many many many many many years before
that
i went to japan expo
which is like the biggest japanese
cultural event in europe like it's huge
it's not only about anime and manga it's
about you know i don't know cars and
japanese books and japanese food
uh
japanese i don't know anyth it's crazy
this is huge
absolutely huge japan expo i went there
i i'm actually not sure if it was once
or twice but at least once and i
remember
i it was quite long ago i remember i i
went there and i did not check out the
city i went there for japan expo and
japan expo was quite outside of paris
and
so
uh
i i didn't even if i wanted to i didn't
know how to
get into the city and i was kind of
scared that like i don't know i didn't
know where to go i wasn't quite used yet
to traveling alone especially in a in a
country where i don't speak the language
and all that so
i was like maybe another time i will
check out paris but not this time so
yeah um
so finally this time i was like
i
will see paris i i haven't even seen the
eiffel tower yet even though i was in
france paris a couple times before how
is that
possible you can't forgive that i have a
name and then the freaking eiffel tower
yeah so this was my chance
finally
and so uh i i saw way more than the
eiffel tower and
actually now we'll get to this later
okay let's start let's go let's start
[Music]
or something like that
yes yes
a triumphant
thingy that is
i
you know when i saw this was the first
thing i saw basically um actually no
wait uh
hold up hold up my brain i'm scattered
all over actually this was on saturday
morning
or actually saturday
noon time
i arrived on friday evening but i
arrived really late and all i did really
was eat some room service dinner and
that's it so
uh i didn't know anything but this is
the
first day basically
so i met up uh with the girl let's call
her fmt for now friend magitensi or
french friend magic french french fry
french f okay let's call her ffmt french
friend maggie tensi
okay french we could even call her f
that's a french female friend magikenji
free
ffmt french female friend magiteshi okay
and
she she came to my hotel which was by
the way um
i i will this time i will not show you
any uh pictures or so but it was a
really really
beautiful
nice and
famous boutique hotel
uh there are many boutique hotels in
paris uh but it was
i've never said in a boutique hotel i
think until though
i don't know what was so boutique about
it maybe just because it's smaller um
but still like beautiful
um but it was a very very nice nice
hotel i i
i'm telling you i i treated myself to a
nice hotel
wait you know what i have to delete one
picture i think so that you guys don't
figure out where i was
okay you know maybe this one too
okay
um
and
yeah actually so my ffmt
she said that she really likes this
hotel she wants to stay there uh one day
uh
apparently it's a really nice nice hotel
tote
she made a plan for what we're gonna do
thankfully i didn't have the time to
plan it out at all and look up what i
want to see so she planned it all out
and we from my hotel we first we walked
the whole day we walked we didn't use uh
uber and stuff
one time when we were uh dying but
besides that we were
walking until we died so
good job kiwawa good job
[Music]
so
this
uh thing when i saw it i was really
really uh
emotionally moved because
uh
i
when i see this
building
i think of a
[Music]
a little bit louder i hope it's not too
loud and
[Music]
so this is actually a little bit
connected to japan expo
uh a long time ago i went to japan expo
because two of my favorite idol groups
uh betty school betty's kobo and kyoto
from hello project
came to japan expo as guests to perform
there which is why i went there in the
first place and
they took a commemorative
memory photo
right there right in this position from
where i took the photo from i think in
front of this
[Music]
and yes
and i remember it so vividly because
they got they were wearing these cute
outfits and all that
yeah
yeah very a little loud okay very
symbolic um
[Music]
because of me being an idol
[Laughter]
that was really big and actually uh
f f f
f f
f m t is really bad with directions
uh even though she knows perry as well
um and we were
this is like a huge roundabout somehow
and we were running around it for so
long
uh trying to find the subway station
uh
because somehow
i don't know it was really weird we
couldn't find it it was so weird
and uh yeah it's a huge roundabout and
and and and we looked on google maps and
it was leading us through some really
weird paths
even though it supposedly it was so
close but then again it wasn't we
couldn't find the entrance to the subway
so it took us a while
um weird table in the picture what do
you mean
oh ah
[\h__\h] table have some respect
actually i don't i don't really know uh
let me look up i want to know the
what this is about
[Music]
oh actually yeah my my ffmt she told me
that it's really good that i came uh on
this weekend because only a few days ago
i think
they had
this thing
covered up
completely
with
bags
apparently or a bag
or bags i'm not sure
so you could not see it
isn't that like yeah they said it's art
but what the [\h__\h] this thing is huge you
have you can't even imagine from looking
at this picture
to like like how big it is even if you
have like comparison on the picture but
still it's huge it's massive
and they put like
millions worth of uh bags oh oh on top
of it apparently and let me i want
actually i didn't i don't know what it
looked like
maybe
is it this oh
is it
what the hell
i see if you google it you can actually
figure out what it looks like
it's uh
well
it was a success everybody talked about
it
it's uh i'm glad i saw it in this uh
version the original version yeah so i
had good timing
and
i want to actually figure out what was
this i don't i didn't have i didn't know
about the history of this
uh
english
arc de triomphe
is one of the most famous monuments in
paris france standing at the western end
of the cho chomp elizu
at the center of a plural
place
ja jal de gul formerly named
not place plot plastic black platy
[Music]
12 radiating avenues the location of the
ark at the plaza is shared between three
around this month
16th something
the arc de triomphe honors those who
fought and died for france in the french
revolutionary and napoleonic wars aha
with the names of all french victories
and generals inscribed on its inner and
outer surfaces
oh
beneath its vault lies the tomb of the
unknown soldier from world war one
whoa
who is
who is that
[Laughter]
little
aha
interesting see now uh now i can figure
out what all these things are today
we don't know oh okay
okay
but this was massive and impressive and
then we ran around and then we uh uh
finally at some point finally we found
uh the entrance to subway i don't know
how we did that but we did it and then
[Music]
eiffel tower
the
most famous apparently
it's not allowed for professional people
to take photos and professionally show
them uh on on a professional
uh platform
if if it is nighttime and lit up but i
took the photos of the eiffel tower in
the daytime so suck it
yeah yeah
but i i did see the eiffel tower at
night time as well and uh it was it was
sparkling like a christmas tree uh crazy
it was sparkling so much when i saw it
and actually took a video i think but
it's uh for my private use
yeah so we
uh
we we saw it and then we went into it
and voila
uh
it was so crowded you had when you had
to when you go in there we had to we got
our bags checked uh like two or three
times
and vaccination checked of course
and
or like tests i guess you can get in
with a test or whatever uh
i think just anything like that so but
it was really really controlled not that
anyone can go in and
but no no
no yes uh if you
like there's like a
kind of like a park around it which you
can
look around for free like you can look
at the edit from below for free but if
you want to go up you have to pay and
there is two
uh
uh two floors basically
and there's a second floor in the at the
top
and and this is us lining up with this
on the bottom instead is a ticket for
going up to the very top
oh [\h__\h] wait a second that picture
does that count
wait
wait wait wait
wait the ticket
wait the ticket doesn't count
i don't know
i mean
whatever next one
this picture is good isn't it didn't
they didn't do a good job
didn't i do a good job with this picture
this was on our way to the eiffel tower
the tree in the middle is so beautiful
[Music]
uh
yeah
it was i really liked the
um
i really like the wait here you see my
mouse i like this this uh the patterns
here yes yes very pretty by the way i
think it's 300
meters tall
oh
[Music]
and then from below i took a picture and
on the right side unfortunately they
were doing construction
but uh
fffmt said that the constructions right
now are happening because uh and i
didn't even know about this until she
told me uh but france will be uh holding
the next olympics
yeah i didn't even realize
i didn't i didn't even know but so now
did you guys know now they're renovating
[Music]
when is it 2024
oh
wait that's so soon what the hell
that's like oh my god that's so soon
so and then we bought a ticket to go to
the very very very top
uh this photo is from
uh the second floor looking up
and i have to tell you
there's like a you take an elevator uh
to go up i mean you couldn't feel you
also walk but who the [\h__\h] would do that
at least on the second floor you can
walk up but that's crazy that's insane
it's exhausting people i saw people
walking down and i see that as an option
but walking up hell no
but yeah so we took an elevator and uh
i am not particularly scared of heights
so when i was like on there it was okay
but in the elevator when it was going up
it was going quite fast and it really
scared me
it freaked me out
it freaked me out it was scary
but once we arrived it was all good and
then we were here and it was pretty
windy and the view actually um it i i am
i am officially
because it said that it would rain both
on saturday and sunday and it turned out
to only be cloudy it didn't really rain
so hallelujah but
the view therefore looked like this
[Laughter]
it was amazing anyway but we couldn't
look that far uh as you can see it's
very cloudy
but uh yeah
doesn't this look cool
this is one angle i think
i'm not sure what that is on the
on the
ground
in the middle
but looking at the city i felt like the
city looks so
organized you know like
the buildings they
almost all of them they have a very
similar or same color the roofs and the
buildings like the buildings are all
like a cream color
and the roofs are all like a grayish
color not all but almost all like it it
blends in so nicely and i've been
wondering if maybe because they also all
have pretty much about the same height
if maybe that's like a
like a like a regulation
if you
like if they're not like allowed to
build any higher and if they're if they
have to keep like a certain style i
wonder i i would understand that because
obviously with such a big famous city
you would want to have certain look
um
there f f f f f fmt told me that there
is a part uh in paris
the only part and you actually see it
here back here
uh
it has skyscrapers
and looks modern but it's really just
this small part
of it
that's the only place they're allowed i
thought so i thought so yeah
where are the french people what is this
place called la defense
this part or or this part
which one is it
ah
this part is trocadero and this is like
why is it it's
why is it called dead
are the high skyscrapers defending paris
what what that's a weird name
the defense
i wonder what's the
meaning of that
is there a meaning
against titans
hmm
[Music]
for defense
[Laughter]
i don't know
i don't know we by the way i walked up
to here
uh in order to take
actually uh
this picture
that is taken from
here
yeah yeah
and
[Music]
then we actually went even higher and
oh my god that was first of all so scary
and second of all it was so much more
windy and cold and i don't have a
picture from up there because this view
is actually better because you can see
it more clear um
but we looked around and then spent a
little bit of time up there but not much
because uh
my feet i'm telling you i i was wearing
heels on this day because i wanted to
look cute
and i knew i i knew that i would suffer
from it
and and
my feet were really hurting at this
point
especially
actually my left foot
particularly my left foot
was hurting so much um
so i know i know i know because i wanted
to look cute for you know
for myself okay
i decided i want so cute
ah don't worry i and the next day i
didn't do that again
so
then after that we went to
a cafe
dance wait order here is a little bit
off let me switch that really quickly
[Music]
okay
and so then we went to a cafe and my
ffmt she made a reservation and
we thought there would be afternoon tea
because i wanted to do afternoon tea but
turns out uh
oh my god she told me she called because
i said i wanted to do afternoon tea she
called 20 places in paris
to ask if they have a spot for afternoon
tea on the following day
in 20 places they all said no and then
she called this place which is a great
place
and they had a they had a spot a
reservation available however turns out
it wasn't actual afternoon tea it was
just a la carte
lunch dinner whatever
so
it's a
it has an amazing location it's
called
le marley cafe i think and
it uh it has
you can sit inside but everyone wants to
sit here outside on the balcony because
the view that you have is this the
louvre
yeah that's literally the loot right in
front of us we were sitting right in
front of us and and having food
yeah
isn't that an amazing view to have
dinner slash lunch and we saw when we
arrived it was a daytime but by the end
of it it was uh already dark so we saw
it in both
both colors yeah during the daytime and
during the night time
you friend it very well yeah in the end
i was thinking good that everyone else
turned us down for the afternoon tea
20 different places because we ended up
here holy moly this is probably better
than anything else anyway
yeah
and
i really like the architecture here and
and this is this was like a really long
uh
balcony thingy to the to the left side
it was about the same
uh length as when to the when looking to
the right side we were about like in the
middle
um
actually we switched seats uh because it
was too cold after a while
you see on the on the right side there's
like uh there's
heating lamps so we switched to the back
seats but in the beginning we were in
the front seat so looking at the louvre
we were sitting right here before
and at least i got a good picture
okay
ignore the next picture
no this one ignore ignore the one before
we get back to that that's kind of
situated wrongly and this one's uh
what ff fmt ordered lamb chops
actually she or also ordered a full gra
and
which first i was like
i don't want to even try but i tried it
and i realized it's basically the same
thing as a labor labor burst
just a bit more
fancy
i'm glad i tried eating it because
i realized it's not bad
i was scared of it but no problem
and she was drinking hot chocolate and
this was lamb chops and hot chocolate
and i was eating also meat because once
hungry and i ate just some beef steak
and actually i ate it with her sauce
because she doesn't eat her meat with
sauce
and her sauce was fitting my meat better
actually
[Laughter]
so i i took her meat
yeah yeah yeah yeah so this is coffee
marley
in the palais du louvre
yeah
and here's the louvre at nighttime i
hope there's no copyright on that one
inside is a museum but we didn't have
time to go inside but the real mona lisa
supposedly the real mona lisa is in
there and
so
i think the one that
oh my god i just realized yeah on the
night before i saw this louvre
i was playing uh animal crossing in my
hotel room and
red came by and he sold me the real mona
lisa which i think is just a funny
coincidence out of all the things that
he could sell me
and
on that night it was the real mona lisa
yeah
yeah so i was thinking because he gave
it to me the night before that probably
at this very moment in the louvre the
mona lisa is not there anymore because i
have it in my nintendo switch
you didn't go in no not this time but i
i want to go in when i come back to
paris because i want to come back
yeah i didn't have the time but but uh
yeah
very very nice too
so actually uh
after this after this lunch dinner
actually it was like a really awkward
time when we were eating and we had a
reservation for a
dinner in the evening
and
we realized that we kind of ate too much
food here and that we were both not
hungry enough to actually really eat the
dinner that we planned on eating so we
cancelled that and i got the idea that i
want to eat something else we'll see in
a moment but on the way to where we
actually ended up for the evening
and we also saw
these this is uh i'm not sure what this
is called but it's close to the louvre
if you walk away from the louvre
there is this big park
and there's this big gate they have so
many big gates they're all so pretty
it's not the arc de triomphe no
no i know it looks like it but it's not
that no it looks different
maybe it has the same name
but no it's not the same
no no no no no
oh this one is also called
eh
oh well it was a beautiful gate
arctic carousel oh
apparently
let's zoom in here
[Music]
and then there's horses
many horse many a horse
look at him with his fancy hat
wow
this looks really nice
really nicer
oh nice nice beautiful
beautiful
and actually right behind this
what is that the eiffel tower
lit up
which i took a picture of too but i'm
not allowed to show you because i am a
professional and professional people not
allowed to show
because it's copyrighted yes yes
so we wanted to go through this park
that's behind this but it actually was
closed so
we were like what are we gonna do
and
we just went made our way to uh
something else but this is the
opera
right yes i'm pretty sure yes yes look
it looks like the up do you guys know
the opera cake do you guys know that
cake
with the like gold on top chocolate cake
with gold on top this is the opera
and
building
we i saw this one too i didn't go around
i just saw it from the front to be
honest but it's very pretty very big
[Music]
the opera cake is as far as i know
inspired by this building
yeah
there's a cake of this yes yes yes there
is
yeah
big cake
this no no this one is not edible oh
it's interesting you see here the
there's like
golden heads
of people
in here
wow
[Music]
what's it uh there's there's something
in there because you can go in i see the
museum or what was it i was told but i
forgot academy national music
music academy
music music something
apparently
it's an oh there's an open round
a concert room
and that makes sense
my concert hall
opera is a style of
music
[Music]
okay okay hold up
and then tata
i was surprised that there are so
many
crap places
all over paris or france i guess
in every corner there were crab places
and i wanted to have a crab so this is
what we ate for a
late dinner
normal dinner yeah this was so good yum
yum yum we went to this little place
that was really cozy and the waiters
were really nice and the crap was really
yummy
[Music]
i like sweet things very much
this is a random
but famous cafe that's right next to the
opera by the way
it's uh cafe de la pop pop pop pop pop
pop pop pop pie pop paw
patrol
[Music]
yeah apparently this one is really
famous we didn't go inside though we
were only walking past it
okay okay okay that was basically
i mean it feels short but it was
basically day one
and so we did but i saw all the all the
big important things i saw the eiffel
tower i saw the luck
i saw the lag the car
i saw the
uh opera oh wait this picture
ah we have to go back
[Music]
i also saw
notre dame
beautiful beautiful notre dame
this one looked so beautiful
unfortunately at the moment you still
cannot go inside because there as you
can see they're doing repairs here but
from the front it looks
gorgeous and beautiful and you can't
even go closer up you can't go past this
wall
and so you can't see the bottom part
right now because as long as they're
repairing it you cannot go past this
wall but uh here on the wall you see
like from schools and the children they
drew pictures of
of
the notre dame
and what i thought was interesting
was uh in some of the pictures
i noticed
on top of the uh
burning roof
birds
uh or a bird and one it specifically
looked like a chicken and i was like
what what what did my chickens do this
time
what why chicken
and then she told me that the chicken is
the national
like um animal
of
france did you know
you know
the chicken
is the national animal of france
[Music]
i guess the rooster okay not the chicken
the rooster well for one level pretty
close same thing
it's common knowledge i don't think so
look at the chat being surprised
[Laughter]
i am not the only one who didn't know
that
that was so funny to me though
yeah
yeah so that explained why there was a
ah i think was it uh
[Music]
i hear this this was actually this was a
bird
and then i saw a specifically
here there you go this is
a rooster on top of the notre dame
okay
which to me
really only means one thing
we
must
take over
france and we must
go to japan expo
and we must
get more french
viewers and we must learn french
[Music]
i don't think there is a connection
there
there's there's a connection that i've
i've always felt something was there but
i just didn't know what it was
but france and kfp
kiana flores phoenix
it's meant to be
so anyway that was a day
one i saw
so many things in one day and it was all
very beautiful and i want to see more
the only thing that i was able to go
inside was the eiffel tower so and next
time i go to
paris i want to go inside of these
buildings especially the louvre and that
would be really nice
i want to see the museum i'm not very
much of a museum
type of person museum goa but
i will go check out the mona lisa
however fffmt she said that there's a
always like
like in this museum always just around
the mona lisa there is always a crowd a
big big big crowd who is staring at the
mona lisa the other
paintings or whatever no not not really
no but the mona lisa of course everyone
everyone is standing there staring at it
but i will i want to see it one day
i must i must come back
[Music]
and then we go to day number
two
yes i ate
french toast for breakfast and now
i have
found a new knowledge
fact is
holy macaroni
french toast
does not come from france it is not
french
oh my god
and this one was actually not even that
good at all ma the one that i make is
better but anyway
french dog i was mind blown my mind
exploded when i found out
actually
i was talking to ffmt and i asked her yo
french toast
why is there so many crab places all
over paris but no french toast places
when it's so delicious and she was like
what's french toast and i'm like it
french toast you know french toast
then i looked up the french name and she
was still like kind of confused
she has never even heard of french toast
so
yeah pan perdu is the french name but
it's not so popular here in france and
it's not from france so
the more you know
[Music]
france
i'm not sure
why they call it french toast then but
oh well
my life is a lie
[Music]
this
uh
was just
a big
greek
uh
church
which
doesn't even look like a church to me
but
really really looks impressive to me
just all over paris you find these
insane buildings that are so beautiful
man
ah this is funny pun film
the pantheon oh
i found this and i was like what is this
it's huge it's massive
apparently it acts as a
church
um
roman yeah great grillman
yes yes
yes it was beautiful and if you look
closer i found someone who was missing
his head did you guys find him find his
head has anyone found his head please
report to this church and then bring him
his head
he lost his head someone help him
attack
[Music]
an uncommon sight in france i was so
surprised to see something greek roman
looking here in paris because it really
really sticked
out though the
architecture was really sticking out
and
so actually i saw this today and i took
this picture today uh
and now the pictures i from here on out
the pictures are getting a little bit
mixed up uh excuse me
uh you will now see my dinner from
yesterday which i already spoilered on
twitter my dinner from yesterday
was
french
[Music]
aka cheese fondue
with cold cuts and potatoes and
wee-wee bucket
yeah
so when i posted this on twitter i was
like yo guess where i was and you guys
were like was it france was it
switzerland was it uh what was the other
guess italy
and i mean all of these choices are
uh
yes possible but apparently this is a
very french way of eating chocolate
apparently with these cold cuts that is
apparently very french thing and there's
many countries who love cheese but
this
way of eating it was
a french
apparently
and uh
ffmt really wanted
me to try this and i am not
like a insane cheese addict or so and if
i eat cheese i really only eat them the
normal basic types of cheese nothing
that's like like i don't know
molding if you know what i mean the blue
cheeses and whatever i don't like that
at all but this this cheese was really
good of course chocolate cheese so no
problem with that one it was really
yummy so we put it on top of
the boiled potatoes those were boilies
and uh and and the cold cuts and the
baguette and it was simple
but uh
fun dinner and it was in a
in a restaurant that
had a very good
reviews but also at the same time was
um very popular with locals apparently
here's a picture of the cheese melting
whoa when i first saw this huge piece of
uh
cheese
when he put it when the waiter put it
there i was like
we're not gonna eat all this though
right because it looks so big i thought
there was no way that we could eat all
of it but we ended up pretty much eating
all of it at this point it already was
really really small
it used to be bigger
than
for two people this was for two people
uh the amount of cheese and you with
that knife on the on the right side with
this one you kind of scrape it down
and then put it on your plate and and
combine it with whatever you want
and i actually
uh me me and my family we often need or
ate raclette for like christmas and so
on but we
didn't have this fancy device we just
many of you guys probably know what i'm
talking about it's like a grill with an
oven underneath with like little little
uh
shovels that you
put stuff on and then cheese on top and
then on the grill on top you grill meat
or whatever
and bacon and vegetables and stuff yeah
yeah yeah yeah i did that so many times
but this was my first time to see this
way of the college
it was fun and then i ate
oh miyamoto
miyamoto was that italian sorry
[Music]
maybe
creme brulee
i actually was craving creme brulee
in the week before my trip
and and i was like where where could i
get a good creme brulee in my city and i
couldn't find
uh any creme brulee so i was getting sad
and then i realized oh my god when i am
in paris i can get
creme brulee
it's so
good
if you guys don't know what it is it's
basically underneath it's like a vanilla
custard creamy thing and then
on top it looks burnt but this is
caramelized sugar i think and so it's a
layer of
caramel caramel sugar that you have to
break through and then underneath it's
like a
sweet vanilla custard cream it's really
yummy and i ate it in this place but i
also ate a creme brulee in the first
night uh
in my hotel not to say even though the
one in the hotel was much more expensive
and the hotel in general was just more
like upscale
this one was better
and i told the waiter i told her
your creme brulee is so freaking good i
love it
so yummy better than the one i had in
the hotel
yes yes oh sorry
day two
actually i went to disneyland paris
we
[Music]
so
to be honest the original idea was for
me why i wanted to go to paris was for
disneyland paris i felt like going to
disneyland paris and i wanted to go to
disneyland paris halloween season
which
was happening for quite a while
even after halloween
and
[Music]
i booked my trip and then turns out they
changed to christmas
decorations
one day before
i arrived
[Music]
so even though i wanted to see halloween
disneyland i didn't get to see halloween
disneyland but
you know what no problem because
uh christmas disneyland was absolutely
beautiful and
emotional and stunning and gorgeous i
loved it
it was so much fun
and i was in disneyland paris before
and but um that time er
i don't know it seemed very
i went in in january i think and it was
it was raining a little bit and it was
cold and it was empty it was really
really cold like insanely cold and empty
like there were many attractions closed
and most of the food places were closed
but we literally didn't know where to
get food
uh in the early early afternoon which is
insane if you ask me for disneyland
uh
yeah by the way i i got permission to
show this it should be fun
so i didn't really make such good
uh experiences the last time i went here
but this time uh i went with a very
experienced
disneyland
tour guide
aka fffmt
so
yeah this is the entrance to disneyland
park
very pretty
and
the pictures here will be very mixed
again so
yeah
it will be weird but
uh here we have a
a pirate ship this is from a
pirates of the caribbean
and we did a pirate of the caribbean
attraction
and uh apparently was allowed to take
pictures inside so i did
so i did ahoy ahoy
yeah the pirates of the caribbean
attraction was like a boat that goes
through
well a tunnel in the water
and with like on the left side and right
side you see like things and music and
they talk to you and blah blah blah
so
there was a chicken
i don't know i just had to take a photo
of that but i'm actually not sure that
might have been
in a different attraction but i
there's a picture of a chicken there
when i saw it i was like oh my god i got
some i gotta take this picture from my
cave people
this is a french kfp uh member
yes
[Music]
and uh this was a captain jack sparrow
in in that attraction he looked this is
not a real person this was a
um
like it kept on moving it was a puppet
a big puppet life-size puppet and you
were able to hear like the
the french voice of captain jack sparrow
animatronic yeah that's that's it that's
it that's it everything was animatronic
yeah he looked very good though like his
face looked exactly like
jack sparrow
i know
what if it was him it was not him
yeah he looked like johnny depp yeah
very much so
and
after that we see
just uh
a beautiful scene area but i want to
show you guys some more scenery of
disneyland paris but i also wanted you
guys to see the duck
she wants you
they were ducks and your name is so cute
but i just want you to see the
general scenery this was pretty i don't
remember where exactly that was but it
was in disneyland
oh my god actually
the first thing we did on uh when we
went into disneyland was um
go to this attraction uh it was a roller
coaster but it was not the most exciting
one it was the
rather exciting one
oh
i i forgot which one that was um
uh
i forgot
[Music]
it was a roller coaster not space
mountain i was too scared to go into
space mountain
[Music]
it was a different roller coaster but
even though there was no loop
i was this was not the first time i was
in that specific roller coaster so i i
knew that i would cry again but
uh
i
i have a special relationship with
roller coasters where i i hate them and
i like them at the same time
so i don't mind
uh going to the roller coasters and
making use of them but by the end of it
i'm always like
why did i do this
to myself and throughout the whole
roller coaster i'm like screaming and
and then i i lose my voice and then i'm
just like uh closing my eyes and like
going
and dropping my head and like trying to
escape
i literally cannot sit straight in the
roller coaster
i try to hide myself in roller coasters
uh so yeah i i'm not good with dealing
with them but it's not like i completely
uh hate them
yeah i felt dizzy and and and sick and
[Music]
if i would have had my heart rate
monitor on i would probably be over 200
[Laughter]
hiding from what i thought i was gonna
die
there were some times where the ceiling
was extremely uh close to my head and i
don't know i just felt like i was gonna
fall out of the rollercoaster
or the roller coaster was going to fall
out of the rails or something
i was so scared
[Music]
the big one the the best one the most uh
exciting one we didn't go to that one
big
something space space mountain i think
yeah we didn't go to that one sorry
because i was too much scared
and all over the place i was finding
making my minnie mouse balloons lost in
the ceiling and i started taking
pictures of that
and
i just thought it was so sad to see a
minnie mouse
here and there lost and
asked
crying for help
one thing that i really enjoyed that i
did not get a picture of i think was um
uh
an attraction where you drive a car
it kind of is mostly like it
it controls the wheels mostly automatic
if you don't control it but you can also
control it
and you are the one who pushes the gas
yeah that one
i really really liked i was driving you
had i had a lot of fun
autotopia autopia yes yes yes yes that
one that one
and very much for children but i had a
great time
[Music]
this is another uh balloon
lost
save minnie
there's mouse
this is inside um
uh what's it called again uh
the world is little or the little small
world so something like that
the main disneyland attraction small
small world yeah yeah
yeah it was so pretty
that was so pretty and at the end there
was an alfveda sand sign
yeah
and in german we see our freedom but the
stream is not over yet
[Music]
this was also the type where you sit in
a boat and you just uh
are being led through a river i like
this type of attractions yeah they're
they are not so uh exciting but you see
many beautiful things and you hear
beautiful music so i like it not
low low effort attraction from the side
of the
uh
visitor you don't need to do anything so
yeah very nicely um
[Music]
and i like the i don't know though
they're kind of refreshing i like being
in boats
and
then this one i i went into for the
first time the star wars star tours
attraction
and i am not really interested in star
wars but i remember watching a little
bit of it when i was a child
uh of the first couple maybe the first
and the second movie
but star tours holy [\h__\h] this one was uh
one of those where you go into like a
cinema type of room
and with maybe 20 people or so
you sit in a couple of rows
like like in the cinema and you look at
this big screen and we had 3d glasses on
and basically
you fly
and it moves like you really feel like
you're you're flying in high speed and i
want to know how the [\h__\h] they're doing
that because it's not like we're
actually flying but it feels like we're
really flying so far yeah the chairs
they move like
it was so
convincing yeah
they dropped the floor
but they don't have so much space how do
they do that it's crazy uh hydraulics i
understand that but it really feels like
you're flying for quite some distance
it's crazy it's
magic but it made me feel really sick
[Music]
[Laughter]
the movements are so
convincing and realistic um i've been in
one of these i think in
in japan and and i think it was joy
paulus
uh and inside amusement park not
disneyland and um
that one was also really convincing and
really cool
i i like this attraction because it
feels a little bit like a roller coaster
but at least i know i'm safe
because i know i'm in a inside a movie
theater and things are not really moving
i mean they are but just at the same
time they're not really moving like a
roller coaster but it feels like a
roller coaster so i i like these types
of attractions maybe the most because
they're really impressive and
fascinating and they're they are a lot
of fun i had so much fun like
flying was so much fun there yeah
and then
there was a
toy story attraction
this was the last one that we did
and
you
this was like a shooting attraction
where you are in a boat and again going
for water but you're looking at the
scenery and there's like targets and you
have to shoot them
but it's like here yeah and this one
holy [\h__\h] i was absolutely killing it
ffmt before we entered she was like i'm
gonna be so bad at this i'm really so
bad at this and i was like don't worry
i'm also really bad at these kind of
things
but
this was our end score
me on the right side over 9 000 boys and
girls
[Music]
i was really good i was looking at the
at the score from the card to our left
and right side and they didn't have
higher score than me i actually had a
pretty damn high school yeah yeah if you
look at this uh i was uh fffmfmt
was uh from the bottom the
second one and i was from the bottom the
third one ranking wise
that was fun it was like actually pretty
difficult because like
when you shoot
you only sell like a tiny tiny tiny
laser dot on the target or wherever
you're shooting but since there's so
many people shooting you're not even
sure like is it your dots or is it
someone else's thought so
i wasn't even even sure like if i was
hitting the targets or not
i am apparently made for fps games
and then after this i think in between
we might have done some things that i
didn't show but uh yeah i like the car
thing uh but besides that
i don't remember maybe we did one more
thing yeah the first roller coaster i
didn't have a photo of and uh
we didn't do the the mansion the horror
mansion thingy because i wasn't there
before and uh
it didn't really impress me
much at all
so i didn't care for it
uh
[Music]
yeah and then after this
we
saw
the christmas parade
and it was so beautiful the music it was
so christmasy and then finally we saw
the princesses because normally in
disneyland paris as well there's like
princesses and and so on and
throughout the park that you can like do
a meet and greet with but um during
these current times they don't show up
they only show up during the parade
and this was the christmas parade and
they i saw cinderella and i saw
tinkerbell
um and no elsa but uh who else was there
i don't quite remember
there were a bunch of princesses but
there was also someone special anyway so
this is uh
uh on top you see uh
and not not milky mouse but the
mickey mouse and minnie mouse and
this was the first uh thing of the
christmas parade we we actually came
right when it started so we didn't get a
good spot you know what was funny i saw
someone
in front of us not in this picture but
there was someone in front of us who was
filming this whole thing
with their [\h__\h] first generation
nintendo ds
and i just couldn't stop laughing at it
it was so funny to me
he was holding it up high and it was
filming his [\h__\h] nintendo
in this day and age everyone has a
[\h__\h] smartphone which probably has a
way better i don't even know that you
can film stuff with your nintendo you
can't i don't understand how this is
worth but it wasn't intense it was a
small nintendo ds
maybe not first generation but like a
different generation but it was a small
nintendo ds i i i definitely recognize
the small nintendo team
oh no that was so funny to me dsi ah
not gonna
oh man
the 3ds could fill in 3d it didn't look
very big i don't know
[Music]
ah
that cracked me up anyway this was
really really nice the parade was so
much fun the music was fun um last time
i went to disneyland paris uh in 2020
january
um they had a projection and a firework
uh protections and fireworks after the
parade which was the absolute highlight
for me unfortunately they don't
currently they don't do the projections
and fireworks but but i am however lucky
uh sff
says because the parade literally just
with the
christmas decoration that came like two
days ago that started two days ago uh
the parades came back as well so if i
would have gone the week before i might
have had seen the halloween decoration
but there wouldn't even have been a
parade so
uh i was lucky with my timing yeah
yes yes yes yes
yeah but one day i want to see those
projections in the fireworks again
because uh that was really really uh
i don't know inspiring even though i'm
not like a huge disney fan but uh
yeah
and here more uh parade stuff who's
who's on there ah
donald duck
was on there so we had mickey mouse we
had donald
oh that's probably also some ducks i
think i don't see it well
and
and on the ground i didn't see them on
the ground but they were like dancers
and stuff on the ground uh
yeah in between the big big cars
and then
uh
the princess says unfortunately i didn't
really take a photo of the princess but
look who's here
[\h__\h] santa claus
i am so sorry i thought santa claus was
not real but obviously he [\h__\h] is
that was a real person up there and he
was going around with his cart
[Music]
and i was thinking to myself what has
santa claus to do with disney
did disney buy santa claus
i was actually confused about that but
uh
are you [\h__\h] so sad the clown's the
real one
i i i know that uh
like i know from netflix shows and stuff
american shows tv shows that uh in in
shopping malls sometimes there is a
santa claus where you can sit on his lap
and tell him what you want for you for
christmas but we don't have that in
australia at least i've never seen it
before so this is actually the first
time i see a santa claus in real life
this is literally the first ever time um
he's alive he's real guys he's freaking
real
i was so excited
this was so much fun i don't know man i
just i was i was feeling like a child
which makes sense i guess because in
disneyland you start feeling like a
child
and then at night time the christmas
decorations were so
pretty look at this
i took this with my nighttime
mode on my camera
i had to stand there for a little while
but it looks nice doesn't it
wow
and i was i was looking at this i'm
thinking good that i didn't go for
halloween good that i went for christmas
because oh my god jingle bells jingle
bells
jingle all the way oh what fun it is to
write
attractions in disneyland
it was so pretty the tree was so big
there was decorations everywhere there
was music going on and i think at this
point yeah you see here the parade this
was when the parade was over in the
castle
it was done in like the castle area and
then they went back to this is like the
entrance area all the way here this is
the entrance area if you don't know how
disneyland looks like and they went this
way so people started following i
thought it was already over but we
followed them the party was never
freaking over it kept on going and going
it was so nice
yeah early christmas man this was just a
random corner a side street um that i
thought looked pretty hmm
[Music]
very
pretty okay look at these lights man
so nice
here we have a pretty princess because i
said uh actually it's a queen
i didn't take pretty princess [\h__\h]
but i
this was
the only
i mean
i i saw i saw the the father of
pinocchio
outside and the queen of
the hearts yeah the queen of hearts
um from just i saw her from very far
away because i was standing in line for
the the car attraction i think at this
moment um
but this is like actually my maximum
zoom ability this was actually so so so
so so so far away with my own eyes from
far away i thought i was looking at a
beautiful beautiful princess and then i
took out my phone i wanted to zoom in
and take a picture of a beautiful
princess because i thought they don't
come out except for the parade
and it's zoom in and it turns out i look
at this face and i'm like ew
i thought i was gonna look at the
princess and zoom in and i'm just like
oh
who the [\h__\h] are you then i realized
it's the queen of hearts
i didn't remember the queen of hearts
had a face like that hi i'm it
[Music]
was really it was so tiny for me in
reality in reality it was like it was
like so small for me i swear and i just
saw someone in a big big dress and i
thought it would be a beautiful princess
[Laughter]
on the parade were much much prettier
um
this is just a random shot of
outside of the small world
attraction
really pretty i really like the way they
designed this whole thing
with the pastel pink colors and all that
it was really nice
and this is a proper picture of the uh
castle of disneyland paris which was uh
of sleeping beauty right
or right wait no rapunzel
like who's who's catholic again
rapunzel
who knows sleeping beauty
cinderella
no
cinderella is a japanese disneyland
castle
this is not cinderella
as far as i know
yeah if you want to see the cinderella
castle i am
pretty sure that it's uh is somewhere
else
at least not here
according to ffmt this was a sleeping
beauty castle
yes indeed indeed indeed hi hi hi i
don't know
what's her name aurora
her name is
aurora right
now
has these pretty pink colors very pretty
and this was a
a nice picture of the big tree in the
entrance area
yes yes so as i said the pictures are
kind of mixed up so after disneyland we
actually went to eat the
the fondue the cheese chocolate fondue
and that you saw before i showed you the
disneyland pictures and so basically um
after the raclette i just uh
was absolutely dead on both days i'm
telling ya
after the paris sightseeing and uh i was
already
destroyed i i went into my hotel room
absolutely dead
couldn't move i fell into my bed and i
slept pretty early i i was i didn't even
watch netflix or disney plus or anything
on that day
and then after disney i was about i
brought different shoes i wore flat
shoes but i was obviously still
so exhausted after that day as well
and i was
falling asleep pretty quickly yeah and
then today on monday um what i did was
uh
i
took a swim in the swimming pool
and uh
i went quickly i went shopping quickly
in paris um
and
uh and alone by the way on monday i was
alone
and and then after shopping
i
uh quickly went to
the airport and
actually when i flew to paris i was uh
i gave my actually i booked an economy
class
uh but for my flight home i
decided spontaneously to upgrade myself
to business class because i realized
it's not even that expensive and 55 euro
by the way not really i didn't think it
was expensive 55 euros decent and i
didn't eat food anyway and you would get
proper food at uh at the business class
so i thought okay two birds with one
stone
so
yeah because i was also stressed out and
i just wanted to
eat food and relax the moment
you know
i thought it wasn't that bad yeah in
short
distance flights it's really not that
bad but
the difference in pricing with uh
business and economy when it comes to
long distance flights is so much bigger
so
i have yet to experience that in my life
on the on a long distance slide but this
was
a nice i treated myself and their food
was so good
[Music]
yeah france business class so we that
was uh i was surprised it was actually
really edible all of it
and i'm starting to really get into
cheese now
[Laughter]
the cheese was yummy and uh this was uh
uh it looks like rice was actually
noodles in the shape of fries uh it was
a cold uh
lunch and
but i really needed it it was yummy and
the white thing was a white fish i don't
know which fish
yes no i did not drink wine i drank
coca-cola
because i was tired and i was hoping for
it to help me
and then the i think the the dessert is
probably something like a
realized sounds like shoe cream
which is a french dessert and i really
liked eating that in when i was lived in
japan
and i think it's something like that
because there was cream inside and uh
that's the actual name in french i guess
in japanese it's called shukurimu and i
when i was eating it i was like oh damn
that actually sounds like shoe cream
that's not so
not so
tasty sounding
i think that's what it is it doesn't
have the typical shape that i know but
it tasted like it was hazelnut cream
though
hazelnut cream inside very yummy one
thing that i forgot and i regret i
wanted on the last day before flying i
wanted to buy a macarons but um
i was actually pretty close to missing
my flight and i was really stressed out
i was running i was running
through paris and for the airport
so i couldn't make it i couldn't buy
macrons i wanted to buy them from this
shop called the lord lodurei
and the famous one
[Music]
that felt really really really
regretful to me i'm not a huge fan of
macrons i don't think it's like the
yummiest thing on earth but i felt like
i want to buy some proper macarons on my
way home macaron
i don't know how to say it in english
in german it's macron
and last but not least i want to flex on
you with my uh camera with my phone
camera ram i was looking outside when i
was flying and i saw a plane in the
distance
and this is the
normal
view and this is how i saw it basically
but when you zoom in with my phone let
me just flex on you real quick i was
able to figure out what airline it was i
mean i actually i mean you could see it
if you saw that airline before you could
recognize it i guess shut down
[Music]
isn't that impressive this is the
maximum zoom on my phone from this
it's this
is
[Laughter]
um this is
normal
um
the normal lens but there's also wide
lens that makes it look even
even wider i used the wide lens so
i think this was was this white lens i'm
not sure um but yeah
look at this look at that
you can see what what airline it is i
mean i don't know which one it is but
you could see it
yeah it's powerful
i i will not say which one it is because
i don't want to advertise but it's not
an iphone and it's not as
not a samsung but i'm sure that the
samsung nowadays has a really really
great zoom as uh as well
my phone is actually by now
yeah
one of the
not none of the newest generations i'm
thinking of getting a new one
but i was so happy with my
phone's camera when it first came out
and uh i'm still happy with it but
i'm thinking of getting a new one at
some point
and google pixel
why is that your
why is that your conclusion that it must
be a google pixel that's air india
really
that's air india
ah speaking of hair candy
did you guys like the video that i
uploaded yesterday
[Music]
uh i'm so sorry it's such a shitty [\h__\h]
post
but
i'm
i'm so sorry i felt compelled to make a
video like that because i saw
i i found out about this these i'm so
sorry i i have to be honest where my
inspiration came from i saw these uh
indian
whatsapp good morning greetings
and i was like
this is hilarious
they apparently send so many good
morning messages over there that it
clogs up the internet and uh
they break whatsapp and stuff
[Laughter]
and they look so so like like graphic
design is my passion
style you know so i was like i need i
need to make something like this
so i was trying to hit up some clippers
on twitter and uh pudding helped me
to make a [\h__\h] post video
um
actually i um i first told him that he
can make just he can like as long as
it's inspired by this and looks as
shitty as this uh i sent him like a
sample and then all good please um have
fun with it and make a [\h__\h] post but
then what he sent me first was actually
too cursed i i thought it can't be too
cursed but it was too curious so i told
him to like tune it down a little bit
so the the original version that he made
was even more cursed this is this is
quite tuned down
but please send this morning message to
your friends and foes your
[Laughter]
yeah yeah i just thought it was funny so
i'm yeah this is kind of like a parody
and uh oh yeah we had mb
mb on saturday i hope you enjoyed it i
took that before i went to paris
so that you guys would have something to
look at
did you like mv
[Music]
it was cute wasn't it i'm actually queen
bee apparently
i was a queen
[Music]
[Applause]
are you still here and i want to watch
the b movie i know you already saw it
but i want to watch a review because
you're a bee
i'm maybe
that might be the cutest thing alive i
swear
yeah
anyway i don't know why we're showing
this here let's show something nice
there
[Laughter]
[Music]
we'll never watch it again
wow wow
these are cute
[Music]
anyway that was my trip and i have to
say
i really really really enjoyed it and it
was so worth it i
treated myself to a nice hotel and stuff
and we ate good and and also very
authentic uh food and uh i was with a
with an acquaintance who turned
immediately turned into a super super
super awesome friend and i i really
really like her and uh we were both like
the whole day we immediately clicked and
we were talking so much and i really
really like her and
it was it was really difficult to say
goodbye because we both said oh i won't
miss you i will miss you i will visit
you no i will visit you again
um
yeah she's such a sweetie yeah
actually
uh uh
when when we met um
[Music]
because i know her from you know way
before uh
we were never really that close until
now but so i when we met on on
saturday morning at
noon time i asked her
i wanted to you know know like
how much
she knows so i asked uh
do you know what i'm doing nowadays
and she said
yeah i do
yes
i actually do
and i was like ah okay
good to know good to know that you know
but that way
it was
it was good because i
we were like able to have a
fairly
more or less open conversation and
she told me that uh you want to know how
she found out
okay i will not go too deep but someone
someone
uh was sent showing her a whole live uh
uh
footage
and uh
yeah then then she saw it and she was
like i know this girl
she didn't tell
that person who sent it to her but
she she herself to herself she she
realized oh i know i know and turns out
she ever since then has been not really
watching the streams but she's been
watching the clips and she's maybe even
watching the stream right now in that
case
hello thank you so much for giving me
this amazing tour for paris and you
organized everything and i'm really
really grateful for that it was great i
i was able to really shut up down my
brain like um i didn't look at my phone
for the whole day on saturday
on on saturday i did because like in
waiting line for the attractions
obviously
what the hell are you supposed to do
um
but yeah i did not do like any business
stuff during the day i did not answer
discord messages during the day and last
time i was this was the thing that i was
complaining about that during
my spa trip i i wasn't really able to
relax that much because
um i was just constantly
um i felt obligated to constantly check
my
um my phone and my discord messages and
stuff and twitter and everything because
i don't know first of all the
feeling of obligation and second of all
i could i wasn't able to calm down
without looking at it like i had to look
at it in order to get to a peace of mind
you know what i mean yeah but this time
uh probably because we were just
clicking so well and and constantly
having conversation and constantly
looking at interesting things like you
know the eiffel tower and and all those
things uh luck
the
and stuff like that um
that i just didn't think i didn't even
think about it yeah
so
i was so happy it was really an
exhausting trip this was not a trip to
relax it was a trip to have fun and do
something else get my mind off of whole
life for once for the first time in in
one over one year and yeah it was very
successful yeah so thank you thank you
so much fffmt and thank you parisianki
france and having a french person with
me was really really a huge relief
and and i want to go back yeah i
definitely want to go back i didn't see
everything obviously uh but i got a
great overview and um i i really
um
liked paris a lot i want to see more
i know
[Music]
i will go again after winter maybe in
like springtime or something i don't
want to go in winter time i don't want
to travel too much in wintertime unless
if it's for skiing because
well
it's just way cold man yeah last time i
went to france it was winter time it was
just freaking cold
but
not good
yeah
oh you know what's also funny uh someone
said to me
i told you guys about this before maybe
um
there's this netflix show emily in paris
and i watched it and it was so cringy
and i really didn't like it
[Laughter]
but the only thing that i like about
that show is emily's cute outfits and uh
during this trip uh
two people two people told me uh that i
uh dress uh like uh emily and paris
it got me excited
made me happy
yeah
yeah yeah it is a
a bad show i don't like it
i like the fashion
emily in paris
[Music]
yeah yeah i'm glad some people know what
i'm talking about
fashion game on point hell yeah you
gotta be fashionable if you're in paris
see that's why i was wearing high heels
uh around the around the eiffel tower uh
i mean i understand why but like
there were so many people selling uh
merchandise of like the eiffel tower and
they were also selling a lot of berets
and weirdly enough they were selling
like children's toys um but yeah they
were selling all kinds of stuff but
mostly like eiffel towers and they were
like all over like literally everywhere
and they were so up in in your face when
you when you leave the eiffel tower um
park area there's like this gate and
they're like
so in your face with the eiffel towers
they have like these huge keychains
um like the key key chain
not like not what you think of maybe but
like a huge circle where there's like
hundreds hundreds and hundreds of eiffel
towers attached to it and then they go
like shaky shaky shake shake shake
whoa you want an eiffel tower
yeah
i mean
it makes sense because business eiffel
tower tourists go get your eiffel tower
but i actually bought a eiffel tower in
the eiffel tower
in the eiffel tower that was an official
eiffel tower merchandise shop and um i
bought this uh um
snow globe
and
when where there's an eiffel tower
inside in the snow globe and you shake
it and there's like snow falling i
thought that was really cute
yeah
that was the only
uh the only souvenir that i bought and
it was for myself
because i forgot about the macarons and
otherwise i would have bought that too
but yeah i didn't want to buy too much
because i had a small small suitcase and
i i knew that uh i wouldn't be able to
fit anything anyway so
sancho fell for all the tourist no i
didn't
no i didn't fall for a trap i bought one
eiffel tower thingy in the actual eiffel
tower in an official shop so
i wouldn't call it a trap
[Music]
and i wanted it so what the hell
i wanted something to take with me and i
chose that
yes
yeah the snow club was so cute there
were some other weird things there was
like there was a
one of the merchandises that they were
selling there was
half of an eiffel tower
and for some reason so there were
there's this i think from 1788 or
something like that maybe maybe i'm
wrong with the date maybe it was 1877 or
something like that was but there's a
half
eiffel tower from like the midway
construction i don't know why they're
selling that but it's literally missing
50 of the eiffel tower
like the top half is missing
yeah
no it's still the same price as the
other eiffel towers but apparently
that's maybe collectors want it because
uh
a 50
finished eiffel tower is special
i guess it is
welcome home boss thank you i'm back i'm
back i'm back
oh by the way where the french people
are the french people in the chat
[Music]
where are my french people
oh wee wee wee oh my god there's so many
right now
and
i
am going to
ask you guys for
uh something
okay
so i want to go back to france and i
want to see more beautiful places but
regardless of that
remember how i was a special guest at
dokomi and i went there in person and we
had the meet and greet and the concert
and all that wouldn't you love having
something like that at japan expo
huh so i think there's a chance i was
surprised to hear um from fffmt that
there's actually a french
whole live discord i mean i guess i
guess maybe there is for every country
but yeah and and and i realized maybe
there are quite a lot of whole life
bands in france so
you know how dokomi worked out
i told you guys to contact the
conventions when you want us to come and
tell them that you want us to come
because that's how conventions work so
what you must do if you want me or all
of her life or part of home life to come
there's a chance for any convention if
you tell them that you want us to come
that is the most effective thing you
can't just expect from these conventions
to uh think of it themselves some of
them are really really really boomers
and they don't even know what whole life
is partially and then they don't know
what they're missing out on so i would
love to bring whole life to japan expo
um i i think that would be amazing
and and i have a vision for it but i
need you guys to do the first step okay
i want you guys to take the first step
the french people need to unite
and write to even i think if you're
lucky maybe even one person is enough
because because for dokomi it was one i
think one person basically
um you just gotta reach out to the right
people i guess
normally you can suggest special guests
to conventions i don't know about japan
expo because japan expo is pretty big
like
i don't know where to reach out but if
there's a place that you guys can find
to reach out to and suggest a special
guest
and then please tell them to bring a
whole life or takanasikiyada
specifically
to
japan expo me as the soul
and single
european holy life member i would love
to represent whole life in japan expo
and you're welcome to clip this and uh
show this to japan expo if you want
yeah
and you know what if that happens i will
i will try to learn basic french i'm
really inspired
as as painful as french language is to
learn
i'm sorry but your language is really
really difficult from what i've heard
the poor poor german people who have to
study french language in class i've
heard so many horror stories
but i will try okay if that happens i
will try
it was it's it's pain yes yes yes it's
tough
you got a really difficult language
there
yeah but it would be my honor and i
would like to represent her life as the
european one
out there
so if you would do me the honor and i
will do everything but you guys gotta do
the first step please i'm counting on
you if it doesn't work out then it
doesn't work out maybe you can also um
maybe there's a second biggest
convention in in france that you can
also recommend us to but you gotta do
these kind of things like pretty early
you know
usually
at least half a year
ahead of time of when it's taking place
but maybe for japan expo even earlier so
go do it now
okie dokie
french is hard because everything is
generous well german is too my
my first language we have three genders
yeah that's also a pain in the ass but
at least it's my first language so i
didn't have to learn it the way that
other people learn it
yeah as far as i know japan expo is it
either in june or in july
you can speak german
you know if i didn't see your name just
now i would have given you a serious
reply because
[Music]
uh
and with that i will not be reading
super chat today tomorrow we have a long
super chat reading stream planned and i
will see you guys there if you want you
might get some more details or whatever
about my trip otherwise in another
stream and you're welcome to hang out
with me i will leave it at this and
because this was my story about my trip
and yeah i hope you liked it
[Music]
thank you
for waiting for me thank you for letting
me go on like smaller trips to recharge
and and you know relax and have fun and
stuff thank you so much
and i really had a great time and i got
to make a really good new friend
yeah
that i really like
thank you guys
yeah
i think my next trip will be a skiing
trip maybe in like january or something
yeah
feel free to take more trips in the
future thank you for now
i really feel
revitalized re-energized let's see how
long it
will hold up
[Laughter]
don't break skis now please don't die oh
actually oh my garden is
man i am
i don't know what happened but on
saturday after walking for a while
not that i did like one specific
movement but at one point i noticed that
in a really weird spot of my thigh
of my left thigh
i had
a lot of pain i could barely lift my leg
anymore for
until now still i still feel like so
during disney as well
um i don't know maybe i strained
something or or i don't know i pulled a
muscle or something i don't know it
really really hurts
in this really specific
place in my thigh
and on saturday evening after the
parasite thing i went i took a hot bath
and i tried to massage it and stretch it
but it didn't go away so on sunday i was
in pain the whole day and and now now
i'm fine because i'm sitting down but
but when i walk or when i go upstairs i
feel it especially
i i think it will go away um in a few
days but uh it made me realize
holy [\h__\h] i'm i really
am even too old for this [\h__\h] or i just
no no that's not it it's just that i
just barely ever move like i go out for
one day
and walk a little bit and then i have so
much pain in my body
it was just everything was hurting so
much because i don't ever
walk or move
it opened my eyes guys
every time i try to move my body i hurt
myself guys
yeah i need to touch more grass
yeah i'm so out of shape
i need to do a physical exercise holy
macaroni
i pulled i pulled something there
yeah
i
relatable really i'm happy to hear that
how
[Applause]
[Music]
i'll see you guys tomorrow okay
see you guys tomorrow
wee-wee bucket bucket
get a treadmill
have a membership in the fitness center
okay shut up i just don't use it because
i'm scared
and in german we no
and in french we say
okay
but
yes also afrida saying in german
[Music]
bye bye
merciful cool
party
[Music]
do
oh and i missed my cat so much but uh
bestoferendo took care of them
and their smoothie hellas movie
yes yes
yes movie
yeah
you guys don't hear her maybe but she's
meowing very aggressively
my babies i'm gonna cuddle with them now
in sleep sleep
now
you hurt her you have such good ears
maybe it was me though answering her
if it sounds too close then that close
then that was me
bye-bye
[Music]