[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
hello
is the sound okay i'm not wearing
headphones i have no idea
it sounds okay i'm wearing the
headphones in this house
no no no no no longer muted
hey welcome so today's uh
smash stream i guess let's smash let's
go
kane is waiting to voila yes today uh
it's not gonna be a free talk stream
kiara's gonna show me the ropes to uh
super smash
bros
[Music]
yes no pressure no pressure game audio
game audio lounge
i can't not that i can hear but sure
i don't hear it either i don't know yeah
we don't hear the game sound couch co-op
smash let's go this is my absolute first
time
opening the game i don't even own the
game i'll buy it after this but yeah
when i was like picking characters i was
like hey i want to use violence she was
like no no
no i'm fine
i'm like okay fine then what can i get
like before the stream she played some
stuff and like unlock some characters
yeah i got a few new ones because i also
just bought the game a really short
while ago so as you guys can see i'm
lacking the characters i'm sorry but
some cool ones are here like the inkling
and so on
yeah i guess because violet is you know
bye bye for me then i guess
[Laughter]
uh i have chosen uh to play joker
i like joker
when you select someone you go like um
here and then you
click on your picture i go on where you
click on with the joystick you go to
your picture with your controller
you see you see this one is yours oh
yeah move that over here
but first you have to select first
isolated and then
click here
how do you select it before it
start on without starting because i was
able to select someone
let's go here
ah yeah look it's so good
oh
so many colors oh rainy raining joker
did you play that game
which one this one the personal one that
he's from i play in my spare time
really i've never played the personal
game before i never really finished it
though like i left off like
you know it's like when you leave off
like a very long game and then like uh
and then when you come back you kind of
forget everything i should yeah he's
really handsome yeah which which which
color is good like this is his like
student look and this is like this
phantom thing
on the blue one the blue one the
reigning joker yeah okay we can do that
okay
okay i don't have sound on so you know
this is the first time that you're
playing the game so i'm gonna go easy on
you like she didn't even practice oh oh
okay
so
we're on a random map here again you can
go up on on these platforms for example
wait this is so smooth
oh yeah we wanted to use the other
screen oh my god
[Music]
oh oh double click in the middle double
click
oh
i'll be i'll be so nice and show you
this item math for you oh no please it's
a math
[Music]
[Applause]
so and then normal hit is a normal is a
then and you can combine it with like up
a right a little bit down and down here
what happened to me
oh no don't hit me i'm teaching you why
i always already have 100 huh this i
told you before is the old team
uh you have to hit it a few times and
like volleyball like playing volleyball
i
i hit you i thought i was i'm getting
hit oh there you go see so i i activated
the ulti
and if you're in here on top of someone
and then and press b only b one b but
you have to stand in front of them
otherwise it won't hit them oh
okay okay okay okay i got you and some
of these items you have to collect
several of them what you just collected
was one of those i think don't go too
far outside because then
yeah you'll die
um
so and then so normal attacks are a okay
the special attacks are b b
and you have up b down b every b oh and
try them all out and see what you got
okay
here's a pokeball
ball
cute i love her my baby
i used her in my pokemon playthrough
there's another pokemon you tried uh
then how do i uh how do i with eight you
pick up with a and you're throwing a oh
it's a squared
well see on this stage i can even go up
here it looks like a background but i
can be a viewer and did you try all the
attacks no there's like okay okay
[Laughter]
all right hit me hit me
when we both still have like um too much
like the same amount of lives
and no one seems to be winning the
battle then they do a countdown and then
sudden death and one hit pretty much
decides everything okay okay
[Music]
so you uh wait yeah you won oh my god
you won oh my god i'm so good at the
game
first try i'm just kidding
you oh who's this oh
i know that guy i think i know him some
guy
he looks badass okay listen yo you hold
i know you from the gamecube times oh
[\h__\h] wait who am i you're in your choker
[\h__\h]
i didn't know which one was me wait did
i not get him oh i have to go in there
okay
[Laughter]
oh we don't need murph anyway it's okay
uh what stage is good you can choose or
you can go random
but yeah yeah let's take a look at the
shoes there's so many things
ah oh that's nuts
oh my god i tried to draw some mementos
oh that looks like personality yeah that
is persona 5.
and then we have a dress
yeah i haven't even seen all the maps
yet you can choose it's your game no i
don't care know it's your channel
oh it's my channel
what's an easy what's an easy oh ahoy
easy
easy easy well easy with maybe one of
the ones who don't move too crazy
let's make chad pick let's like pick a
random comment from him
you want the
memento story oh my gosh here do you
know about the toy story it's basically
just a story about how i um
[Music]
yeah that's not even like the comments
of the story
that's the setting of the story oh my
god okay i hate that okay yeah yeah
you know tell me something else um oh
okay i'll think of something you pork
city
[Music]
if you want you can try different ones
violence
like violence oh wait that's the wrong
one oh you're like not the guy no no
cute girl cute girl the
elven guard viola the the guy the guy
from the blue house that had his hair
look like you know string cheese yes yes
so uh
what else can i teach you i don't even
know much more than a and b maybe and
you know you can double jump how oh yeah
and okay here's maybe not a good example
but do you uh see any attack would be
where you feel like you know like mine
uh you could like um rescue i'm not the
same okay good so let's say you're
falling off a cliff there's no clip here
but yeah you when you fall off you think
you're dying you can rescue yourself by
aiming aiming at the closest cliffs and
bring yourself back up with that wait
why am i not doing that okay nice i
think what
anyway i started blasting
oh that's cheating that's cheating
that's cheating okay that's fine yeah
oh i have kelly's son yeah
[Music]
when you just
when you just came back from dying from
reviving then uh you are shortly
invincible
i need you forgot how to do it huh yeah
i forgot
you have to press b right in front of me
okay
no no no no no no
or as long as i'm in the same lane
you're in the same lane usually it
usually works
oh no i'm metal
oh amazing you lost it by the way it's
still floating around i i like kind of
kicked it out of you well you can't do
that yeah apparently
what is this why do i have things what
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
you have like an extra bar that i don't
have yeah it's like character it's good
it's not a persona thing yeah it's a
persona thing oh see now we have a clip
so if i if i um kick you off a bit
eventually
oh good job
wow oh bye-bye
oh the cliff is gone
oh no no not again
the game is telling us which is slow
again
wow what's that dragon okay thank god
that we already have some depth
i need to learn i need to learn this
it's so fun i don't know i don't even
own this game i was going to be like you
know when i first started playing the
switch getting the switch i was like i
want to buy this game like smash
brothers yes i don't even know
you don't have to press a oh okay sorry
i don't think any of the id girls on
smash either i don't know
yeah
wait we should change um some of the
settings
[Music]
you can okay
yeah we'll make this we'll make the game
longer yeah
teach me
turning on cpus and changing it to score
timer oh so it's not like a 1v1
press a to change it
i'll edit okay
style is
remove the baby oh maybe and maybe no
time at all
where am i here
like see feet
ah
stock oh yeah let's just stop um you
have like a certain amount of lives and
then whoever dies first is the loser
uh we'll do
we'll do
five stocks time limit
ten minutes or no no no time well there
oh there must be a time limit what's
them and now uh
ah oh my gosh i just yeah yeah the
weather is [\h__\h] the weather has been
pretty shitty today uh that was just a
stock that's the most classic one and
we'll do
15 minutes okay
wait no i don't want to name it just let
me save it
huh one more moment you know i have to
do that
go go go
go
and yeah don't worry guys weather is
[\h__\h] now but we went snorkeling in the
morning yeah yeah yeah yeah it was fun
i'm so glad we did it yeah
maybe tomorrow we will wake up early and
do that again yeah
i actually
i woke up so early today because i also
fell
like 7 15 or something
because i also fell asleep so early last
night right i felt like before midnight
yeah i was just so tired i didn't even
watch netflix i just said i gave my ipad
to dana and i was like you you can
launch but i don't
know
i'm so sleepy
[Music]
where are we we are in me and friends
see where b we're friends
i need to like um get used to the fact
that jump is up
oh
yeah
i need to get used to the fact that
jumping oh you have the suspension
flower oh you threw it away nice yeah i
threw it away like how do i even like
what is that
it heals your percentage if you look at
mine
oh as long as you're holding it it heals
it oh okay
can i borrow no cut
right now
no no no what is that
what is that i want to hold them
look
wrecking me
help she's way too aggressive you have
that fancy thing again of course
only the fancy people get to have the
fancy thingy whatever that is okay but
i'm also gonna tell you she's playing
with a pro controller that kind of gives
you a buff you're the one that has audio
come on
oh you got it
what the [\h__\h] just happened i don't know
i got the ulti and then it kicked me out
of the game yo
it's not there oops i'm being bullied
here
what
why am i being fully lend me your
headphones
oh
what's that
uh yeah i think that's a curvy item
oh my god
i'm really bad
you can't run over
[Music]
why is there a pokemon because i use the
pokeball
it's just saying hi goodbye pokemon
please no don't chase me around why are
you doing like this but it's so cute
look at it oh no
it left because you said you don't want
it
i wonder if it's on my side
what is that i really i don't even know
what this item is goodbye
forever what is that
what did that heal the stock fast
are you kidding me i feel like that
healed our stocks
ah so sad why do i not get the ulti come
here
oh no i can't yeah
now
are you
trying to get away from me
bye-bye
oh my god
this special i want to see what his
special looks like oh wait i'm still
alive ah no no that one i'm alive
yeah but like when does this end you
know what even if uh even if you didn't
get to play biologicals i'm playing
volleyball i'm very happy to hear
that you like bella i like violet and
then you like fire glam yeah i used to
watch your um
stream back then
she got the pokemon yo the cute grass
pokemon don't you like your veggies
you like your vegetables right
i like this pokemon i like it more
eat that
eat some stars
wonderful i like seeing them
the traffic
actually uh
would you like to
do you think you can tell them the story
of what happened to your floaty
yesterday while you're trying to kill me
um
i
uh what happened i wonder genie um so
okay the wind was like pretty good and
we wanted to swim
yeah it was really stormy really really
really stormy and then i was like
and then you know i'm too lazy because
like the float is really big it's one of
the floaties that like oh you're
supposed to lie on it yeah you know and
it was a big like illuminati eye
yeah but then um as soon as i threw the
thing
as soon as i threw the thing like in the
water it just starts going away
going away like getting washed we also
may have to note that it was high tide
so the water was so high and the waves
were so strong yes it was pulling the it
was pulling it in the
the booty
like gravity yeah it was flying away and
then
we were like [\h__\h]
yo we have to rescue it but it went away
so fast away so fast i was so sad i just
bought it i got so bad
it was so expensive too
it was so expensive it was so sad and
then today
[Music]
so right before the stream the weather
actually cleared up a little bit so i
was like elena i kind of want to quickly
go into the water
and
then i
um
i was like i was standing on like we
have like a ladder that goes into the
water directly from our big house thingy
and i was like i'll go in can you like
give me because it's difficult to go in
the water while holding the floatie i
was asking if she can give me the
floatie when i'm already in the water
yeah so i'm like okay i'm in the water
can you give it to me and then she's
frozen and the wind blows it away put
you on green yogurt is like okay i'm
gonna roll it downstairs okay and she
was like yeah
and then it immediately gets like blown
away by the wind
and i was like no it's not happening
again no but this way the floaty i'm not
i'm not focusing i'm finding that yeah
this way this time the floatie went a
different direction
and it kind of got stopped by
like different houses that were like
built on the water yeah and then it went
to like the other side where another
like house was overlooking the water and
luckily luckily there were some of the
yeah tourists were on their own balcony
and they were looking i guess at the
ocean and a lady she saw the floatie was
like floating away
and by the way when we talk about
floaties i i'm just meaning uh that that
that ring that you can float in i don't
mean that the one on your arms yeah
the big one wait what is it supposed to
be called
apparently you don't call it bloaties
and people think we're talking about the
arm thingies oh no
no no the big big ones you know okay so
the lady sees it and she immediately
runs into the water yeah like where are
those like rescues she she first put on
her the the flippers from
snorkeling i don't know how she did that
so fast but she put it on she jumps into
into the water and swims after the
floatie
like
so josue she was so good at swimming
yeah it was so fast she was like you
know like oh beach patrol beach
wrestling yeah it looked like she was
like a pro swimmer or something and she
while she was um swimming
that floating man it went
to places that i've never seen before
uh yeah so
she was really fast it was really
dramatic because the hotel staff were
also
like kind of watching what was happening
and
our butler actually just called like
someone to
from the staff to rescue it first but by
the time they arrived the lady already
grabbed the
the floating blue team yeah and gave it
to us oh he said i but i'm i'm like i'm
just feeling really embarrassed about
the whole thing sorry it was my fault
you don't need to be embarrassed
it's funny because it happened twice
i must think like what a bunch of stupid
and right before this happened
right in the message the butler what did
you say i um i told
her like hey can you
like hey can you uh get me like a floaty
that's you know like a new floatie like
i got yesterday or like
yeah so basically because like now my
float is gone she only has we only have
kiara's one yeah
and then
basically yeah you guys really
disappeared forever forever yeah i was
so sad no but like to be fair if i was
like to it was if i was like quick
enough about it then
she would be able to rescue me maybe
yeah how long are you gonna wear that
ulti around with you huh i don't know
can you like let it go for once what let
it go let's go like that loading that
you let go
what
what was that i don't know
i have no idea what's going on okay
listen i'm just like not looking
[Music]
and at
long okay at this point i almost want
you to just use it on me so that you can
like okay okay please no
no no no no no i'm not gonna give up no
no no no no no oh my god
so yeah yeah basically that happened
yeah now i bought something like uh
oh what's that big brain i'm a big
brainer what's that mean even
i can't even like go up oh i can never
mind
be brainy there's so many things in this
game honestly
chicken
is that your chicken i don't know it's a
it's a it's a wild chicken
my chicken now hold on
my chicken no give me
yeah my chicken now
oh actually i don't know if it's random
oh it's cute wait what can i do with the
chips you can hold it
oh now it's angry and it's attacking you
now oh no
oh my god oh is that a reference to
zelda chickens oh i don't know like so
many angrily started attacking you so
many of them
i'm really not using my my skills my
gamer skills even though
you're tutoring me that's fine yes
exactly i'm going easy on you
an icicle thingy an icicle that's cool
okay you already had like 200 oh my god
we're just waiting
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah just do it oh you missed it oh i
missed so good that's good i don't have
eyes sometimes
it's not sometimes but you know
yeah
okay i'm gonna i'm not gonna have mercy
anymore really yeah
you can't learn stuff when the uh when
the world goes too easy on oh
you'll just
be spoiled by the world okay and when it
attacks you finally you'll you won't
know what to do okay
ah i keep getting hit by the car
school bus
it should be more careful man
i'll be careful it's a banana it's a
banana yeah you want your bananas
breakfast
they have those cute little tiny bananas
yeah it's so cute and you like take it
off of the banana thingy by herself
in the first place in the buffet
and we have like a for breakfast we have
this big buffet and then you can also
order extra like waffles and peppers
it's really nice
okay
[Laughter]
revenge revenge protect me
protect me no
it's not fair you have to go easy on the
newbie
the last pitch was by yours truly
i love how it's like we're like red and
blue
um
oh last time we were streaming um on my
channel um
we were drinking like our children's
champagne oh look at him oh what a cute
baby
but today before the stream we actually
there were some like activities
[Music]
yeah
i think so i guess so
all right all right back to what i want
to say young link is available and
before the stream
uh we're told by our butler that there's
actually like a little class a cocktail
and mocktail mixing class going yeah
yeah so we
said
which one's fun i wouldn't mind a
mocktail
maybe we can participate so we took a
class and we were taught how to do a
margherita and then i was like sorry
dude i don't drink alcohol and then he
made an extra
mocktail for me
it was really yummy
it was good it was good she gets like
this special thing all to herself like i
mean but like there was like a lot of
people too and then like
it was like six yeah
that was that's a lot of people you know
six people collapsed yeah they're a lot
six people collabs they're a lot right
so i'm saying i'm just saying
you say that's a collab
are they be too faced yeah maybe
oh what the hell is that nice
oh i hate i hate this icon no
you sent it back to me and killed me oh
what unbelievable now i don't know what
i did okay i did my best
why am i so slow
my wife's a slow man in this world
yeah because i don't know
anyway you know i don't i don't know if
it's normal but these margaritas at
least were like uh served in really
small shot glasses
but everyone got those tiny shot glasses
for the margarita and then he made this
mocktail for me and it was huge like a
huge
big passion fruit and stuff right yeah i
got a huge well a huge cocktail i'm so
happy about it
no what is going on why is she killing
me
it's like you're like aren't you happy
what
if i'm not killing that means you're a
bad teacher
you even know when i'm
trying to shoot you
[Music]
here no please
please yeah
hello what is this
very cute are you
joker's overpowered i'm telling you
never no
no no no aren't you happy that your
student is doing
okay
aren't you happy yeah i mean i gotta say
i'm a really good impression
oh
oh yeah i'm getting the time
i like this one it's so fancy it has
like these special effects yeah
[Music]
i don't know about these i don't know
how the connection is like if we play
online because we're oh we're actually
having a off collab yo yeah
maybe you viewers don't realize it
they're still i'm probably thinking
we're in bali
yeah i don't know why like some viewers
are like oh they're probably in bali or
something even though we've already
talked about this vacation for so long i
know oh you all went all the way to bali
wow
so nice right no i went to want to
[\h__\h] maldives man
i don't know
that's uh that's somebody who's helping
you oh
[Music]
what else did we do today um we um i
don't know we woke up pretty early right
yeah because i won't be loved yeah you
were like poking me and i'm like
yeah i was really awake and i was like
oh the weather looks actually nice so i
looked outside and i realized
i saw that the water was really shallow
and like way way more shallow than
last time we entered and lost that
floating i was like lost that floaty one
maybe we should make use of this because
the weather really here it's so
unpredictable even when i look at the
weather report and it says next two
hours rain then uh
it still kind of changes and sometimes
it's sunny in between sometimes and
suddenly right after the
uh
right after this
sweet breakfast today yeah breakfast uh
yesterday right after the breakfast we
also had big rain like all the time man
yeah
i feel like today the weather is kind of
worse but also there were a bunch of
really
yes there was a bunch of i don't know
fun stuff that we could i don't want
this weapon anymore
what do you want yeah
why am i so [\h__\h] today
maybe it's because of the weather maybe
no what the
i mean
that was the map right that was not an
item i don't know it's just the part of
the map somehow oh wow
i got run over
oh no why do i keep getting run over
[Music]
man i get red i get run over all the
time that's why i have to be careful
yeah
we still haven't tried the bike right oh
there's like dust around here yeah i
don't know why
oh yeah okay we didn't tell uh we didn't
mention this
we did um post it on twitter but after
the breakfast we went back to a room and
i i turned on um i went into the
bathroom and i saw and i backed up that
was
oh so confused you were like i was like
i was following you and you were like
hey look at this look at this man look
at what
yeah it looks so romantic and my first
reaction was i thought it was like maybe
a mistake maybe oh actually i thought we
were in this in the wrong room and yeah
they were like are we in the wrong way
yeah
this is our stuff right
maybe they thought the maybe maybe the
housekeeping put it in the wrong room
and somebody else was supposed to get it
why the [\h__\h] did i get hit now
well
yeah but then uh later i asked our
butler if she did that and she said no
the housekeeping did that and it seems
to be on purpose there was like a no i
noticed it super late but there was a
note that was like enjoy yours
have a nice day have a nice day yeah
have a nice day from housekeeping or
something now we both have the old day
oh
who gets to hit each other first
[Music]
so sad
no no no
[Music]
put on your swimsuit immediately so we
put on our swimsuit yeah and we went to
anytime and we went into the bathtub
because it's big enough for two it's
like a whirlpool and it was perfect
because the moment we left the breakfast
it started like
a
rain so much so so we just watched
outside we were looking at the storm
outside and inside we were just enjoying
our own pool kind of
yeah so big that could be a bath
yeah
it was nice though i made a bubble
mustache yeah lena immediately started
playing
how do you uh throw away your item guys
what even is this how do you throw away
[\h__\h]
okay i don't know what happened i'm so
done with this game
it's
aren't you proud of your students you
got your the fancy side was that even
[Music]
i can't even look cool now
hello you look cool see here your thing
matches my pet
your outfit matches my my pet see it
looks like
oh
what's that oh it almost stays there i
hope
you put mental hole man
let me out what's that
there's so many items inside
[Music]
yeah they said like
oh what's that thank god stop there oh
pokemon see you have a pokemon you can
have a pokemon yeah i would like to have
it
but if you like me
[Laughter]
and then you can take
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
unbelievable um i'm just doing this
because i'm still teaching elena you
know
yeah
i wanted to have a good experience oh
get rid of items with r no ah
yeah
okay and then now it's too late
that's too late no it's not it's not too
late oh
okay okay who is this you want to play
oh like this is your game so like you
know i don't want to like lose
you
i i'll joke
let's go
what
yeah you have bonkers isn't that the
path from the wii u we think
we're moving
wait what this is so cool she's so fast
and agile what the hell i want to use me
for trainer but joker is good too never
mind i started joking already joke is so
fast man way faster than violence like
in movement yo um
i see
i need to experiment more with other
characters huh
yo
showing off with her yoga moves man
i'm just looking at what she's pressing
right now i don't know man
i'm looking at what she's pressing
through button smashing okay that's what
you do
yeah yeah yeah what you do but this is
also a cool map
nice spacey
yeah let's use this map later so what is
this before she's like
oh
what is this scares me
it's like someone took over her and is
controlling her but we have the cpu man
it's scary
this is not how i know the trainer from
we fit so
the dark aura
hey she might kill me man
if i'm not careful okay it's okay
honestly i swear today is the first time
i'm ever losing those um new character
matches usually yeah i always kill them
first try
before you also online like two people
right i think i can't multitask when i
play super smash brothers
oh my god this is from kirby right oh
yeah it says oh yes yes for me that
one's cute i watched enough sort of you
know senpai streams to know that that's
from curvy
have you ever played kirby no
that's right i wanted to try it but also
hey you wanna you wanna do you want this
place we fit studio
yeah let's check let's do it let's do
this um
oh they get harder with each unlock what
really oh okay are you for real are you
for real that makes sense yeah otherwise
because you're playing the game and
you're getting better too you you want
the fluid
and you want it to be a challenge
i'm going for mint green violet
mint green
do you guys like mint chocolate like no
it was adults no no green is the color
of vegetables
let's see if maybe now i can finally
show you who the real boss
who is this me
ceo of campy man
yeah
i am your student don't you be happy if
i win anyways like oh my gosh you're
teaching me so much stuff
[Music]
kept on using the same attacks you at
least kind of
seem to mix them
mix and match them
i guess
[Music]
can you please just like
oh my god she's so aggressive but you
have to be aggressive in this kind of
games i think
stop
maybe some smash bros
thank god man oh i'm out of reach for
the pokemon hallelujah
what's that that's like a rocket
launcher thing i think that you have oh
wait oh
fly higher or jump higher
[Music]
oh thank you for giving me a head start
no you're not the favorite i did the
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
looking better looking better give me a
chance please i gave you so many chances
it gave me so many yeah
you're always relying on this pokemon
but that one is useless do you want to
use this for real yeah
for real i mean at least in this
position
what in what position would it be useful
when i'm right in front of you
oh my god i'm sorry
why i'm so slow slow motion slow motion
a sword
a rifle
now i have no other thingies that you've
been using
[Music]
oh my god oh but it turns into you yes
it's me
it's you it's kind of like
[Music]
oh i already have a weapon so i can't
have the same thing next okay
nice you didn't see that one coming did
you nah i thought i could have double
weapons
but wait who's hitting me where am i oh
i [\h__\h] up
sometimes when there's so many like
weird item characters on the map i i
kind of lose track of like where i am
wow
pokemon so you're also relying on the
pool come on
but i think if you count how often each
one of us used one i think you
would see i've been using less
hello
fight for me be great
what's this
protect me what is the big brain
how do i shield in this game
ah i didn't teach you that huh but i
also don't use it so
it's probably better
[Music]
but you can't do it forever
it's a bubble see oh wait hold on
wait
you're so dirty you should protect
yourself from my attacks when you keep
on what do you mean holding on
is
[Music]
oh yeah he's placing all the bombs um
yeah yeah what is good
bomberman no
goodbye when you know the names yeah i
don't know all these games gift box
what's up
more presents
i love this item
[Music]
i didn't get a chance to see it it was
it all happened so fast yeah
okay
uh should we maybe try different
characters both of us
i don't know can you buy this if you
want to
it's up to you i kind of want to learn
more about this character this is my
first oh okay you can you can try using
different characters if you want oh i
really haven't really played this game
since the gamecube time it's been so
long
i want to try
never played inkling before i never
played splatoon before play samus
we have her no yes we do and no
what don't wanna
kirby
you want me to use those energy tactics
and energy strategies
and she always uses curvy and she only
uses two attacks
[Music]
oh my gosh oh it's a dark one
but we are orange
we are orange orange
yeah
all right yeah oh it has a stream
it's yours
oh my god it's this map so cute
oh yeah this guy is way faster damn
oh
okay you can jump yeah
okay i'm gonna i'm gonna absolutely
smash you welcome to super smash
super smash sisters
[Music]
i've never played this character before
i don't even know the attacks wait you
should give me a warm-up face too but
you're the one
i don't even know the attacks what is
this
a bomb
i don't know what that is ah my
boomerang
this is like an upwards attack and then
oh
ah
it feels familiar from just i'll also
like you know
check my attacks through that
you've already checked them
no not yet
okay fine
be that way be that way warm up time is
over
be that way if you're so desired [\h__\h] is
that why am i slow is that good or bad i
think that's bad no oh my god
people dying i don't know
what that is
usually every character has some kind of
a pop and b okay okay okay i'll open the
i get it i get it see it's an honest
mistake because i don't know the
controls
you have a
bird brain what makes you forget are you
a [\h__\h] bird
too i hate this map you know what yes i
also have a bird brain i will admit that
oh what is this spaghetti spaghetti but
you know what elena also has
what besides the bird branch is also
very very clumsy
uh the amount of times she hits herself
what do you do what are you gonna tell
them
she's very very clumsy always hits her
leg oops
and did you guys know how clumsy she is
kind of cute
it's kind of cute it's troublesome yeah
it's always the same leg so yeah it's
almost the same for some reason my right
leg is a little bit you know
i have like the unlucky leg the unlucky
leg is that i don't know why
yeah i can't even i can't even find it
probably in this man
and also oh my god one more thing
like suddenly out of nowhere will become
like you guys think carefully thinks i'm
really getting startled by horror games
easily
but reyna when she
like just sits somewhere normally with
me suddenly she will yell out and then
we're like
oh
i think like
she gets started by really really random
things
that that are not really that scary but
yeah yeah
[Music]
and they're like
this surprises me too i'm like whoa whoa
whoa what what what what are you
screaming for
well that was dead
i don't know
yeah i don't know how to get through
like this that let's see that when
you're on the on one it will go down
really fast you gotta jump off fast oh
that item just never gave us a chance
okay see like how do i how do i do that
see eh you jump in an upbeat to rescue
yourself
this map sounds so advanced it's not the
map for me
fight me properly don't make use of that
training take advantage of you it was a
random map take advantage of your newbie
student huh before you were killing me
the whole time yeah you were pretty good
and now suddenly
yeah that's because you were giving me a
chance you know no no i think the
difference is that i this character
suits me better i need to give up by
left you're welcome to use baloff now i
need a chicken
chicken
chicken okay i'm gonna use violets after
this you're not gonna use my left i'm
gonna use violet though and welcome to
you spotlight
try to figure her out it's the cutie
okay i love bottom of my fire emblem and
play more fire emblem
hello chicken you want the chicken
chicken
chicken chicken
i'm so sorry i hate the chicken
yes you're getting erased i'm giving you
a raise okay and forgave me i'm still
alive i can't believe i'm still alive
after all of
that oh my god
oh you got the oh yeah i want to see the
healthy oh
wow my eyes are glowing
gamma
[Music]
wait how long has she been out of the
room just now
huh have you guys been seeing elena all
this time
i just now yeah okay just because um
the batteries are dying
you should connect it
connect them
everybody
oh [\h__\h] that was the wrong thing no no
no no
we're gonna check something
i'm trying no room is still there yeah i
don't see either
we're both gone no no wait guys we'll be
back soon
well you should probably
charge it too yeah yeah
okay
troubleshooting
actually we had some technical issues
before
the stream too
because our internet wasn't working
anymore yeah
that's why we delayed actually
we had some
staff fixing it
[Music]
well she's
oh it's coming back
[Music]
but i have it sometimes too i say i said
ouch or so when something actually
doesn't hurt at all
just as a reflex
you know what it's okay we don't need um
actually it's also been an hour now
we only wanted to do it for one hour can
i can i try using violet for like one
game then maybe we can call it a day
okay
guys one more game one more game one
more game let's go oh wait i have a red
one
[Music]
this time i hopefully can manage to kill
so them
but there it's two versus one that's not
fair
there they're they're they're they move
they also know this world much better
nice background too yeah so pretty it's
like cold and breezy
[Music]
do your best to do this
i mean the character is this one
easier to play oh my god
[Music]
yeah it's not fair she's alone i still
remember the ice climbing map from the
gamecube super smash bros
what's your first
gamecube gamecube yeah
oh that's so cute yeah looks like a bear
looking thing it's my my first and my
only one okay okay okay
okay well what the actual [\h__\h] and i it
seems like i need to just how back in
the day when i was a child i need to ask
my brother wait wait wait wait wait wait
can we show you yeah i'm going back okay
uh we need to ask my brother to help me
uh
oh wait we choose the map first yeah we
chose the map version of the character
uh that's great i thought it was the
other way around
uh do we still want to do six maybe we
should do five yeah
cool
you still need to ask my brother to help
me and i'll be like
bro
oh need some please help me get those
phones so i can get more characters
i'm too bad at this game
yeah it's like you gotta ask somebody
girl like oh yeah i will unlock you this
many characters please you're gonna do
violence now i'm gonna do violence yeah
okay how do i switch to f by
[Music]
which color is good i don't want to do
the
green
i don't think the edelgard fallout is
hot
yeah it sounds like your color i'm going
to choose the deep bowl okay
last match and yeah we know that we know
that uh elena is still invisible but
she's just
that op
that what the hell is this man oh this
one is stuff did you choose randomly it
was random it was random yeah
i thought it was better because we can
know all kinds of no wait that was me i
thought it was violence because i don't
know what so used to being violent oh
wait wait let me check let me check oh
let me check oh yeah okay
[Music]
is
and then what what about like i feel
like i played this game in yakuza
as a mini game
i don't like music like how am i gonna
like practice
practice if i have to like focus on like
not falling and just stay on these
platforms they don't really move
they don't they always kind of like this
hello
no
you should be testing your attacks do it
yeah i know
i know
that's what i'm doing
that's what i'm doing that's what i'm
trying to do
on me
yeah you're on you like what am i
supposed to do
yeah you see you just check aha down
down um be inside up the right beans
down
up these dads
let's see that hey
you done
yeah i'm done
but yeah this map is kind of yeah see
that's my random spoon
like i know you're like a gotcha addict
but you know i'm already down to three
because
i was your punching bag
come here elena let me give you a hug
no
no let me give you a ground pound no
please i we love peace aren't you here
to teach me okay i'm like trying to like
ground pounds there we go
[Music]
you can't kill a child can you
i mean if i'm determined enough i don't
know you have no heart
you have no heart
i'm shocked i thought you knew
no i know you as a very
loving
sweet caring person oh you are mistaken
i only make mistakes in life
what is going on do you like retro games
like this one in the background general
retro games i mean i like it but doesn't
mean i'm good at it like i don't have
enough experience with them
i played zero of them
what's this
i'm not sure what exactly it did again
oh
i see i see i see
present
yo
i almost didn't hit you
[Music]
two four
i thought i was gonna be fine but then
dana was too talented i see it's my love
for violet i see it upcoming soon on
reynolds channel
super smash brothers marathon you're
going to be playing this all week i see
[Music]
wow that hit both of us is that what
happens when you when like two players
hit the ultimate ball no idea like i
have no idea what's ultimate bomb or
like what's not ultimate bomb or
something
no then while um why don't we have some
time is there an answer that was a fake
oh there's fake there's faces
[Music]
you hit me with a fire sword i hit you
from fire arrows that's cool
what is this oh they even go down when
he's down there normally they're not
just straight violet only has straight
arrows because
that looks great
but she was able to marry girls too
yeah but like only a select few of them
so like slash yeah i was so mad smash
bros things like oh no so maybe that's
not enough
but you know how
in fly emblem you can marry uh like
mary yeah marry the other characters
yeah yeah i was playing a female violet
and i wanted to marry a petra ah too bad
i was so in love with her and then
she was like
and then but then i heard that like if
uh like like petra um she doesn't marry
the female pilot but she would marry the
dwarf that was it dorothea because
anyone would marry dorothea or something
like that i think that was the thing
anyone marries dorothea anyone marries
dorothy but petra generally doesn't
marry uh girls she just doesn't like us
yeah
and i'm like what the [\h__\h] is up with
that uh dorothea you would
[Music]
yeah
i wanted to you know like i think it
would
i don't know i was just still kind of
salty because like you know as like
female
females you can marry elgar you can
marry like the the the the lady
the green lady and then uh you can also
marry the
i don't know but then like as male
violet i think you have less selections
like it's like you can't marry like
claude or something for example oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i'm glad i'm glad i have someone who
knows fire emblem
i don't really
know anyone in whole life english i
don't think anyone in hollywood has
played it before
real hot
okay well reina is not here but uh you
know what you'll talk i'll mouth your
words yes what
i'll smooth my mouth oh yes so thank you
guys for watching today's stream it has
been one hour it was a very fun baby's
first smash experience very cool smash
sisters and somebody's asking you know
how has melody's been treating you guys
it's been good it's been good we're
excited to i don't know eat dinner
very excited to eat dinner yes
i guess yeah yeah yeah yeah so i guess
um you know hopefully hopefully tomorrow
we'll have more stuff to do we have a
lot of stories but you know we were too
busy like playing the game so we
couldn't really tell it too much but of
course maybe eventually we'll you know
we'll have that recap episode
embarrassing i'm trying to exaggerately
move my mouth
um yeah i think tomorrow we won't stream
right we want a day without streaming um
and i actually have a lot of videos
still uh like
even more than i originally planned out
yeah
and so you'll see that uh i don't i
think we'll at least do one more stream
on the maldives
um maybe like on
around the end and and say
yeah i'll talk about the experience as a
whole
are there any videos for today yeah
uh well this is the stream this is the
video for dana's channel my channel yeah
i might upload something too
and
oh yeah oh yeah one more thing that i
don't know if you you have a talk to
your viewers about the fact that um i
was planning uh a song cover with us
together oh yes yes did you tell them
did i
i thought it was gonna be like still a
secret so i don't know i've been talking
about it uh a lot
um no they don't know that but i told
them that we're translating a japanese
song to english they know that
oh yeah i i told them as much as you and
i are doing something together but not
to the extent okay okay okay yeah
originally we wanted to release it
during the maldives but you know stuff
happened yeah yeah
we're definitely releasing it
next month on my channel so yeah but
besides that we have some more videos
and also uh maybe one more stream coming
up and we'll do our best to enjoy the
vacation
yeah i hope you guys will be excited for
it we have we still have more okay okay
okay so thank you for watching today
thank you very much for your attention
everybody
[Music]
really excited like when we were trying
to figure out some technical things oh
yes uh german yeah for example obs my
obvious is in german and she was like
reading things and i was like should i
change it to english for you and she's
like no no no i want it in german i'm
like really but you don't you're not
able to find the things you want to find
and she's like
i want to eat german i want to read
german i can't read german have it in
german at home and then like yes you can
change it and she's like still you want
to still feel it won't feel the same
just like you know like typing on the
keyboard like where the hell is the y i
would say oh yeah yeah my keyboard yeah
my alienware laptop is in german too
there's like some fancy lettuce with
some dots cnc german keyboard anyways
yeah okay
bye-bye bye-bye
[Music]
oh no no no no no no do we choose this
stream