[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
e
[Music]
a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
K ah
k
can you
guys uh hear
me I have two screens this time I'm so
prepared oh my God I prepared so much I
prepared even decoration for the table
oh my God can you believe it we hear you
with the other mic yeah I mean it's
supposed to
be this one you hear me punching the
microphone right it's well not my usual
microphone but uh is it
uh is it
quiet it's the right microphone I
think oh okay okay okay okay actually
cie had a really nice like separate
microphone for hand cam streams that I
kind of want to get but at the same
time I want to use the one I already
have
so yeah I love the decoration thank you
I have this like really old um Snowman
and that I bought at a Christmas Market
a couple years ago and look I have this
new
chicken which I don't know if there's
supposed to be a magnet inside cuz this
looks like a magnet but like it
immediately when I try to pick it up it
like lets
go so I wonder what happened there but
it's so well made so
[Music]
pretty chicken it's you guys I can
separate you very easily so be careful
what you say to me today and what you
say about my cookies it better only be
good
things no more laughing yeah but like I
mean it's not like uh it's not like we
[Music]
really need to see them that badly I am
protected I I cut holes into my shirt so
that I can go through it with my thumb
so that way
it doesn't like keep on like going all
over the place smart wow
[Music]
genius no more flen tuber oh no what
happened to me a so sad guys we are in
any case working on a
tight deadline and that deadline is
whenever this camera dies although last
time I did a members only stream how
long did I have this camera on the the
the puzzle not puzzle Lego Stream that
we did I think I think it was on for
quite a while like 2 hours
maybe and I charged it fully again so I
think it should be fine because in
theory
this uh these cookies that we're making
today are really like simple very simple
I chose a simple recipe because I want
to start simple I don't have much uh
experience in baking
[Music]
M uh
yeah making should not take so long yeah
um I mean really nothing should take so
long the thing that will maybe take the
longest is like
um
creating the decorations because I have
where is it here I'm going to be making
well first of all I'm going to be making
simple butter cookies I just got a
random recipe off the
internet um and then the butter cookies
when they're done I want to top them
with some normal sugar glazing which I
saw I don't have to buy I can just make
it myself with some powder sugar water
and a little bit of a lemon and I have
all that so uh we're going to be using
that and some other cookies I want to
try um to
cover them in this
Nut Chocolate uh it wasn't like this it
had a cover but uh I already opened it
and it's chocolate so this one I'd have
to uh
melt
but I don't
know I never melt chocolate and fury it
should be simple oh no chunky wonky is
here why are you doing chunky wony I
dare you I dare or I don't dare you
please stay where you are no no no no
nine
nine okay good good baby she jumped down
the the the chair she was on the chair
and sniffing the
table stay away I'm streaming girls I
know I'm not in my usual streaming
environment but that doesn't mean I'm
not
streaming so yeah I want to melt this it
says to like cut it up and then melt it
on a
on a a water
bed so on top of hot water I guess but
can I also just throw it into
the uh uh a
microwave it doesn't say here but like I
wonder if I can can I can I do that like
a little
bit should be fine no no I don't see why
not that's that's what I'm
thinking no no really that's a bit
annoying it will
burn what what if I do really low power
like 360 watt I think it's
[Music]
watt yeah I I'll just do it slowly I
won't even I won't even fully melt it
I'll just like not not so that it turns
liquid but it's just like melting so
that I can like twist it twirl it with a
spoon would that be okay cuz then it's
certainly not burning
right low power and yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah is that that okay I just kind of
don't want to I don't want to have to go
over to the kitchen side because then
I'm not here you
know uh and I I I find a water uh bath
kind of annoying to prepare we're not
Cooks well AR we all Cooks uneven he did
so do a little bit Yeah okay we can we
can try it right like a little bit at a
time you know probably would be fun okay
okay ah yeah wait so simple bter cookies
um bake them then uh decorate them with
the sugar glazing and the chocolate
glazing and then top them
with
sprinkles I bought oopsie I bought many
many sprinkles we have these
sprinkles then we have all kinds of
sprinkles and then I have some have some
older chocolate sprinkles uh but in
according to the date on the back
they're not good
anymore I guess I won't use them cuz I
have all this but it I feel like it will
probably would still be fine but you
know if we don't have to risk it for the
biscuit then let's not risk it for the
biscuit yeah I guess let's get started
with making the dough
um
[Music]
easy I washed it there's a few water
drops but surely that is fine right well
don't worry I don't really think this is
reflective it's like that type of like
metal where I mean it's shiny but can I
see myself in it no well I might be
regretting my words later
but I think it's matte yeah okay oh wait
no it's not like that [\h__\h] uh I put it
put it on and
then no reset yeah okay reset to zero so
it says 300 G 300 G meal and I bought
cheap ass clever German people will
know H glus meal it's like Smooth smooth
type 300 this is 1,000
so have you guys ever made butter
cookies before
you know I'm kind of scared because for
I have quite a bit of experience uh with
um cooking at this point with baking not
really and people always say baking is
easy but you just got to be really exact
with everything well I don't know if I
can be all right
300 free free sugar cookies baking is
easy we'll see about that nothing's easy
for
[Music]
me 100 oh oh smoothie has jumped uh over
the table like she's on a she's watching
from above cuz I have on the walls I
have some stuff mounted for the cats
oopsie H almost
there okay that's 300 nice to 300 M and
200 g bua the BHA I probably have to cut
a little
bit right
do I have to cut the
buot I think so we'll cut it into small
pieces and then slowly but surely add it
into their this whole thing is
250 buha Austrian buha this is
how this is how we uh sell butter is it
different than from your country I mean
we have it in some like plastic
containers too that's usually what I buy
but this is good
b b
bua and yo I'll be so happy if this
works like really quickly and really
easily I'd be
delighted okay well if M what did it say
250 or 200 250 so if that is 250 maybe
like so you can't you can't see that
what I'm doing right now I'm doing a
professional guest work how small should
this these pieces be I wonder cuz they
have to be mixed into this
whole
thing so I don't know I feel like they
should be relatively small like what if
I cut them into pieces like this this
looks like
[Music]
cheese just like this or even
smaller cut my butter into pieces this
is my cook baking stream looks small
enough you better way the ingredients or
the MK will be you mean like
separately I mean I can totally do
[Music]
that how do I wait let me get I guess a
like a like a a separate
container I touched something I didn't
want to
touch oh
well
okay how about I do like this is there a
reflection on that I don't
know one 2 3
4 that's kind of
big
five
six we are
at
M yeah still very far does this really
go up to 250 this this butter it should
be now we are
at 100 exactly
uh 200 according to this recipe I need
200 should have just gone with a recipe
that says 250 so I could have used I saw
a recipe that had 250 I could have used
that and then I wouldn't have to do this
so stupidly exactly oh well
at a fine Pace yeah I hope I hope I can
have these ready in let's say an hour
would be amazing for me because like
generally of course like this whole
baking process and all that I feel like
it's always um
slower cooking and baking I'm always
slower when I'm streaming
it oh damn the cut the piece that I cut
off is almost exactly the 50 g that I
didn't
want nice how about oh oh oh I'm can you
guys see a you almost you can almost see
the gram thingy here now it should be
NOP it didn't change I wish I had a more
exact one cuz I can't trust this one the
scale and now it's St two the [\h__\h]
okay this is what I have left goes back
back into the
fridge but you can do it in an hour well
I mean certainly other people can do it
in less than an hour oh my hands are so
greasy
[Music]
um by the way my my kitchen machine
that's going to mix everything is like
also in the back part of this room so
I'll I'll go there uh to mix it but
anyway uh two two two 200 right then 100
G Suka well that I
think you know what I can put it in here
if we want to have everything really
exact
separately I can put it in
there
100 the kitchen machine the kitchen a I
don't know cooking machine in German we
say cooking
machine oh one4 oh one out six oh
no they said I should be exact different
think six GR Raam is like Yeah
Boy And and then one egg it says one egg
I was surprised there's no milk in this
but I guess that makes sense cuz then it
would be more
like I don't know
pancakes it's fine it's fine okay here
here here it goes and then um I think I
saw like some videos where they put in
the egg after they mixed this first or I
don't know they were like doing some
things like separately do you think it
matters can I put in the egg
now our little friend uh
oopsie he gave me this egg thank
you sh is this on purpose I really
wonder I should hot glue it I usually do
it after it matters usually as it
mixers oh okay so let's make this into
something first and then add the
egg H really also I saw some people do
it with their hands I mean I could try
but you know I I don't think it'll be
that
[Music]
pretty I wouldn't until the butter is
mixed okay uh
then okay I'll I'll I'll throw it into
the
machine I'm still here though I'm only a
few meters
[Music]
away using like
um I'm using not this but like the one
that has like less of this and it's
thicker and it's supposed to be for
kneading I'll put this away I miss her
own shut
up I think that would be the right
choice instead of this probably yeah cuz
it needs a bit of
strength
[Music]
go
a
okay I put it on like pretty low it
surprised me cuz suddenly the the flower
went
[Music]
like that's a nice dist sound right last
time when I was baking something I think
I had it like on the table and it was so
loud right it freaked me out but now
it's like relatively far
away M that's that's nice oh you here to
bgm
right not a food
processor
[Music]
a maybe this is
better
wait come
on
now that I look at it doing the thing I
kind of want to do it myself because
it's like not probably if I wait it
would happen but I don't trust it I'll
do it myself yay fine I'll do it myself
yay I can do it right oh wow it's butter
it's
soft like I literally can't see how the
machine would be able to do this also
but I I don't know how I would be able
to do it it's not not really turning
into anything
[Music]
yet oh yeah right I have to like put it
into the fridge for like 30 minutes
dough the the dough once I have the
dough I have to put it into the fridge
for 30
minutes you like this
part and at this point it's normal right
that it's not turning into anything
right I need the
egg I don't know what's the right way to
do
this now the B was a fridge temperature
cuz that was important and they say I
should be fast because otherwise it
won't be cold enough
anymore use a whisk no you don't use
whisk for this yeah it's pretty Dry
still but like I don't know this is like
some
somewhat
okay okay should I throw in the egg now
I don't know what what I'm like what am
I looking for
my hands are already
exhausted oh this
exhausting mix it well it's mixed
well I'm surprised there's no in this
recipe there's no need for my vanilla
vanilla Suka vanilla vanilla
sugar kind of
sad maybe I'll throw it into
the uh
glazing it's not
bad actually not
[Music]
bad [\h__\h] this is exhausting until the
butter is well incorporated into the
flour I think it
is hold it shape crumbles with little
force it does it does it kind of does it
holds its shape but it crumbles with
little Force course
yeah okay can I can I put this
in can I open can I crack the egg let's
let's crack
it the opening of the
egg oh this is nice H high quality C in
4k oh [\h__\h] yay
eggshells I hate it when there's like
this like uh like some something still
there and it doesn't want to go out like
[Music]
why e
disgusting okay let's
go that used to be me well who are you
[Music]
now ex shell extra crunch no no nothing
went in there don't worry I'm like
pretty picky when it comes to stuff like
that I'm so careful cuz like because of
my cats I wash my hands like a million
times when I cook
something I'm really careful with that
oh it it's definitely more mixable
now oh
yeah but this [\h__\h] exhausting holy
[\h__\h] is this like ASMR does the
microphone pick these bounce
up he had dreams C hair is inevitable
not if you wash your hands five times
each each cooking
[Music]
step not really damn okay I I do want to
get an ASMR microphone just for like
stuff like
this I actually like the only ASMR that
I really find like interesting to hear
is cooking ASMR but still ideally with
some talking like not trying to be super
asmari it was just like having the
cooking sounds like chop chop chop and
the sizzling and all that that that I do
kind of understand okay what do you
think about this consistency the
texture is there someone who can judge
this who makes butter cookies
sometimes
what do you
think it it feels
proper I don't have
um uh the the clear wrap but I have uh
different wrap the the shiny silver one
I wonder if I can use that to wrap it to
go into the fridge for 30 minutes a
little bit more
okay more more more I see
[Music]
I can't yeah uh aluminum foil oh [\h__\h] I
can't please tell me it's over I'm so
exhausted probably also part because I'm
like reaching quite a bit forward cuz
this is like the middle of the table and
the table's pretty big and I couldn't
get the camera to get to go uh more
towards my
side I want to melt the but oh right
right yeah okay this is fine this is
fine this is fine this is fine this is
fine let me get
the the aluminum foil
[Music]
oopsie there we
go
okay okay wa aluminum
[Music]
foil
okay I like this don't worry this is the
less reflective side and
then yeah just what I saw they I saw the
like ladies putting it in in different
shapes one made like a sausage one made
a ball so I'll just go with
ball this will stick so hard to the foil
maybe I
should I mean that it's fine but I can I
can put some baking spray on if you
think that will
help that bad effect with
that still
[Music]
love oh
flour um anything
okay
[Music]
I mean there's butter that's basically
oil it'll be fine so that will go into
the fridge nice ball
y okay guys 30 minute counter
please and I shall maybe I'll change the
gloves I guess do I need to do anything
[Music]
or
now I I'll try to keep them on they're
pretty clean I
guess 4 the minute
counter should I turn off the camera
until then because then we can save some
um or I try is it too early it's
probably too
early can't finish my sandwiches I could
try to start the melting the the choc
chocol but I think it's too early so
let's turn off the
camera uh wait let me turn it
off here
first let's turn it back on in wa a
minute and I will take off the
gloves they're kind of
like they feel kind of moist
inside so yay yeah yeah yeah camera will
be back soon so ideally the plan is I
wanted to do one of these cooking
streams per week but I wanted to start
last week and I had to move it so this
is the first one and then until
Christmas maybe I can do like two more
cook uh baking streams I wonder if I can
manage to do that that would be nice did
you guys did anybody put a timer I'll
also look at the oh oh wait it is it is
a like 8:30 now so maybe at 9
[Music]
mhm maybe I'll sit down actually wow I
can sit down on my dining table so the
next step would
be uh putting all the the floor flour
over the table and then uh rolling it
out and then uh I have some shapes that
we can cut it out oh but we roll
it we already roll it out on on the
baking paper paper right let me check my
[Music]
video in the video okay she wraps it in
she puts it in the fridge she brings it
out she cuts it into like two pieces the
ball and first she rolls out the first
ball oh oh well that's on on on
normal normal table she just like first
like Kneads it a little bit
more then she rolls it
out
oh oh no okay she cuts she cuts out the
shapes and then places it on the baking
paper on the baking tray
N I have to mix some peanut butter or
we're trying I'm trying to do the most
basic thing ever here on purpose cuz I
want to start simple and then see some
progression in the other cookie baking
streams and then she bakes it for 15
only 15 minutes wow and I'm currently
already preparing the oven so don't
worry about that it's uh probably
already hot
enough sorry I'm late
welcome no
problem yeah maybe maybe we can do
something more advanced next week I did
do in case you're curious last year or
last last year oh the toilet cat
toilet's moving was it last year or last
last year when I met the vanilla vanilla
quo
cookies vanilla kipy the Austrian
[Music]
ones work your way up to macarons no I
wouldn't dare to challenge
macarons that was a while ago right I
made it with pre-made dough oh my God
maybe I did that's that that's so
cowardly did I
really are you
sure wasn't that the for was it
really I
did but I did I pre-make it or was it
the store who pre-made
it I could have been the store the
gingerbread house one my mom pre-made
the
dough uh because it's like kind of
difficult and then like we made it
together though we made it together and
then I put it together on
stream my C aren't that hard really what
so link uses the recipe and make it for
real did you want to make L yes next
time maybe I I hope I can make
them ah the Hilton cookies wear from
scratch oh my God you remind me of
wearing the best cookies ever oh yeah
the Hilton
cookies remember okay for guys for the
people who don't remember I uh went to
London like what 2 years
ago uh with my friend with my old rmt we
used to live together uh and then we
went to London together for a little
trip it was winter time and we stayed in
a hotel that was by Hilton but it's not
a Hilton it's a yeah a Double Tree why
are you why are you spelling it out like
that um and uh oh Bak laava oh she loves
Bak laava was it really two years ago it
feels ages ago honestly was it the
double Tre yes yes you know they're good
you know you know right oh my God it
seems like a thing they do all
throughout all of the Double Tree uh
hotels I wonder why they don't do it for
Hilton and so on they totally should but
they those hotels they always have like
these fresh chocolate chip cookies that
are so good and really big and like kind
of uh chewy too I think H yeah you can
get like fresh ones when you check in
they give you fresh ones and some like
you're only supposed to get them once I
think but like I would go there again
and and ask nicely if I could get
another one and they of course give one
to you I mean why the hell not right so
yeah and they're warm yeah that's like
oh like especially cuz we went to the
hotel in Winter and London was just so
[\h__\h] unbearably cold and then you go
to the hotel you finally arrive cuz that
Double Tree it was like pretty much on
the outskirts of London it was kind of
weird weirdly placed weird location and
we finally arrived and we're like uh but
then we get co uh warm fresh soft
chocolate chip cookies from the
reception and I was like okay this is
the best hotel I ever went
to [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah
little did you know the W wobbling water
is a new future yeah that was a
different London trip yeah honestly we
should have gone to that stupid Double
Tree Hotel again cuz that was the same I
went with the same lady yeah yeah we
went to London twice we went to London
twice and once to Greece uh where I
almost broke my neck speaking of
oh yeah yeah we went on a couple trips
until now now I hope I hope next year we
can go on another
trip yeah we only went to London this
year I was hoping we were kind of
talking about going somewhere else too
like uh maybe Spain or so but like she
already had plans and I was like she was
offering for me to tag along but the
place where she was going to go to was
like a pretty
random City that I don't know if I would
like to spend my holidays there I mean
it looked nice sure but like it wasn't
really a holiday vacation
destination uh yeah so I was like no
maybe not also the the timing was not
the best
either I'm to Mexico oh I think just
today I saw a picture I think get did I
was it Mexico like it was Mexico of a
Mexico Beach yeah and the water was like
actually so nice looking I was surprised
does Mexico have like pretty
beaches feel like finding pretty beaches
all over the world is actually kind of
difficult at least in Europe it's kind
of difficult you know like the like the
most popular beaches are all ugly and
not
nice you do like maybe like if you have
a car it's like nice like easier to find
nice be Beach is because you can just
drive around and stop wherever you want
but if you're like if you have to rely
on public transport or whatever or
whatever Google says you know then H not
much choice they have pretty beaches all
right Mexico's beautiful come to
Portugal I want to that was also one
thing I was considering maybe next year
for sure I want to travel more of Europe
next year Mal has some great
beaches I I suppose so I wasn't blessed
to see it yet ask crony how Cancun was
oh wait oh yeah Cancun is Mexico
Mexico
oh I think I looked it up when she told
me that she's going to conun I looked it
up and I saw how far away it is and how
expensive the flights were or like how
how not existent they
were it's so far I'd rather go like
somewhere else then I think I
know unless I don't know unless it's
like with someone for some reason like
if a end of a whole life member really
wants to go to Mexico with
me
man you better not forget to go to Spain
I I I I mean I've been there I I'll go
again anything that's like close by you
know I'll go I'll
go
yeah the Canary Islands oh I I looked at
the Canary Islands too but something
about them was also like um like too
expensive or yeah I think it's too
expensive or or actually surprisingly
far or something like that something
that just didn't really you
know support me going there uh oh yeah
you know what I let's talk a little bit
about about uh what I was doing last
night uh besides watching the game
awards before I watched the game awards
until [\h__\h] past 500
a.m.
um I oh I do want to go to Okinawa I
never been been to Okinawa I've been to
Croatia yo yo when I was younger and
anyway I was I was uh finally trying to
set up my my $113,000 accent
suit and I got it to work to the point
where I can record some something but I
haven't tested my $6,000 gloves
yet uh because I just wanted to like see
generally how it works and like if I can
make the program work and everything
um I don't know like from what I
saw like compared to the other home frd
that I used like mopi and the other
thing that the one who shall apparently
not be named for some reason um those
like like are really
cheap compared to what I have now so
stuff that really doesn't work is like
jumping and running and all that because
first of all like you move around you've
seen probably in all the other girls'
streams how they will like get further
and further away from the screen
right stuff like that happens and also
like when you jump uh you could suddenly
within one jump just zoom out of the
screen or it will just not really like
see it will not really accurately show
your jump like you it won't really look
like you lifted your legs at all stuff
like that is like really
[\h__\h] um the rest isn't even so bad oh
but yeah I also what I what I would have
liked to see more was like um you know
any kind of hip or chest movements are
don't look
as big as it it's supposed to look like
in reality at all um so now I thought
with this one it will be better the
jumping I can say yes the moving away is
not happening and and the jumping like
you can really see the the body lift off
of the ground and all that so that's
like really accurate um so no issues so
far it's really smooth there's like
no not much jankiness to it I mean I
maybe have had some chunkiness but it
was only probably because of the first
time there can still be made some
improvements probably I can figure it
out probably hopefully I better because
I spent so much [\h__\h] money on it um
but the like the the hip and the chest
movements I'm still like not really
satisfied TBH but whatever in the end
this is just like
for yeah like not for I wouldn't use it
for like a like a proper like 3d concert
like my upcoming birthday concert right
but I can use it for like a little K
dancing or some YouTube shorts or uh a
music video it's fine too in my opinion
because in the end a music video will
not be like fully dancing anyway like
you can always cut some weird Parts out
and all that but at least I can like to
some extent record
choreography I would hope and then yeah
not fly to am for every freaking music
video you
know does it also use a base station
uh base station you mean like something
to put on the ground so it knows where
the ground is no surprisingly not um but
that's like normal with these types of
uh motion capture methods that because
those are those are like trackers and
stuff that you put on your body and
they're connected by Wi-Fi uh and
they're sending signals rather than what
Amma has is like a whole room where
there's like these uh lenses these
cameras all over special cameras not
normal cameras and and you put you still
put on a suit and trackers but they're
different
trackers and the cameras detect The
Trackers the more cameras you have the
more accurate it is uh and this is
generally more reliable but more
expensive um but the suit that I got is
like I would say the most expensive
version of that kind of
tracking like as expensive as it can and
I mean within X since there's still more
expensive options a little bit a little
bit more expensive um but yeah like
compared to M and so on which is like in
the same category basically what I have
now is like the as expensive as it gets
there's not even much in between from
what I've looked researched there's like
really cheap or really [\h__\h] expensive
yeah can you go to the toilet with it
yeah actually yeah so xense has a a suit
option where you put on a whole suit and
zip it up and The Trackers are already
inside or you get the The Trackers that
you put on straps and the straps you put
on yourself and then you put take them
off again but generally you're wearing
your own clothes more or
less uh and I have that because I I
spoke with kodu who had has the same
thing and he said that's like uh more
recommendable
[Music]
apparently so I could do that
yeah but for
me it it wouldn't look as Derpy as when
M Senai did it because my uh suit is
like way more uh higher in
quality I would hope it wouldn't look so
therapy I know that that was funny but
if my suit looks like that if my suit
shows such movements I'm giving it
back but yeah my next step is trying to
figure out how the streaming works it's
kind of difficult to figure it out
because there's no one else who tried
accents with our whole life application
before uh like connecting the accents
program to our application I tried it
last night and I just I don't know I
just couldn't find how to do it even
though it should be similar to how they
connect other things but I just couldn't
find it and I was trying I was trying I
got the other things to work that seemed
pretty difficult to me and I
oh I could show I could show
you
uh yes so
yesterday uh the little data that I
recorded I didn't know what to do with
it because in the end it's just like
like weird um body data without a body
and I I sent it uh to chagy because I
thought maybe chagy can figure out how
to use this and hell yeah he can thank
god um so maybe I'll
actually I could show you this the first
test without finger
tracking and with without I mean there
there's still maybe some there's room
for improvement and there's no finger
tracking yet do you want to see it just
a small like me jumping
around so we we we're going on a journey
with this guys we're going on a Kiwa
tries to figure
out uh how to get
decent uh very basic but but still
hopefully high quality motion capture
going in her
[Music]
home
yeah
okay I I think it has no
[Music]
sound okay well also like the thing is
like it's on a put on my MMD model I
think so you know it has that usual like
skirt messy skirt thing going
on but yeah okay
uh so hands obviously [\h__\h] up and I
think like I was wearing the gloves that
come with the accent so I do have gloves
on but no finger tracking but even the
gloves for some reason they were kind of
um turned around I don't
know I don't know
but okay see the legs move
nicely no weird jankiness so
far also no face tracking at that point
either see this is what I mean with like
the the the upper body is absolutely
stiff as [\h__\h] like I was you know doing
like a like a low key twerking and a b
uh booby
popping but see how stiff that is so
that's really unfortunate for
$113,000 I'm quite disappointed but yeah
there's no Dynamic there but the rest of
the body is
fine here
unfortunately I don't know if I can fix
that because I I put my hands together
above my head but like one is going into
my head so they should have been at the
same position pretty much but I don't
know and here's the jumping I'm not
moving I'm actually jumping you can see
I'm jumping the legs are lifting so
that's like for me that's that's amazing
so there's potential I I would
say whole torso is like a box yeah get
more trackers that's not really I don't
know if that's possible um the thing is
how many trackers did I have on I had
two on my on my back
shoulders oh yeah there's and there's
one on the neck like on the on the
collar
pH yeah that's like pretty much it and
then one on the on the hip on the back
of the hip on the center of the back of
the hip I think that was it that is like
really barely anything
yeah I'll ask them if there's any any
way I can improve if they can send me
another tracker or so oh actually I
think I had two trackers left over did I
no nah no I didn't no I didn't no
trackers just the straps were left over
but yeah that really leaves something to
be desired but I need to try to like
dance a little bit with it and see how
it looks if I dance something
proper it'll be fine for a music video I
I think I
think I wonder how much they'll charge
if I ask for one more
tracker Honestly though the the the the
gloves make up half of the price
so
it's probably one more tracker won't
even be so
bad yeah yeah I'm just starting out and
and I'm offered her help even though she
doesn't have an extent suit but she
offered her help she's so sweet I feel
so bad like asking people all the time
for help but I don't I'm kind of lost
right now I Tred to do everything as far
as I can but
yeah
[Music]
crating settings no there's like
honestly the calibrating is also kind of
[\h__\h] up like I had like I I I
calibrated like several times and then
um most of the time it was like really
iffy and it says that the calibration
process was poor did not go so well it
says like in the message then one time I
I I figured out uh a way to get a like a
d decent calibration and said this one
was okay decent and that's what came out
of that decent
calibration
[Music]
mhm she probably wants to learn how to
how it works to yeah maybe
[Music]
maybe asking for help do to feel bad
about thank you oh I think I did I made
you polaro by the way guys I it's in the
in the pin comment so you probably saw
it but uh I finished the BS before the
stream I did it there were still so many
uh but I signed
130 Polaroids so if you still were
waiting on the Halloween Polaroids they
should be up
now yeah I finished I finished let's go
did I miss the stream no we're waiting
for uh my dough to it's almost done I
think we can like get it out in like 2
or 3
minutes it's in the fridge
now Christmas po wordss yeah I'll
probably be doing Christmas polar wordss
I need to hit up D but I I don't think
I'll do as many options this time and uh
I'll
probably raise the price again back to
the original
press because otherwise there'll be too
many I hope that's okay inflation guys
inflation yeah sorry guys I'm happy that
at least like maybe sometimes I can
offer them cheaper and I'm happy that
some people were able to get it this
time
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah but I I I realized um I
made it too cheap no like it's not
really too chip like I it's obviously
like more than enough for it but uh it
it it it makes me suffer from success
yeah yeah yeah maybe limit how many
you'll
do yeah I could do that too but then I
feel so bad if someone comes into the
stream later and misses out and like Oh
no I got just cut off oh no I don't want
that either I don't know that's
difficult we'll find a balance I'll do
them every once in a while so in the end
I think everybody who wants one will
will eventually be able to get one
[Music]
so yeah hope I can afford but but this
time you got one too didn't you I
remember writing you
one why DJ Callet
approved couldn't make it cheap but 50%
could make it
cheap what you're too good to us am I
you too good to me too we got to be good
to each other we got to try to give each
other back what we want and you know
give what you want and receive hopefully
what you
want what outfit would you use for the
Christmas b word oh I don't know I'll
just put on like cute aets blue is
working on some I
heard maybe until then then I have cute
Christmas
assets yeah I could also just use the
ones that I made which don't even look
so
bad the one you drew look cute thank
you good to each other in a circle of
good exactly exactly reindeer waa I want
to be a reindeer oh actually no you guys
should be my
reindeer you guys should be the reindeer
did you see the new monster hunter game
yeah but I'll be honest it didn't really
like i' I've I've never been like so
deep into Monster Hunter I tried it for
like two
streams
but I don't
know I don't really I don't know it was
not really my thing but I saw other
things that were interesting to me I'll
talk about it once uh uh I have rolled
out the
dough so let me turn the camera back on
smovie is sleeping like an angel on top
of
the cat uh what do you call those
[Music]
things camera on oh what it says it's
still out right cuz I was I guess I was
still connecting it to the laptop so the
laptop was charging it it's back at
100%
[Music]
wow
wait where is
[Music]
it on show
time let me put on gloves
again Jing
gloves a one a
two
I'm so glad I like figured out that I
should just use these gloves oh wait
it's actually not moving wait I'll
figure it out in a moment instead of
remember when I was like doing stuff
with like like cooking with clothing
glovs still which as long as you don't
have to touch anything I guess it works
but
[Music]
still okay do you hear this this is ASMR
did you hear that I held it really
[Music]
close oh oh no it's moving hi
hi rber
ASR okay and then piing of rubber I hope
my dough not be like
rubber so we have to like knead it again
and then oh I guess I should first
before I start kneading I'll get rid of
this this um before I start kneading
I'll
put uh here some FL flour F FL
flow speaking of flowers did you see a
clip of um crony teaching hot some
I have to
say I'm sticking out my C so funny to
me good job
crony I love how she enjoyed herself too
you got to like be in charge of your own
happiness you know and she took charge
of her own happiness which I respect see
I I don't like that I have to do it here
because there's this like middle thing
cuz I have a table that you can make
bigger and this is the the big version
so it comes with these
cracks that's
unfortunate hopefully it won't affect it
too
[Music]
much go go
there
okay and then shouldn't there be some on
the I guess I'll do that in a
second problems yeah we'll
see we'll
see get all yeah don't worry I'll clean
it afterwards I I had this before all
right here it
is looks like dough I
guess wo nothing's sticking at all uh
wait I'll I'll I guess I'll cut it in
half too and then put the rest back into
the fridge
[Music]
look at this
texture
interesting it looks like I could eat it
already cookie dough but not you
shouldn't eat it
right put this should I put it back into
the fridge we let's see how fast I am
hopefully I'm relatively
fast okay and then I put it oh yeah I
need it I need it a little
bit like a pro oh this is exactly the
movement that the lady was doing I think
yeah yeah
oh yeah oh yeah you like that you like
that huh put it back in really probably
fine look how fast I am I feel like this
is already already exact exactly what I
want all
right okay and
now
uh now we roll it out and for rolling it
out I feel way more in control over this
at least and over my other cooking
and baking
streams so that's a good
thing remember this
friend
I don't like this feeling it's really
rough I hate
it I hate it
okay there's so much dough here now is
that
okay okay let's go roll it out oh I
don't really know how thick it should
[Music]
be
how thick should it be
[Music]
guys that's probably not like a that
uh not not not like that like 1 mm is
going to make such a critical difference
right 1 to 2 cm no wait that is like not
that big but I
think
okay it's probably
fine probably if not then we have
another batch I I bought some basic ones
I I I know I had some like really
interesting looking ones but I honestly
I just wanted some simple basic shapes
like the basic the basic ones you know
just the basic ones so we're going to go
for the basic ones actually let's go the
heart stop
dle we're doing
it oh wasn't there like an advice that I
should
whatever
oh
oh how many cookies should we make how
many cookies can we make a this one's
actually quite
[Music]
oh didn't think that through oh the
light do you see the flickering my my my
LED light is flickering like
crazy oh the cookies as many as possible
a million we'll have to make at least
enough so that we can also feed the taco
dais because you know how desperate they
are for
cookies and I just don't get
them that's kind of sad I can't look at
that and
anymore they have an interesting crunch
when I go through with the the stencil
do you do you guys see the flickering is
really bothering bothering me right now
let me
try
off see what difference that makes
though holy
[\h__\h] it's good that I had the the light
prepared oh it's still flickering I
think
M I mean do you see the flickering not
do you see the
light guys come
on oh so many cute
hearts you don't see it okay well it's
really
like um throwing me
off but I'll try
to I'll try to ignore it oh no it's
really bad what the [\h__\h] wrong with
[Music]
you maybe I maybe I'll just leave it off
for a little while maybe it needs I
don't know some time
off sorry it's going to be a little bit
dark
for maybe uh a few minutes actually it
doesn't look so bad without either
but I'm a professional
YouTuber so I want the best quality now
that I have this great camera I realize
the only way to get the most out of it
is if I get a good
light y it's going to be all Hearts
uh oh I made too many hearts but one can
have never too many hearts
right but this is like how thick it is
that'll be fine right going to place
some on the seet
[Music]
now looks great looks good they're so
soft a babies I don't want to hurt them
I feel like I I can easily squish them
the hearts I don't want to break the
hearts m
[Music]
it's it's little chicken
heart very very
sensitive don't want to
hurt these what what do you call it
vulnerable SK hurts got to treat them
with care and love and
respect well that one might have been a
little bit too
thick probably
f
they eventually get broken when they
eaten don't say that don't even mention
that I will not eat these
cookies until the stream is over now
just kidding oh I have to eat them all
stream you know what we'll make the
first batch with um the normal sugar
glazing I think so that I can focus on
one thing and then the second batch will
try the the chocolate glazing how's that
[Music]
sound I will not eat them now no I don't
want to get salmonella or something like
that and break my
tummy then I wouldn't be able to stream
tomorrow
probably oh yeah I was going to talk
about what looked interesting to
me um uh during the game awards let me
tell
you um I think one thing was from the
Moon Studios the creators of Orie one
and two you know that there's is
Austrian Austrian Studio game Studio
which I'm really proud of the fact that
they're
Austrian um because there's not really
much from Austria to be proud
of uh but yeah they announced a new game
and you guys may have also found it
pretty interesting I saw really good
reactions from
[Music]
everywhere what's it called uh no rest
for the wicked
right it looked like uh was it also
metroidvania I'm not sure
actually let's make some
[Music]
Stars
mhm looked really good right I already
forgot everything but it looked really
good yeah action RPG true true true they
did say something about that so I really
like the
visuals and I'm I think I'm pretty
excited for it and then besides
that I knew about the series but I never
played one before the Mana the Mana
series
they
also announced a completely new one
right no remake or
so one
tree and that one looks
amazing
[Music]
yeah uh what was it uh uh what did I
call
it something of
Mana what was
it Visions yeah visions of
Mana okay I'm basically done I'm scared
that I already had it out for too long
but uh should be
fine they're like they feel softer than
before
now I
think here this is what we're working
with I can only do one at a time anyway
I think so let me throw that in right
now and then I think it's 15 minutes 15
minutes counter guys
[Music]
please yay I'm
excited I'm so excited wait let me let
me actually put this uh back into the
fridge though
got to go back cuz 15 minutes is pretty
[Music]
long
okay feet sickens the table scraps no
you'll get sick I don't want you guys to
get sick
[Music]
either look this is my
my new cup that I also got from
fans it's from the soul
Starbucks it looks really
[Music]
nice really cool right come
on I think this was probably given to
the staff ages maybe even over a year
ago and I just received it on my last
triend
shrimp eating raw cookie though y o n I
would not want to risk it right
[Music]
now I never I don't think I ever tried
it
before I'm too
scared was it from popcorn I I assume it
was but I'm not
sure I don't know I don't even know
which Korean bro gave me that but if
someone knows oh this is from me then
let me
know cookie dough ice cream is good yes
I love cookie dough ice cream anyway did
someone look at the time it's already
been like what 2 3 minutes maybe now how
long should we wait you guys have a
timer can I rely on you guys I'll sit
down a little
bit although I guess
oh no wait a little bit I'll wa a little
bit been 2 minutes okay maybe maybe if
there's 5 minutes left I can bring the
dough Back start preparing it and I roll
it out probably by the time I roll it
out I can take out the other cookies
from the
oven
[Music]
and oh my God why is she so cute H I
wonder if there's a preferable timing of
when you put the decoration on the
cookies can already be cold right or do
they do you want the cookies to be cold
I
[Music]
wonder H who's being cute smoothie she's
like she's up there she's so cute like
just by being herself and just by being
a ball when I was signing my Polaroids
for like 2 hours
today uh she was also like right next to
me next to my keyboard next to my screen
the whole time so every time like
sometime I I signed with the left hand
with the right hand I was petting her
then I had to let go because I have to
save uh under the right file file name
and then I go back to signing and
petting and tap tap tap tap and signing
and petting tap tap tap tap signing and
petting and she was the whole time she
was curled up in this nice fluffy
ball so
good
want to go annoy her no no know and then
I have to take off my gloves and all
that no no let's not annoy her
now such a super cute and annoying baby
yeah she woke me up uh like wait too
early again tonight and then when I woke
up I was like what the [\h__\h] I
feel
terrible somehow like my my head was
like m
how to say I don't know everything felt
so heavy
and
just I didn't I felt like I was getting
sick um yeah
so I gave her food so she would shut up
I went back to sleep and when I woke up
finally I still had a headache a
headache I felt a little bit better but
still had a headache but I just took a a
painkiller because I wanted to get
through the day and do this
stream yeah not necessarily feeling
better I only think I feel better
because I took the
painkiller yeah I don't know it was
weird I had this weird groggy feeling
yeah yeah yeah
yeah but I I think it's like yes head
pounding yeah just
feeling groggy but I think it was maybe
because lack of
water and lack of humidity and yeah just
[\h__\h] like
that maybe I I may have not been
drinking enough water hydrate
everybody ah lack of winning game of the
year for ttk yeah I mean I feel like I I
totally understand why balers gate won
it and I I won't say I didn't they
didn't deserve it cuz like the more I
thought about it the more I agreed with
it that Tok shouldn't get it because
breath of the wild Got Game of the Year
right and totally deserved I don't know
if if breath of the wild was up against
Boulder's Gate if breath of the wild
would have still gotten game of the year
what do you guys think but now I think
breath of the
wild if if it was breath of the wild and
there was no Tok yet versus B gate free
then for me personally it would have
been a way harder choice because then
the like the freshness the newness the
uniqueness the the like amazingness that
is breath of the wild would have still
been like something so new right but Tok
is basically the same game just with a
new
gimmick same map same world I didn't
complain about any of this this is not a
critique point for me but certainly a
point where I can say like if you give
Game of the Year award to
Tok you basically already gave you're
giving it to the game a second time you
know what I mean it's like basically the
same game if TK had a completely new map
maybe the graphics a little bit like
changed up and all that then I I could
consider it an like a new separate game
that might
also be uh um what's the word deserving
of a game of the year award um bre of
the wild definitely deserved it did Tok
deserve it now that I think about it in
uh if there was no other good contenders
maybe yeah but against balers gate
no balers gate is also just like breath
of the wild was I would say In This Very
year at this moment it's something new
that stood out
so much just like breath of the wild
stood out but TK now unfortunately
doesn't like throw you off your feet
anymore because you already witnessed
most of this already with breath of the
wild yeah doesn't take away how amazing
Tok was I [\h__\h] love that game and
honestly for for in the in the category
where it did win in the
action adventure action RPG no not RPG
was it action
adventure that's fine totally think it
it can get that award where what was the
competition anyway again what was it
again acual Adventure
yeah probably isn't going to be top for
like a
decade yeah I mean in the same category
in the same like type of game probably
not lies of PE lies of P I never looked
into that game so I really can't
tell may have a lot of bugs but still
delivered in all the important aspects
and then still you have to think about
wait in in the uh Game of the Year
category were they all AAA games or were
there any other indie games besides
balers
gate you tell me cuz I don't remember I
don't
know all see see that's even more
amazing because that then the the one in
the game that got nominated
wins against the triaa games which
hopefully will teach all the Triple A
Studios a lesson I mean not that their
games are bad but maybe I will tell them
it show them give them a sign that you
can't just lean back on this now look
how these in games are coming for you
and it's not even any game of the year
No it one game of the year so be careful
guys be careful companies it's not any
see I also have like that's that's a
discussion we went into in my preet last
night can you still consider B gate an
indie game cuz like it it doesn't feel
like an indie game to me but officially
I guess it is an indie game but now then
I was saying like Okay if it wasn't in
the game until now could could you say
that from now on it will maybe be
considered like I don't know a major
game because I mean look at what it has
delivered can you still call this Indie
it's
AA okay then I guess it's not
indie yesterday people were telling me
it's Indie it's Indie it's Indie it's
Indie so I just uh listened to
that but still that's still like same
point though still like all the AAA
games versus one small company who put
so much love and passion into one
game like their
reaction says every like if I look at
like these
AAA game companies going up to the stage
to receive the award don't they most of
them or like all of them seem like
pretty calm pretty Collective this isn't
a big deal to them not really but then
to laran Studios they seem so moved and
so emotional and like this was a hugee
big deal to them like I don't think they
took it for granted either you know and
like they they really appreciated it so
that that was really nice to see yeah
all right I will uh get the the dough
and in in a few minutes we'll get the
the baked dough let's go so let me turn
this back on the
[Music]
pH
I smell the
butter
oh I think they're supposed to be like
really slightly brown
right just really slightly
oh really slightly Brown now right now
they're still very very light
so maybe I should you said you guys say
3 minutes I think I'll let leave them in
a little bit longer than
that
uh in the
meantime cuz they might have been
thicker than the one from the
[Music]
lady the bodyy smell can you smell it
cuz I definitely
can okay the second batch because one
batch of cookies is Never
Enough all
[Music]
right
yeah's go we're back in the
game but yeah besides that um besides
those two games did anything I mean some
games I reacted positively to but games
that I really felt like I want to play
was there something else guys for the
people who were in Pre yet
there's something else that spoke to
[Music]
me big walk I don't even know what that
is
[Music]
anymore I yeah the game by the goose
game makers just because it's like a a
relatively cute looking Co-op game so
just for streaming
purpose I would
say it sparked some interest in
me
uh
yeah big walk what what was big walk
what game was
that or is is that the the goose game
[Music]
game that is ah yeah the AR okay I have
to
say I I I have to say it the ark kns
game oh my God that looked amazing and
cuzz I I really do like Ark Knights so
the visuals like this is exactly my
jam holy moly they have new characters
they apparently it's a
spin-off um but I immediately recognized
it I just didn't expect
it I haven't been like following so
actively anymore so I don't really know
if that was like already announced
before and I shouldn't have been so
surprised about but hello it looked
insane
yeah little too gray for my taste like
generally I prefer more colorful ones
too but for that game it just kind of
fits everything just looks so sleek and
cool and the character designs are
[Music]
M so good oh back to the cookies let me
check
[Music]
again um
it's
like the it's kind of uneven for some
reason the ones on the very
right are looking a little bit brownish
now but EV the every other cookie
doesn't
look done
yet oh wait turn I think they're too
thick I think I made them thick I don't
know but this batch might be a little
bit less thick um yum let's make some
bells oh is this a
chicken no ah it's a is it a hat oh it's
a it's a it's a Christmas oh
camera hello oh I think it killed
itself what's going
on
huh huh what
wait why is it off let me let me turn it
back on why what did you
do uh on what's what's on good oh it it
should be streaming oh let me just
refresh it here
[Music]
then there ah what the hell my OBS is
kind of no never mind it's on ah there
it is woo what was I saying I think this
is the the head of a
Santa with the beard and the
hat kind of hard to tell though this
shape is kind of weird it could be a
chicken if I hold it like this you know
what I mean or more like a
turkey oh no I I'll take the
Bell some
[Music]
Bells
oh it's like doing weird
things why maybe the power is like not
catching
up ah let's do some more trees cuz I
didn't make so many
trees will will the camera recover
itself Al so let me look for the
cookies probably fine now yeah wo
on my
eye in my
[Music]
eye
okay okay the cookies look good and my
eyes are fine
[Music]
maybe yeah I think it was a
uh a stray
eyelash which lost its way did I lose my
way I see
[Music]
day let me
put
this
here going to put it on a on a
wooden uh chopping board
[Music]
first oh oh hot hot hot hot [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] my my glove is barely working I
should have used the kfp
glove okay what the [\h__\h] is going on
with this camera why is it like dying
[Music]
okay
um I still
haven't oh oh wait it's not working
still [\h__\h] why why why why
why it's not the battery though it's
just like
some connection is kind of weak wait let
me change the
USB I think possibly things are
[Music]
overheating just like the
cookies I want to show you the cookies
[Music]
let me disconnect this
too uh you're still streaming
really
oh if you say
so try giving it a cookie you think I
can bribe
[Music]
it
yay take aside please look at
this wait it died
again it just worked for a
moment
what why why is it so
unstable
please this thing don't go
away remember
this no don't die my other one is a
crocodile
this one was kind of like not strong
enough for the
heat but look the cookies look like this
I think they're probably fine I'll let
them cool out I guess for
now uh to like finish
this second batch and once we have the
second batch I'll start decorating I
suppose yummy well now there's nothing
on them so they look kind of boring I
would
say but we'll get
[Music]
there okay maybe it's stable
again you need
sprinkles while it's hot I don't think
so it didn't say anything about like
having to do the icing while it's still
hot
I I I can't really logically find the
reason why it has to
be I think we're probably
good it would be nice to eat hot cookies
but I might just try one without any
glazing before it completely cools
down test
nipple yeah it's usually done cold right
like how else is it going to
dry the the icing has to dry
anyway
[Music]
I was going to buy food
coloring uh just to enhance this a
little bit more but then I realized
today is a [\h__\h]
holiday it's a [\h__\h]
holiday it's a crazy
holiday no shops are closed no food
coloring for me
camera what are you
doing I
think something is not handling this
well either the connection between the
camera and the laptop or OBS or
something but it's not even like on on
my laptop OBS I have like barely
anything on there so it's not that like
OBS is like not clean enough don't
worry
the cable loose no it's
not it it's like a just overheating yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah stay or don't don't
stay just
move I I guess I I'll do some stars like
these
[Music]
ones kind of small
though
[Music]
no it's stopped again what the
[\h__\h] maybe the camera has to rest a
little bit I don't know but I don't want
to accept I charged you [\h__\h] you better
work for
me I charged you and you're charging
me
my my
patience
showing hand cam but at the cost of my
nerves okay last
one
here
okay I keep on having to deactivate and
activate
it but when I do that it's fine oh I
think are you guys hearing
these there's like
some uh yeah USB connection noises
oh well okay second
batch um but I I can't place them on the
uh baking tray right now because they're
uh it's like really hot right
[Music]
now
unless you know what I
think do it anyway got to be fast
would be bad
connection maybe the USB cable oh yeah
it stopped
again
uh I can try to find a different
one but wait let me let me get rid of
all this extra dough right
[Music]
now
let it s let it s let
it tomorrow I'll be in Texas how is the
weather in Texas is it snowing H does it
ever snow in
[Music]
Texas what can I expect I mean I won't
be there in person of
course but I want to imagine I want to
get the vibe I want to feel like I'm
there
[Music]
crazy snow stor before the whole State
loses power not only hot it's 24 C in
Houston what
now
24 oopsie
[Music]
24 holy [\h__\h] 24
20 oh my
[Music]
God yeah and we're talking Celsius cuz I
I only understand
Celsius do Texas people get like
offended when I say like howdy to them
I mean if they do then it's already too
late anyway
but what do you
think no they like
[Music]
it you love it
really kind of cliche
though I say howy all the time is
Oklahoma in
Texas
oh
no hell no partner hell no
partner so who's going to who's going to
be there is anyone here who's going to
be there tomorrow on my Cali and Wawa
panel who's going to be
there not
me uh I wish I
wish how in person yeah that's the
question well I won't be there in person
but I'm asking who who will be there in
person I wish not me I wish
H I know there's some where where are
you guys
at couldn't make it
what
unacceptable point about my mom got
trampled by a horse what text you're
you're joking
right please tell me you're
joking hash Texas problems this like the
Australian problems like um yeah well um
there's an I don't know a huge figh that
could potentially kill me in my
room I wonder if that was really a
joke
okay all right
uh what do I do here what do I do with
these where do I put
them oh it's already cool down it did
already cool
down the cookies didn't really though
okay I'll eat this one just single
tree Blacky
M
ah
oh they're really
[Music]
good they're still a little bit
warm
wow
wow stay there I need a new one oh why
they so
good I'm surprised even without anything
on they're still so
good
wow
okay let's throw in in second
batch the M I'm placing the ones that I
have off
screen is this moving still oh it is
okay maybe the camera just has like an
idol meeting I didn't want to be
disturbed are those butter cookies yes
they do taste very
buttery I wonder I don't know they're a
little bit dry but at the same time they
feel like perfect I'm not sure I think
they're
perfect I think they're also the right
amount of
crumbly so you guys can if you are
looking for the right recipe you can use
use the same ingredients that I did if
you
want by must be me T who was sharing the
road of horses last week are you
sure I mean even if you share a road of
horses I I feel like being trampled by
one that that's like
H they certainly wouldn't do it on on
purpose I would think the
horses it must have been an accident if
that really happened for Mom my
me I want one made by by me just make it
with the same recipe while watching my
stream and then imagine that they're
from my
batch you can
totally just hallucinate
that I give
permission I I allow you this coke this
coke shall be
yours where's the recipe well I mean if
you listened while I was putting
together all the ingredients you would
know but don't worry I can I'll put the
recipe in the description after I'm done
how about
that you took your
meds well then I can't help you but if
you took your meds then you don't really
need to cope do
[Music]
you
let's try to
make one more whatever whatever I can
get out of this and then I'm
done uh maybe a bit
[Music]
more if only I could share these cookies
with my
[Music]
cats Texas wins can be bipolar it can be
snow
ice oh like both at the same
time oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] well that's kind of exciting isn't
it you never know what you
get why
not okay um how about the last batch
will be these
angels the Chris Kint angel
so in
Austria actually I don't know maybe it's
different nowadays but the way I was
raised and we're not even uh we weren't
even um
a religious family but for
us it was not Santa that would come to
our house at night it was the Chris kin
a little female
angel that is I guess some of what's
descendant of Jesus Christ because they
call it Christ
child and yeah like my parents would
send me outside me and my
brother to play at
night until they prepare the gifts but
then
allegedly the gifts are from this this
child this
cookie
[Music]
yeah and that's that's why the 25th
doesn't matter to us at all in Austria
we don't celebrate the
25th because we already get the gifts on
the 24th at
night
[Music]
yeah
okay okay there's still a little bit
remaining but whatever I don't care
maybe that will go into my vanilla ice
cream do
that still very festive yeah I think it
is you know doesn't have to be Santa and
in the end Santa Claus is like made out
by Coca-Cola anyway isn't he a [\h__\h]
fraud this this Christ child is not made
up by some oh oh I'm getting canceled by
Coca-Cola it's not made up by some huge
company I guess
no no it's
different I'm actually running out of
space
here Coca-Cola don't cancel me
Coca
okay I'm putting it in
there
okay W that's so many cookies holy [\h__\h]
I don't know if I even glazed them all
on stream because I don't know it seems
kind of stressful let me glaze let's
start glazing the first batch how about
that
um a little bit of cleanup I think would
be nice
while the camera is dead
[Music]
anyway
basically
basically I mean this is kind of
f some water and get some new
water
[Music]
MH Yum Yum
Yum okay
[Music]
um let's create the
mixture I'm getting a
ball
[Music]
okay okay okay okay let me fix the
camera
[Music]
camera hi guys welcome
back okay we're making the sugar glaze
oh by the way did you guys did you guys
know when I put it in because let's do
20 minutes now not 15 minutes so it's
probably been what 2 minutes since I put
it in 18 minutes timer
please
okay T tast has already the did one
they're amazing the way the way they are
ah
camera it disconnects itself I hear
it hear
it don't be such a
[\h__\h] please hello it disconnect do you
guys actually hear this cuz I just heard
it put all my headphones
again it's being a little
[Music]
[\h__\h] actually it disconnected the mouse
I think where's my
[Music]
mouse you didn't hear the okay I think I
have desktop audio muted where's the
mouse oh maybe it was the
[Music]
the
I think it's too many
[Music]
USBS to
many too many USBS I I have um because
the laptop only has three USB Outlets I
attached a USB outlet thingy I have more
Outlets try different P there's not
really much more I can try whatever I
don't really care so much oh where's my
mous go there it is okay I need 200
[Music]
g 200
g of powdered sugar I'll put it in there
where is my
[Music]
scale
uh yeah let's put that on here we're
going to make it ourselves I could have
bought it but I want credit from you
guys for actually making this myself oh
cuz it's so simple the ingredients are
like
nothing powder sugar is
[Music]
unpredictable 200 200 it's basically
just
sugar surprise who would have
thought oh that's
200 218 oh well that's fine too I'll
take it and then it wanted like some
lemon juice and I have this old lemon
it's a couple days old but it's probably
fine the smell
is it's the smell
is it was in the fridge it was opened
still I cut it open for a different dish
and I had it in the fridge for a few
days it smells okay it's probably fun
it's got
fun o squeeze it
in there you guys see it
happening with my grip
[Music]
strength yeah different
side
[Applause]
squeeze I don't even have
a uh uh what do you call a squeezing
thingy
I have a juicer actually but it's in the
storage room I never use
it interesting this smells like a mature
[Music]
lemon yeah no no it's fine it's probably
fine but I have to get uh two spoons of
luk warm
water uh I'll switch my gloves cuz
they're
[Music]
wet and I'll get the look warm water to
the oh [\h__\h] now how do I take it from
the side from the side
ooh two
[Music]
spoons
my
[Music]
no you know that Mexican meme that's so
funny
okay fast I don't know how fast I have
to
be how the science is behind this glaze
but let me just put on my gloves
again
[Music]
I like that I like that
Meme any does somebody have on the
timer are we good my hands a little bit
wet I can't put these gloves on [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
whatever I can see it but I don't know
if this is really enough
water no it's fine actually yeah
ooh interesting 12 minutes to
[Music]
go I can't
get just one by
[Music]
one oh chunky wonky hi chunky
won look at
this wa that's pretty
thick and there's still sugar in there
is it supposed to be this thick that's
crazy it actually requires some strength
in my
arm have you guys made this before sugar
glazing
pretty
[Music]
thick it's good probably who okay
okay uh right we put that on before it
dries and then we uh add some sprinkles
sprinkles sprinkles sprinkles sprinkles
sprinkles sprinkles
okay the lady I saw one video did it
like with a with this but the other lady
did it with her
[Music]
fingers my nose is
bleeding I just wiped my nose and it's
bleeding my nose is
bleeding it's okay it's okay I don't
know
why I think it's just a little bit alarm
alarm
it's okay it's okay we got to get this
[\h__\h] done anyway
[Music]
uh it's probably just like a little bit
it's not like a continuous
thing probably
probably it doesn't feel like it's
running I don't know it's hard to tell
maybe my cats can tell me so basically
the lady do like this oh God uh I don't
know I don't know how the [\h__\h] I'm
supposed to do this
[Music]
yeah like this but that's like a lot
sheesh I need help guys help me with
this how can I do all of this before it
dries how fast does it
dry oh
well the coming might make it easier the
lady said it makes it worse oh look
there's so much blood
everywhere she
yes uh well I'm eating them it's my
[Music]
blood yeah it it it's not running it's
not
[Music]
running should change your gloves it's
my blood and they're not going on the
cookies see they're like only on the
blood is only on the
side
[Music]
I'm alive still breing
stop realize that to survive someone's
got to
[Music]
fight take it
anymore feelings are
temporary but broken
[Music]
hearts the darkness no longer scares me
I'm chasing and hunting and this time
I'm coming for
[Music]
blood
yeah okay how much time do I have until
I have to take the other cookies out
[Music]
guys the cat
hair where' you come from oh it's in the
cookie that's
okay uh 6 minutes 8 minutes okay you
guys are kind of like giving me
different timings but okay I'll I'll
I'll alarm me when it's like 6 minutes
then or when 6 minutes are over I mean
and then I'll
check uh
you this doesn't seem like the most
efficient way to do
[Music]
it okay my first time doing
this lot of glaze
shees we had some action with the Bloods
that's
exciting call an ambulance
guys
[Music]
beding
loveing
keeping you cut me
[Music]
open it's
okay uh I'm not going to dip them in for
the chocolate I might dip them in I was
thinking like dip half of of them in for
for these ones though I want this like
look that it's just like
topping them and then you
know W ah I touched
[Music]
it balls sugar
balls don't waste sugar
balls
yeah
cute they're going to be so
sweet let's try a different one how
about oh these balls are super tiny
these are much more
[Music]
tiny oh they don't
stick oh I have to press them in ah but
they do what the [\h__\h] they want
[Music]
no
these
[\h__\h] oh these are pretty these give me
like Sakura
Vibes cuz there there're like a
light green and the the
[Music]
pink I don't want to waste all these
small balls I just want them to go where
they're supposed to go pour out and dip
oh
like
like oh
well I'll just continue doing what I'm
doing right
now look at this beauty do you see all
the
[Music]
sugar who here has
diabetes you don't have it yet you will
get it with these cookies
oh
yeah or I I don't really understand
diabetes the only like source of
diabetes knowledge I have is scrubs cuz
of Turk and I I'm not sure I really
understand diabetes because like in some
way you want sweet stuff but but then
you also don't want too much sweet stuff
and there's certain times where you do
want sweet stuff right and then that
means your blood sugar level is too low
but you also got to be careful that you
don't have too much right I don't really
understand
[Music]
it depends I have to be this type
one oh does it depend on the type too I
guess so yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah different type it's a balancing act
uh oh there's a yellow ones now I only
got yellow and green ones out not even a
single pink one that's kind of
[Music]
Lucky okay they may not be like the
prettiest that's a lie they are
beautiful they are
[Music]
gorgeous why don't you just drop where I
want it to drop
though kind of
[Music]
bro sha sh sh yeah
huh okay stay okay uh next cookie next
cookie I'm so slow I'm so
slow oh oh something has died I heard
the USB disconnect and it connected
again but yeah I probably need to
reconnect the camera on my
own
why I don't have have the leeway to do
that right now my hands are bloody and
sticky and
sugary all messy I can't touch my mouse
right
now so please be patient
everybody I I'll try to be uh
efficient oh cute this is like
confetti oh my God that's
cute
oh I'm using another separate new
one this one's like confetti
circles
cute we're waiting for your hand cam
yeah please wait a little bit
longer you have 1 and a half minute for
your cookie oh my
God oh my God okay when I get those
cookies I can try to activate the camera
again
[Music]
and I'll switch my gloves
maybe nose bleeding let's go let's
go I actually I don't think I ever had a
proper nose bleed maybe when I was like
so young that I wouldn't remember now
like who's who knows maybe like when I
was under 10 maybe maybe
Den you usually get no no never like
never but like recently with how dry I
think it's because of how dry how dry it
is in my
apartment like I I might get like you
know like a little bit of a nose bleed
but not like a continuous one
thankfully
[Music]
okay I'm going to decorate this one and
then I'll go to the
[Music]
oven Shak Shak Shak
Shak I should gift some of this to my
friends if only I had a ha no just
kidding if only I was if only I had any
plans to meet
any
okay I
will get the cookies I didn't see them
for a while so I hope they're fine uh
get the the chicken oven M you will you
will carry the heat for
me even though I'm the
Phoenix it's your responsibility to keep
me safe I'm counting on you
[Music]
okay they look
fine yeah they look good but there's so
[Music]
many a one a two a one two
three oh
[Music]
okay
H new
[Music]
gloves okay the the cookies look nice
they have they're like maybe a tiny bit
darker than the other batch but totally
fine and
then C
around how you
doing activate and
activate we're back we're so
back Tada T did you miss my hands my
blue
hands I hope this cannot dry
out cuz it's like still like the
bigger you know Mass
liquid it's it's fine worst case I'll
add a little bit more water that will
probably do the trick I always miss you
I mean
[Music]
what
continuing see how long this is taking
me H and the second batch has way more
cookies ah those you but if we if we
decide to dip them all in chocolate the
dipping should be easier than
this like
glazing
situation I
[Music]
imagine okay uh next
cookie first polar words and cookies
busy day yeah I'm like a I'm a factory
today a Polaroid and a cookie
factory so efficient so uh
productive recently like just recently
I've been very
productive as I told you with me
cleaning
[Music]
everything get on there get on on there
nobody will escape this
cookie this is your
destiny that's not that much but that's
okay okay let me try to like dip it in
there I don't know if that works no it
doesn't
work like I mean if I really dip dip it
then maybe it works but I don't want to
dip dip it I want to just gently hover
the top
[Music]
okay actually no no no I want them to
look like
this that's what they look like in the
video
too I want to give these tiny ones a
chance again but
[Music]
like
oh how
[Music]
how they're like everywhere ah it's not
not
good oh it's good it's good cuz I
actually really like these kind
of thought I want more of them I should
m M wait I can make a little container
for these cuz for these ones I can dip
yeah oh okay here we go let's try it
like this see if that
works like doing it on my hand is maybe
not the best way of doing it I I will
admit
that probably the first ones I made are
already like dried and
edible but I will be
[Music]
patient reshaping a little
bit oh this is Art this is a form of
art
oh yeah okay why did I not do that
before cuz the the lady in the video
didn't do it like that either
m but that was so w
smooth evenly
[Music]
distributed yeah
whatever shaping
[Music]
shaping okay and
say
oh that's really a lot of sugar on there
woohoo it will look better sprink no but
then there will be so many like lost in
between I can't do that no this is fine
I found the perfect way of doing it
now the lady in the video sprinkled it
all over randomly but I don't know like
I tried that man and it didn't satisfy
me it didn't spark happiness in
[Music]
me just got to make sure if I give any
of these to my friends that they haven't
seen the VOD and haven't seen that like
my blood might be in the
cookies no just kidding I don't think
any blood is there you would see it it's
a see through translucent white glazing
you would see if there was
blood no W blood was involved in the
making of these
cookies only in
indirectly oh please do do not be
concerned it is not your concern my nose
bleed is not your
concern that's
[Music]
a oh
God
huh there's a little bit of the
hair maybe no nose bleed but uh no no
blood involved but definitely some uh
cat
hairs definitely some of that
mhm okay 1 2 3 four five six cookies of
the first batch
[Music]
left I might make some more uh from the
second batch because I still have sugar
glazing and it's like an uneven amount
otherwise you guys don't
mind
yeah what did you guys like about the
game awards was there something uh you
were maybe like from the announcement
trailers was there something you were
surprised about or so what really shook
you I think there was
one
game that was coming back that people
were uh surprised
about oh yeah what do you guys think of
that coim
game what was it
called Monster Hunter yeah most people
say monster hunter
fre yeah the free God of War DLC that's
crazy oh it died again give me a moment
free God of War that shook me cuz like I
was watching it and just thinking yeah
this looks really amazing nice DLC
sasuga god of war and then they say it's
free and it's coming out like uh in a
few days like 5 days hey yo that's like
next level fans
service kind of fan service that's that
I want to
see yeah that's so exciting
[Music]
yeah like normally you could totally
charge a good amount for that but
[Music]
no camer
reactivate
hi
yeah finally okay this was not part of
the game of horse but I'm going to go
snowboarding next week in 1080
snowboarding oh the camera immediately
died maybe maybe we should let it go for
a little
bit it seems like when I force it to
come back too too soon it doesn't really
take that
lightly yeah I can't believe that from
those games they announced like over a
year ago
the one that I was looking forward to
the most is the one that they just don't
release
until the very very very end are you
kidding me this is not
fair sugar glazing is yummy I just took
a
little a little
lick
okay
I hate
you yeah why like why why did it have to
be last but okay I got really excited
hearing it so next week I want to play I
want to play 1080 snowboarding and I
also I kind of want to play more Hol
parade
but freaking
gotcha the freaking Goa speaking of
gacha you guys seem to all agree with me
like whenever they mention mention
something about oh mobile games mobile
games in the game awards I was
like I don't want any game to become
playable on mobile I want to play them
on the PC or on a console I don't need
mobile games thank
you and like just generally the the
whole mobile
game hype or whatever this like Arc of
people making mobile games only one of
the reasons why I especially just like
it is because it personally affects me
okay I used to play uh like anime mm RPG
so much like that was my jam that was my
addiction oh my God the USBs are going
crazy right now I hear it and then they
kind of stopped releasing them and you
know why because phones got like better
and better and so instead of bringing
out these like low cost anime MPGs on uh
the PC they started bringing them out on
the
phones
and I didn't want to play them on the
phones cuz like I don't like the
controls and I don't like to like I
don't want it to be on such a tiny
screen I want to see it normally on my
on my big uh screen you
know yeah just an easier Market to sell
to yeah I guess mobile market is huge
like if you offer the game for free and
then give some gcha that's like the go
to thing to do
now but I don't know it just seems like
such an easy way out like oh let's make
money by making a mobile game that way
we don't have to put that much effort
into it either okay some mobile games
they do look like more effort than
others
but I don't know it's it's just like for
me it's like really just like me not
wanting to play on the phone because
that's just not my console of chice
choice you know and it also kind of
ruined the
whole
production of anime mm RPGs like it kind
of died with that
Trend and that is just
something that I can't
tolerate don't don't want to sacrifice
that for phone
games sure okay first batch is actually
done but the second Bou is bigger
where's my mouse oh my mouse is
disconnected what the [\h__\h] it's this uh
us it's just the USB
um Hub it's not as strong as I would
like it to be oh there it is it's back
the mouse is back okay the fact that the
mouse is also
disconnecting now I know what the
problem is but
look
look TI but there's like way more
there's way
[Music]
more I don't want to do all of
these
so how
about I glaze a couple more of the sugar
glazing and the chocolate glazing I'll
do in my private time tomorrow or
so because I I am I don't have this
patience so I'll do a couple I'll do as
many as I can with this sugar glazing oh
they're still warm let me try this one
again M yeah I can keep some of them
unglazed too they're really
good oh
yeah yeah I can Fe a whole
classroom oh yummy these don't look
darker a little
bit so so good they're so buttery but
the the dough is perfect we totally
nailed it
[Music]
yeah oh yeah the way they crumble in my
mouth it's exactly the way I want people
to crumble in front of me out
of all oh a w E I can't say that
word want him to to crumble in
all all
oh in oh oh
[Music]
oh why is that word so difficult okay
I'm continuing to glaze [\h__\h] you
camera I don't know I need to get a
better USB hub I guess or get a second
USB hub and then split them like not
everything in one USB hub it's just it's
just uh free free things that are
connected on the USB
hub I don't know why it's being such a
[\h__\h] I need to connect these things cuz
one thing is the lamp one thing is the
mouse one thing is the the phone the
camera and then on the laptop uh USB
hubs I have um the
microphone
um the USB hub and the camera the camera
is actually wait the camera is actually
not on the USB hub I just realized and
[Music]
why and maybe it's the
laptop wouldn't wouldn't it be the
laptop then if just everything is uh
disconnecting what this [\h__\h] gaming
laptop can't handle 1 2 3 4 5 six USB
[Music]
be the
[\h__\h] yes yeah of course it all goes
together and inside I can imagine but
like what I spent so much money on this
alien wear laptop you can't even do this
simplest
things it keeps on
saying I'm glad you guys can't hear it
it's like I hear it
constantly takes USBS a lot long
it it's it's a gaming
laptop it needs to be able to handle
that that's my
expectation it's going crazy right
[Music]
now yeah I don't know the the the laptop
just generally seems to struggle cuz I
hear it getting really loud too like you
know
[Music]
airport there it goes
again sounds like it might be a cable
issue the USB cable
or you had that
airport the
airport that was
weird
spooky
[Music]
spooky are we
back are we back okay I don't know
what's going on guys I think it's not
Christmas it's
Halloween there's a lot of spooky [\h__\h]
going on right
now
maybe it's asking me to end the stream
how long has it been 2 and a half hours
well I could probably end like the main
thing is is
done oh let me just I want to finish a
couple more and I want to try one I
wonder if it's like ready to
eat and I'll finish them while watching
uh Home Improvement I'm in the second to
last season I think right now
where the youngest son I totally forgot
about this happening do you guys know
Home Improvement you know at the end
like when they the sons are older older
older the youngest son he goes like kind
of emo he dresses all black and then he
makes this movie about his family this
like horror movie where he tries to
imply that they don't love him or
so yeah yeah yeah I totally forgot that
that was happening sheesh
she poor
boy poor
[Music]
guy I remember that yeah I watch it but
I don't remember anything you should
watch it if you have Disney plus it's on
Disney
plus currently my current um just you
know brain empty show and kind of
nostalgic and and happy
show but like when I watch it at night I
I recently I've been making no progress
cuz I fall asleep so fast these days
which is a good thing
really I fall asleep so fast and then
yeah I only watch like 10 minutes and
then I'm falling asleep and I don't
remember
anything actually crazy no disy plus so
no Nostalgia for me oh no maybe one day
if you ever get Disney plus then look
look it up that's a blessing for real
cuz like my whole life I needed like two
or 3 hours not kidding 3 hours to fall
asleep because of my fibromyalgia and
all that
[\h__\h] I don't know if it's real but I
mean what else can I blame it on but you
[Music]
know
okay another Bell
cookie in the
[Music]
making well uh since the dough turned
out so good I'm more confident about
trying more different cookies next time
like you know I wanted to
make I wanted to make the the linsa Alan
next time which is
basically probably a very similar dough
I would assume but you have two layers
of it and then in between there's jam
and there's a hole in the top layer and
they come in all kinds of shapes and
forms they come in uh star shape they
come in circle
shape uh
Etc some even are chocolate covered mhm
those are the
best so that one I want to make
next yeah yeah yeah yeah
so maybe next week we can try that and
by then I don't know what to do about
the [\h__\h]
USBS I don't
know I'll I'll I'll try figure out a
solution okay I feel like for now I have
enough Let me refresh
the camera and I do think that the first
couple ones are definitely
dry let me move this around a little bit
so you guys can see see wow so many I'm
a cookie factor I got a whole ass cookie
a whole ass
Factory
sh don't don't you say something like
that about a a lady with nice
assets or so isn't that a
thing a whole ass Factory a whole ass
whole ass Factory oh
last a bakery well I am
[Music]
baking a bakery ah the mouse
disconnect I can't refresh the camera if
the mouse
disconnects come
on come
back I guess they won't come back with
cat
noises swear to
God I swear to my God why you got to I
prepared everything so nicely in such a
professional setup okay and why why you
going to do this to me
[Music]
H let me disconnect the mouse
overall is
[Music]
this
activate
[Music]
what one second
guys
[Music]
hello
I'll connect the mouse
again spooky things are happening I'm
haunted this laptop is
[Music]
haunted the mouse it's gone
again it was connected for a
moment
please
oh oh my God
[Music]
I have to walk around the table cuz my
laptop is actually like really
[Music]
far I
think
this
streaming function of the camera turned
itself itself off did
[Music]
it wish I had an assistant you guys want
to come and be my
assistants hiring
now a finally it's back look at this
this is the last picture you'll see
before you die
it's the last thing oh it immediately
died so at least you saw now the final
form because it already stopped
[Music]
moving the mouse
died I'm so [\h__\h] done let me just eat
this cookie okay um how about this one
okay this one's
definitely uh dried out okay here I go
let me drink some water before because
my mouth my my throat is dry as
[Music]
[\h__\h] the laptop is just dying I hear the
USB disc connecting and connecting sound
uh every second second every two seconds
oh no every second
actually
okay um
oh oh oh it's not completely
dry oh my God that's
sugary
oh it's actually not
dry but that might be I mean an
interesting
[Music]
experience oh my God shut up please shut
up
[Music]
that wait let me just close the window
[\h__\h] guys I'm going to end the
[Music]
stream it's
ridiculous it's ridiculous I'm
done thank you guys this was fun
though it was fun I made
cookies we had some nice
chitchat I hope I hope I'll see see you
again tomorrow in my member stream and
in Texas at the convention and on Sunday
I'll be having um a pretty important
Koka stream so please be there or be
square which you can't be cuz you're a
chicken cuz you're round and
fluffy so sorry it had to end like
[Music]
this
yeah I'll I'll take a picture and upload
these cookies on Twitter and I'll I have
to cook some actual dinner as well
actually unfortunately yeah it's almost
11:00 p.m. so actually it's a good time
to end it
now bye bye guys and join me Salas in
cookies I'm going to turn into the
Cookie Monster
now I put these into the fridge I
wonder I want the the icing
to to dry properly cuz I I put such a
thick layer of icing that's why it's
taking so much time to
dry okay byebye
guys oh man I have to walk around the
table to turn this
off anding
go
[Music]
oh
bye-bye
[Music]