[Music]
oh
uh
[Music]
oh
do
[Music]
see
okay
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
that i love you
hmm
[Music]
oh
i found like a million amazing songs on
audio stock again before the stream
here hear this
cute elevator music
[Music]
oh my god
it's so cute
[Music]
audio stock we should write a
valentine's card for audio stock as well
all your stuff needs some
some love too oh yeah let's chill
aggressively
welcome everybody welcome
back
hello
everybody how are you doing
i have verb on my head today to
represent you guys
we're gonna write valentine's cards
today
um
and i guess i haven't been very clear
about it because you guys were
speculating or saying like oh she's
gonna write one to me
[Music]
[Laughter]
no so actually it was happy birthday
those plans that i write them for other
holy members
but it's okay i can write one for you
guys as an um entity
[Laughter]
[Music]
i mean you guys deserve one too
of course of course of course
um
in in
some time zones it's already valentine's
day so happy valentine's day
[Music]
um i have another valentine's day themed
stream
themed stream
planned tomorrow
uh
i wanna make chocolate cookies
you know how i tweeted about wanting to
make
chocolate chunky
cookies a while ago well now's the time
i haven't decided hundred percent on the
recipe yet and i have not bought the
ingredients yet
uh but supposedly it's happening
tomorrow
that was a while ago no you just feel
like it was a while ago it's not that
long ago
there will be no hot glue in the cookies
now
originally i just asked because
generally i want to make them but when i
was thinking about what to make for
valentine's day i realized yo chocolate
chocolate is the best way the best thing
to go the best way to grow so we're
making chocolate cookies um
yeah uh okay okay okay okay so wait a
second
wait a second you might have seen it you
might have seen it a box
[Music]
later today
my
song covered with a miss
is coming out on youtube on my channel
yay
also my schedule for next week is gonna
also
come up sooner or later um
yeah uh
a.m for jst
uh my time 11 p.m and i don't know
anytime so you just check the
reservation
and then you should know
yay it's soon though it's in six hours
six hours from now like in six hours it
will already have been revealed but now
you know which song it is it's dreaming
tattoo it's a pretty
uh well-known vocaloid song it goes like
[Music]
cats are playing with paper bags again
um
[Music]
it's a very chaotic song you think so
spoilers
um i actually
didn't necessarily want to show this
thumbnail already because the thumbnail
is definitely spoilers um
i i i wanted it to be more of a surprise
but then again i was like whatever i
just will need a thumbnail so
yeah um
but uh
as i as i said before that i designed
outfits for original models
for this
uh yeah i designed those school uniforms
and and and i added those little hearts
and stuff and i decided
yes both of me uh had a beret for ame
and the park and the
cardigan
were properly worn by alma cardigan
around the hip if you see it
for me and so on yeah as uh
a
matching school uniform so you know as
if we're going to the same school
yeah and
i i was inspired to
do
um
something with those little pony models
because
preacher is the one who originally made
a
low pony model of me in my sparks outfit
and i really really like the sparks
outfit
uh
and the low poly model i don't know i
thought it looked really really original
really cute
and and and and yeah but i couldn't use
the sparks outfit just like that
obviously because it wouldn't match with
amer although ahmed already had a low
poly
uh
low poly model made by priycho as well
which was coincidentally a school
uniform but i wanted a different one i
wanted something more matching so i i um
designed original ones and then i sent
it over and preach you remade them
yeah i wonder if i have the
i don't know if i i have
the
thing
if i find it immediately i would i would
show you i
but i don't think i can't find it right
now oh well
it's beautiful don't you think so well
i'm i
i i actually um
preach it it just did such a good job at
um 100
uh uh like like
copy pasting it onto the models
that i was like
thinking yo you didn't have to make it
that perfectly i felt i thought
you could probably improve uh some
things there but this is really like
one-on-one what i gave her
the diffusion dance work oh we're doing
fusion here now we're doing a heart
it's a very simple one i kind of wanted
to go all out
in like doing something super detailed
crazy but first of all didn't have the
time second of all i thought it wouldn't
fit the theme anyway so
yeah uh here we are uh you're gonna see
it soon in action
so this is like a spoiler
this is a spoiler
isn't it
isn't it cute
i think it is
[Music]
red and brown colors brown is
you know chocolate color
[Laughter]
and poop color but mostly chocolate
color
[Laughter]
uh yeah um
anyway that's that's uh that's not
really what the stream is about we're
making valentine's day cards
and i'm drinking a pepsi on the side
[Music]
yeah you can already see the credits in
the
in the video reservations so by now
i can't hide it anymore kana udu
made the video
um
that's why i said that this is
again something very special and uh
we went all out on it and it's my most
most
costly song cover to date
i did not spoil it before i just said
car that could have been anything
but yeah it's an ambitious project
and uh yeah just i just thought you know
the only way to top
what uh the last sun cover was which was
animated would be having a 3d video this
is the only way to top it so
um and and i kind of thought you know
i i maybe should keep all this chit chat
for after the video is revealed but
the reason
why i wanted
another reason for it was that when i
think of ame
i think of 3d
and
i don't know i think of 3d shenanigans
and and when i think of 3d shenanigans i
also think of kannada i don't know if i
just kind of just kind of thought that
it's a it's a great combination
[Music]
and originally i was i was thinking um
when i think of ame i think of small
ammo
so originally i was considering doing
this music video in small
uh wealthy i'm a wealthy kiara
but i wanted them to dance you know i
wanted them to dance properly so
that's why i ended up throwing that idea
away and got some got some models that
are able to move
more without it totally
like
disappearing in the
wealthiness of the bodies
yeah
yeah the small models if they dance i
mean they can kind of dance i mean we've
seen it in my
in my christmas uh collaboration with
canadu
my small chiada had some sexy dance
moves but it doesn't come across
quite as sexy
[Music]
um yeah so i i wanted this to be very
focused on dancing that's why i figured
a prop a bit a model that's a bit more
properly
[Music]
uh
proportioned
[Music]
yes yes that's what he said that's what
i said
ah
so yeah look forward to it now we want
to
write some valentine's cards i'll put
this
somewhere behind me
yes it will be there oh and now i have
now i have matching twitter profile
pictures with abe
um uh i told them as she can if she
wants she can get rid of it like
in like a month or so so
it's okay it's okay
it must go eventually but i'm glad she
changed it
[Music]
um
screen please
[Music]
wonderful thank you
[Laughter]
thank you
uh for the screen
for sure
um i don't i don't exactly know
how i'll be doing this
um oopsie uh
making oops
making valentine's day
cards i don't really know i need your
help because i'm really bad at
making like
um
uh
i don't know i want to flirt i would i
want flirtation as valentine's day cards
guys
eh
i don't know if i can do that without
your help and i need you guys can flirt
really well so
i mean relatively well no this is not
handcam i'm sorry we'll be making it in
photoshop but i might um i might draw
with what with my hand
uh at some point you're sure
oopsy
[Music]
uh oh
no no
uh ms paint uh it's maybe more charming
but no
no it looks shitty anyway don't worry
okay
okay is this uh you guys it's not too
loud for you right is this a could it be
louder
okay so my plan is to make um
at least for all of the myth members a
card and then make a few extra ones for
special people
yeah
okay
yes i am i am quite lucky sometimes
yeah so um
um
where do i even start i think should we
put like pictures of the members that i
that that they are for on the card i
suppose i could do that
uh
i think i have some
okay
because i have this one here right now
let's start by making one for
inya
okay
i think i already have an idea for
inaudible
[Music]
i've seen like i think last year also
i think one of didn't last year one of
the myth members make
valentine's day cards
but like generally so that you could
uh use them to send them to others was
it
ah yeah it's an it's a very ahmed thing
to do but
you guys i guess can use it as well but
generally this is just me writing it to
inna
but if you want you can
you can do that should i write with my
hand i would have to move the window to
a different screen again should i wrap
with my hand
i can write with my hand it might be a
bit scuffed though
see when i move it from
from one screen to a different one it
will uh kind of change sizes
okay
so i have an idea um i don't know this
this this
this uh suddenly came up i felt very
inspired it might be a little bit lewd
but it doesn't have any loot um
implications it's only depending on how
you imply what i would write but
um
this is the only one that i already have
an idea for so after that we might be
[\h__\h]
okay
uh
let me
show
uh
open
[Music]
dear
enoch
yes handwriting let's go
i have i have a rough idea but how do i
phrase it
[Music]
ah
i want your
tentacles
to
hold
me
tight
see i mean
it's just yeah it's nothing to worry
about it's
i just want to hug
i just want to be squeezed by her
tentacles
so i hope she brings them because
they're actually not attached to her
that's uh that's that's that's something
that a lot of people uh think but it's
not true they're not attached to her
they're actually just uh yeah
floating around back there
yeah
so it's not really it's not really a
part of her
but
so she must bring them when she when she
visits me for if she if she visits me
for valentine's day
[Music]
or should i rephrase this i could also
say
uh bring your tentacles tonight
[Laughter]
uh
bring the temples to tentacles tonight
to hold me tight
and even runs should i ride that
bring your tentacles tonight to hold me
tight
okay
i think maybe that's better
because it's a rhyme we want i think we
want we want to try to rhyme on these
bring
your heart
your
[Music]
head
the
close
tonight
[\h__\h]
now it looks weird
too oh well
hold
me
[Music]
i wonder how she'll reply to this
so you can i guess edit this and write
your own name here but i will say
um
from
[Music]
let's draw her tentacles here
oh maybe she could be
oh
she has a tentacle around her
let's let's uh add some scribbles here
and there
yeah it's very useful
very useful with her tentacles and she
can go shopping all alone and her
tentacles will hold the bags man
ah
i'm jealous
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] up
another tentacle
coming through beep beep beep beep sorry
when i look at that screen over there uh
my body stops moving
okay
pretty cute i would say
pretty cute maybe a different is this a
good background color i think it's it's
fine we can change it for the other ones
dear inna bring your tentacles tonight
to hold me tight from kiawah
cute um
one second
does it show up on the screen if i do
like uh i don't think it does oh wait
you didn't see the side
you didn't see the side here
sorry there's a tentacle on the side
put love and there's a lot of love in
there
why don't we put love in it
[Music]
no love kiara oh i thought it was pretty
if this doesn't show love then i don't
know but okay
[Music]
let's make her into a cat
or something like a cat
you're cute i like scribbling
a cat with tentacle tails
lips my god
no no the tentacle's already enough but
i'll remember that for another one
all right so that one is a go yeah that
was fast but for the other ones i have
to think deeply
uh
to ena
safe
i saved it
okay next up
um
next up
oh
uh first of all let's do like a fancy um
gradation
of
pink and
blue let's write one to
to gura
oh
wow
i like that wow i like those colors
together
yeah let's do good uh let me find the
picture of gouda
i mean obviously with guru we can do
some fishy f no i mean i mean
i mean
some slimy jokes i don't know or feet
foot joke i don't know
so many possibilities
where do i have a good uh image though
ah here
nice she looks so cute in that dear lord
let's put it here
okay
well but let me actually i want to add
uh
this i think
oops what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
i barely see that um what color
what color
okay
oh
all my handwriting i don't know man my
handwriting uh i guess is decent
okay
ah who so pick up lines for gooda let me
think
dear good i'd like you underfoot
good i don't like sifa but i would eat
your love
that is true i do not like seafood
my love for you is not small
can't wait to get my jaws on you let's
feed chocolate wow
is there room for two in that bathtub
life is never the same
oh there's so many good ones [\h__\h] life
is never the same summit
ah
those are some gems oh man
sharks are and home dear no but maybe i
should
i want to change your guys's up a little
bit so it's a little bit of me as well
um
maybe let's go with something about the
bathtub uh
ah i have an idea
i will combine the same at the bathtub
i think i will try um
[Music]
um
ah no wait um
thank you thank you
i want to do do something like i i have
i want
i think i have the
same
bathtub as you can i go to your place to
check it check if it's the same or not
but that's like too long and i want to
rephrase it
[Music]
[Laughter]
is that
no
lame i know it's lame
[Music]
want to take a bath in the same tub yeah
something like that you know
your guyses were already so perfect but
i can't just copy paste what you guys
tell me can i
go back
[Music]
oh i have an idea
ah
wait so someone said i'm gonna make you
out tonight but i want to change it to
like i can make you more than just uh
tonight
i'll bring you to
death or so
i or i'll i'll i'll have i'll
our night won't end at a
will do the whole abc
or so
that's pretty compact
how about
how about that
i'll
i'll make
more
than
just
smaller capital
ah uh
uh maybe tonight is not should i do is
tonight necessary
i'll make you more than just uh
i'll
oh
[Laughter]
uh
quote box on the same level
scale to what on a scale
of one to five or six
when when's the others
uh i'll teach you the whole ah now i
won't i'll have you
the whole alphabet
[Music]
or
today's menu is more than just uh
do the whole alphabet i don't know
we'll go all the way to
oh we'll go all the way to
cute
no that
[Music]
um i'll teach you what's between a and
z or q
but we will start with n we stop at z
oh
that's that implying sleeping
tonight we started a
but then we ended at that set
but does does you think that the
reference to her eye is still obvious
[Music]
i mean that's pretty good
maybe maybe like that
i'll make you
i'll make you start at a
[Music]
i'll have you start at a
i'll
i'll make
you
i won't um i won't let you
i won't let you go
until no put quotes around a yeah i'll
make okay but then maybe a cat
capital small i feel like her uh was
more like a small ah
i'll make you
i'll make you start
at a
ah
and lead and lead you to that dead
and
lead
you to
set set
uh
are my implications obvious enough guys
perfect
perfect perfect
[Music]
[Applause]
let's decorate her a little bit um
yeah she's been she's been bullying
nerds recently so let's make her into a
nerd
or something like that
as as close as i can get
that's
that's that could be acne but it could
also be a uh what's it called again uh
uh
uh what's it called to get a freckles
i used to have
i used to have um
acne though so don't worry guys it's i i
i understand how it feels it's tough man
um maybe big ears
[Laughter]
cute yes very cute
give her something to hold oh yeah good
idea
[Music]
what's the other thing she should hold
maybe a fish
a squeezed fish
how does that look like a fish
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm poor beach man he's getting squeezed
[Music]
help
a shrimp would be good too but this is
cute it looks cute with those big round
glasses i love big round glasses they
look so good i have fake ones i don't i
don't wear glasses but i have fake round
glasses just for fashion purposes
it looks so cute i love those
all right this is a good one too we got
kuda down yeah
[Music]
yeah we're too fast i can i when once we
got mip down we can write so many to
other people too
and
to goura okay
that one is done
[Music]
okay okay
next up
uh
we shall do
let's do let's do amen
[Music]
do i have like some kind of
pattern in photoshop
or don't really have
oh i should have used one of these
shitty photoshop patterns for good eyes
wait let me go back
it's jackie
oh wait what the [\h__\h]
oh when i put it on top of the gradation
it will only do it like in certain parts
no no
but i mean this one actually looks
pretty good i gotta give you that
photoshop
there's also
this one oh
oh
isn't that one nice
but then the colors of the font maybe
don't stand out so nicely anymore
looks nicer without but we want it to
look
fitting to her no
writing is harder to read
that's okay we can fix that
and we can fix that how about a drop
shadow oh why is it so red
[Music]
change
the font color
can do can do
uh
color overlay
just a black black is fine i think
i'm using photoshop uh
[Music]
photoshop i don't know which one it is
the the new the newest one i think
darker blue
okay
blue is better let's make a dark blue
then
darker darker darker darker blue
[Music]
yeah
does it look good it looks fine we want
a little bit of
crap crappy crappiness
freckles look bad nah freckles cute
gosh i wonder
oh you don't see that okay
two good uh two i'll just save both of
them
okay okay okay
and then
now we get rid of
this and then
let's see what other patterns i have
grass a grasp
uh
this weird
i want a potato pattern for amer
[Music]
[Laughter]
it doesn't really come with many
patterns to begin with
kusa
i want potatoes man
oh well but you know what um
i want this to like
we want we want uh this no we want
let's see
oh god this looks this looks fine i
think
okay and then we put an annie picture on
top of that oh my beautiful
look at her
oh
she's so gorgeous
ah
my cutest
doesn't she look beautiful
stunning yes
okay
ah there's also so much we could do with
ahmed like detective jokes
investigation jokes
uh
gamer jokes
there's so much we can do ground pound
time travel jokes
ground ground
what they don't like the color
yeah
but her image color is yellow
this is just ugly don't you think
maybe
i mean like that we can give her um
like a
something like that i don't know
yeah
the brownish one
i guess so
i guess that works too but
[Music]
okay
you like the ground pound i'm mommy we
all know what comes next
i don't need a time traveling watch to
feel like time stops when i'm with you
[Music]
it's no mystery why my heart beats
faster around you
i didn't know you had a mole can i see
if there's anyone
oh wait i know i know i know i know i
know okay okay
now this has nothing to do with her job
or whatever but but but but but
wait a second let me write on that layer
um
uh
we'll change the color later
dear
mrs
mrs or ms i'm never sure mrs
watson
i am
uh
this is a serious letter
mrs okay
i am a dir
meh photologist
and
have
spotted
uh
possibly
dangerous
um
on
your
chest
please
let
me
it's it's not harassment
you know
it might be valentine's day but
for for safety reasons we need to you
know
make sure she's healthy please let me
uh
inspect
it
further for
your
own
sake
um
[Music]
should i write my phone number down
[Laughter]
investigating respectfully of course so
only only respectfully
their aetologist eh what
didn't i write it correctly i think it's
correct
[Music]
your
service
[Laughter]
totally serious i i run a totally legit
derma
i'd run a totally legit business okay
it's all legit
what color
oh
damn it the colors really look bad here
maybe it should just be black because
her dress is black too
[Music]
during my talent eh
dermatologist i wrote it correctly what
do you mean determine
huh there derma that's uh
dermatologist not derm that's an a
that's how i write a
that's my a
do you not see the difference
here and here look at that
[Laughter]
there's people who write way way way way
way less uh readable okay
that is an a
it's how i write a
okay i think anyone can read that just
fine
guna teaches girls away
don't worry she'll be teaching me a but
i'll teach her everything from b to z
tonight anyway
[Laughter]
she can teach me a i'll teach her the
rest
okay let's stop let's decorate amen um
[Music]
this one
a hat
hat there's not much space for a hat
[Music]
but we can do it
[Laughter]
uh
okay uh
uh what would we write on the hat
oh
[Music]
how the [\h__\h] do you draw a dog
i i don't i don't recall what her dog
looks like [\h__\h]
probably does that look like bubba not a
dog
oh wait he kind of needs like something
like that doesn't it looks like a bear
now
boo bow or baba
bubba has no mouth oh
what's that so
yeah longs and bears really do look kind
of similar
let's just uh
draw it like that
yeah it looks fine um he needs his
little hat oh yeah
does it look like that
he's got a kind of cute hat yeah the
more skirt the most cursed blah though
is the
human size bubba the dancing one
boom boom
[Music]
wolf
is more like
be like
looked
hello doggos who are listening all over
the world
my dog
uh hello to everybody's dogs
to ina uh you know to amen sorry that
was my recommendation of titles by
windows
yes this one is uh very professional
this is not really a valentine's card
it's okay because we're already getting
a song cover that's valentine's theme so
we don't need we don't need a very
flirty valentine's card for ahmed
everything is already conveyed in the
music video don't worry about it
this is it this is all we need
this is more important after all it's
about her health guys
their priorities it's a bit too much
text well it's it's important to convey
her my professionality if i would only
write one sentence don't you think that
she would kind of doubt that i'm a real
dermatologist
i'm sure she would doubt it
yeah a real dermatologist wouldn't write
just one sentence and be like let me
look at your mole
no no no no no no no that doesn't look
professional
she needs to understand
okay it's a very full card i know but
that's because i have a lot to say to
amen
okay let's write uh next one
uh
this is fun this is fun i like writing
these cards
let's get rid of that
hell yeah transparent yeah yeah
why should i
shop
that's right to uh callie
cal i hope you maury
here
oh
oh wrong layer
it's like she's a she's a new uh
uh super smash brothers character not
not yet revealed
okay
so cal i'll be maury my dear
[Music]
mystery woman
this has to be a sweet
pink
just a
oops what the [\h__\h] huh
yeah yeah
yeah okay that's fine
simplicity sometimes we kept enough also
pretty simple so some of them we have to
keep simple
hi windows
why do i hear boss music
yeah it is pretty pretty much a boss
challenge to flirt with cali um
because she will turn down any advance
so we gotta be smart here we gotta make
it sound like it's it's not an advance
guys but we gotta be really smart you
don't be too obvious
no no no not just let smash
oh
wait
oh my god i have an idea
she will never get this she will never
ever get this
uh whoopsie where did my other thing go
dammit okay um no nevermind um
we're going again professional style
dear
mrs
kelly
calliope
this
is
a
serious
[Music]
invitation
you know where this is going chat right
[Music]
to
super
smash
[Music]
brothers
in
um we gotta hide this
we gotta hide this somehow let's let's
go low opacity
um
hmm
i want to write something around the the
the brothers to make to to to make that
into a separate sentence so we can
always say this never was about inviting
you to super smash brothers girl um
you know what i mean
no she will never get this she will
never get this
oh maybe yeah i could get rid of that
uh
oh
oh also
how are your brothers i don't think she
has brothers but how are your brothers
doing but like in in really uh hardly
readable
hardly readable letters
[Music]
no need for the brothers also do you
have any brothers
don't worry about brothers
[Applause]
let's super smash brother
do you have brothers
[Music]
uh
is your brother single
no no no no also totally unrelated on an
unrelated note do you have brothers
wait
on
an
un
related
note
do you
have
any
brothers
[Laughter]
can you read that no she will never see
that it's
she has bad eyes bad eyesight she won't
see that no
it's barely noticeable she'll have to be
really looking close yeah this is a good
sneakiness good good amount of
sneakiness dear mrs collide but this is
a serious invitation to super smash
unrelated note do you have any brothers
oh wait i read it wrong i read it wrong
dear mrs calliope this is a serious
invitation to super smash
do you have any brothers
she is a businesswoman she will she
would love to be on super smash brothers
there's no way she'll turn this down
she'll take that opportunity yo i'm 100
sure
[Music]
it's foolproof
there's too much space down here darling
let's make it link
gorgeous perfect perfect perfect
i know that makes it stand out too much
we'll keep it we'll keep it like this
only
[Music]
okay time to decorate
cali
maybe remove the super
but it's called super smash brothers
and the invitation is to super smash her
so not just we're not gonna just smash
her if we're gonna
do anything we're gonna super smash her
so
[Music]
also to make it more believable you know
that it's super smash brothers
i i need to sign my name oh yeah
oh yeah
um
looking
forward
to
working
[Music]
with
[\h__\h] got no space
let me redo that
also probably should be bigger how big
was my pencil before
just it with me
oh there's a line at the top oh yeah
yeah where is that from oh it's not from
a different layer
bushel
where does that come from ah
i throw her oh
it's from her png
there we go
um
use bro instead of no
it is called super i guess it's if
anything it's called super smash bros
but
the official title is b-r-o-s right
oh well
it's okay
this way we can't even if she complains
later on that we deceived her we can say
well the official title is b-r-o-s
this here says brothers
kelly
i
i would never deceive you this was
obvious from the beginning that it was
never about super smash brothers come on
it was never about that that's just
that's that's your problem okay
intelligent hundred 300 iq thank you put
a calmer after smash
maybe maybe very very very very lightly
though
smash
[Music]
that could look like just a little
smudge on the on the
invitation okay and then
[Music]
huh still feels a little bit too thick
looking
forward
to
hearing
from
oops
what did i push
[Music]
we can't do that we can't possibly do
that
i'm obviously kiara from nintendo
um
gotta stay consistent here
okay now let's decorate her hmm
how do we decorate her
i don't know what i'm doing
[Music]
no wait she needs a mustache
a mustache
and uh hmm
censor the boobies
rated r18
oh shrek ears oh good idea
don't they look like this
yeah if she
i gotta say if she gets into super smash
brothers i think we need to uh censor
her boobies it's not not not good for
the children you know there's a lot of
people a lot of children playing super
smash brothers and
we cannot expose them to her exposed
chest
no no no no no they're still very
innocent very innocent
we wouldn't want to have a controversy
about uh the bubas yeah
yeah yeah
oh
but no we don't want to imply that she's
smoking no no no no
no
but uh but you know but
this is totally different but i do want
to see her smoking a pipe
like gandalf
that's okay
that's okay that's okay
what that's not as bad pipe is cool pipe
is stylish
ask gandalf
that works rachel
i realized that was a bit too big
go go go go go go
go go go
go
go go
i feel like i need to redo enos now now
now eena seems seemed too simple oh is
it katakana oh [\h__\h]
it was katakana all along
true true
enos being simple works for her i guess
so i guess so yeah yeah yeah yeah we're
kind of um overdoing it making too busy
i suppose
all right all right this one is finished
two calories
you guys guys want to see them again
let me show them and put them all up on
the screen
so the one for ena looks like this
the wonderful girl that looks like this
a wonderful almond looks like this
hello wonderful canyons
this is beautiful i'm so glad i decided
to do this stream i originally wanted to
do a karaoke stream because i was really
in the mood to sing but i was like
everyone else is doing karaoke tonight
so
maybe i should do something else and
here we are
oh those look so good
oh
it's going down
no but yeah i guess it does it is going
down
the one to ena was actually still kind
of say so
no but the one for amis say so too
because it's professional
[Music]
so the others i want to write is one for
subaru one for nene one for dana
uh and then i'll think
one for one for genma
okay
let me get rid of those
let's do those four uh four more uh
genma reina
uh
i don't want her to
think i have a creep but maybe maybe
maybe maybe
gotta firm all the big nets that's true
you never know
who i mean obviously it's gotta land
somewhere i should be able to land
someone
these these cards are
legit you know these cards definitely
are have a hundred and fifty percent
success rate
the castles
they're cute but
i want to oh i can't write a card for
everyone i need cards for my loved ones
me and the council girls we aren't that
far yet i feel like
and and iris too yeah yeah but um you
know my beloved ones are
ninety
so why do
cron chrono
cr cr cr
cr the thing with cronin is i
after that one day i haven't heard back
from coronal anymore
i guess he went out to buy some milk
[Music]
he didn't come back yet
i don't know where he went i haven't
heard anything before oh
no no there's no way that corona would
go ghost me or anything no that there's
there's no possible way
um and but anyway um
[Laughter]
i don't want to believe that
crono has
an affair with cronie
no that's
possible impossible impossible
impossible
okay okay okay okay okay
you're sure
okay uh
let's
uh pngs for those people though i
think i'll have to google them
uh
let's write one for nancy
uh honorary
[Music]
is that oh that's actually a png perfect
oh my god
nancy
what do we say tonight
um
let's change the color to orange
or then zoo let's go
usual
maybe a little bit of oh i have an idea
oops no
oops what the [\h__\h] did i do
there we go here's some heights
oh
ask for her seal
see seal of seal of what
you have many husbands what about a wife
yeah yeah
yeah
um
seal of approval for making love
say
i'm gonna steal your heart and all i'm
gonna steal our
uh
wet wedding
marriage marriage uh documents
marriage certificate
i wonder
to you forever
next
see
sealed with a kiss
now let's seal the deal
oh
that i like that one that's cute she she
might even read that on the stream and
be like
and try to understand it that would be
so cute
um
[Music]
what color would be easy to look on at
and on this background
let's see
[Music]
my
beloved
let's
[Music]
see you
the
deal
oh red ink for the seal no nice it's
okay it's okay i wonder if she'll get it
i mean she must have by now uh
found out what the word seal means what
but as the animal
i don't think she knows the other
meaning
i'll have to tell her that it's a pun
uh translator's notes
no i want her to find it out herself
throw a little pudgy seal on the bottom
how do you draw a seal
oh seal
seals are so cute
oh my god
i don't think it will look cute when i
draw it though
i'm going to try these are the hands
[Music]
i started so a weird part sometimes i
don't know why i started doing the hands
oh wait it actually looks pretty cute
so far so far do they have uh
do they have those squishy bits
that cats have on on the other side of
their pot no i don't think so looking at
the picture right now doesn't look like
it but they have like claws
gotta be careful that she doesn't
scratch us
wait it looks cute
it looks cute
[Music]
come on
oh
[Music]
it's the seal does it i wonder if it
looks like a seal
oh
oh i like it
now we got to decorate here though
that's a sea lion
where's
where's the difference uh
uh
this is this is a seal now
and this is the seal of approval
this seal
is the seal of approval
she doesn't even need to do anything
anymore
is it a mall uh
[Music]
those are not paws they're supposed to
be flippers
it'd be okay
don't forget oh my name
my name my name my name
uh
yours
truly
yay
[Music]
seals don't have nails then what was
that photo that i was looking at okay
i'll get rid of them
maybe maybe it went to the nail salon
maybe i wanted to be fancy for ninety
you know when she puts the ring on the
flipper you wanna have your flippers
look good don't you
oh
oh let's
let's let's give her
chihuahua braids
let's turn her into me
because i can't think of anything else
yeah
what do i look like and she needs
feathers why am i turning her into me
in a different world
at least into the current me
oh she looks cute afraid
looks cute with braids oh man
ring on the finger
wait on which is which hand do you
usually wear right hand on left hand
because this is the right hand but i
guess it doesn't really matter here
let's put a ring on the thing
if you like it then you should have put
a ring on it oh that's hand oh that's
the right hand oh well
oh well
it's a pre
pre-pre-marriage ring ring
okay
has been
successfully turned into me
[Laughter]
just cosplaying me
engagement ring is the other hand is
that is it really song promise ring do
you really is that is it really a thing
that you wear it on the other hand
depends on the country oh really is that
so
well this card is also finished
yay
i wanna do survival next and you can bet
that's just gonna talk about it on the
history
so many hold on live
gonna do her best on this one
show
open image new tab save
cute
those 3d models do be looking cute
follow me and win
okay
[Music]
i see i see i see it i see what's going
on
let's make it blue
and yeah so pink some pink would work
too
oopsie
i have committed crabs you can handcuff
me oh
handcuffs oh
that is um
[Music]
oh
it's a little bit kinky
[Laughter]
but didn't she didn't
didn't she already turned me down though
when i uh
jokingly asked her
to to marry
she said something in the stream about
she wants to be best friends not married
um in reply to my discord message that i
sent her a while ago
i did see that it's just it's it's okay
i mean i never was serious about it so
so it's okay
i was just joking you know of course for
real though like subaru is like
if if i were still in japan i would love
to go hang out with her again she's so
much fun to be with i love her like
really i really appreciate her
but okay i'm guilty of loving you take
me in cubs officers
i like that one
i'm guilty
i'm guilty of loving you
yes you rejected because i was not
serious enough no oh
i'm guilty of destroying your trash can
could write that too
i think no i think
[Music]
i wouldn't duck my court date even
yeah no i want the first one but i
already forgot uh uh if loving you is a
crime then i'm proud to be a criminal
arrest me officer
okay i like those
if
loving you
is
uh
a
crime
and then
i am
guilty
[Music]
arrest me
officer
[Music]
oh yes you can have the handcuffs in
there and good idea for the scribbles
yeah yeah
yours
oh
that is so
beautiful beautiful flirty line thank
you that is i'm gonna take it like that
because i really like that one
scribble time
how to draw handcuffs
[Music]
like that
and then what else looks like a police
officer
[Music]
how to draw a duck
that doesn't look like
i'm
oh yeah oh yeah
shades and maybe a donut
cocoon
ducks have round beaks
[Music]
does that look more like a duck
80s cup
mustache how does an 80s cup mustache
look like
[Laughter]
[Music]
air pods what
oh that duck looks like airport what do
you mean
[Laughter]
upside down you ah but this looks cool
too
wait what else did i say i wanted to add
or did i even say it i forgot
headphones
headphones police badge what does that
police patch look like
new york police department
nypd that's that's all i know
i got donut donut donut
oh
there's no space for donut anymore [\h__\h]
maybe a donut hat
how will it even look like a
like if i do it like a
no that would look weird
that part looks weird we can keep it
like this
make the cups donuts
true could do that
weapons gun a taser
[Music]
how do you draw
i don't know i don't know we don't have
space for that okay we'll keep it like
this we'll keep it like this but
we add some hearts
she can't possibly turn me down the
second time
she can't do it two times no no no no
airpods need a hat what do you mean
about airpods there's no airpods here
oh you mean the duck oh
oh
it was legit wondering what do you mean
okay we got it one for superglue senpai
looking forward to her trying to figure
this one out
uh i hope she can read it though two
subaru
yay
hopefully gonna go on a vacation
together
it's gonna be amazing
i just don't know which picture i want
to use the basic picture
has she ever sent me
a png of her
i feel like she probably has let me go
through our discord really quickly
are you here
it's not offline
i'm scrolling through
my discord
at the same time
where is mine ain't a png needle q1
there needs to be
all these youtubers they need to upload
more pngs on their twitter like me i do
that every once in a while
i do that every once in a while for you
guys because i know it's going to be
useful for you guys
[Music]
it's pretty late there that is true we
can also just take a non png and i guess
so scuff edit it
scuff
the heck out of it
[Music]
cute png doko
oh
do you guys have a cute png of reyna
i see when i google her i see a lot of
fan art i don't want to use fan art i
want to use uh official
whoa
i saw something on that reddit can i
show you guys
look at this later
[Music]
selena without without all of the blue
oh
good job ready
damn
she looks up that look that could be
like a swimsuit
she looks uh
like she is a bit cold maybe we should
warm her up
oh i love that art that her mama did
over her in the swimsuit though do you
guys know what
boxy mama
oh wait i know which one we're gonna use
we're gonna use the that rule
i want to use that
pochi mama art of her in a bunny suit if
i can find the bigger one but have you
guys seen this before
holy [\h__\h]
she is
hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's quite quite the woman i must say
sensei
you guys have the big version
you guys happen to have the big version
i can't find it right now
other one of the of her in a bunny suit
though
based cultured
oh
what is this motion
no that's not what i want motion i don't
want this basic gas standing picture
give us a sec i'll give you a second one
but i am walking
[Music]
oh what is this one
this this is the one that i want to use
have you guys seen this before
uh let's get rid of the scribbles
we'll have to also get rid of that black
background though
well
we like
what
what happened we like this scuff don't
we that was the wrong tool
here here
okay
is that good enough
uh
40 percent
i want the card to look nice for elena
it looks so scuffed
[Music]
damn
okay i'm gonna
of this maybe maybe if we change the
background color and maybe
look so bad
but let's go wilfa
uh a
congratulation again of perhaps
oh no that looks like [\h__\h]
ah
[Music]
is that too dark
maybe oh i have an idea oops no
yes yes bubbles has hooked up a drawing
in a bunny suit yet no and i don't know
why why not
why not hook a papa
but you guys are welcome to draw me in a
bodysuit
if you wanna
you're always welcome to do so
also let's do
[Music]
something like this and
delete i love this part
okay
now reyna what should we
write
how how do we write to you
rain
we have to be respectful under any
circumstances guys
um
are you sure you're not a turkey because
that gobble you huh
i'd gobble you up oh my god
[Music]
want me to stop
stop
i said respectful
stuff
nothing about stuffing a turkey please
um
i like that one though are you sure
you're not a turkey because we're not
implying she's a turkey she doesn't like
that when we reply to it but but we're
just asking because
we're not saying she's turkey
yeah i like the gobble up part
gobble gobble gobble gumble gubba
wait someone
replied to me is that elena
oh no
no no no no no it's something else okay
i'll kill okay i think elena is sleeping
she'll be surprised when she when she
sees this the next morning so
oh why is it red oh my god
[Music]
why is it why does it look like that
dear
reina
are
you
sure
you're
not i hope she's gonna doesn't get angry
looking at this i don't think so i don't
think so it should be safe are you sure
you're not
a
turkey
because
i'd
[Music]
i hope this doesn't change her mind
about going on a vacation with me
oh no no as you can see
i'm not i'm not serious about it i know
i'm not serious about it at all
but gobbling gobbling her up doesn't
isn't
sure could be a
could have a different meaning too
she's going to get revenge
i don't like her getting revenge on me
while we're on vacation
it will just be
her and me
maybe she'll throw me
into the water but i'll i'll drag her
with me i'll i'll grab her arm and
take her into the water with me
and then we'll we'll like splash water
at each other and be like
oh you know like in an anime episode
[Laughter]
fanfiction no no no reality my dear
people it's the future
this one looks nice okay let's save that
soon two days
and now
last but not least
i think we'll do one for denmark
genma are you awake right now if if not
then keep on sleeping um
keep on sleeping genma you need you need
that sleep desperately
oh but what picture do i use for genma
uh
uh there was a cute one that uh
mama only drew before right general
jen
jen my whole life fan wiki what
genma an english manager for whole life
ian is the manager who works most
closely with kiara amelian gouda that
needs to be updated emilia has a
different one now even after kiara moved
general continues to be dedicated to her
as stated in various
instances on the stream similarly to ch
chat she has not yet made an appearance
on stream
her current design was first run by mama
luni whose current design is based off
of the description by kyada which was
first shared with members but permitted
to be shared with non-members from fan
art after finding the concept art by
mamaloni endorses and has not yet made
an official design herself
[Laughter]
trivia general was first mentioned as
manager during the pecora ex-chiaro
collab after the collab kiana revealed
that she could not hold back excitement
upon hearing piccolo's voice and
repeatedly slapped genma's leg out of
acceptance
yeah yeah she was right next to me
and i was trying to not freak out so i
was like
slapping her leg licked
jay in genma does not stand for japanese
did i say that before genma stays up to
watch canada streaming even if it is
late in japan yeah yeah gemma and kiara
had one final meal together at the
convenience store before kiara moved
at a convenience store
before i moved to
austria yeah we ate uh we did eat
convenience store food uh today did i
say that i don't even remember
mentioning that
gemma and kiara spent a lot of time
together before she moved kiera says
gemma was very sad when she was leaving
but hopes to see and genma actually
cried
don't make me remember that
early on a million could have referred
to jenna's and mother to her being the
only manager at the time yeah i was like
trying to
you know have it be one person but
but then i loved genma so much i wanted
it to properly be addressed as a
separate person
while discussing some of the accessories
and actions to of her new outfit emilio
you know that anime and gemini have
different roles
attended the dokomi convention and yes
in which sakurajikana participated
between august 7th and 8th 10th 2021
yeah she was there for me and i have
high hopes of meeting genma again this
year
um
there is this one image uh from mamaloni
that looks so cute
i'll have to delete and model this it's
not about edma
how about this
oh she's so cute
my angel
rachel
can't read of that get rid of this
get rid of
is really cute like i'm so proud of
having her as my manager
the other day
the other day um
um
i'm not sure if i can say this but i'll
say it the other day some of the other
girls especially the the council girls
saw
genma for the first time i think and and
and they were like oh my god she's so
cute oh my god
she looks so cute and i'm like yeah
that's my girl
as always i don't want to go in too much
into detail that's all i say but yeah
my gentleman is [\h__\h] cute
okay calm down kilauea it's like i'm
sipping for for my match
understandable you guys do it all the
time too
yeah she has a halo for a reason guys
[Music]
best manager out there so for the best
manager
we wanna i honestly really just wanna be
wholesome this this you know what this
will be the only
the only serious and wholesome
uh card that i'm writing today
because i want to actually say
thank you i love you
so i will not take any ideas i think
this will come from my heart
dear
genma
how do i how do i convey my feelings
properly
i have an idea i may
be
a phoenix
but
i couldn't
live
without you
it is how it is it do be like that
i love you
[Music]
thank
angel my angel
[Music]
injured
best
beast
yeah this is just me being genuine
genuine gen magen you
gotta be genuine to genma
based dope simply
based on what eh
i
i don't know i'm just trying to copy
what you guys always say
based best what's another word would be
beast beauty yes beauty yes
beauty
she is a beauty
[Laughter]
bowled
[Music]
no no
no
bubble i'm bobble
does that doesn't even look like a
like a like a pacifier let's let's do it
about the pacifier we need to admire her
beauty look at her do it for her can
someone make that do it for harming but
we need we need more no need more memes
and more fan art of uh genma guys make
more fan out of this gorgeous lady
please uh i'm begging you bae she's a
bae
she's a bae let's put a post-it note on
her that says bae
she probably has post-it notes
everywhere because she has so much to do
you have no idea she's busy
unbelievable i don't even know how she
functions how is she it's like it must
be impossible
to function like her like she can't even
be human that's why she's an angel
i want this to look cute
maybe
brighter color
and then
these
um
[Music]
this is important this is important
she's she's she it's gotta it's gotta
live up to her the great end was nice
but maybe a pretty ingredient
maybe
no it looks stupid
maybe like that
and instead of a black outline
more uh
a little bit of a
dark red outline yeah yeah yeah
that's creepy
if if we now add some blood splatters
then this could be very creepy that's
kind of yonder but
no no no that's not how how i think
about her
gender
no no no the red makes the undead
[Music]
oh my god
how about this
i couldn't live
without you is that better is that what
yonder
spike is sparkle sparkles sparkle
better okay
and
let me uh
decorate it a little bit more on like i
want some borders
the dialogue the letter itself is all
over the place so let's make it a bit
more smaller
and give me some
space
graphic design is my passion i'm
surprised i didn't say that today yet
yes yes graphic design
is my passion
oh wobbly hand there that was not on
purpose
well cover now may hire me as a graphic
designer if they want to but i would
like an extra salary in that case thank
you
but how could you not hire me with these
graphic design skills
it's pretty hard to top that
i would say
cute
let's do
a smaller line
[Music]
and i think oopsie
i think i like it like this how cute
and just to expose your value oh you
mean her the artwork oh but that's how
it is originally i guess i could make it
a bit brighter
uh
yeah okay
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
there it is okay we did four more cards
so let's line them up again
my beautiful
masterpieces
we should
so we have
two
nano and it's my beloved let's seal the
duke
simple but
sometimes simple is best as we know
and we have uh tusupadu
if loving you is a crime then i am
guilty arrest me officer this is uh
kind of
thirsty but
still still
say so somewhat say so not so bad not so
down bad as some others that i have
written
and then we have their data are you sure
you're not a turkey because i'd cover
you up
that one i was firsting behind the
scenes for the images
and then we have to genma dear genma
maybe of things but i couldn't live
without you i love you thank you for all
you do yours
this is just me being genuine
ah they turned out lovely
[Music]
right now i want them all together let's
put them all together
[Music]
eight cards how do i put them all on the
screen
[Music]
you think they'll be happy about this
yeah we'll upload them on twitter too
and send them
bring our dm on discord i don't know how
to put them all on the screen so awkward
awkward size damn
16 cards
now i think i'm happy with the amount
here
what's up
i don't
did um i'mma wrote those cards last year
like generally right she didn't write
any like directly to us right
[Music]
okay
okay i'll write one more for kfb
i'll write one more for you guys of
course
oh wait that's the wrong one
i made a different one
this one
with the c background
this is fun
i want to make more privately
dear mrs watson i'm a dermatologist and
i've spotted a possibly dangerous small
on your chest please help me inspect the
throat
i love this one
i i remember because like everyone was
like so shook the moment
she revealed her new outfit everyone was
like oh my god there's a beauty mark on
her chest we didn't know about that
oh my god oh my god
remember because i remember do you
remember
there's no space on this collage
okay
then
we should
but what picture am i gonna use for you
guys the dakuma picture but which one
let's go stop dakuma on twitter shall we
oh cute what the [\h__\h] is that
oh the one in the
oh let's chicken in the in the thingy oh
this
[Music]
taco one thinking cute there's so many
cute ones
oh but this one is actually
wait we should have this as a members
emote to be honest different version of
the kiawah love
emote but
uh
this is pretty good for a valentine's
day card i would say it's very fitting
look at you guys being adorable
yeah we're matching i give you heart you
give me heart
one hand washes the other
you are cute yes correct correct
okay
my beloved timkens
my beloved jenkins
[Music]
what should i say
there's so much to say to you guys
what do i say
get to work
no no no that's so cold
thanks for hey
that's so cold
no no no
no
um
no maybe something like
let me massage your thighs
before you jump into the fryer
[Music]
why are you guys
being so cold to yourselves this is
supposed to be
charming to you guys no that's weird
you're weird
it's a valentine's day card not not a
letter from the company
not a warning letter
[Music]
i'm reporting you to a
no you guys are horrible at this
only when it's about yourselves
for the other ones you you were so
helpful
you may take a day off stream spikes
you make oh is it that now we're getting
there you make sparks in my heart
[Music]
i
see
[Music]
right
pull
in
[Music]
you
we recently came up with that one just
like last stream or so came up with that
one for the first time
yeah it's not good
it could be anything right but
you may interpret it however you want
you can't be i see great potential in
you
x o x o
he
i will decorate you guys honestly i
should just turn this chicken into fried
chicken right away but that's kind of
difficult
[Music]
let's give you some
lashes looking cute let's give you
some lipstick
this little lipstick doesn't look like
lipstick
uh
oh let's give you some nails
i know you guys we're looking at those
human customers and always thinking oh
man they got nails that's so useful
i wish i had nails there you go
and those kissable lips
yes or maybe some eyebrows you guys
don't have eyebrows this makes them
really
stunning eyebrows
ugh
but you don't need all that makeup
though just so you know you look
beautiful the way you are but but you
know can we get a forehead kiss yes
is that does that look like a kiss mark
[Music]
oh you look so cute
i like it
ah it's like it's like a
it's like playing makeup with like i
don't know a young young daughter with
her mommy or her young daughter just
without her mommy knowing it using her
mommy's makeup oh oy okay if we stop
using my makeup stop using my makeup but
you do look cute you know what you can
continue using my makeup you should also
try stepping into my shoes one day one
day you'll step into my shoes and i'm
sure you'll do great
isn't this wholesome you guys wanted me
to roast steal it but i'll be roasting
you sooner or later but i don't need to
roast you in a in a valentine's day card
come on
i wait
let me do it
[Music]
i rarely do these kind of like creative
style streams like where i just draw or
scribble or i don't know something like
this but this is fun this is fun
i hope you guys enjoyed it um it's a
fairly short stream two hours oh my god
can you believe it uh but i think with
that we're done
and i want you guys to remember that
after this
uh in now four hours
two kfb safe in two hours there will be
uh
three hours three out four four hours
what the hell am i saying in four hours
there will be
dreaming to do the sun color with amelia
watson premiering on my channel thank
you guys for the memberships and super
chats make sure to check that out and
and uh also tomorrow there will be
another valentine's themed stream
so also make sure to check that out
and i'll be making cookies
so let me put that up here
ckfp i see great potential in your
exo chihuahua got no space now
same with nine cards it's really awkward
now
[\h__\h]
ah
damn it
[Music]
time to make one more a car no
not true then it would be free for free
you're right you're right you're right
right
mathematics
it's dead simple
there we go
[Music]
cute
okay i'm happy with that we'll stop here
we'll stop here we could continue
endlessly but you guys also want to come
to make some valentine's day cards oh
and oh make sure to uh if you make
anything for the heart challenger
anniversary because this is kind of kind
of uh i suppose a high challenge
anniversary stream in some way didn't
really mention it but it is um there's a
hashtag in the title
heart challenger anniversary uh tweet
out uh your valentine's day cards or
your
um fan art for heart challenger or
whatever
anything maybe someone wants to make a
remix
and you can tweet all that out with a
hashtag and i'll be going through it and
yeah your thoughts about today's streams
uh stream are also welcome if you want
to or clips or whatever i don't know or
song covers suncoast or challenger i
mean there's there's a there's a metal
metal sun cover out there that uh i can
recommend to you guys
yeah and i think i'll read super chat so
while we're here because why not because
we still have time
and
yeah stream high challenger maybe you
for today and tomorrow i would be very
happy
if you would do that i think i'll also
play it in the background now how about
that
challenge
was my second original song and um
while it has been kind of uh
overshadowed by a
shadow band um thank you youtube uh
because i i i was bamboozled by youtube
uh at the same time when her challenger
came out and and that was kind of
unfortunate
yeah but
um i hope there aren't too many out
there who haven't heard it yet it would
be a crime if you haven't heard it yet
to me our challenger
meant a lot it does mean a lot to me and
the the creation of it was so much fun
so i'm so proud of the music video i
really want you guys to appreciate it
and it was also it was also after you
know hinotori um
i um i asked mama i don't need to draw
lots and lots and lots of art for this
uh song and
and yeah she
i had like a whole
storyboard and she drew so much so
quickly
and yeah she worked very hard on the art
so i want you guys to appreciate the
music video as well
maybe we can get it to two million views
sometime soon
and i'm gonna play the
instrumental
yay
oh and with our challenger with the
announcement remember
last year when i did that first
chocolate making stream
and uh yeah gemma was around wasn't she
she was there to take care that there
are no accidents in my cooking streams
yeah i love denmark
unfortunately this year i can't spend
valentine's day with channel i'll be
spending it with you guys but that's
okay that's okay
she ate something yeah they tasted
decent but i mean there's not much that
i did besides
yeah using
the ingredients that already tasted the
way they ended up tasting so
tomorrow will be a bit more of a
challenge maybe because i never made uh
chocolate chunky cookies before i'm
excited i hope they'll taste really
really good because i'll make them every
[\h__\h] week if they turn out good
[Music]
yeah you know what to celebrate we
should sing it once
[Music]
oh
let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
is
yay
[Music]
[Applause]
i need to tell you that i love you
through and through
kfb i love you
there's no one else in this world that i
would trade for you forever
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
oh hey
wow
yay
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you i think
heart challenger deserves more love so
give it some love
uh stream heart challenger again
stream heart challenge again stream
challenger again it's been a while since
the last time i sang that song damn
it
was such a fun song it's so up tempo i'm
looking forward to the day
when i will finally be able to perform
this one maybe in a kiwa concert one day
i really want to because actually this
song has a has a choreography
a bunch of my songs have
uh choreography
[Music]
yeah but i want to perform it in like
infrared in a
proper kiwamo concert there's no teas
there's nothing planned yet but
i i suppose i should start
working on it but i feel like i need
more songs before i
uh
start thinking seriously about a chiara
solo concert but it's definitely
something i want to do maybe like by the
end of this year
could be realistic if like until then i
put out maybe at least at least two more
songs hopefully more
because of a concert kind of need more
songs although although others have sang
covers and stuff and concerts too so
could probably combine it
combine originals with cut with covers
and oh yeah cause i was always hoping
that one day if i have a concert or
maybe on i don't know my birthday stream
or so oh thank you
thank you guys i could uh perform all
the
all the song covers that i did so far
with the girls like have them as special
guests
yeah that that would be good for
a 3d stream having the girls over for a
special guest and then performing them
live together
still wish i could buy covers oh
well they're free but you can always
support with super chats if you want to
now you have all the covers of them
exactly now i have all of them
but also there's something uh we we said
we mentioned it uh in the stream with
nineteen but there's a song cover with
energy coming up as well
probably
[Music]
it um come out in march
[Laughter]
that guitar man
saw the card
she says ah thank you for the card kiana
yours is the only serious one genma
are you i oh oh brainer
hey replied to me let's let me send her
the card because i don't think she's
watching the stream
let me send her the card and get a
reaction
i scented
for you
i made
um
[Music]
okay
i'll i'll let you know if she reacts to
it
but until then we'll read super chat at
day super tense reading now
reading super chat
super chats super chat super chats cook
tomorrow i'll probably not get to read
it oh
i don't like reading them after after
cooking streams because i have a
different setup and it makes me feel
uneasy
your vibrato always so good thank you i
used to not be able to
do it
well at all it just kind of came
naturally at some point after singing
for years and years i think i think like
when you get older
you kind of learn how to do it just
naturally if you sing a lot
thank you
oh a lot of people wasn't that hard to
understand a lot of people misunderstood
my
or
purposefully misunderstand my tweet
about it being the last
song cover collab with myth
i mean
from my side
that this is the fourth one i feel like
if you watch my streams then you
understand what i'm trying to say
but some people were like hey what do
you mean what does that mean are you
gonna graduate are you never gonna sing
again is nobody in myth ever gonna
collab again what
are you stupid
come on
i mean maybe i could have phrased it
better but
i feel like
i feel like it's yeah legit got those
those uh replies
oh and i'm not wasting my time
explaining it to them no no no but if
you guys see a reply you're welcome to
explain it to them
goodbye their collaboration
right what's another thing when i put
out goodbye declaration
people first some people first had a
shock a heart attack
thinking that i was
declar declaring my graduation
so sorry guys this is my goodbye
declaration
oh my god
i wouldn't do it like that i think
goodbye saying
no no no no need to panic be calm
[Music]
that's not my phrasing that's just a
song title
yes okay let me go for the super chat
[Music]
uh yeah so i hope everybody enjoyed the
stream so far you can uh stay if you
want but from here or not we will be
reading super chat toes which is also
always a fun time
there's not that many anyway so
shouldn't take too long
[Music]
i can never not vibe with oh i have a dm
ah no it's not from right now
i can never not vibe with that guitar
holy [\h__\h]
i like the super chat readings thank you
they didn't know you were making video
cards or does she think you just
randomly hit on her she doesn't know
about it but i think she'll
understand
and mystic has mixed duncan
thank you thank you i'm glad you liked
the idea it was uh very spontaneous as i
said i originally wanted to do something
else but
um yeah tomorrow we'll be making
chocolate patties
and putting challenges in spanking
petra from fire emblem
hey hey
kiana you didn't have to but my answer
is still no i did not even ask this time
i don't care
for my arrives oh
my answer however is yes you made me a
card too right
quisada would have said yes damn it my
phone by the way um
autocorrects
kisada and turns it into kiara which
just is even further proof that i am
kisara
i mean
oh red super chat thank you by the way
is
[Music]
i think
yeah i was actually saying in
english as well um
let me say it in english as well and
that valentine's day in germany in
austria or at least in austria is not
it's not that big of a thing it never
really has been i think it's
i think we austrians don't care much
about
valentine's day here
so
it's it's not really common to celebrate
it i think i think if you're
in a relationship then you may just see
it as an opportunity to give some give
your girlfriend flowers
but
yeah it's not really not really that big
of a thing yeah japan japan really
um
made a big thing out of it but they also
really changed the way it's originally
celebrated from where it originated i
suppose but i like i like the way they
do it because like
let's say in america or or in europe as
well
the the man the men give the girls
flowers and chocolate but isn't that
like always
mostly mostly always like that anyway
like even outside of valentine's day
it's always the the men
not always but like most of the times
the man giving the woman
something
as a present to to make them
be happy and all that so i think it's
nice how in japan valentine's day is
about girls
uh making chocolate for the boys that
they're into or
the girls that they're into whatever
or french chocolate as well
and it's not just buying chocolate but
also making it
mostly making it themselves like
most girls make it themselves yeah of
course it's white day to to um give
something back from the the other side
the
opposite side
but
yeah i like how in japan the girls are
the one
giving it and also they make it
themselves rather than just buying
something
making the chocolate on your own is
uh not really something that the guys
in the in western culture would consider
i think
just buy some fancy pralines and and we
could right
which
they might even taste better than the
self-made ones but still a self-made is
is pretty
makes it pretty special don't you think
so
guys
yeah i think that's really lovely
one can actually could actually learn
from japan in this case and uh
copy them
what i don't think they adapted well is
christmas
cause for christmas japan is like let's
go get fried chicken and uh okay
fried chicken from kfc or so and we good
it's like ah
and also it's not a family day it's a
lover's day in in japan
it's kfc day but i guess we're going to
turn it into kfp day i should look at it
from a business perspective
christmas in japan is a big big big
selling day for us a stock stay
yeah
yeah the business woman inside of me
can only look at the stones rising
thank you
for having me
[Music]
it's a nightmare for us oh because
they're either gonna be
doing uh putting in a lot of over hours
or you're gonna be the one eaten yes yes
understandable
understandable that is terrifying
[Laughter]
kfc saves christmas when this christmas
let's save it this christmas
ah
okay let me continue
patrick chandang savage thank you for
the rest of the chat i sent a super chat
for boy who has always helped me
understand english personally oh buddy
says help me attention savage have
kidnapped me and i want to go to the
usual room eh
bonnie wants to go to the usual room
sandwiches what the [\h__\h] savage kingdom
buddy no give him back
no
give barney back
he's such a good oh you didn't say the
last one i thought i always thought so
yeah it seems suspicious
hashtag free bunny
he's such a
good good cafe employee
he's only been good to me savage unlike
you
gotta save him
i'm sending my my save
troops
to save booty
thank you savage but if you're sending
the super chat for a bunny then the kiss
will go to buddy
buddy
that's what you get
booty donkeys in by the way also sending
a super chat
[Music]
sir sir buddy i'm sorry sir buddy of
course i forgot how could i have
forgotten
free sir bonnie
that doesn't have quite the ring to it
but yay sir body
chick thank you for the pinky release
sir buddy right now swinging a chicken
leg and threatening it
chick is also very passionate about it
good job good job i think i think boys
say safety body's freedom
is guaranteed
he's a knight yes he has been knighted
the one and only night in
kfp it seems
thank you chick for the pinkie
feel excellent thank you for the red
super chat thank you i've tried my best
but i don't think chocolate and chicken
go and chicken meat go well together
oh
really
i would not have expected that at all
i fried my right leg and dipped it in
chocolate but it just tastes weird so i
think the only contribution i can make
is to donate my feathers to decorate
your cards oh
pluck if you don't mind oh that is cute
but that reminds me
my chocolate thingy
my chocolate contest where you guys sent
me
chocolate
self made chocolates
didn't someone send in a chicken covered
in chocolate
was that a thing
wasn't that a thing yeah i was already
very disgusted by that
so felix i could have told you or you
should have already known
i don't know why you tried it but i
guess you're very experimentative
and a for effort you get
thank you happy valentine's day to you
felix
hello
for the red super chat past midnight
here true true i'd like to create you a
happy valentine's day and here's a rant
for you my wonderful adorable aussie
please forgive my verb memory but could
remind me of my employee number thanks
much thanks and much love thanks mate
happy valentine's day
your number shall be
since you're asking today
this is just a coincidence but it's 2 1
4.
what a coincidence wow it must be fate
i don't know that how you did that like
almost like you knew
you're welcome
thank you for your support happy
valentine's day to you my sweet sweet
chicken
[Music]
dog joseph thank you for the pinky yeah
i just want to say why is it so
difficult all i want to say you see the
thing is
be brave chicken she must know how you
feel the way i feel about you get it
together man and or you're going to run
out of characters kiawah
[Laughter]
[Music]
i know how you feel about joseph i know
it
don't worry about it
hello no i love you that's what you want
to say right right
right
or i love no he started descendants with
kiara so it can't be can i love genma no
no that can't be it no
wait now you're making me doubt it i
look up to you
it could be that too but that's
wholesome i would accept that too but
now i question
i question
what i think that i know
maybe i don't know anything that i think
that i know maybe i'm only thinking that
i know it but in reality
no
[Music]
do you love me
do you love me dog joseph
i wrote you that valentine's card
you should write me one too
thank you soon for the thinking
as well wait it's been a year since i
started serving heart challenge
apparently yeah well here's to another
year of the same here's to the best boss
i could have ever asked for i don't know
if i if we deserve you but we certainly
are amazing thanks amazingly thankful to
have you thank you
it's been a year
it's uh nice to be having all these kind
of anniversaries with you guys
and you all probably remember them
better than i do
but this one is easy to remember because
i released it on valentine's day
but hey we have so many new
anniversaries so many memories together
that we can continue celebrating each
each and every year isn't that beautiful
yeah but don't forget to remind me
if you forget to remind me then i will
forget about the thing that you should
be reminding me of so you're school
thank you typhon
say roy166 i don't know thank you for
the red super chat hey kara i've been
saving up for a red super chat family i
can do it been watching since day one oh
gotta say you've grown a lot and have
made us all proud thank you for the
content and smiles you give us all i
hope you're happier than when you
started oh i definitely am
thank you so so so so much say roy dan
kitchen happy valentine's day to you and
thank you for supporting me for so long
day one is quite some time ago and i did
i did change uh
a lot i think since then
but i am i am much happier the beginning
was tough because it was just such a
such a big change
suddenly
um
like
yeah
suddenly having so many eyes on me
suddenly so many so much attention and
not obviously not only positive
attention but i also can
handle uh negative attention much better
now like i feel like i i i can look at
it much more objectively now thankfully
but then then again there's also
thankfully less than
in the early days
so i'm really happy that i didn't
give up in the beginning and i continued
doing what i'm doing but that's only
thanks to the
positive
positive okay of people in here
yeah without you guys i would have
completely lost hope but
yeah
we continued and now here we are
thankfully
overcome we have overcome those
difficult parts
and we're even stronger now aren't we
[Music]
keep on
thriving and improving
that's what i want to do
donkey
[Music]
is this when i was singing her
challenger spanking i'm danish and
barrett's dancing thank you
daisy
roses are red violets of blue waves are
why aren't they violet
[Music]
good question
but violet is
quite the blue color though that blue
that we used for raina's card
it does look a little bit violent um but
yeah that is um
are there are there violent
violence
wait violent
are there violet violence is that a
stupid question violets are beautiful
wait they are violent
people just say they are blue but that
is violet what the [\h__\h] that is purple
the pictures that i see on google excuse
me but they are far from being blue
wait
that poem is just [\h__\h]
it always has been
they've never been blue
so every [\h__\h] poem that starts with
roses or red violence violence of blue
is just invalid
what
all those poems are [\h__\h]
how come people are using that
it just makes no sense we've been
bamboozled all along good that we didn't
use that shitty poem today
[Music]
it's just so inaccurate
poem was run by the cop by a colorblind
person probably
what
it's all been a [\h__\h] lie
oh my god what even is true anymore
wait hold on a second yeah what the [\h__\h]
huh
well i mean
what violet roses are red violets are
violet for god's sake
i
am
broken i don't know if i can continue
streaming this is just too much of a
shock to me
i
it's unbelievable trust no one except
you out exactly oh my god what a
realization
the things i learned thanks to whole
life man i would have never realized
that before i never thought about it
that
deeply
what the hell man
thank you daisy
i am
almost too shift
shocked to give you a kiss but uh
i'm confused
and shocked
and quite possibly bamboozled
rubies are red sapphires are blue
that's unrealistic expectations
rubies are red
but once again sapphires are blue here's
a diamond for you baby girl that's how i
uh i would propose to someone maybe
at least sapphires are blue okay at
least i'm not lying to you
saying violets are blue
very much incorrect
unbelievable this is uh i don't know how
people can spread this
[Music]
i
i can't i need to continue otherwise
i'll i'll
i i just can't cope
colors are hard
blue dancing what rooms are red violets
a blue screw deceiving i i wanna see you
cute but your poem is in balance because
violets are not blue blue
you should know because your name is
blue
what about
what do you even know blue you know
nothing
there is darkest and james box broke
down question for two pinkies
congrats on one year of heart challenger
and happy valentine's day when heart
challenge was released
a very i a very casual view i was a very
i was a very casual viewer but i
remember looking for your thoughts and
being disappointed when i couldn't find
your content in a youtube search at all
[Music]
it's clear how much care and effort you
put into heart challenges so i'm glad
you have a tenacity to overcome even the
most boosting of the mood much you're
awesome thank you yeah i think a lot of
people who haven't been around back then
don't remember but you were legit like
not only able to not find heart
challenger but yeah you couldn't find my
streams in general
um so that was pretty [\h__\h] that went
on for a while
and
it was quite the hurdle for me
um
yeah oh yeah my channel wouldn't show up
either
if you typed in takanawa my channel
would not show up
it's
it's just oh my god i'm getting salty
thinking about it
and at the worst possible time when i
released a song
[Music]
i was gone from the radar yeah
thankfully
like in the beginning back then i had so
many troubles with youtube but nowadays
we're
knocking on wood nowadays
they have mercy on us man
[Music]
oh man i still remember that time when i
was playing fire emblem and the stream
kind of died
but everyone was so
motivated and and holding the line
[Music]
yeah yeah
this is
holding the line good old times
so yeah um it's it's bad memories but
now at least we can laugh about it thank
you james blackburn for
uh
like still not giving up even though you
couldn't find [\h__\h] thank you for still
trying to find me and
now still being here thank you so much
for your support and happy valentine's
day jay's fought for ma
tara danke
oh my god so many of you are using that
shitty poem and all i can think about
now is violets are not blue
roses are red violets are blue no love
is sweeter than the one i bear for you
oh man this is ruined it's [\h__\h]
ruined roses are red violets are blue i
forgot my meds please mary
[Applause]
thank you
michael that's what she said
roses are red bird eggs are laid you
make me feel warm instead that's inside
what that's what she
michael
he wouldn't say something like that
tanaka duncan roses are red phoenix is
an orange wait what rhymes with orange
[Music]
good question
door hinge
it's really not much that rhymes with
orange huh
orange
what are we gonna do with that how are
we gonna make a porridge
orange porridge
i guess a little bit
sponge sponge orange spot no no
dear range
damn
well we need more words in the english
language that rhyme with that then
george
cringe not more cringe orange more
cringe no it does not rhyme
mortgage
orange mortgage
it's kind of a stretch
spinach orange spinach no
oh that's tough
good question
jay one dankest and happy valentine's
day skydiving for the rent to pretend
it's valentine's day in my time zone now
i know i wouldn't have a chance but
still today i cannot be a chicken
attention would you be my valentine why
can't you oh we can see
because you don't want to be scared okay
okay
ah well i made a card for you i you
shouldn't be asking me i'm asking you
[Music]
skye will you be my valentine hmm
happy valentine's day thank you for the
red super chat is that happy valentine's
day in korean
papago
no it's not bud
tomorrow
it says manager give me chocolate
chocolate
and tomorrow i will make chocolate
for you
noodle we had chocolate
mango
okay
for him for all of you
for all of you
of course
okay okay oh yeah don't forget
valentine's day is choco sensation's
birthday so give her some love too
don't forget don't forget
every reduction gym tracy duncan
[Music]
you guys are so unoriginal
roses are red violets are blue audio is
stuck but not as much as you
thank you
but
i can't unsee what i have seen and what
i've known
thank you doll
happy valentine's day spanking time
give your kitties lots of love and hugs
and tutu
brutal no
come on
nothing brutal only soft and gentle
[Music]
thank you for your support
have a lovely valentine's day
baby cor duncan fang dragon spain duncan
chris clark thank you avenged me
[Music]
channing
it's my chocolate oh thank you
[Music]
thank you i will
eat that after the stream then thank you
very much for your support and love
all my love back to you father
[Music]
chocolaty kisses
wait when does it say
five days after dying has it been
huh
hasn't it been longer
did the baby die
again what happened
or did they forget to count has it
always been what
what happened did you guys what no a
baby baby can't die that easily
baby is already
angel
[Laughter]
can you guys stop killing the [\h__\h]
baby
it's trying it
it did us a favor to return to us
and you'd bank it by killing it again
i can never
trust a baby to you guys if you if this
is how you treat it
yeah i will never ask you guys to
babysit that's for sure
oh my god
good job kfb
that's why we have so many anti-stonks
because you guys also keep on dropping
the eggs all the time and breaking them
well you know you gotta lay those more
eggs
the more you break the more you gotta
lay okay so
get to work get into those coops and lay
me those eggs
[Music]
you break it you make it
i keep them safe well i hope so
some of you lay eggs i'm sure
somebody isolate them
time and thank you for the pinky wait i
seem to have gotten a bonus this month
so here's my bonus for the mom
i can't wait for the song but i'm sure
it's amazing i've been so hyped for
amitoni song sing you say it said it was
happening since it was i said it was
happening uh-huh viva la viva la chiara
x everyone thank you
i think you guys will like it we sound
pretty good together
um i kind of almost want to give you a
little taste
not of the video you know what i think
i'll give you a little taste you guys
want a little taste
i'll
play a little bit for you of the chorus
maybe
if you don't want the spoiler well then
you can mute the stream for a few
seconds
one millisecond
[Music]
so delight
you don't hear that do you
[Music]
it's so cute oh maybe
ah so cute
i can't wait for you guys to see the
music video oh my god
okay let's do like this part
[Music]
[Laughter]
right it's so cute isn't it oh you gotta
listen to the solo parts of ahmed she
did so great
she sounds so cute and her pronunciation
was pretty good too
safe to unmute yes yes yes yes yes yes
it's safe to unmute let me
before i accidentally play let me get it
out of the playlist there we go
okay
back to her challenger it's done it's
done
but it's coming in three hours anyway
so
i think you could have spoiled yourself
a little bit
looking forward to it in three hours yes
yes everyone has to be there
everyone has to be there
all right continuing
typing thank you again happy valentine's
day to you
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
then
of course
[Music]
happy valentine's day oh my god three
words free words from tai chi
oh my god oh
i feel like we're actually having almost
the conversation titan
thank you happy birthday to you too
[Music]
thank you for your love tai chi always
hope you're
not allergic to chocolate because you
should be eating chocolate today or get
like i don't know chocolate ice cream
chocolate cake there's so much with
chocolate
i'm gonna eat some chocolate too
afterwards
yeah okay arty dankeshin
yucky thank you for the rent to pretend
hello here is my love letter i know you
already refused me twice but i will
never gonna give you uh this time please
accept my love and marry me will i need
i accept your love
about marriage
look at all these girls that i'm sending
valentine's cards to that you have to
compete with
it's looking a little bit tough here to
be honest
but
but but imaginary is okay imaginary is
okay and i will i will let you know
and i love you too love all of you
for your support oh thank you and i'm
sure that
you will you will find
someone even better than me one day i'm
sure of it
that's a little bit of a serious reply
but
yeah
i hope since this is valentine's day i
hope you find
a very special loved beloved person one
day
[Music]
if you haven't yet
but for now you can enjoy
the imagination i guess
but no no no
thank you yogi happy valentine's day to
you
thank you for your support
lexington the lion thank you ezekiel
thank you for the pinky and just
dropping my contractually obligated
valentine's gift to you
my checks the script most beloved oshi
hey why do you need to check the script
for that am i not your most beloved
oshie
is thank you well ezekiel what's wrong
what's going on there
how am i supposed to take this
i think
i think you just you just had to look at
the script because you're nervous right
but but it's all true it's exactly the
way you said it
thank you for the thinking i wish you
the happiest valentine's day ever
thank you for your love
generally dangerous and siren dancing
for the red super chad
roses are red
violets are
not blue
as if i got something for you
as if i got something for it
[Music]
are you sure
you want to ride it like that is that a
typhon
[Music]
oh
but hey you got a red super chat for me
so
i mean
i mean i'll take that
i'm not giving that back
the super chat is mine it's mine now
mine's mine mine's mine's mine's mines
mine's mine mine's mine smash my
sanctions wow
red like the heart that is beating
from you for me
[Music]
thank you soon happy valentine's day
foreign valentine's day yay
oh yeah i forgot you were the sunday
chief so i guess that makes sense
as if i got something for you
it's not like i care about you or
anything
i i
this chocolate is not homemade chocolate
it's homey chocolate
yeah you're you you just hold me to me
it's not like it's not like i like you
or anything
not like i put all my love and my
feelings into making this chocolate
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my god jet luna duncan skye duncan
sally it's an a it's not celio b
that okay
on that one i guess i can kind of see
how that looks like an e
wait it does
that one looks a little bit like an e oh
the thing is also that my a's sometimes
look um
different
i have two different ways of writing
them i also see that like in invitation
i wrote it
differently than i did in calliope it
depends really
so
no uh i'm sure she can if if you want to
read it as an e then you'll read it as
an e but if you want to read it as an
egg and i think you'll have no problem
reading it as an a
damn
this celebrity related to cabbie
yeah yeah she's not one to talk
she can't even write her own name so
duh
skydiving isn't
[Music]
[Applause]
tk do you mean me do you know what's on
valentine's day menu
me and you oh
wow
did you think of that yourself that's
pretty good
oh
oh [\h__\h]
smoove alert oh my god it's so smooth i
might slip oh my god
time to put on my ice skating shoes
wow thank you happy valentine's day to
you
miss this thank you soon of course i had
to i am a tea time
brand to
oh my dear p hen you really tr ruffle my
feathers that's cute
we're already finished unfortunately
calling for kuwait
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat hi
tinsel hi challenges anniversary marks
one year since i discovered you oh you
discovered me right before the shadow
bamboozled then
i
discovered you and became half a broke i
was in a very miserable place at the
time and seeing your positivity and
tenacity in the face of your own
challenges helped keep me together i
admire you greatly wow
thank you
i am as always very happy to have such a
influence on others such an effect on
others thank you very much thank you
soon i wonder how you found me though
did you just
did you just see uh me promoting heart
challenger on twitter or i wonder how
i would be curious to hear more about
that whenever you want to share again
but thank you so much for your support
and your love for staying here for such
a long time
yeah
supporting me
and loving me
all the way thank you so much and i wish
you all the best whatever challenges you
have i know you can overcome them
any challenge can be overcome just gotta
believe
believe it believe it
yeah you can do it
you can do it i know sometimes some
challenges seem very very very
hard to overcome
but
it will be okay just believe in yourself
sasuke
[Music]
happy valentine's day lovely to
celebrate with you
yeah it's not quite valentine's day for
me yet but i'm happy to spend it with
you guys too
review with my cats
[Music]
happy valentine's day
also hopefully i'll see you tomorrow as
well to continue celebrating because
it's not over yet
ginger ranger
happy valentine's day and happy heart
challenger anniversary attention this
masterpiece is one of my favorite songs
ever and even after listening to it
almost every day for a year
i still love it as much as the first
time i heard it oh thank you what the
[\h__\h]
thank you
oh my god you still listen to it so much
what
that's so sweet thank you soon i'm glad
you like it so much
it's a very jpoppy idoly song so i
understand that it's not everybody's
taste but i'm glad that you like it so
much really
[Music]
still love it after one year thank you i
love it too
i love it too
i love a lot of different kinds of music
but this is like
i don't know this poppy kind of j-pop
music it's just
ah
it just makes me feel
huh
[Music]
yeah
i like the the positive vibes that these
kind of
poppy j-pop songs give
thank you unknown that means a lot to me
thank you
sit down thank you
oh
oh proper poem
shall re-read it
chiada my liege of the everlasting flame
i stand before you with my shield and
blade in response to the challenge you
proclaim my heart will speak true and
unafraid
it felt like a dream when i saw your
light like you brought up the sun for
the first time seeing you love was a
breathtaking sight flying through clouds
of grace so divine
it was that moment i knew that i would
love you through and through
through
happy valentine's day oh well that is
beautiful that is way better than that
stupid lies about violence being blue
at least these words are true thank you
so much happy valentine's day
vermonter thank you for the rates of a
chat this was so much fun i enjoyed
every minute of it you being creative
and spontaneous of chat is the best can
this be considered an art stream as
always love you
i probably won't put it in the art
playlist
but
if you want to consider it as such then
you're welcome to do so i mean and then
wear some scribbles
it's a it's a writing stream
it's a creative stream that's definitely
what it is
danke shin i'm glad you liked it thank
you for being here today mwah happy
valentine's day
[Music]
congratulations on the one year
anniversary of heart challenger it's an
awesome song and legitimately what
introduced me to you so it's pretty
special to me
oh wow
that is rare but i'm very happy to hear
that thank you for discovering heart
challenger and discovering me for that
yay
so that song must be very special to you
same for me glad we shared something
thank you soon and happy valentine's day
gym tracy
and dragon fire dancing for the rest of
the chat forever
thank you
thank you happy valentine's day dragons
fire
hope you're having a lovely day today
with your beloved one or
kiara
which is i mean the same thing right
[Laughter]
for the red super chat happy anniversary
to her challenger the underdog who never
quit exactly hopes smoothie and chunkers
get some special treats tomorrow who
though what the [\h__\h] does chongas even
want not even wet food hey but she she
does like um she does like this the long
stick snacks the soft ones
i
am
she doesn't eat it directly off the
stick but she i i i break it into small
pieces
and then i give it to her
and she likes the liquid ones every cat
likes the liquid
snacks
every cat does
yeah
of course she does yeah
but
i wish she liked white food too because
i i feel like kind of bad for giving her
mostly
the kibbles
but i can't give her snacks all the time
every day i feel like because
i'm sure that they're not
really safe to give every day i feel
like they must be like human snacks
they're like there must be something
about them
that would make it
not as healthy as the main food
i could be wrong though but i feel like
i shouldn't be giving it to her every
day
so i i don't actually give it to her
every day
but she's getting more and more jealous
of smoothie when smoothie gets the wet
food every morning
uh and she just gets kibbles but yo
chocolates if you want something eat the
wet food i'm sure she would like it if
she would try i don't know what's her
issue
and she doesn't like any variation of it
no matter if it's beef or chicken or
fish she doesn't care about it at all
man
yeah it's easy for the messy cat to
become overweight i think so too and she
already
kind of
feels overweight so i don't want to give
her too many snacks
but her weight has been pretty stable
it's not like she gets fatter and fatter
she's just consistently
a little bit chunky
she isn't already the last time i
brought her to the vet
where she kind of
i'm
sure she didn't like gain much weight
since then uh the vet said she's fine
actually she said that smoothie uh could
use a little bit more maybe
but movie is just sporty she exercises a
lot she lifts she goes to the gym so
yeah she doesn't
look or feel chunky but she's not on the
weight
she's on the old lad she's coming on
this game not quite not quite
although i wouldn't say it's a negative
thing either
she deserves her chunky name she does
she does so cute
today i chased her around the whole
apartment she was doing zoomies and
running away from me and chased her from
the living room into the bathroom into
my bedroom it's so funny she goes like
like a like a like a dove and runs away
and i run after her and i giggle like a
stupid idiot
then we run around the couch and see
things she can hide under a cardboard
box when i'm like i got you and then she
goes like boom and then she continues
running into the next room it's so cute
and then she stops for a moment until i
reach her and then she goes runs away
again so cute
it's so cute
living alive yeah yeah
she she trains me i train her
we both hate uh working out for too long
[Music]
[Laughter]
sorry i love talking about and thinking
about my cat
thank you this longer we unhappy
valentine's day
wow
thanks for showing your face
every once in a while happy to see you
hope you're doing well
uh i'm not like planning on doing
a song collab with like everyone in
halloween but i do want to eventually
definitely do one with mumei
um
actually yesterday i saw
a video of someone putting together our
uh us singing complicated from every
levine and it sounded pretty good
together i feel like you know mummy is
an amazing singer
uh she has more like a
softer jazzy voice i feel like than i do
um but i still feel like we could do
well together
[Music]
or even a horotoni
sun cover
[Music]
but i do want to sing one day with mummy
yeah if she if she wants to i'm up for
it
uh
but i don't know if i'll get into
planning
that right away uh because uh
next up is energy but that's more on her
side that's been planned on her side and
then again i think mentioned that
she wants to do a song cover with
turducken
um i think that would be mostly planned
out by
elena um
but i definitely want to do that to
reduction sun cover
uh
yeah but then i also want to do a
one-on-one song cover with raina one day
um
of course we already talked about it but
the one song that i really really would
love to deliver
is i think ng
so i gotta find another perfect song
that i think would be good but i think
we need we need a song that
reina is also an amazing singer it would
have to be something that really
shows off
both our vocals
and then
and then after that i'll continue
thinking about what to do next no magnet
yeah probably no magnet
unfortunately
i it's kind of perfect i love it i could
totally see it but i don't think it's
happening
yeah but we'll find something else
could you do more songs with me again
yeah i mean of course it's an option
but before going back to collabing with
them again
uh
on song covers uh
i want to leave you know
give and do some stuff with other girls
you know and and
until now all these sun covers were
planned out by me if they want to do a
song cover with me i'm always up for it
if they want to do it on their channel
i'm always up for it
but yeah i've i've paid for the
production of all of the song covers and
so
so maybe maybe next time they want to do
it
yeah
i get distracted whenever the guitar so
what happens me too
me too i don't know how i resisted just
now
with pekka and senpai i also like it's
kind of a dream of doing one with her
but i also am very shy about asking her
because i don't want to put her into an
awkward position
if she doesn't really want to do it
and she doesn't do much
song covers herself alone already
and yeah collabs
even less obviously
she's very focused on streaming
and she's very very busy so
yeah maybe i'll ask one day in the
future but
i think she's super super super busy and
we will see
[Music]
i know i know she did with luna
are you trying to hurt me
by saying that
uh no i don't i don't want to push it
too much onto her um
but
maybe i'll try one day but for the
moment i have plans with some um and
some ideas with other girls so
let's work on that first
encouragement
bae and kiana i can see that too i think
i think
that could work well
energy-wise
well hell yeah i can see it
motion thank you for the pinky what's
going to save this for tomorrow but her
challenge of singing means i'll send it
now ah thank you yeah i probably
wouldn't be singing it tomorrow been one
year since i faced a heart challenger
and my heart hasn't been the same since
oh wait i'm the hot challenger
i love this song and it's special to me
for more reasons than one it deserves so
much more wait did this continue i need
to refresh my
my super chat thingy my window
[Music]
refresh
where is it
[Music]
where does it continue
wait does it not continue it sounds like
it would continue i don't see a
continuation
it didn't continue
250 characters okay yeah but i thought
now it's incomplete what the [\h__\h]
you're just gonna leave it there
you're just gonna leave it on the
cliffhanger
i can't sleep like this
yes
oh my god are you asking to go into the
usual room
well then at least at least do me the
favor of sending the continuation on
twitter as a reply
i need answers
good endings
how what
oh you did already in the hashtag okay
oh thank you thank you very much it
deserves so much more love and attention
is that what what motion wrote in the
hashtag
it definitely deserves more love and
attention i agree with that thank you so
much
it's been one year wait motion are you
saying
you've been around before hard
challenger no are you saying you found
me for heart challenger
i feel like you've been around since
before that
[Music]
for appreciating her challenger the way
it's supposed to be
thank you and happy valentine's day to
you there it was again the guitar solo
captain jerkbands thank you for the red
super chat
happy valentine's day
lonely bot donkey shoe and shadow pencil
dance and red brick thank you thank you
yes please make fun videos or anything
fan art fan videos
hi smoothie
[Music]
i was just talking about you
not only was that hashtag but if it's
something that's not related to heart
challenger then of course you can use
the other hashtags like kfp or arts of
ashes
she seems very smoothy it's movie
[Music]
what was i gonna say she seems very
tired because she moves so slowly
she moves like a
what do you call those
the one in zootopia
the one that goes like very slowly
slowly
[Music]
soft yeah she's like a sloth right now
just woke up i think
man girl did you wake up like this you
look beautiful
sk that crazy max duncan
oh uh
um
that's that's that one right next above
[Music]
is
today was such a great day thanks to you
really
it was not even uh that long of a stream
but i made the whole day great for you
the stream was hilarious and cute and i
had some good loves there really is no
one else like you
oh
and also i got it finally my hands on
your birthday merch said love it thank
you doctors and i actually saw a lot of
people are getting the the plushies
right now
exciting to finally get the birds right
i'm glad everybody is receiving what
they paid for
oh oh i got the ends
[Music]
i was also
resting on
art
from your mama to you
she asked if i made it on stream she
said thank you with a surprised
uh
and embarrassed smiley
[Music]
hey
you need to chat you're so sweet
it sounds like you're
head over heels for me
thank you you're so sweet thanks and i
wish you a lovely valentine's day
tomorrow we'll also celebrate together
okay
the proper valentine's day
today is just early celebration because
i i wanted to be with you guys
wait oh accidental kiss you need to chat
oopsie doop theme
i thought that was a red one
you you can have it you can have it no
need to give it back
you've been so sweet to me
it's like a reflex now giving kisses it
comes automatically
yeah yeah you can have it it's okay
it's valentine's day so whatever moon
dog
and artistic night sappy reduction
yeah you're the best i'm so glad your
whole life there's nobody else like you
thank you
i'm so happy that i made it into like
especially like looking back there must
have been so many
so many auditions and i'm so lucky that
i got in
i would have been
so [\h__\h] if i didn't get in
i'm really really so grateful for the
opportunity
to have
um to to join whole life and to also
have met all of you um
happy valentine's day
[Music]
you guys always use these days these
opportunities to be sappy to me huh
i like it
roses are red violence art
you've said too much i'd run if i were
you
[Music]
wow that
sounds like we're in some kind of horror
game or thriller or something
yeah bye what's happening
scary scary no no no no this is a
wholesome stream
band is crazy about this phrase i don't
want to hear it anymore violets are not
blue
violets are not blue
how many more times do i have to say it
violent apple garden
thank you
are you really violent though
are you really violent
i have to check
send me a selfie
crazy weirdo thank you
[Music]
happy valentine's day travertine
roses are red kiana's violets aren't
blue please play mass effect so we can
hear we can all hear harbingers say this
hurts you
i might just unhinge
you're trying
oh it's good thank you soon
oh
blue dancing roses are red some violets
are blue this poem is still valid don't
make me sue you
why would you sue me on what rounds you
don't have any grounds to sue me
thanks for the pinky though you tried
again to make it work
it it at least rhymes
so i'll give you that
how the [\h__\h] do i read this name
party
[Music]
it's in some fancy letters is this
supposed to mean
party
i think so party duncan
thank you
green wilder thank you for the rest of
the tag
roses are red violets are violet let me
show you the world the truth is i'm a
pilot
we'll see cities and mountains and have
a great time all i need is your smile
it's simply sublime
amazing
you extended it into a proper poem
this is how you do it learn from him
learn from green wilder or wilder
he's doing it right
[Music]
can i get a leader of cola and uh number
two
oh man green will there's a case for you
happy valentine's day
my smile
you need my smile i'm smiling all the
time almost by default so
[Music]
there it is
are we at mcdonald's here or what
until then thank you for the rest of my
chance this stream was long enough to
last until midnight so now i can
officially wish you happy valentine's
day oh it's still not midnight here but
thank you
it's just one day in the year but you
should know that i love you every day
try not to eat too much chocolate you're
sweet enough already
oh stop you cutie pies
thank you
i love you too everything
thank you for your love happy
valentine's day i'll be catching up soon
so please wait for me
i'm on my way
thank you
for your love
please continue supporting me
i would be very happy to have you in kfp
continuing from now on too
i'm fully web thank you for the rest of
the chat kiana i'm listening to you
while at work love you thank you i hope
work is going well and wait on a sunday
oh man
you're one of those people who have to
work on sundays huh
well
i wish you
a lot of fun at work
and hopefully you can get out of work
soon and then chill a little bit but
thank you for watching me during your
work day
appreciate it
hope it's not so bad and busy
you are working on a sunday yeah i don't
know i have a
i have a very flexible
flexible schedule after all i'm very
flexible you know
but it's well i decide but i kind of
really thought
like already like two days ago kind of
that it was already sunday really
confusing
thank you
happy valentine's day soon
[Music]
boo hoo seven two three donkey
it's that time of the year where from
the bottom of my hair i have to say you
mean heart my bottom from the bottom of
my heart i have to say love you tainto
well i say that at the end of every
stream but the feelings behind those
words for this day at least are slightly
different love you love you love love
you love you love you too thank you
happy valentine's day
thank you for always telling me it's
nice to hear it every day
super nerf duncan mental jetty duncan
for the rest of the chat happy
valentine's day
on this day i just want to let you know
that i'm never gonna give you up never
gonna let you
[Music]
thank you for that
i feel very loved
[Music]
i'm always
welcoming requires
always
thank you mental jetty happy valentine's
day mwah
john monday thank you for the rest of
the chat your attention happy
valentine's day happy valentine's day to
you too
thank you very much mwah gargantuan
kitchen for the pinky hey tanjo just
wanted to say you deserve every bit of
love sent you away so here's some from
me oh i won't make a flower rhyme like
all the rest all i can say is you're
simply the best
thanks for another fun stream thank you
you're simply the best
better than all the rest
i don't know the rest of the lyrics
though
thank you
happy valentine's day to you i like your
poem
very much
for the red super chat
[Music]
finally got home from vacation happy
early valentine's day and love you lost
potential
oh missed certain parts of your live
stream since you came back but we'll get
and finish them like a good channel if i
love my imaginary chicken left yay
welcome back how was your vacation how
was it how was it how was it how was it
how was it how was it how was it how was
it how was it where did you go where'd
you go did you tell me already where did
you go i forgot if you told me i forgot
tell me again tell me again tell me
again show me pictures show me pictures
did you enjoy it are you are you are you
uh uh did you get some sunlight did you
touch them under some grass or did you
touch some some snow or did you touch
some water did you did you touch all of
it
how was it how was it did you eat some
good food
did you have a good travel back home did
you make some nice memories did you make
some friends how was it how was it how
was it tell me tell me tell me tell me
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's a whole little talk speed quiz
round
tell me on twitter
[Music]
oh oh man oh what he doesn't
he doesn't even like wet food and dry
food
any of it
what the [\h__\h]
well that's tough
[Music]
well you could maybe try
maybe as a last resort is making
cat food
kind of yourself i've seen people make
dog food themselves but i also think
i've seen people make cat food
themselves which is definitely also the
healthier option because you know what
you're putting in
but then you got to experiment trying to
figure out what they like
um
that's tough
oh
mother makes cats with herself oh
does she also eat it herself just
kidding
around the kitchen
[Music]
yeah the coco cosplayer looked amazing
i'm happy to hear that
she looked great
she should cosplay me while she's
doing orange cosplays
maybe she can reuse the wig
restyle it into kiwawa wig
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
i'll do my best
refreshing again
how many super jets are left
julia blonder thank you for the red
super chat
as a champion i may not be eternal but
my love for you is you're my son my life
shines the brightest thanks to you i
treasure every moment with a special
amazing verb
ah happy valentine's day love you kiawah
stop
some things look cute
and charming
thank you
wow happy valentine's day to you
oh my god
i love you too
karma student thank you for the red
super chat rose is from titanic violet
is from evil garden
and not a real poet but i love you and i
ain't afraid to show it oh
happy valentine's day wow wow
thank you
that was unexpected
thank you soon thank you very much happy
valentine's day to you too
wish you all the best
[Music]
so we all know you'll never stop talking
about how much you love cats but have
you ever heard the song i love cat
splash mojo haul
no
you're welcome to send it to me on
twitter because i don't i don't want to
look it up right now i wanna i wanna i
wanna finish the super chats and go eat
something
thank you for the
sorry for bringing this up now but i
think you need to know if you thought
you could stop me from being a dd using
a secret you are brainwashing technique
you were wrong it was your sweet and the
dating cast is a new personality that
made me want to tell me you'll love you
might i see you for a sec
i see what you did there
thank you
i love you
thank you that's what i like to hear
a bamboozle that ends positively
thank you
happy valentine's day to you thank you
for letting me be your aussie
[Music]
i need to tell you that i love you uber
went through
there's no one else in this world that i
would trade for you
for the pinky happy mountain day my
country not really gets into this day
yeah same here
but i want to say i love you and could i
know my kfp employee now but my card is
still empty thank you danger
yes
it is
giving out two numbers today one is two
one four and the other one is four one
two yours is four one two
thank you happy valentine's day
as a zombie
[Music]
hope you had fun with the stream i
didn't
i have a little something in the works
from kfp and i oh hope to get it done
soon but late for for today no problem
sorry lots of love i wonder what it is
now i'm curious wait is that another
like community project
[Music]
oh yeah yeah
from kfp and i
i wonder what it is
sort of oh i'm looking forward to it
wait if it won't be done in time for
today will it be there tomorrow tomorrow
tomorrow or the day after tomorrow when
when white work
uh but yeah i hope i hope i will catch
it not miss it please uh use uh all the
hashtags you want to make me notice it
you saw it already what
the [\h__\h] i can power fruit oh no no no
take the time take your time um if it
ensures quality
quality over
kiwawa begging for it
yeah but thank you i'm excited to see
what you worked on thank you so much for
your support and happy valentine's day
last one
so now i will go before you guys end up
sending more um i'll see you guys
tomorrow uh and oh yeah schedule coming
in a moment of jackson
jackson pretty nicely for the pinky
roses are red i'm not a poet i hope i
get fried soon so i can go in buckets
bad poems aside happy early valentine's
day tanjo thanks for all your hard work
and the upcoming song i know it will be
a banger
thank you
i can't wait for all of your hearts to
explode uh looking at the tete music
video
working with kannada is such a pleasure
because
he just put so much
love into and so much
creativity into these videos that he
makes
i'm i'm so excited to have you guys see
that video
and the song turned out cute too so
yeah yeah stream heart explode
[Music]
um
schedule coming out soon also there's a
holo talk next week so
yes we're coming back we're going back
into the usual rhythm hopefully
and
you will see who is going to be on whole
talk on my schedule
thanks everybody for watching today and
in german we say auf wiedersehen i'll
see you when it's valentine's day on my
time zone
yeah
oh and i'll also be at the premiere but
thank you for your love and support
everybody
and
yeah thank you for spending your time
with me today sky dancing these cards
turned out so cute i'll be uploading
them all on twitter afterwards
bye-bye
[Music]
muchachos
you pretty hint excuse me
hey
you fight i wouldn't say that huh
i'll have a talk with you behind the
scenes
[Music]
thank you for renewing your membership
also or actually i guess it's a
membership message but still thank you
[Music]
i want chocolate
hi
[Music]
is
hey
that's that's a correct rather cmca
right