[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
as ready as we could be
as ready as possible hey look you know
what let it be said that we tried man I
grinded in this game we've been here
early too we've been practicing as a
team yes I don't know it's pretty good
we weren't doing well I don't think we
lost yeah we had some good batteries we
were too strong together
I feel like the BC buff
today's stream if you're not aware is
the pre Pokemon World Championship
events
[Applause]
thank you a huge thank you for including
thank you very much thank you exciting
the first Pokemon unite World
Championship to be held in Asia we'll
start tomorrow from August 11th to 12th
in Yokohama and in the Pokemon unite
category teams from all around the world
will fight for their championship and we
will also be fighting for championship
against Indonesia and JP representing
team Hollow Ian and who's in serious
business it is serious
here for our team I am serious fauna I'm
be taking the Pokemon Wiggly tough as
full of support
we also have Miss Calliope Mori would
you like to introduce yourself everybody
more Clive here
um I will be playing as Garchomp the
jungler
um I will be jungler or I uh I will feed
so
I mean mid later mid later sorry sorry
mid later I will be mid laner excuse me
and Iris Would you like to introduce
yourself uh hiris it's Iris
Iris uh using
music day animation's wearing very cute
clothes and I will be bottom today
[Laughter]
um
I'm representing every European out
there who is currently awake at 4 5 or 6
a.m I've been staying awake but I'm very
awake still so I think I will be fine
let's come buddy muscle I'm doing alola
nine tails because yeah what else
it'll be great it'll be great
Amelia Watson please introduce yourself
Amelia Watson number one detective today
I'll be your tank yes rely on me please
just stay with me
I'm going top with uh Kiara yes
you chose My Bodyguard yeah pretty much
it's only a little bit of time left
before the world championship I'm sure
everyone is okay final championship oh
wait yeah for today there's only a few
minutes
left
so how about we watch the PV together
okay I'll do a little countdown and we
can all share it on our streams okay I
hope I don't blast your guys's ears
the start one yeah yeah yes yes first
one
three two one go
[Music]
I broke the budget for this one whoa
look at that cash money
it kind of looks like Crush
I wish I looked this cool when playing
Pokemon I know I know right we will I
will look this cool we're just holding
our switch Pro cons today exactly
high five
I did not recognize that fish Pokemon
just now is that something new one of
the muralists
so which one you mean there's so many
shows right now
cute
[Music]
what do you guys think wow cool right
that was really cute
it's fun to show anime on on our streams
yeah
uh let's move on over to the event
overview I believe we're ready
yup that's the slides
I'm not ready I'm ready wait the slides
uh the the the slides right okay wait
yeah
these slides
it says here we're first this is wrong
it says em first oh
[Laughter]
was it changed
um
and we thought that that was a good idea
because you know it would be a ninja
can you find out for us if this is
accurate right now and we'll just talk
over it for now yeah hello I'm a Pokemon
unite World Tournament is a promotional
event for the Pokemon u9 category of the
world championship 2023 well I'm a whole
life English and whole life Indonesia
will battle head to head to settle who
will shine on top hopefully it'll be us
the three matches on BJP versus ID IDE
versus Ian and JP versus Ian and the
match will follow the WCS rules
therefore Mewtwo will be banned oh wait
are you guys showing the slides sorry
yes yeah
the shoes like it's like black wait wait
okay
reopened and in a case of a 3D pie the
team who scores the most will be crowned
the winner no so okay for points
tournaments go
the winner wins the winner wins
wins and
yeah I think there's there should be
like something right here
mm-hmm
next slide please
the MVPs each team will be awarded with
like real physical prizes the WCS
official uniforms which are not for sale
they're very exclusive and a cute
plushie wearing the Pokemon United's
halloware
and other teams will be awarded with 2D
trophies according to their placements
[Music]
difference in color that's all you know
yeah you can just put something
different except for the color if it's
just on the star screen no one will know
yeah they'll think we're the winners
yeah me too I know it's beginning of the
shirt our characters in game are also
wearing this shirt which you can also
purchase yourself from the shop the
digital version in the in-game store
it
we are going first seems like it yeah
apparently okay
that's great that's amazing mentally
ready for ready oh well trial by fire
here we go we are doing good just
remember how we were yeah remember we
were winning
okay JP team it's fine
you darn sweaty though yeah no problem
we can be sweaty too just gotta get in
the mindset you know yeah
other participants for the tournament
from JP we have okay
um
[Music]
one British girl
the most mythical of creatures
I know in Hollow Yen I've really been
wanting well I guess we have we got on
me we have British ones
[Music]
I miss hearing your British accent you
don't bring it out very often you know
I wish you would let your natural accent
shine sometimes
it's okay
next slide
oh
we can close it and we put away the
slide can we close it okay I close it
okay
as mentally prepared as we thought
um
I was still debating on what Pokemon to
choose
how do we get into the room
uh they will send a code and we will
input the code make sure not to show it
on stream I love how the order of the
matches it makes it seem like the whole
alive JP and ID are like the the finals
and I get to sleep early if yeah I mean
yeah I guess
I'll probably stay awake anyway though
let's be honest we gotta fight till the
end yeah
we're never gonna win if we have this
kind of attitude
formation when the objective fights okay
if you're losing your lane matchup you
know who to call
the code will be provided to us exactly
right
yes I'm gonna go into meet the rest of
the
should we do we wait until they are oh
it looks like they are I think they're
going okay okay we go there okay are
they is there a Lobby already the all
regions Channel it looks like oh to
produce for introductions yes
okay we go we go let's go do it again
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
come on
let's go let's go
[Laughter]
yes
please
yeah yeah because I taught it too good I
think that's why thank you Kiara thank
you
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
please share your feelings now
I'm feeling motivated confident and we
need to go into this with optimism
believe in yourself I'm proud of you you
guys have been climbing the Rings
you can beat let's go JP and ID teams
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no I'm motivated
I'm looking forward to seeing your good
fight battle thank you yes
[Music]
oh it seems that's the battle already
started right the gold
that was faster
[Music]
yeah there is
everyone here
you can't do that to me
believe yourself
[Applause]
[Music]
because my tummy hurts oh no
the food you ate
before nervous food don't be nervous
we'll be fine food just gotta Focus
foreign
you know if they screw up big time are
we good is that the code okay
here we go it's over quickly
yeah there's your code okay I gotta hide
okay I hide yes hide code Avi search
I searched the lobby
I'm in the lobby
oh I think it said something like we are
supposed to be
uh
uh like at top
or at the bottom like there's a specific
order they want us to be in really
yeah it was in the in the like
explanation for me but now that the
order is changed I'm confused too but
maybe we're in the right spot because I
think it said for the first one and Ian
down for the second one
let's go with that yeah
I think
should we decide on that beforehand yeah
it might be situational depending on
where the others are
um okay
um I should be high enough level at a
certain point where I can kind of guard
the bottom and then also take out the
bottom objective by myself if I do the
jungle correctly
it would be good
out of my jungle please
stomp us and then get our first our
first uh
goal down and then they also get an
objective we can try to go and steal
their Farm in the jungle in the
wilderness well wait your command
apparently um JP team struggles against
aggressive players so we really need to
play aggressive okay let's play
aggressive oh it's starting oh shoot too
early
oh
[Music]
I wonder if it's
especially so for sure yep
um and then okay can we can we try to be
not like screaming all the time because
it will freak me out yeah okay yeah
we'll go we'll be calm but call me cool
just like we're playing against the bots
so that we can also hear fauna clearly
when she wants something from us right
they have a question too okay so Dragon
Claw is the meta but I'm going with
earthquake so that I can take out the
bigger Farms of swablu in alteria so and
also attack from a bit more of a
distance who's going who's going Bottom
with me I'm going Bottom okay
just like practice it's like we
practiced you just slap oh God my hands
are so sweaty already
pop this really quick I'll use it again
later
for the middle go for the middle I mean
oh gosh darn it oh see they're here ah
they are here of course they're here
Mama do you need help thank you I'm okay
though did they steal it just do it what
do we do next do we attack them I am
useless until level five well we'll just
poke a little bit okay let's go and get
this they're scared they're scared come
on
don't let them steal it don't let them
steal it
I think they did
going back to rest one second
okay
who needs more help bottom or top
should we go we're doing okay we're
doing fine right now but yeah
um
their their middle person oh let's go
for the middle one
okay
yeah yeah
this thing traps you damn okay yeah
okay
yeah
nice Kelly okay
nice nice
take it down here yeah let's go
score
okay
higher level
okay I need to level up dude's almost
dead though oh damn it it's okay you
guys can tell okay I'm lagging pretty
bad she on this back
40 seconds
okay
should we should we uh I got it okay
should I join down there
um
[Music]
I think it's my internet
uh
thank you is coming if I do okay
wait wait here don't attack yet
for bottom yeah they're going for bottom
should we should we interrupt I think we
should try to steal it seven
okay let's try steal it okay
you guys can go for it okay good okay
but like distract them
thank you
okay
nice nice nice all right okay good job
let's go
okay let's not play too aggressive yeah
I mean I'm back play safe places back go
back if you have to
and I want to grab Center form again
hold on oh actually yeah
you think they're gonna steal it they
might but we could grab it we could grab
it we should actually believe because we
got it we got it you got it nice nice
but we have to protect it uh they're all
right I'm coming let's go coming let's
go top
two things
that's okay let's go over here okay
we're coming no we're coming we're
coming
it's okay oh no problem yummy
where's Umbreon
it's fine it's fine don't worry don't
worry
I can't really fight um
it's okay just uh be the bouncy person
okay
just be bouncy I'm gonna back up
my dad really we don't want to fight on
there
there you can I'm trying to get out but
I'm lagging oh no I'm sorry it's okay
we'll be fine
mm-hmm
oh there's scissors you're gonna pop it
out real quick hold on I can't do
anything hold on okay
nice I know I'm so sorry oh did one die
this one day all right sorry
I'm sorry it's good I also died too
we're good
they also died one of them died I got
greedy I got really greedy I think that
was my little teeth
run back my game is updating sorry about
that guys I will be back okay let me get
over here and help
nice actually
on scoring bottom okay hold on um
too much
I think we need to farm a little I think
we're focusing too much on trying to
fight them yeah okay uh he's a bad girl
trying to kill me all right hold on yeah
we can try to get the braggy
I'm a business but I can hold it I can
hold it you can try to hold bottom yeah
wait what level are we is everyone
higher than us no they're Nine and Nine
yeah
behind me
bottom
okay
Shield is good
I don't know who who I know I know
either can't pop a speed
I really need to drop my my scores
though yeah we shouldn't get greedy
though because we have an advantage
right now
oh they just got they just got ready
guys okay let me okay okay hold on a sec
no worries we're coming back
I should have known they were down there
I was not paying attention
thanks guys I will be there in a second
I need to be a higher level
crazy okay
[Music]
I'm dead okay hold on
I'm not high enough level yet yeah we
should be careful about team fights I
think I think
there's only two minutes left actually
we should oh God we should defend I
think okay should we go down or up I'm
just gonna get a buff really quick are
going up yeah but we might need it we
probably need to take my closet right
yeah already
be safe okay
full attack we're all here well here I
think we should here let's go let's go
100.
okay I have something to score uh we
should defend if we can too oh they're
they're doing like crazy over there
hello
why am I scoring here I don't know
it works no it doesn't work
[Laughter]
I know where did they come from
[Music]
yeah
oh no there's like three of them oh God
I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead oh damn it
[Music]
I don't know we just have to stop them
from uh depositing points and we can
still win we might be even right now
[Music]
um
I'll defend I'll stay in defend if you
guys go yeah
to go over I was willing to risk it for
a biscuit the hell got me at least hey I
distracted them where are they right now
at the bottom no they were all the way
to the right at their home bases at
their home base okay so I probably can't
can't they're probably Defenders
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's not bad next match
we'll get them next time good job good
job
I'm proud of you guys I thought that was
pretty good yeah we got the recoils
yeah he was closed it was close because
so
[Music]
it's kind of rough yeah anyway
let's try yeah maybe maybe check chat
for one second yeah I needed far more
I'm like going inside my presence Ambush
um
so we're leaving the lobby right
are we playing again immediately yeah it
seems immediately yeah we're warmed up
it's true but my hands are shanky I know
controllers
Chad I'm sorry oh is there already a
room is there a room
another one
what about now Chad
I thought it was just super quiet champ
okay okay wait do we still have a chance
okay yeah okay well wait a minute
yeah we do we do we're only behind 200
points as long as we'll see how ideas uh
again
oh
oh wow they know our cards
okay they watched that is true they have
that
okay had a fun time damn it all right I
think I know and I thought we'd be in
that position for this next one yeah
yeah I think in that one team fights
were our weakness
because we weren't arriving all at the
same time yeah yeah gotta make sure not
to start and I was doing this
before everyone arrived oh whoops I'm
sorry wait hold on is this the wrong
weird
thought they went to the wrong one
um yeah I will try and help if I can but
I really need to try to focus more on
farming otherwise so you can put this on
farms and we can just try in the
try to defend yourself try to help if I
can though yeah yeah
since you were looking at the time a lot
um oh yeah we just need to remember so
seven minutes the first objective
unlocks and then a two minutes Rayquaza
so around like 30 seconds or a minute
before that we got to be prepared to
like it at three after three Thirty
don't use your old I think so yeah
when there's yeah 3 30 left okay
how do I move my position wait
over here are we supposed to be bottom
this time I think yeah they were all on
top so
it seems like it but I don't know
[Music]
we missing fauna here oh yeah
okay
um
yeah I I get so tunnel visioned and I
don't really get what was like after I
get to a certain level I'm just like
what should I do now yeah I think just
stay with the team or something
[Music]
in the beginning because Evie is weak as
hell in the beginning and yeah I have to
wait until I get to like at least level
six or seven to get ice shard
yeah I think it too
we were focusing a lot on fighting them
we probably should have just been
staying back and farming yeah yeah
we can try that too
okay okay okay
maybe she was only using it for that
stream I don't know but
they were going with like a pretty
pretty
meta-ish I think I forgot
I've got your back so let's show the
screen I forgot about that okay okay I'm
glad you're back so cute I'm going to
focus on being the strongest
whoa
good work no
I gave up on Lapras
anyways I think Lapras is too too weak
for this
comp
and also also because lappers did not
have much outfits yes
I really don't like zorark
oh yeah yeah
um I think she's juggler yeah I think
she is oh God we're gonna have such a
bad time
confidence up
okay okay all right all right
I believe all right I'm gonna be the
strongest right now seven minutes and
three minutes beware yes
three minutes what happens in three
minutes should be ready okay what 3 30.
don't use your old how long does it take
for the ultimate it depends on the
character yeah but it'll be safe if you
win 3 30.
well arranged
dang it
I want to get that form
steal it I think I saw it nice I'm
scared oh man we'll be fine I'm going
back to heal
oh okay
they're being very aggressive
[Music]
okay I'll come down to grab well you
guys got the form
what do we do
um
she was ready for those Burgers they're
scoring right now okay
um should we go should we go
I needed I need to actually get some
Buffs go back don't make sure
it's strong
it's okay okay
in the middle so yeah just try to place
it don't die and farm as much
okay
I'm gonna speed up I need to keep
farming actually I need to focus on
being the strongest I'm gonna go for
Middle Farm yeah there might be an
ambush
I think they're all going for a top is
it just me I think
Iris do you think you can hold your own
down here
I could I could I'll try I'll try you
can you can go up I'll I'll try it
zero scary
Thailand Bots
right go down don't fight right now come
come
oh that was close that was close yeah
I help them I was gonna help them but
never mind oh okay
I'm lagging again oh no oh gosh man yeah
he's here
yeah just try to hold them off and just
try not to die and get it I want to
score
I can solo this
[Music]
yeah and I'll try and farm at the same
time
points uh should I try to defend or yeah
we should try to defend
um but we'll have extra Farm after this
in this Lane
I shouldn't have sandwiches
[Music]
yeah they're really coordinated
two more minutes left
and we can take it yeah the Pokemon in
this Lane in the Top Lane there will be
bonus mons of uh spawn oh because they
didn't give up stuff yeah because they
took ours oh they're getting their Farm
yeah they're all in Top Lane it's scary
I think I saw at least
group up yeah okay
where should we go I'm actually pretty
good just keep on top I guess we should
we should Farm probably I'm gonna farm
so they're gonna come in and try to kill
like anyone
okay
alarm time I don't see any form at the
top right now yeah
jungle okay
should we go
they're trying to kill me they're
already killed me
this is scary
how are their levels doing right now
uh let me see uh I'm still a level above
we're in it I'm gonna go bottom
amazing bottom right now
let me know if you need me somewhere I'm
farming yeah
I think it's fine though okay we should
probably go Top
Gun actually I'll wait for you oh wait
they're all down in the bottom Lane are
they okay we could just go top though
Kyla's bottom Lane wait did they leave
they left she can solo everything yeah
it's pretty strong okay I have
successfully or try not to topped my
score okay okay
do we want to go aggressively for once
maybe maybe last we can get it they
might be waiting this little bro here
they come
oh no
you see now that was a party yeah
are you kidding me I love being useless
to my team
yeah it was because of the leg let it be
known let it be known that was because
and see if we can make it count okay
okay yeah
I thought I didn't die everyone should
be saving all their stuff so we can try
to win and I'm saving us okay
um
we're really struggling yay I'm really
struggling actually hold on oh here
comes
oh
okay
yep wait
yeah dang it
um right just get ready for Rayquaza oh
yeah yeah I still have my old thankfully
we do have a lot of points we could put
in
you might need someone to stay and
defend I'm not sure
I don't know I feel like all of us can
just go
I think they're all gonna go Rayquaza oh
they're probably getting the bottom
yeah you can't get that in time
they're definitely down there oh oh
Kathy I thought you were Kyla oh no here
no no no
foreign
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
your best try to score
I'm so sorry they're so strong so bad oh
God they killed me
yeah here I got I'm gonna pick up the
points yeah yeah
thank you I need help Cali I'm coming
they're guarding the middle regarding
the middle maybe you can go top top the
topper the one is great
[Applause]
I'm coming
I
just one person on top is enough
leave there's no way there's no way oh
nice scallions
[Music]
okay let's see let's see
there's no way did we I don't believe
because did we actually I didn't know
[Music]
[Applause]
so that you can live longer nice job
bait
s
[Music]
look at the T-shirt you can get the
T-shirt
wait we're doing the doll yeah yeah use
it for every match I think it's for
every match right for every MVP yeah
let's go yay
I'm so happy I'm proud of you guys
we did really well in the first week
hey I got this shirt guys that was MVP
yeah
[Music]
I'm so sorry
if we maybe got a second place hopefully
we'll see after the next match if they
tally up all the points that doesn't
work so like if and deserves
if I do loses somewhere first I don't
get away how does it work you have to
get less than like 300 points which is
unlikely unless JP is
we'll see
okay
okay download the points oh
I want to spectate are we able to do
that yeah I'm gonna set up once Fonda
makes the room we just join the
spectators first okie dokie
too much excitement
and we did good nice job yeah we won a
match yeah I'm proud
I'm glad that we practiced a lot yeah
I'm glad I grinded like like 10 11 hours
yesterday
yeah you guys worked hard
you too afana thanks for helping us
learn the game yeah I wouldn't have been
able to do without you thanks for
playing
also thanks for the the tips uh chat as
well to improve my jungle game I feel
like that second that second game was
much better yeah yeah good good strong
mid lane game let's go
she just comes out of nowhere and then
bam bam bam bam
so scary can we get a run back with JP
now can we try it again
[Music]
uh I know kiwawa you want to sleep no
it's not because of that I'm not even
tired even though I've been awake since
I don't know it's adrenaline yeah
oh
[Music]
happy yeah now we get to sit back and
watch back and relax no matter what
happens we've already done so
I know yeah
I'm really curious to see how these
aggressive teams play against each other
so wait for us to get first place if it
were to happen
um then
what wait wait so if JP wins then we
definitely then JP definitely gets first
place right um tiny wins then there
might be a chance depending on point
difference they could get like 800
points yeah we don't know it could be a
close match with these two teams
yeah yeah I think because I don't know I
don't know if we'll amount to uh like a
third place because of our points it was
pretty close third place oh maybe
yeah
yeah oh it is
we still we still
we fought we won one match
the JP match was close it was it was
pretty close it just kind of slipped up
at the end and yeah I should have been
stronger but the thing was holding me
back
it's the pain
yeah
the lag really got me the last one okay
we're starting
oh we're starting okay I'm starting okay
I wonder how spectator looks yeah
do we get to fly around probably ah wait
I need to show oh that'll be kind of
cool I think that you can I think we get
to just fly around the camera did you
guys know that like on the edges
edges of the what you would call it the
the map there's like this Magnemite
holding a camera yeah I'm seeing so cute
it's adorable
it's a cameraman thank you
so what do you guys who were you betting
on
um
if he was not very aggressive so ID
might have it yet very aggressive yeah
no we will see though
because they're both pretty strong
[Music]
it will be exciting I know I can't focus
though my adrenaline's too high I never
need to chill
chat who do you want me to to focus on I
can follow someone specific
I want to see how she jungles that
question I mean mid lane yeah yeah Kayla
because JP got a break between maybe
they've you know recovered
um
yeah true so cute
the baby babies
[Music]
so efficient I didn't know the flower
was like a shark fish looking thing in
the beginning
a starfish it looks like a starfish you
know the red yeah right you're right it
started with the flower or like a star
fruit yeah yeah I could see that yeah
they seem so determined oh my God oh my
God
go for it
you can do it yeah they're playing
aggressively oh yeah
this is the most important level going
oh okay the Kyle is inside there right
now higher level than Kayla right now
oh
[Music]
she's back in the rotation to get the
Buffs again
she's level six so is Glaceon who's
playing going soon
right now okay
[Music]
they're strong
Anya's chilling
[Music]
two versus three on the top
oh Kyla's low again
I mean they're scoring yeah
they did
push them back
[Applause]
I'm glad they didn't honestly I think I
would have choked me too yeah
oh yeah he's going first
for the top yeah
okay almost down pick whatever Retreat
oh oh Japanese
yeah
I feel like yeah JP put in most of the
work
let's go all about the final hit
everyone's on top right now yeah
everyone's ignoring the atom I guess
he's much more important defended really
well though
this is exciting I like spectating I
know
I wish I could zoom out oh my God
assuming let's go
let's go go where's she going it's
dangerous cool but there's free there's
free enemies coming
oh
down here oh
they're aiming they're getting they're
going for the Regis okay
I know right that's so weird it seems
like JP is winning but
yeah I just been picking them off
getting some kills yeah
then
[Music]
I guess the others are joining
oh they might score a lot here oh
they're scoring a lot here yeah oh oh
that was getting close
JP with the late game is so they know
what they're doing they know what
they're doing they're constantly farming
always picking up this poorest moms yeah
[Music]
up top
yeah it is well Cuba's going for the
bottom they're going there yeah okay we
have it uh ID has a plan for Ray Costa
yes
oh they got Ollie oh
I feel like they would be very good
communicators the ID girl so they're
gonna discover their Minecraft server is
anything to go by yeah
[Music]
um
so
the point difference we need you it's
not too big still yeah yeah Rayquaza can
still turn it around but us being third
place has probably already set in stone
yeah
is it by games one
okay I think I think yeah if I mean if
if he wins this then I think
by points we'd be okay
but okay if they get requested what is
what I mean
Kyla is going around
[Music]
here
this was the bait JPS is super
coordinated as well
[Music]
one minute
yeah we'll see how Rayquaza goes Sophie
that's the main point yeah we're all
cheering for ID for a lot of reasons
I see how coordinated JP is I'm feeling
like proud that we held our own against
him right together pretty good against
them to be honest
oh it was close if only I didn't die
that much I'm just like uh
dang it uh I should have aimed my old
better
[Music]
our last minute our grind was I think we
did pretty good yeah
[Music]
it's only in our practices our enemies
weren't so good so so I know again
really they're really going for Reggie
Reggie like you when Rayquaza's gonna
yeah they are respond really soon
interesting yeah yeah I'm just gonna go
for it yeah
he's gonna get it oh oh they took they
took down one Japan man the other three
they're three oh okay they took down the
energy too
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's gonna be so close
it's too close
yeah there's only one guarding I think
and everyone else is going offensive
what is the right answer for this one
be careful be careful I don't know
ID defend Maybe
yeah they don't know what the points are
yeah
they have no idea
thank you boss I'm so excited
yeah people keep running
yo yo oh my gosh
they got the points in yeah oh my gosh
fubiki's gonna try and score these
points
[Music]
that was awesome that was so clutch
wow
I know good matches they're really good
match yeah great it's like clothes for
everyone that was amazing oh wait so
everybody won one match yeah yeah
oh
well guys we did our best
I'm proud of us
I mean look at how scary and chaotic and
crazy that battle was yeah
going up against these girls is quite a
challenge huge that was huge
for that MBP
Japanese sign
everybody did well
I am I'm proud of everyone I'm proud
yeah everyone knew what to do pretty
much yeah there was nobody that was like
fumbling around like I didn't practice
Yeah
I can confirm I did practice a lot
that was fun it was really fun it was
fun that was really fun yeah I think I
might try to play more this season to
hopefully get to ultra I'm playing yeah
actually this was I feel like my mom got
closer you know yeah it's it's really
like it feels like sports like the team
camaraderie yeah I want to play games
together too like I don't know yeah yeah
fun collab game I think it's a good
zatsu game too yeah in general yeah once
you know what to do yeah if you're not
too sweaty
so what happens now we we go they're
telling the points
okay
[Music]
we must capture the slides again
okay awesome excited for that it will go
well yeah we fine I just need to prepare
yeah because the chat asking we don't
know the final tally yet we don't know
not yet we do not you know Max then you
may know
don't tell us we don't want to know we
want to stay oblivious yeah no man yeah
if you can do math your band
okay don't mess around you can't be
smarter than the fifth grade first
grader
at least being the top three I think so
yeah we're on the podium
think about it like the Olympic bronze
medal is something very something very
proud an
otter it's true just like that right
yeah yeah as big of an honor as that
I'm proud that we won a game I saw so
many people
is gonna get destroyed they're not gonna
win a single game
walk all over us yeah
we've been training we've been working
but I was ready to be the most beautiful
carpets there to be these things
orange carpets
yeah it had to be a flying one where am
I flying to Flying to Victory
pad
for a dog the underdog prevailed
well chat did you guys enjoy watching
that did you know what was going on all
the time man it was always fun to watch
yeah
so sweaty like these kind of games yeah
yeah yes yes
like this like you know and I see like
tournaments going on and whatnot I look
at it and I always like oh they're just
spamming skills it's just like an MMORPG
I was like oh that was fun but I don't
why is it
so now I get it yeah
[Music]
when we like joined this in kikaku I
don't think we any of us expected it to
be dead Syria
it would be a fun
fact
friendly friendly competition
but I'm really excited because I think
we trained enough to make it like
interesting matches yeah
definitely
it wasn't too one-sided in any of the
matches I mean yeah the thing is like a
lot of Japanese and ID members were
already like really well practiced in
this game from what I've seen a lot of
Master
ranks so you know yeah we just started
playing a lot of us yeah
yeah
but we put in the work it feels good I
was playing in my dreams like last night
did you win in your dream or did you
lose uh well I was just like attacking
stuff in my dream but then when I was
trying to fall asleep I was like running
around in the game and I kept running
into walls and it was really frustrating
oh yeah
I get chased a lot in my nightmares just
like here in Pokemon
so it was a nightmare no no not at all I
wish
I came while we're waiting
yeah
rematch rematch
I'm happy with the way we've performed
yeah
it's so much more fun to like play with
like friends and like VCS and yeah it
was so frustrating yesterday when I was
like yeah you know queuing by myself and
then like oh yeah the random would like
you know leave me in the in the area
alone and I'm just like why everyone was
at the top in the beginning I'm like
what the what are you doing that I'm
like I'm Central
I'm Central I'm jungle and then I wait
like five seconds and then right before
the match starts somebody else says I'm
jungle and I'm like are you kidding me I
might as well not even do it
yeah I also had troubles playing alone
soloing regileki so many times I was
like why don't you girls wanna go up
there and get that objective why not
[Music]
feels bad man
feels bad but this feels good man yeah
I'm like playing with the five stack yum
yeah I'm still I still don't know if the
held items I chose was the correct
answer though I didn't go with like the
most standard build I went with
I chose something else for the because I
wanted to make myself less squishy but I
was still really really squishy so I'm
just like maybe I should have gone all
offensive I don't know oh they're going
up now yeah I think it's time okay the
final results
foreign
[Music]
I got it size wise it looks a little
already
sorry this wasn't supposed to play this
I'm sorry
how do I turn it off oh my gosh sorry
[Music]
oh God is almost done thank you for your
good photo Arigato yay
thank you
yeah
[Music]
are you ready for it okay
not even
[Music]
um
I feel like I'm hallucinating places
thank you
[Applause]
he's a really amazing
let me know you were sold
um
as a leader in leader please here you
are sold
I'm really proud of everyone many people
doubted the ENT but I hope that we show
it
our abilities today I think we did I'm
proud of everybody
[Applause]
thank you for your team it was really
amazing amazing match yeah
as a leader only time please say
yourself hi
um we we all worked really hard like uh
all of us really strategized a lot do
you guys have anything that you guys
would like to say ID team ready
[Laughter]
we can see a very good teamwork
communication thank you so much
and we really enjoy Ed
I'm really glad you enjoyed this much
[Music]
no no no
more today
[Music]
many balls
[Applause]
[Music]
and not only this so um
MVP is
oh
my God
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
congratulations
great leader you go to MVP in the first
match and you're really supportive
yes
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah you go to MVP and you
contribute to the comeback come back
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
thank you
oh so we on the stream now or something
so we showed the last video
just give me a second hold on
because when we left the slide thing
awesome you played it
reminds me play the videos
okay
let me pull up the Slime
what time hold on is it slides it's not
not the video
Spider-Man videos
[Music]
you can also do predictions right now
it's true you can do foundations in the
in the game if you get predictions right
you get prizes yeah
that the
is absolutely cracked really really yes
oh no no I don't know
because I like the Nikki
I predicted also on a range
oh you did let's go
oh yeah
I should probably cheer for them
go Europe go Europe
let me remind everybody and did the
Pokemon unite category of WCS will
happen tomorrow
and here is a slide of all the
participating team members on the
Pokemon category will be streamed on the
channel listed in the description
tomorrow 9 00 PM November 11th jst
tomorrow and of course you can predict
in the game
get something for it right you don't win
prizes if you guess correctly so please
check it out please watch the stream and
cheer for your favorite team yeah and
we'll see you all tomorrow
everything up I'm really proud of you
guys I think we did really well
considering considering like you know
how much we didn't really know yeah much
in the beginning
yeah that's why yeah
it makes a lot of sense thank you I want
everyone to get MVP though
[Music]
I think I really like because genuinely
we might have got third but they were
close matches they were good matches
yeah exactly it was it was pretty close
[Music]
with Margaret shall we play the ending
PV and I guess we should okay live
streams but
[Music]
let's do three two wait wait wait wait
wait I'm not ready
all right we're good okay
three two one go Pokemon unite recently
celebrated its second anniversary allow
us to introduce them congratulations
oh cool I didn't even try that yet I
wonder if it'll be a just a sweaty
[Laughter]
[Music]
why Mewtwo was this like tiny
plus we're also holding a second
anniversary price machine event
is a great chance to get popular
holaware for Pokemon like Pikachu
stylish
I love the pirate outfit
cute
yeah
[Music]
yeah thanks so much for everything you
guys that was fun
for inviting us for this thank you very
much a lot of fun yeah thank you I'm
really glad I was able to take part in
this and experience this type of game
yeah yeah
I'm glad we were able to train in the
morning yeah yeah it really helped I
think it did rise and grind you know
it was my first first type of this genre
game yes it was fun thank you
I'm so tired
well I believe that's all we have for
today we can let everybody get some rest
we tried our hardest
thank you thank you thank you very much
thank you very much thank you okay
um
[Music]
is have a great day
thank you