[Music]
fore
go
[Music]
it dra
a
[Music]
go
baby
[Music]
[Applause]
fore
here you you are you
[Music]
ready
fore
[Music]
it
na n n n n n n
hey
[Music]
take
for
go
[Music]
baby
fore
[Music]
let go
Baby
[Music]
[Applause]
foree
[Music]
are you ready 3 2 1
go hi hi hi
[Music]
hi
it
[Music]
hi da da
hey okay where do we go uh let's go to
the
[Music]
office
oh
KY wait let me get the
[Music]
chat one more Loop oh I would love to do
one more Loop and another one and
another one and another
one I need to get the like now approved
official instrumental cuz I have an
instrumental probably that's not like
that wasn't the final final
one if I get the final final one then I
could probably use it as background
music for my
stream although I
wonder if then
it will automatically take money from my
ads because it's not my song not really
is it I don't
know not even my own song from the early
myth days was my own song if you know
what I
mean and
chat there you go okay
[Music]
m m
fry fry
party party
exactly hey K
hello um water
water I love misu Mizu Mizu and Mizuki
Mizu and
Mizuki very good things
let's go on audio
stock and find some
bgm oh
Loop what kind of
bgm do we
want what if I type in cuz like if I
type in Zelda and stuff like it brings
me similar music what if I type in Honey
Works
honey oh no
honey I wonder if I don't type in
[Music]
Zelda yeah off brand honey
works okay we have we have some stuff oh
oh har oh kind of loud in my
[Music]
ear I see what is
this oh my
God we're in the
shop
oh but it's very
repetitive oh it's very repetitive
that's so sad cuz that could have been
so
good
uh yeah something like that would be
amazing wait let's let's look for
accordion something with accordion
because damn accordion are nice and
underrated
[Music]
H what is
this whoa whoa whoa
loudo
whoa ah that one I had that
[Music]
before ah tails off let's go
a oh my God that's so tails
[Music]
off
wow
wow wow
[Music]
wow damn this
dude is incredible this this composer
just giving out these songs to audio
stock almost a waste of this dude's
skill I mean there's a lot of different
dudes but
um this dude's
crazy what's
this
oh Bo
boing
oh
wow wowow
Bo W there's so much going on in this
one I kind of love
it but like it's not really suitable
I'll I'll put it in my actually I will
download it someday maybe I need to have
a boing boing sound that gives me also
RPG Vibes maybe that's exactly what I'll
need wait which one was it was it this
one okay boing boing let me name it
immediately immediately I keep on
forgetting to name these
things um boing boing RPG with a flute
okay
[Music]
okay oh that's so
cute hey
[Music]
w
wow that's so
cute
oh
wo
whoa there's so much potential on audio
stock what the
[Music]
hell
nice that's actually pretty
chill
actually that's kind of nice like in my
ears it's really loud right now but if I
played it like pretty quietly then I
think it would be pretty
chill I I guess maybe I'll use this one
for now cuz I I can't decide it does
have an accordion I
think according to audio stock it has an
accordion what is what do I name this it
says officially says like a smooth or
like
lightweight uh accordion wall
uh uh all according to K all according
to
accordion accordion yeah
accordion swing B
meow okay let's put that in my DLC
[Music]
I stayed up so long guys I'm so stupid
and I got up so
late
but oh wait my VLC is not not correctly
routed but I made french toast for the
first time in
ages I went out to buy some fresh
berries there were no good strawberries
very [\h__\h] disappointing even the
premium ones where like they look like
they were sitting there for a couple of
days even though it's Monday I wonder if
they had it like since
Saturday I wonder I wonder cuz Sunday is
never open I wonder if that's like left
over are they out of season well last
time I bought them from the same place
they were fine they they looked fresh
relatively there was only one strawberry
in there that was no
noo strawberries man so hard to get the
good
stuff uh but yeah I got raspberries and
blueberries and blueberries were also I
should have bought a different different
brand but oh well the raspberries were
really good M I made french toast I kind
of was a little bit
too too soft still in the middle I
haven't made it in a long time so I'm
like out of practice with with French
toast why does it why the [\h__\h] would you
refresh that oh my
God please play oh there it is oh you
guys hello oh there it is oh there it is
oh there it
is oh the loop is uncomfortable it's
like a millisecond of
not
connection still tasted good it did it
did I had a lot of cinnamon and like
vanilla sugar in
it you want some french toast right now
can't help you I ate it all I ate it
all yeah I just had it so I won't be
hungry for a while I hope I just had two
slices of French toast with some berries
that's it
basically but that's always a good start
to the day to have like a a really nice
breakfast that you envision in your
head what do you mean you don't know
what French toast
is how can you
not how can you
not it's basically like you you can use
any kind of bread but the best choices
is just like toast bread or like milk
milky white bread um and it's ideal to
make it with bread that has gone a
little bit stale or even bread that you
put into the freezer and what I like to
do because it should be stale uh or like
like a little bit hard you put it into
like what I do if it's frozen I put it
into the toaster so it's unfrozen and
it's like you know crunchy it's perfect
perfect perfect and that in in that form
let's say you don't have stale bread you
can also do that you can use the fresh
bread put it in the toaster then it's
basically so to say
stale and then you uh put it in the
mixture that you made which is like for
one person I just make one egg uh then
add a bit of milk I don't know how much
it is I say a bit but it's like okay a
good amount of
milk then lots of cinnamon like maybe
maybe
one or two a lot how much you want
vanilla
sugar a pinch of salt and there's a lot
of recipes that have like different
amounts so it's like whatever you don't
even have to do cinnamon or vanilla
sugar but if you have it you should put
it in cuz it's makes it
better and then you mix it and then you
pour it for example I just use like uh a
a high plate like a like a soupy plate
and and you pour the mixture in there
and then you put the the toast on in
there or the other way around put the
toast first and then pour the mixture
over it and then it should soak it up
and ideally you uh let it soak in the
fridge for maybe half an hour or so can
be less too if you're not patient enough
M yeah yeah no don't soak fresh toast
spread unless you toasted it you should
toast it first otherwise it's already
like too soft it will soak it up better
if it's like stiff
bread you have to let it sit uh I've
I've seen it recommended in recipes and
I think that's good because it
definitely soaks up more of the mixture
if you let it sit for a
while yeah yeah yeah yeah so I put it in
the fridge for like half an hour while
I'm preparing all my berries washing
them one by one and checking if they
don't have mold on
it yeah takes a lot uh uh enough time
you've been making it up optimally yeah
try again try again with the waa strats
you won't regret
it and then and then you throw it into a
frying pan with lots of
butter and then you just wait and then
you then you flip it to the other side
and then you wait and until the top and
the bottom is both like kind of M
crunchy yeah I think the inside being
still kind of soft is definitely
something you want to go for but the the
outside should be like it should have a
crunch it shouldn't be soft still
M and then I uh eat it with Nutella and
the berries but that's only for
breakfast if I were to eat this as a
dessert throw in some vanilla ice cream
let's let's
go yeah never salt the butter oh I don't
know if mine salted butter is like often
salted uh here I don't know um might be
salted but it's I think it's okay even
if it is I didn't notice any saltiness
even though I had a pinch of salt in the
mixture sugar more sugar if dessert add
more
sugar yeah it's oh I should make a short
out of it maybe I'll just you know make
a cooking short with the actual like
footage of me making the French toast
laa French toast Wawa French toast
yeah we haven't started yet with the
super chats I'm I'm like still still
still getting into my
groove
okay um
oh when I was like why is my microphone
so like
low and now I see chunky wonky cuz she
was lying on the on the roadter on my
sound mixer
she she touched everything and she moved
everything now that I look at it it
looks very different
uh but it's
okay it's okay as long as she's
comfortable n she didn't actually do
much damage not that I can
tell
uh
interesting
um okay what is there to say I want to
say something about chunkers
guys I think chunky
wonky wants me to train her she's trying
to optimize my sound well if only I had
a technician help me with that uh I
think chunky wkey wants me to train her
for the human
toilet I think she wants to learn how to
use a human
toilet she has sent me a
sign no honestly I think she's a
genius so I I think I told it before
they like never have accidents um at
least not unless like maybe they would
have an accident if the the the door to
the toilet to the cat toilet was
actually
closed um
but normally they don't have any
accidents and I told you like when they
were
younger what's with the
skimy when they were younger every now
and then they would have like a a butt
incident where I have to help them clean
their butt a little bit right because it
would get stuck a little bit in their
fluffiness but that hasn't been
happening for a long long time like
really rarely maybe once in half a year
or or one
year yeah don't say gross she'll feel
bad about
it don't say that to a toddler you know
they can't help
themselves yeah so okay no what I want
to say is today I woke up and I went to
an idle meeting and I I open the door to
the idol meeting and I see well the door
to the idol meeting is always open
basically I don't I don't really close
it like properly uh and I see on the
floor of the idol meeting
room uh a cat
poop for like a dry one so you know is a
a cat poop there I'm like H I'm sure
that was chunky wonky because if
anything the the following probably
transp
transpired she went to the cat toilet
she did a poopy whoop it got stuck in
her butt she ran out of the toilet and
went like we zoomed around maybe uh and
then she's like something stuck on my
butt and she's trying to get it off and
for some reason she managed to do it but
in that moment she was in the in the in
the human idle meeting
room out of all the places she could
have left me that present the poopy [\h__\h]
could have been in the kitchen could
have been in the living room could have
been in my bedroom could have been in
front of my computer could have been on
my bed no she chose the most appropriate
place besides the cat toilet room she
chose the human toilet
room to leave that thing poopy
[\h__\h] I think she's so
smart I think she knows that I go there
so she
of course he knows there's like a shelf
right next to the the human seat yeah uh
and even though it always confuses me
she will jump onto the shelf and it has
several levels right she jumps exactly
on that level that is on the level of my
butt you know what I mean on the height
of my butt and then she will just look
at my butt she does that all the time so
she knows she knows she
knows she gets the first row seat I'm so
sorry but she gets the first row seat
first row tickets she wants to see it in
detail man Koba would like to have this
conversation together with me
probably uh
yeah no no we have meetings in there we
just sit down at meetings don't you sit
down for meetings as well like everybody
sits down for
meetings you know that's what meeting
rooms are for seminar rooms and all
that your cat sits with you in the
bathroom too but does she sit like on
the floor watching you or do you also
have a shelf right next so you can give
her the best view ever your
cat she sits on the tub in front of me
aw
having an epic showdown you and your
cat she wants to play the staring
game now I find it amazing she chose the
perfect place I can't even be mad at her
it's it's a
toilet leaving her poopy whoop There is
I couldn't think of any better place
besides her own
toilet
[Music]
no I wouldn't be mad at her like I can
totally imagine it just got stuck in her
fur I normally don't trim her butt fur
but maybe maybe I I should maybe she has
a problem right now
I
I shut up shut up I will read super
chats if I when I want
to I used to trim specif specifically
because of that yeah that's just
smart that's just
smart but she won't let me trim so much
she's like she's so
skiy she's like so what's the word
[Music]
ski uh hi Hipp
Skiby skiddish yeah that's like exactly
what I'm thinking of so my mind wents
SK she's so
skittish my skittish Kitty Scott my
Scottish skittish Kitty imagine if she
was Scottish Fold that was that would be
amazing for this
pun
I don't even know why you guys so mad
what does that even mean SK I don't even
know what that
means it's a funny word I like
it can we pretend that she is a Scottish
fault that is
SK poopy
whoop yeah okay I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry
SK it's just a funny
word meaning someone is evil or bad
what
what why Where What Where what word does
it originate
from okay Can
it can I change the
[Music]
meaning I just wanted it to be a word
that's versatile where you can use it
when you're in a funny
mood what one guy no two people sad two
two people sad it means like
evil
okay whatever guys I'm going to read
super chats by the way we're back in
this office for the first time in a long
time
and it's spring officially now in Wawa
in Wawa's
brain it's spring in in the kfp
world I don't care what you say I don't
care if you say it's winter
still it's spring if I say so
it's ski
spring ski
[Music]
spring so we're not going to I I I wrote
it in the title but I I ideally want to
be a bit more efficient than that I want
to read uh a bit more Super chats than
usual uh I don't think we have that
money that many anyway because uh the as
you know the polar Roy super chats are
not uh meant to be read on this
occasion I say this every time but I
mean it like this is especially because
this is a Super Chat reading stream if I
don't read super chats then what the
hell what is this for what's the purpose
we're doing this
to get some stuff out of the way and to
feel more comfortable in the following
streams yes yes
yes no Yap no
Skiby uh even though I feel incredibly
brain empty right
now I feel so brain
empty I need to clean up this office
here Tanto plaque has to go
higher uh what the
[\h__\h] where is
[Music]
this
oh
oh oh why is this
double why is this
double I have everything double
no
huh okay
okay aha aha aha aha another
double
aha more
papers so much work to do so many
applications why why what happened why
is it so also like
chunkers is not I have a chunkers layer
but chunkers just I probably moved the
moved the
folder smoothie smoothie is also gone
[Music]
smothie
wait can I find where I put
it this is now an office spring cleaning
stream
oh wait for what this says smoothie
window for what window was that supposed
to
be is it like like this
[Music]
that can't
be but I can hide smoothie Behind the
Chair should probably be a bit smaller
like
this and have have smoothie
sleep
cute okay
nice a sweet baby and then
chunky
ah
[Music]
ahuh you know what for chunky wony well
I'm going to bring this out that I
haven't used in a
while
SC cuz it's animated it's so
nice
and video filter no effect filter color
key getting her squid scratch I feel
like because I streamed for so long
these past days like so many eight 9
hour
streams they they
like Mommy where are where are my where
are my
pets cuz then I as sleep like I I really
didn't have time to cuddle of them these
past days it's really terrible
absolutely
terrible terrible days
for waa and her
cattos okay this is nice this is
[Music]
nice maybe I'll take off my
jacket
yeah so that's also a reason why today I
don't want to you know go too crazy too
long
let me get rid of the
papers here so it's more comfortable for
us or is it better with the papers it
doesn't really make sense considering
the where the pillows like she would be
floating shuny wony would be
floating
[Music]
unless
what if I do
this here another one to support the the
chunk another stack of paper to support
the
chunk oh my God what what what's all
this
stuff
there it is that's that's that's support
that's good that makes sense that
supports the Chunk we need good good
stable chunk
[Music]
support cute
okay okay I guess we could read some
super
chats
just checking one last time what is
this aha aha a bigger
plaque the bigger one is nice too
but found another
double found another
double okay the rest I think is
unique ah yeah that's
me that's moving that's that okay okay
okay okay and
[Music]
then we can play the Cinderella again I
don't know this stuff is old I need to
replace
this this doesn't seem to exist
anymore this doesn't seem to exist
anymore
hm
[Music]
okay
text uh wait actually I don't need one
you know we're Super Chat reading I
don't need to write down that with Super
Chat reading but I need a I need a
thumbnail where where are we reading I
think last time I finished one specific
stream
completely
button game I have to read the button
game
[Music]
okay that was so
random that stream was so
Random definitely one of my least
favorite games that I've ever played in
my three and a half years of whole life
just because of
the
immense boringness
and stupidity and lack
of
[Music]
substance
yep I I would say you will put it on the
completion list because
otherwise
otherwise I'm going to be angry mm
H or you just don't count it as all
because at all like not not so don't do
it in a way that it would drag down my
ratio of completed
games
SK I have some NP oh yeah I will check
it out I will check it out but let's
read this one first
this would be a painless stream yeah
unless motion puts it on the
non-completed
games then there will be
[Music]
pain let's go Jacob 47 D Nathan thank
you for the pinky I believe in you T no
silly IP problems can keep you
down I got
[Music]
back yeah
yeah um ISP you little
[\h__\h] it's okay everything has been
finally
resolved kind of unnecessary and
annoying that it happened but it's good
we're hopefully we won't have issues for
a while now yeah and and I get uh a good
compensation
so we're good we're good I'm probably
never going to get that present
though not that I want
wanted because you are my present
Nathan than soon D soon for the red
super chat yesterday 15th was my
birthday and that is the third one since
I joined kfp wow thank you for so much
all this time and let's hope that your
internet problems get resolved soon I
don't know what to write to be honest I
love you I love you too thank
you happy belated
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday dear Dan
happy birthday to
you
dun I say to you dun thank you for being
part of kfp and spending another
birthday with
me thank you so much I hope you had a
lovely day and a lovely Year and I hope
the coming years will treat you well
well and maybe next next birthday we'll
spend together too
[Music]
maybe San Blood
Donor D toilet paper D happy belated
birthday to you too happy birthday to
you happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday on your toilet paper too happy
birthday to
you I hope the toilet
paper was the softest it could have ever
been on your
birthday that's his
name that's his name Bruce D thank you
trash tier
D
Bruce
what oh that discussion
again last Brain Cell
[Music]
Richard C
or
uh
no
and
P ah she already know
Pella
o Korean bro what about
[Music]
K how do I how do I ask I know I dance
with Nika
[Music]
buta
or there's something in between surely
something in between ah
[Music]
ah and then how do I say like
no
[Music]
for
Wow Come on my Korean Bros I can't
believe there's Korean Bros you guys are
really really always hiding in the shads
I thought like man I didn't address you
guys for a while and this is so random
and it's just a Super Chat raing stream
but you're still here what are you doing
here thank you com
[Music]
p p p what I I think I remember what
watch watching
means p
p p p p
p is
watching or so something like
that pomu just got to think of pomu
watch the pomu pomu p
come thank you for
watching my secret Korean
Bros you may think they're not watching
but they
are pomu I don't know about pomu pomu is
probably not watching but I'm
I'm I've got my eyes on her
anyway
H we are always watching
chint
okay Greg
[Music]
D Jimmy Fred prank pruin Jimmy fried
pangu
complicated super chats NZ
D Pyon
than rainard
[Music]
than
if you thought your internet is bad now
it literally takes 5 to 20 minutes for
radio signals to reach Mars from Earth
oh that's pretty
good Pluto is even longer distance away
imagine the lag that's good I mean what
do you expect like a stream like just
for communication it's fine but I'm not
going to
stream I'm not the plan wasn't to go to
Mars and stream if I'm on Mars then I'm
not going to stream
[Music]
so there's no need to worry about the
chat
delay cat Bob than skellum
than sorry guys that's the one place I
won't stream for
you back seating arrives five five years
is
late oh
hung
in
[Music]
k
okay reading exercise done now Translate
[Music]
please
the yawns man oh oh it's a
question did I read it correctly
hung
yeah I think yeah I think I read that
correctly it says Koreans why don't you
watch
Kiana around 25 I will be more to just
wait just wait just you
wait we're always watching yeah I think
I I realized that once again I can't
underestimate my International fans All
Over The
World Scum D good son
dun uh Studio Rob thanks for the red
super chat a studio rob you were one of
the people I wanted to ask I don't know
if you answered me um need to check the
community post Studio Rob are you here T
it breaks my heart that I'm not smart
enough to help my oi with her computer
challenges challenges it seems the aners
missed potential to a it's okay don't
worry I I need to deal with these things
um mostly I can solve the issues more or
less on my own or like I mean the
provider [\h__\h] I needed obviously them to
fix it but like if if you're talking
about like sound stuff and game capture
card and all that I I fixed it I fixed
it so we good we good but yeah if you
could help me that would of course be
wonderful but it's okay as long as I
have your support your sweet
words that's helpful
too thank you Studio Rob for the sweet
words and your r Super Chat Mah and if
you haven't answered about the polar R
cuz I think you sent a big super chat
but I you didn't request any polar
number as long as I'm not done with it
you still have a chance to give me a
number because I'm so nice you know I'm
so nice I give you another chance to
request it
properly you don't have to send another
Super Chat for it though just uh you
already sent enough just tell me the
number
Jackson FB thank you for the red super
chat ha Wawa for your 100 light years
question the fastest ship we have goes
uh 692 th000 kilm per hour and 100 light
years is
about
9.4 607 * 10 then I don't know how to
read that
sign 14 km therefore correct me if I'm
wrong Chad but it should take
about
uh one
367 53 1 180 hours
or
156,000 do 715 years to get
there h
that's longer than I
thought okay so but what are you saying
are you saying we should wait for
them just lay back and
wait we should wait for others to come
to us we should meet
halfway oh good morning unknown it's
okay your excus she excused oh man
arriving in school late after having
like missed a bus or two or like having
overslept or so when they already
started is like so [\h__\h]
[Music]
embarrassing that's why the Generation
ship is an idea yeah but now I thought
even for a Generation ship
years
is I don't think even uh we might have a
war breaking out within the generation
sh within that
time and they will kill each other all
of
them
like multiple Wars possibly Star
Wars like in
156,000 years I don't think these
generation ations can like these several
families I don't think they can get
along for that long something will
happen even if there's no weapons on the
ship but we kind of need to bring
weapons because what if we arrive at
whatever planet and then they are
aggressive and so we have to fight back
and so maybe we kind of need
weapons um but they should be stored in
a way that they can't be accept ible for
war wars inside the
generation but I feel
like there may be many many conflicts in
those
156,000 years so that might be a
problem it's not like Star Wars at all
oh it's coming out as a Netflix series
okay well then remind me when it's out
although I don't really like
um I don't really like science fiction
thank you
[Laughter]
blank it's been a while yeah I'm glad
you're still around I'm glad you you you
didn't ditch
me it's wonderful to see
you have you seen a new Avatar no and I
heard it's terrible and you know I don't
I don't really watch um blue people
unless it's
YouTubers w
what if our plan our new planets are all
infested with dirty aliens we to clear
them out
no oh my God
ah
Nagi thank you for letting me use the Ys
emote it's
perfect we have already been getting a
lot of use out of
it a
lot thank
you everybody call naggie you little
[\h__\h] because I'm sure he or she would
appreciate
it you little
[\h__\h] thank you for the free emote emote
donation let's
go she yeah I thought so but I I I
sometimes you know sometimes the
knowledge in my head is wobbly and I
don't want to risk uh insulting anybody
so I'm not like brave enough to go
there also when I when I ride Polaroids
for the future if you're a lady some
people are already doing it but if
you're a lady you're welcome to ask me
to add lashes to the chicken to make it
more feminine I've been doing that for a
few when they ask for it and then
sometimes I get like pull over
requests from people who I feel like I
feel like I know they're female but then
they're not requesting for Lashes and
I'm in that moment I'm not sure I'm like
wait weren't they female or was it that
other person and I'm I'm like doubting
myself and I don't want to give you
lashes if if you're not so just ask for
it if you want lashes just ask for
it I'll add them onto the
chimpin next time though if you didn't
ask for it this time then
it will be too much bureaucratic chaos
so this time no unless you already asked
for it what if I'm if if you're a guy
you can ask for it too I'm not going to
draw your beard because your beard is
more than just like free little
[Music]
strokes m
lipstick lipstick would probably look
kind of weird so just lashes okay don't
go overboard guys I said lashes are okay
they're not too much work they're easy
to implement for
me no no other crazy requests okay chill
chill chill
chill
[Music]
y to find
Simpkins you guys once I give you
something once I reach out like the the
finger you want the whole
[Music]
arm oh [\h__\h] I can't stop
yawning I could be got
of course you want the whole arm right
cuz you guys don't even have arms or
fingers
so
[Music]
understandable it's hard to type you
chickens you got to use T text to speech
no speech to
text what speech to text I
[Music]
mean mips thank you
aone
oh now I got a nice a nice yawn oh thank
God thank you
Jackson for breaking my brain Bruce soon
soon Richard g
humre t for the red chat jeez you really
know how much you miss someone if you
haven't seen them for a while I have
been just sitting here with a big grin
on my face while seeing your stream
again I'm so glad you're back yet even
if your internet is trying to ruin it
yeah I think they're the
Illuminati that's why they have it out
for me they they're looking for me they
want to destroy me they want to destroy
us because we have grown too
[Music]
powerful take my words record them for
eternity in case one day I'll
disappear yes they have given in this
time they have given into our power this
time but we cannot become too
confident you got to be
careful what is this cable why am I
sitting on it okay and so tasim Mo thank
you I'm back you're back
together together
forever drag ttic Arrow Danon and a
second time thank you as well Danon P
gags dun uh chocolate Andia dun GD d j d
oh here A bunch of people are telling me
what tickets they got for the Expo and
the festival I'm excited you guys got
the tickets and today the honeyworks wa
wa Koop song got released as I played it
in the loading screen you may have heard
it isn't it so
cute it's so cute it it has a very
typical honeyworks sound which I really
like
though actually everybody's songs is out
now are out
now thank you for transcribing my words
onto
stone that will be the only time in my
life where I'm I'm going to get
stoned whoa whoa
w wow I did a straight edge weed
joke
[Music]
yeah the pr tangent is going to take up
a lot of stone I think
yeah but yeah um it's up on YouTube on
like kop it's I have it pinned right now
but make sure to if you have any any
like
um music streaming thingies like Spotify
or YouTube music or apple music make
sure to stream it there too give it a
few
streams you know it's really cute and I
think this song is really really really
easy to understand what you should do in
the live
version at the concert if you're
there
[Music]
and then we go like thank you
D are you ready 3 two 1 go yeah it's so
much fun all the
Su just scream your heart out please
[Music]
do I like all the calls
yeah recording that song was really fun
I don't know if I told you but
um when I recorded it uh me and kachan
recorded
separately um and then I I think I told
you like some of
this uh but yeah
I I I feel like it was so smooth sailing
to record
it honey Works told me that you know I'm
singing it
perfectly and I did really feel like you
know it's a it's a it's the type of song
that I can sing
well
yeah so I didn't have to do much
retaking like I would sing a line like
first you know practice practice and
then we go into the real recording and
uh they click the recording button and I
sing a line and I sing the next line
like we do it in like little parts and
then they're like okay this was actually
already perfect but you know just in
case we got to we got to get a second
one and that was usually about
it
[Music]
yeah and the harmonies were also really
nice maybe you can hear them if you
listen closely
[Music]
yeah it's such a cute song I really I'm
really happy to be part of this cuz I I
was a honeyworks fan for a long time I
really love honeyworks songs and it it's
it's surreal same thing with dickle 27
dickl Nina um being involved in both of
these is really amazing cuz I loved both
of the producers and their songs and and
oh God I didn't think I would be chosen
twice in a row to participate for these
things I got really
lucky probably won't be in next time I I
highly doubt it I mean we can be
positive thinking as much as we want but
I doubt that I would be involved a third
time in a row let's be honest uh it will
be someone else's turn
so yeah really glad though really
happy that I could be involved with such
great
producers yeah
manifesting it's not really about just
being a great singer I think for dickle
and in a way honeyworks 2 they also
looked at who already
covered songs from these
producers um they would get like
extra uh chance to be
considered
[Music]
yeah but for Deco Nina I was uh chosen
to just do a cover and for honeyworks I
got an original song with kuul so now I
was able to experience both I'm very
very happy I mean I may not have gotten
a music
video uh but that's fine my my song is
super cute I'm excited to be on stage
with it with
Kuan k
myi t
[Music]
yeah yeah I I very much wonder who would
be their next producer they want to
collaborate with for like a special
stage if they continue doing it but now
they kind of started it now it's already
the second time it feels like it's it's
becoming a
tradition
I don't think they would consider K
because we all love K but uh I feel like
they would have their eyes on Japanese
producers more before going to someone
like
K yeah I've been saying what have I been
saying I've been saying
mitchi uh
Giga Teddy Lord probably already have
some connections there
through um previous collaborations
M yeah any kind of vocal I producer
really that's a little bit on the bigger
side oh supercell supercell would be
freaking
insane
wa that would be
crazy I don't know if
that
is realistic
though I don't really believe even that
one would be crazy but I don't really
believe in it
TBH o this year I'll be at more than
half of the Hol fests that have happened
so far yeah that's pretty crazy like
when I joined whole life I thought I
joined a place that had already been so
established
and already like I'm it felt like I I
joined pretty late so to say like I'm
late to the party but now looking
back I don't know it doesn't feel like
that that
anymore and you're right like like I I
look at uh some said by celebrating her
fifth year anniversary and I realized
I'm not that far off of that I'm
celebrating my fourth year anniversary
this year
I I don't know for someone like s Senai
I thought like we would be at least 2
years apart but we're only one year
apart huh how is that
[Laughter]
possible or or her fifth year
anniversary it wasn't exactly on that
day was it was it just like delayed
wasn't it was it actually on that day
her
generation uh that W
was yeah was more like 1.5 years that's
still like a tiny Gap I it felt like
there was bigger gaps between us but
yeah thinking back
now my perception changed
and myth is definitely like one of the
big Senai now H kind of
crazy kind of crazy
and yeah we'll forever be the Ian OG
we'll forever be the the group that
created Ian as in like we were the first
we will forever be that part of History
that's so
[Music]
crazy the first
step of becoming International with
allive
a historic group yeah damn
damn
damn crazy Legends we're Legends yeah I
agree wow something to be proud
of and you guys are part of that
Journey isn't that
crazy that's something to be proud of
too I'm so proud of you guys for being
part of my
journey yeah I'm in a really special
position and I'm very aware of
that and I'm really honored to be in
that position so
continuing and wi tun D soon
oh oh that's so sad you maybe you could
you have
switched a d random collusion wao what's
this special oh it's Valentine's Day
thank you for the red super chat with
$214 what does that mean huh welcome
back Kiana I just wanted to express my
appreciation for how much you inspired
me to be stubbornly positive and fight
for happiness really and don't worry too
much about rescheduling the stream every
day we you is Valentine's Day a that's
so sweet
so
Charming well we will celebrate it on a
day that is very similar and very
connected to Valentine's Day we'll do it
on on the on the white
day yes exactly guys I I I
know I know oh you're here yay I'm I'm
I'm actually really glad you say I
inspire you to be like that because I
feel like there's definitely been some
times where cuz I'm such an emotional
person where I spread more negativity
than positivity I can't help it you know
I'm very NE I'm
actually I like
to
portray my
gy happy character better but I'm I'm
I'm pretty negative pretty often really
I'm pretty pessimistic yeah um the
presso is presso
um I'm so sorry I don't want to spread
that to you guys um so I I felt bad when
I
sometimes did do that but I'm happy that
apparently I didn't do that for
[Music]
you oh my God so many comments
help help very Austrian of me
there's nothing wrong with venting yeah
I would agree with that but at the same
time it's like also um ruining my
reputation because like Clips are
clipping those negative
things um maybe also the positive things
but they they clip my vents rant and
Vents and they they get more views and
then the the general perception of Wawa
changed a little bit I think which is UN
fortunate and it's my fault in the end
but um damn
[Laughter]
it
damn everybody has a negative side
that's real helps me realize that even
negative people can hope oh that's a
nice way to look at it
yeah one thing one thing that I do like
to credit myself for is how I am always
able to lift myself back up
again and even though I'm such a
Negative pessimistic person
um in the end I am
always the
drive that brings me to all these
achievements and
goals and yeah so like what would I be
without me
nothing so yeah
I'm strong on my own I'm pretty damn
strong on my
[Music]
own oh wholesome I see we're we're we're
in a wholesome territory right
now thank you
guys ah g hi
thank you guys thank
you thank
[Music]
you you also a pretty negative person
high five
hey that was very inspiring oh Eric you
you can do it too you can be like me
too we we all have I think that strength
in
ourselves it's just like you need to you
need to really just believe in the fact
that you can do it you can overcome all
the hardships and the bad
[Music]
times take that step I know it's [\h__\h]
hard take it take that that step out of
bed take that step outside of your door
into the outside world take that step
and do the thing that you got to do take
it cuz once once you take the first step
your feet will automatically start
walking and then it gets
easier wow philosophical
[Music]
Phoenix
I did that today
too I took a step outside even though I
was lazy as [\h__\h] and I was like I don't
want to go outside and I oh my God I
have so many so many of these days where
I just don't want to get out of bed and
I don't want to go outside just even if
it's just for buying groceries but once
you take the step then then it's easy
and then you make it and then you buy
those things you do those things and
then you're happy that you did it and
then then you're like wasn't so bad I'm
glad I did it and I've gotten a little
bit stronger I gained those EXP points
and I I keep on leveling
up and I get better at handling the
depression that I don't like to talk
about but that is
there
yeah even the simplest things can be so
hard to overcome and I really really
understand that so much man
even getting up and taking a
shower
is the most difficult thing sometimes
it's ridiculous but it
is it's like no I I I don't want to do
anything I don't want to I want to I
want
to you know
just
stay what's the
word that's really stay disgusting and
just don't
exist happens to all of us yeah not
stinky but yeah
[Music]
stinky miserable yeah [\h__\h]
yeah so yeah that's that's me a lot of
the time but I got to give myself credit
and I'm sure you guys could give
yourself credit for that too for every
little thing that you do end up
doing and every time you do accomplish
the
thing you can do it look at me guys look
at
me I've accomplished some crazy [\h__\h]
even before whole life that seemed kind
of
inane to even think of where other
people other people oh I think I I told
you this but when w was really small all
Wawa said waa said uh I think waa said
something like waa wants to move to
Japan wa wants to be Japanese idol and
this and that and I was laughed at I was
like yeah sure
okay uhhuh you're not that's not going
to happen I'm like okay
[Music]
whatever Who's Laughing Now Who's
Laughing Now Wawa will perform in front
of thousands and thousands of people
next
month y y y y y y y kind of crazy kind
of
insane for the third time
yeah no you can also take into
consideration all the all the
online streams where I've performed even
if they're not at a venue those are
still performing in front of lots of
people who want to see me wow we're such
a we're we're spreading positivity today
aren't we holy [\h__\h]
okay damn yeah you can uh include the
Ian concert
too
mhm KF
positivity hi hi hi hi hi no hi hi hi hi
this is um Wawa I just I'm just calling
um to tell you something I I um recently
tested myself and turns out I am K of
positive yeah I just thought you should
know thank you so much for supporting me
bye
I am KF
positive don't be KF negative be KF
positive
wa
[Music]
so is it contagious it is so contagious
if you watch the W
streams just watch the W streams and you
can also be KF positive who
come get your share of K of positivity
today at K of P Wawa what stream yeah
let's go get the waha
fever okay enough of that enough of that
I need to read super chats thank you
random collusion you kind of brought me
on this weird long
tangent but I'm so happy for you yeah
thank you so much
much looking for the top than H than I
am a team
than a
d h I stream uh I sing Japanese songs
quite often but I haven't done a
Japanese only stream in a
while but I do speak Jaan every now and
then I just feel kind of awkward when I
don't see them in the chat but then you
know they show up and there's always you
know a couple of them there even if it's
just one or two I I still want to take
them into consideration so I'm sorry if
I randomly speak some Japanese out of
nowhere but but uh I feel like you know
I want to include them I want them to
feel included even if it's just one or
two
[Music]
this isn't 2020 you can speak Japanese
all you want yeah that's funny because I
got quite a bit of [\h__\h] about that back
in the
day and I feel like nowadays there's a
lot of members who speak a lot of
Japanese and I don't think they're
getting [\h__\h] for it so times have
changed and I I kind of like completely
stopped for the most
part because like I felt like I was
forced
to speak less and then by speaking less
I lost this small Japanese audience I
had more more and more and now they're
like barely there
so you know feel like I lost them kind
of
sad
yeah I don't know why you got hate for
that I don't know either like it wasn't
even that much in the first stream it
was quite a bit in the debut but after
that I I wouldn't say it's like like
that that
[Music]
much
yeah so I don't know I don't know but I
guess it was the argument of like your
whole life English you should speak only
English what happened to Cave positive
it's okay I am cave positive
still I am glad that at least the times
have changed and others don't have to
experience the the [\h__\h] that I
experienced um wow I paved the
way #
positive
yay that happened to waya as well waya
way I want to hug
way you actually inspired me to finally
start learning Japanese even if it's
only dualingo for now did you guys see
my tweet
yesterday dualingo what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] do lingo like whoever
is in charge of the social media I mean
it's always been crazy from what I can
tell but them getting a Brazilian butt
Li that
video you only saw screenshots guys have
you seen the video though like oh my God
it's even worse in the form of a video
dingo is sticking out the Gat for
Twitter and for Tik Tok and for
Instagram he just wants to show of his
booty and make it
wobble Make It Shake and
[Music]
Shake
Megan shake and twerk how about that
Megan shakeing
twerk it's a booty what's wrong with
dingo that green bird
man I'm
insulted where's my Brazilian but left
where's
mine
what kind of it's so funny though cuz I
read the comments and then somebody
asked like what does this have to do
with language study and dualingo replies
nothing absolutely nothing they're so
funny they reply to all these like
comments too and like damn that social
media team is going strong and I think
they're kind of
crazy out of control
the blue bird out of control the uh
green bird out of control the only bird
that is still in control is this orange
bird so ignore all other birds guys
ignore the green ignore the blue come
here to the orange one
kiaha is the only
[Music]
choice with blue I mean Twitter not
narissa
[Music]
oxygen oxygen
do uh M CLA
JB oh thank
you do Moonlight thanks for the red
super
chat G
believe actually I kind of um uh
suggested that to
narissa for her to do it with her in the
lead
role yeah cuz I I talked with her about
akai's Musical and I was like did you
watch it and she's like yeah I watched
it now and then um I told her yo you
should totally also someday do like a
musical thing like Aisa you could do
like the same thing with VN members
mostly you should do it do it I don't
know if you can recreate the Elizabeth
musical but um maybe reference to
[Music]
it well I am the leader of holon so of
course I have the right to say
that mayap thank you for the pinky if by
take you to a shooting range he means
showing off his shotgun collection so
you know what you're messing with if you
try anything funny he needs to do a
shotgun
wedding wait you confused me at the end
there why does he need to do
that but no I don't think so oh I I
would be uh kind of scared if if he has
a shotgun
collection o I wonder if there's a gun
in nissa's
house oh just the thought of that scares
me oh damn I'm so
European night slush Fri scw Julian
V yeah yeah yeah Richard
Dean what the [\h__\h] is that yach rock
music
what what's that rock music on a
[Music]
boat you guys think there's guns in her
house I have to ask
her Jimmy Buffet is yach Rock like the
panina colana song
oh
P colada is yach
Rock in German we say y by the
way Jimmy be is not yach rock oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh a fight is going to
happen oh not in no no no
no but you guys
within yourselves fight out what yach
rock is and then tell me
and uh Rich G Dan sa L
Dan shut up Fano d
mp53 uh garx thank you for the pinky I
simply do not have time to listen to
other albums medieval or otherwise my
car only has one CD player and is
reserved for the classical Masterpiece
album known as point of
view he
exactly I already read that when it came
in on stream I think and that is one of
the best super chats I have ever
read in my time of whole life y yep y
yep yep yep yep pretty pretty
based pretty dope based super
[Music]
lit thank you so much I hope you're
enjoying
vibing two point of view
still mp13 King St Min Stardust
than oh yeah what happened to the
stingray did they how long is the
pregnancy did the did the babies come
out Stingray
pregnan
see 5 days ago 3 days
ago 3 days
[Music]
ago
so it did become pregnant for a rare
form of asexual reproduction known as
parthenogenesis so not for the shark so
it's probably just going to have normal
Stingray babies what do Stingray babies
look like Stingray
babies pregnant stingr updates Charlotte
is not having shark
babies oh my God they look like oal
lopas
oh what's the English word again for OA
loopa oh my
God baby stingrays look like tiny
ravioli stuffed with damned
Souls says Google Axel yeah they look
like
axelos what the
[\h__\h] look holy
[\h__\h] it's cursed and cute at the same
time oh my God why is it so crazy
looking
okay when they grow up a bit more than
this they look really adorable though
holy
[\h__\h] they look like Axel yeah like
weirdly shaped flattened pancake
axles like if you rolled over them with
like a cookie roll
thingy and you can see like something
that looks like feet down there but but
but why does it have feet since when
does a stingray have
feet I'm sure that's not really feet
right but like why does it look like
feet oh my
God look at
this it has
feet
what it's kind of cute now that it's not
so safe for anymore it's getting
cuter oh it's leftover from being a
fetus
[Music]
really oh my God if you guys Google
Stingray baby you'll find some crazy
pictures oh my
God oh my
God
damn damn damn damn
damn
damn what how is this
real how is this
[Music]
real damn I'm
fascinated the ocean is
fascinating sting rings are
cute and dangerous
very dangerous but I'm happy for that uh
place with Charlotte to get new
stingrays because that lady is not
supposed to have babies but I mean who
are we to not
celebrate new Stingray
babies o there's poka dot stingrays
they're so
cute oh cute oh cute sting vtuber
when she said [\h__\h] it I'll do it myself
yeah shark Stingray hybrids would have
been very interesting yeah I would have
liked to see that too but I wonder if we
already had this discussion I think I
don't know if we came to an answer but I
wonder if it would have actually been
like a mix no I think we came to the
conclusion it's either or right it can't
be like a mix
probably would be a stingray coming out
of the stingray not a shark coming out
of the
stingray no I guess like the stingray's
jeans would
be like Superior or something like
that what the [\h__\h] there's a video Beach
GES help Stingray giving birth to
multiple babies and send them all back
to the ocean oh I need to watch
this
[Music]
oh my God can I watch this it's one
minute
long
whoa coming out of right
there what the
[\h__\h]
what oh my
god oh
don't touch
it yeah I I'm just giving you Snippets
of audio holy [\h__\h] but when she started
giving birth n
n oh my God Is it normal for a stinger
to I think it's said here it was it was
caught
by yeah it the stingray was caught on a
fishing
line so that's probably why it's on the
Beach it's like upside
[Music]
down
OBS can you hear me OBS died for a
moment did they send they sent the
babies back into the ocean but did they
send the big mommy also back into the
ocean holy [\h__\h]
so many baby
stingrays oh oh yeah they they did they
did they they just flipped it over like
I flipped my French toast holy
[\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] if you want the link I'll
I'll give it to
you what a
[Music]
[Laughter]
comparison
damn that's crazy
I need to watch more Stingray bfing
videos after this I'm really
curious plop it comes out so easily
too why is my ooshi like
this
damn I'm glad you agreed and it's super
smooth and another one one but they're
cute and it's nature and they got more
stingrays in the ocean Now isn't that
nice it's giving
birth holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] nice uh where was I oh yeah oh yeah
thank you m Stardust for the
update simply D and now now we we're
done with this one
hooray Rejoice
celebration oh oh
oh
ooh
M okay okay okay
okay hey I I I I was faster than you may
think
so and the next
ones the next ones they don't have that
menu super chats either so don't worry
about it don't worry about it I'm going
to just finish all of these and then
then I'm going to check over the
Valentine's
ones we're going to do the first Yakuza
stream
now and this one with that awkward
smile supposed to be flirty though
it wasn't slow it wasn't
slow oh yeah it's supposed to be smug
actually yeah
ja7 the G
Lord
K ghost of
P the ghost who touches grass a a thank
you thank you sh been a long while uh I
last watched your stream what a better
way to be back than we've seeing you
embrace your inner dragons infinite
wealth have a good stream thank you I
actually just talked to Pomo today I
thought you would like to hear
that I talking to pomu deeply
deeply
yeah gasp I think she's doing well
yeah
oh yeah I'm still hoping I'm still
hoping she'll meet up with me
sometime now that she's a ghost you
know I don't know when there would be a
possibility anyway spam thank you for
the red super chat welcome back W I miss
you my cats miss you my cats miss your
cats a we should make our cats
meet I love to hear from your cats you
know and you always have you you I'm so
jealous you and your cats watch my
streams together but my cats don't want
to be with me when I
stream
our cats cycle Circle would be complete
if my cats were here while I was
streaming but at Le they don't like
spending time with me when I stream only
outside of my streams they don't want to
be here when I'm like yapping Yapp
yapping yapping yapping yapping
understandable I
guess to some
extent yeah that's why the Indiana Jones
thing was so weird that smovie joined us
during Indiana Jones I feel like she
thought okay she's like more quiet than
usual because during watch alongs I'm
obviously more quiet than usual but I
still
talk and normally the moment I talk she
leaves the
room but that was a special moment for
me
yeah I wish she would be here like all
the time I wouldn't mind that at all
even if she takes up like the whole desk
space they can be
here oh well oh well thank you
spanheim give your cats some pets and
some scr scratches from
me Jimmy back Funk D Psy D CWS
D Nathan coton thank you for the pinky
trust me tent to every time a girl
agrees to a date guys act like that at
least in the
inside ah you mean like panic
and like each
bun oh I can imagine I mean at least not
maybe not every guy but um
maybe there's some more confident guys
who think they're like the best and the
coolest but they're really not but they
think so and so they
they they don't really get that excited
about
it jumping up and down dancing with
random
people yeah Ian's reaction was pretty
cute um but
yeah calm down ichan calm
down you need to calm down I already
miss him I want to play more you know
yesterday yeah was it yesterday yeah
yesterday yesterday after we were
done I was in a good mood right and I I
went to actually get some some fast food
some
burger a quick burger and then I was
like I was bringing my food back I was
like feeling like damn I could go for
another 8
hours I could I totally could but it
would be so so stupid of me to do to
start a stream at midnight after eating
and streaming for the night another 8
hours that that would be insane
yeah but I
could
yeah so I'm I'm looking forward to
playing more more and more
soon but as I said I don't think it's
happening this weekend I could do a
stream before the weekend but I feel
like you guys might prefer these long
streams to be on the weekend
[Music]
right
maybe one stream not
two I see you guys generally saying
weekend is better and I get
that but chances are that this week
isn't going to be like a six stream days
week worst case not even a five stream
days week maybe
uh uh worst case worst case of four
stream days
week and then if one of on the weekdays
I stream
along uh Yakuza stream you could watch
it on the days when I'm
[Music]
gone yeah I'm just saying four is like
worst case and then I'll do uh if this
is really happening it's still not 100%
set and stone but if this is really
happening then uh we could do a Kad
rebroadcast on one of those non
streaming days which will make it a
streaming day
officially
yeah the most recent one I would
rebroadcast the one where uh that was my
like comeback stream although I think
even the one before I never did a
rebroadcast for did
I
yeah I could do both in like one
[Music]
sitting
maybe yeah I guess the previous one was
the 1.5 million Subs
one
no that's a sixh hour one
oh damn have you thought about looping
them a few times like other members do
no I haven't cuz I don't know who
would uh start and end the stream for
[Music]
me you would say JMA but then she
has to
stream it on her side I think cuz like
she can turn it off on YouTube but who
turns it off on OBS you
know I don't know I I I have to think
about this I still don't
know where uh when I'll go if I'll go so
it's still all uh up in the air
but yeah just know that it's uh I'm I'm
possibly going on a small short
3 to four to 5 day
trip maybe uh this
week at the end of this week probably
[Music]
maybe yeah but it's pretty short pretty
short don't
worry you sound so uncertain cuz I am I
really am like it was already delayed
like two times or so and uh yeah there
still nothing set in stone but it's
supposed to
happen oh it's not with
cie Callie is uh traveling on some other
uh on her own I don't know what she's
doing can you even say what the trip is
for afterwards yeah
afterwards it's
secret okay where was
i t
non thank
you o oh nugget chicken D nuggets Jacob
27 D pepper cat D the gamer cre D oh
that that first stream man there was so
much spaghetti dropping indeed the gamer
bad gohost right Rafa
2385 723 d kjx d Alin thank you for the
red super chat dear Idol I wish you fell
asleep during the live broadcast today
and have a nice day what you wish I fell
asleep during the live
broadcast you mean you you probably mean
you fell asleep during it maybe I'm
sorry if I spelled your name wrong I'm
sorry I'm ah no you
misunderstood that's the
misunderstanding you didn't spell it
wrong someone else spelled it wrong and
you thought it was about you you didn't
even spell my name you didn't even write
my name at all in the Super Chat don't
worry about
it yeah you did it you you made him feel
bad alen it's okay it's okay thank you
so
much for the big big super chat I hope
you're doing well
I hope you're doing super well have a
nice day you
too thank you sh for the support and
then we have valdian with a rainbow I
haven't heard from valdian in a while
cuz valdian has been tanking right
valdian has been riding those
tanks my French
tanker yeah but you're here
yo I'm glad to see see you
again
ban bonjour
Monami you're not here now of course but
I hope tank life is treating you well I
hope you're happy I hope your
successful I hope the tank is
comfortable I hope it's nicely
ventilated not too hot
inside I wish you all the best thanks
for showing your face every once in a
while thank you so
much speed collector dly Dan RS Dan oh
and valian again followed up with a
pinky I didn't realize how much I missed
those
streams what did he say like
how much he can watch my streams didn't
he say like he'll be gone for quite a
while or what was
that or just generally only on week or
what was it I don't remember the exact
details
anymore I guess yeah maybe Mo mostly VOD
gang damn it VOD gang is really
suffering right now I think with the
amount of streams that I've left in
these past few
days
oopsie oopsy
whoopsy
well yeah there were certainly over the
years there were several people who are
like I'm going to the military
bye won't be able to watch his dreams
sorry
like how much are how how much does all
the that take like what two three years
the day when they come back I'll be I'll
be like that girlfriend when her
boyfriend comes from the Army
I'll be like that and I'll I'll I'll
welcome you back in your
uniform oh so
romantic so romantic take your meds
hey I will
not I ran out of them I'm getting a
prescription tomorrow but it's it's just
it's just a lady
pill it's just a lady pill
don't worry just for my skin so I I can
stay poess
forever extra pills no I don't need any
pills I don't need any pills I'm fine
I'm fine I will welcome you back with
open arms when you come back from the
Army I'm fine I'm fine thank
[Music]
you
ah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] why do I need to yawn so
much today [\h__\h] I'm so
sorry when I yawn around your super chat
it doesn't mean your Super Chat is
boring just saying I just lack oxygen
today but I did Stretch stretch I
stretched I I I stretched my body a
little bit like 10 minutes uh with with
a
video cuz my my spine
felt
shitty I need to get a massage again
yeah my last massage I went to uh a
different place
and it like for the first time and it
was a good
massage but it was so
like not personal like I I go in
normally like I mean the service in
Austria is very different from in Japan
okay but the least they
do uh here usually it's like at least
they tell you to like maybe have a seat
for a moment and um they give you for
the time while you're waiting they give
you maybe maybe like some
tea but no tea and I wasn't asked to sit
down for a moment either I was just
like just I was just existing in the
void and then after a moment I I just
sat down on my own cuz I can I'm capable
of doing that that's fine but it's just
noticing like they were treating me kind
of coldly not even water
no I'm like okay whatever I I know how
it works in these places I I take the
slippers I sit down for a moment I just
do it on myself but normally they at
least like tell you to do that and
they're like welcome please wait a
moment and you know but they were like
yeah they didn't give a [\h__\h] I'm like
okay mhm and then they uh finally they
call me and um they just say come
basically so I follow and even that
seemed like kind of like
cold so then she shows me the room and
then she leaves without saying anything
so I'm like uh uh sorry am I supposed to
like strip down like everything until
panties or what do you
want uh so even that I have to like pull
out of her uh and then she confirms and
she leaves and I'm like okay doing the
usual putting my hair up and all that
and I lay down um I have to say that was
one of the most comfortable massage
chairs at least that I've ever uh been
on because the the whole the face face
hole is so
important so many of these face holes
feel like they're really hurting my
forehead or like they're not like big
enough or they're you just weird but
this one was really comfortable
actually
H so I lay down and she comes in and oh
I wish you know in J in Japan they ask
like where does it hurt they ask in so
much detail they often give you an iPad
or so with like um like a like a picture
of a body and it's separated in several
body uh parts and you can like click
aart and then it will turn green for
example and so you click all the parts
and mark them all in color where you
want them to focus on and yeah
so yeah yeah it's it's super detailed
and they they
really make make sure that you get your
point
across and they make you fill out a form
of like I mean that the form is maybe
more more common in other places too um
like you know fill out on the scale of 1
to 10 how much pain do you have where do
you have it BL blah blue what's it from
what do you want what do you want to
focus on do you want to get the massage
for stress or for uh muscle relief BL
blah blue or headache or sleeping
problems Etc you know so I always feel
like really well taken care of in Japan
cuz their customer service is so
good and then yeah so they didn't give
me a form they didn't give me anything
like that they didn't ask me so I saved
myself she when she walks in and I'm
like already naked on the table I'm like
um uh so my my shoulders here and my
neck here please uh that's that's where
it's the most painful but they already
seem like so uninterested so like I
don't feel like I can really tell it in
detail and show it in detail so I'm I
just try to do it roughly and see what
happens and I and she starts and like
it's two weeks so I say after a while
cuz I I don't want to say it right away
cuz sometimes they just start weak and
they get stronger and they get annoyed
when you tell them cuz they were going
to they were going to go stronger anyway
even without you telling them you know
what I mean so I don't want to it's just
like test the waters I wait a little bit
and then I'm like okay she's probably
not getting stronger so I tell her
please please a little stronger would be
okay too and then she's like
stronger
okay uh and she she didn't really seem
like she wanted to go stronger but her
technique was really good so if it only
was stronger then oh it would be amazing
the technique was really good but then
she does get a little bit more strong
and I'm like okay I feel like especially
in certain areas she could go even
stronger but the problem is when they
don't want to like talk so much in
detail in Japan I feel like I could do
it but when I here in Austria I feel
like they don't want to be told too much
and they're get annoy it and I I I need
so much courage already to speak up
anyway so I can't be like okay here
stronger and then here weaker and then
here stronger and then here weaker cuz
my my the parts of my body are very
differently sensitivity very different
sensitivity okay yeah and there's a part
in my spine
that I've always wondered there's one
small
part really small part in my spine
around the
middle that hurts to the touch always
for
years it's in the middle of my spine a
really small spot do you guys have that
too so generally the whole spine I love
it when they give a strong massage but
then they reach that point and it hurts
so bad but I when I say weaker then they
do everything weaker so I can't really
say it so usually I just like suffer
through
[Music]
it pressure point pinch n yeah I don't
know but that that thing I also have for
years and I wonder if it's like got
anything to do with the
rest herniated
disc herniated this who knows dis pain
yeah probably it's like one very
specific
spot always hurts during
massages but yeah so generally her
technique was amazing everything was uh
pretty good she could have been stronger
in some parts but then then she was too
strong and I was like suffering through
it
hurts at one point I did say oh God weer
please on my buttt cuz
oh why do why
do why do people always massage my butt
so strongly I don't get
it one thing I also don't like is head
massages and she would massage my head
at the end and normally I even say
please don't massage my head but she uh
I forgot to say it and she already got
started and I'm like okay let's let's
just let it happen see how it is this
time but her head massage she was like
scratching my head really
aggressively
like the
first scratch the second scratch was
okay but then she like scratched the
same spot really fast and um like a big
area of
it like for the sixth seventh time and
I'm like damn this starting to hurt a
lot why I hate head
massages now once again it's been proven
to me that I don't like head massages it
when the when the hair hair is wet I
like it a bit more but when it's when
the hair is dry I in my whole head I
feel the squ scrotch and it's giving me
shivers it's like that that sanding
paper to
me
[Music]
yeah yeah anyway and then the massage
was done and it ended so suddenly
normally I have had like 300 massages in
my life I swear they have like finishing
moves like in a like in a battle they
have finishing moves normally where when
you're usually just lying down during
the massage at the end they make you sit
up and then they do a few more sometimes
if it's a tie massage they do a few
stretches while you're sitting uh on the
massage chair um or if it's not a Time
massage whatever they still might like
um um do a little bit of squeezing here
and there yeah yeah they do that oh my
god with with Tha massages the end
stretch is always so awkward to me cuz
in Japan they usually don't do it naked
but in Austria they do thae massage is
like you know I mean the massager is not
naked but I'm naked and so they make me
like I sit up cuz they tell me to sit up
and I know what's happening already so I
try to kind of like cover myself with
the towel but then they like make me put
my arms cross them uh behind my head and
then they pull me all the way
back and my my towel drops and I'm like
okay don't be don't be
self-conscious they they're not they
behind me they don't look at my boobs
not okay she's not looking she's
probably seen a lot of people naked
anyway I don't worry so much about her
but it makes me so nervous cuz it
happens all the time then she pulls me
all the way back and she does the
craziest moves to stret stretch
me and I try to adjust my towel but I it
keeps on falling down and I don't want
to seem like too self-conscious about it
either yeah um
yeah it's always quite funny with Time
Massages but yeah this this lady she
just leaves the room she's like okay
we're done she leaves the room and I'm
like this is so weird like it was
actually pretty good massage but like I
feel very unwelcome here
yeah then when I went to pay like there
was basically no conversation either and
I asked I asked Joe if they have a a a
stamp card cuz I might come back and uh
that alone should make them think oh
okay she's interested to coming back
let's be nice to her but no she did give
me a stamp card but then it was done she
gave me the stamp card and I said
goodbye and they didn't say goodbye they
they seemed better
very very much like
they're they don't want
to be
nice but generally generally overall in
Austria it's always kind of like that
but this was one of the worst ones in
terms of customer service but the
massage was
good
yeah the massage was good so I I do want
to come back I want to give them another
chance
yeah complicated feelings
yeah but that's why I enjoy massages in
Japan or even like in the Maldives of
course in like Resorts expensive Resorts
like that they also care they show that
they care and they uh give you like uh
like a paper to fill out in more detail
what you what you need what you
want 20 of Super Chat thank
you
yeah that was my massage tangent sorry
very sudden I don't know what why I got
there well thank you Roman there uh I
have some places that I like it's okay
it's okay at least uh uh I get some of
the pain out of my body a little
bit yeah I wish they would adapt the
customer service a little bit
from other cultures
but you've never gotten a
massage yo I think I told you or someone
else before like once you get started
you can't stop getting massages you
you'll get like this urge to get more
your body wants more
so
yeah what do you mean to take it over
the fish bth the fish bth was
interesting it's it's miracles of nature
yo we have to appreciate
that I only had one and I don't think
they did any finishing
[Music]
moves the especially Time Massages have
really noticeable finishing moves let me
just say that other massages may not
have anything that you see much as a
finish move
although
yeah I've experienced it it often also
they have fin starting moves as
well yeah yeah yeah I I know it all I've
done it all been there done
that yeah starting moves starting moves
it's the
thing what no
of course I've never experienced a happy
ending I I really wonder if that's not
just a
myth I don't think I don't think there's
actually places like that in
Austria I don't think
[Music]
so I don't think it's a m well then I
hope I never accidentally stumble into
one of these because like I hope they
make it clear that
they're that kind of
establishment wait if if they offer
Happy Endings do they also ever do like
normal
massages like could it happen that I go
there for normal massages and meanwhile
at the same time there's other people
who get more than just a
massage do they do
both oh God I don't want to go to a
place that does does both makes me feel
very uncomfortable just thinking about
that I don't want someone in the room
next to
me no no no no no no I I I would like to
have a guarantee that they are say so
massage
please oh God that's just a myth okay
it's just a
myth that is just a myth I don't believe
it
goodbye so much Danish and Mund Danish
we're done with
these but that is just a theory a
massage
Theory okay cursed topics next one is um
the one where I changed the thumbnail to
this I've updated the thumbnails to be
fitting to what
happened on the Stream except for the
first
one shut up Michael
don't
no massage
[Music]
FY
jacob7
Lord uhhuh uhhuh
mhm gaming than thank you oh my headache
is gone finally completely
y happy
birthday Jim
[Music]
try spank Anheim dun py dun J Monkey D
crash ss1 D Mexico thank you
guys thank
you thank you naan thank you for the
pinky hi atten you hooping in my in
hopping in hopping in on my break to say
hello and wish ichan a good trip to
Hawaii yeah so jealous why does ichan
get to go to
Hawaii
thank you doll and I'm sure ichan is
happy to be supported by you too you're
so nice you share your love even with
Ichiban he deserves it though he's a
Chad he's a good
[Music]
man all I got was a trip to the
moldes nah I'm I'm fine I'm fine I don't
need a trip to Hawaii
no
no no not at all not I don't I'm not
curious at
all no but it's really kind of
glamorized in Yakuza with like the the
beautiful and pretty empty
Beach I'm sure IRL it's not that
nice right so I don't have to feel bad
about not
going
yeah well you you guys you guys said uh
there may be gangs IRL too so that's
that's also concerning I don't think
there's gangs in the
males at least not on the islands of the
resorts so I guess I'll choose moldes
over hermit crab gang hermit crab gangs
yeah those may exist they did gang up on
that one hermit crap that was
terrifying haai page says I mean that's
kind of biased but they say is they're
the third safest state in the
country third
safest I guess measured by how much
crime there
is well of course there's less crime if
there's gangs who like make you don't
report
it especially if the police is corrupt
just like in the
game I don't want to claim that let's
hope that that's not
true third
safest you have free arms no I do not no
I do not what are you talking
about
what are you talking
[Music]
about I love love chunky
wonky I love
[Music]
her it kind of almost looks more like
realistic like this doesn't
it
sniffing the
[Music]
cat
I love
[Music]
her oh
you did that to your cat today when you
got home nice I hope you do her you I
hope you do it to her every day as she
deserves
it just cat love Yum Yum
Yum he okay I hope you do it to him
every day he deserves it ah
than Massachusetts Massachusetts
Massachusetts
easy
thomasy not a good
username the silver tongue
slacker oh D this song made me so
emotional when emotional when I first
saw it Sander's three and a half now and
he's so big we listen to the Yakuza Koka
songs
together whoo whoo whoo that's a
comeback you guys still watching Noah
sometimes oh my God Xander is free and a
half now guys he's growing with
kfp
I hope you guys got that merchandise of
the chicken because the chicken
hat of the chicken employee plushy could
fit pretty well on your 3 and 1 half Yee
old
child you could maybe even take off the
the jacket from the chicken plushy and
see if it fits
Xander that would be amazing
[Music]
that would be amazing I want to see
that the the jacket is probably like uh
attached in some places but you can open
the stitches in theory probably I would
assume
yeah starting them early well we started
when Xander
was like three months old or so
[Music]
what if you bring it to a so so
stress or so maybe they can open the
stitches and take it off
properly without damaging seam stress
that's
it
the seam stress kind of seems stressed
today man maybe I should look for a
different one to give that job
to
wo
whoa probably not the first time this
joke has been made honestly I could see
a seamstress making that joke on her
own seamstress be like I I I seem so
stressed
today but I'm funny at least so I got
that going for
me
BS okay I will change the bgm
now it's beenin enough
enough no more of
that
AKA
[Music]
no
amazing one of the songs of all
[Music]
time
o
yo
[Music]
nice I saved it as Cafe
Jazz let's go
chill randomly clicked on one track and
it was already amazing don't even have
to go looking
much all right uh what was I ah Lord D
East Coast Overlord D squid coyote D Jim
Tracy D doomday Dan D L moonight thanks
for red Super Chat Hello Ki my beloved
finally got home now now it's time to
enjoy somea good you're amazing he looks
like a cool 40-year-old midlife
crisis yeah he doesn't look like four
years 40 years old though he's kind of
so so fresh
looking I'm
jealous I'm so
jealous thank you D for the Super Chat
thank
soon
now
uh
um thank you for the
[Music]
pinky
warhound second
pinky spiked B cute right it's a very
cute until I hit you with
it so be careful be care careful
around thank you for the
support I see I see hope you were able
to catch up uh ronal clips
than Shiva thank you for the pinky um
boss did I hear that correctly did you
wrongfully call me aunder yesterday
that's outrageous you may be my call
call me Yoshi
what you but the one I truly love is
Tanaka kishara and her glorious chat of
course
[Music]
H
Ohi call me Yosi call me that's that's a
almost
unrecognizable
[Music]
N I do like Yoshi
though but me made me think of Yoshi
Yoshi Yoshi is my Oshi Yoshi is my Super
Smash Bros Oshi I never play Yoshi but I
love him I love him I don't play him cuz
I'm not worthy of Yoshi's
greatness
Yos yeah tanaki sakaria is uh my
preferred
alternative it's like tanakak caria is
like the the gluten-free alternative or
the the vegan alternative to takanashi
kiar that's what she is in case you were
confused about
that organic Wawa
yeah off PR
W it's all that she's lactose free she's
glutenfree she's vegan she's offbrand
she's
organic just all of
that so powerful actually gotta be
[Music]
careful yeah her being yellow kind of
ruins it
all if only she was orange that would
change things that would be a game
changer Maple Le thanks for the pinky
management as for song requests for the
application how many hell project songs
do you want Ki KI yes that is basically
what I said
yeah yeah I see I see where this is
coming from I can remember the
conversation
yeah you get it you understand you know
how it is and they said no exactly
spanking thanks to the pinky as well cat
hair is delicious oh it
is here is the
proof the proof is in the
[Music]
chunkers cat hair yummy JP D thank you
so
much SP thanks the pinky I call my cats
of hey
dude I thought it was Sten B and Harden
B what the [\h__\h] spanking I'm you're
misleading me all this
time but hey dude probably works quite
well
too it shows the bond that you have with
your cats yeah hey dude they probably
call you the same thing but it doesn't
come out the same way
[Music]
German always works
yeah
thank yeah I think we talked about that
too RS than Yoshi Senai D ah than for
the pinky thank you so much no words
with it had nothing to share I see just
wanted to give some support I appreciate
it thank you so much and spy meow meow
to you too meow
meow that was the first aaza
[Music]
Dream very productive you didn't think I
would be this efficient did you huh huh
huh yeah underestimated my
power oh wait that's the wrong one next
is next is uh this
glorious
[Music]
thumbnail grind blue Yap
toy
yeah gold fum thank you thank you I
tried my best
here graphic design is my
passion yeah I saw Zeta is isn't she
streaming right now or maybe she ended
already but I saw it in in Hyer that
she's up to some grind blue Yap to see I
hope the yapping
isn't harming her hope it's
okay hope she's doing
well yeah yeah she's on it k k
ma a thanks for the pinky very excited
to see this one Tel don't worry you
really don't need to know much on the
mobile game it's completely separate oh
and the grand blue fighting game would
also be great for collabs they even
added 2B to the game yesterday
oh Grand blue fighting game I I've seen
several of you guys like mention it
I'm not really
interested not uh at the moment
Grand blue fantasy versus
Des yeah I don't really care for it
right
now yeah I'm a Tekken player excuse me
no I will not say that for
certain I'm not particular any like I
okay yeah I used to play Tekken
on the on the
arcade when I was a
baby but I didn't know what I was doing
and it's not my favorite game genre
[Music]
now yeah Super Smash Bros is pretty much
my limit and even with that I'm really
really bad at Super Smash Brothers
so but it's cool that Tob is in it now
Tob is like
everywhere Tob
[Music]
Tob what if we pay you to play it how
you going to do that with super chats
but then you send super chats and what
if I don't want to but then you send all
these super chats trying to pay for it
and then I feel pressed to do it but no
please don't do it because I don't
really want to if I'll play up I'll play
it out of my own
will Tob is just iconic she
is yes to
be junky chunk thanks for the red super
chat T you the game is fun hope you like
it and able to have fun in the future
cab thank you I hope that will
happen I hope that will actually
happen wait so I'm finished but I didn't
do the epilog and Ena finished and is
doing the epilog what about
beu God there's so much I need to clean
my my my desk mat it's like there's
honey I don't know how it got
[Music]
there oh it can be done with a within
Co-op well
[Music]
yeah
uh oh she finished it but she didn't do
the
[Music]
epilog basically or finish did she
finish the epilog
[Music]
too if anybody knows let me
know
but at least TAA is also still behind I
caught up yo I caught up so hard thank
you chunky chunk
RBC
come thank you for the pinky February
21st is my birthday dear Tel I'd love to
say this all seems difficult to study
and get over the hard time but I'm sure
we'll be brilliant like a star so long
as we go straight forward I'm rooting
for you forever TR H what is this about
the studying thing is that about Korean
or just randomly thank you all for the
nice words for supporting me
[Music]
RBC
yeah we will we will go forward straight
forward sometimes to the left sometimes
to the right but usually
straightforward sometimes in the
squiggly
line but yeah
Galo
fighting and happy belated birthday to
you too
s
IBC
congratulations I am so happy that you
felt like you wanted to share your
birthday with me I appreciate it I feel
honored pople maybe discounted pople do
you want
[Music]
one purp for a pinky that is
scandalous discounted birthday
[Music]
to it's Mony D do Moonlight thanks for
the red super chat D the fact that you
reference my favorite moment ever in The
Simpsons and as an Argentinian I should
wait the the the spider pink I should
add the s are practically a core part of
our culture at this point really makes
me extremely happy enjoy the stream I'll
be sure to catch B okay so this doesn't
have anything to do with the Simpsons I
guess but I would say it's relatively
close so I can tell you this the past
two days I've been falling asleep to
Family Guy I don't know I was like I
need something to fall asleep to and
like I don't know I don't feel any of
these other things that I've been
falling asleep to right now um so I just
turned on Family Guy I still haven't
seen like the most latest season I think
but it was the first time in a while
that I watched Family Guy and I was like
holy
[\h__\h] this show and its jokes oh my God
it's quite
something it's quite
[Music]
something it's
wild it's so wild and I I had to Google
because I was at an episode where they
kind of
even though they're owned now I guess at
the point when that season and the
episode came out they weren't owned by
Disney but they they they
really portrayed Disney for one joke
they portrayed Disney in a pretty
terrible light and then I was like oh my
God I wonder if Disney suit them over
this but apparently they didn't and then
they even decided to buy a Family Guy
maybe they decided to buy Family Guy to
make them shut up and never say anything
bad about them ever
again wait they're owned by Disney
yep they are cuz they're on Disney plus
now you know they've been I don't know
when but they've been
bought they make fun of like
everything but um they've apparently
they' ah yeah Disney but fox fox owns
Family Guy yeah so
but uh apparently Family Guy only has
been sued three times over the years
three times and I think all of the
lawsuits failed
anyway I don't think Family Guy ever had
to do
[Music]
anything it's crazy though like some of
the jokes are really [\h__\h] up um but um
yeah generally
it's
generally I have to just like close an
eye on a lot of the jokes but generally
I think it's
[Music]
funny because I like the dog
and I like
Stewie
yeah yeah I like Brian
Brian I just like the the the connection
between Brian and Stewie a
lot yeah a lot of the travels they go on
together through time and space are
pretty funny mhm they're iconic
yeah
spinoff oh I did try uh The Cleveland
Show mhm cuz like at the point where I
was done with all the seasons with
Family Guy I was like okay what now and
then I saw they had a
spin-off uh yeah I watched a little bit
of that I
think can I do a L's accent L's accent
or L's
voice uh what
loise
[Music]
wait a
second what the [\h__\h] whoa whoa what the
[\h__\h]
just ruined my whole
sound
ah I can't hear it trying to hear
L can't hear
it trying to get into character
yo P it's probably something like that p
no
uh what's going on in this video I
always I don't hear the I don't hear the
voice see everything's so [\h__\h] up even
without my capture card everything's
[\h__\h] up ever since I got that stupid
roadcast Duo I don't like it I don't
like it at all I want to go back to my
gar really
nasy PE p oh that does sound like
her p
p
no what's what's a famous thing she
would say besides Peta obviously like a
sentence like maybe Peter
don't um pet Peter stop
um
pea I'm warning you
okay Peta Brian is dead Peta the horse
is here oh I don't know how she says
that one but I'll
try wait the horse which horse is it the
is it the brain dead horse that that's
actually the the episode I just watched
last night the one with the horse that
he bought is that that really really
that one is that what your reference I
just out of all the episodes that's the
one I watched
[Music]
yesterday what context did she ask the
horses here to ah H when they're in the
car and it's like behind the
car paa the horse is here now only the
Pea sounds good I have to listen to
that oh I the dining that was in the
dining room h you guys all know that
episode P the horses oh it comes
up
oh the hor is
[Laughter]
here I already forgot it was so
so so omnus omous om
I know you can hear it as much from my
phone
Peter Peter P Peta the horse is
here
Peta the horse is
[Laughter]
here
Peter the
[\h__\h] pean wait my nose is getting used
to it it's starting more and more normal
Peter Peter the horse is here Peter why
the [\h__\h] did you buy a horse my
nose I became toad it's a fine line
between L and
Toad but yeah I could try I could
actually um practice that uh that mon
that that impersonation and make it my
secret
skill Peta the horse is
here Peter Peter Peter the horse is here
I just realized
recently L's voice actor is Alex Bor
Borstein
borin
and after actually it took me quite a
while to make this
realization quite a
while uh
after I
watched
um you know yeah the Marvel is Mrs masel
where she's not just a voice she acts
and she's one of the main
roles and I really liked her in that
role she was so good and then after
watching a long time later I I randomly
watched Family Guy again and I'm like
wait a second
the L's voice and then it clicked in my
brain and I realized holy [\h__\h] isn't
this the same voice like just like more
dramatic like she doesn't exactly talk
like that in the Marvel Mrs Mas but it's
very you you didn't finally notice oh
wait is this the same person yeah she's
amazing in
marvelous Mar The Marvelous Mrs
M
yeah but she's an amazing actress
yo yeah she doesn't yeah she doesn't
sound quite as whiny and nasally yeah
that's obviously like her character
voice
amazing you can also do the nanny
impression The
Nanny I don't remember what voice she
has
[Music]
that's all I can give you the
song okay bring back the
music oh Mr
Shield yeah I used to watch it every now
and then when I was younger but I didn't
like it when I was was
younger it was already too old for me
when I was younger I was like this is so
old this is I don't understand this this
is like too old I'm I'm a Zoomer I was a
Zoomer at the time you
know dude Jan is from
friends chantler you're so funny
[Music]
Chandler
I love her I love her
Janice you like that
[Laughter]
[Music]
one she's amazing she's so
[Laughter]
amazing do it again
no wait now it's not so good what
happened what happened the second time
is always
worse tler marry me tler I don't know
now it got
worse there's like a little bit of like
uh
huskiness mixed with the
nasly uh
pitched M
screeching m
no don't go okay okay okay I need to
read some
CHS gobble gobble jaob
47 for the pinky W my armor finally fits
oo over three years you filled my days
with joy and
love it's been a great honor to be on
this adventure with you and I'll still
stick with you till the end before I get
my myself lost may I get an employee
number oh my God how do you not have an
employee number
yet
how how is this possible how did you
just slip through the system until
[Music]
now what do you mean unforgivable curse
what found a way to beat the system
hey
[Music]
yo oh Harry Potter thing oh man I
haven't seen Harry Potter in a long time
long long
time so I didn't get the reference sorry
H okay your number so this n i could
coincidentally give you the date of
[Music]
today I could or I could give you
something like the numbers and the Super
Chat value that you
send
or I could give you
coincidentally the time that I'm being
shown by Hyer when you sent the super
chat
or since you're the ninth Super Chat in
that stream could be something like that
[Music]
too of course all that would would be a
coincidence because actually
your your your employee number is
[Music]
8113 what do you think that
is what do you think that
is hm you won't guess it you will never
guess
it
[Laughter]
[Music]
why no no no what could be you have no
idea do you guys you have no
[Music]
idea that's a number to your
luggage oh write that down
guys
it's it was the kbps that I had in the
moment
on
[Music]
OBS and those change like every second
so it's like a number generator for your
employee
numbers I saw UF mod also doesn't have a
number if you want one I give you
[Music]
8447 you're welcome yeah the gamer Creed
than you
oh
wow yeah
wow pric slime here with a pinky thank
you and later you followed up with an
insane
$400 I never found a prismatic slime is
that like in the
epilogue but thank you so much for the
support you're kind of crazy I wonder if
you're like someone else and you changed
your name or if this is always your name
and you were like waiting for this
moment that we would stream this because
I saw you also send a super chat on
ena's
stream in the same manner so I wonder if
this is just your destiny and you have F
fulfilled it yeah H I'm really curious
feel free to share your life story with
me and if this is really you know you or
if or
if there's something behind the slime
and you just felt like this was your
calling who knows but thank you so much
Prismatic slime I don't know if you'll
hear this cuz I'm not playing grand blue
and maybe you were the just there
because of grand blue fantasy you know
but thank you
m Ricky DOA thanks for the
pinky as well this one's also with no
words what what's wrong
you guys don't want to talk to me when
you deliver your salary what's
happening did I scare you off with the
Janice
laugh my
nose I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm so I'm sorry I'm I'm sorry
Chandler please marry
[Music]
me
what what's your problem with Janice
guys you guys are so mean to Janice
that's a
goat and
goat okay I'm out no no
hey stop please
stay I'm just happy I found a new Talent
please let me enjoy the moment let me
celebrate the moment
[Music]
Janice is so Charming
guys why are you so hateful towards
[Music]
Janice capture the moment if you
will
okay
[Music]
oh you want a number what's that panking
number four then eh what's that what's
that
[Music]
number employee number from somewhere
else huh
[Music]
huh what's that
about
I'll give you a number I'll give you a
number and it's hopefully your only
one how about
celebrate the birth of another kfp
number write it down write it
[Music]
down another employee
number nice really well organized relx
like to see
it game
[Music]
tud thank you for the
red thank you always so so so so so
generous thank you so much I hope you
enjoyed the stream and had a good time
while I was
grinding
Wiki Tunes D thank you gold break D take
47 D Prismatic slime already said and
kissed you said my thank you to you but
once again thank you H music thanks for
Pinky glad to see you back y I'm going
to H of Fest again this year I got some
tickets Expo in stage one this time also
going to meet some more kfp employes I'm
staying for 10 days and I'm really
excited and looking forward to the trip
ooh let me take a fro
candy I'm happy to hear that yeah I'm
excited so many of you actually ended up
getting some
tickets and even if you didn't guys you
can still watch it online when it's
happening and it will be just as great I
I'm really curious about the um camera
work work cam work this
year really really
excited hope it will be
[Music]
good do you guys know
yet what do you guys know what do you
guys
know what do you
[Music]
know
uhhuh John Snow nice
reference yeah I don't
know I don't know you don't know I don't
know we don't know I don't I I don't
know we will know one day we will
know eventually we'll
know one day we just have to know when
we know we know then then we know that
we
know okay good good good talk yeah cool
cool thank you
[Music]
nice but yeah I will be uh in the honey
Works thing obviously and on stage
one day one first one the first one the
very first so I am nervous uh but hyped
very hyped uh it's getting closer holy
[\h__\h] every day it's getting
closer but also I'm excited to see the
girls
again the
girls the
[Music]
girls I'm on the same day with goba too
so I think I'll stick to goba
mostly
cuz behind the scenes I mean cuz
otherwise she may be feeling
lonely or stressed or scared I'll be by
her side
go
L yeah I'm excited to see her again U
but thank you thank you H music and yeah
go bring some light sticks in Orange of
course and I hope you have a great time
there I think it will be once in a
lifetime
experience waya too okay I I'll hold
Way's hand too
my blue
women and
bond
e thank you than thank you so much for
your support and I I hope you feel
better I don't really know what that is
the aplastic anemia it sounds like um
like blood something with blood
[Music]
right I hope you will have a good
recovery yes fighting
take it easy take it in your own
[Music]
pace un need to chat thanks for the
pinky I think some from some things he
said it sounded promising But he sounded
very reluctant like to like fully commit
to your case wait what is this about
maybe he will need results ah the doctor
thing to like actually get it sort of
but yeah they was just too much know at
once for it to feel satisfactory exactly
and also I don't know about the results
I already brought uh like certain
results like the blood tests and the
um the X-ray thingy that I did already
tried to bring as many informations as I
could but it's okay let's not talk about
that topic anymore thank you for raring
though I appreciate your concern and
your your sweet kindness
than uh golden Michael
H TI as Milan danash J JF Dan and JF a
second time
danash oh you were the guy from
Katon thank you I'm so like I'm actually
like really fascinated and and happily
shocked that you guys wear the
merchandise at events like this even
when I am not there like as a performer
or
whatever
so sweet you guys are you guys know you
guys know where you belong to and that
you have to represent
kfp
yeah I really love the dedication you
have the orange must be
spread Orange has to be visible at all
times it's the only chance to wear it I
wouldn't say the only one but it's
certainly a good opportunity to wear
yeah yeah yeah and then you can easily
find other people even if they're not
wearing orange they might see you
wearing the the kfb merch or whatever
and they they can be like hey oh my God
I I actually really love H live and kada
too let's go and then you can become
friends and the power of friendship will
save the
world yeah yeah that's how it works
so thank you though for really for
wearing the merch makes me happy to see
it really
tasim very squishy thank you for the
pinky go buy yourself some cake oh
really may I maybe I will maybe I
will no I think today I already had
french toast that's enough sweet
happiness for me for for
now not saying that I will not consume
some chocolate
later
but a cake is probably too much maybe
tomorrow oh maybe I'll maybe I'll have
cake for breakfast no I still have
berries I think I'll make French toast
again tomorrow I have one more egg I
still got milk I think I have all the
ingredients to make another French toast
tomorrow
[Music]
M yeah and even though that was the
first French to in a while and I said it
wasn't the best one I ever made it was
still miles better than that French
toast I had in that restaurant holy [\h__\h]
that was the worst French toast I've
ever had can barely call it a french
toast what they made what they put
[Music]
together yeah I don't know what's the
best French ju I ever made made it
several times in my life now I just
taught myself I think how to make it um
while I was in Japan cuz I had this tiny
tiny tiny
kitchen and not many cooking skills not
much cooking experience and I just Tred
to make simple
things yeah then I found out how easy it
is to make French toast
[Music]
wow oh yeah I think sweets like desserts
in Japan are usually bomb the one thing
I've noticed is like you know the the
the big fluffy pancake thing was
trending like everybody every restaurant
was suddenly making big big big big sule
fluffy
pancakes and I've heard some people
tried it and thought it was like not so
good it looks amazing but it doesn't
taste so good uh maybe it depends on the
place though because I had something
like that in in
Asaka and I thought it was really good
though I
mean normal pancakes may be
better but mine the ones I had weren't
too
bad are they custody I don't know I feel
like uh the the the criticism
[Music]
was I don't know what was the criticism
to Airy M too eggy I don't
know but people at least like from the
tourists and so on that I heard they
didn't like it so
much but I think Japan makes a lot of
things look very very very tasty and
generally they also do taste really good
but some things some things are really
just like
superficial
Aesthetics that's the goal to make
things
[Music]
instagrammable style over
substance but honestly that's that's not
quite fair to Japan generally I will say
99 out of 100
cases food in Japan is
amazing
[Music]
amazing it's really not fair to say that
that's a a common
thing you eat with your eyes too oh hell
yeah hell yeah I
do oh dstar what's wrong what's going on
dstar blink if you if someone has a gun
to your head and if it's me don't Don't
Blink at all don't
don't why did narissa stream at such a
Time
[Music]
narissa waa waa narissa
infiltrating My
Monopoly was that a member stream cuz I
don't see it on Hyer thank you
[Music]
Nisa
weisa w w have you ever seen sting gray
babies they're C
crazy worth Googling go Google Stingray
babies yeah yeah
yeah they look like um really weird
flattened uh what did I say uh
axelos they're cursed
ravioli I don't know about that they
don't look like ravioli to
me
[Music]
H well anyway thank you for the rain and
welcome everybody we are we are
tanging endlessly but I've made some
progress with the super chats some Pro
and we've realized that I can make a
good impression of um Janice from
friends and L from Family Guy
pretty good pretty
good
pea the horse is
[Music]
here
p p get the horse out of
[Music]
P okay okay I stop I stop I
stop thank you for the memberships wow
wow oh yeah I've been seeing my
Anniversary merchandise arrive with
everybody a and I still don't even have
my whole talk merchandise from last
year oh turning into Janice sorry I was
just feeling
um questionable
feelings about not having my merchandise
yet but I'm going to Japan soon I'm
bringing two empty
suitcases and I'm not going back without
my
merchandise
ski what what
what
[Music]
interesting
X you speak my language actually I'm
very common in the language that you're
[Music]
speaking actually you you don't speak it
that well
anyway I can speak that language better
than you
[Music]
but who knows if I'll get there today
cuz I'm still on the
stream yeah okay where were
[Music]
we uh here Nathan thank you for the
pinky Nathan always with the pinkies you
really like the color pink huh hi T hope
you like the game I'll have to be V gang
for this one unfortunately but I wanted
to offer you a chimpin hug as a
compensation you don't need to
compensate for anything but thank
you chimpin hug chimpin hug is always
nice always like to hug a chicken yeah
get yourself a chicken to
hug thank you so much for trying your
best you like pinkies especially
promises me too those are
great I like when our pinkies touch and
intertwine for a
promise it
[Music]
feels
reassuring that's what you do with a
pinky promise
guys your pinkies touch and
[Music]
intertwine
yes
it is true it is
true it is known I have witnessed I have
seen and I have done it myself yeah with
you with you guys you guys gave me pinky
promises all of
you man I wish I had
fingers oh this is so sad don't don't
remind me
of you
guys not having certain body parts makes
me sad I wish I wish I could give those
hands and fingers to you and maybe some
feet while we're at it and maybe maybe
proper ears cuz bird ears are the most
terrifying thing ever to think
[Music]
about fingers cut up cuz they taste to
good chicken fingers you
mean your love gave me a full
body if you're saying like that the
others will have expectations that I can
give that to them
too
hey Nissa it wasn't me it was you
yourself you manifested yourself into
human
[Music]
body credit yourself give yourself some
credit
lady you should give us human forms
actually
actually I think just today I was
thinking
about wanting to draw a human form of
chunkers and
[Music]
smoothie like a
ginka just just for
fun because I think they would look cute
I I don't know I I I would make chunk W
wonky really
fluffy
and
cute and
cheeky but like in a different way cuz
smoothie is also cheeky but in a
different way and then and then smoothie
would be like she would have long
straight really shiny
hair
and she would be like the beauty while
chunky wony is the
Cutie no no not I don't want I don't
expect anything from it I just I just
want to do something that's related to
my cats cuz I love my
cats not expecting anything can we get a
k jinka too but but then I need to make
1.5 million ginkas cuz every single one
of you is unique and
special I can't draw that
[Music]
much and what's the point in the end
you're chicken
so eh sorry
okay you you you you can you can be a
human like never no no no you can't no
no no I can't lie to you I can't lie to
you yeah you're a chicken you good like
this okay good good good I'm happy to
hear that
cuz I can't help you like there's
nothing I can do you're born like this
and that's how you going to
[Music]
die I like being friend shaped nice I
love being a chicken oh my God I'm so
happy you guys are happy with your body
I guess you've been listening to a lot
of Lady
Gaga chicken's listening to Lady Gaga
get gaining Confidence from
that I'm human no you're not you're a
chicken
remember weird coping
[Music]
chicken round and pudy and
fluffy Lady Gaga is in fortnite Lady
Gaga from fortnite oh my God why why
what's
why why guys why why why bring fortnite
into my
[Music]
chat you brought ski into it okay nice
exchange nice
exchange although skib is better I like
the word I like the word a lot
[Music]
na again time this time for Pinky thank
you life hack to give Tak more money
number one go to the H life Shop number
two select any cat boys pack number
three add as many as you want to your
cart for number four K
profits and no YouTube cut yeah I mean
yeah definitely no YouTube cut when you
guys buy
merchandise yeah merchandise are
generally it's not just The Voice pack
oh just any of my birthday or
Anniversary merchandise
or future green looking
merchandise uh has a good cut for me so
that is good merchandise not all
merchandise has the same cut but those
ones are good
yes
yes generally I guess that would apply
to merchandise that it's like only only
Wawa like if it's group merchandise but
then there's a WWA
part like solo WWA in a bunch of group
merchandise no comment but solo wa solo
Solo solo wa good please bye bye bye
[Music]
bye oh no and in the end all of it
supports me if you want some merchandise
I would be delighted if you buy whatever
you know floats your boat whatever you
[Music]
like in the end in the end yeah it's all
helping me one way or whenever
mhm yeah thank you so much for getting
merchandized so
far for building your Taki
shrine at home with the beautiful
merchandise you know you support me
probably no matter what but I try to at
least you know give back to you by
making merchandise that is
useful that is worth buying yeah yeah I
need more place for Merch I can imagine
yeah that's the
problem I'm slowly building a Signature
Collection oh yeah polar are always fun
it's basically meriz you guys are
welcome to print those out if you want
to I got your album
ooh yeah everybody who has the album
since that was time limited everybody
who has the physical one
is a Chad and you will forever have a
treasure special
[Music]
treasure you haven't open your is
actually that's fine I mean you can
listen to it digitally
anyway then the the physical copy is
just for safekeeping and for flexing and
just nice to
have for knowing that you love the
[Music]
Wawa oh yeah right you can't listen to
metal Sparks though if you don't listen
through the
CD will there be a rerun no no not not
not of my knowledge nothing planned
um yeah but you can always get it
digitally like the the digital songs are
always available in my digital music
[Music]
library yeah you never listen to meal
Sparks what the
[\h__\h] why
not it's pretty dope
Metal Sparks
remix I put my waa sign Polaroid by my
Raina sign Polaroid Raina you mean uh
her actual like merchandise
Polaroid probably
right cuz I actually also have a proper
merchandise Polaroid as well as the the
it was the the bonus for the anniversary
I
think the anniversary
merch yeah yeah
yeah our anniversary and birthday
merchandise were so close together that
I mixed up what items were in
[Music]
what the plushy chicken was in which
one was it in the
anniversary I think anniversary right a
birthday
oh
oh ah okay ah right anniversary is the
backpack I just saw photos today it's
the backpack it's the the pen and the
the block
and
and the the luggage tag yeah I think
that's it that's it right
good stuff I like the luggage tag I
would put it on my luggage if it wasn't
problematic to put it on there for
me I would totally use it man totally
especially with how much I travel man
one day one day when it's not
problematic anymore I'm going to start
using all my merchandise I'm going to
wear my merchandise
[Music]
outside M arrive during this stream oh
nice
timing
nice is it to identify your luggage yeah
for example if the luggage gets lost or
also sometimes luggages suitcases uh
look the same so um when you pick up
your luggage at the airport at the
luggage
thingy um normally you're supposed to
check if it's really yours ideally by
checking the luggage tag or or if you
don't have a luggage tag you would check
like the the the ticket thing on the
luggage to see if your name is actually
on it but it's easier to check with the
luggage tag especially if you have such
a unique luggage tag you know
immediately that it's
[Music]
yours you just tie a handkerchief use a
red ribbon yeah but you know what you
could also just use the luggage
tag please go ahead and use it guys put
it on your
suitcase I think it would be so
[Music]
cute ah oh see Han's cute character
plushes of her bag M no remember that
guys keep an eye out for that guys for
narissa
suitcase oh DHL thank you for delivering
to
brutality thank you for doing your
[Music]
job now you
know I have the waa wallet I have a waha
wallet I sold a wallet I don't think I
ever sold a wallet did I I don't
remember selling a
wallet maybe I should in the future yeah
no W wallet W
[Music]
wallet our myth had
wallets to what Tak
wallet
uh ah
those it's a card case though I would
say
[Music]
say okay just as a reminder for the
people who don't know this is I think
what we're talking
about left is cie right is
[Music]
Wawa it does look
nice damn did you guys get
these who got one of
these all life shop hey are they still
available now cuz the starter the
starter goods are always available
right I have one and inas I got one I
got one I did oh so many of
you it's regular merch mhm mhm oh this
one you can buy physically at the Tokyo
Station at the whole life store that's
probably gone now but
okay
[Music]
oh nice at least on geek Jack get sold
out e did you see today they uh they
showed off a new merch
item this I was like oh the shower back
one is perfect as a cat transporter to
take my cats to the bed I'm just joking
by the way obviously it's too small but
in theory I thought it would be a good
joke yeah we have our own EA bag bags
now isn't that
nice
[Music]
M
oh well I'm looking at stuff from the
shop now
a
interesting I still need to decide add
one more item maybe I'll do it after the
stream maybe I'll finally make a
decision after the
stream where was I oh I'm pretty much
done with these
um Manuel
D let's not say dun looking for the top
D boo 723
dun uh oh wait there's I leave the
thumbnail up cuz I use the same
thumbnail for the following stream
[Music]
thank you for the clap clap wow so
motivating it's like I'm running a
marathon take 47 moonight for the
pinky
m
brandona h the G
Cruz thank you for the
this is really a personal choice but if
you wait to buy new recruits a yeah okay
I mean I guess this really doesn't
matter now cuz we finished but for the
epilogue I could probably get new
characters still if I'm going to
actually play that I don't know
and yeah but like wait so for
Co-Op those quests that we would play
together are those the epilog quests or
is it something else that was in the
mind of people and in
[Music]
know no yeah yeah but Ena is playing and
finishing the
epilogue
[Music]
what there's more after the epilog
okay
[Music]
H so okay basically I have to finish the
epilog until we do
Multiplayer or can I do whatever they
want to do without doing the
epilogue but I would probably be to low
level cuz like I mean I looked at ena's
level and it was kind of
crazy
okay what did I get myself
[Music]
into yeah you guys you guys should level
me you know apparently was carried to
level L hard through those epilog
quests you guys can you help me too
please
[Music]
please that would be nice I'm sure
there's not too many uh but a handful of
people right who play the game a handful
who play the game and can help me
yeah maybe you two wiky Tunes you seem
to know a thing or two about it too much
Yap for me that's okay you don't have to
play it we have a handful of people who
can help
scum Herm
her
alud Jones dun chag Channel dun M A
thanks for the pinky I'll put more into
the comments but if you want to try out
uh GBF best time to start would be the
end of the month du to how the start
Dash start
Dash works plus anniversary next month
with roulette for free draws oh and
there's a Tales of collab that sounds
great but is it active right
now isn't that kind of stuff like you
know they have that collab running then
that one's over and then they start a
new one and then that one's over and
then they start a new one and so on but
in general I'm it's permanently active
oh damn but I'm not interested I don't
want to start a SCA game out of nowhere
on unless I'm
sponsored thank you for the nice
explanation but I'm I don't know no no
no no I don't have time for that if I'm
going to play a game in my off time it's
not going to be a gacha
game
[Music]
yeah I can Sky d t BOS or Ty BOS D thank
you I can
Sky
G thanks the pinky congrats on clearing
the grand blue fantasy realing potential
hope you had fun bearing all the yapping
and I hope the collab goes well too glad
I was able to catch both strings from
start to finish hope you get some much
needed rest wow I definitely needed a
lot of rest after that
yeah wow thank you damn from beginning
to end on both of the streams that's
crazy those are really long streams that
got really yippity
yappity thank
[Music]
you I'm also pretty yippity yappity
right now know my Thro has been kind of
weird
[Music]
today
ah yeah I I I I uh witnessed some whole
life members being part of the GBF
um festival thing
yeah anyway thank you Ark I guess you
you're a big fan of the series or so
otherwise even if you're not thank you
for for staying through that whole thing
that was a long time appreciate it and
Nathan also thanks for the pinky
congrats on marketing yet another game
on your finished list a marking oh but I
was also kind of marketing it though by
by default I'm marketing all these games
on my
channel but I marked it off of my finish
list although maybe marathoning it over
two days was a bit much yeah no well I'm
I'm fine I'm I'm actually glad I did it
in 2 days um
[Music]
F them cuz I didn't feel I didn't feel
like using the thumbnail a third
[Laughter]
time yeah it was fine like a little bit
of marathoning here and
there yeah getting something off of my
list it just feels
good I it kind of the thing is it felt a
little bit like a task that I had to do
that I had to get done because you know
of the collab
thing so for me it was very satisfying
to just get it
done losing my mind was fun
too that was
fun I was having fun that was very
different from other instances where
maybe I suffered a bit through
marathoning
something this was not the
same
it added to the experience oh it sure
did J swack BG thanks for the pinky epic
Gaming today grandle is such a cute day
that was fun to watch it was cute it was
cute it was beautiful beautiful
Aesthetics
Graphics character designs for sure the
combat was
fun uh yeah so it was a good game well I
mean maybe I rated it a little bit too
high like considering other games and
how I rated them
but whatever it was a good game wasn't a
bad game for sure thank you for watching
I hope you enjoyed those intense hours
together aluda also thank you for the
pinky you got through the Yap yapping
congrats thank you oh my
god H it was a lot but not only I got
through it you got through it too we all
deserve a badge don't we or a t-shirt or
a mug something
something I'm so proud of us been
practicing for 4 years excuse
me excuse me what does that mean
huh we've conquered
it trophy trophy would be
amazing
yeah I've watched it like twice of you
and Ena
damn I'm surprised
you like I don't know if I could do
that like once yeah twice
though like in close
succession if it was like a year
between then maybe but
uh so close to each
other maybe you were only half
listening that could make it
easier you watched punua and me play
it oh oh you too oh my God what's you
guys actually really love the game or
are you just doing it for us like the fu
nail
say which one is it
huh I like y'all I like the game for the
girls both oh
for the ladies for
[Music]
both
both okay wow all right all right all
right all
[Music]
right for the wowers for the
ladies you guys are so sweet wow we are
so blessed to have you guys
[Music]
Jac 47
than I see you here today
too for the pinky congrats T glad you
enjoyed a part of gr's world although it
wasn't entirely your choice thank you
for choosing to play
[Laughter]
this with it getting busy soon you might
not play again until March but by then
there will be a new boss oh okay not
that I needed
one but yeah uh I think
H I wonder when we could do
[Music]
it if we don't do it before the middle
of March before going to Japan then then
we might not do it until uh April
TBH h
oh by the way I just remembered you guys
I saw your reminders for the Easter
thing thank
you can you remind me
again like on the day off or so this
week on a day where i'm not streaming
can you remind me
then when you reminded me I was like
reading the tweets I'm like yeah yeah
yeah no
couldn't be bothered to think about it
um
so and which day I don't know anytime
just remind me
[Music]
sometime I know yeah you're like my
parents yeah yeah you are sometimes you
are do you need idea brainstorming
M if I can squeeze a member stream in
this week which I can't promise but if I
can then that's something we could
discuss there
[Music]
yeah okay of
parenting remember the in thank you for
reminding me wow I needed
that h space waterful than game
8910 than the quest also artist than for
the pinky they also released the 12th
episode anime oh yeah I read this
already it's for free to watch on
YouTube that's pretty amazing that is so
amazing but I'm not going to watch
it but D Jes
G and EV
D actually it's really good I believe
you but I'm not going to watch
it yeah yeah I know I know I know they
did that with Tes of Symphonia
[Music]
mhm S2 has fairy
yeah yeah but I'm not going to watch
it thanks for the membership thank
you
[Music]
next I'm really motivated to get this
done guys
[Music]
ASAP ja 47 d space water D is I right
thanks for Pinky hi K I hope your vacas
went well just wanted to pop in and
thank you for giving me that awesome gym
speech
ah I couldn't squat 250 KJ kilogram but
I pulled
272 Kg on deadlift okay you couldn't
squat 250 but you deadlifted 272 is that
like like more impressive or less is
like
squatting more difficult than
deadlifting probably right cuz for
deadlifting you lie down on the bench
thingy right and for squatting you squat
which I'm guessing puts
more pressure I don't
know I find squatting more difficult
picking it up on to your waist and
putting it down ah never mind oh oh wait
okay it's not you don't lie down and
that's bench pressing oh okay what do I
know
okay so if that's both standing up
basically then maybe they're pretty
equal just different muscle groups
huh that's still anyway insane like
that's since I only weigh one kilogram
you uh Lifted Me 272 times and that's
pretty [\h__\h] amazing that you can do
that
yeah
yeah you're so strong impressive Isaiah
very
impressive you could also lift so many
chickens if we need to go somewhere and
and the chickens maybe don't want to
walk you can lift them
all
amazing chicken transporter isah right
if you needed a title that is your title
now the gamer cre T Michael H D thank
you Lou moonight D for the red J 4 hours
is a short stream for KF let's go long
live the
waa yeah that stream was certainly not
short and the one following certainly
also wasn't short you're welcome
kfp catching up with you know streaming
hours that's all I'm doing oh oh
[Music]
Z K's fitness program yeah I mean I'm
not taking part but you guys are welcome
to take part in the Kiana fitness
program get fit don't skip like they
[Music]
period also don't skip
don't skip leg day don't skip flap day
flap day is Wings flapping
[Music]
day
yes
yes time to get
swo like that swo enemy in
Yakuza imagine imag imagine the swle kfp
that exists like Isaiah and
sakasi perhaps
Cruz dressing up like that swoll enemy
remember from
yesterday what a funny
[Music]
thought nah you guys don't need to get
swoll only if you want to only if that's
something you want to do but I just hope
you guys guys um for your own sake are
able
to uh you know be somewhat healthy
somewhat for your own sake not for
[Music]
me for
yourself you do want to get
swoll such a funny
word is that even a real
[Music]
word
ooh summer
B yeah I could never I I can't not
because it grosses me out but like I
don't even have the motivation to do
it running machine
[Music]
win so lazy I'm so
lazy I'm so lazy I should be the
protagonist of Lazy Town
imagine lazy town but not pink just all
orange blindingly
[Music]
orange wouldn't that be nice so
spin-off no I hated sporticus
no get him out out of my face he's baded
from my lazy town
ew I hate
him no I'm the girl why why would I be
sport
CU but he's blue so what not every blue
person is
cool did you like Robbie who's Robbie
to Lazy Town
Robbie oh no wait that's that's the same
person eh
what how
wait it's not they look the
[Music]
same
wait no I mean I'm looking at a picture
of all three of them
I mean I don't like either of
them I don't like either of
them simple as
[Music]
that they have the same Vibes it's
just evil and not
evil but they have the same vibe to me
those two
[Music]
like long
asparagus person in a skinny suit
with yeah with
interesting facial hair one has a funky
mustache and one has funky
eyebrows
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah oh God he does have big valigi
and oh my God he's literally
valigi you know you always wonder like
oh man why does Nintendo never do
anything with
Waluigi if anything it's only Wario but
Waluigi gets completely ignored and then
it's like what do you mean Waluigi is
like playing a big part in Lazy Town
what what else do you want literally has
a
liveaction
show and you guys don't appreciate that
maybe that's why he doesn't get anything
[Music]
else maybe you should have appreciated
it more and then he would have gotten
more more content more games more
shows but
anyway where where are
we here
maybe yeah py D SP wonderful D Lord
evoke D do thanks to the pinky that's
the game or for you finishing hold your
RPG in the middle of another one
exactly
skill the gamer ofen Cruz D Michael H D
Michael H D Michael H dun gu D Michael H
D Gerard D Lord roke
[Music]
D you changed your profile picture I did
not approve of this change what is this
profile picture what is
[Music]
that that's Kyla in the middle isn't
it oh what
o m what happened what happened what
happened I need an
explanation what is the meaning of
this are you
here are you
here Kyla is
cool
yeah cooler than your mama no sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry I don't see him in the
[Music]
chat I am [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] uh you have two
mommies you have two
mommies
[Music]
near Rampage gaming dunan Michael H
dunan Michael H D Michael
H Michael H really wanted my attention
on that day
huh looking for the top D bottom of sh's
boots D for the pinky
Michael H D Jack 7
D I see
[Music]
you than pinky wait why is there so
many why is there some why is there so
many empty pinkies a thank you for the
pinky V T sttion thank you for watching
me for one year I do think it's a long
time it is it totally is thank you
Nathan D for the yeah I did a bit did
I uh it wasn't it the Alo
happy no that was later you guys were
saying aloh happy in the Super Chat this
is something else I
guess yeah this is not the Alo happy bit
you guys were just giving me empty super
chats because I complained about ah no
because I complained about bottom of
Shield These Boots maybe I don't know I
then start it a wave thank you guys
naan for the pinky motion for the
pink unknown D for the pinky and Anthony
web D for the pinky you actually wrote
something oh cuz of the kidnapping wait
yeah something some bit I did something
there Ki what a lovely baseball bat you
have there
[Music]
mhm thank you I saw a new one in the
making on on the
hashtag yeah I don't know how that will
ever reach me if it will reach me but
looking good so far Lord EV Danish oh
wow oh damn boom baby Dan Maple Leaf
[Music]
D yeah yeah that was kind of
special Cruz D Spirit
vet spank thanks for the pinky
judgement yeah
judgment Yakuza has so many iconic songs
m d Sky
D thank you for the r Super Chat here
comes the Alo happy
donations for w bang thank you
maku ah I appreciate your donation
lunchbox d l d Jackson Indigo 5 Alpha
thanks for the pinky no words again
thank you
though I guess you were just so all
happy you couldn't put it into
[Music]
wordsy
Galaxy Michael H thank you for the red
chat more more
happy thank you Michael H you're n Super
Chat this
[Music]
time of amib don't be sad don't be Al
sad dun mang no happy G dun you are dang
Jackson and Alvaro the only sane person
who didn't tweet about Alo
Happy who didn't talk about Al
happy than
soon
yeah into the frer goes that thumbnail
never to be seen again oh
Alo yeah Alvaro the most aloan
chicken y Yos I'm almost there oh we're
not halfway we're almost there
oh we're living on a
[Music]
pray
Yum Yum
[Music]
Yum the Animal Crossing stream
mhm that was
fun and I'm I'm surprised I had fun with
that in the
end cuz I was a bit annoyed by the
yapping but I had fun yeah overall the
whole stream was fun not just the Animal
Crossing section everything was
fun nice yuza weekend for sure J monkey
CI than Moonlight thanks chat just want
to wish you an Al happy stream T thank
you the Vault pile is getting huge but I
wouldn't want it any other way whatever
it takes for happy w l kids what do you
mean whatever it takes for happy
waa I'm doing this for you
guys
[Music]
where where does this yapping term come
from that's all
games what where does it come from I
don't know where it comes from but I
like the word I think it's Zoomer
language cuz I heard it in zomer videos
on YouTube before I used it on you
[Music]
guys it's not oh but I never heard it
until recently from
Zoomers maybe it's like fashion like old
things coming
back and being trendy again could that
be could that
[Music]
be
who who did you hear
[Music]
[Laughter]
that
I need a
massage I need a I need a life partner
just for
massages one day one day I'll I'll I'll
just like go and find myself a massage
therapist wrap him around my
finger
and
yeah
that will
be my path my key to happiness massages
daily massages for free for
free for
life I mean it doesn't have to be a
massage
professional you some people are just
good you know just because just because
you you can get good you can have
massage uh classes like cooking classes
too wink wonk time for you guys to take
massage classes go go guys and girls go
take those massage classes for the
W just kidding oh my God that's too
parasocial I take it back I take it
[Music]
back but did I tell you Nissa gave me a
really good massage like like so nice of
her cuz I was like in so much pain and
then she was like come here sit down
I'll give you
massage did I tell you yeah and then she
could have done it for just like 30
seconds like most people do but no she
like really got into it and did it for
like I don't know 5 minutes or so 6
seven felt pretty
long
no
just marry her then all right then okay
I will maybe I
will maybe I
[Music]
will fine maybe I
will narissa you hear that or you gone
we're marrying shotgun wedding after
Andy narissa does your does your dad has
some shotguns because when you need to
go do a shot let me tell her
that
[Music]
hey
Nissa does your dad have some
shotguns Let Me Wait for the
answer I know that's not what a shot oh
wait oh wait oh wait oh wait wait wait I
CL this not the first time we had that
misile histic wa wait wait what was that
again oh she says yes oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] I was going to say let's um have
a shotgun marriage but I just realized
I mixed up the meaning
again wait
uh uh wait F shotgun marage just because
it's fast you know when you shoot a
shotgun it's like PE so to me in my
brain that means you run away and
quickly have a marriage really quickly
like in Las Vegas or whatever that's the
second time we have that
misunderstanding what was that
again that's eloping yeah but shotgun
wedding could be just another word for
that
wait but that's really concerning what I
just found out ask her what kind of sh
no you ask
[Music]
her are you get in touch with her
dad go have Dad
[Music]
conversations so narissa really is
pergant oh oh wait wait you guys left
the important information out so shot
shotgun messages when you elope because
lady is um already
[Music]
prante now
now I have the full
[Music]
picture why did I forget this again and
I literally when I was like no I know
when a shotgun I was going to say that
right in that moment I was like I was
thinking you were going to say to me
like uh like something like you know a
marriage is not like like shotgun
marriage is not like something where
somebody is shot with a shotgun I'm like
I know that I know what a shotgun
marriage is it's it's when people elope
really
spontaneously okay no that's that was
not exactly
it not quite not quite pretty close
pretty close close close
enough of course it's not taking
literally
yeah of course of course of course
[Music]
that's what I was going to say to
you girl's dad has a shotgun so the boy
has to marry or else really is that
the the
origin terrifying
terrifying
[Music]
terrifying uh Jacob 47
d d Johnny F wow
D oh yeah I really like that Super Chat
talking about that with some deep [\h__\h]
Lord EV Garden
Park D attack thank you for the Super
Chat greetings Teno
reporting I already read this I think
yeah I already read this uh when it came
in thank you so
much you have a
creative
Talent thank you T
tag glory to
kfp Stone yellow
Kumo hi Ultima Jimmy Jack
Funk
Tracy
73 coefficient yo D muffin a D T Mo
thanks for Pinky man I'm bad at skiing I
think I went last year to the Alps in
Austria and it's been super long since
my last time and the first thing I did
was skiing into somebody because I
didn't know to stop super embarrassing I
haven't been skiing since then oh man
did they crash really badly
or did they get hurt you don't have to
feel bad I'm sure it happens a lot you
know and you were begin you you were
probably on like a beginning slope right
so not very skilled people are there
often surely and you
know yeah yeah yeah you guys are I
reacted to it when the super chat came
in I was like oh coefficient
oh
interesting I saw he was doing something
in a moku
cosplay where is the takanashi Ki
cosplay yo if you're so ready to show
your mid riff then takanasi cosplay is
the the way to
go I need to see the W cosplay too huh
I challenge you coefficient to show me
your swoll
Bard show me your loyalty which I'm just
now claiming that there is
loyalty in the most beautiful color
there could ever be orange in a
takanashi Kiana
uniform I challenge
you
[Music]
with both
hats yeah two hats or
more could be more but minimum two hats
required to a Dell uh I
mean I don't know about
that I challenge you to wear the
uniform because if you show up here
without your
uniform then you're going to get
fired you need to wear the uniform you
need to be properly dressed when you
come to your shift at kfp you can't just
walk in here drop a Super Chat and not
wear the
[Music]
uniform looking forward to seeing you in
your proper attire as discussed and uh
signed in original contracts when you
first first joint
kfp you must properly fulfill your
duty if you don't wear your uniform
properly I'm going to get in trouble
from all the all the health companies
whatever that
check us out yeah protocol protocol
needs to be
protected just as much as your
smile don't be selfish with what you're
going to protect protocol needs to be
protected otherwise yeah it's an OSHA
violation as much as it is a OSI
violation uhhuh uh-huh all right are we
clear or are we
clear good moving on I'm sure that will
reach him one way or
another
Cole played tunic recently oh did he
finish it
though the golden path the golden path
good choice in game though very good
choice he likes the game oh pong watches
coefficient a coefficient if you're ever
lost with tunic just watch my V my hour
hour hour hour hour long V
there the the solution to the golden
path is in my
[Music]
stream and nowhere
else H where where where where was we
okay yeah Tassimo I feel you I'm also
scared but maybe we can be strong
together and go skiing again sometime
yeah even if we're
traumatized a h d a h d why are these
all deleted
ion
[Music]
oh I'll take 30 more minutes of tangents
thanks
no could be B the
leing they got a time out h ah Dan ah d
space waterful Dan
v d m guy D thank you you're welcome
thank you for the first Super Chat ever
Jacob
47 thank
you R fre d z d spam D
Sky Anon web D ah D ah D Michael H than
soon Lord EV than Michael H than
Jackson
FB birthday of
Jackson hi wa today is once again my
birthday I couldn't ask for a better
gift than to be a chimkin so thank you
for giving me a place to
be if it weren't for you guys I also
wouldn't have a place to be it's mutual
thank you so much and happy
birthday happy birthday to you Mom love
Ino
AIC in
the Happy Birthday to
You German version for once
[Music]
wow Jam in the shoe apricot in your
pants I don't understand either guys I
don't know it's so
Random that's literally what the German
version of the song says I mean not the
like I mean it's not the only version we
have we also
sing but sometimes we just singing like
this it's a kind of maybe a childish
[Music]
version happy birthday to
you there is Jam in your
shoe there's apricots in your pants too
happy birthday to you that's
it
I think it's
poetic it's deeper than you
[Music]
think if you can't appreciate that
song's deepness then you're not ready to
ascend
too deep for
[Music]
me so oh my God it's almost 10 p.m. but
my stream is still pretty short I'm I'm
going to I'm going to finish this
finishing move
W thank you Jackson FB you're the best
thank you so much for being part of kfb
I'm so happy to have
you my my my Canadian maple syrup
buddy thank you so much free kiss today
M cuz it's your
birthday it's your birthday we go party
like it's your birthday it's your
birthday going party it's your birthday
something like
that LE knle let's go a so much Canadian
love wow wow thank
you you said short stream yeah it's it's
shorsh Michael
h d h l d GD D black d LC
D wait now I need to look it up cuz I
don't think I actually looked it
up KFC
Che
oh it's uh for some reason I imagine it
to be even though this is KFC we're
talking about for some reason I imagine
it to be on like non breaded
chicken the fact that it's on breaded
chicken makes it better
um yeah I don't know if I would call it
a pizza just like topped with some sauce
and other toppings but yeah okay if you
want to for marketing sake call it a a
CH
[Music]
sure maybe maybe I'll have KFC
tonight maybe I
will I wonder if they have this CH in
Austrian KFC
though KFC
Austria not that I would order that
necessarily pull
there I don't think they have it at
least not on
the H the newest thing they have is a
crito like a burrito with a
queue I don't really ever go to KFC so
not not not often um I feel like there's
not even that many KFC in Austria
anyway so this is a burrito with fried
chicken basically
[Music]
clue no no qu but yeah they don't seem
to have it yet we have not blessed by
the chah the
chea if you guys have Che in your area
go get
it and tell me if it's good could be
good probably
decent spank time thanks for the pinkies
see you next time on the island thank
you oh I hope you guys are having fun
with my aaka playthrough because it's
still going to be a
while Cru
than
okay not sponsored I tried it and know
it's dry ooh ooh oh
no that's not good that's not good at
all uh from what I saw a couple years
ago it was already a thing years ago
next story but should be extremely hype
oh oh
interesting I want to watch it but I
also want to play the game myself first
well go play it then play it alongside
me go do
it don't let your dreams be dreams and
stuff like that you
know
so
um
I shall read the super chats from
today and I
will turn them off now just so that
there's nothing new coming in oh thank
you
[Music]
gr it's closed guys you can't get
another quicky in there
mm-m why is there so many pinkies and
reds the
[\h__\h] I thought I was getting done
here okay but it's
not that much number I
guess I can do this I can do this yeah
the Finish Line you got emotional not
our fault did I today I guess I
did oh yeah I guess I did
[Music]
Suffering From Success nah I'm good I'm
good I'm not suffering I'm not suffering
I'm good
so Jacob 47 py
S2 thank
you thank you especially J P you're
enjoying those thank you I'm happy to
hear
that Georgie Anthony thank you and it's
your birthday Cong congratulations
Georgie
yo it's your special day happy birthday
to
you sweet sweet happy
birthday let me guess it's your sweet
[Music]
16 forever
16 happy
birthday we're blessed to have you stay
the Way You Are
[Music]
Queen
Sena really does that mean you you turn
like 18 or
something I doubt it I somehow doubt
it or 15 oh I I doubt
[Music]
it but okay let let's just stay it's a
girls turn 15
ah oh that's so nice I didn't have a
quinera what the [\h__\h] should we have a
quinca in hindsight like
now one of these
[Music]
days or can I not have it am I not
allowed the way I pronounce it
[Music]
shush k
k k
K that probably is more accurate yeah
I'll have everything I'll have a K I'll
have a b mitv I'll have uh everything
all of that please all in one go
[Music]
please that would be a fun stream maybe
actually it would be a funky idea to
just do all these kinds of like parties
even though is not my culture but by
doing that I learn the culture too like
I learn what to do the
activities and we do a vtuber version of
it yeah oh yeah I can invite the
mariachi band AKA audio
[Laughter]
stock
wait is that would that be cultural
appropriation or or is or is it fun and
cute
I feel like it's kind of a cute
idea it's just like my snackbox
review just with
parties learning and trying out other
[Music]
cultures I'll think about it I don't
know it might be an idea for like much
later when I have time Lam gang doesn't
mind let's
go just have a Latina there okay I'll
have like
[Music]
guests I want to have a bitza to
celebrate my gender transition to
correct the mistake of my bitza when I
was younger to correct the mistakes so
it's the same idea just a cute party
cute party I love cute party iron Mouse
oh oh would iron Mouse
know oh I'm sure she would love to help
me have a k
yet I'm sure she would love to help me
out she'll be my one
[Music]
guest wait that's so cute that's kind of
cute my idea is
cute
[Music]
nice culture consultant making sure you
get it right exactly
exactly I'll I'll get some
food yeah it's super down for this idea
now oh my God hey we just kind of out of
nowhere created a cool stream
idea yeah got to put on some like stream
uh accessories some some assets for my
body some
outfits
yeah cie too what what does cie know
about kining
[Music]
Yas or do you mean just because she's
good with iron
[Music]
Mouse she's from Texas
closest American thing to Mexican what
just because there's an X in
[Music]
there white girls celebrate
kinas you're confusing me
now it would be like if I really really
really want to go all out on it I could
make a like VR chat sets like let's say
in the studio that we have I make free
different sets one is a
ketta and then we do that for like half
an hour 40 minutes or so then we move
over and then oh we can have like you
know Iron Mouse but we can also have
like whoever I don't know who would be
the representative for B Mitzvah but
basically we could do like it's a four
people collab three different themed
parties and the three guests are each
like representing that but then when we
go to the other party basically iron
Mouse for example would also be
experiencing that for the first time and
you know we're like exchange cultural
exchange it's cooking she's
[Music]
cooking uhhuh okay find me find me
suitable YouTubers but what would the
third party
be what what what else is there is there
something Asian like an
equivalent oh ah ah well there is
there's a Japanese equivalent but it's
like when you turn uh uh 20 20 right
20 with the nice super long kimon
no
yeah that that actually I know some
stuff about and we could get like a we
could get
Iris cuz I don't know she she she know I
I know a little bit about it but I feel
like maybe maybe IR knows more about it
and then she can speak English too
so that could be an option if I can't
think of anything else debutantes ah
debutantes that's kind of something
I aspire to because you know because of
gilo
girls Korea is coming of
age Korea too yeah
h h
H I'll have to choose something for for
Japanese coming of H day I could at
least uh easily find someone I'm pretty
sure it's going to be going to be a sick
party yeah oh my
god let's
go do Italians have anything punu loves
you Italians not that I know of not like
something that celebrates a
not that I know
of in Indonesia that would also be cool
cuz I could call someone from ID
but we get blind drunk British
oh no it should be more cultural uh
culturally
um distant from
me something that I don't know that I
could be taught
about I'm the guine
Pig did someone say British yesterday I
watched a new video from Max F he's so
funny and I found out that in
Amsterdam uh British people are not
welcome I'm sure it's kind of like a
joke though
but there's several apparently several
articles or so where amam is like
British people don't come here because
you guys are too crazy you guys get way
too drunk in Amsterdam and then do all
kinds of crazy [\h__\h] we don't want you
here go home is apparently uh a
thing I thought that was so
funny do you see when he made rat yeah I
love Max f y I watched all all his video
I when once I found his channel and I
watched all the newer ones I I couldn't
help but watch all the older ones too I
think I've been through it
all pretty
much Max fos and um uh the other one
that he often brings into his videos too
was it
Zach yeah
[Music]
Zach those British YouTubers are so
funny I love the one where he broke GL
in front of the place yeah yeah
yeah one of them was of a
horse
Peter the horse is
[Music]
here yeah yeah yeah he did a lot of
funny things I love uh how he keeps on
dragging his sister the thing with the
book recently was crazy so his sister
just for people who have no idea is
British rtu with Max she makes funny
YouTube videos and he has a sister he's
like he has this whole like you know war
with his sister uh one one time he
legally Legally in court or so confirmed
that he is the favorite Child you know
he does silly silly things and then
recently one of the news videos was um
his sister brought was like going to
release a book
and uh he released uh like book book
with the same title and all that and he
just wanted it to be released like a day
before or so just to like be the first
in the family before her to release a
book so like it goes through the whole
process of getting that done uh
yeah he's so
funny yeah he's so petty but it's
obviously just a joke and his sister is
having fun with it
too you just got my merch thank you so
much thank you yeah that's the guy who
uh tricked an airport by putting up a
sign yeah no yeah wait was it Max or was
it
Zach I think it was Max that must have
been
Max yeah he's also the one who bought an
airline for a day and who bought a
roundabout yeah I mean they do similar
things those two they they make uh
collaboration videos too your merch is
here too let's go oh my God everybody
keep an eye out for the
mailman or lady the Luton sign yes yes
yes yes yes exactly that one went viral
and was in the
news the luggage tag is so well made
thank you I really want to use it but
you guys you have to use it so that I
don't feel sad that I can't use
it mine's getting delivered today oh my
God everybody's getting it at the same
time
wow damn all at once we're keeping those
delivery people busy so let's be nice to
them until they're not nice to us then
then maybe
[Music]
not you also just got yours oh my God
I get mine on thur day that's still
close
enough your anniversary mer ship before
the birthday why that's
weird Okay Psy d
h do Moonlight than for the pinky enjoy
the tangent stream friendly reminder to
the new chins we don't read super chats
in the Super Chat reading streams we
just chill and listen to W
stores yeah pretty much yeah I actually
can't uh also I sounded like a horse
just now did I not or like a
donkey the yeah I sounded like a donkey
I'm embarrassed uh but yeah that's how
we do it here at Wawa Super Chat
readings
Cru [\h__\h] wa have so embarrassed I feel
like I need to end the stream right
[Music]
now
I thought I was
St now I'm forever confirmed this
dony that's so embarrassing that
noise oh God I can't get it out of my
brain
[\h__\h]
no shut
up I need to listen back to it and then
cry and you guys are going to put me on
Donkey faces any donkey even real
donys
man that's like the Nery seal edits but
for me it's just going to be
embarrassing
I doned myself
no I'm donkey now I can make a I'm
donkey but finally I have a new idea for
an M2 video
great M
[Music]
donkey Bruce stey Dan and Avenged me Dan
naan thank you for the pinky I'm here
for my 30 minute Super
Chat no I'm too embarrassed right
now I need to get out of here so I need
to finish the super chats I can't spend
30 minutes on a tangent Nathan also it's
not like you haven't already started
enough tangents in this
house no that's right Nico raven d last
Brain Cell than vanel
d jaky d
[Music]
D donkey sh shut up oh my God I can't be
here
anymore tiet Monkey D sh an
unknown I can't I
can't okay just for now we're switching
to uh feel and
dank it's an emergency situation feeling
Dan uh sorry I'm late boss I just woke
up oh no problem don't worry about
it I wish you would have woken up after
the the donkey incident
now thank you feeling dank for the pinky
blank feeling dank for the pinky as
well long time since my last superjob
boss always love you you thank you I
need to be careful with my words now uh
love you
too it is so nice to see
you I feel secure and relieved I
appreciate it thank you feeling
d mp53 g feel it's in my blood guys Nagy
feeling dunk space waterful feeling dunk
hyra thank you for the feeling
dunk hello Miss oie I'm I'm you oie I'm
visiting Japan for the first time this
summer I'll go to Osaka Kyoto in Tokyo
are there any places shops restaurant
you can recommend to a firsttime visitor
your yaka play for is so much much so
much fun much love from
Germany feeling d uh I think for these
questions I finally have a good answer
because normally I'm like
who who now I'm supposed to suddenly
pull out of my ass like a freaking
tourist guide for you
guys and give you
like a whole plan on what to do on your
vacation so now what you can do now is
you can go to my shorts to my YouTube
shorts that I upload especially the ones
that I uploaded during my
break and there's a couple of things
there you know the the the cut the
restaurant uh what else um the the the
crap Place may be
not uh selling the same things anymore
but you can go uh to the gcha machines
they're they're still around
[Music]
's you can go to a girly afternoon
tea yeah okay that's that that's maybe
it did I have anything from before
[Music]
oh uh you could if you're going there in
summer you can go to a Summer Festival
if they have one somewhere okay that's
that's kind of it but okay just a little
bit there but I always say yeah
enoshima I usually recommend
enoshima for like a short day trip out
of
Tokyo and uh in Kyoto I would recommend
arashiyama um
uh yeah very much Alama but in kyto I
don't think I need to give you
recommendations cuz there's like I mean
all of Kyo is a
recommendation in Osaka for me Osaka was
mostly just like cuz I lived there
before for me it was just like a fun
place to live in I loved shopping in
shinai
Bashi um brain empty right now so I
can't really think of like anything
besides that but but Osaka is really
cool like uh I think you should maybe
try if you speak any Japanese you could
go to uh a comedian show in in the
shinai Bashi suji it's like a Long
Street that goes through sh shinai Bashi
Namba and so on um it's all connected
and yeah do oh yeah yeah that's also
there uh and that's also there's like an
area where all uh like where where a lot
of comedians perform in venues there so
they actually be advertising it too
mhm so if you look it up maybe you'll
find some info on it too but I'm
assuming you maybe can't speak Japanese
in that case I don't
know I don't know I've given you enough
information Google can help you out too
probably sorry but I I can't spend like
half an hour on giving uh travel
advice uh yeah but generally I think you
should also go to
k and uh go to family restaurants when
you're when you're not sure where to go
for food um I feel like one safe place
to always go to is a family
restaurant I love going to family
restaurants they usually have a big
variety of food also
Japanese M they have like Western food
and Japanese Food both usually and drink
bar and the food is uh pretty cheap and
you can stay there like really long
comfortably and they're all over the
place and yeah they're really good I
really love Japanese family restaurants
we don't have family restaurants in
Austria
yeah
yeah oh yeah Celia is crazy but yeah
that's focused on Italian food but the
other family restaurants are more like
mixed like gasto uh hosu Royal host is a
bit more expensive uh Japanese Denny's
is amazing Jonathan's is amazing like
Gast Jonathan and um yeah Su I love
those H talk
question yeah big
recommend
mhm yeah so have fun
uh I'm sure I'm sure you'll make some
amazing
experiences also go to an
onen of
course got to go to
[Music]
onen I could like give endless
recommendations in theory but
yeah you can't make me yo I'm also super
worried about it if you're not going
alone maybe you could go with whoever
you're going with
maybe that could take off some of the
pressure although I would actually be
the opposite like my first time going to
an onson was alone without a friend
purposefully so at least the people that
do see my naked body don't know
me having someone who knows me see it is
worse
anyway enjoy have a safe
travel
and also when you arrive in Japan now
they kind of ever since cor Corona they
changed some things um and when you
first arrived like I was kind of
confused once they changed things I was
confused I was like it uh I thought you
were done with Corona and like having to
fill out things in advance online
um because there's still signs that say
like oh QR code and so on and then I was
like [\h__\h] I don't have it but um don't
worry you don't have to have it uh most
people apparently still like do it
online and bring the QR code and this
and that but uh you don't have to you
can still just go there arrive and then
fill out
everything uh at the spot with your
hand but there's a choice to still do it
online too
yeah and one thing I've noticed they
used to give out the things to fill out
for immigration in the airplane but I'm
so annoyed cuz they stopped doing it uh
but it saved so much time to fill it out
in the
airplane apparently they generally just
stop doing
it uh and then problem is you go there
and the lines are forming from all the
people who get off the plane and you
can't stand in line yet cuz you need to
go pick up the papers which are only
there around the immigration counters
you take one of the papers you fill it
out you have to stay there unless you
brought a pen so maybe one life hack if
you're not going to do it online bring a
pen so that you can just take the papers
and maybe fill it out while you're
standing in
line
maybe or just do it online
[Music]
anyway thank you it to you when you went
a week ago but was probably different
between el oh yeah it probably
is probably
is thank you for the red super
[Applause]
chat
[Music]
mp15 free uh garlic
stank super bear hero ah feeling D
feeling
D Remy feeling d h feeling D oh you're
also going to Japan but you're missing
all of us oh cuz you're going to in in
May yeah have any suggestions for places
to
eat again go to the T cut place also it
really depends which city you're going
to the tonat place is in Tokyo if you're
going to cor check out Japan eats uh
Instagram or YouTube shorts
whatever most of his places are in K cuz
he seems to be based in
KOB he's been doing like a series where
he reviews
uh every not like not only that but like
he also reviews currently all the
restaurants in one shopping mall
underground shopping district whatever
in Kuba and I just I just feel like a
fan right now cuz I want to go there and
go to all the restaurants there just
like him and I'll be like oh Japan eats
was
here I want to go here I want to go
there and eat the same things
[Music]
yeah the teer list yeah yeah
yeah so funny other people think like
this about me they're like I want to go
where Wawa eats but then I'm like I want
to go where Japan e
eats but genuinely the food looks so
good the food that he
finds yeah mp53 scx thank you for the
pinky I feel like you talk yourself down
sometimes things you say you can't do or
won't happen you an amazing vtuber and a
member of the legendary Hol myth
literally the bridge head never heard
that for V tubing outside of Japan I say
you just shoot for the
stars yeah I mean I mean we had we
talked about this I'm generally like you
know I I I get myself back up on my fees
and I achieve things that I realize are
pretty
great um but I'm also a realistic person
you know you
know some things just don't seem very
likely to
me but
yeah I will do my best to thank you for
the support I wouldn't be able to do
anything if you weren't supporting
me thank you for the kind
words very very
sweet Wiki Tunes also with a pinky back
when I said you helped boost my career
it was your honesty storytelling about
your old jobs that made me second guess
my career and stop being just
comfortable your stories venting pushed
me to to pushed me to try new things
things double double double
double I appreciate that thank you
M that's that's really amazing to hear
wow so one day when you accept your
Oscar on the
stage will I be one of the people you
thank when you take the the
trophy and you will say dun right I want
to say Dan
Tak most amazing YouTuber out
there who inspired me to go through with
this path this dream that I
[Music]
had and I'll be in the audience in my
fancy golden dress and wiping a tear and
clapping you have no need to thank me
wik
Tunes applause
[Music]
applause why wow and
cut Santiago Martin thanks for the ree
CH W have a nice weekend Care thank you
you too I hope I hope we're going to
have a good week I'm a bit uh nervous
cuz I don't know what's going to
happen I'm shaking in my
boots but hopefully it's going to be
good thank you H uh feel for the pinky W
love H love
uce that's some
pinky
completely feeling D completely honestly
like 3 years ago I was absolutely
miserable every waking moment no I'm
so no I don't want you to feel like that
you were a huge factor in getting me out
of that hole now I'm better than I've
ever been thank you for being a ray of
sunshine
wall oh man I love you guys ifite I can
help you like that I'll stream forever
and ever and
ever man M sauce I'm so happy to hear
you doing better you deserve only
happiness cuz you're so sweet you're the
best you're the
best El mp15 free garlic than space
waterall than for the pinky you never
failed to make me feel better and more
inspired and motivated I told you before
on my birthday how miserable my life was
you really saved me and thanks to you oh
my God all these stories I'm a hero I'm
starting to turn my life around thank
you for letting me rely on
[Music]
you I didn't feel any weight or pressure
so you can continue doing it if you need
to you're welcome I
guess damn but that's on you too that's
on you as
well you took that step you moved your
legs and you did the
thing you turned it around good job
space waterfall good
job chicken
Ovation yeah
S sim it's a s version than mp1 fre G
than thank
you understandable Nathan cotton thanks
for the ah pinky I didn't know there was
a pill to keep you from being poor pure
you mean I guess we'll need to send more
supas so our attention won't have to
rely on a
pill what wait what let me think about
[Music]
this to keep me from what I don't my
brain can't
comprehend
[Music]
uh yeah the pors but the way you wrote
the sentence I thought you mean
pure is it uh no no no nope Nathan I I
don't I can't
um D that's what I'll say cuz my brain
is has left the
chat good try good
try good
[Music]
try glass than you soon Michael H than
soon Viet
D happy birthday Cru dun Michael H Dan
imaginary stranger Dan K Dan thank you
you got the number now o o mod oof mod
UF mod
[Music]
thank D stoping with
pinky
period
mayi
dun let fly dun and
Le it a pinky I [\h__\h] did it love you
w glad I'm finally in a situation where
where I can afford to Super Chat more
let's go let's go I guess you got like
promoted or
something
yo you killed
it
congratulations good for
you and you are so so selfless to share
your
wealth thank you oh your art has been
taking off let's go oh L
kids that's
great amazing
amazing
still thank you so much for the
support I hope that good streak will
continue for
you yeah yeah okay we're done
[Music]
I'm am going
to go over the Valentine's ones next
time I
[Music]
stream I need to take a shower now and
get rid of the
shame that I have brought upon
myself
[Music]
yeah
shame ding ding ding
ding thank you guys for listening it was
5 hours of super chats that's actually
um more than I
thought good that we got rid of it good
that we cleaned out the storage of super
chats thank you very much
uh don't know yet about tomorrow don't
know I'm going to a doctor and
I
maybe maybe we'll
stream
[Music]
maybe
ohow bye bye J say a
Zen I want to get him
[Music]
s but not now
no no thank you guys you guys are the
best I appreciate you guys so
much yeah I hope you know
[Music]
that thank you for the gift
Michel
Michael New Egg being so active huh
nice Dogo you have by the way is that a
husky today I saw on Twitter
for me and great samet dogs with painted
ears I hope uh safe for dogs but uh did
you see it I liked it on Twitter so
maybe you saw it that's literally like
my favorite dog race you can't do that
to me that was so cute I love seeing Sam
yet so
much
man yeah so cute and then of course the
moku one was barking the whole time I
don't think the fuaa one barked a single
[Music]
time
yeah oh breed yeah in German we say R
which is like race so
[Music]
I get it mixed
up don't laugh at
me more shame okay I'll
go bye
[Music]
bye oh my God thank you for the 50
memberships unknown you're
[Music]
crazy you're
crazy you're so crazy
you got a kiss for
that oh
no thank
[Music]
you
make sure to check your emails these
days for the invitation to my k y all
right if you're not invited then too
[Music]
bad just kidding it won't be anytime
soon
[Music]