[Music]
foreign
good morning afternoon evening everyone
hello we're here now
and I have arrived it is
n't even take that much time prepared
wow okay good job
no more quizzes
yeah I think just cool our heads with
some drawings now uh which one do you
want to do
missing piece stop there's even a solo
mode now I never saw that before okay
it's time to draw
um do we just draw something an
incomplete drawings
incomplete drawing okay
but does that mean we draw something
complete and they remove something or
then we just Draw Something incomplete
and other people have to finish it okay
okay okay there's gonna be five each
yeah you guys are only seven
oh
I finished my first one already okay I
got mine yeah nice you got so much time
take your time
do we have to only draw one uh I mean
what's what's it telling you yeah one
out of five I'm gonna draw our first one
and then we get the next person so we
gotta draw a little more of it
and then like okay it gets passed down
they're gonna be five in total I think
so
there's a lot of time there is so much
time I mean this polish up mine a little
bit make it perfect yeah I guess I could
add some more details
okay I think I put too many details I
kind of want to not put too many I guess
once everyone's done the timer just gets
true I guess I'll have to no really
done
oh okay done uh okay done
I guess now is the zatsu part yeah
what is this how much do we add just one
part just a little bit I guess so that
there's enough for five of us to draw on
one thing
I didn't understand the game you you
asked for this one I've never played it
before just doodle like imagine you're
doodling on like a school desk and
everyone like has something different on
it okay so it's a big drawing collab
we shouldn't have too much right not too
much
will people catch my drift of what I'm
going for or should I give more hint
[Music]
oh
looks really nice though I wouldn't mind
this after stream
today
can't you technically erase something
somebody did
oh yeah you can you could just
completely erase with it
beginning of this game then you can
blame it on them like go to where'd you
drop
this is like among us but your phone
who erased this
I think later we'll find out though when
we see the oh yeah it does like a replay
yeah yeah probably that's true okay I'll
leave it simple so people can still
change it change the ways I think if
they want
um what the heck oh we got another one
oh what the hell is that
what is what's that
who did this one thing with the with the
red tongue looking thing what yeah
what was that
um
well I'm so clueless
oh God I can't draw oh yes I've just
remembered I cannot you
but I love your drawing yeah you do you
make good cute drawings cute yeah
agreed
what does uh
what does that thing look like
um
mm-hmm
oh maybe maybe I read
is there a Paint Bucket over there there
is
oh ah okay
what's what's in what's Abby again in
English shrimp shrimp
thank you
[Laughter]
so you know Halloween
I think that's what this is yeah well
mine my first language isn't even
English right
I I I'm lacking so much vocabulary even
German like even the easiest vocabulary
I feel like once you know more languages
like the less you learn of like the
languages you already know
and just like yeah
um
if one person presses done does that
mean it moves it on to the next oh
oh
is it you're not playing a different
game
what what
it looked different yeah it looked
different for a second because it said
like memorize it
um
[Music]
okay I have an idea I have a good idea
this will be good this will be very good
laughs
is somebody just like waiting right now
and has nothing to do or is everybody
doing I'm dry I'm dry I'm drying
flowering good okay
me too yeah me too I'm drawing
cute this is turning out cute you can
change the color to something
that's not in the palette right or sure
[Laughter]
[Music]
a chance
you can pop up you can't stop me
[Music]
I'm almost done timer's running out
okay be honest who drew an ass
no no I might have to draw an ass now
okay okay I see
um
oh this is so stupid I have an idea I
need some time for this idea to
perfectionize it but it will be so worth
it you need to pretty quickly Google
nice
[Music]
stand by my side
wonderful
okay okay
I'm so concentrated right now this is
this is gonna be great
yeah why have you not unless I'm wrong
why have you not played passport 2-2 yet
I
please play it
it's so much better than the first one
they like made it so much bigger there's
like quests and all that it's like
incredible now oh I'll definitely check
it out I haven't played it since like
near debut time maybe it's a
it's a good time it's about time
and they have so many more tools too to
draw with
it's incredible so many new canvases and
colors and oh
everything else I've never played that
before it sounds fun though yeah not
even playing the first one no yeah
they're all so good yeah but if you
never played the first one either maybe
you could skip right to the second one
because it's like so much better but the
first one with the the lack of things
also has a lot of charm to it yeah it's
like you get limited tools and you gotta
make a really good you know artwork out
of it yeah sounds like a fun challenge
it's basically an art game
oh
[Music]
it's five out of five we get to look at
what everyone do now instead of my
artworks wait is this done after this no
I'm not it's five out of five we get to
see everyone's lovely artworks who loves
Marine the most out of whole life
Oh shoot no time me oh
okay okay
[Applause]
all right all right drawing do I go
manual I'm excited for this
yeah manual means like you can scroll
through okay
eyes
but then it turned into so much sharp
cheese
did you catch eyes
[Music]
oh maybe some of the lines like
disappear per person so like oh that's
what the missing piece means
oh okay that makes sense do you draw
something and they remove something
random okay
all right okay
oh I didn't see that at all I saw a
salary man
so it started from the taco eyes and it
turned into something
okay all right all right next
um
this is awesome Amelia Watson started
off with
the whole mouth part I think when the
eye was missing it looked more like a
shrimp to me oh this is what that was
okay except for the tongue the tongue
confused me
the guts are spilling out
the Tom disappeared for me
this is great okay so the shrimp was
gone for me I have my Invisalign the
letters were there
the letters were there okay
I like where this one was oh that's so
funny okay but why did Kura have normal
teeth here you know
I was I wasn't the one to do it it was
yeah
this is a very interesting turn of
events unsharked shark on sharks
do you get things stuck in your teeth a
lot when there's like you know spiky
like that I feel like it's less right
they just fall out a lot oh that's true
okay what's this
yeah
he's naked
not naked
[Music]
I ended up seeing this oh you guys saw
this
yeah
oh my God is he's thinking of you know
about sniffing pants or wearing oh I got
was tacos I drew that's not cute
what happened all I got was a blank Taco
are they thinking of bananas
yeah oh but who's in the back
because I don't have those blame ones
it's alternate you know oh wow this
turned out very interesting started from
champion and ended up with
um
Universe Ina and taco interesting
okay oh
this is
what I said I was like I wouldn't mind
having this after stream such an
innocence
let me explain so the Sunday disappeared
oh
oh no
so I'm scared to click
what did they look at
them
[Music]
he does look like a salary okay and then
what is getting slapped I only had
something like a butt left over there
so I drew
oh nice
who would slap her butt and Guru and the
last second said
I thought it was like a really buff
shoulder
no it's her bun
okay I see it now I see it now
you got to pull it across a masterpiece
yes yes okay thank you thank you next
okay what the Cali start with
for a second
okay and I turned into a burger
left it was missing the parts in the
middle so
Burger fingers
squished blue gave him stupid
[Music]
I couldn't match the colors
from the stupid juice everyone
[Laughter]
[Music]
write a narrative using only the
previous sentence as a reference oh
okay yeah
very good let's try it
cool fan fiction then baby perfect let's
go wait right let's go Okay no Okay
so if we only see the last sentence
she would start with writing more than
one sentence or
I'm just writing something relatively
simple
okay yeah
[Music]
oh dude there's a limit I can't think of
anything
um excuse me
um there's a time limit
come on
I hope you guys are
writing something
very interesting let's go to the phone
okay I guess this is uh yeah
there's a really small limit we can't
write that much yeah yeah okay I see how
it is I like this problem oh okay
um uh
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
he I think I got something
okay
yeah yeah
okay okay okay right
oh
[Music]
um um um
okay okay
[Laughter]
this is cute I like this it's like Mad
Libs on Craig yeah yeah and speed run
Mad Libs
oh
[Music]
um
it smells smugly schmug ly
smug ah
okay you gotta finish it with an opening
right yeah more or less because the last
one is closing this is probably the last
one right yeah this is the last one
I think so focused
uh
okay I have a good ending for this one
thank you for giving me a good opening
for a good ending ending
uh
okay okay
okay okay okay okay
shall we like have everybody read their
sentence
yeah yeah narrate Your Own Story okay
well we'll marry our own story
hey okay so interesting my problem the
first yeah was Bubba walks into a bar
right
oh yeah I followed it up with and finds
a pretty cat called chunkers she wants
to flirt oh
and then we'll wait a second remember
she has five children and is it a loving
marriage
[Laughter]
so Baba didn't get the chick didn't get
the girl you got the cashier you're
charged
to be continued okay okay next problem
mama said
um a rainy day at the whole live office
the door opens and and
Amelia runs slipping them
[Laughter]
immediate violence and then
but she managed to strike a post with
the action camera
it's basically we're writing the script
for the next look
when checking the photo they realized
she wasn't shown on it oh she's a
vampire yeah I couldn't write more oh
brainstem
that kind of works out like a smell you
know like Amy has blonde hair male
simple has blonde hair it looks like
Adam is the one slipping but it's
actually male simple oh okay
right here
it makes sense that this happened
okay okay next story
said
Tuesday good I woke up after a terrible
dream but she she
couldn't remember if she brushed her
teeth or not her mouth her mouth
um
I was wide open when all of a sudden
[Music]
[Laughter]
Crown is in the room okay
first time she said and
and
proceeded to fly off until the end of
time
wow so she left huh
[Laughter]
this is just like the chat just walks in
it's just like
first time
girls still still wondering if she
brushed her teeth or nothing
[Music]
you can't forget man a confusing morning
for everybody involved it could also see
another another one of those holographic
silver nothing makes sense like yeah
they won't expect her their next move
kind of thing
all right next story next story is
prompt says wow suddenly
I love how I uh uh wrote about you but
you wrote about me
fryer
chicken fried I ran after him but he
turned around
oh my God
at her and said actually I'm your go and
flu
no you're not and then everyone clapped
because you flew way into the sun
[Music]
me too of course
he needs an Onsen vacation but since
can't be employed jumped out of the
fryer yeah who put him there it wasn't
me it wasn't me it wasn't you
[Music]
it will also who says it's really Yago
this this chicken is delusional I'm
telling you I have to deal with him so
many times maybe that's why they were in
the fryer it's the correctional right
yeah yeah okay he's a bit crazy sorry
excuse him please it's okay flew into
the sun
all right he's probably coming back
someday okay yes
last one
kfp is a popular topic
one chicken spontaneously combusted
drama it's impossible
oh this this sentence gives no context
so this is where my my turn around to
help until suddenly until suddenly
asked
oh wow okay so yeah this makes
absolutely no sense
your life of course it was a yes I mean
it might happen you never know yeah but
who is he asking I thought there was
someone there probably he's asking the
champion boy yeah maybe he's asking the
Flames like there will be a flame Flame
mental YouTubers
I was still there so maybe I'm there
watching the chickens combusting and the
usual room a flame me losing everything
that I built so far and then Yago shows
up and he's like okay I see you're
losing everything right now wanna join
whole life whoa is this your origin
story this
origin story
oh that was pretty fun yes
yes this is good you know the Hologram
like staff should just like play Karthik
film The storyboard this is how this is
maybe that's how they do it maybe maybe
that's how they do it
should we try another one of them yeah
we did that one
you treat it together
oh um
[Music]
delete the sketch let's see let's see
how I recommend put this chat you guys
are gonna see us play
lots of game one animation
animation yeah I think we could yeah the
foundation takes time it'll be perfect
anyways oh yeah all right let's go
animation
what
do we start okay yeah okay it's hard
cat spit out some ideas come on yeah
come on ideas ideas
poke chat poke poke oh I have a cute
idea
okay I'm getting an idea okay
okay uh uh uh okay oh no there's no fill
bucket okay
there isn't nope oh maybe not an
animated one yeah yeah
oh why wouldn't that make things easier
it would
sure
concentration time has begun once again
yeah animating is
once the first piece was done I think it
gets easier if you just have to add on
to others you just have to be creative
you know yeah just a little bit of
movement like the important thing with
the animation mode is that once you
start adding to others it doesn't have
to be a big change just a slight one to
make the animations move
true
I'm pretty sure there was like an option
to like direct people to how to
like Adam eat it but I don't know how to
do that we can be more creative
oh God there's not much time left oh boy
yeah like a third
oh
I'm curious you hate me
uh clock
wack
[Music]
do your best you can do it
no no no all right I think I'm finished
with mine
I'm not ready
uh excuse me all right so that's the
best I can do does someone sneeze no no
no no no
okay I guess it's okay
okay
last seconds This is complicated okay
maybe that's mine
oh my goodness what's happening what
what's happening hold on
this is
okay I see
bring some motion Into The Locomotion
oh yeah does it give you it it gives you
like color choices from who like the
person who used it before yeah
that's cool
and like the brush like size too which
is nice to match it up
oh man
this is kind of tough yeah a little bit
okay I believe in you guys
we can do it it'll turn out
marvelously yes
I feel bad sorry y'all with a mouse
it's okay we used to dry with masks yeah
okay okay
Pros
this one was super easy I'm done with it
oh really yeah yeah
[Music]
um
okay okay nice I think I'm done too
oh there's not much time
and then before I add
oh
a little bit of time
oh no oh boy
one two three four five okay
it'll be worth it in the end right yeah
definitely it's gonna look like a
masterpiece okay
what the hell oh God
this is cute ah
okay
[Music]
I hope I am
interpreting it correctly
this is three out of five right
[Music]
I'm trying I'm trying concentrating
everybody drawing at light speed
for real
yeah
this was uncolored but I'll add some
color just so people know who this is
I don't know if this is
it's cool it sounds okay
less than half okay
man
I don't know how to animate this
happening all right
you got this
what are you girls up to what are you
drawing huh I can't wait to see your
secret artwork
oh God I'm not gonna finish
[Music]
ones are often the best ones
hydrate
I was done early yeah I was done early
oh you're the other one
and there was one with a lot it was very
difficult
I can't finish the time
okay
oh it's so cute oh
dance dance
all right
oh sweet is it only gonna be five frames
I guess yeah yeah I saw a short
animation I see a drawing with the mouse
was probably
not the best for animation but it's fine
why why don't don't you have your tablet
right next to you why do you choose not
to draw it's like out of the way so it's
kind of a
into place
understandable
oh this is cute
this is cute yeah
super cute
not as cute as all of you oh
we are cute aren't we
chat chat what do you guys think we're
pretty cute
we're like top-notch level cuteness
yeah a little bit yeah all right I
finished mine
done less than half time left ah
[Music]
uh I'm excited these have all looked
good so far yeah
what everyone says
what's the short form for Industries
like the what's the oh like the federal
investigation FBI FBI maybe just i-n-d
or I would I don't know actually maybe
chat oh ink ink Incorporated
Incorporated okay that works thank you
gotta hurry
okay
[Music]
last one okay
last one
uh what am I supposed to do with this oh
um
help destroying is creeping me out
I know
um I'll keep it simple
it's the last person so it can go all
out no I'm keeping it simple
it'll be good nonetheless I think
if I understand what has happened so far
correctly
and
I am done so no speed
I shall I shall fill the silence then
with some Chit Chat yes
yeah so we have two more collabs to go
and you know another question
what we have it we have more
announcements or something at some point
possibly oh yeah yeah look at the last
one the the other one right that's where
we announced something oh
guys what's your favorite memory of myth
in the last three years I'm not asking
you girls focus on drawing I'm asking
chat
what's what's Chad's favorite memory
with myth in the past three years it has
been free full years isn't that
incredible oh my God yeah let's hear uh
uh ttrpg I think it's our what RPG means
that was cute oh many TT RPGs I'm
wrestling the arm wrestling incident I'm
glad so many people like the ctrpg it
was fun then
it's nice that we did that together
um
oh everything
first time you've all met yeah that was
like this one one time where we all like
maybe you know me yeah we met before but
there were times where we finally oh yes
yeah
that was a really that was a special
time
all right
it is time all right congratulations
let's go it's a top-notch anime brought
to you by Hollow myth okay I started off
with crony my girl oh nice and simple
yeah
and then um
instead of instead of flying she's
flipping I was thinking she might be
fine but I decided to make her fly away
and then she's she's flying away
yes
okay okay
all right now we see the entire
animation
yeah I know yeah it's like reverse I
think it's a bit late yeah but
it's okay it's like a camera pen you
know it pans over
Studios
all right very good very good
very good all right next we started
they say she we haven't seen her since
oh this is
I'm supposed to be good at throwing
something yeah Oh I thought it was a
cookie oh
just use the feet and they look so cute
though
she's more free
[Applause]
yeah it does look like a My Little Pony
okay
the horror the little curse but I was
minding her own business when suddenly a
foot appears she wanted to become
friends but turns out it was too stinky
too stinky too stinky that was cute
though yeah all right it's a good one
yeah yeah okay oh I wanted to do
something interesting
I wanted to start this fishing scene
yeah
you girls are so cute so good I want to
say so good at escalating this oh my God
the finale
this one turned out really good
so cute I loved it on one yeah
can you fish I've never been I don't
know we need to fish in Minecraft
I think it's fun
[Applause]
that's my favorite so far okay just move
next we have
oh no it was you
oh yeah so it was huge it was you you
should have known all right shake that
booty
twerk it Twerk it oh yeah
okay he's dancing
oh that's a little dance
that's cute
[Laughter]
it kind of works though I like it I like
it yeah yeah it almost looks like he's
doing a flip
somehow yeah oh wow like when it's
looping those it looks like it's saying
hi and then like it turns around yeah
[Music]
drive a lot
that was easy to okay we knew what to do
yeah everyone was dancing it wasn't up
to interpretation more dance
more dance
lots of action yeah oh yeah
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
um I guess I can do like a very quick
shout out uh I have a merch too oh look
oh it's not the full picture I think
it's automatic I forget slippers oh
there it goes there you go wow
rubber mat keychain slippers
bonus wow super cool
I love it but yeah we still have two two
more collabs to go oh my goodness
exciting and while we're here at the
topic of flippers um we also only have
two more myth members who need to bring
out uh slipper merchandise
but for the future if you're thinking
about what merch to do you know you know
people could collect all the miff
slippers if you would chime in to make
moves yeah
we must move on to the next year lab
which is going to be on Goomba's Channel
now everyone head over there and wait
for us to come back