[Music]
[Applause]
it
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
OT
feel it R through me
[Music]
me
feel it
R feel it like me
[Music]
yeah e
uh
uh KY
rcky hey I forgot looping dad that's
okay hello welcome
[Music]
everybody how y'all doing it's we're
still alive yeah we're still
alive alive I'm just saying we're we're
still alive like you know oh yeah that's
just my greeting I'm just like are you
guys miraculously preserve today M
preserve what a fancy way of saying that
learn from 16 they're like you're Mascus
preserve oh yeah that sounds like
something they'd say super British like
them little crusty but we're
miraculously preserved like a bog
body
yeah girls are speaking in riddles to
me should we introduce ourselves yeah
let's start from the top can we who are
you
people I am
the Christmas p
hi hi everybody oh I guess dang it I'm
so Rusty at this it's been so long me
and a song it's me Mory kipy H live
English myths hardworking Grim Reaper
song singer writer song mus I stream too
hey everybody what's going on hope you
guys are doing well and I'm going to be
speaking in a pretty low voice because
I'm sleepy I'm sleepy it's very it's
early in Japan okay that's fine I I'm
excited to be here for this exciting
event where we play a game that I'm not
very good but I'll do my best to be
helpful
so
Y no Cy I think you'll be fine because
you have in the past one year I would
say definitely improved with Minecraft
so I have been trying my best we'll see
what happens yeah I'll nice to meet you
oh yeah nice to meet
you K
op okay who's the one with mustache I
thought this was girls only yeah what
the heck man out here this is it's not a
real mustache guys okay come on is
marshmallow is that looks like is
relative I'm Watson Amelia actually not
yeah you guys call me Watson
today
Watson h number one detective H myth
English
hello she real you're
Rik Minecraft yay I picked some
mushrooms from my lawn today and I had
to think of you did you eat them no I
didn't they're not edible and I I hate
mushrooms anyway what there's a very
specific way you got to do it I hear
don't take things and put them in your
mouth everyone yeah put them in a
blender put it on your pizza randomly
when it comes to mushrooms you take a
picture you ask Google they're edible
and if Google says no Then you don't eat
them or you give them to wo buto must
try all can we get the
[Music]
please I missed him so much that little
mushroom
okay I guess I knew who you were
oopsie
hello introduce yourself I I I got a I
caught a little dolphin here
Batman I caught a dolphin you know know
Batman you know what I'm going to do to
that
thing wait why is cie laughing so
much I'm a G and I'm so excited to be in
Minecraft today with my
buddy yay Minecraft with mcraft yeah
mft wait so what was that a meme what
why why was she why was Cali laughing so
much at what you were saying cuz I'm so
funny right super funny really good in
Joker impression it was a joker
impression yeah yeah she said the Batman
Jer says oh I had no
idea okay sorry I'm I'm not keeping up
with you girls it seems I'll send a you
later don't worry about it
[Music]
okay she knows who I
am of H of
Englishman I'm I'm here to be the King
of the Hill that's what this this uh
this one block thing is about right we
we conquered the one block standing push
each other off one standing
no no te ladies te if anything we hold
hands so that we don't fall together
hold stream yeah well we've been
together for what almost four years now
I mean why not yeah almost half a decade
is it okay I guess I guess cat won't
mind yeah we can hold hands together
it's allowed after almost four years I
think we have permission to hold hands
hand holding perms okay
okay and then uh last but not least I'm
not part of that nice color strip over
there unfortunately who's the orange
lady over there in the
corner have no space but yeah I'm Wawa I
I had the idea for this but I never
played one block before so I want GAA to
explain it to us because just yesterday
I found out thanks to my viewers that
you actually already played one block
before I already played some not a good
too I didn't even remember I did that
but no bed one there's one block to rule
them all that's all I know no give us a
wrong explanation teach making you give
a presentation shut up I mean what yes
how do how do we get more
blocks think really hard I don't know
you hit the block the one block that
you're standing on always
responds
it'sa yeah it'sa oh what what I mean oh
spoilers
oh okay wait so I'll I'll try um
basically we get one block at a time it
can be any kind of block uh we start
building ourselves a platform in the
beginning it's kind of like we're on one
block I suppose that's why we didn't
enter the world yet yeah cuz I thought
if we all enter at once we might fall
off immediately and that is good
streaming content we we want to I've
seen the smok play through I'm not going
to fall off put it in the YouTube short
yes and so yeah we're going to start
building everything at some point we'll
have access to stuff like the never um
diamonds yeah I guess diamonds but the
end goal is to get ready for an ender
dragon fight which will be the second
time no actually I mean
third but for only myth it will be the
second time that we take down the Ender
Dragon right wait do you stand on one
block the whole time no not the whole
time you can you can build up basically
one block what happens is that there's
different biomes and and different
basically different levels you if every
time you you know mine the block you get
closer to the next level which is like
another biome and stuff and then you
keep going and going and going until you
get to the Ender Dron
gate I remember but I think the Ender
the Ender the never and the end both of
those are like normal you make a portal
you enter and that's like normal you
don't stand on one block or so from what
I you can build on From the Block but
the block you mine is always the same
one the base
block shine around it I guess we can
yeah yeah but the safety department
might have a word with us
OA
uncertified so okay well I guess we can
get ready to enter I you all should we
go one by one because this kind of
scares me that we fall off we go all on
one debut order I I'll go first cuz I'm
the camera okay okay true enough and
just general note for all the viewers
right now this stream is as it's the
beginning and all that and to keep it
organized and you know it's on only this
POV but from now on my voice is a little
bit low really oh God I'm loud
apparently for once damn it I've been
trying turn me down a little bit I've
been
trying a lower just turn me down on
Discord it's fine you guys don't have to
hear me but I also generally lower the
everybody's uh audio a little bit so
that mine gets balanced out cuz mine is
already at Max actually y oh wait
actually I can do a little bit how about
this is it better how how is this just I
I I heightened it by 2 DB
Diel
okay stop it stop okay so what I was
saying yeah so from after this stream
onwards there will be you know however
many povs if there's two people
streaming at once you know then
hopefully we'll have two povs or just
one when somebody joins somebody else's
stream or so um but yeah there'll be
more povs after that uh and just keep an
eye out we might be streaming at any
given time just follow
us yes be ready keep up with the Lord
cuz cie cie already has a reservation up
for a stream afterward I I might move it
if no one else is
playing be solo car no going to get to
the portal next time we log on yeah I
finished the game for you ladies sorry
game no don't don't go too far you know
without us especially if you're playing
alone maybe don't go too far with
progress remember to build in a straight
line I remember to build no don't
don't please okay dig straightforward
ladies let's I'm going to go in three
okay two I hope it works I hope it works
let's
go what gov
let me check if it's safe okay uh uh uh
okay I think it's safe but I think we
can't com H coming in hot
hot all right so I'm I'm not going hey
know when you do that I
off both of you Scoundrels away
Scoundrels who pushed me not me I'd
never do that bro bro
wait wait stop stop me i' never do that
we have only two other free recovery
kits
left we no pushing pushing okay wait
what's a recovery kit like I don't know
I honestly don't know I think it's the
the Box the pickaxe that you get oh
ladies L ladies
ladies consider wait which one is
it oh chest appeared oh o no not not
flower you you can mine the chest right
someone make a
chest yeah I guesso crafting table is
the chest the one that has to be mined
now I'm not sure yeah you have oh wait
important okay flat who took
my
couple oh it's okay wait I have like I
have
crazy CF
tables there are a lot of them well
right now this angle might be good wait
there's an instruction guys chest can
also appear yeah yeah that's uh the
mining block
no careful you gra it now you have a
chest
oh I can put the chest on top of no this
not what I wanted let's make a platform
first of all okay yeah dirt is fine
right dirt is fine everything is useful
there 10 phes guys
10 I made clay
so we need to put I think we should Mark
where the uh the block is Right
different blocks and mobs will
spawn lat very rare blocks oh not so
fast I oh my God it's been a while oh
whoops I made a pickaxe who wants it
have a pickaxe got free pies I'm good
okay never mind yeah well should I have
oh should I have made planks oopsy
we'll get a lot of blocks probably oh I
have a chest wow
there's one apple for five of us good
luck with that sharing the food sharing
is
Clay can make
bricks what can make what oh put your
items into yeah okay wow we got a chest
another one nice no monsters are going
to spawn right cuz it's turning night
make a torch they might spawn I mean
they got to spawn but do they Spawn from
the block or from elsewhere is the
question we covered it cuz there's like
a certain radius around a player where
monsters don't spawn oh really okay damn
we got pumpkins pumpkins are good for oh
[Laughter]
whoopies
pumes food storage or something pump
yeah one one pumpkin is in this chest
over here if you're hungry if you're
really hungry iess totally start a farm
already I
think kill it
no Karma I guess that's what I get the
one food source you know we got to keep
it
[Music]
safe sorry you I just saw the meat and
o oh it says how many blocks we've mined
oh wait why is it turning black
watermelon
watermelon why is it turning black what
there was like scary black lines coming
out of it what does that
mean melons yeah melons I got lots and
lots of
watermelon let's go make sure to put
items in the chest cuz if you fall we
lose all the items yeah as I just
realized from a moment
ago uh are we going to organize the
chest ladies cuz I just feel how get
itch under my skin when things aren't or
organize it yeah you
can okay this one's got food and this is
materials why can't that's strange
opening is e it's not opening though
crafting section oh that's a nice floor
pattern actually I'm
digging keep digging bring us reason
that I can't open the chest I
wonder do they belong to someone I can
open that's we oh hello cow sorry I'm a
bit of a dum now cow we got a cow
oh we got to make a safe environment for
our
animals yeah make like a farm or
something so they don't get attacked
yeah I was going to say maybe we should
make a farm and then if we start farming
we can feed them and then you know
multiple yes yes yes we have seeds too
so I'll put the seeds in the bottom row
so we can grow watermelon yeah how
water maybe water will also be a
buckets buckets okay can find iron and
then like make a bucket or like can make
a Collen and then hope that it rains or
something that's all chicken chicken we
got the first chicken finally the first
kfp Branch can be opened is this how the
world was
made first there was a chig we start
growing trees too this is how it all
begins with five cute girls on one block
I knew it organize the chests I'm going
to put another chest up too and then
this one will be something different Aly
organizational Mor I have to or else I
start to really kind of go crazy a
little bit just organizing I'm just
thinking I have one brain cell and I'll
use that to early on early on right so
why does it count how many blocks we
have does it high score oh some you dig
I
think how many you have in your
inventory cuz I have two wow big we're
getting big [\h__\h] let's
go exponential growth Little Island
exp ke by the way replace the floor I
think maybe you don't know you maybe you
know by now just just so you know e that
so that you don't fall down maybe press
um shift as much as you can actually
that's the reason why I did not die once
in the
beginning ena's hoarding all the blocks
Ena you're hoarding all the blocks
no that's how many I I
destroyed I don't own that many blocks I
only have like
two like nine soils okay but but I'mma
feel free or everybody else continue to
use me as as like a teacher kind of um
person punching bag yeah okay no not as
a punching
bag wa who just punched a cow with the
intention to punch me I was I'm going to
expand a little bit further this way it
was
me okay what flowers I got to eat tulips
for dinner a salad well with flowers we
can dye things which will be totally
useful right cuz I want to got sheep C
Cosmetics basically we got two sheep
let's have let's have organize this our
real a little organize
it cramp here passing through
Pass got a couple sheep yay it's getting
fluffy we can make beds with their wool
we just need some have we ever gotten an
iron block yet or something like that no
I haven't seen any cuz for shears we we
need iron 100% right we we can't make it
with anything
else we need that torches I really want
some coal personally that's what I'm
looking forward to or is it too early to
get
[Music]
iron you got to keep digging guys
iron iron I say iron and I say biomi and
by all means complain if you want about
about my
biomi well it's just incorrect you
should fix
that
oh you my pronunciation
support it when it's correct
biom bom bomi you know I I've been made
aware that I've been saying it wrong but
I've thought I'll stick with it because
it's cuter to say biom okay I will say
aler
Al kicky a
[Music]
beer well do you even know how to say it
correctly I'll beer Z No Maybe I don't
even know anyone you're just pretending
to say it wrong do you know how to say
biome correctly yeah biome so you're
choosing to be in correct yes but for
iron for iron I genuinely can't say it
correctly iron iron o
cows there's so many creatures here iron
iron like I earn money I earn iron
iron I don't think these are good
locations for m
I earn money iron oh my go where you
running where are you running
to I I yeah I run I run I run I am
running I running can we build like a a
farm or something like a yeah farm would
be good we can make fences uh yeah yeah
fences and stuff so the cows don't get
in my way and I'm moving the chest don't
worry I just have all of our inventory
in my hands right now don't push me I'll
make I'll make fence stink
alent gift an empty map almond I got a
water don't push me wait is this the is
this the last thing before the next
level oh we're upgrading guys what where
did this where did the T I got him I got
him don't worry I'm putting everything
I'm
many the world's on the belly uhoh guys
we we really need to uh get stuff made h
I'm going
to I'm working on on fence wait wait
wait let's let's uh let's make like
weapons and stuff for the monsters just
in case yes swords sorry can I be hole
digger what where are you digging a hole
into the block hole what did I make what
did I just
do yeah yeah go for it Grandpa I'm tired
of digging blocks that's want make a did
I just make
[\h__\h] move cow or I'll kill you that
works oh wow that's pretty violent I
will who would like a sword I can make a
couple swords oh yeah please do all
right I just made two swords oh man I
need a
pickaxe okay get
some
oh maybe like a all right I'm going to
put a sword got a big does anybody have
like hay or so to get the
animals into the okay can you like grass
or grass seeds I don't
know got no grass I can also plant some
trees too yeah plant some trees that's a
great idea we should have area I'm going
to start destroying the environment here
here here oh sorry
sorry I have
several
here here it's under it already I'm
trying the Sheep e it oh you this is my
last one I I gave out four this concrete
one what
the next to the flower okay yeah thank
you okay let's see oh nice bu trees a
fence over this o the Stone Edge
Anga exting I'll go ahead and put a
sword in the bottom of one of these
chests
like a sword what can you replace these
two crafting boxes with something else
please nice I don't I don't I don't have
anything I'm coming up with a with
something it's okay I'll put something
there can you also I have Cobblestone
can somebody make a oh an oven you have
Cobblestone that was my single
Cobblestone actually does anybody have
any more wood
uh no not really yeah I can put W wood
in the left chest cuz we should make a
cobblestone big
a right I actually don't we can yeah
stone pickaxe well we need an oven to
cook the stone first yes we can do
torches I have three cobblestones if you
need I'll put it in the chest I'll put I
will join you I have I'll create an oven
really quick push ladies progress
progress push iron iron
iron yes let's go iron okay it's
starting to show up so that's a good
sign we should make shears oh oh oh
let's go move maybe the farm we should
also make some torches too just in case
Tor yeah iron got an egg egg uh what's
the configur oh that's like oven go back
go back wait are we not getting the iron
cuz we don't have stone or did you guys
get it okay we should make we should
make the stone pickaxe okay I made a
furnace ladies um let's put it where the
animals are yeah the cows are so
heavy I can't push him in push him in
push him in oh you oh you better oh
maybe because you're not shifting what's
with this door did I so we can we can
probably get in but they can't get out
okay I guess that works I I accidentally
put it like that but yeah P going to
kill me okay pig follow me hey fell
[Music]
caveo you're in the way you're in the
way I was your first pleas ladies please
inside here
uh yeah pig is in the way now how about
how about I build a little little
farming section here oh yeah goodidea
know the farmer I I knew that farming
was your calling
damn it wonder what do we have a shovel
does it matter I I'll make
[Music]
one what in the what in the what is that
milk milk endless food
source
[Music]
C fall get in get in can it get in for
that gate or do we have to open it wait
we can oh does this work oh yeah that
works let's go okay hopefully no creeper
blows it
up oh man protect protect the animals at
all cost oh they're very important do we
have some more
blocks lots of
stone dire gold gold is the gold our
first gold we have roet
nice nice nice nice wait why are we
cooking
Cobblestone why are we cooking
Cobblestone we really don't need to cook
Cobblestone do we why why are we wasting
coal and cooking Cobblestone no it makes
makes ni Stone but we don't need for
reason to make a stone pickaxe we can do
that without you ain't got to cook it to
make it what it's okay call Stones I'm
sorry fcy St cook the iron let's cook
the who has iron
iron uh I've got IR ore but it's not I
have one iron
ore
oh oh sorry I ruined the chest
organization my bad you're just giving
Callie something to do that's good yeah
she she wants to feel useful I'm sure
hey don't patronize me Kiara SC I'll
beat you up fight fight
fight a spider don't go out don't go out
get back in get back in get back where
are you going Harvest its organs make
sure that you harvest its organs not
this is not a copi vamus Empire collab
get out of here get back get back where
you belong okay chest
collected yay we got feathers we got
string okay let me know if someone has
if someone has another water
bucket a water bucket nothing yet
no so with this iron ore what do we need
uh to use on it in order to collect the
actual iron from it cuz right now it's
just ore that we've collected free range
wait what we have iron or blocks that
we're colle in the oven oh the whole
block yes ma'am oie
dogy uh let's see okay well it's closed
off now it's only belongs to the red cow
now well I'll
I'll keep on watching you guys for a
little bit how's it going we can also
use wood can't we in the furnace For
What in the furnace yeah burning things
yeah do we need all these cows cuz it's
just no kill
them freaking kill them just don't let
them fall
off how come they got out weren they
they Wen they in here I'm just trying to
put them back in like they all escaped
escap except for the red cow
how I want them back
[Music]
in okay okay nobody died it could have
been so much worse yeah the cows are
like yo what was that they're
chilling
nice no not maybe we shouldn't built the
farm so close to the uh the spa true
well this is temporary temporary
maybe this one is just for the cows in
particular I don't
know oh what
this are you guys finding cool stuff
yeah should we put um something around
the block to like Mark it like hey this
is the block yeah yeah yeah
no why' you hit it in you got to hit it
off oh red almost died
[Music]
nice fixing but yeah should we work on
moving the cows and stuff before getting
any new blocks maybe per that's a good
idea all right let's oh or what we can
do is like we
can block off the so that like if a
creeper spawns it doesn't see us so we
can kill it yeah oh yeah we can make a
house around the building block per not
really a house just like just like like
a little pillar I guess mhm mhm sure
sounds good I'll start building around
this
area I push this back in get
in get in Oh yay iron guys we have seven
irons I'm putting them in the chest
wow good
job yay all right cow is in stop pushing
in
[Music]
there the Sheep are in the way I'm going
to kill
him no no please he's innocent they're
fluffy they're too fluffy to be
killed yeah let me try to move it move
move Yum Yum Yum Yum
Yum what else can we cook torches even
really help at this point my lunch break
is over torches yes okay you think it'll
be useful yeah for sure torches are
always useful it's the it's the one in
the middle of the hole Oh wrong hole
sorry okay it happens
[Music]
what what oh I that was the wrong one
too what do you mean was this cender
one it's not that one oh maybe I buil it
too close which one is it I want a mine
too what's it which one is it is it this
one what's it oh that one okay sorry
I'll fix it
making like a little surrounding thingy
what if we extended a little bit behind
where the cows are right now and moved
the pen they like me more than the
carrot maybe it's cuz your head is
orange I'm going to try and
do yeah what do they normally eat in
Minecraft I thought it was carrots
carrots that's for horses no pigs would
eat it but they don't know how uh
probably they surely would eat at IRL
wait can you move for just a second let
me move all right I like oh it's hey
oh it is carrots right no yeah no they
CH says it's also carrots for pigs I was
right pigs and or not pigs uh carrots
and potatoes can you ride click them
with the carrot does that work on them
potatoes Well I this is the thing only
carrot so I don't want to I don't want
to use it on them oh oh I hear zombie
nice cont
flesh I don't know how to make it so
that creepers can't see us I think uh
needs like an extra block or something
somewhere maybe glass I mean glass work
no no you can just you can just block
off the thing okay well I guess it
depends cuz like if like a something
useful spawns might like maybe yeah yeah
yeah and then we can just stand on this
side they say a whole block above really
maybe someone should build an iron sword
we can pass it between who's the block
Digger mhm oh nice idea oh be
nice wow we start
moving this way or trap doors could work
too
actually wait why is she walking up
there cow
p
[Music]
p oh a mushroom cow cow mushroom another
one wow we've been blessed free him
blessed the
cow thank you for your offerings lovely
cow all we need is some some
bowls maybe I have a bowl you have a
bowl One Bowl One Bowl of mushroom stew
ooh okay I'm I want to make my own
bowl Iron I'm going to take one iron
iron iron iron iron iron iron iron iron
like Iron Man like Iron Man robon Man
Iron Iron
Man how how to make
Bowl not a bow a bowl okay I made the
bowl what did I say bowl
wrong no way dunked
[Music]
him wait who's digging with me is that
I am yo let's go but we're not why are
we not losing any appetite thingy H I
was going to say it's interesting
because we're not running I know cuz
you're not doing anything that is
true three blocks I see you there's no
space for digging y'all are
occupying block block hello my good
shall I make quick question you guys
shall I make an iron sword or an iron
pickaxe which is more important pickaxe
right yeah pickax
yeah pickaxe oh want to fight go down we
can make a sword as well we have let's
have a a vote all in favor of a sword
say I actually make an axe oh okay there
you go do an ax it's the cuz you can use
it for the trees and it does more single
Target damage
hold on a sec let me all right I'll I'll
finish making it really quick hold on a
sec hold on Mouse hey
Mouse hey Mouse okay all right omegan
next see oh B big
[Music]
brain oh but what about diamonds coming
up in the next face
maybe I think we still all
way okay guys so we're going to I'm
going to make a special chest for tools
and we can all share
it
[Music]
okay
chest wait dunan wait dun dunk him dun
him dunk him dun him DK him make him
regret
living you are not part of me you must
die get him out of here nice this is a
five people collab not six exactly
I all right I got War somebody cannot
sit with us right you can sit with us
piggy yeah you can sit with
us okay what the heck are we going to do
with all this clay give us some bgm you
guys want bgm and all this chaos okay
I'll I'll find you some bgm simple get
rid of a little silence are we we love
silence I love silence silence is scary
why the
voices just drown them
out I'll do I'll put on bgm for Amit
even though she will not be able to hear
it oh thank you anything for
you what about
[Music]
this okay you guys hear this I mean chat
can you hear
that oh
a friend here I
am no bgm is better but do you guys also
want to vote chat do you also want to
vote just like US
democracy yo who's the mayor
BG yes
no I think generally cuz we're five
people there's no need for PGM but I'll
leave it up to the chat to vote in a
democratic matter put some R time jazz
on
[Music]
70% don't want bgm oh it's getting lower
just bring your own bgm guys yeah bring
your own
bgm yeah that's that's a big majority
against
bgm if you want some you can get your
own bring your own bgm to
workday yeah I'm listening to what are
you guys listening to right now everyone
everyone I was say except k come on
listening to
us I'm listening to a 7 minute Loop of
Yoshi Island UK G I love Yoshi Island
that's such a good idea I'm going to
listen to that too nice choice I love
Yoshi Island hey you're spider speeder
speed ooh escaped he escaped him take it
down take it down I have no weapon Hur
my friend to me I got you w did it drop
something
SPID okay ooh this is looking very
organized
wow yeah I'm really trying my hardest o
iron my pickaxe is going to break broke
he's gone maybe we should make an iron
pickaxe now cuz we have enough iron
would you guys like to make an iron
pickaxe yes you can share among okay
cool go make one can I mine a little bit
too I have blocks on my record Captain
get in there no how dare you even
suggest that uh do we have another stone
pickaxe or
so I'll put an iron one in there the
cameraman the cameraman never
participates okay you should probably
grow
tree yeah good idea we I planted them
but they just haven't been growing I
don't know if I need to do anything else
they need to be surrounded by like three
blocks of dirt I think 3
by3
yeah hey yo does not work with diorite
oh no I need sticks okay I'll just
extend more there are some sticks in
there I got it I got it
pickaxe it has to be Cobblestone it
doesn't work with Dior ride a y c
Stone L why put it back in why not
thanks
nope move
move py
I'll make another wooden one let's go
all right wouldn't it would it save
blocks to go in a straight line
anyway but you mean like one I don't
know I'm just going to go forward like
uh with I don't
know I'm mining but actually oh another
cow maybe I really shouldn't be mining
cuz then all all the chat will see is
this corner of blocks so okay is that
your plot all along mine I love Mining
and then I'll mine and then I'll
organize it okay yeah I'm putting my
pickaxe back to the
chest and I'll Ober the tree grew what
are you doing we did it nice nice nice
touching the Rocks big news touching the
Rocks we got more
trees I'm making a ton of um very
productive I like rocks oh yeah what
have you done seven blocks McGee I'm the
cameraman I'm the
cameraman that's just like
just I
made so that I don't have to dig no I've
made I've made a fence for some cows
some of them we got so many
R you put the whole stream together
you're allowed to be cameraman y don't
worry about it y now I'm going to mine I
want to mine mine mine mine in there
another hit it a little bit Yeah I hit
it yeah M cow thank you
let's mine can we get meat from the red
cows too I think they just dropped
mushrooms no oh mushroom I want to test
it we have too many of you guys do you
guys think I deserve a sweet treat I'm
trying to say I don't but I think I do
it dropped me oh what's that upgrading
in 18 seconds y also I got bone what
else do I have yum yum yum I got ice
blocks oh we got ice oh ice blocks I got
two ice blocks I'll put them
but I want to I want to see thing in oh
yeah my ice
block wow
stone stone who I get it now I
understand W oh it's gravel snow
biome snow oh snow I want to make a
snowy area
wow wow
beautiful is it just going to be snow
forever now until the next phase
happy oh gravel is
back gravel and Ice gravel and oh that's
a Beau axe for that right yeah okay
maybe making a wooden axe or something
might be a nice
idea what what wood was that dark oak
log
nice that's nice right I'll put the ice
in here
too I don't know what we can use it for
but I'll leave it to you guys now it's
good to just keep in all the materials
that we don't need now we might need it
later in some way
[Music]
so oh shovel yeah a shovel would be good
for the
snow yeah I made a shovel oh nice all
right all right you're doing well what's
happening over there you you really are
we are we making another path to
Atlantis or
what room that would be pretty fun not
going to lie nostalgia
wait why put a a water feature here or
we could like you really just doing one
line is this is there like an actual
reason for making it in one line
or I it'll feel like we're going
somewhere you know like oh like this
part is gaville like over here welcome
to
[Music]
gille okay right I I'll I think for now
the line is very nice depends on how
long it will get oh you'll you'll allow
it right I'll I'll let it slide for now
I do what I
want I'm as dangerous I'm as out of
control can't be T get her on a
leash leash leash oh leashes leashes are
hard to get by that would be I'm hoping
for a chest true M chest would really
help it's a
doggy oh he's no he's he's killing the
Sheep he's I killed him cuz he killed a
sheep oh my God
unacceptable bro but I got
a rest in peace BTO I can't get out
Balto he lived for 2 seconds but we
loved him like a
brotherto can somebody put me to work I
don't know know what to do please get
out of the
way can I do something
else CRA things oh the tree go maybe go
extend on the other side where the cows
are okay oh yeah I did extend that area
back so we could move the pasture a
little bit farther away from the main
block but yeah that would be nice love
the
animals what are you
doing I lost one oh hello all my smack
you I'll mine lots of iron and then
we'll cook it I'm sure feel like
smacking me in my fever Knight
outfit very smackable outfit is that the
boa one
yeah the liquid one oh no what happened
she lost her Focus I took 38 stone with
[Music]
me I pressed shift I meant
tool let me out be good to have onle
instead of next time ah yeah it's going
to be a different password next
time next time you assume you assume I'm
going to do it again I mean come on
probably think it's a safe
assumption I took a pickaxe with me oh
that's okay was it an iron pickaxe
here's a wood pickaxe no
we're good oh bone meal is really nice
cuz we can get we can get um
[Music]
Whatchamacallit we can get grass and
then we can get seeds and then we can
tame the
cows that's really odd the cows I mined
a bunch of iron blocks and they're not
here did you m it with the yum yum yum
yum oh my God what he's going to kill
also oh no is he okay mind cute they
only H like rabbits I think okay he's
carrying coal it wasn't a bunch of iron
blocks it was like two we didn't lose
too much it's
finey stone pickaxe I have a stone
pickaxe now we're fine new friend new
friend we're fine we're fine we're fine
happy friend need more
iron oh oh ice oh
ice come here ice I we can make a
campfire we can make a
sign yes a sign yes sometimes I just
want want to say hey we have this here
this is what this chest does what is
this
oh labeling is important for
organization terot okay I'm not
going from
the what's it
called what biome do it Mesa biom biome
I feel like I saw something just
now what you see Mom sure
it don't worry about it don't wor oh
there's a chest there's a music disc and
a snowball oh so we can finally get some
natural bgm in
here but we don't have a music player ah
I take it back I'll mind now I've made a
couple weapons here St I'm taking one of
these ice block is the only way to get
water somebody
said oh there two ice blocks in the
T oh you put it next to fire right oh
maybe we'll make a little okay I'll make
a little bowl
two two ice blocks in the
chest excuse me surround ice block by
fire stick was there a rabbit okay did
it die oh yeah that's what you're doing
bow you have the ice did we get it we
spawned a Rabb it and I didn't even see
it it was immediately killed by the fox
we build a bucket with iron we have one
full
bucket that's okay we're about to have
more iron ladies don't worry okay stone
pickaxe now car car come get this on
camera we're melting the ice oh this
never before seen I'm I'm curious the
blog Chad are we doing it right
scientific evolution
for water I'll use the the iron nice
okay melting it's melting is it I can't
said make 2 by two boil boil water
trouble I
am I don't know if we'll use Redstone
but wa what two I'm sure we'll use it
for something said punch it 2 by two
punch it but then how do you capture it
won't that no that'll break it won't it
yeah no we want to melt
it okay here pick wait can we pick it up
with a pickax oh the oh there polar bear
okay he's going to kill our animals
there's a bear as long as there's no
polar bear baby around I guess he'll
stay chill this is the baby bear no that
kind of
small the bigger one is bigger no that
looks pretty big to me that's a big baby
yeah it's a big
baby looks like a it's a baby to me how
cute cotton ball hello I thought it was
are you do we have to make
right click it with a with a bucket or
so I think chat says it needs to be two
by two so we need three more blocks and
then uh I guess for now we'll just leave
it cuz it's not melting anyways so
what's that noise okay something di I'll
sit on it oh the bear is thear is wait
those are really AR dangerous oh oh okay
wait there's two now what the hell is it
yeah is it he don't like you he don't
like you he's targeted he's locked in on
Watson don't
like there it's
dangerous apologize the bear just say
sorry simple K him yes iron oh we got
another ice block push him off the maybe
he wants to hug you who knows
be he does like
you
bye it had a
fish wait we got water water I sitting
on it it
worked nice did you did you put your
feet in this water just yeah is it water
now or wait we need we need a bucket now
we need two if we have a bucket cuz we
have a water bucket right so we can make
infinite water if we have a bucket let's
do it bucket where's the IR I'm going to
cook more iron actually we have a bunch
of iron blocks I we need we need three
right for the
more the
watch nice we're making some good
progress yeah we're so fast with it
we're like rushing through it I mean I
guess five people that'll happen be
careful cuz stuff might spawn if stuff
if like a certain area isn't lit up yeah
okay true let's light them up by the way
I was thinking for any future streams
just so that everybody's always like
kept up to date that we should keep a
diary so that for example if cie and me
were streaming and then a for example
picks up and she has no idea what we did
and what needs to be done maybe we can
make a diary like that you die oh you
say we did this and that can you an ink
well not at the moment but worst case we
can use signs I
guess can just write it in disc like the
it would be it would be so much cuter if
we have like an actual sign somewhere
here like a sign board and then we put
our own signs on top of it and say hey I
did this please continue doing this or
so if you
can yeah okay B on pass
me that would be cute guys I'm going to
make a well a well somewhere o I want to
see I'm going to watch you building
water this water
Bren where should I put it area like a
farming area captured yeah where should
I put it should I put it like right here
yes gold gold not too far away from the
main point I would say wait does anybody
have an iron pickaxe or I can make one
right now I have can I have one oh maybe
I'll put it beside the farming area let
me see I promise I won't jump off the
edge with it I promise oh yeah you sure
about that pink you promise you promise
me yeah all right I'll see I'll think
about it no I'm kidding I'll make you
one hold on a sec I'll make you one
let's see okay know your pants are so
short gold yours too all right G don't
lose this are they short are they pants
still I don't think they're pants right
they're pants they're bua Bloomers wait
I'm hungry I need
food how do you make a bowl you up my I
give you here mushroom St did you pick
up the IR pickax I gave to thank you oh
so sweet I would have made her say
another magic word no I lost my chance
what's the worst thing you would make me
say I have to think about it oh God I
need to think about how yeah we're going
here oh
God it's okay Mercy this time
Mercy goodbye you scrubbed all the
floors in gon then we can talk about
Mercy take him away red stone is that
our first Redstone or did we already get
some I think we got some oh I was hoping
that am would build us some useful
things with red stone I was going to say
Amelia Redstone watch
railroad a railroad down thatth that
you're building
sure AIA tired Watson yeah another
railroad you can build a railroad and
then at the end of it you can build a TT
okay let's go I'm a building
construction company is
back that was legit when I was thinking
about this project I was already
thinking who can take what roll what are
you doing I think it's an underwater guy
is itell is he what is he danger danger
kill him let him out kill him kill
him he's gone but all of a sudden we're
really stinky oh it's trying to be
protected by I think only you have it
yes get some nutrition I'm smelly I've
got a ball chain on
meckle
rle pickle o red
stone yes get that red stone oh call has
shot your Speedy even if I feel like I'm
useless um at least I can mine that's
nice one at least you can W wo wo
another bear oh it's dying fire got
stuck in the it's it's better this way
he on his own
fuma he's he's cool he's cool cool until
he sees you chill he will no longer be
cool don't gr at me buddy I'm just I'm
chilling in my home want
some youa are you building the the well
uh that was the
plan
the what it was the plan but you're
you're still on it right yes it didn't
change
okay W oh no it hurts to see so many
bears dying
stop BL
you is killing him I didn't do anything
GAA if anything GAA was standing right
there so she's the culprit no I'm mining
you could have saved the bear her own
business mining her own business yeah
you know what you could have done you
know what you could have done you know
what you could have done yeah yeah tell
me ladies
ladies oh oh there's ice in there too
yay ice and iron
nuggets I
think just wanted to
for a
moment where should the gold go put it
here there's monsters spawning over
there guys don't go don't go to the end
of the hallway hang on o
creeper kill this
man that is the danger zone look Amed
what you have done what you have
created you said you wanted cont right
yeah go
go bu
okay I'll put a fence there oh the well
is finished beautiful yeah what should I
use to mine Ice by the
way does a normal pickaxe not normal
Stone oh oh well I guess that should
work did you pick it up just now yeah I
did okay cool just making sure I really
don't want to lose
things and one block of ice no
problem okay
I I still have a gate wait wait I have a
gate no
no I don't want to be on this
side here I can
extend block to Wolf no no you can't you
cannot eat them you cannot eat them yeah
bab extendo all berries I want a sword I
want to kill those
enemies uh I have a wooden sword if you
want that that wood
M I'll make I'll make a golden
one should have some weapons in the the
stor I'm going to push those things off
the Edge's going to do it wait you got
to wait for she's going to she's going
to film it it's a shovel oh oh oh wait y
okay if you're going to do it let me
film
you okay say go capture in 4k go taking
a YouTube
Vlog content War oh no oh no oh oh
oh okay skeleton died really fast just
fell off but the SPID is more
resilient
die did you get a drop I need a
bandaid no I'm push them off the
edge your pants please oh my
God I I was just healing
you I need uh make a
y our kiss we're we're still do kiss
after
all I wait
wait from like I don't know two years
ago or so our indirect
one why you going there
again
extendo
oh is this after all still the Atlantis
stream part two extend oh my God the
tunnel tunnel to Atlantis ooh berries
but this time not a tunnel extend
itis must extend can it be healed big
expand I don't think there's a cure what
she
die
wend is the cure not reaching
Atlantis no I get too big what you you
get too big I expand too much damn it oh
I mean oh no
sorry damn I guess this is how we will
lose
GA I'm going to pop on
stream nice
balloon pop on stream yeah that's
cont that's how I'm going out boys I'm
going to pop on stream damn it what are
you doing good creating full blocks
there you it's a pattern right shut up
it's a pattern
no I'm incompetent that's the pattern
did the others die are they alive no I'm
here I'm making a bunch of stone
pickaxes and such to put in the Box okay
we're getting so far they are unloading
from the world yeah for a moment I
thought we had like uh the voice chat
that's um what's it called distance
voice chat I'm just I have one one brain
cell and it's being used to mine this
one block block donation keep mining my
donation to The gur
Foundation feel the gur
expandation
expandation rabbit I thought we were
supposed to stop it not encourage it the
longer the path the bigger the GAA hey
artist please don't draw this I know it
may be tempting
but not this one I think something is
dying it's the polar bear it's all right
they do that
sometimes bur
the sound you can hear
it oh you may have dropped the salmon
amazing salmon find our technician has
created
Next
Generation
technology pretty cool damn she's sced
oh more iron you that okay oh baby she's
sced what are the roles today what are
our roles in our team uh okay so see
actually originally I did have some
thoughts about that I'm a
Redstone Builder but like I thought that
Ena could also be very capable of that
so maybe those two Ina and am will be
like the biggest Builders of useful
things the big
bees and then I thought uh what did I
say about G I thought GAA was going to
be like like Hunter I think G was the
hunter of the food collection
yeah goba the
hunter uh and uh CI the all helper
everywhere lame and now now you're also
the organizer you're the organizer let's
go a real job what's that oh can build a
bunch of weapons and I can make stuff
yeah no you I think your organizational
skills are very helpful thanks we need
that appreciate that big you're the the
boss guy the executive decision maker
who runs around and says for that just
says that we're doing everything
wrong no no no you're doing everything
right except for that long path over
there
but it's a myth
tradition it is
tradition know you stay away from the
animals just a taste but I think I'll
I'll try to make some plans every day
like hey we got to do this and that oh
they're really getting angry at each
other maybe I'll give you guys some
quests it's the CLE of good ooh dark oak
sapling nice a lot of trees in there
maybe someone can keep the forest oh I
can I can keep you can keep on with the
uh call it
upgrading upgrading upgrading w w w w w
what's next what's next maybe your boy
can be an animal riding can I have it
cuz I do I didn't want to move these
backward a bit so makeig fces how high
are the chances
Tri I want a Tron you'll get it in this
game because in any other game you have
a really low probability of getting
one what's that wait that's that's
actually maybe the right
uh the biome marine
biome can you use stone or do you need
an iron pickaxe uh just I think Stone
should work try try yeah beautiful
pretty that feels like the Trident
should be where those blocks are but you
can build your own Trident with this
maybe
goo I don't take take the prismarine ooh
I'll save it as a snack thank you or or
start building Atlantis with that good
luck I'll make an ocean chest got to
start I have an idea I'll close this
gate and you're forever stuck behind the
fence until you finished building
Atlantis over there hi guys this is
where I die girl any last words no no
just build like a small little Atlantis
Shrine and then you know we we'll we'll
call it a oh my God Atlantis oh my God
oh my
God years make it a doorway so we can
walk through it congratulations yeah you
got to make it at least walk Frable
through walkable walk Frable oh my God
is that Atlantis guys it could be it
feels like it you tell us you should
know it years later oh it looks just
like it I'm getting so nostalgic how you
remember it just like home it's just how
I remember it yeah that's
pathetic
wow shots fired that's I mean okay that
looks
better uh oh let's go sponge a turtle
wait we're getting there that looks
pretty good now H guys welcome to
Atlantis Welcome to My
Crib not pathetic yeah by the way that
looks ecstatically pleasing already oh
you're so quick to change your
D I got a little bit scared I got a
little bit scared
[Music]
IES dry K blocks these are good for fuel
a
turtle wait why is I'm a building
Atlantis now why is it not good cuz she
has the blocks you're higher me I'm I'm
I'm yeah she commissioned me you're
you're the cont she hired the contracts
in construction yeah what shape of a
favorite letter hey he is that is that
what a stands for for Atlantis now
you're on it oh what I figured it out I
figured it out that's what she's been
trying to tell us all this time she can
never finish Atlantis cuz she can't say
she can't go past a or is it or is it
the other word
she can
never I mean I guess it is a while till
te H I can't count any higher than a I'm
sorry but you all know this oh man is
that also some some illness like your
expendi also some
illness better
you come here wor about you turning
into down there go to your home go to
your home your is looking a little bit
moldy today
moldy I am a creature of the mold it is
only nature that actually actually what
would you what would you call this color
mold just like resent evil no aqua teal
yeah I would say te turquoise Nissa
would called this um green although it's
pretty green is GRE
oh she's color blind is she not she is
yeah recently we have made the discovery
that she's no pretty color blind wow
want to go back isn't that really rare
among ladies like I thought it was
mostly guys that are color blind wa
sorry I'm trying to push him in he's
still hold on I'll make a slab I'll make
a slab and push him over is he going to
Atlantis won't it be too cold yeah he's
going home idea he going home to isn't
it cold in Atlantis to
no it is it's a balmy 65 F what's that
in
Celsius all right be careful going to
make a path here so don't fall
jelly you un pathing the path
yep oh oh oh
good move the
water she yeah we
can let's go yum yum yum yum yum oh what
Atlantis is
real it's real baby is real that's one
good way to use the prismarine
blocks the best way the only way it's
like a a drive through Atlantis it's
like Vegas but it's
Atlantis
wow yeah we can be married in the
Arch oh but it's just one what happens
in Atlantis stays in Atlantis yeah
now yeah yeah that's it sorry we need to
make it wider for that oh maybe we can
put a a bell here at some point when we
find the Bell oh yeah right in the
middle or up at the top on the other we
got to find a bell how do you make a
bell find one yeah you can only find
them as far as I know maybe it'll spawn
in a chest possibly o but are we ever
going to like what about cuz the the end
and the nether is like its own thing
where we can go I wonder what is how can
we ever find like villagers do they also
just spawn
there I
wonder o oh
feish W oh wow there oh my God what's
going on it's loud those are beautiful
wa the wooden Stone there's dark
prismarine
wo I love that more music that looks
like my
couch oh yeah you love that emerald
green stuff huh yeah The Great Gatsby is
my
aesthetic c big gats ow ow ow ow ow oh
no the the blow
fishy just W don't mess you
up super chest super chest
thanks for the super chest what's going
organization we have a bucket to we have
many buckets I will take this bucket I'm
trying to organize everything I eat it
no not yet potato chip and eat
it not yet py py py sorry I'm just
putting things in the chest I hope you
can organize them C oh yeah leave it to
me
no problem I believe in you a super
chest yeah where's the wood chest this
will be wood this is wood in here chest
opening
ASMR o I have ocean chests you you want
the ocean chest I'll put it in here I'm
sure you'll figure it out uhhuh is
that is this wool what is
this materials in here oh that looked
like a oh god oh jeez oh god oh jeez
burn the dried T block I guess make
pretty lanterns with those it looks like
christm oh yeah eventually hopefully we
can find lava so we can make a big trash
can Diamond
W nice nice the
excitement watch out is what is that
again what do you call that again stupid
fish the guardian thing it's fell down
okay
sh let's I'm going to make something I'm
going to actually make some wood in
here we have wood
chest I'm going to make something where
will I make it
here start labeling these what are you
looking at
huh shroom for brain
big
vacant soulless eyes not a thought
between those ears either is
there between those
shroom who who kill it oh good
green what is
that he followed me from he's going to
kill
me it's Assassin from a I got it that
does a lot of damage oh my God nice man
that was awesome I weak 169
blocks really yeah you had and in the
moment you killed that enemy you had 169
blocks we have nice
uh I think I'm going to explode I'm
going
to let
is that the doph was talking
about to a bucket of salmon fish fish we
can make a aquarium we just need sand
a there's I saw I took
them I'll put them in the chest later oh
I can put them in now I guess I'm going
to
make okay
another yeah I remember
that I have Diamond by the way I'll put
it in the
Box
[Music]
uh H
think P are swea ow ow ow not the again
whatever I'll just do
this you put oh sorry I forgot what I
was doing
[Music]
L got the
diamonds I like how you can tell cuz of
the
achievement out it immediately what is
this is this a billboard for science
yes okay in
process
Dophin he's dying he's super dying dead
good care of
well we never had good intentions with
the dolphins
good Hey where's all the fre dirt for
fuel
what where's all
the we don't have
any sand it's a lot of sand my ping is
too poopy I cannot keep
up my P actually for me like Everything
feels pretty
normal polar bear if you eat these seeds
I will make you into a rug I will not
something is dying oh that sounds nice I
hope he does it I want a polar bear rug
polar
bear why does my
finger you guys ever get like invisible
ouchies like it feels like you cut
yourself but you didn't yeah sometimes
oh for sure
salmon
goodbye now I'm
wondering you can either um have them
right underneath what they've done
[Music]
today iron or is a dried kill block is
that
new I don't know but it's good for fuel
from what I remember
seen me neither until today
yeah for now it's with signs in the
future it will be hopefully
[Music]
books
done
day okay is this maybe I'll take care of
the animal does this make anyone unhappy
because this is written differently
I'm sure it's fine and then this what do
I do here dirt on the plant
trees all right Lorax time baby Lorax oh
yeah Lorax
time I'm The Lorax I speak for the
trees yeah old Lorax Memories the board
is for now complete it will be improved
in the future sure so like yeah you find
your name and then underneath you write
in as little words as possible what you
have
done really doesn't like keep it
brief until your next stream I I can't
Rite an entire light
now I know I I love I would love to do
the diary thing but we got to find them
Diaries we we just have to find one
diary and then we can all ride into the
same one one book what do you need for
that
one book cow SK Lea and Pap what leather
and paper we have Lea just need paper
yeah that's very manageable very
doable one myth
them yeah sugar cane if we find
sugarcane then we can make
it feel like the only place you can find
sugar cane is probably from a chest
mhm I would
thebr and then we want to farm it or
make a farm out of
it we'll make a farm out of you the
fish
God
how Call of
Duty yes
Duty turtle eggs turtle egg what do we
do with them o yum can we eat
we were on the same page
there what you
doing uh looking over my plants not what
are your plant oh your plants not your
plants okay no my plants all right we
have more sticks than we need food cuz
we don't have food we have a ton of food
we have the red cows go cows go take the
cows milk okay so I'm the cow area so
leave that to me Lord been that yeah may
we just use cow milk for now it's it's
but like take the red cow's milk with a
bowl it's mushroom
steel very very
healthy I kind of want to make mushrooms
too for dinner now you can the ones from
my
garden but no are you telling me to
die they would they wouldn't kill you
but they would probably give you um some
stomach issues W I need
wood all right cow don't look oh it
escaped ah it's zooming again uhoh take
it down take it down it's a zooming fish
it takes itself down sorry ew it's so
plippy you're going to
[Music]
die one
block it's still loose oh a bu is hiding
amongst the animals that's not fair it's
smart PR to one of
them how's it what's everybody up to
right now build do we have any iron you
can make some shears to make a bed yeah
oh yeah the iron just finished cooking
actually I'll make it I'll make it yeah
go look in the oven there's some
actually I'll just put it in the like a
Yoshi egg I'll put in the yeah we have
seven iron he's
chilling can I
iron IR
sorry thanks for the organization Callie
doing my best it's actually really
useful
Callie thanks I'm glad I'm can be useful
cuz I think I guess are we all like
super messy and C is the least messy in
myth or is it just a Minecraft thing I'm
not sure that's just the mcraft thing
right
really are you sure about that my house
is very
clean oh kelp is good for making more
water let me see for water block but we
have infinite water so I guess it's
okay Kelly Kelly you've been to my home
would you say I think back then I it
wasn't the cleanest it was but would you
say my home was like it wasn't
offensive it wasn't offensive what yeah
it was fun I didn't
there that was that me I know it doesn't
sound very nice but but just trust me it
was it was fine one thing we you can say
and I have high standards so it's okay
although I don't know if you perceived
it that way is that cat hairs are
everywhere I mean it doesn't really I
mean I have two cats so I don't really
notice but everything it wasn't super
cluttered or anything like that clutter
is the main thing that I
detest again and dirt okay so all of it
maybe
yeah okay time to plant more
trees I'm sorry I tried to get wats and
stew oops oops oops oops oops oops oops
have you heard the cow or
what don't hurt them I have a question
for chat chat if I sheared the mushroom
cows by accident did they grow
back I feel like they should I can you
do that no is that even possible they
say no all right do not cheer the last
Red Cow there's only one left oh wait if
you Shar him it turns into a normal cow
yeah yeah I didn't know what I didn't
know either because I would have never
tried such a thing in the first place
wow I thought you could harvest the
mushrooms and then you could grow more
yeah that would be amazing uh-oh oh he's
coming in hot
ow flap flap
flab all right the bar will be expanded
soon you'll
[Music]
see come on little seeds you can do it I
believe in you I guess chill cheer them
on girl that'll make him feel bro come
on little saplings you can do it don't
we have any more bone meal we have bone
meal you want what bone me no my words
my words of encouragement will work
trust me wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait I I I think I think your words
will do it okay say something to the
plants come on little seeds you can do
it reach up high to the sky partner grow
towards that synthesizing Sun you can do
it I'm believeing
you bam you did that did it work it
worked he's so excited to be here KOA
did you actually learn magic in that VR
stream yes I did
wow all right promoting you to head
wizard from now on present it grw even
more wizard yes but what about the
others the others are there you go oh
can you say some more magic
words bub boo I make you
grow to to yeah the sun tell to the
sun the sun woo it's not
working what what do you mean it's not
working it worked twice now why wouldn't
it work now over here it happened over
here oh I don't know your magic is very
all over the place no but it's try
something try something
here skib D make it green
green stop wa Mel there's no
way there's no way that's pretty big EG
it's not working all right I will now
free you animals oh he's coming a felon
give me some
melon Watson's a fell
this okay that's that's pretty much
about it flap flapping around what do
you mean that's it oh well I guess this
one t she lost the magic
powder oh wait I just realized it's
melon it doesn't have anywhere to go
that's why it's not growing
give Protec you cows don't worry about
it cows I'm protecting you wait why why
did you why not dirt blocks why Stone I
thought you wanted to have any we don't
have any I have one it'll it'll flop
over under the stone
right oh my God are they attacking
me oh my God there's
one killed by my own
Bears all your stuff is here got to get
okay that's that's cool all my stuff is
still there is it gone for the greater
good I wasn't holding a ton of
stuff boy Bears what's your
problem I think they're mad at the the
fish thing wait they've
escaped oh no oh you made it bigger oh
yeah that was kind of the plan kill them
don't forget your stuff oh my stuff yeah
iron thank
you iron oh y new home for you guys yeah
nice and spacious I'm not picking up the
things am I where you go maybe I need a
proper
pickaxe no I want to do
oh this
music I take the
music
what I gave you some dirt blocks oh oh
upgrade up
time g g it feels like G but it's
totally not gcha it's already decided
it's totally
preed it's cool though what exit wait
they're escaping oh this
Humanity it's fine it's fine it's
upgrading let's go let's go I'm excited
I wonder what we get this time next
level biome wa I think I'm going to try
why is it taking a
while oh 10 9 8 7
4 2 2 1 happy New
Year jungle happy New Year jungle time
jungle jle dungon happy New Year
[Music]
Chad oh jungle baby wow wow wow wow a
lot of
stone happy maybe we can say happy half
year because we're like pretty much
halfway through isn't that
crazy time FES I'm so mad I'm so angry
at how 2024 is already halfway through I
hate it no yeah why need more time it
feels like it just became diamond
diamond
diamond let's go we're getting good
amount of
diamonds
nice my par
parot where are your parents it would be
a shame if
it you know you know why did you laugh
it would be a shame if it disappeared
you know magic
[Music]
trick Viller what was that what was that
vill I did we kill it
Viller I think there's no way I think we
killed it or it fell down the Villager
might have he might have fallen down no
way I'm sure another one will come
back just got to be careful I guess
would it be smart to put one block under
the block that we Min so things don't
fall down as easily that we don't want
to fall down where's that that should be
loud right I don't see why it wouldn't
be
possible yes oh they say it's very very
smart to do that let me try to do that
then
okay wait how do
how do you build underneath
this do I have to like
become like Superman and fly underneath
wait
I need water make a waterfall
what make a water what water I'm going
to die I'm going to fall
down I'm going to do it the W
way yeah sometimes which way would that
be
M let me show you oh okay this should be
wait let me put
diamonds okay I have so many blocks now
okay so I would but like still how do I
get
lower how do you how
[Music]
that uh what I have to okay okay I'll
try I'll try I'll try I'll try um Callie
maybe we need a chest um to just like
wait I have a chest I'll I'll put a
chest here where oopsy I'll just put
stuff in that I don't know where to put
okay well here like a miscellaneous
chest yeah and then you can look at this
one and then take those things and put
them okay yeah just for sorting
basically like a sort this commission
please sort this I got
you
nice okay I got you now do we have a
bucket somewhere yeah it should be in
the like other random things it's not
really random things but I have an
announcement you have an announcement my
tummy hurts oh no carry
on thank you for your announcement thank
you for listening
M do you need a you dog
no uh Kori could you please lead me to
the bucket bucket so it's right above
the blocks it's in the middle here
there's a like a a gravel and dirt chest
it's above it so wait oh the bucket was
in there no I can't see it oh I'm
holding ony no wor best friends
[Music]
forever okay so now I can take take
water I think this tree thing is bugged
it's
like oh is the is the water and in the
farm endless
water yes yes it should be oh I'm why
are you planting where are you planting
what oh Jag you planting oh melon I used
all the melon seeds to get the bird how
will I how do you get a bird not die
here uh you can get a bir there might be
another one oh they spawn yeah cuz we're
in the jungle dungeon
biome the dungle bungle biome
yeah does your bird save stuff not yet
do not W as how do you with with space
going to teach it okay I don't know but
get away from it I don't want you if I
die that's
okay if I die what would I do we oh oh
stop stop can uh the the block that you
guys are mining there but it becomes a
block that is like very oh Panda Pap
Panda there's pandas panda panda but
yeah can you block like that cuz it's
recognizable for
me okay okay get in there I'm in I'm in
I'm what in I'm I
okay is my bird did my bird come
I have an idea find
yes M now this just like that one sh I'm
drowning oh I forgot about drowning I
forgot about drowning what happened I
almost I realized I was drowning it's
just like the one show with the Three
Bears we bear bear yeah look at
thems we like the brown bear right the
deadliest of them all one of those in
Minecraft do they a brown
bear I've never seen one
Brown bill look at cocoa beans the sun
is below me or is that he we got a book
we can start a diary oo nice don't we
need like a book stand though or we need
ink or something don't we we have ink
sacks
yeah one I'm going to start labeling the
storage why is the panda moaning I don't
like it
Pand
pandon again what does that mean again I
don't know it's like crazy like oh chaos
okay I have created a bottom level and I
have secured the the mining block below
Escape we kill
him I've done something useful I fell in
in dead M something useful is a panda
can climb
right I guess so
yay should I take the water back I think
it's fine to have it there if we want to
go back down
again the turtle there's a cow that
escaped uhoh kill him just take yeah
I'll just kill it like we don't know a
witch we have so many yeah WI bit of
meat you kill her yeah
[Music]
ni all right wait how many stages have
we done so far wa no idea no isn't it in
the text in the chat in the so oh we
stage five well they're counting you
guys are actually counting a lot wow
Chad as always super super organized s
keeping
notes I don't know what I'm doing
think well horsey horsey horsey wow we
can ride it all the way down my long
hallway yeah I
[Laughter]
was move
Pig we need a saddle
I will be your sadel oh he's cool he's
like Creeper
Creeper
CH the turtles were blown off what no
what the turtle exploded he
he them
what I didn't know the horses had such a
big problem with oh it wasn't the horse
it was a creeper oh wa wa wao I didn't
know they would do such like lips hey yo
I just captured the panda FP Panda
that's so cute that's sticking his
tongue
outow
Panda I'm building a p wait that's a
different Panda from this one what dude
your Panda does front flips back flip
yeah it's
crazy oh my god I've actually just like
recently watched a video about how
useless and difficult Pand
pandas aren't real they're just people
in
suits they're just people I like that
idea I think this one has a neurological
disorder
yeah I got more books and a bamboo we
can grow bamboo just cute that's it
that's all you are you lazy there's
nothing here next to the treesa we can
carefully it doesn't roll off the
edge oh it can tot planted a bamboo you
got to put up a baby game so it doesn't
roll theed okay ladies everything is
labeled you got Gates you labeled it yes
labeling it I feel like you might even
have a labeling machine IRL I would not
put it uh what's the word past you
behind you
below panda baby D panda
baby okay okay oh it's fine f I punched
it out of
here oh my God hey why does it look like
that it's chilling stinky down there why
he his tongue out at me Stinky pull that
tongue out of your mouth chest I think
shove it in a place you'll never see oh
w w w
w Savannah cat hi pretty
baby I love you no come back no please
don't fall off first I fall it was a new
Minecraft animal I thought it was a a a
leopard he's too fat come on bro you can
do it's an ocelot an i o for real are
they that tiny they name you Revolver
Ocelot Ena of the cat
double is it an ocelot for real
officially all
right you're
pretty what's this button dude it's gari
oh the gate goes there we got to put it
back it opens the the gate part of the
fence stay there stay inside there
need to hurry up and learn how to tame
animals guys that freaking panda is so
dumb flipping us
off thank
you I I activated that myself it's not
even funny Chad says you can't tame the
ocelot no they keep creepers away W oh
just like normal cats then is that what
cats do right oh no do
they like normal Minecraft cats also
keep creepers away no oh yeah I think so
can someone make a a carpet and put it
the edge of the Game Stop carpet well
yeah wait I think we have some a luxury
no we don't have a sheep I I was trying
to make a bed but no sheep oh my God
wait we had sheep what happened horsey
horsey wait maybe the foxes killed all
the Sheep what are you doing
no why isn't he leaving stop it out stop
it
no
well why did the horse go oh no wait oh
it was a second horse Ian I freed him
but he did not want to listen to
me it's okay he lived life according to
his own code I can respect
it can you um is there a like a podium
pz or do you just put it on a normal
block chat no that was a stand right the
bookst what do you call a
bookst
book
lecturn thans one we need door a
bookshelf H
difficult okay for now where should I
put the book I have the book right now I
have two more books two more books yeah
I'll put it in in the in the weapon
chest
okay damn did you get them out of
another chest yeah
oh wait everybody can have their own
book maybe at the end of the
stream maybe maybe nice and then I I'll
do like a picka thing and read
everybody's
Diaries yay not a bad
idea so everybody has to write really um
chal uh Diaries just
likea all right in direct Defiance of
you Kiara I'm gonna write the most Bare
Bones like I found some wood today no
has to be Dr a little statue it was sick
bye oh no uhoh why does this keep
happening no horses like to die right
I'm not interested in B it's almost oh
whoopsies he was not going to
I feel like his existence was pain there
was nothing we could
do sad see I wish we had more dirt
blocks to be honest so that we could
expand for can I Fe the
panda do
it feed the panda I can make this doing
tricks I can put the can I put a book on
the picture frame or is you like this CH
you like this
you want to eat
this hey
you yes perfect okay all right guys I've
decided I'm going to start taking care
of these animals so I'm going to try and
make something I can doable what are
those what are
those what are those what are those what
are those sounds
W oh no oh no oh
noex who's Vex K it what's the Vex kill
it we need armor we need aror we need
armor yum y yumy I'm close to
probing is it gone is the enemy gone
it's the v no they're not g they're
still here help me I'm dying let me out
let me out I want to pick up my it build
the house build the house wait my bird
don't hit my
bird I died these guys are nasty got so
much
wa okay um did somebody
[Music]
my my my lever did anybody pick up my
lever by any chance let me check if I
did I might have picked up some stuff
and the books I have a here books Gua
here you go thank you and then you had
mushrooms and then oh yeah lever I don't
see any lever though someone else may
have picked oh leather you mean leather
sorry oh what did you said lever sorry I
can't say th I swear to God man will
always be my biggest enemy should I make
everybody an iron
helmet you can okay was I doing was what
was I doing I'm just going to lay a
foundation uh stick
right what that that thing that we just
fought where does that under what
circumstances do find that normally I
don't remember isn't that in where the
skeleton boss guy is skelet ah the
Wither the
nether the Wither right is
it really I've never seen villagers yeah
right oh I thought it was just a random
witch but then it spawn stuff it can be
at pillagers mansions and Woodland
Mansions yeah yeah is that that's not
the same thing right is it interesting M
I've raided one of those before
for okay wait that was fun
helmet oh thanks touch your top teeth
with your tongue as you say th okay give
me a word with th uh wither with wither
oh do I did I do
it english- speaking people around
me wasn't listening I thought you were
talking to the chat no to you to yeah I
thought you're talking to chat okay
listen normally I would say W wither
thank you probably and now I say wer wer
wither
wither with her with her but that's so
with who
with with wither with with who with you
with M with
mid M that's
right no hey you're getting that's too
annoying to always put my tongue up
there another bamboo but that's correct
I don't want
to I don't want
to how many do I need coal can we cook I
want to cook some stuff I'm going to
build a base behind the farm so that we
have like a place to run
into okay a shelter or something or
actually I'll do it in this corner right
over
here yeah
W I'll grow another bamboo right here
I'm going to
expand expand mine
genius actually beautiful your main
[Music]
expansion what is that noise I hate all
these sad crying animal songs hearing
during the stream another Panda having
a you're having a panda take
over double
Panda where'd you get
that the totem of light what are you
looking at yeah where did she get the
totem from I serious I killed the mob
and he gave it to me wa the one that
summoned the Vex yeah oh there was one
before that that summoned the Vex in the
first place carrot hey
you just got to give it
seeds you got to find seeds if you take
one watermelon slice you can make six
seeds with one slice it's fa soul that
is watching us M yeah I think you would
be paper and bamboo you'd be the most
suitable for the fauna bird give me the
fauna bird if you put her on your
shoulder she can watch upon us play
Minecraft how do I make it land on me
come after you tame it you just walk
over it and it'll land on your shoulder
careful there's another one of the
things oh no do so do we you guys got it
as a
witch there's another witch okay God mon
that was my first
enemy what have you been
doing capturing in
4k
uh I parot keeps saying ooh how do I
make it stop oh that is very in
character for a moment I thought
rods
interesting am it what is happening in
the Watson area uh I'm just building a
platform for the house and like
boundaries for the walls another one is
that a villager yeah no it's a witch
not
wit we get a villager sometime
who lost their fauna bird me it's going
somewhere else it hates you it's cuz I
made
for is everything lit up come here bird
there there's another green bird there
huh what did you feed what did you feed
the bird melon seeds seeds Okay I want
to try this one
too
seeds wow that's so cool now
okay I'm just going to toss everything
into the
sorting blocks yeah put in the Sorting
I'll take care of it
chocolate maybe not the best thing to
feed
it oh it doesn't bamboo I have
chocolate do you
have the muffin man wait that's know we
have two a now
seeds I'm so happy the more C the
diamond diamond I have five
diamonds well how do I nobody spawning
around here I just take these I take
these oh if I eat the Watermelons do I
get seeds probably not no you got to put
them in
the the grinder yeah the the maker box
box where is maker
box the the the 4X 3x4 Square thing 3x
what is that 3x3
thing don't want to come back what she
talking about they they fun no say o I
didn't mean it oh this
oh
this what I'm still learning things in
Minecraft after all these years there's
a blue one what blue oh it's blue
orangee everybody can have a parrot
nice is this rust you're building an a
loock yeah it's cocoa beans not ran out
I ran out no
no we put wool maybe in here is fine
where did it go where did it go oh LA's
going for that one okay wait for the
next one sorry it has partially orange I
I feel like it's calling me okay I got
it what colors are there is there like
um purplish one
too that would be nice there
blue blue is now taken there's red yeah
true there there will be red one of
these days okay nobody's mining let me
mine a little bit go I was just making a
new pickaxe oh
okay I want to make one there's also
lots of stuff what is this get that out
of there
iron
ion
pickaxe all
right
okay what else wood wooden wooden wooden
I'm going to build um I also want to
build like a little base house behind
the farm or like a farmhous or
something's probably getting an axxe but
I
[Music]
will I just wanted to do this so that
the cats stop walking across it a what
and it's bright we can see a wait when
did we get that rod from the box W wo wo
W oh boy that
Panda goodbye Panda that hurts to listen
to no that sounds a little bit like a
suffering cat as well yeah there's a
very similar I hate it
bone paper and Bone paper is good paper
is very good bones can be good
too sorry I can't be mad is this what
you guys have always been enduring when
you mine here that's so painful yeah
that hurts to listen to it reminds me of
suffering
cats don't think about it imagine he's
moaning in pleasure instead Jesus Christ
what mine over matters give
me good idea give
me look at the size of that another
another one let's go that's Happy sign
good thing oh another
melon cat please stop oh there's another
bird get out of here what color what's
the color is that is a girl's bird it's
green do I you have bird wait where's
what the oh I made my bird
sit that's why you're not with me friend
you made green bird friends to
I have green bir friend oh
there is that yours yeah that's probably
mine okay it's just that it doesn't want
to sit on
me wait what oh you haveit my bird no
yours is on your shoulder wait is there
a new one a new one
maybe possibly wait that is a new one
yeah everybody's Birds accounted for
seems like it the new one well C do you
also want a green bird sure I'll have
one hold on I need some torches real
quick [\h__\h] P there seems to be a blue
bird without a without an owner is that
yours the blue bird is mine there was
another green bird that just came out of
nowhere but I don't know where to go
isn't that a Naruto song we have so many
cats so many
ocelot bad no Bluebird see Defiance
going on there straight
Defiance I didn't you know
[Music]
chat at what phase choking on candy do
we get to go to the ne I mean that's
probably pretty
far I mean we have to find lava and
obsidian make make or find
obsidian enough of it
150 is that a real answer the 20 sounds
pretty
legit and we would need a diamond
pickaxe I mean I think we have enough
diamond in free phases what do you mean
in free phases we get obsidian or what
chat you're confusing me 10 I we do get
another I think we get nether
Whatchamacallit nether Zone like blocks
too from what I
remember okay cool cool
cool Sorry get out of there panda
[Music]
oh some things just aren't meant to be
they're not built to
survive cuz all they eat
bamboo the weak yeah Only the Strong
Will Survive what's happening over here
selection sorry panda this is
pretty it's uh it's it's it's like an m
in the shape of with the colors of a
myth the door is supposed to be like
orange it's like a light orange color I
like
that that is so
cute secretly doing something adorable
design sense that little design sense is
really good that little
army not not small army little army
there's a difference small army OHA but
what's in the ins going to be is it
going to be our beds or push him yeah
just like a safe house M good idea
[Music]
and our birds can stay in here yeah once
we have a roof over
it what was
that
Hy did somebody whistle or was that the
bird in game toally the bird bird how do
you befriend them again H you you get
some seeds wait I still have two seeds
but you need a bit more than the two
seeds oh I see I'll put them in the food
chest thank you and then you right click
them with the seeds but I needed like
six or or five or so
a upgrading in 43 seconds ooh O Let's
Go W is the white bird
new white bird looks
new there's a white bird yeah under the
upgrading thingy or where did it go I
look away for one second then it's
gone where the
iron
15 Wonder going to be this time oh yeah
probably was Amy bird where's the IR
Need You Can Mine the the uh the the
blocks of uh pumpkin and so on over
there red desert hostile places of heat
dust and
death death I'm death and then you put
the watermelon or you put it in your in
your um crafting thingy just one block
and then it gives seeds oh cool yeah ni
thanks sand we love
sand eat
sand don't eat sand not yummy yum yum
wow orange sand
let's
go very hot sand becomes orange it's
science oh yeah yeah Kaba orange yes my
orange what's that
OHA aaia do you guys call them aaia UHA
no I would call them say villager
villager villager villager villager oh
fre him him no killing right
trap
him you know I was making a house over
there maybe we can put him in the house
oh yeah Boat Boat Boat put them in the
yeah put them in this house I'm making
okay okay oh there's another wow we're
building a whole village maybe this will
look like even more futuristic than the
Ian
server maybe more effort to get a
boat okay this will be his little home
no the bird hey get out of there that's
my bird what are you doing in there bird
it's your bird under control yeah okay
I'm I'll try wait control your animals l
oh ah bird is hurt bird hurt he's okay
he's okay get on my shoulder wait
where's the boat who has the boat uh he
might fall through we got to get him out
of
there did you pick up the
boat I did my bed he's got to walk off
he's got to walk off he wants to leave
oh nice you can't do that all right
we'll put put them in uh we got to
finish Callie's uh little thing she
build it over the house yeah it's almost
done it's just a little house really
make it I have doors if you don't have
doors that's all good I got one one door
delivery V over here who's got an iron
pickaxe I got
it right ins moving
in I'm the moving service thank you we
there's like jail doors
if you want to make him our prisoner I
was going to have him be just a nice guy
that
lives we can keep an eye on him if we
put can I put doors keep those pretty
doors oh I guess he can open
those yeah sure wait prison doors can
you actually only open it from the
outside ow
zombie prison doors I don't think it's
just a normal door though they look nice
but they can open it right oh well he'll
stay in the boat for now prison doors
how cozy mhm they let some light through
it's nice breathable no poor
[Music]
soul hey you like your house
buddy oh are those nice Terra terracotta
blocks or
what yo yeah they're ter and white claw
[Music]
Emerald I'm sorting now don't worry okay
I'll put some more stuff yeah more
things for me to sort yeah
sorting I love sorting G has a sorting
addiction maybe I I might oh wait n we
got a traitor who oh get The Boat Boat
what you got what you got make a boat oh
where's oh there should have put him in
the more important house not interesting
maybe we can make him a shop Trader
without llamas get out of here yeah
that's lame he's got gunpowder wait so
we shouldn't keep him no I mean why not
always we should always keep him yeah
can have gunpowder from him not cool are
youer tra go deliver him we have the One
Stop taxi to
jail
jail you just boned his head on the
concrete
spawned in and went right to
prison prisoner villager came out oh
he's free oh no who forgot to close the
doors he open it open them oh oh yeah
I'll make extra boats to keep them in
the boats I guess
yeah I love how everything looks so
Lively already
sh you must stay in your
uh Stay
Stay what me in a boat for you get in
boat get in there dummy look how nice it
is he's too
smart oh oh you following me bro got a
bone to pick with me he's judging you
what's wrong with my
house need some work oh he's going in in
get
in it look ceiling for you guys wait
wait wait wait wait now he's in now he's
in now he's in oh they're both in the
same boat okay they're in the same
boat it's so nice of you to actually let
me out I felt like being nice just this
one time
only this one time
though Panda you're going to die again
and I'm going to be blamed back up give
me some
space there's so many birds worried
about
cute what do you do with all this
clay we can make terra cotta with it no
can
we oh wow dead
bush wow super
boy
clay what do you do with a dead Bush man
where eat it you can turn into Twigs no
I don't know oh yeah make a Yum Yum
Salad
no no oh doesn't turn into is that a
llama it seems to be it appears to be
surprised it's not like dying in there
with its long leg long neck cute get out
of there cute I get out of
there cute yes it's slowly coming out
yeah I collect them it's slow y y
Yama when I think about llamas I think
about middle school and everybody being
really obsessed with llamas they're like
kind of like lolxd random kind of
animal yeah yeah wait that doesn't space
Lama
rain how
calming don't go in
there get out of there birdie Bird come
back
home you're blocking the way of my
bird
[Music]
me bird come
home you I have to hold the
seed
huh you good Kara how dare
you you I I
H
you help me Callie help me help me what
happed what happened Blood for Blood
wait oh you killed
mine oh no a par for
parot I for
for parrot I thought it said Ena was
slain by the parrot like parrot late Ena
I was like eh what oh wait we got some
hay Oh yay really wow wow well seems
like this um this uh uh problem has been
solved between us in a peaceful way for
now was it peaceful very peaceful was it
peaceful I mean the axe you carrying
that Axe and looking at me like that
reminded me a little bit of suicide
Senpai in the most unpeaceful way but oh
is that a witch
or wait does f oh I think it's a
Pillager yeah we Must
Destroy cannot be
good I think it's a it's a Pillager
no some people say villager in the chat
but why does it not say when we look at
him it only I think the clothes look
like a Pillager not a
villager Enderman holdable
what end it's a Pillager yeah right okay
it sorry cat
sorry sorry oh yeah it was a Pillager
okay we have plenty of
cats why is
it I want to make a chest for ore what
was that that did it spit at
me is a llama spitting
fact llama fact of the day I have been
IRL once Spit On by an
alpaka it was a baby alpaka actually
what' you do to it yeah what' you do to
it I went to like an alpaka farm and um
there were some babies and the sta there
oh what was that the staff there let me
hold the baby oh no I think he was
holding the baby and then I was like
petting it and then yeah I got pissed
off really fast and just spit right in
my face or so on the side of my face and
let me tell you that is in like
impossible to get rid of the smell ooh
stinky imagine the
smell of the alpaka baby imagine the
smell I'm okay I'll pass I don't really
want to do that stinky try to not get
spat on by alpaka don't recommend
mine don't recommend zero out of
[Music]
10 had to shower real hard that was the
hardest shower of my life did you steal
wool from the alpaka no Ste no still
still
wool went whoh over her head but I do
have some like uh I have an alpaca wool
blanket for example not from that time
but I I have alpaka stuff you turn it
into a wool blanket
yes I put them for a blender and it came
out as a
blanket is that what you wanted to hear
is that what you want look another
Merchant what he he's dead he's freaking
dead oh it's okay uh the merchants are
not that useful merant really what if
you get one that like if you have
emeralds you can give them a bunch of
stuff like I've seen at con the shop uh
that's like when we make a Trader out of
villagers the merchants don't have much
useful stuff usually but a donkey are
you so like the Villager that we have we
can train him to become a merchant mhm
oh another llama alpaca Sor going to
give him like a a job first cool
oh I kind want to make this prettier I
think the Merchant's still here it's
just invisible it's invisible how fun CU
it's night
time yeah I'm going to make it pretty
colors this area I heard Atlantis had
been built I'm here to witness the great
Monument let me show you let me show you
good do you want a tour us for
Atlantis viewers who just arrived hello
dear viewers welcome to good ass
crib yo yo my name name don't mind the
panda come on in So Random okay let's go
don't mind the
panda well it's very very wet here that
is authentic yes
yes wet this is epic gooda this is so
cool yeah this is so cool yeah pretty
pretty yeah we're totally underwater too
so the rest of Atlantis like sunk right
yeah uhhuh yes
it sunk really deep
man maybe if we follow the water
elevator will'll reach Atlantis maybe
all of this is Atlantis hey hey go o
slime ball
go go
gooa you've been so far so many emeralds
you went so far gooa oh it's a zombie
could you please come back
nice I think you may have um possibly
left me behind I I think Atlantis is
sinking again oh no you better hurry up
and open the door well there is
something in front of it that I could
remove but um I wanted it for dramatic
effect to be
you that reminds me when we played
phasmophobia and you got stuck in the
house and then the door locked oh
no so good those were some rough times I
could hear was you SC your mumbled
screams from the outside of the front
door until she went silent rough times
man I'm so sorry I was laughing at your
expense but it was really funny contents
content yeah do we have more books by
now or
what where are the
books where are the books oh that that
that gives me a a good idea put another
block here yeah what what's the last
book you read the last book I read oh my
God I can't even remember to be honest
right then it must have been when I was
like a baby child no way you've read
more books since then no I'm trying to
think there was this book series called
The Mortal Instruments and it was kind
of like
a like not it wasn't Twilight it was
like cooler and it was steampunk or
something like that and I remember that
was what I read in Middle School oo
vampire novel
oh classic yes you guys remember that
you guys remember that you guys remember
Mortal Instruments I figured some people
might remember
never Twilight there was a romance
though so gooda what is the last book
you no what do you guys read yeah yeah
I'm going around what what is the last
book youve
read um I probably reread the mini
Hobbit that I have wait when did you
reread it I don't remember are you
willing to read it
again why to Fresh in your memory and um
this wasn't what where I was going
originally but I am planning a The
Hobbit book club
episode where we read The Hobbit and
then talk about it like we're in a book
club I can do that is it the Mini
version uh not that's all it's already
pretty mini by default isn't it is that
what it is am I thinking of the regular
Lord of the Rings then there's the
Hobbit which is tinier yeah The Hobbit
oh I guess you're seeing The Hobbit as a
mini version of load of Rings or so I
don't know no it's I mean it's it's a
separate but I just I don't know I just
I like
called what's your favorite
part uh when SM went like haaha and then
blew his fire all over the place
oh that's the dragon right I know that
guy yeah SM yeah SM I may have not read
it but I can still come up with moments
you didn't read it that's why we're
doing the book club that's why we're
doing my favorite part is when the
trolls are sitting around the fire and
they're having really funny conversation
silly accents I saw that in the movie
the movie is terrible though no it's
fine it no it's not once you read the
book you will realize we got a donkey
the movie the movie robs you of a lot
okay that that's why we'll do the book
club okay you can you know share your
opinions on it too mommy you need to
move thank you did okay wait what this
book club this thing the
donkey no not that there's a donkey next
to it see look oh is that a we not have
any more iron is% a donkey just put the
rest of the iron ingots in the this top
chest oh okay
oh he's dying the Don is dying donke
he's
dying why why do they do this to
themselves we are that annoying to be
around yeah
sorry suffering for what got some
leather hey do you like the cool shop I
made this is a Shop officially shop shop
shop let's see the shop W you it a nice
Ro it's here where the yeah I gave it a
cool roof for him so we'll make him into
a
let's go looks nice donkey donkey died
feel pretty good about that goodbye
donkey I like the idea of making a bunch
of different structures I don't know
yeah donkey buildings get it it it the
more we build um things like this the
more time this project will take overall
and that's good let's stretch it out
yeah I want to spend more time with you
all yeah sounds good to me whoa who is
this next to to me Ena ena's so fast at
this by
now no you just destroy like apartment
complex or something like that but we
looked at what's inside and you and you
took it out like do we all get to have
our own rooms oh our own rooms like a
Terraria room C just walked outan house
H Ian house but in Minecraft oh
yeah can I get rid of this llama you
want to un un alive it it's okay I'm
sure it'll un alive oh another chest
diamond diamond iron y where's the iron
going get out of here why are they so
slow we don't have a
lot yeah we need more iron there's one
iron ingot in this uh top items chest
okay cool thanks I'm going to put so all
the ore is going to be over here on the
other side across the way in a tiny
chest orang gems we put in there do you
want lapis l in there too I don't know I
thought it fit better in the ocean chest
a oh you know it should make blocks
maybe so they take up
less oh
yeah that could be a good idea yeah you
got to go you got to
go you got to go ow oh roast
them skin oh one what's with the
is come
on but I like this one's color it looks
so soft sorry I am just trying to keep
uh this place you should start a llama
Farm here it's an axe not a sword yeah
why not you could do
it just make a
fence and then put all the llamas
specifically in there I think you
think'll villager guy by that that's the
merchant that turned invisible I think
oh he got cactuses to he got blue eyes
you which red we probably will not meet
in this journey but um still
cool oh I heard something break in you
yeah that was my stone
pickaxe you want you want another
pickaxe you know we have a bunch bunch
of weapons I think stone pickaxe would
be nice Stone okay I can make one for
for
you thank you no problem I just made a
bunch of need more space so I'm going to
expand yes expansion expand expand on
don't expansion I she's expanding no I
didn't say anything here Ena this is
your stone pickax
cute that's that's
Watson
hello can can I can I have my pickax the
K he threw at you is honey also a new
item someone else
uh not that
new no but new is oh no wait did I did I
pick it up again
Ena I got it I got it oh you got it okay
wait hold on a sec you know I have two
iron pickaxes would you like one I could
use another one there you go thank you
iron we got lots of iron popping a
[Music]
many
many what is everybody's favorite Gem
and don't say
beu black
diamond fancy Black Diamond wow yeah
when I get married someday I want a
black diamond oh my god oh it was him oh
damn he's damn who's doing that he's
Stone little man what a piece of garbage
know what's your favorite gem my
favorite gem
never really thought
about Sapphire maybe wow Sapphire is uh
the blue one right yeah yeah legit have
to think about it oh that's a bad
guy goba what's your favorite gem me H I
like pearls pearls is that
of what's your favorite
gem
uh I don't know you don't know Amber
Amber yes Amber's nice color okay
sure doesn't seem like a gem kind of
lady I do like rocks I just like a gem
what's your favorite gem rock what about
a
are nice but that's like crystals not
really gam right count if gets to say
pear count pear fist the way I pronounce
it it's definitely am fist yeah fist
that's my favorite
Jam
huh anything
with can't take it oh maybe J Jade is
pretty right Jade Jade was Jade
Alexandra is pretty cool it's like the
one changes color like red or green kind
of fish girls you know just a few weeks
ago uh I think during Hardcore Minecraft
I had the biggest realization of my life
uhhuh that obsidian is
real what you think I thought it was a
Minecraft
thing everything in Minecraft is real
hey what happened to this B oh yeah like
witches and zombies so does that mean
that Bedrock is also
real yeah well that's yeah you never b a
rock in your bed
before yeah when your bed feels like a
freaking Rock no but it is bedrock real
what do you call it in German
then I mean technically if you go down
deep enough into the Earth you get to a
a layer that's kind of pretty
yeah
binin B German so un serious g g g
[Music]
ginin that makesense
farton why is everything like Stein and
ger well Stein is Stone what is
Stein Stein Stone that's Stone
everything's Stone and gr is like in
this case it's like Bas so it's like
Base
Rock Bas super based dope
blood okay who's doing something
interesting so I may capture it with my
camera am is doing the most you get me
organizing all your chest that you guys
made me
organize I'm digging a hole pretty
interesting right
now yeah we can't really dig can we here
in this want to dig Minecraft is all
about digging I mean we do have one the
one block dig on so sir how are you
today it doesn't really feel like we're
digging that one though we're just
mining it get out of my hole a little
different I was thinking more like when
we dug like tunnel yeah yeah you you
missed that you missed that I mean only
cuz it's nostalgic that's about it yeah
keep
going if you if you Coke him maybe it'll
motivate him keep
moving my good sir get out of here
amigos
no on on on your oh he's G he's
G rubber banding what is this
ping on your
K shoe on my bud yes you understood that
or you just
gu no no no
who see oh
um wait you should have a espanol
conversation with am try your
[Music]
best they talking [\h__\h] about
us trust
that hear that they're laughing about us
yeah
I'm a good
say oh my God they're laughing at
us I feel really excluded right
now they're so mean they're talking in
Spanish they're talking [\h__\h] o oh my
godie I you a word teach me hon oh what
a clown on him clown on
[Music]
himone Harmon Hermon
Hermon what I say I think is that isn't
that ham ham bone ham
bone do we need glow stone for anything
yes for pretty prettifying things okay
cuz I have some emeralds we have some
emeralds to spend and a glowstone cost
two emeralds what do you guys think no
glow St emeralds yeah don't use theal
use it we should just save them yeah
yeah yeah only makes things look pretty
hey what do the sound what does the
sound what was that what
Chad what was that that oh another
villager Welcome to our town another
vill get The Boat Boat kick off the
animals off the boat oh there's an empty
one yeah get him yeah don't let him
Escape you can put him with the other
villager every time I look over there
the panda is just F the he's up here
looking at well freaking
hey come here buddy we going to take you
someplace real
nice all right you got it C he loves
jump in with him and steer connection
soio come on plant PL PL I've never done
this before actually you know what
should I do push just right click on
like the back of the boat like this oh I
see yeah and then you're riding it right
click on the back of the boat yeah don't
shift maybe don't that's the back of
no anywhere really am I but get up
you're like I think it's cuz you're
crouching yeah yeah yeah yeah dang it I
do that way too often I'm so afraid of
falling off guys I really fear that the
cliff is really far don't have to when
I'll open the door for oh you can do it
oh you get you got out of the boat
trying my best I thought I'd have to
tell you how to get out of the boat I'm
trying wait can you guys hear me hello
yes hello yeah I can hear you
now oh God
I disconnected
ISP hey why' you do that Kiara I didn't
do anything guys boat I will break the
[\h__\h] and we'll lose both of the
villagers you don't want to play these
games with me Kiara I swear to God I
will Wrangle your neck I feel like you
were in the same kind of situation as me
uh a moment ago where you feel like
you're really stuck but all you have to
do is open the door and mine the
blocks yeah making things too difficult
ult for
ourselves um can we get another boat we
got another villager another one wow a
lot of visitors there's one here one the
animals I think I have enough to make
another boat yeah we should have enough
wood uh we go guys uhoh if I disconnect
I'm dying don't worry about it where are
you right
now by the tree
cute KOA of the tree what is your wi or
what I think they oh there's there's a
zombie oh left the game I'm dead
therefore she has officially left the
challenge and is disqualified
forever no too bad oh did I forget to
tell you that rule you've been voted off
the island
no do I get to come back before the
season finale yeah bring me back only
for the Ender Dragon yeah bring me back
y please come back anytime when you feel
like it i r a donkey Pi check hold on
where you riding the donkey were you
really yeah look look can you guys
believe all
this waa oh wa there's a [\h__\h] ton of
creepers over there at the corner oh my
God we're next to the Cali house shoot
anyone have a bow and arrow no we don't
have such things
yet them to
what is it what is it creepers oh I
forgot to put I forgot to put don't
don't runes down maybe we
can go to run run
run will
be to the end of the that's good that's
good it's okay I pushed one of them off
we only lost two blocks over here P died
there was two more creepers on the other
side of the door we put more you should
have fought off the panda should have
sacrificed
yourself look man they were very tough
okay guys there's another Panda over
here oh no let's just pretend I he I
heard something blow up let's just
pretend torches is that why these guys
are spawning yeah we need torches
there I just built this like two ago can
we bring a panda back to
Atlantis we need some bamboo that was
good I captured the right
moment oh my goodness you want to move
the panda I got a boat oh yeah oh the
wait doesn't the panda take up both
seats of the boat oh no he sits up right
doesn't he it could work it could work
get in there oh no he
does darn it so we'd have to capture him
just like right there where he we oh
wait does it oh wait it works once you
sit in there he sits up nice awayo all
right let's go Panda
Express
yeah Atlanta Panda buddy number two
isn't Panda Express oh I feel like I've
heard of such that's food
yeah all over the world doesn't it I
think we also need to light up the top
of the building
here flip anymore oh the FL oh yeah that
makes sense okay I'll go put some
torches up there how's it feel to not be
able to flip us off
anymore how's it feel Panda man I got a
new bird cuz my bird died no no
baby bir died too that was the not by
natural causes today never forget what
those creepers took foret never forget
never forget what and never forgive oh
go
ball she she she I'm suffering I'm
fixing it I'm trying
time he's talk okay you're good don't
worry about it
oh she
back and she looking like a
snack I can't see anybody though I see
you don't worry okay she loading
in what that what's going on what is
happening what's happening oh he's
invisible oh he's he's stuck in the boat
behind the behind the Villager he's the
coward
why are those cats not I mean ocelots
not moving from the boat that's strange
we got a lot of ocelots heard some crazy
I'm going to expand the forest if I can
I wish we had more dirt though have a
lot of ocel cuz they're ocelot wait hold
on we got to kill the
Piller here's what I'm going to start
doing I think I'm going to start
replacing the dirt that we have on the
ground with other blocks and then use
that dirt to expand the
forest how to ride boat Google we'll do
orange brown hey there's a there's a
there's a invisible uh Merchant behind
so you can here I thought you meant in
the
house watch out I'm going to Star to
ground around here
[Music]
guys make so much
sense so what is there a list of things
that we'll need for fighting the under
Dragon maybe that we were kind of aiming
to get well yeah but first of all we
need to get into The Nether
that's the obsidian obsidian lava obid
this yeah I need to be able to make my
trash can to get rid of unnecessary
things I'll be your trash can a girl get
over here I would if I
could take your time W Ena has over
2,000 blocks
oh oh we got a lava bucket just as we're
talking about it let's
go
oh we have summons the lava buckets yay
yeah I'll put the lava up here and we
got blaze powder and blaze rods too
that's let's go wow that's
[Music]
huge we still haven't made any beds yet
have we yeah I think still
nothing we we haven't really needed it
much true yeah there really kind of
isn't any need yeah I think we don't
really what's next though I wonder I'm
curious we had jungle
underwater snow alive are there no kind
of don't go in
there gooa
is
pogging what what am I doing uh P oh
three two one happy New Year what do we
got so wait we don't need to go hell
Dimension and spreads chaos wow wow wow
wow Soul Sand oh we can make Soul Sand
torches I was like why is there floating
milk bucket I realized it was the
merchant
[Music]
wow W is that Fortress oh obsidian oh
obsidian oh we need a diamond pickaxe
for that yeah we have enough diamond for
pickax or diamond we can make diamond by
now w we can make a couple actually we
have 12 so we can make like what
four yeah I can make a couple Diamond
Pickaxes with the magma blocks can we
turn those into lava somehow why is my
ping 700
oh
no make a another chest maybe dang I
wonder what's going
on two FPS goba you're so
beautiful time
you no all righty stop capping be
capping
[Applause]
that those HS they just like say so much
more than any of our human words could
ever say any English
language nothing says as much as
one there's so much emotion yeah so much
passion and so many things conveyed in
one simple
hello H welcome back Daddy
M do you do you remember this
place yes looks familiar sort of hon
that's all I remember look Kaa we have
obsidian here in the in the where here
here in the block area oh
wow obsidian Ina will mine
I guess I
am all right Mak diamond we making the
diamond pickaxe oh
ooh I get the power sure if you'd like
one for what else will we use diamonds
for if not diamond pickaxe probably
diamond
swords diamond armor but we're going to
get we should probably only make how
about we make two diamond pickaxes and
two people at
it all right I will bestow one
to someone else who else wants a diamond
pickaxe power I am
trustworthy the magic
word
please we hear B can I please have a
diamond yes yes you can stop I'll do it
for a Scooby Snack oh you can yes
take byebye thank
[Music]
you okay I'm going at it
whoo whoo
whoo but even if we get enough obsidian
to build a portal let's not go yet today
that will be too fast I feel like we
need to space it out okay space it out
yeah sure we should collect materials
yeah work on getting diamond armor for
everybody also pigs diamond armor put
the diamonds
back yes all the good stuff yeah a lot
of glow stone
oh yeah glowstone good thing we didn't
use emeralds wait maybe I shouldn't have
a diamond pickaxe cuz what if I die
somehow like P wise if I get thrown to
the ne chest whenever there's something
like obsidian every can borrow it go
ahead and put it back in the weapons
chest should be fine okie dokie there's
some more iron o we're getting a lot
more iron which is good oh let's go very
necessary
nice oh wait we don't have do we have
Anvil no oh no we haven't made one I
don't think we need Anvil yet we need
gear before that yeah enough that's
true how do I plant the cocoa beans I
think you're supposed to do it on the
trees but I couldn't I couldn't remember
how I think it need to be a certain type
of tree possibly certain type of tree
jungle tree maybe jungle we have jungle
tree saplings I want to try
let me go to
go
AAA we should have AAA s jle oh jungle
okay thank
you thank you dear
viewer where are the sticks you know
what would have been a good idea for
organization is to have um all the
chests like a one chest for every biome
that we've oh be smart whated oh
suddenly big freaking
mag
bo bo where did you come from how did
that kind of hurt how did it not like
like Al alert us when it
spawned in the first place oh what the
hell so many of them they are a present
from the god of resources and materials
oops big Koopa behind me
sorry I oh scared some some someone
behind me guys Chad is is someone behind
me noise I don't see anyone behind you
I'm Tod I can't look behind me what do I
do llama footsteps cow Mo the problem
when
you're and you can't look wait the cow
escaped hello the mushroom cow escaped
no no I'm scared can you guys see what's
don't look back I can't I literally
can't look back him I don't see anything
behind you okay already the gates it's
[Music]
me okay okay go find your place
goob you're still so laggy I know it's
that
bad it's okay you're beautiful no C this
way thanks you're so get back in there
back we could have really use a
Le wait can we make a leash cuz we have
slime ball I think so m oh oh I never I
thought you could I thought you couldn't
craft one I thought you had to find one
yeah it's like four strings and one
slime ball we have string okay yeah we
have string we have
string okay I got it wait I'm already
pushing him back in I think it's okay hi
guys okay well we have two leashes in
the in the weapon chest actually he's
he's being disobedient okay get this
guy get
him who who
oh yeah I see don't kill him that's
that's not what we
want get over here I'll mine a bit
more maybe we're too
efficient nice just so you know smoke
apparently managed to clear it in like
12 to 15 hours so we do
that that
bad oh it's the Ember maker man
the rod poop outer Dr pooper outer yeah
the rod pooper outer the PE poooo man so
yeah I think at at this PO man uh at
this speed we might really not need a
whole week for this project but let's
let's really uh take our
time hey guys we're running a little bit
low on food um so I'm thinking wait we
just to make some more mushroom Ste
yeah infinite food refill your B are you
sick of mushroom stew she's sick of
mushroom
stew oh
no
can't get your SW out what do we do
Parry Parry
Parry he's destroying the
bamboo we don't have
arrows what oh what you got to Parry him
oh yeah that good p
let's do it okay it's burning the the
cows are burning we need water
water somebody save the cows the cows
they're going to fall the water buckets
is he just going to
leave put it out again can you not put
them out like
this they
fire oh no got the let's
go let's go I am it oh God we didn't
lose our stuff did we uh I lost a lot of
things a few two diamonds maybe cool
you're doing too good anyway oh I almost
died I'll try and fight him back here
maybe it will become one the clouds it's
it's in the sky it decided still there
it's one the CL I think we can make a
bow bow and arrows so let's do that as
soon as possible some right now
that was I found the feathers we can
make arrows uh we need to make a bow is
saying it will probably despawn oh it
may have already despawned honestly it's
gone okay anyways though yeah next time
next time it happens we might need
it we need to we need to make arrows we
don't have any Flint I don't think we
should don't we all right I guess I
guess a lot of our gravel and stuff like
fell into the void so we we didn't have
a chance to get no guys let's not fall
down we God the donkey is
alive you should fix the uh floor though
so no one you gave us so many great
resources where did the donkey love what
did the no cow escap hey at least our
mushroom cows safe I'm just glad they're
alive I got floor stuff that won't burn
oh you guys stop trying to enter the
human
Place hey you know if we use a boat we
could probably slowly but surely move
them to a different area so what if we
made a different pen somewhere else and
organized I'm making another area back
here if we want to use this one sure
it's like more protected kind of oh yeah
that's kind of nice yeah place to
protect the
animals I think uh the reason that that
may have happened Kiara what just
happened just now is that we were
talking about how quickly we were
we're doing so good guys I love it
o I love it I love chaos need a little
bit of a setback story arc very good A
bit more please no no no no that's oh we
got two more lava buckets and some
gold I love a lav maybe don't mind until
we finish
uh you know fix everything cuz I might
SP new stuff but
chaos what what needs to be ah the
animals oh don't worry about them okay
we'll organ we can organize them now K
don't worry about
them chaos so it's a good thing
really just got to slowly but surely put
him in boats and move him around it's
chaos is a dish best served
cold with friends yes with friends
oh
beautiful I'm going to walk off the edge
this is not good we've got another
obsidian please we need to put torches
down in this new area that I made if we
have any more uh I have a couple where
is the area behind right
here I have like four I think that's
should oh do the do the phases um repeat
like uh rotate the uh restart Yum Yum
Yum Yum isn't it random oh is it random
I thought there a order to it I know but
when we Circle back to the beginning so
no uhoh get too big but we won't get any
of that stuff back what it's too big
that means certain materials like the
prismarine is like limited to only that
face and we will never get it back hey
yo ow ow ow okay but it a certain Point
they've got to we need more blocks so
they're going to have to we H does
someone have a
[Music]
bowl you can't you can't shoot Enderman
I don't think never mind I'm already
healed bows and arrows I'll get skon oh
was a wither skeleton oh okay well I
guess it didn't drop a skull that way in
our
chance oh what do we need this skull for
where you you go you trying to visit am
we don't need the skull technically no
I'm lagging out I'm sorry I'm trying to
fix you it's okay I need boats how do we
make boats again I'm sorry I always
forget I'll type in boat into the recipe
thing recipe book oh yeah that
book
okay
book the magic book sorry boat the boat
Bo okay it doesn't
seem oh what happed sorry I'm I I always
get really startled by I'm so sorry I
hope I hope Discord muted my stream for
you slimy mommy big mama big mama slime
big mama oh little
baby
spicy my
bird careful don't hit my bird that's
your bird yeah oh goba what you want to
be small
huh I can be big no I made you smaller
cuz you seem to be really hoping to be
small I wanted to be big but I was too
big you should look at YouTube how small
I made you oh my
God it's like Plankton all you guys hear
is wait better
idea all righty we're going this way
I'll round up the
animals could I please look at
YouTube very funny no they totally know
how funny
indeed yo small G
tiny wow tiny tiny
baby baba I've got the dolphin now
there's no stopping me yay I'm going to
do things
wait I need food where is food I'm
running around in circles cuz I'm scared
to touch anything I'm going to launch
myself off the map a creeper or
something yeah I heard that now a moment
ago I see one all the way over there
well maybe it's underneath and it's
making that noise
oh
um D your worst
nether oh it sounds like a creeper
yeah I think it oh
maybe it's underneath in the water it's
not in the waterfall I'll go
check oh there's no there's nothing
here
okay weird it's
weird not the block thing is it health
is is it heavy is a dolphin heavy nah
I'm so strong oh oh is it the creeper
over there
n no is it can it be can it be
torches maybe it's underground there
something might have spawned underground
because remember there was lava and then
water got like poured on it and then
there's like a platform underneath where
a building
yeah
oh so it's possible what the what's
you're building a platform
underneath there was lava and like fire
I guess that hold on a sec um under
underneath the block that we have
remember when that guy shot a bunch of
fireballs at us yeah and there was like
lava and then I saw it it's
underneath let me look here I'll show
you check it out magma BL watch out Oh
you mean the one block underneath there
I put that there yeah look underneath
there what's with that I don't see any
guy though but things can definitely
spawn down there I bet M no it do be
empty maybe we put the Llama there no oh
okay
you can be safe there it it can it can
occupy the space and and maybe keep
other people
away n it's okay yeah we could magma
it's the parrots oh people are saying
it's the parrots I that's what I was
about to ask I like I think it's my
parrot it's like doing it right in my
ear I'm getting rid of this thing it's
it cuz it's green green parrots make
creeper sounds Grill it there's a
creeper right there Grill it oh yeah
know but he's he's harmless is this
parro
ASMR where'd the pig go I ate him but
they don't really make those
sounds maybe I should stop expanding cuz
we need more torches m true the more we
expand could spawn right here yeah the
more torches we
need I'm going to
dig
oh she going to do
it should I put back
to her
portrait she Blends in so nicely I
shouldn't try that with
[Music]
everybody
they H H stop
a more
up she's manipulating our faces
guys hey what are you doing over
there yo yahua what's going on
[Music]
good oh it's so good
oh can somebody move this massive
fuzzy really likes
you why is why is there what saying
what's with foreigners what yeah for
Fore it's a meane oh am I doing a
foreigner thing oh it's because I'm the
Foreigner foreigners just kind of like
to do that I think they just like to
manipulate that's fore that's so weird
that they're saying that who's a
foreigner oh it's a moco meme I mean
they do they just
[Music]
do kill him time to die I don't have a
sword right now Parry him Parry him can
you parry with a
pickaxe oh oh my god oh jeez oh god oh
jeez oh God to fly away actually oh Ena
no
Ena uh-oh don't wait what if everybody
hides I see I see where it happened just
go indoors
I'm going to sit inside cuz I'm going to
it's despawned already I'm lagging so
I'm going to sit inside too I'm lagging
also we just have to stop panicking it
just despawns no Panic no Panic he's
moaning cute it's just a cat uhoh uhoh
oh
no anytime now guys I can I mean I guess
I can stay here e
oh what happened it's fine I had to mind
my way out of it too but here I'll free
you sorry you
know free me anytime she
says that's my bird he's sitting on your
shoulder how much how much stuff did you
no my bird's sitting on your shoulder oh
I have a bird already oh yeah it is
crowded in here let me tell you what
looks like broccoli how much
asparagus um everything including a
diamond oh diamond pick your bird make
another one it's fine smells like
broccol have one
more yeah oh you okay oh I didn't think
it hit you I thought it was further away
I didn't think it would it would hit you
I'll put you we got five dudes living in
one house
[Music]
let me fix all of
this I don't want to play Minecraft
anymore I want to play house okay if we
play house I want to be the
cat you like decorate or something in
there maybe that'll occupy your time huh
oh
no we play house instead what's
house so someone's the mommy someone's
the you know like that kind of thing oh
I thought you you're talking about that
show oh doctor
no now we're going to be
doctors we're running out of coal guys
what do we do use wood back to the mines
help back to the mines oh yeah wood yeah
we got tons of iron so that's good at
least we can you know still make new
iron stuff oh wait can we make coal with
like or maybe not maybe I'm thinking
about charcoal dead yeah
charcoal get in there I'm getting rid of
this parrot this thing
is creeper sound in my ear it's making
me nervous
too maybe we don't want the parrots
maybe we get rid of the parrots I'll get
rid
of you could play house with the parrots
there you go
okay no he's leaving no you don't get to
leave I'm your babysitter now I didn't
think that they could open the door with
like the but I guess they do weigh
something here I'll put a boat in there
cuz they'll sit in the boat come sit
with me I think we need to make more
homes guys cuz we have five villagers in
one house and they do not seem happy
well we it's a door fine they don't have
feeling
Co if you say so you know usually the
the Minecraft Geniuses they put them in
into a like a two square two two block
uh room
like really no space to move at all so
this is nothing this is fine get in
there hello asparagus you're going to be
with me now wait we have a lot of coal
we have 60 I think your bird can also
sit in there better how do don't get
them off me N Coal
jump there're two peas in a boat to the
Y cute come look at our our
Birds asparagus and broccoli asparagus
and broccoli my favorite green Foods
besides cucumber do you guys need you
need a cucumber e
cucumber e no bring cucumber you don't
like cucumbers if we have another one
BBS cute now we will never have to
listen to them again I used to have a
green
bird but then what happened yeah I used
to have a green bird you know even if
you still had it up until this point you
would have taken it down with you
probably just now them no they can fly
yeah yeah I actually I have two birds
like this I have parakeet now cuz my
family Birds yeah two two two parakeet
I'm a pet
expansion yeah this is the first
time about
this they don't have names though
they're just bird one and bird
two you got to give them names wait is
is parake parakeet is what you have yeah
yeah they're budgies little budgies oh
my God you got you got to put them into
like a kitchen um uh what do you call
the the the not the kitchen things where
you put in the plates and so on a
cupboard yeah you got to put them in a
kitchen cup and he'll yeah make like
music and try to knock things over he'll
get like super excited not in the oven
don't put them in the oven what about
the microwave no no just the cup cabinet
it could be fun put them in the cabinet
govern it they have they have a big cage
they're
comfy has a whole my mom makes toast for
them every day cuz they like toast a lot
cute
a
cute they look just like those they need
names I think you got to name them well
this is
[Music]
amazing I let chat name them oh chat
will probably name let see ski and
RZ stop stop it no stop but no for real
you should name them aspar some
broccoli okay are they are they green
are yeah they're green perfect perfect
that's Destiny I would say once a girl
when's a boy and they might like there
might be an egg one day oh my God maybe
a you think they will make
egg oh my God that would be so exciting
you the baby art
choke baby art choke no cucumber
ew
no but it's a cute cumber oh chest chest
you want to take it take it donkey scary
the animals have been rounded up but I
can't seem to put the donkey into a boat
so they're too smart yeah don't think he
will accept
it yeah the other round he's being an
ass
[Music]
oh slime ball Diamond
CH at least I got the
diamond
mine wait isn't that the good oh it's
quartz never mind the good stuff organiz
I thought I thought it was the funny
swirly stuff funny swirly stuff
yeah oh oh there's a blaz rod oh fun I
don't have I don't have a
sword that fire sorry sorry get in your
hole
donkey yay BL Rod w
w yo it's already been three hours I
feel like it went by so fast damn too
fast we're too
efficient I'm going to write in my book
you're already writing in your book
entry I'm writing in the book book oh
how do you uh how do I write in the book
you pull it off of the picture frame we
need two more books though okay how do I
write in my book can we make another
book don't think so we don't have a
stuff oh oh wait if there's no feathers
wait yeah we can't write in the book If
there's a okay we have feathers kill the
chicken oh we have 11 fethers oh can we
make the quills
and quill is ink sack oh no we have ink
sacks yeah we have H 14
okay nice do we have more book okay
oops stock of
inventory damn and books are we are low
on food
though damn okay maybe uh so there is a
lava
thingy ow
that's really bad it's fine it's just
one of these guys try get him away from
the
forest it was it was lagging so it was
kind of standing there so I was like huh
and I bumped my head into it twice and
then I'm half
HP I look like a sweet jelly right hello
my hello hello
hello ow so spicy
oh what food do we got if we don't have
five books by the end of the stream
we'll just have two people write their
diary on Discord um for for the first
day wait am I still on the am I still in
the Stream like me no not anymore I
reversed it do you want to be your PNG
thing um I can come back I think what do
you oh wait what do you mean wa what did
you mean saving you I'm doing it because
I love you you're still visible yeah
okay oh I thought you meant if you're
still in the PNG
thingy I'm doing it because I love you
there he
goes why do I get so
shook what scared me
now all right I saved one more llama
we'll put him back wait so we have
enough obsidian to make a portal oh yeah
you said we're going to do it next okay
yeah yeah wait wait maybe we don't have
any Flint anyways like or what is it
like the we can we can light it up with
this lava we have a lava bucket ah okay
uh
question would yes is lava lava slime
possible answer are you girls free
to do an all five stream tomorrow around
the same
time tomorrow no oh Ena is doing Elden
ring or what no I'm busy that
day oh my
God what happened oh Yik there's a lava
guys oh no sorry I'm going to use your
sword wait what's three out of three
recovery
kit oh that's I think the I think the
server is lagging pretty bad so the
recover kit I time to wrap it
up the the thing um oh thanks oh yeah
here's your here stuff is over here yeah
you're good
thank you thank you thank
you and this and this and this and this
thank you a thank you okay um well in
any case I'll definitely be uh starting
around the same time again tomorrow so
if any girls want to join me what are
you going to do uh well the more we
are the more I would find it uh likely
to do the never I don't want to do it
no I'm not going to do it by
myself I don't know maybe we can do for
me should be fine no NE stuff but uh we
should probably I mean we can just
figure out a schedule after see if
anyone's available
in the days
upcoming I decide now I am in any case
available for I I made my whole schedule
empty for this so I'm always available
for
this Minecraft every day all day every
day let's go Minecraft mythcraft
MyCraft Minecraft equals
myth a
new oh wait that doesn't go there for
some reason like the combination of myth
and Minecraft gave a lot of people like
strong
Nostalgia yeah man H things were very we
were born in Minecraft born in there in
the trenches of Minecraft yes yeah born
and
raised Minecraft is an integral part of
the Hol live experience that is true or
I feel like it used to be now not so
much anymore but this these are you know
Hardcore Minecraft or this one block
Minecraft are ways to bring it back so I
find that very
delightful yeah there are definitely
some roots there
mhm can't give up on Minecraft Minecraft
is everything wo St the oh no no no I'm
hiding in the house okay okay come on
hi no not the
bamboo shoot me
no there he goes oh there he goes he's
done oh wait for the first time I'm
seeing the the we should walk off now
let's go uh I think we're good yeah the
off there's the those M things when you
don't sleep Phantoms should we all L out
then the night can pass or is that I
don't think that counts does it he's
coming back he's
coming get to cover just hide yeah until
it despawns just hide okay
well we just got to wait it out no he
definitely sees me he sees me run Kelly
inside fine I can kill him
who are you
killing uh the Phantom oh okay where are
you oh here by the chest come here be
careful jerk a the
babies I need food yeah chat we don't
have any any beds cuz we didn't get any
sheep we I don't know where they went
well we did but they died we do think we
have one wol but that was it are we
never going to get sheep ever again if
we
regular biome right the grassland biome
it's it's it's not random to get biomes
it's like in order specific order so
we're not getting anywhere blocks but
that's why that's why I was wondering if
it circles and rotates back and we get
the normal biomi again at some
point biom me Chad says the dogs killed
the Sheep oh probably why yeah somebody
said they will spawn on grass we just
got to have grass somewhere oh yeah I've
seen like grass dirt blocks but we don't
have like a what do you need a
diamond they diamonds it needs diamond
we don't have Whatchamacallit we don't
have soft where is it too late to get
grass dirt blocks then
too I think touch that's what it's
called yeah we would have needed silk
touch to get the grass blocks unless we
do something Fancy with the dirt blocks
around the one block but then
it's okay takes while like yeah we put
dirt and then get surround it with dirt
and then see if there's a grass block if
it ever comes back and let it spread
I'll think of some missions like that
like uh like create a grass block
somehow and make beds and all that so
that for tomorrow we have some goals
like
that bone meal but I tried bone mealing
dirt earlier and it didn't do
boneal I don't know if bone meal on dirt
actually works or if it's just a low
chance cuz I remember I tried before and
I
just doesn't have to be on an already
grab
block makes it
grassier I mean try it right there's
some on the chest you could try mhm we
have only works on actual glass block
like the dirt block has to have the
grass on it for yeah we we want grass
dirt blocks chat not just
grass
grass block damn real grass dir block
what about
moss can they Spa on
Moss h I think we're already past the
place where we can get moss blocks or we
have Moss blocks so oh we do you can Gr
stuff on moth stuff just have mossy
cobblestone it's not a oh it's not a
m yeah it's not an actual
mod but I mean for the for spawning the
Sheep I don't think that would have
worked anyway I guess what happened tell
we don't have any more bone meals God
and the bone meal I might have died with
it too much of her
Magic The Magic is the bone meal no the
magic is my magic oh we need
diamond
diamond okay I got it are you just going
to the
next next change
or see what okay I really going to I'm
going to look it up if it's CES back let
me just mine this one it
doesn't then how are we ever going to
get
beds ever we don't sleep in
Minecraft we'll figure it out wait it
does cycle back as somebody says so I'm
just going to look it up so we know for
sure um you can make I mean you can make
wool with string but then we would need
like a lot of spiders
we have seven cobweb and once you
complete the Final Phase the cycle
repeats and there's 12 phases so after
12 phases how far are we now we're
around like six right now no watch
out doesn't do anything on just plain
dirt it doesn't work all dirt no I'm
trying let's give him a prank our
version only has 10 phases I remember
from the start then that's even better
oh why did you give me the bone meal you
can try to check and see it doesn't work
okay you be like no try the bone meal on
the dirt eat the bone
meal no bone meal bone meal no working
no
working oh we're in PH phase seven right
now so we're close to
circling
back but yeah we don't I think it might
I I wouldn't mind playing for hours and
hours but maybe we should like stop soon
give it a rest this feels like a good
pause
point the next chapter I'll start
writing and thinking up some challenges
and I'll put them on the on the
board a quest board or
something well not really challenge but
like to-do list Quest yeah I'm
oh yeah dangerous
dangerous very
[Music]
dangerous let
Tango do we still have some paper
somewhere I think so we should I
definitely put some away unless someone
used it m oh I see four paper four paper
but probably not enough very very
dangerous whose keyboard is that it
sounds
awesome hiina
yina what are your key caps okay then
I'll ride some into somewhere else uh
I'll have to look at which one the one I
have is I have they're so
good thank you
wonder if I do this
[Music]
I I do grass block grass block grass
block what grass grass I was about to
what I do what do I do what I do let's
make a dirt path so it can spread yeah
yeah nice idea here I'll pick up some of
this dirt that's here and replace
it
grass
caaa zusa zaka zusa block
oh my
God I was I said that that I'm replacing
it what did you lose C Oh I thought it
was are you lot of things oh
no it's okay setbacks are good let me
out let me out making a a path sorry do
you have a diamond
anything maybe uhoh
it's fine don't wor about it we come
back don't worry about it we we'll make
it back it's
fine it's fine we're going to grow lots
of
grass all right hopefully it'll spread
we just got a
wait oh the danger never
ends oh I can edit no mining for a
little bit are you are you are you
flexing at me yeah somebody say we
should make a bottom floor we have a lot
of like uh Sandstone so we could do sand
bottom floor SL that might be a good
idea okay oh or maybe for tomorrow
bottom floor is one Mission how about
that sounds yeah how do you I'm going to
put a ton of slabs in the record
box I'm right I wonder if we can put
bone meal on that one grass block
probably
make the grass
long it's not
working one guide several guide I'll
ride it at the end when I have a full
list here's one thing that I think I
want to do is I want to make a house or
structure that has uh chests that hold
all different blocks of every single
phase so like if you don't know how to
like organiz or whatever that's what I'm
going to do interesting planning
that sounds good I'll do that I'll it
with nether brick okay
okay over here Callie are you going to
like how far back are you going to move
your your
stream uh probably a day
okay okay be able to play tomorrow but
the following day I think same
time uh maybe do you have all the bone
meal I don't no it's oh there's bone
meal right here I put it into the chest
on the left
grass
put
CAA Spread
spread how do you say grass and
Spanish uh this will be
dangerous oh gosh oh it's like nine
years of Spanish oh my God the grass
block who did that just spawn there that
grass block let's go
past past that's one letter off from
past oh yeah
past P past El
past I've never heard that before
okay
elor
Sak El what are you trying to say what
are you trying to say gr she will be
communicating
El Pasto everybody is so
chatty Pasto is a Shepherd
[Music]
what past is a
shepher that's what they're saying
everybody
here okay I'm what uh are you what are
you
doing I'm watching the grass
grow it's like watching paint
dry are you hungry was that your stomach
oh no come
come I think it here but as I said
anybody can log in whenever they want
ideally do it while streaming though uh
okay I heard that oh right your di
though maybe before you leave okay write
your Diaries sure how do that it's more
important for or when somebody's
playing like on their own or so so that
other people know today we're all five
so it's not that important but let's
just write it for the sake
of
completion
compl oh wait yeah we
don't no qu Dam right we were going to
do that we were going to make quills we
should have the materials
uh ink we need ink sack and feathers
four of them
four there's some fethers okay I got
them uh I need to pick up the
books because I think I got to combine
them
oh yeah you go thank
you okay let's see
quill qu quill qu are you all right
uh
beautiful beautiful have you guys ever
written with a quail no uh-uh I think I
have old school little too old school
for me yeah oh why is this one
turn it's the am way Amy you have to
ride in the am
way oh upside down you are the
Australian of the
group can I have my book book
bag
G oh you sucked up my book please please
you thing is so Superior to mine please
say the magic word running through the
bush C the queen of ping please may I
have my book back it will suffice for
now
gracias oops
n titty myth is so titty
no bullying in this like like always we
don't bully No
Bully oh I'm writing in my book yeah
write in Cho language if you must
Captain's Log day
one if you want we can do this off
stream though if you want to
focus they're already focused okay okay
now I finished I finished speed how can
you ride so fast when you have to ride
upside down how do she do
it gamer gamer do I sign
it okay okay that's what I thought
that's why I didn't do it I had a
feeling someone said that and your boy
wasn't listening all right done uh uh
okay let's uh think uh B build
uh what do you call the floor that we
want to build underneath second floor
basement build
basement um make to the basement
man get
sheep get sheep to spawn with the grass
we got to cherish that grass maybe we
should put the grass under a uh
roof yeah here I'll put some I'll put a
dirt block like underneath uh like a
different block so that way it can
spread I don't think it can live under I
guess it needs a slab above it I'll just
put slabs over the grass armor and
tools well the beds the shape leads to
the beds
so I think that's okay we got to make
diamond tools diamond armor that's all I
a
storehouse build a beacon how can we
build a beacon
already I don't think we
can you need a never star for
that never star never
star very carefully mhm kalea wither I
wonder if the Wither also just Rand no
way right it won't just randomly spawn
in there it will I hope he does we have
to make him spawn I would think like you
normally
would would be funny though if he
randomly
spawns hey we should eventually also
replace these these floors cuz if they
catch on fire uh all and St yeah replace
floors and then also um make the one
block the area around the one block very
beautiful yes decorated okay yeah that
is important too but we can all just
yeah do it together watch out I'm going
to dig some don't fall that for the
heads
up getting the from here that
uh oh make stone generator do we want
that many
stones we might need wood yeah to
replace the floors it might be good just
have stone floors Stone
generator I'm just writing down some
things we can do before we go to the
[Music]
nether what else
chat we just need more resources of
everything in
general more food also
probably oh yeah more food we need to
solve the food problem yeah we need like
a more consistent source of replenishing
food farm F make a potato farm potato
farm food farm okay so a stone generator
a mob farm if somebody wants to take
that upon themselves that sounds
difficult a food farm we have space for
it over there on the at the end of the
hallway yeah
iron farm is that can we like we need a
Golem or I guess the Golems do they
spawn on their own when we put villagers
in a certain condition or
so maybe I'm not too sure I'm not very
familiar yeah the villagers need spit to
be considered a village we hopefully by
tomorrow this
one yeah maybe maybe iron
farm then yeah if we can manage that
sounds difficult but
yeah needs a zombie ah 10 villagers
makes one Golem oo so we got to give
them bread too we need to make bread
bread bread M there skeleton over
there Dead the game hey dead beads get
away from what I'm trying to make over
there what are you doing [\h__\h] he
likes it he feels comfortable there cuz
you built it it smells like you that's
awesome I'm going to kill him now
skeleton
smell dead be's luring they do have
holes in their noses nose area yeah you
got to
die I was sure I put enough torches oh
oh the Betrayal oh no oh that's
dangerous don't don't fight up there on
the roof than that's cool it's more
dramatic that way Kara it's more dram
the
content now you got them corn let's go
let's go almost killed by my own fans
how could they do this to me okay has
everybody written their d
we yes yep
mhm you class is dismissed class is
dismissed guess
my my CH starting from tomorrow you'll
have povs from everybody who streams or
maybe just like okay not necessarily
everybody who streams eh no yeah
everybody who streams has a PO but
everybody who plays not
necessarily right but you don't have to
come to my channel okay so check out on
on the schedule or so whoever is
streaming to find us seems like some of
us might get together around the same
time so yeah we will await
you let's be productive tomorrow just
like today yeah we did so much wow we
did a ton of stuff actually I would say
yeah it's beautiful it looks like what
do you call the like is it patchwork
oh yeah yeah quilt yeah the floor looks
like a nice Patchwork
quilt yeah there's a zombie
zombie oh he's they
spawning because of no light not enough
light where is the lack of light late
night maybe I got to put more torches
everywhere I suppose it' be good to have
like a zombie or skeleton farm that way
we can mhm you know get bones and stuff
yeah I I did put down mob farm so make
whatever you want if you feel
inspired we can try to build it together
too
tomorrow if you're up for it yeah put
him in the boat next time oh okay
perhaps we can try that okay so I shall
end the stream here
gires okay what's up
a thank you so much for watching guys
thank you for
participating it was fun inde see for
the next one k
that what's his name but Ender Dragon's
butt see you guys there and not tomorrow
not tomorrow tomorrow no soon
tomorrow bye everybody two
one see it outside bye
[Music]
oh