[Music]
[
Applause] [Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Applause] [Music] [Applause]
[Music] [Applause
]
[Music]
[Applause] [
Applause] [Music] [
Applause] [Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
Suddenly, of course,
countdown
[Laughter]
Please
[Music]
Chat
Thank you
KoukaOkGoogle
[Music]
I also write in my usual voice. It's
really, really, definitely when I get excited. It's a great machine gun talk. It's true, it's true, it's true. It's true, it's true. It's true, it's true. It's true, it's true. It's true, it's true that it's true. It's true, it's true that it's true. If it's not
loud, it
won't be able to get into the microphone on stage or something.
That's why I'm positive.
[Music] Let's
do our best and mix in a little bit of Japanese English.
After all, we're representing Passion English,
so we can introduce ourselves in English.
[Music]
Todesu
[Music] There's
not much English in it
Well, it's
Little Devil
[Music]
Hey,
I'm Takanashi
[Music] It's
happened, this is the second time, the second time, the world
Time Meading Full Time
[Music]
TNT YouTubeokay
Guru Gurushi
Yakiniku
[Music]
At that time, my senior
really liked my style.
Well, that
was really impressive. My
hands are really smooth. But I guess that's true. My hands are really bad, and I haven't been feeling well lately, so they
're smooth. The
texture is so smooth. It looks
cute.
But I'm wearing gloves now, so you can't see it.
Yeah, those are
definitely beautiful gloves. I can see them a little.
Maybe I should turn on some BGM.
[Laughter]
[Music]
It's BGM Pythian.
Hey,
[Music]
Let me ask you some questions first. Okay.  We're
looking for questions so we can get to know each other better.It seems like we
haven't really been involved.It
was a little awkward, but it's still there.Until
now, until today,
until about the time of Yakiniku,
until the time of Yakiniku, we
hadn't really talked
[Music]
So, I was wondering
[Music]  ] I
felt distant from him,
but when we met at Yakiniku, he
was incredibly friendly,
so it was really hard for my seniors too.
Yakiniku
Now  Like, that's great.
Sorry. Please
leave a comment. Okay, so here
's my question. I
came here in English for a moment, but once in Japanese, I said
English.
[Music] I
love Disney, oh yeah. I do
n't hate Disney. I'm
sorry.
[Laughs]  ]
[Music]
Movie My favorite
Disney movie is
difficult, isn't it?
Rapunzel Rapunzel
I also liked Rapunzel Car
Remember Me is not here. I do
n't know.
What's that? Why did the BGM stop? It
didn't loop. It
looped. It
looped.
Here and there. Disney Yes, remember me. Hey, hey, hey. I do
n't know about Chrome.  The one I
go to
[Music]
I see.
Disney songs.
Wow.
Eamon. I wonder
what I like the most. I
quite like it in general.
[Music]
Disney If you go to Disney Sea, what's your
favorite attraction?
Traction
Japan
Where do we go first?
Beauty and the Beast
Beauty and the Baseball Museum It
's just a normal
thing to see and see I haven't been there yet
[Music]
Disney
Sea is not that
Disney Sea isn't there It wo
n't come out Ah, that one that won't come out  I've probably never ridden a character
before, but
Prime Minister's Sorin Soarin was made about three or four years
ago,
so it seems like it's new
[Music]
Not really
[Music]  It's not like I'm
going up, I
'm watching the video.
[Music] It's
like traveling through different worlds, and things like this don't fall. I
didn't know that.
Yeah, that's
pretty interesting. This is the one I want to ride. I like it the most right now.  What
I'm talking about isn't exactly the jet cost,
so I
definitely don't like roller coasters.Even
though I like broadcasting, these days I
prefer watching those rides rather than riding them.
[Music]
Even if you feel scared, it's okay.
Rand and C are
in a dreamland, so your heart won't fall.JapaneseJapanese
sounded better right now.It
's a dreamland, so I
can say that.
OkOk
thank you, that's a
good question.
Thankyousomuch
Ah, what should I do? I
just saw a story about my senior who was trying to learn Korean, but I
can't speak it at all. Starting around next week, I've been having
private lessons one-on-one every week.  I was
planning to study Korean for about a month, but I learned how many
words you spoke in
4 languages.I'm sorry, but
how many languages ​​can you speak?I was
originally in Germany,
but I was at that school, so I taught
myself Japanese, and
next time I
thought I'd try my best at Korean.  It's said that the German language is
difficult.
[Music] I
missed you. How
long will you
stay here?
How long will you be here? How big is
this pose?  I wonder if it's
about this long on its own. If it had a tail, it would
probably be a little
longer. It's cute.
[Music]
Because any cat can become a munchkin. So when you
talk to WhatCATISS [Music], it becomes like this.
[Music]  I
talk a lot to myself, and I
say this all the time.
[Music]
[Music] I
had an allergy, but it's not that strong, I
guess. Yeah, I used to have a really bad cough.  I think I'm
cured, but I don't have it now.
Maybe it wasn't related to the allergy. Maybe it
was something else. If
I were allergic to cats, I wouldn't be able to live anymore. It's
okay. It's impossible.
There are allergy shots,
so it's true.  People who really love cats
get an injection and then put up with it and live with cats.I see,
that's why I decided to learn Korean.I
speak 3 languages.I guess I
like Korean music.
Women who like groups of girls
She's cute, she
's really cute, she's
good at dancing, she's really good at
K-POP, and K-POP dances are really fast, they
're cutting-edge.Korea is actually mine,
what's the name of the single she released today?  I
made it into a genre,
right? I reacted to the two fair-skinned clothes. Is this guy
or cat this cute
?
[Music]
Scary,
scary, scary, scary, scary.
Oh yeah, and I
also like a lot of things like Korean programs and food,
so yeah, I like a lot of
things that are similar to Japanese, so it's similar to Japanese.  It
's not that hard to pronounce, but it's a
little difficult to pronounce because even though the letter G is written, it's often pronounced as a K,
so I
have a lot of Korean friends.  from that  My
Korean
friends are also in Japan, and they play
games.I
have a lot of friends, and most of them are Korean, so I
only learned to report simple games.For example, let's
go left and right.
[Music] It's music
[Music]
[Music] We
're friends, we're comrades, we're rivals, so
come on
[Music] We're
still fighting, APEX.
[Laughs]
Since you asked me, let's just sing one song.
OK for now. I didn't say anything out loud, so it's not
good. It's okay. Let's start with which one.
Which one is good? Let's
go,
let's start with Starda Stone. OK, we
did it right.
[Laughs]
Thank you.
[Music]
Thank you for your hard work, but I can see this. It's
not small.
Wait, I'm going to make this 100% bigger.
This is a triangle. OK.
[Music]
Then I'll scroll through both.
[Music] I
made two things like that, so it's okay
Hard mode Hard mode
OK Master Dust song It
's been a while since I've been singing it, so I don't remember it.It's been a long time as well.Old
Chasing somethings
Thank you very much.I don't remember the part of someone who doesn't remember anything at all.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
give me a lesson.
[Music] I
see the same smiling face as always.
[Music]
That's
not a satisfied face, it
's a shockingly timid one.
Morning sickness will tell you the same truth someday.I
want you to accept everything.In this accelerating world,
we're running away.The
snow has come.If it's a
destined fate, I'll
fight and find it.I'll
raise my voice
[Music]
Just by looking at my feet,
I know to the best of my ability Is it possible for me to touch you?
What should I do with you?My heart
calls out to me and
accelerates.As we live in this world, we
won't stop walking towards us.
[Music]
Or
[Music] I'll
stand up
and fight for the sake of what Itadaki is aiming for.
[Music]
It'll turn into strength It's
difficult, it's okay, there's no problem. There
's nothing wrong with it. It's my own guidepost
[Music] Carve
it into my heart
In this world that's accelerating  I've come to live my life.
If it's a fate that's been decided for me nearby, I'll
fight and find it. It's me. I
want to be myself at all times. I want to be myself now. If I were to
give up without my wings, it would be
too much.  The
volume is bad. I'm always standing at this volume. No, no,
this is a bit
messy.
Actually, I'm
streaming out of fear, so I'm sorry.
[Music] It's
tiny, it's tiny, it's
not really tiny.
[Music] I
feel like it's
true.
That's the
streaming.  Not really. They're
both different at all. Wow, they're
completely different. That's better.
Ok. They're
so small. I want to hear my own voice clearly.
[Music]
isHEREOFF It's
been a long time since we last collaborated on karaoke, but we did it at the porridge and money house about a year and a half or two years ago, and we were laughing the whole time.Isn't it okay to be too playful?By the way, I added background music again.This one felt just right.
[Music] I
think it's the song that was included. It's the three of us,
Flare Senpai and Senpai. It's a
strong song, and I
really like it.
[Music]
Senpai, beyond Senpai.
I like cool songs and cute songs.If I had to
choose one, it would be both.Which one do I
want to sing?
These days, it's cool.I
like cute songs to listen to, but I do
n't think singing them is cool or anything.I like both.These days,
that's the case.  I used to
only like cute songs, like Hello Project's
idol songs, etc. Well, of course, my
seniors
listen to all the cool songs after all
[Music]
Japanese rock or foreign rock Japan or
something?
It's hard to speak English overseas, but you
should also listen to foreign rock.
That's right, it's cool.
Lesson 2 is
Whatmusic.
This is the place I really want to go to.
[Music]
Just the name
Famous  I guess it's a rock
group. It's
completely different. I don't
know. I don't know.
Someone like Queen Queen Squeeze.
It's a very old, famous song.
If you listen to the ACDC song, you'll understand.  I
changed it again, so it was there, but
it's a Korean hot
dog.It's not a Korean hot dog with cheese, it's
not
a little, it's not a little, it's a variety of potatoes,
and it's a little
sweet.I wonder if it's a
Korean hot dog.  Isn't that the one in the wind?
[Music] Is
n't that the one with a stick like this?
It's got a bar, but it's potato fries.
[Music] It's hot.
It's hot cheese. It's a lie.
[Music]
That
might be my favorite Korean word on Skin.
Where did you eat it? Have you ever been to Korea
?Pervert, I
went there last year and was the one who did the
translation and transmission.
Amelia Watchong, a first-year student at my house, had a
mother who
lived in Korea.
[Music]
That's how we became friends.  I mean, I
went there with Mr. Navi, who
guided me around every day, and we also had meals and things like that,
and the amusement parks in Seoul.
It's scary
Yo System
[Music]
Lotte World was fun, it was fun I can
go even if it's raining It's
nice that it's indoors It's amazing It's really
good OkOk
let's
[Music]
How the
singing How did that song
become so good?  I'm not that good at singing,
and the
way I say it doesn't make it sound that way.
[Music]
That's why I
started liking you.
Wait
YES
[Laughs] For
a
long time, but for some reason or another
[Music]
Around the time I found the Hello! Project music,
I wanted to become an idol too.I
was living in Austria,
so I
tried my best to learn Japanese.  After all, when you
can do something you like, you
want to remember it. I
know, I know.
What do you like about netfli
Please
turn it on. He talks a lot, so I
love Netflix.
[Music] There's
something at the end that looks
like a high school party. He's
dancing. He's
got a serious face. He's dancing. There was a lot of
buzz about
who he likes.
After all, that
wolf.  She's not that cute, bright girl.
That girl
is cute. It's surprising because I like cool songs,
so I thought she'd prefer cool ones. I
like characters, so that girl has been with me forever.  You're
so kind. Who's that wolf?
[Music]
[Laughter]
Some of my favorite shows
have similar themes.
All of my senior's favorite dramas.
[Music] Even
though we have the same experience,
Fantasy Dog
can use magic.
You also like live shows, right? [Music] [Music] netfli
what game of
[Music] Um,
if it's in Japan, yeah, if it's in Japan, where
can you
watch it? [Music] You can watch it on something called U-NEXT.
Look at it, and then
buy it on Blu-ray.
There are 88 seasons. It's
long. It's a
really long episode.  Is it 1 hour
or 1 hour? It's the same as a drama on Netflix. It's
very related. It's
a little related. The
final chapter is terrible, and it's not popular in Japan. I
feel like they told Japan they liked it. They lied to Japan.  It
's not popular, but the
problem is that it's not advertised.The suggestion
is Yabe, but he
never refers to his juniors as his seniors.He always
refers to his juniors as his seniors.Especially
Koyori-chan,
333 is a great professional.  Senpai: It's
not because I'm solid. It's solid.
[Laughs]
[Music] It's
coming out.
[Music]
Netflix is ​​also on it.
It's Netflix, and
Amazon Prime. I might
not watch it again.
Netflix's original dramas are
so interesting that I don't watch Amapura.It's like
that
[Music] It's a little
weird to have a feverish daily life.Everyday
[Music] I
love it.
Everyone was really angry about the final episode of ``
So I guess it's a type of gossip.'' Well, I've never seen this before, but I quite
liked my friends.It's
like the story of a woman's life in
society.
Basically, most people
have mothers who have raised their own daughters alone, so
those two are amazing.They
get along like friends, and their bitterness is so
funny, and that's when the
daughter becomes so
important to her own nature.  There's a lot going on before I go, I'm
looking for a fantasy where I don't
see everyday things.Okay, so I've seen it before.It's not that
long.I slept for a long time, about 3 hours.A long time ago
[Music]  When I
watched it for three hours at home, it stopped and I was like, ``That's true.''
[Music] It
's a legendary movie. Even legends say it's interesting
. They say, ``Lord of the Rings'' is really interesting
. The people in that movie are going to die. Well, they're going to
die.  Is it interesting? I
said I like that kind of thing
[Music] I
want this person to die before I get emotional.
Before I think, ``Oh, that's cool.'' I
think they've done that.
Games purposely
keep killing people they seem to like.  go
Not quite, just
fine. [Music] They're chatting a lot, but they're not singing. Which song are they singing? Umm, is this a live show? Well, I'll ask for this one, but here... [Music] This one isn't color-coded, either.  No,
there are people who do it.
If you search on the Internet, you'll find it. Which one will
you do? The one with pink hair, the one with the pink hair, the one with the pink Kirby, Sheryl, OK, Towa, Senpai in [Music] Me, etc. I also use the Roman alphabet to
differentiate colors.
[Music]  It
was in Japanese.
[Music]
So if it's something like that, please
hit me. I'm OK. What do we do when we sing together? We
're the same. Double
punch
[Laughs]
Touchhapping without realizing it.
[Music] It's
okay, let's do it
properly. Let's go. It's
strange.  But it
's
okay. On the contrary, it's okay.
[Music]
If you sneeze in the middle of the world, it'll be cloudy somewhere.
[Music] If
the door is unlocked, it's no good.
[Music]
Something strange.
Strong and strong
[Music] I
want to survive, but
with the guidance of the constellations, I want to
remain on the moon that I just found. Show me your big body, which is being left behind as you reach the end of your life.
Tighten me, I
won't fall asleep.
[Music]
Ok,
turn up the volume.  Because
[Music] I
'll head east
[Music]
[Music] There's
still a
ray of life deep in my bones If I can guide you,
we'll meet.  Give me the
countryside where I want to go and wither away
until I show you what I'm
serious about. I won't sleep. [Music] The life I was allowed to go on now. I want to sink into a hotel next to you at the end of my warm life.
Until I show you how serious I am, I won't sleep.
[Music] I
want my breath to light up. I love you. I want to wake
up. He's going on alone. I love you.
[Music] I
want to be still alive. I love you.
Until I try.  It does
n't make me sleepy
[Music]
Hey, there's
something going on, thank you so much
[Music]
I can't stand it The
type that cuts off at karaoke
[Music] It's
not right,
but I get it That's what happens
when you stream It's scary how long it takes to stream
this song It's only 5 minutes.  5 minutes
[Music] It
's only a good feeling, right? It's written in a way that it's not good here. Do
n't take it too seriously. Don't say what you really think.  They say the
contrast is good
[Music]
I know it's a no-no I
know the no-go button
[Music] I don't want a
good one I'm
borderline There must have
been some good singers I
think this is it I've never
used it before
[Music]
Maybe this is a
no-no  I don't think so. This should
be OK too. I feel like it was pretty.
That one is better. The
singing is better, but this is a song by 5 people. I
definitely like it, and it's cool, even though they're young.  You
have a really good voice
OK
[Music]
OK I'll do my best with my heart I've never
heard of rap before I'm sure
I can do it If I'm
not singing I'll
forget.  Right?
[Music]
Was it a Bloom song? Well, I
don't like all the songs on that album.
This is
okay.
[Music]
That's Japanese. By the way, the
Japanese language has its own life as well. It
looked like it was really difficult, so
thank you. Thank you.
[Music]
[Laughter]
If it's too loud, let me know. I'll adjust it along the way.
[Music]
Right?
[Music] Let's
clap our hands.
[Music] We'll
pull together. We'll catch
up. We'll
come back.
[Music]
Because we'll connect with sparkles I want you to keep looking at me so
raise your hand
[Music] I'll
take it
[Music] We'll
create our future [Music] [Music] We'll create it
together [Music]
All the way to the other side
[Applause] It's
warm.
Shake the world, it's
coming
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] It's been
a while since we've seen each other. Everyone's clapping excitedly. You're amazing. That's crazy. An hour has gone by so quickly. [Music] Let's talk just a little bit more and
make an impression.  For about 10 minutes,
until my life runs out. OK, I like life when it disappears. That's
why I extended the encore. Yes, my
senior loves dancing. I love dancing.
How can I get it? The sound I can get back is Chinami.  My
body is really stiff, so it's true
that I can't move at home.
[Music]
When I learn dance, I watch videos myself.
Or do I memorize it by myself? Or is it the teacher who teaches me the
video that the
teacher made first?  I try to
imitate a little bit of what the teacher sends me,
but it
seems like it would be faster if the teacher taught me the detailed movements, but Chiara
is basically overseas.  I
currently have 5 original songs of my own,
but the
choreography for each one was done by an American teacher overseas instead of my Japanese teacher, and
since I can't meet him, I always
memorize all of them from videos, just by myself at home.  It takes time,
but it's not hard.
I'm already forcing myself into it. I can't concentrate. If
there's a movement that I can't do, I
can't stop there. Sometimes there are rhythms that I'm not good at.
Hmm, this rhythm, this rhythm.
When I feel like I can't get into it, having a teacher is very
helpful.It's
helpful.I came to Japan and
made my 3D debut, but yeah, I
took dance lessons with the Miffy members, which was great.As expected, I had a
teacher there, which
was great.  Well, having a teacher is
helpful.
It's helpful, but it's both a lot, but what's more,
when I dance in that video, I
can do it at my own pace.  That
's true.That might be true.Today, I'm
going to do just 10 minutes.It
seems like I'm going to memorize this much.I'm sure I can do it, so that
's good.I want to
dance with you.I want to
dance.Practice.It's
really interesting to practice that forement.My
guest is  Because
[Music] My
body is a little
stiff, and I want to fix that everyday
Isolation
[Music]
I get it,Isolation,
like pushing my chest out or pulling it inward
[Music]
Wow, that's amazing, that's
dangerous, but
[Music]
I also have a stiff body
, so I'm not
good at that either.Maybe if I did that stretch, it would get better.It's hard to
bend.My body is stiff, so I
can't bend.I
really
want to do it.How
many dances can I remember when I had a teacher?  Well, the
teacher who memorized it
took three hours. Well, that's right.
[Music]
But it actually
took three hours to finish, not just this three-minute song in three hours.  I
turned around and practiced for hours more at home
That's right. That's right. Everyone is so great. It's
so bright. I
want to ask you one more thing.
[Music] That
name is interesting. What's
this guy? He's not a waifu.
Twif twice, hmm, yeah.  I was
curious about Toa Senpai's creation. How did I get interested in WhatSPECT?
How did it get started? And how did I
become good at it? I'm not good at it at all.
When I went out for the first time, I felt
like I wanted to try out some kind of experience overseas.For
example, I liked
milking cows, picking flowers,
riding horses, and so on.  It
was a barium making experience.I
liked it because I had some time
left,
so I thought I'd do it to kill time, and it turned out to be
pretty easy.Once I put in the flowers and added the oil, it
was over, but it's kind of fashionable now.  I
was making something, but someday,
if I read Towa-senpai, I'll definitely ask this question, so I'll ask you the same thing again.I'll definitely ask you this question again, so
please take care of me.I
know something similar to Hellohello, Terrarium,
Plarail.''  What do you mean?
I think terrariums are probably focused on cuteness, but terrariums are
just normal. I
know this. I know Ame-chan
makes a lot of them as a hobby.  It's
really stylish. This is also good.
But I like watching videos of this. This is
stylish. I like it a lot. Actually, Ame-chan
made something for that art festival.
Everyone, please go see it.
Yeah, I made something.  I made Valium
[Music]
[Music] I
'm posting it on Twitter, but
what am I doing by the way?
[Music] I
made a puppet for
this Live English. I put a photo of everyone in this Live English.
It's a lie that was streamed.  I
want to see it.I want to see it.It's cute and nice to be seen as a strange person.But I
think it took a lot of time.
[Laughs]I was
in trouble, so I opened it for a month.So I
made it.It's
cute, so I brought it back to Japan.
Here we are, our seniors. We are
girls.
[Music]
What Poito-senpai does is like a girl. Well, it's
said that I
like beautiful things. I
like beautiful things.
This, this, this
[Music]  I can
give something cute as a present to anyone.
Hololive's logo is rainbow-colored.
This is a bonus because I feel lonely
.
[Music] I'll
sing one more song and it'll be over.
Three songs are being
sung. The Stardust Song and the
Lion.  It was blue and I got it
[Music] I'm
not going to go at all
[Music]
huh
OK, what should I do? Then my senior gave me the OK
[Music]
and
Batchri
Batchgoo  I
wo
n't even say it in English, so you'll have to guess what I'm thinking as a married woman who hasn't been looking at you for a long time.
You'll have to wait. There
's no way the princess will understand the speech bubble trap. I
won't confuse you with sweet words. I
'll see right through to the depths.
You're being moved the way you want It's simple,
isn't it?
I won't give up on the people who are playing games with me.  It's like a
Cinderella
run. Show
it to me. It's so obvious that it makes my stomach twist.
You've already made it.
Until the next one, it's
OK to not be satisfied.
[Music]
Google
[Music] You're
exposing your desires to make me feel cold. The
logic of the world is drifting away from me.  You,
you're
all, you're all on the stage
[Music]
The meaning of being here is that each store and trump card is
in the hand of the city. I
must have made a mistake in my head and heart, right?
Isn't it simple that you're being moved the way you want?
By turning all the people you're playing into [music], I've come to
understand the form of love
[music]
You laugh at the end, and the
two children are accelerating. I
love them.  Stage
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] The
two voices
harmonize beautifully Let's sing
together
Let's sing together It's
because our voices are so different that I
think they fit together, right?
It drowns it out, but it seems to drown it out. That's why I don't think my
voice is deep. It's
low, and
it's thick, so it's a bit amazing. When I
sing with someone with a gentle voice, the tiger's voice is
too loud, so I always have to turn it down.
But Towa-senpai's voice is heard by the bassist.  I feel like
it's a good balance, like songs that everyone sings, so it's
pretty balanced.The
combination
[Music]
[Music]'
s white hair ornament and that black
hair ornament are true
[laughter]  The
flowers are beautiful and cute. Thank you for the flowers.
And then there's my senior. I was so busy
asking for a request,
but at the end, I just
decided last night.
Thank you. It's funny.
I
don't play FPS games like APEX or anything like that.  It seems like we
haven't had any collaborations like that at all.The reason for this was that we
didn't really match each other's hobbies, but
now that we have Netflix, Game Strong, I
'll send you another message next time.  It's
really only at the very end, so
please trust me. It's
hard to confirm if you watched it properly, so let's watch it.
Thank you
[Music]
.
[Music] Let's
talk again when the popular soap season is decided.
Please. I want to watch it with you.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
[Music]