[Music]
[Applause]
o obession i don't If I Was Made if I
could always see
[Music]
I
need me I you I don't you know what to
do
this your me around
[Music]
[Applause]
I sh
me you see what I want I need do you
you
[Music]
come on me I you up don't even know what
to do with this
[Music]
[Applause]
good
[Music]
that's so [\h__\h]
hype even I can't deny or of course I
can't deny that's so hype what the
[\h__\h] I love how they changed like in the
bridge the like length of the notes if
you know what I
mean you never see what I want what I
need or do you like the Rhythm a little
bit normally it's like you never see
what I want what I need oh do you but
they made it into you never see what I
want what I
need it's so good it's so good it's so
boppy I'm going to
morb from now on all my songs will just
be Euro beat by
default cuz I need to get more of
[Music]
that ah [\h__\h] it's so good I want I want
the
instrumental apparently
yesterday when was the first time I used
this I think yesterday when I put the
herob bead remix on my loading screen
for the first time
the the how you say the M the remix guy
how do you call the people who make
remixes uh was in the chat I didn't see
it but I'm glad they
notice the usage of the
remixes the mix master oh that sounds
cool you never see what I want what I
need or do you no
no oh and they did that probably without
the AC capella version cuz that was like
a a month ago that they uploaded the
remix so good
hello hello Sor I'm drinking
cocacola
from uh a cup from the fast food
restaurant that has now several times
kind of disappointed me I think I'm
actually over it I think I'm over my
favorite burger I think I don't know if
I'm if I don't like the taste anymore or
if they're just if they just don't taste
as good as they used to I'm over it
yeah it's just disappointing these
days it's so
sad I don't I don't know man why why
this is why we can't have nice things
man but then again maybe it tastes
better if I actually went there instead
of letting it like get delivered to
Me Maybe maybe the extra couple of
minutes that it spent
on
transportation makes it lose all its
spark what do you
think H but that much it's it it's still
kind of lukewarm when I eat it but I
don't know the taste there's just the
it's not there's no no special oomph
anymore
I'm stalling right now because for some
reason battl net thought they need to
update my game
now and it's so
slow it's so slow but uh I'm getting
there shouldn't take too
long
yeah
[Music]
yeah how you guys doing stick it in your
oven no ew because then the salad and
the uh the Tomato will also be warm
that's supposed to be
cold good doing Dandy
wow doing
good they need to update the for the
warcraft Direct in an hour wait it's in
an hour it's overlapping with my stream
I mean it's not like I was going to
watch it but it's interesting that it's
um happening to overlap with my
stream you guys can live react to it you
guys can watch it on the side and tell
me what's going
on oh I think it's finished in yeah yeah
it's finished it's finished reclaiming
space what do you
mean okay it's
finished did I not say it I guess okay
after after over 4 years I'm starting to
like lose confidence in my Kik ke please
I don't really I don't know I don't feel
it so much
anymore it's rough maybe it's time for
an image change and I just switch up my
greeting and
everything just like the burger it has
kind of lost its oomph to
me I'm in the midlife crisis for a
vtuber this this might be the right time
to get a midlife crisis because 4 years
in as that's probably at least in the
middle of my
lifespan so it's time to get a midlife
crisis what's midle crisis in
Japanese what is it what could it
be I'm sure there's a word for it
[Music]
go buy a sports car not much that a
vtuber can do with a [\h__\h] sports car
I'm
virtual midlife crisis
nongo there's no proper
word Chun no Kiki
what a what a they don't have a proper
word oh oh I see like somewhere it's
called T Kur so they just reuse the [\h__\h]
the English
word and add the word for middle
age Chen
Kur sounds cool
Crisis
crisis that sounds so cool that sounds
too
cool I'm in a midlife crisis no no no
gotta say it in Japanese I I have a I
have a rare Condition it's called
[Applause]
sounds
sick okay I'm hooked on the word let's
play a
[Music]
game I finished uh Arcane at least to
the point where you can finish it now
and I uh am at season two of Breaking
Bad now oh that's so loud surprising
ly uh short first season I thought it
was going to be longer I was surprised
ah suddenly I was in the second
season but the first season is just half
of the length of the
other
uh ah oh yeah
right good call
[Music]
get into the game first don't show
character creation
screen
okay is why is it doing these
things okay calm down calm
down we're back we're
back no no no no no don't worry
a little bit louder for you guys oh
wait
ta great thumbnail thank
you no no no no that was just weird
things when starting up the game okay
they already attacking me I just arrived
give me a [\h__\h] moment to settle
[Music]
in thank you for the membership welcome
you oh oh I I I didn't even I forgot
that my old
T today I'm not singing all the misery
today I'm
singing oh we're like so at the top of
the map we're going into the hey pix off
oh the misery
[\h__\h] I said I'm not going to sing that
today leave me
alone leave me
alone right let me make myself a little
bit
[Music]
smaller me and my chicken ball of Hope
and
Glory what's up here
ancestor
Heights ah I remember I was here last
time H the grass looks so
fluffy no
actually when I look closer it doesn't
look fluffy anymore it looks very spiky
you
know but it looks really nice from up
here
oh I don't know if I want my ulti to be
on one
thanks to eating Eternal I'm like
constantly
spamming all these Keys now without much
fa but I guess that's okay game a little
loud now it's too loud
no
okay okay
amethyst fragments amethyst
amethy why is there so many of
you Aur wait that looks rare and
interesting
uh wait where did it
go oh yeah things have different names
once you pick them up right that was the
thing is this the alur that I just saw
on the
ground why would it change name so much
that I can't recognize what the [\h__\h] I
just picked
up and why is my inventory so
beautifully empty wow good job old
Wawa so this is like my chicken
ball but I don't think I need it okay
you identify once you ah I see makes
sense I in good old Diablo 2 you still
had to identify things yourself with an
identification scroll back in my days so
I just couldn't believe that that's how
it works excuse me
ah woo sappire brag
are they popping up more often
now I like the chat saying kandra has
engaged in Dreadful vengeful Spirit
terrifying in uh brackets
terrifying she is
terrifying they ramp up as you go deeper
into the game the the the fancy
Stones yo I just saw you kill that
person
what's wrong with you oh the rats can I
not kill is it already dead oh look at
my Hydra
go my
[Music]
babies I can't even roll this one
over where am my Hydra come on do your
job Hydra
feel like I'm always full health I never
need the healing Wells kind of lame they
should give me other
Wells terrifying serious not in
Minecraft is it is this still an a RPG I
was going to ask you actually what is
this genre
anyway in the beginning of the game I
thought so I'm
aware this is an arpg
ahuh
N guys I paid my taxes yesterday let's
go
I'm not going to get arrested let's
go also paid a lot of other bills that
were
outstanding what an
outstanding deed I have
done taxes are no they're all the time
my taxes are all the time no this year I
paid them uh I paid them in four
installments fouring from the four
quarters of the
year do the
math Fairline goods are those Uggs are
those fresh Uggs let's go no they're on
fire take them take them don't let them
burn what the hell is going on here is
this some event cuz it's yellow
or is this the reason remains
huh sorry little Panic moment
here what the [\h__\h] is going
on what the [\h__\h] is going
on
bro
huh do I kill oh my
God okay
call I can't attack ah yeah
no ow ow ow ow ah get out of here bro
should really just let my Hydra do the
thing oh now I can attack
them
ooh ah
ah pots
pots is it
dead it's over
but at what cost and and and at what
reward nothing I didn't get [\h__\h] from
that
H this is very worth it I must say huh
oh the
irony everybody wants to lie to me
now XP I
guess but that's
all
H have you seen the signs as I
have no hell is coming and my people are
not ready to face it not yet
okay you you are already strong
yes you know it you know it girl
forward I'm on my way amulet what I what
did I
get oh just the blue
one but I look look at my
Uggs oh they're good they're good
they're actually good I'm taking good
hydas are great for early game yeah I I
like them I don't know maybe they'll
stay with me
forever into the late
game I don't like how it's so visible to
you guys how I'm just mashing buttons if
you look at the bottom of my screen you
can tell I'm just
have you
noticed it's like I'm trying to play the
piano you stand still we can
tell it's fine my fighting style is fine
it's perfectly fine you didn't notice
until I pointed it
out always want to make sure that my Hy
are out as much as
possible you know and my bats but
they're like whatever it is can I switch
them
no but like they they die so fast that's
why I constantly need to respawn them
and that's why I spam the
buttons and they don't die so as it's
like how they work I guess you know they
go and they explode and then I need
more hydration check Hydra
check I do be checking my Hydra only one
of us will walk away from
this you're at the top of the world let
enjoy the storm a moment that's a cool
place to
chill very dramatic Nature's
music the dead are killing your people
as we speak and you're just chilling
here some will die yes
but that is the way of
nature it is a
crucible it devours the weak and makes
the strong
stronger and those who
survive they will save this land from
hell so she's saying people die if
they're
killed no
no this is my choice smart Lilith only
granted me the power to do what must be
done cool viol what did you give her all
things must be earned in the Wilds even
knowledge prove
yourself and you will have your
answers I don't need to prove myself to
nobody
wait okay I guess I
ow what is this ball by the way it
protects me
right ah I moved too slow I tried to get
out of
those I
swear go get him go get
him
who that other fight we had is very s
similar to this right
now but oh she seems weaker
generally this is fine a little hug
snake hug will make you calm down
right oh now the rafts have to be killed
again
no problem easy where is
she easy easy easy no
problem you happy now did I prove myself
enough to you yet
the
stronger
prevails so
be could have told you the outcome
Lilith I told her of the Ws around as of
prison how to break that why would you
do
that
why thank you
Kevin my people I forgot what it took to
defeat
asra they must learn again what if they
cannot Vanquish
him how can they stand against the fool
might of hell so you're saying give them
Double the Trouble instead of just one
trouble just to test if they survive the
first trouble cuz if they don't survive
the first trouble they won't survive the
second trouble but are you for real
because you're weakening them then the
chances of them surviving the second
trouble are honestly kind of lower to me
in my opinion but okay you do you me
[Music]
lady
loot uh I forgot how those works we will
think about that later ooh word of The
Unbroken tether 10.8 resistance to all
elements oo intelligence plus six
maximum Life Resource cost reduction mhm
chain lightning has a 41% chance to
chain five of the I don't use chain
lightning though that's the only sad
thing should I still wear
it oo finally finally something good for
my
head
nice you you gain 30 free armor but your
evade has 100% increased cool down wait
how do you invade
again EV evade how H this this this
swoosh oh my God you had a cool
down oh God I oh cool down well good
that I barely use it I
guess I guess I'll wear
it I think you never do no last time I
think I used it a little bit today I was
looking for the evade button while I was
fighting against the lightning things
but I couldn't find it I couldn't
remember it
okay was this teaming
mail why is it not comparing it on on
its
own
[Music]
okay well I'll keep what I have for now
cuz it has the gems
inside okay wait what
now all the way back all the way back
yeah yeah
yeah it up
exactly good argument hello chicken wow
cute look at them
go they're so muddy poor
chickens let's talk oops let's let's
talk I found idia and killed her
she is at peace now I
hope I need a bath should i b you you
would turn out like this imagine heroism
hand cam stream and sacrifice me bathing
a chicken are often entwined in the
course of
Fate my mother's Lux luxury spa
treatment I must still father what has
happened for chicken what Lilith has
done we cannot let her destroy anything
else and then I cook
it got to clean it before I cook it
right of
course no what for real for I was kind
of thinking about that uh you know when
I saw videos before of
like when people really treat their
doggos for a special
Spa
uh
experience kind of as a joke I think but
the Dogers seem to eny enjoy it got to
do it for the
chicken but what
if what if what I'm what if I I I I
promote this stream as
me doing you know a luxury spot
treatment for a chicken and I put a life
Chicken on the thumbnail a fluffy life
chicken and I I promoted as me doing it
to a live chicken but then the stream
starts and what I bring out is
just a chicken
like a whole a whole chicken that's dead
but like from the
supermarket and then I just cook it are
you guys going to be very
disturbed would that be disturbing to
you but now I already told you my master
plan so
too bad what do we do now should I go
here because there's no more big
question marker uh Quest marker here
anymore should I go to this area feral
nature or yeah yeah probably
there I'm guessing it's a long way
though do you class Quest first ah where
is class Quest how do I see class
Quest is it in the main city
I did finish the quest
okay purple purple these
ones gem crafting tempering
mounts sorcerer
enchanting this one
maybe the purple circle purple circle I
like that word okay I'll go there
I'm on my
way I spoiled the
surprise you seem
disappointed oh wait mark it let me Mark
it ikim we're going on a uh school trip
with my
chickens audio is being a little B oh oh
MAA your turn yeah MAA R thank you
welcome welcome to the
stream MAA I heard your new song I don't
know if you rate it together with your
viewers if you're here
listening but I listen to your new song
I really like
it I was bopping vibing to
it hey yo
okay I think MAA not in the chat
but
[Music]
Multiverse can't wait to oh oh my God
here it live someday oh my God
isn't this like the beginning area
didn't I start out somewhere
here so the mobs are seemingly
weaker fire snake maybe you eclips her
check behind you wait shouldn't she be
eclipsing
me ah the beginning area did become
stronger nice more of a challenge a good
reason to come back
woohoo where's my mouth
here there it goes my
ulti coven's trunks what someone's
pants yeah War
rival ooh this one's got intelligence I
think I like this more but H this one
has two sockets but I mean I don't know
I would probably still prefer this
one ah but 285 item power versus 270
item power it's still a bit better but
just because of the sockets
really we'll think about it later once I
start out my in inventory and by that
point who knows maybe we have even
better ones what is going on
here what a waste of my
old Idol of the
Imp
destroy yeah go Hydra go Hydra go Hydra
oh wait something came out of it the
arch
demon ah no no no don't
FR I pulled some other
enemies I'm so
slow hug care for hug don't be so
antisocial did you guys see I did the he
he
hii
test but I don't I don't know I um I
know I know that um I got a high score
but I
think
my the way I stay in the way I shot in I
don't think it's like as
concerningly like sickly as some people
can unfortunately become like worryingly
shut
in I'm like like one of the big reasons
why I'm just also never going out is
thanks to my job
being from
home so I have even less reason to go
outside that really adds to
it yeah yeah yeah congr on your high
score thank you
but yeah if I have the choice I'm
definitely always staying indoors and if
I have the choice I'm also not
interacting with anybody if I
can and just chilling with my cat
so that's just how it is for me and I
don't think it's like something to be
worried
about cuz also I'm still
like m how to say like I feel like I've
seen cases of hicky
Kumi where even the whole living
situation is concerning like they're
usually from the concerning cases from
what I saw it's like their
whole like indoors is a mess with like
some of them get yeah surrounded by
trash and so on right they can be quite
the hoarders I don't I mean yeah my I'm
I'm my home is surprisingly clean these
days h
as
what yeah so I don't know I wouldn't be
worried about my lifestyle
um
mhm you even on a cleaning mood recently
yeah
even even you know doing the whole thing
with my garden that's a lot of work
man it's a huge spider who F the spider
so much people say oh yeah keep your
spiders alive in your home because they
eat the they eat the the Flies and the
bugs yeah you should keep your spiders
alive don't kill your spiders yeah then
one day they'll turn out like that
they'll eat more and they grow more and
then one day they're as big as you and
then they're going to eat you so what
you going to do then huh I don't know
about keeping spiders
alive what's if you are you not going to
talk to me
bro is he hunting oh
yeah yeah yeah
yeah what's going
on they thought they trapped me but in
reality I trapped
them that was sick though good attempt
guys
Dam no hurting spider oh yeah I saw like
recently the first gen they got uh
like
cute cute Hood Parkers
thingies and hat got the tarantula one
so
cute she's so cute I saw a little bit of
her unarchived stream
today she sang cuz I'm a
[Music]
que I'm a we
cute stop being so annoying
go stop attacking me at every [\h__\h]
corner I don't belong here I never sang
that in Koka before
huh maybe I should oh they see me from
so far away I just wanted to peek
oh what
the holy [\h__\h] I think that was some
weird ass uh oh God the
poison the
poison okay wow
if you sang that my tuny heart would
burst
again who the [\h__\h] is setting up these
traps catching me off
guard I don't know why I'm even going
here I'm just trying to like check out
every nook and cranny
how are you supposed to non right I feel
like I got to because especially cuz the
cooldowns are so
small it's motivating me to spam am I
playing it wrong where where where where
is last time there was one viewer who
really was good at giving me Diablo uh
advice are you are you here again who
was
that can you tell me if I'm playing the
game wrong
PA passive skills also reduce cool
Downs I always spam Diablo good okay not
only me
then I used to memorize this but I
forgot most of it so it's been a
[Music]
bit Yeah there's so many
builds I'm just relying on what chat is
telling me to do mostly why is this so
far probably cuz I'm taking so many
battles upon
myself maybe Diablo is actually a rhythm
game
yeah if you play it like a DJ I'm
sure it'll be
fun you guys really want to fight
me I'm going to I'm going to retreat I
don't want to I need to move
on I'm I keep on getting
distracted going on a different path
cryp of the necro dancer yeah that game
looks
interesting I forgot that we have FMS
for
that are you guys excited for the next V
update I'm excited I don't know what's
coming you guys got to send me the email
as a uh screenshot again please probably
I don't think I'll be able to see it
again probably 900 p.m. right 9:00 p.m.
my time
yeah the tevision I
know cool collaborations nice to see
here when cool people get together to do
cool
things okay who what's this actually
haunted burel like a tiny little mini d
ah should I get distracted no no no no
no no or maybe maybe
maybe I was so close to
resisting it's very fast okay have I not
already been
here well maybe not doesn't look
[Music]
familiar oops
oh who
something pushed
me oh my
god oh that's really it okay so if we
kill these then the the mini burrow is
done okay wor
it nice nice nice
yooo pick it up pick it up
um Highborn vow
wow nice vicious
heirloom but I guess I'm just going for
staffs now oh wait there's oh a better
version of my
stuff
mhm
15.3 CR no it doesn't have Critical
Strike damage but it has Intelligence
it's just like a little bit better than
my current one maybe I can just leave it
Lord
guide no I have a legendary Helm no
thank
you yeah okay good loot
[Music]
bot I wonder is the int or the crit
better for me int is better
okay then I think actually I have one
thing with
me 10% basic damage sure we could do
that
uh right now we have Critical Strike
damage wait we we're talking about the
weapon right
yeah see no good perfect I mean basic
damage you guys said that was good last
time a good choice
I ditched a helmet for
what oh because I have Max what the
hell because I have Max
armor why why would I ditch it for some
what what would I oh my God what would I
ditch it
for that was a weird greeting it's
almost like the burrow with a
trap anything that's not hurting your
Dodge
Oh you mean do uh for
[Music]
but when I find another legendary Helm I
wouldn't mind switching
it oh I don't need my dog that
often okay I have arrived finally I
guess oh my God
oh let's fight
woohoo
ow what
the world W Oh I thought it said World
wrap it's wood wrap wait I need to get
the wraps okay okay okay taking care of
good job
Hydra unchain the chained
ones oh my God there's so many of them
if I'm too slow does he keep on adding
on to them I
wonder I'm trying my
best is there a
timer but just for like Mastery don't it
should be
fine oh he's ready he's ready to die oh
he's dead is there more oh oh oh
oh
oh oh this is so
chaotic this is so
chaotic oh did I do it did I do
Mastery no I guess
not damn
it I got something purple
I saw check Miss monster probably so
close you got a gold chest so you did oh
I did all right let's go yeah I would be
surprised if uh 26 seconds went by so
fast because the moment when I looked it
was 26 seconds left and it didn't feel
like another 26
seconds a nice dagger that I won't use
ooh 270 item power ooh Max maximum life
oh okay I might wear this
[Music]
one these
are
[Music]
okay attacks R attacks reduce evades
cool
down oh hey what I didn't know that I
that this effect could help me with my
100 second cool
down the more I attack the more
my cool down will be reduced there's
some Synergy
there but besides that I don't know not
much different 18 and 19 One Life per 5
Seconds five maximum not much
different anyway I need to look at this
I know I have a point available for a
while
now
[Music]
um should I just strengthen my Inferno
or should I add you deal 6% increased
burning damage this bonuses increased to
25% to enemies while they are affected
by more burning damage over time than
their total
life
okay killing a burning enemy increases
your Mana
regeneration right now I don't have Mana
troubles yet but who
knows infer repeatedly pulls enemies to
the
center
oh sick
go all in on firewall I don't know I
haven't been using it that much
anyway I want to strengthen my Hydra if
I
can I love you okay going to L now thank
you Max HP better than
regen regen is better ah different
opinions oh no please forgive the mental
intrusion I could only trust another
Mage I've searched too long and too far
for the hidden archives to give up at
its
entrance I'm looking for a book known as
The Forgotten codex said to be in the
archives maybe you should ask sh the
Forgotten codex is a compendium of
Enchantment techniques developed by the
Ania Mage clan m some say zultan C
himself was one of the
authors unfortunately
the place is overrun with demons beyond
my
skills if you can retrieve the Codex I
can teach you the magic it contains
could be an excellent outcome for both
of us say I suppose so I'll see what I
can
do he's my brain worms my intrusive
thoughts and now I'm helping my
intrusive thoughts
so that they can
rest and leave me
alone yeah it's nice that she has a
voice and she talks quite a lot for a
protagonist very
good those freaking gummy worms they
look so
yummy get them out of my face
and looking for the right
book nope nope not one of
these if this was
realistic I would be looking for every
single one of these books here and here
and here and that would take ages
suck him in yeah did you see how they
got sucked into the
middle stay in the middle like you a
little is that my snake what the
[Music]
heck h where are you
book
[Music]
hello I'm looking
for uh the Forgotten
codex it seems I have forgotten about
its
placement get in here get in here get in
the middle
yeah oh my God who's sucking my
blood
you look at
me a beautiful
statue of the beautiful
keandra uh okay no we good we
good I like these blue
light
sources was so
pretty I wonder who used to wander these
Halls before these goblins took
over what happened
left or right maybe left cuz here's a
dead end and
then and I don't know if up or
don't what's the snake again that hugs
its enemies to
death don't all of them no some kill
their enemies with just poison right
pythons boa Anaconda yeah I was thinking
of an
anaconda my anaconda don't my an don't
my an don't unless you want some
what can't help it
where am
I why you
die should I not go over here maybe it
will Circle
back how come there's no snakes in all
life
H maybe in the future you never
know
actually
wait no never
mind wait did did reglos have an animal
or were they all
humans I think reg GLS are all humans
right but flow glow has a tiger at least
cuz I was going to say
recently there's just been a lot of
humans
debuting at least on the Japanese
side they're all humans okay but
like I guess she's just like okay she's
still a human she's just tiger F okay
then that's a hell lot of humans wow
[Music]
okay are they trying to appeal
to
humans foolish foolish ambition
there's just still so many possibilities
so many vtubers you could create so many
animals that you could make into a
character or objects even I really love
how for example
Ana the the concept of making
a a traditional dagger into a vtuber I
love that I love when they get creative
like that
I mean nothing against humans their
designs are really pretty really cute
really
stylish really
aesthetic I should actually be glad
because if if they weren't like
restricting it to humans who knows they
might have added a bird if they were
including animals they might have added
another bird and then I would be like
what the [\h__\h] do I do with
horony help bird overlo
overload oh they despawn oh there they
are birds too crowded needs to be
controlled okay
I'm I'm glad because like I don't
really want to
oh want to like gatekeep hotori too much
but I don't like it if it gets too big
either so thankfully they stopped the
bird
spam you you guys could actually count
as a branch n no I think we're fine as
just a little little unit
[Applause]
blast blast with Arcane power brings
destruction okay I should have activated
that
before right there's a there's a boss
here yeah wait that wait nice
that that just one hit killed the boss
I very
nice that came at the right moment okay
come on come on get some more get some
more now it's
gone
ah
ah why is the music so dramatic
and I need to look at this room
mechanical pedestal interact what do you
want me to put something on
it don't think I can deal with this
now oh my
God what
the the [\h__\h] did you see my HP I was
chugging I was chugging
real hard holy [\h__\h] no go
away that [\h__\h] menu can I turn it off
completely to never show up even when I
what what's even the button that I'm
pressing middle
no you don't need to complete the
dungeon for this Quest you just need to
find the Cod ah ah is it e the [\h__\h] off
wait I opened the chat ah wait why do I
keep on pressing that it's pissing me
off I think I know
why cuz like w ASD right for moving and
then above are the 1 2 3 4 five and then
e is this menu emote it's just too close
when I'm like trying
to go from walking to
[Music]
attacking I want to rebind
that where is it
wouldn't it be something like
emote let me look for the the key
instead e e ah action wheel action
wheel
um here a button that I don't even know
where it is if I was looking for it
because my key caps for those buttons
there are just cat
faces so yipp my e button is free
it works guys it
worked these just cat facing yeah
they're
cute
oh oh no
move okay why I cute
who is this wa that you speak of I like
cute girls could you please introduce
me to this cute girl you
mentioned can you tell me more about
her how are the cats doing the cats are
wonderful what is this Goblin hug him
hug him don't let him
go he's dropping coal
is it good to kill him early or should
we let him drop
things hey wait
for poison a
trap kill
him that's like the the golden bunny ooh
oo that's a lot of stuff do you get
better stuff the earlier you kill him
maybe it's like the golden bun in
Zelda loot Goblin go Goblin Goblin loot
Goblin I'll look at this later but o wow
nice
maze H wait sorry I don't say you mean
go gobbling these I think that's what
they're going to say no my chat wouldn't
say that there they are pure and
sophisticated oh I have a box with me is
that for the pest
pedestal yes you
are don't doubt yourself I believe in
you
oh yeah my cats have been really good
actually Smoothie has been very well
behaved and not really forcing me to
wake
up like maybe she'll meow
once but she actually gives up pretty
fast and lets me sleep so I thank her
for that very demure very
mindful just like you guys the
com I picked up a codex why is it
not I didn't know I had these I think I
just picked them up in this dungeon
wron codex
huh what it's the unforgotten Codex oh
leave me
alone okay
okay play hard to level up fast no I'm
good I'm good with this difficulty
good stream title yeah I can't really
think of good stream titles or like
tweet descriptions for this game can't
think of anything good but at least this
title is good that's all I could think
of what let me look at the map man
ah we're close to getting back so then I
I guess I put the thing
down in its socket oh there we
are uhuh okay I might be able to finish
the
dungeon not just the
codec oh wait we need to go up
evil and hot you think that's hot really
thank you wow what the hell do you have
the
Codex hey don't run out of my snake
that's
unfair oh my God he's crazy he's
actually kind of crazy he's actually
kind of [\h__\h] buff holy [\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] look how barely his HP
goes
down
a he's butchering
me this is a [\h__\h] nightmare this is
going to show up in my
nightmares this thing chasing me and
buttering
me at least he doesn't hit too strong
but holy [\h__\h]
what the
[\h__\h] oh good
drops what the [\h__\h] guys full
inventory Mama Mia old enemy from Diablo
1 yeah
really
e and his his axe oh man unique axe am I
going to get a unique weapon from my
class at some
point ah damn it I don't use axes but
that looks
strong I guess I'll sell it wait does
it oh yeah
37,000 nice uh rare Helm 46 armor 19
okay
okay ooh juggernaut's exceptional h oh
this might be a good
replacement no this also you gained 23
armor but your evade is 100% increased
cool why this one
too
no but it has two
sockets yeah and it's generally better
so at least I'll switch to that at least
[Music]
ooh another weapon that I don't use yeah
I saw that one before hey wait can I do
uh portal to city and then come
back cuz I want to
sell and do these items still stay
here bro they're so
heavy
o there we
go where did that go throw out the blue
stuff yes they do they stay okay but I
guess for
[Music]
now they don't have the intelligence at
all become injured while crowd control
grants you Unstoppable for 4 seconds
These Boots don't really seem the kind
of boots that I would
want
sadly you can read the scroll okay good
oh yeah this one too sourcer motion can
now be used for
tempering pyromancy augments fiery can
now be used for tempering okay okay
okay oh 18 intelligence plus maximum
life
plus a
socket
sick okay okay uh so I I I if I
go oh
wait if I go to kill
theot by clicking this I can go back
right to the dungeon where I am
now t for teleport oh thanks
okay just it feels like the dungeon were
pretty far through it but I need to sell
some
things
um who
lag pretty Okay so I'm
lagging I'm lagging in this
shop a break down
oh
everything father sell the unique axe
okay anything
else
no
um why do I do that again at the at the
at
the are you the you you the one oh
temper learn type of recipes from your
inventory um yeah that's a that's a
purple Quest
huh yeah maybe maybe
later I want
to salvage
yeah I'm going to get rid of
these
[Music]
sadly wow
you can just select magic and it will do
all
Blues okay I like to go through them all
one by one to look if I'm really not
making a mistake but
[Music]
okay um what do we have yeah the Rings
might be worth looking at but not this
oh wait I get my oh this is not the wait
wait wait wait the the one on the right
is yeah I think I wanted to switch to
that
one
[Music]
mm this is the one
I
exchanged and
5 ah ah this one's nice
I's gift to urine a druidic ward Stone
set into a ring inscribed with the Rune
with runes that bear the promise to keep
the wearer safe a gift from the past to
safeguard the future ooh
bound good ring yeah it seems like a
lore
ring
uh
27 wait wait wait wait wait pants 270
intelligence I was going to wear this
right but the
sockets n maybe I don't
know we don't even need
forns sock more Val it maybe if I find
another I one of two sockets sometime
soon and then this um no and then this
uh
oh lurking vestments
sorry I have to look at everything
slowly I'm always looking at the numbers
and
comparing it's necessary I don't want to
make a
mistake um we don't use
books take your time thank
[Music]
you this is my old staff so goodbye
my old
best
[Music]
22 might wear
that and police car same [\h__\h] trash for
fashion
yeah it's close it it it is it was like
a little bit
better attacks of those shoes reduce
your
Dodge really what the
heck kick
rival ah movement speed
nice about 17 Riv
19 bye
that's my old old helmet
right okay so now it's between the Rings
um let me look at them
uh we
have these
Rings
3.8 which one's the best 280 270 230
okay maybe not this one then this one
for sure
right maybe exchange with the ring that
doesn't have a socket here
this one's this one's also a story
ring 17 intelligence 23% damage over
[Music]
time
uh I don't know maybe this one isn't
even that
good Max life plus int is good
right so this one I think we can switch
out with should I switch it with this
one or this
one yeah less armor if I switch at that
one no but I can if I switch this one
with one that has a socket I can just
put the armor thing into that
one I foret that if you hold out oh yeah
shift no oh
ahuh I don't know Swap this strish
treasure
out
[Music]
okay Mage to advance from
a
what there's a whole life Guild in
Diablo
Rift band is bad despite the
socket uh oh
okay should I exchange of the blood
Lantern we're just losing 250 uh
armor not really worth it maybe I'll get
rid of all these now
you have a kfp
too up for
real what guilds in this game for what
for online play and stuff I'm I'm
completely seeing it as a solo game
again not that I'm playing solo again
what I can
roll stats on the
ring still wearing the distinguished
one yeah cuz I mean the 250
armor I could put it on this one but I
don't know I don't know I'm thinking too
much let's just uh get rid of the other
rings
B the ulst let you reroll one what
that's so cool but it's RNG
huhuh
oh look at this group of people who have
friends and who aren't playing
Alone look at them and then look at
me all
alone all alone fighting through the
wilderness fighting for myself to
survive but yeah inventory empty again
yippee uh but wait do I have any empty
sockets yes I
do wait so this is
not is is the 489
including
uh yes it is including okay go put this
in here more 739 armor
yeah let's get some
more socket thingies this one has one so
an armor 15 strength
dexterity maximum life
willpower barrier
generation 4.5 healing received 10
strength or intelligence as long as I
still have those I'm going to use
those
um cuz intelligence should be good for
me right I'm just going to put it
everywhere there we go no more of
those
okay yellow for armor green on weapon
you get it I get it we get
it
yippe return
me those are blue but
okay no blue is not good enough for
me
ridiculous
laughable 1166
anani to the scholars at the Calum
Palace
Library five moons ago
I requested a manuscript necromancy on
the Transfiguration of souls by Callum
the
Elder it was only yesterday I received
your letter of rejection you call my
work dangerous unethical Blasphemous
that's the game you are too blinded by
the charade you call piety to see the
truth thank you sharing new territory on
the frontier of the magical unknown
unknown mention my research will proceed
with or without you is this a
quest or just some random
lore into the
[Music]
unknown random lore okay I'll go left
first we're back to
party sorry to keep you guys on your
tippy toes in here
uh your salvation has arrived
oh I see something on the
map Diablo
is ow pretty pretty good for like chill
gam play
man so
chill can play like pretty brain
empty I mean sometimes I panic but it
still always turns out
[Music]
fine I like
it like I would play this in my free
time
honestly now that I'm grown and not
afraid
anymore I know that I ran past it don't
worry doing it on
purpose ow
my snake is so
good guys next
week um
um I'll be gone
for half of the
week just so you
know wait no not no wait what week are
we yeah next week next week I'm gone for
half of the week but I also have an
exciting
collab plan
for next week to send you
off before I go I
suppose mhm I won't say
Yes any hints
no you must
suffer and wait it out
y [\h__\h]
hello League of Legends of
G
nah don't worry it's not
that it's something more worthy of me
hyping it up
I have the second thing to put on the
pedestal yipp then I can finish the
dungeon
probably is it going to give me some
kind of boss fight I
wonder honestly fun as long as you play
only with friends yeah I think even my
friends my IRL friends I think they play
Lee a little bit or or some other game I
think sometimes my IRL friends play
valerant together my IRL friends
actually play together and even though
gaming and all that is my job I never
get invited to this to their sessions
what the
heck but I mean valerant would really be
my game of
choice they're afraid of my my gamer
[Music]
skills
nah but they probably know I'm too
busy what's going to
happen
uh-oh are we going to fight something
that comes out of that oh
yeah oh no move yeah
oh
easy my Hydra is not doing it I tried a
little bit more like King and placing my
hydras in this fight I don't know if you
noticed but
yeah I'm too
strong
amazing we got some cool stuff again or
what ooh mental
IR
no watchful
wrath
no all this
No frost
cage
o Shadow G 85 but no
intelligence too
bad okay I finished the dungeon
and I am going to return to
Morin where is he
is he
like right out there
yeah so should I walk outside can
I oh oh nice there's a leaving dungeon
thing
okay what simply walk back to
Morin I like your jokes I like load of
the Rings
jokes you get me
kfp oh what the
heck nice ring
I I feel like I saved that guy for the
fifth time
now and he still doesn't thank
me is someone there that's why you like
rings of Power are you saying it's the
Lord of the Rings joke the whole show
huh is that what you say
huh you're so mean dark and
cold please
stay grandfather was supposed to walk me
home no problem this is easy let me take
care of
it
oh why are you Reviving The corpses oh
no careful little boy
it's okay I can handle
this
yeah you do your thing you do what you
got to do leave it to Mommy
keandra oh what the
[\h__\h] what the heck what the heck
Panic Map
opening I don't even see the boy
anymore hello what the [\h__\h] oh the
grandfather oh he's already dead he he
died
twice he was alive he got resurrected
for 2
seconds w was uh was this like a thing
that I could Master again I think I
mastered this event
successfully I
[Music]
did any other
drops
nope okay I don't really know what this
was about and he's still here so
okay goodbye good luck with your endeav
I'm sorry for killing your father or
grandfather
again let's see here yes yes without a
doubt this is the Forgotten codex
finally I am Bound by my word you shall
know the magic secrets contained in this
book we will work together come I have
prepared for this
ritual oh
sorry for that I have some aggressions
that I need to deal with
sometimes look at me I look so cool in
this
outfit all right imagine me in life to
be in that outfit would you be so kind
as to light the elemental
brazers what yes sure easy how do you
you know that I'm a fire Mage wait this
doesn't even work Sparks of fire hear us
SP by the flame to the dark light of the
dark don't stop don't stop just go your
own way how do you know that song bro
you're streaming Sparks
huh the fires are lit dope lit super
based looks like some of these pages are
damaged sorry no matter I can infer the
meaning from
Context are you sure that's wise I
refuse to let caution keep me from the
secrets of this book I've come too far
sounds like something a crazy scientist
would say great powers of the elemental
forces Guardians of the Hidden of the
Galaxy I call to you in the names of the
Divine and infernal powers that you
would hear
us Exquisite that should do it you have
to take a firm hand with these
Spirits uh something is
wrong no what does that tell us don't
assume the context if you don't know the
context either find out the real context
or just stop assuming the context
yeah get
it chances are high that you
wrong
mhm wait there's still something alive
oh oh they're taking a some time to
respond they really taking so much
time
awkward love your thumbnail thank you
graphic design is my
passion or
um photo manipulation of what did they
say foreigners like to
manipulate
images I I don't know what to say I'm
certain my interpolations were correct
or at least in the spirit of the
original all this wasted effort perhaps
my translation of the book was incorrect
uhhuh going back to to study my notes
again I think it's best if I leave the
book with you consider it thanks for
your help you know how you intruded my
brain and became my intrusive thoughts
Mr Sir guy well it seems like this book
has intruded your brain and became your
intrusive
thoughts you should learn a lesson from
that we could all learn a lesson from
that Mr s guy
Mr gu
Sir Mr
surge press G what
why this this new assign skills to
enchantment gain passive versions of the
skills I I can't think explain
what am I supposed to think
use my brain at the
bottom what what do
I uh which one this one I like
Hydra after spending 200 Mana a
five-headed Hydro spawns for 10 seconds
oh Hydro also Burns enemies for an
additional 100% of its base
damage well that's here as well
though so it just brings me an extra
Hydra with five heads instead of four
heads lucky hit up to 25% chance when
dealing burning damage to spawn two
firewalls for 3
seconds each time you summon a
non-familiar conjuration you have a 25%
chance to spawn a family of Familiar of
the same
element
okay someone in the chat good evening
who can PL me from 50 to 60 what
princess Carri or what
pull power
level people do that to random people in
this game
letting them
leech letting strangers
leech Fireball in
it when you kill an enemy they explode
in Fireball for 50% of its
damage that is actually pretty good I
kind of stop
using right I kind of forgot to use my
right click
who okay sure why not I'll take that
also we have a skill
point
um yeah yeah yeah we're working on it no
no leave me alone I already did there I
just did
this wait a
second leave me alone
no what do we go next to we do now the
main
quest is this a side
quest Exorcist Cash Cash SP no I'm not
doing that again bro never again should
I go here get your ass to M okay
chill feral nature Quest
okay then maybe we shortcut it a little
bit from here
maybe Mount Quest should I but wasn't
that like
level level
capped do the purple quest to unlock
more features don't be so
reasonable fine
[Music]
fine that was before they changed it
okay all right fine I'll do the
reasonable
thing I'll do all the purple
things then I'll learn how to do things
tell me about gem crafting how to make a
b boo I see you have an eye for quality
yes I have an eye for quality finer gem
cutter in all of sanctuary I see I see
bring me your anhum stones and I will
perform Mir
[Music]
Miracle wait that's
it Salvage and gems will break them into
fragments that can be used to craft
stronger m
actually some of my gems I really don't
care much
for
like I don't know I actually don't
know wa wait so this is not really
what what wait these are not really the
things that I thought they would be I'll
do the mount
thing you can dust them all
e no that would be
Reckless check the other tabs at the
Jeweler take one of my steeds free of
charge heyo what's the
catch
huh what do I just
exceed uh exceed
ex do I
spill protagonist juices that you can
see and you're like oh man that's the
attack this I have to
exude I have to give her out he's a kfp
uhhuh secret kfp in hiding Ms can be
purchased from St master and or
discovered through Sanctuary once
acquired each Mount will be available to
all characters on your account oh wow
once you have acquired a mount you can
call it by pressing Z while mounted
press space bar for a burst oh now he
wrote it in French
power
level burst of speed to pass for enemies
ooh your Mount can get scared around too
many monsters if the bar fills
completely you'll be knocked off no you
can select your summoned Mount and
customize its equipment at the stable
monster I want the mounts that you get
with the new DLC I saw there's like some
World of Warcraft mounts they look so
[Music]
fancy
who it's just IM immediately started
running wow pretty horse nice
horse very
[Music]
convenient goodbye
horse that's was easy talk to him to
customize it well how much can I
customize it can I turn it into a
cat get one from twitch drops twitch
drops
what o
you Cow Horse what the
[\h__\h] what the
heck oh actually I didn't I I didn't
mean this one but this one would be nice
too but I saw
um there yeah there's like World of
Warcraft mounts I guess you have to pay
for them but this one you get for free
if you get the DLC I
guess but this was kind of cool
but I don't know it looks it looks like
it's been for some [\h__\h] let's go with
the fresher
one oh
wow this is like
something an orc would ride
on
maybe but I like this it's very
honorable n wait I can't see go away I
can't see
properly this thing in the way
this barely looks like a cat
now okay I'll I'll do
this oh wait I can
buy I can afford a cat I can afford a
p is it the waste of money I have
463,000
but I might get the DLC soon
wor that's very cheap you get plenty
money you have enough oh yeah I don't
know what else to use it for should I
get the nantu or the
lucis what fits more to my
character that's a pretty horse
too black
I don't know both are
nice
okay okay you don't buy back
okay
so now I'm suddenly on a cat is it also
faster probably not I think it would say
so but you don't have any proper like
extra armor for my cat what the hell
I can only like if I get the DLC I can
probably add this to my Panther oh yeah
it looks like an elephant what the
[\h__\h] why does this make my panther look
like an elephant I don't know
weird I wish it had something more like
this but no we're more we're more raw
light shine on
you whoa okay kind of
cool wow
I'm I'm riding on a big
cat can you believe it don't let us see
this unless maybe she might enjoy it so
what socket double swapping socketable
in a fully socketed item can now be
replaced by selecting a socketable and
inserting directly into your equipment
suetables that cannot fit into an item
will now replace with stair Set uh
okay man your suck of theable items for
the sucker the bus tab in your
inventory
okay I don't know what to do with
this another time
then wait is the thing gone now no it's
still there what does she do I have to
use it until and then it goes away
sucker the B sucker the B suck of the
bll
[\h__\h] I just heard something else
corpse are
egies go go wait that was the Forgotten
codex was that okay to give it
away too late
now too late
now let
it ELD
[Music]
Mayhem h
kind of
interesting is this good guys
experienced Diablo players is this
good 18
intelligence two
sockets 6 okay I have to wear this I
have to wear the proven cords they have
proven the themselves
worthy I keep on opening this because B
is I think the inventory and E an
eternal B for bag I think it
was stck with the
B and maybe yeah in World of War 2
beef for
bag all right all right what what what
why those no I don't care anymore I'm
not going to talk to them anymore I
don't understand what they want from me
and I don't really know can't be
bothered with
it let's go with my big panther big cat
to the next
region to the next main quest check with
the knights and te M about Li
all right can we just like go by all
these enemies now and ignore them
beautiful I can go even
[Music]
faster what's
this what's this
dot oh a player's name or what couldn't
read
it I'm zooming I'm not even getting
distracted by things
but this is
interesting I want to stop I want to
fight
ah let's fight a little bit otherwise my
exp oh that was too
simple oh yeah this goes hard give me
more enemies
oh
no what's happening
what did I just did I collect gather the
corrupted remains oh it's a little event
again you would be dope if the panther
would fight with me yeah I mean if I was
something like a druid which is I guess
the World of Warcraft way of saying it
but I'm sure there is a druid in this
game
especially now with the DLC right what
was it they they uh
summon some kind of spirits was it
animal
spirits oh no it's that's literally a
druid okay well there you go that's how
you get animals to fight with you
I kind of want to try out Druids man I
loved like trying out Druids in World of
Warcraft
2o cuz I just love the idea of having
little cat not little actually big cat
running around with me fighting with
me so I think even with the
I used to try out the class
also but in both games I never
really got far with that
class I right they
transform never mind I'm thinking I'm
thinking of a
hunter but both is fun I tried all of it
out oo dtic
sickness explosion
[Music]
oh can go up
here Hunter is cool I have Gorilla what
where in World of Warcraft
or
durage you can have a
gorilla I want to play World of Warcraft
now [\h__\h] not for a gorilla necessarily
but I don't know it sounds it just
sounds fire but it takes so much time
it's so time consuming and I don't
know probably not the best stream game I
don't know I don't know I mean all
MMORPGs I guess are a bit difficult to
stream yeah cuz especially cuz I want to
if anything if I play an M more PG I
don't want to like do this like
automatic leveling
thing and make it so easy for
myself oh my God I cleared that in an
instant battle stuff oh we got a
interesting stuff maybe I'll take a look
in a
moment boost were mistake yeah that like
I hate like
I hate that nobody like enjoys grinding
anymore like they just skip it why would
you do that that's like what what M RPGs
are
about but okay like I would see if you
already have like five characters on max
level and and okay the game for example
released a new a new class and you have
to start a new character in order to try
out the class but you already been
through the whole grinding a million
times and you're still playing actively
you've been playing actively the whole
time in that situation I I would see why
you would want to skip it because you've
done it too many times and it's in your
recent memory still perhaps even but if
I go back to a game after a long time
then then I do it for Nostalgia and then
I want to level then I want to
grind
right sorry I just wanted to fix
something because early game content is
dead when the MMO has been
around dead as in you'll be like the
only person running around I don't know
I don't see a problem in that and maybe
less people would be running around if
there weren't those
boosts I don't know I'm not a fan but if
there's enough people who want to make
use of it then of course it makes
sense just not my
thing oh for FF for FF I can see it
because even even when I tried it out
which was already when a big Community
has been established and I was late to
the game but that was years ago also but
even
then there were not many
people in the lowlevel regions leveling
with me why did I open that I wanted to
open the
inventory M two
sockets uh besides that ah no no 40
intelligence oh that's rough but two
sockets 52% overpower damage might be
good might make up for
it not great either but two
sockets
ah I'm just scared of playing it why you
can get an extra socket at the oh
okay can re it oh yeah maybe we can
reall it later interesting we could try
it
out why did I why I just cleared this
region did I stay for too long
I just
chilling beinging
chilling
okay infinite Exp
glitch Mires in your head randomly great
I succeed
yippee event should
I no no leave me alone intrusive
FS I'm on a
mission I can finally Traverse these
lands so fast oh my god look how fast I
got here compared to how long it took me
to get up there
saw it overgrown verit broke another
trap hello welcome your new
master what are you
[Music]
cooking you know yesterday I cooked my
carara again but I kind of failed I
didn't like it I'm so sad and in my head
I made this joke that I really wanted to
tweet out but then I was too lazy to
tweet it so let me say say it here um in
contrast to
wait what was his name
again what's the guy again from breaking
dimensions a breaking Breaking
Bad Vander yeah so in contrast to Vanda
I did not like what I cooked today was
going to be my
joke breaking Dimensions the guy from
breaking Dimensions is Yago the guy from
Breaking Bad is
Vander no Walter who the [\h__\h] told me
Vander who the [\h__\h] is Vander Vander is
Arcane bro who said
that who got me to say
bander V it was
you so much confusion wa now I have to
say it again
um
Walter in contrast to Walter I did not
like what I cooked
today there we go nailed
it Jinx we have to cook no no no you're
mixing things up too
much the whole Forest has gone
mad we're not going out there again
night Captain Razia have you seen a
demon pass
free that's such a weird question am I
the only one thinking that's
funny have you seen uh Satan passing
through here um excuse me excuse Excuse
excuse me excuse me m uh just uh
wondering have you seen
Satan passing from here no no okay oh
thanks
though there's a horned woman in the
Moors corruption if that's what you
mean horned yes she's after The Druids
who vanquished
asteroth ah that mad man nef lives out
there we already tried checking on him
got as far as boglin Stone Circle and
then the druid's wolf companion appeared
and bit one of my
men I'm already short on nights not
going to risk what I have left on some
bastard who hates the
cathedral why does naane hate the
cathedral Naf sees us as Intruders
stealing from his land but how does he
expect us to
survive we need Timber to build or to
forge our weapons Wild game to eat truth
is I think his hatred for us goes back
to Donan they were friends once but they
had a falling out
oh my fingers are still kind of weak
from
yesterday what happened between him and
Donan not sure but I met the duu at once
I was riding through the Moors minding
my own business when he came up and
spoke in the Beast tongue caused my
horse to throw me I broke my leg hasn't
been the same since R me me oh my god
did I just do the I'm just glad Donan
came to his senses and broke it off with
that
me
me thr
me I lost I think I had it for a moment
though what a miracle
we're going to go and search for
nothing oh maybe no need for Panther
it's pretty
close time to kill some mobs who is
you no answer rude
too austan to say
h
um
rude it's a
choice not an
inability what the hell what
the what are these snakes they're
getting crazier and
crazier and their drops even better
y oh [\h__\h] I should have sold
things no we'll be fine I can
teleport no oh no that's the other one
um do I see a itty
bitty
pit we shall check it out maybe it's as
small as the other one look my ban is
there wow he's so big standing up like
that oh this even looks like the same
kind
of uh
pattern as the first one that I walked
into oh it's the same it's the absolute
same easy easy
easy low effort but okay I'll I'll I'll
take it I'll take
it for some good
loot what did you do to the
cabonara yo I I don't know what I did
wrong this time it was just I even got
the better cheese this time and I
I grinded the
cheese by myself instead of buying preg
grinded
cuz they say you going to do yourself
fresh graded yeah graded
shreded and my that was exhausting you
know on the day where I did my whole
gardening my hands and arms were already
so
weak and I shredded that cheese for 15
minutes or
so was actually way too much cheese and
then my balance was weird and then like
last time I had first the egg yolks and
then I put poured the shredded cheese
into it but this
time it was just kind of weird cuz I put
the cheese first and then the egg let me
tell you what came first the egg should
come first and then the cheese if we're
talking about egg and cheese what came
first yeah it was a mistake and then I
don't know what else just the flavor was
kind of off and the
texture and I I
I think I cooked the um bacon too hot so
that it didn't have enough time to lose
enough of its fat slowly because it it
became pretty crispy pretty early on it
was like bacon blocks not
Stripes but yeah yeah the fat didn't
render out yeah I did I did too many
things wrong because I thought I don't
have to look back at my recipe this is
simple I probably
remember and I mean I mostly remembered
but I made small mistakes and now I know
to not do those mistakes again in the
future yeah oh well yeah the fat is
definitely a big key because it tastes
much better when the Bacon fat is like
more apparent in the flavor I I talk
like a real
Chef speaking of Chef 43 minutes guys 43
minutes for another
reveal chef with s yes chef with
s the stone is carved with a message
welcoming travelers to the forest where
they can become one with the nature but
something has been written over it in
dried blood Cathedral dogs not welcome
what those poor dog was that dog was
just a good
dog I'm not one of the knights hi baby
oh
I want to keep
hug a fluffy boy I'm looking for your
master
nef I know it's not literal dogs
probably but they literally spawned me a
dog so maybe it was literal
dogs good boy lead the way okay he will
understand human words that I speak
perfectly I'm sure he gets it
go good boy oh good boy
oh
join follow
okay does he stop when I don't
follow big cat not scared of
dog big cat not give any shits about
dog hey hey hey don't run so fast
where do my dog
go to do trying to protect you oh there
you
are having some fun be right back
doggle Mommy gets distracted
easily all those enemies can become
invisible dragon staff NY NY
n okay I lost my power then it's not fun
anymore let's take a look at this
stuff 50 damage ew not good
enough wait what about this it wait this
this a new
one
53 now they all suck they all are not
good enough I think
yeah the shrines are so good I want more
of
them
oh c
cing I need to ask
the the remix person and just sent me
the instrumental I want to sing Mirage
EUR beat
version and I want to make a new Coro
just for the EUR be version I'm so into
it it needs its own like more energetic
More Bounce Bounce
choreography don't you
think maybe some elements can stay but
some needs to be adjusted
oh they're all great I liked all of the
remixes I hope there's going to be
more I'm just happy there's any to begin
with honestly but I I would love to see
more claw marks riddle the decaying body
a single word is written across the
Fallen nights chest
trespasser
trer very French we
wee how did you do that dogle
I didn't even see you do the
thing I must
question where did you learn these
things are you monkey what the [\h__\h] is
this place it's
terrifying oh
my have you lost your lower body
somewhere
sir oh God let me just walk away from
him I have a skill point
[Music]
enemies continue burning for 3 seconds
after leaving for you gain 5% increased
Mana reg generation per
AC ah which one should I go for this
might be useful if I
ever really have Mana problems and
firewalls
up but
all that is his
blood holy
[\h__\h] that's a lot of blood My ultimate
okay should I just put it into the main
skill
or your pyram while Inferno is active
your pyr that's sick but I still don't
have Mana
problems although that sounds
amazing get Supreme
Inferno but I I I never had a problem
where I ran out of
Mana you deal 6% increased burning
damage for now you
will okay okay I'll
try now uh who's going to clean up all
of this [\h__\h] not me just letting you
know you made this mess bro you do
it how are you
alive who are you
you stink of
D but he is not here insane coward
you're insane he feared Lilith might
seek you
out he was
right she did that okay yeah looks like
her work she put me here makes sense I
am beyond saving yeah I believe it all
you can do for me
is find the
demon I will help
you go to the North she is there burning
well I just came from the North or you
mean the north from here
specifically there is still time to stop
her fear
will accompany
you
hurry fan is the the
Dogo oh yeah oh he's got a name I didn't
know this did we know this
before cute follow the flow of
corruption into the Untamed ficket uh is
this Blood going to be our oh dear our
marker of where where to
go
amazing heavy flow shut
up I am on my
period i i okay I want to fight
yeah tried spamming as hard as I
could literal blood
flame
what my flames in the
blood yeah I guess
[Music]
meor me me me me
me and they drop more oh God I need to
find
enemies what or is it just dropping
randomly what's
happening no it's from the enemies
right
oh it's I know it's the thing but oh my
oh W whoa whoa who
what okay it's
over okay I'll I'll go now where the
quest tells me to go I just wanted to
make use of
the the greed the
greed you took over
me
greedy you know that I'm
[Music]
for I love Ariana I love her too
she she's in a new movie that's out
right Wicked I don't know if that's good
I think I I think it's probably not that
good from what I've heard but Ariana
Grande is in it there must be a way to
bring it down maybe I'll go watch it I
rarely go to the cinema to the movie
theater the lightning in it looks
terrible musical is based on it yeah
yeah yeah what it's based on is good but
but I hear that
this movie is not so good wait how what
destroy the unnatural grow what what how
what where
what
elsewhere like
nearby what
ah this one's still left I
guess oh and this
one oh wa on the left
side the movie is being split into two
parts what so it's not even the whole
thing what
they put out half of a [\h__\h]
movie when's the other one coming out
have they filmed it no
right
[Music]
[\h__\h] no if it's I'm not paying for
half of a movie I know that's maybe not
how you're supposed to look at it but
that's how it feels right now now that
I'm being told that it's not the full
story it feels like I'm being sold half
of a
movie happened with Dune too
really it's like I go to a pizzeria
restaur and I get half of a [\h__\h]
pizza for the price of a full
Pizza I Amin buying
that just like The Hobbit yeah I guess
see there I didn't complain about it or
like for Lord of the Rings either but
for for L of the
Rings I think
wait when I watched it I watched all
they were all out for Hobbit I think I
waited for the upcoming for like the the
other
releases but it didn't feel like I was
scammed it didn't feel like they were
selling me half of a movie or even the
third of a
movie now now that you tell me that
we're Wicked I just feel differently why
is
it I think perhaps it's more
um Justified
for uh or it was more Justified for The
Hobbit for me from my
POV I think some people did say oh you
could have just put all of this in one
movie what the [\h__\h]
bro I don't know I'm glad
they now in hindsight I'm I'm I'm fine
with under old bows hangs the heart
fruit cuz the Broadway musical was one
play One play not two let it yeah but I
don't know that and flood the streams
and borrows I never watched the musical
so it shouldn't bother me
but I feel it I can sense it they're
scamming
me is there anything else that's good in
the in the cinemas right
now anything else good from
[Music]
Hollywood in this Crimson crad coming
let there be born an amalgam of Rage
war of roam soon that's not in the
cinema
right Joker 2 heretic Venom free ah
Venom free wait was that Marvel or the
other
thing uh I'm I'm not really I don't know
I I've never watched a Venom movie
that's
Marvel I wouldn't
really understand anything
it's just silly comedy it's not Marvel
it's Sony okay okay
chill chill chill
relax should come to ausan Cinemas in
the month what for real to the cinemas
wait the war R that's the the the drawn
the animated one right
that's coming to the cinemas I thought
it was just going to be like on Amazon
or
something or Netflix or some
[Music]
provider oh okay no then I have a good
reason to go to the
cinema to The
Kino I go to The Kino and I've watched
the movie In The Kino
Transformers one no I don't care about
that sorry to disappoint
you that doesn't sound interesting to
me transform ne's
blood it all flows
sorry Amal Amal
Amal Amal
I'm amum
amum it's
scription that's what I'm thinking
of ow the heck so you're like everything
aren't you oh oh yes you seem to be wait
I can't attack
you he's
raging chill
come to me Spawn of
hatred we have tender meat to hunt no no
don't run away now hey hey hey damn it
wounded but not dead could I have killed
it I tried
everything
no would I've gotten better loot if I
killed it I I almost had him script it
okay good bro I pisses me off even if
it's
scripted
uh two 20 20 intelligence 300 item power
oo maximum life
o I don't have a sock right now A socker
the bull a socker the bull sock the bull
that's a good ring yipp jackpot
[Music]
okay cool cool cool cool at least one
good new thing return to naine
na okay let me can I leave through here
no where is
he there right wait where was he where
was he nean the guy on the tree
me missed the Waypoint
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] and I can't
leave
like and I can't get all my Panther
right now
[Music]
either still in the tree
okay I'll walk
out duck duck H press e oh uh you mean
this button I am
right account why not is there is
scripted there something happening in
the on the exit or
so no no don't
worry it's okay to remind me I forget
many
things I have a skill point again
okay I didn't even look at this
yet oo crystallized into a rushing wisp
of
ice whoa
what he disappears but this is an attack
to I guess a good way to enter
fight anyway uh tree was like here right
wait should I get the
Waypoint oh it's in the
city G okay no I'll go to the I'll go to
the Bro
first then attack this m cool
I also missed the one in the library
area oh my God what's wrong with
[Music]
me what is wrong with
me are you
gay
sorry I guess
[Laughter]
you stop her no she was already
gone as she always is piece of you
always Chasing Pavements a beast born
from your
blood it's my fault look how good the
boy is sitting there and
listening good
boy to help me destroy the
night Fant
who I told
her your
ASO is
hidden h
i why in her
presence I lost
control
ra
rage raged exhale
there only one thing that sound such a
like such a raged exale end the
corruption the r ex tail sounds
like Get it that's how it sounds like
you're doing it wrong are we killing him
are we ending
him oh sh
oh
[Music]
man I feel you I feel you good
boy sad dog no look at him
can I pet him I think I can only pet my
own dog but he's a good
boy I like big fluffy good
boys yes
yes the fluffier and the bigger the
better sad dog
okay where are we
going oh okay so
far what the heck but I'll make a stop
here here
here is doggo not following me
anymore big dog I mean
okay it does seem like I do have I I I
start to have uh Mana problems now oh my
God what's Happening
Here big
party stop shooting
he'll stay there
a oh oh never
part
Alex another party
hey I love how everybody just dies
simultaneously how
funny who are you why are you
gay oh sorry I thought you were the dog
that was following me before no but you
are
evil Fireball enchantment ah what what
did I enchant uh Fireball on I don't
even
remember
what what Oh you mean the the thing that
I did uh the passive for Fireball what I
thought that just makes things explode
when I hit it
I guess those were
explosions oh wait I think now I
understand in any case it's
cool who is
good yo this is s like un noticeable
make it like more I don't know put put a
a pillar there for me to see I'm
blind I can't see these
things wa I could teleport why would I
[Music]
walk oh they are all from the f ball
okay cool then it was a good choice
thank you for leading me towards
it my misses things in front of her face
too don't we all don't we
all
um what's this
Legion event begins in 10
minutes World boss I want to kill the
world boss one day okay uh we're going
to this place
ignore he's such a dramatic sire and I
just ignore
it what the heck wo
I should put another skill point into
something that helps me with my
Mana what I said before aged
badly definitely aged
badly it's not like really stopping me
from winning
but know I'm starting to be a little bit
critical um perhaps o was there
something
here uh you gain 5% increased Mona
regeneration per active firewall this
could
help I think I'll take it Fireballs suck
Mana so hard
oh let's go with
this they change a lot of the sorcer
tree oh really
yeah suddenly I'm using right click all
the time now I can't stop using it so
now my my Mana is
drained I've got no Mana no Mana I'm out
of Mana
this looks like a place that could show
up in Elden
ring blocked I'll have to find another
way inside do you know the way
I know that way I also know that
way oh
hello where is donut the horned woman
the Beast don't call her dad she's Nissa
them not our steal not our
prayers listen to me I must find Donan
Donan where is
he some somewhere
inside dead like the rest for all I know
the light has forsaken this
place wait L is narissa why do you think
I'm playing this game it's like a Nissa
a dating
simulator trying to
learn how to raise up
[Music]
nza but can the nisla really be
rised the one who
Rises may she be rised
is it
even
fathomable full in Mama
Mia I go to zakov shad and I come back
to this place even though I think the
guy is right in front of
me I'll be right back
oh he looks
cool sorry I get to the city I think it
always did when we played online as
well uh
yeah hello please help me all magic all
blue right yeah and then
came apart
nicely this one
I've think we could wear it's actually
minus no never mind whatever whatever we
don't need
it I don't need it no no you can take
what's left
uh no
no
no no let's go
it pretty ring but
no
[Music]
no no you can take what's
no
no this one I will
wear uh so let me take it
off well swi do a
switcher father bless what do you need
at this level you can mostly just look
at the item power I do I but I do end up
looking at the like looking for stuff
like intelligence
specifically cat jumped on keyboard oh
that's
why your cat wants to get to know me and
I want to get to know your cat
perfect anything breaks hand over your
cat
now it wants me it wants me so bad as
gigy would
say hand it over meow we need a cat
review
[Music]
stream hey yo what the [\h__\h]
tiny Improvement but ah but uh nah
sockets oh but I can add sockets oh my
God I could have saved this person if I
didn't go on a shopping tour really
quickly yeah I should put a
socket oh well if I find a really
cool piece of armor that I want to
use but I'm like oh man it only has one
socket or no
socket then maybe it's ooh stinky bomb
Worth to look
into where are we is this like a big
dungeon I'm thinking like maybe I should
drink one of my potions or is it not
worth it would it be a waste
am I going to hoard everything again
like I always
doow drink it always
[Music]
wor don't have to worry too much about
socket until higher level okay
let's
drink
these
cold so cold I just step over her body
ruthless that's what you got to be in
this
world did you
see did you see everything went
flying it's so fun
I do feel stronger right now the Elixir
is
working guys monkey moment four
minutes 4
[Music]
minutes 4 minutes D what do I do D if I
go in here does it continue counting the
30 minutes
I don't want to waste any
time I wonder what they
reveal like if I do
this feels like the game is still
happening collab with
go to town to be safe but then
definitely what just just standing in
town won't save my time thing you
know fre minutes
stle three minutes sty
oh
[Music]
wow make sure to immediately send me a
link of the
email H not a link a uh a screenshot
please
what the [\h__\h] is this
lag I feel like I'm in the middle of uh
starting
a low
dialogue but it's too
minutes [\h__\h]
lights
ofak I go
into um
I go into uh character
selection news news breaking news
breaking news
time I'm opening my
Twitter I'm opening
v v B Ramen to
yes I'm awaiting my
destiny one minute
D 50 seconds
D 40 seconds die
you drum roll
30 seconds
D
anticipation yesterday was uh apron that
was revealed one out of nine things
today the second one out of nine things
shall be 15 seconds D wait 10 seconds d
they tweeted but they tweet tweet they
tweet
it did
they yeah yeah there's a new oh let me
download the video don't watch it guys I
I I'll download it I'll download it and
I'll show it on screen download Twitter
video and then after we watch the video
I hope we can read the
email but I'll show it on screen but
make sure to leave a like on the video
on
[Music]
Twitter okay the
team video
time uh let me place things a little bit
nicer I'm
here you go here for
now
okay and then
okay begin
oops Ember record room oh this is easy
this is okay this is nothing let me try
the computer and yeah I don't know why I
thought I'd be on uh but the mouse is on
hang on what is this team member records
they really need to improve their
security oh oh oh here we go kfp
un0 the free got chosen the free got
chosen warm that's strange something's
not right about these IDs there's a
class h and a Class C and I don't think
anyone's here at can I
roast the person who wrote this is
probably uh
Tim class why do you why are all the
letters Capital except the L
what a weird
mix something I I I need to take a look
I've heard some rumors about how they
fire people I want to read this status
active facil facility man requesting
lower
shelfing what are these I need to all of
them these Department listings food
preparation versus preparation of food
that's a weird distinction to make why
would they feel the need to do that
don't ask you don't want to know the
answer make
sense maybe maybe this other file will
explain things more this feels so
familiar but remember don't learn their
names wa that that sounded like ena's
voice but I know it can't be oh no there
wasn't supposed to be anyone here I'm
not getting sent to the usual room over
this done with me wait I's not right how
do I know the usual room I saw some time
before they get here I don't know what's
going on this this doesn't feel right
there there's got to be something in
these records that can explain what's
going on guys grab gra before he gets
our
secrets why is it so hot no don't have
time to think about it you know exactly
what I'm talking about I'm uploading
these files to you now arrested
something there we got to get to the
bottom of this I'm we're close I got to
leave I heard footsteps
okay okay in Alert in alert you guys are
so late with your
reaction why are you not stopping him we
need to protect our
business okay let's check my Twitter has
somebody sent it to
me reposting retweeting you don't say
repost
oh oh ah
it's a it's the a name
[Music]
pin let me show
you
wait that doesn't work he's
cute
bro Jif Jif my ass
reading
[Music]
time
okay I nearly got caught agent but I
managed to get to F managed to get find
get to find the dossier on KF O3 I heard
rumors about how they fire people
here these departments listings food
preparation versus preparation off food
H that's a weird distinction why would
they feel the need to do that here's
what I found I've attached additional
Class C and class H records I found too
yeah so okay it's a really dark photo it
I think it looks nicer
probably it does look nicer like in this
Polaroid it looks just dark but it looks
nicer okay they need to show like proper
pictures later on U but it's like a
little uh I I think it's like whiteboard
uh is material in the middle so that you
can write the name and then erase it
again I think that's what it
was so yeah you can if you go to events
like conventions or or like whole life
concerts or so you can put this on your
shirt and then write your name and then
you can have like you know everybody say
your name without asking you
awkwardly yay
Y and it's supposed to you know look
like the name pin that people would wear
on their uniform if if you were to
actually wear one
mhm
yes yeah like a name tag description
animal pin featuring kfp logo Origins
unknown attempts to track manufacturing
Source lead to a non-existent address
writing one's name is strictly forbidden
by management citing emotional distance
protocols
what I just said write your name now
this says Don't Write Your Name notable
observations pins appear to generate own
unique identification numbers management
active oh oh oh so don't write your name
but write your number no no you can
write whatever you want though of course
management actively avoids learning
Bearer names insisting it's better this
way HCL class and cclass pin
differentiation protocols implemented
after several World concerning species
verification errors pin seem to warm to
specific uh team members who have with
previous experience to certain scenarios
what I don't understand this
sentence team memb c87214
24s who visited the usual room for an
indis closed length for losing their pin
subsequent investigation revealed team
member C8 724 had been class H at shift
start research team observed pins
displaying saddle color shifts under the
heat of a
blowtorch really don't test it at home
guys suspect it to be a form of
anomalous communication between pins
communication ceased under direct
observation and removal of blowtorch
interesting payroll reported
simultaneous time card submissions from
research Division and special projects
development sharing identical log in and
log out times despite multiple
Corrections and warnings issued from HR
investigation impossible as all relevant
pins found to have been retired
management frustrated from not being
able to send anyone to the usual room
over this h no I wasn't frustrated at
all research division requests
management stop referring to pin storage
as
the
heavenside heavenside lay bucket never
heard that before Sounds new to me
research division would like to inquire
who keeps classifying team members as
jelal and want CR CA what Jellico if any
is that a cat's reference is being used
for this designation archive test data
suggests current P behaviors consistent
with original project paramas why the
[\h__\h] did
they just because I like cats I mean the
movie also hinder fired employees must
be properly differentiated from fired
employees exit
paperwork
enough
enough that's also cat's reference the
heavy
side I don't remember that Tim is a mad
lad Tim is a mad
land making fun of my cats like
likeness Mama
Mia okay so second item is now a pin you
can combine it with the apron small
animal pin for your name kfp on it y
yipp there's still they're still not
showing the big guns of course they're
going with the smaller items first but
this also very cute please look forward
to more make sure to go to the thing
again to vote for what you want to see
next yeah yeah yeah apron was small well
no but I mean
like you don't know what's to come you
don't
understand you have yet to
understand so much cool merch though
yeah I'm
excited it will be a big lineup so
please continue following this tomorrow
is my day off so we will not look at it
together
unfortunately um but you know I'll be on
Twitter can't be Mecca is
real all right back into the game oh
wait it closed the game completely no no
no no it
didn't
oops accidentally created a new
character no no
no we're going to play a little bit
longer of course I wasn't done
non
Chucks wait where am
I [\h__\h] was I supposed to save the
game something where am
I
no have to redo the little
dungeon no
no h oh okay but is this before I took
the
Elixir no it's after but I don't think
I'm I have the effect of the Elixir
now can't leave mid d a
man I was like right at the end of
it wait so did I lose the EXP and stuff
that I uh gained so far wait are the
enemies gone
all the enemies might be
gone oh
no except for
you no there is
no everything else is safe okay so I'm
getting double
exp fine with me
is this a graphic
bug is this a graphic
bug oh yeah that's a
graphic when I was first only paying
attention to the golden thing but this
this part what is
this what happened here
crazy [\h__\h]
[Music]
man he's a long boy very
stretched all normal nothing
weird double loot maybe
[Music]
also
okay oh oh right I I might have changed
the desktop audio volume a little bit is
it still is it too loud is it too quiet
is it fine
oh Uggs Uggs I love Uggs just a tiny bit
loud
okay I lowered a tiny bit was that tiny
enough
yippee I made an amazing entrance just
now did you see me Dodge that just
now this girl is some
fire what are you doing what are you
looking for who do you looking for
battle staff Galactica
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] was was does that remind
me of the way that
explodes what does that remind me of
what other
[Music]
game no not a party POA but yeah kind of
similar but I'm thinking of a game
where that was also
[Music]
possible you guys not know what I'm
talking
[Music]
about man
B SK
maybe why is sp
G who is who is Bal who is gay who is
Bal
wait I can't attack in
here why are you restricting my actions
light cleanse these Faithful Servants of
their
sin bring them peace who says I'm
Bal someone's house when did we ever
care about that
bloody Miracle you made it here in One
Piece One Piece leth and that Beast tore
right through us could have killed me
too but she left me untouched I feel so
she's toying with me right
now wants me
to watch her destroy everything I've
built how does that stick in the in that
wall even those gaps don't look really
stickable did you see your in the way
you came
no she hasn't won
yet there's still a chance to stop
her you guys with your can't do it alone
perfect
explanations I'm with you where is she
now
an old chamber beneath the keep that's
where asteroth
is I didn't Vanquish him like the
stories
say I imprisoned him in a soul
Stone it was a last
resort I built elim over the stone to
contain its
evil I spent my life watching over over
it keeping it a secret so asaroth would
never hurt anyone
again not even my son
knows I'm sorry for hiding this from you
before but I couldn't risk a stranger
finding out the
truth we should get
moving sorry I was super zoned out for
like two full
minutes if you didn't see your I have no
idea what he talks search on the way not
a single word was registered in my
brain I'm
sorry you
to my even my eyes were like Blurry like
I didn't even see things clearly time
you
saw we were discussing what happened to
a remember Soul Stone and then willth
stormed the keep didn't take notes I
ordered some guards to escort him out of
elim I should
have stayed with him who's who's
he who is
him all right doesn't matter I'm just
here to do my job whatever it is I kill
things his son
oh do we know the name
one of urine's
protectors yurin wait Y is yurin your
son
[Music]
a right didn't we see those two together
uh last
time when we went into that one
little
village I think I
[Music]
remember I had to think of shi's orange
urine thing when I was watching Breaking
bed because there was this one scene
where they just do a [\h__\h] closeup of
the toilet bowl whe when uh Mr White
pees in it and it's uh some blood in
there and stuff and I was like Ah that's
what Shi was talking
about
bro she only has inserted
brain worms in my
brain he was with but it was so on topic
it was the same day evening
night it was still fresh come
quickly yur's mace is
here I told them to get out maybe he and
tried to stop li could she have taken
him
somewhere what possible reason would she
have
he means nothing to
her we need to move the way to Ester us
is through
here oh really through
here you think
so Earth and
page Why is l so eager to find astr is
he going to fight with me oh is he aaz
question but I'm as much in the dark
about it as you are I'm afraid they
share a connection
I'm a strong one at that astero is a
guardian of Lilith's father
misto the Lord of
hatred don't Yap while I'm fighting it's
hard to pay attention you're actually
saying interesting
things a guardian of L's
father mistal the
guardian as if in
like the modern sense or the traditional
sense maybe
both yeah mefisto is Lil's father and
asov was mephisto's
Guardian
interesting C oh oh prison got out
that see we need that
clarification I was thinking of a
different kind of
Guardian like from a minor the
guardian here it
is the Soul Stone
chamber Lilith has what she wanted all
this time damn she took the stone [\h__\h]
no sign of your Endo but there's a sign
of her here let me step into
it
wo ooh that's a soul Stone mighty
asteroth
the Char Duke
himself confined to a cave what in here
in that thing what what a Pity no
way daughter of hatred sounds like I
have an offer s run you will grant me
safe passage to a place I am no longer
welcome in
exchange I will give you freedom
and
more oh you'rein
preny his pride and
joy your
retribution if you give me what had
horns in the shadow I thought it was her
Shadow but then it moved exactly like
him
n you have safe person
oh oh did you have to do it like that w
w whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa why in
his
head was it another Vision did you see
yurin no I didn't see anything
yes
he Lilith stabbed him with the Soul
Stone my
son it's always the hand sorry
[Music]
Don
this this isn't
over I know what
I no there's still
time you have to trust me meet me in the
Great Hall time time for some horrible
crying acting oh no from
Donan guys I don't think this this is a
normal
headache
traitors they did this to me to my
boy what do we do now just find urine as
quickly as
possible I realize how hopeless this all
seems but I've spent half my life
studying the Soul Stone I know its
nature it will take time for Estero to
overpower my boy I taught him well even
now he he he's resisting the demon
influence so wait by planting the Soul
Stone into orang he's trying to carar
perhaps all those innocence to burn will
excite asteroth make him fight harder to
to take control ASO Lilith has what she
wanted from asteroth revive Meo
misto I
he oh okay no asro okay makes him a host
for asro okay that's what I thought
that's what I
thought
mhm eventually he'll be taken over
not why are these guards not
helping releast as in exchange for a
path through h
what are you speaking figuratively or
literally love this comfy playr thank
you but I'm like so zoned out I'm sorry
I I don't I'm not following the story
much she said she's no longer welcome in
wherever Place she's going literally
okay
love is banned from hell so Reviving
asov will let her go through
hell and
and why why she want to go there
again for my
fistol they didn't tell us yet ah okay
okay
okay oh good good good good good I
thought I missed
something she made s and abandoned the
Eternal contct you guys are all using
such difficult words
oopsie where am I going here okay Shadow
over Sagar join Don and Sagar okay if
there's a portal still there we shall
not miss
it Lilith wants to protect Sanctuary
from hell is a general she wants to
protect she wants to
protect something from
hell yeah Sanctuary what that isn't that
kind of nice okay protect well protect
how evil people
right whatever they think is
protecting she and the angel eloped and
had kids so they were banished from
Heaven and
Hell wow crazy
[\h__\h] instead of fighting Angels Forever
she had super power babies with inaras
in sanctuary but she actually wanted to
use them to end the war forever she
sounds
nice she's mother she's
mothering she's mothering and she's
smothering the world with
love
they're they're
here urine can resist she demon and her
ways are kind of evil but effective and
is the well well if evil why
nice if evil why effective if evil why
hot you're still very entertaining thank
you
John thank you oh that's a nice
scene uh-oh I I I I feel danger you're
in Chuckles I'm in
danger you're in narus just wants to get
back to heaven
he doesn't give a [\h__\h] about the
babies he has been waiting for you maybe
the angels are the evil ones we met
along the way ah hi Mommy
where where is
he come
forth what the [\h__\h] yurin what happened
to you kind of Epic though kind of cool
sick ride you
got
wow for
you oh [\h__\h] until his tears became fire
why did she choose urin out of all
people poor
urin damn what a glow up though do as
you please Aster
off I have what I came
for the half to hell or
what
oh
damn Dam am I fighting that am I
fighting that oh is it
scripted I don't I don't know if I
can can I win this fight
bro isn't even helping me
ah
ow are you dropping pots be nice
man oh yeah
where you
going what are you doing are you
escaping just like the other
one
bro I set all my Hydra there don't mess
up my game
plan that was a little bit ticklish
there he goes again but doing pretty
well already past path
I'm so locked
in oh they're all on fire and I'm just
adding more to
it I'm not helping I'm not helping I
feel you have reached your destination
thanks
sick music
though oh he's done he's done
for not now Siri pink
GPS you
have you have now reached your final
destination
hell yipp be
that was too
easy no way for such a sick enemy
design oh you're going to I don't think
that's going to
help okay at least releases his body and
well he's still dead but
[Music]
I'm sorry my
son I'm
sorry Don
I will leave you in peace
[Laughter]
[Music]
what pants what what
pants what pants
[Laughter]
Oh I was like cuz somebody said oh oh
like shitty acting uh cry acting is
going to come up so I was like waiting
for and so I was kind of like probably
more critical of it but then I was
thinking I mean some some people sound
like they're laughing when they cry but
then it it still got me at the end cuz
he like he did the we like three
times cor cried doing the what do you
mean she played it and she she really
cried and I'm just laughing
now n
don't make me look so
evil could I really cried and I'm
laughing no
no
no the absolute
contrast it's got me once I started
laughing and I saw the comments I had to
laugh even harder my my
stomach I couldn't help
it I'm sorry I'm
[Laughter]
sorry sorry Donan I I was I was just
like you I was crying I mean I literally
have tears in my eyes don't you see I I
really
do I don't don't assume that My Cry was
laughter yours also sounds like laughter
why wouldn't mine be actual crying
then Corner cried about this goodie
scene and you're
laughing yeah but even if he acted
better even then that it I don't May
okay h i I guess I'm not invested
enough that the the buildup was for me
was not as strong that I would cry there
maybe I just don't have a heart and a
soul damn it's it's it's my fault I'm
sorry I'll I'll try harder to cry next
time I not
laugh I Shame about Ying was one of us
you know one of us one of us take care
of him and his father
usually I'm well I do
do and we were the ones who would pay
the
cost our presence was no
coincidence everything happened exactly
as Lilith wanted we just dance to her
music is this the end of an act Donan
was
shattered his mind on Grief not
her not
answers no one knew what Lilith was
truly these are or exactly what asteroth
had promised
her but we needed to recover quickly and
we needed to stop chasing her Phantoms
mhm for real for real for
real uh as the world burn who whoa was
was that was that the end of okay cool
end of act two oo what's
this level 29 act two the knife twists
again
completed yipp
Yi reward exceptional gloves item
transmog
oh
Yi a tool points available now yippe
[Music]
huz I don't even remember what did the
guy teach me the guy where I brought him
the The Forbidden no the forgotten to
the Forgotten book
more into ult
[Music]
okay ah enchantment slots
okay now I have fum in my throat from
crying cuz I did cry I did cry
it tabed out
sorry that
was
emotional certainly
emotional okay I I think I want to still
play a little bit honestly um what is
this what what what am I looking at
claim oh oh
oh 100 gold that's like nothing are you
kidding me but a skill point
why did I get that because of my
Renown o I guess if I do more side
quests and I would also get more Renown
and
also
uhuh altars of lul
34 what in one region where are these
altars
I'm becoming Lil I'm fine with
that oh I'm so close here to the next
level one potion hey I want to do this I
want to finish this up fractured
Peaks fractured
Peaks over there hey I'm just going to
like go there now and finish my renowned
level I just need 50 more renown
oh kill the shot I guess I could do
anything and kill the
shot but there is a side quest
here is that the most effective
do oh I have found two altars of L
here uh I've only done three out of 38
[Music]
quests you already got the p oh
what where can I look at the menu that I
just looked
at
uh reown will take
hours I guess it does have the check why
do I only get a
partially okay then I want this one then
but that will that's five out of 300
that's
yeah whatever I guess I guess one
shouldn't really aim for it and just
like hope that while you play the game
normally you're going to achieve
it right uh I guess next we got to go
here the spreading Darkness meet Lura in
kbu maybe from
here ah
oh and that is for all characters yeah
yeah she is level 29
so what I'm I'm also level 29 now yay
I'm overtaking her level now
finally the bottom rewards for s
ah not conquering
strongholds what exactly counts as a
stronghold you mean these Villages or
[Music]
I should get this
wayo is this an altar of lth
no imagine alar of L next to uran's
[Laughter]
gravestone sorry I have no heart
and no
soul why do I see
people wait what are you fighting
bro
help
Jennifer does she need help
she seemed fine so I just teab bagged
her a little
bit okay
wow it's a big place huh let me sell
some items while I'm
here with you the blacksmith
what is these oh 3
20 oh oh
intelligence but no socket but this is
perfect we can try to put sockets into
this one or is it not worth casting ice
armor well I'm never going to cast that
but
whatever should I try to put sockets on
this or not worth
maybe worth a
shot to blow my nose after all the
crying that I did because I'm such a
sympathetic person who feels others
feelings very strongly no empathetic
that's what I mean I'm just so
emotionally
exhausted I can feel the agony
oh the
agony I'm an empath yes yes I am yes
isn't it
clear I feel the
opposite I've been for a lot
yeah remember to hydrate after crying
true true true let me drink some water
wait did I just say the Ground
Pounders those
shoes oh this one's nice too solders
torturer mhm I'll take that
um 20 oh nice that's also
better uh wait
that's 20
20 okay mhm mhm
[Music]
rare wand
okay
o lore seared Through the flames of
combat long ago during the days of
Ash these gauntlets were forged in the
Demonic fires of astero and quenched In
The Blood of Heroes they look pretty
cool
what still got some good in
it
oh oh no no no no no
no 44 Tes we got a
winner
o and it's got a socket and it's plus
n we got a
[Music]
winner 26
okay so I'm wearing these but so this
one I don't know I guess how let's see
how we do it how do we put a socket
um oh yeah this one also doesn't have a
socket oh then I want to put one on
there too do I have to have it out of my
inventory out of my at the
Jeweler
[Music]
Jewel looks like she's here
how does this work craft gems unsocket
add
sockets item to receive
socket oh man
oh what 20 of those and I have 425 or
you need 425 and I have
20 it does it take
20 thank you for the membership gifts
yay use your membership
wisely it's cheap yeah I guess
so this will bind it to your account
okay stars made manifest and then this
one
too
sure can I add another
one I
can sick
maybe I add one to
this oh this is an addiction I want to
add sockets to everything
now can't
okay oh wait oh wait oh wait that's the
old
[\h__\h] that's not the
oops oh
well I have enough materials and
stuff so we're going
to wear this we're going to wear this
we're going to wear that one yeah I'm
going to learn this and I'm going to
wear
these no we're going to wear
these yes and then the rest we get rid
of and then we put some new stuff into
the
sockets sounds
good been star from nothing
[Music]
thanks now what do we have what did we
say what we what do we want for armor
there strength dexterity I probably
don't have any more of the nice ones
except these
ones okay so
intelligence
willpower barrier
generation okay oops where did it
go let's put one here one here and
another one
here
maybe maybe I can put this on the
weapon and
Critical Strike damage over which one
should I which other one should I put in
they all sound good but I don't know how
often overpower damage
happens and vulnerable damage and
stuff craft better Jew oh there's better
Jewels damage over time
fine okay
cold resistance resistance to all
elements yeah like one of these that's a
chipped
Ruby h willow also seems like something
I as a mage would need but I don't know
I'll put maximum life on here but I will
look into better Jewels now do I need my
other jewels to make better
Jewels
probably or is is that the Ruby already
a better
Jewel I'm going to do it I'm going to do
it I'm going to do it I'm going to do it
no there much
better
really overpower damage is condition
damage I don't think sourcers have any
skill at oh okay I
see was that really a good
choice but these are just the the like
how do I make better ones those don't
look so
good oh should I not have chip uh
destroyed the
Ruby need
levels too low of H okay
okay then let's
go to the next
[Music]
area wait should I teleport to
here need to gain more levels for better
gems how many levels do you want from me
[Music]
uh no leave my cat
alone don't Hur my cat
I'm kind of sad I I'm not hearing the
toon to toon that I would hear from a
horse I really like those
sounds not quite the same with those
Paws but if I imagine that in our off
time when we're not riding around and
killing people and laughing at son's
dying in the father's hands um in in the
off time when I imagine that I'm just
like squeezing the paws of my big
panther then it all feels nice again and
acceptable am I already there oh no but
let's get the
Waypoint oh
oops attaching
beans is there anything to do here I
don't even see side quests
so I shall move
on new enemies new
territory this looks very diabl to to
me but honestly I guess everybody does
everything does
[Music]
I think I've
arrived
no yes no yeah is this just a big place
oh yeah I think i' I've
arrived oh wait this this looks like the
desert city in Diablo
2 makes me happy he feels
[Music]
nostalgic have arrived at your
destination have
peace shouting and cursing all
night run him out of
time wake up well he's still breathing
need talk to you I think he's lucky to
be chicken what a nice cop you
have a and there's little baby
pigs good
rooster
D daruk I know I've once known a daruk
he looked very much more friend shaped
than you that old man there he claims to
be horadrim but he drinks like an ox
lur of lur of he came to town days ago
looking for a servant of the demon
Lilith a pale man Lori it seems he
didn't like what he
found I
see take it from here who are
you he and I met in the fractured Peaks
wait the Naro was saw Pale Man in a
vision if you can believe it enough yeah
from he's yours just he's more than just
a narrator I
forgot Laur Wy wakey I've been hearing
your voice in my head so much let's talk
about it my issues time for a therapy
session are you going to
oh y I don't want to sleep in the place
like that what do you want you told me
to meet meet you here lorath remember in
the chicken c yeah of course I remember
typical meeting point for me I'm just
surprised you're not
dead hand me that
bottle what happened to you I was
attacked
obviously by vast ques of
alcohol wielded by my own treacherous
hand then may also have been a brawl
with the goats over this PL M I like to
think I
triumphed who is the Pale
Man The Pale Man is was
herad Herm then you must know
him I thought I did once his name is
Elias it was my
Apprentice he was the one who brought
Lilith to San
it's possible that I did not take the
news very
well what must we do then find it figure
out what he's done yeah sin you know
this now kill
him there's a woman here someplace she
has some messages we'll need and I'm of
no use to anyone right now could you
find her and enough time has been
wasted
wasted GTA check around the Inn ask if
she's heard from the or Monastery mhm
well thanks
bro yeah his voice is so recognizable he
should be a
[Music]
vtuber techin
L of sent me have you heard from the orb
Monastery no no words from orb same as
yesterday and a day before but I have
something else Ruma has it a Pale Man
passed through the abaro canyon some
time ago fearsome fellow dressed in
black after Laura's performance last
night I wer he want to know h
return to update
Lor
okay it's going to be the new Fantastic
4 oh I don't think I ever watched a
Fantastic 4
movie Sick must be a good paying job
strange I monry that many people have
the Abit should have replied by now Tech
spoke of a rumor a pale man seen near
the
Canyons the Canyons why didn't you say
so we go at once let's go but we can't
leave ore
unchecked s it I'm off to the Canyons
you can meet me there or go to the
monastery you seem reliable th
far do not prove me
wrong do not
uh challenge
me
okay I have got two points again to go
to I'll go to the closest one first oops
oops act free the making of monsters
whittling sanity okay maybe maybe I
should I could play endlessly but maybe
I should end it soon perhaps after that
Quest or
so need to find a good spot probably at
the end of act two would have been a
good spot but I want to play
[Music]
more 6% increased burning damage this
bonus is increased to while they are
affected by more burning
[Music]
damage I'm just going to go for that one
that's a little bit more Mana regener
generation sounds good sounds
good
okay that was a short walk a short hike
can't imagine a week without W streams
me
neither don't worry usually it won't
happen I had HED to find a witness who
saw
Elias instead I have a camp of dead
Merchants damn it they were slaughtered
by demons that much is plain s but none
was summoned here we should search The
Canyons could Elias have summoned these
demons easily and assuming he did he may
still be here stay close to to
me okay
scary we'll be
careful ah he can be on the mount
too he's got a
horsey but I got a
pan oh there's a special chest here I
want it
ship which I don't
need but I'll take it with me and sell
it for good money or not I just Salvage
it like I Salvage everything
nowadays shout your rejection no mother
of mine at her towering statue in Rifts
hi Shrine oh is that a a hint to where
another statue from Lili would be and
then I'm supposed to shout no more
mother of mine you
are but I like her she can be my
mother she's not that
bad I hear a stone Carver lives in that
house a man called
ganar it's hidden
isolated perfect for working in solitude
are so
fast show you all all
Adams I wonder if I need perms for Adams
usually I need like
perms for any kind of
modification kind of annoying
oo
spicy I will bring it
on Bring It On more more more more I
brought my snake out answer
me I showed you my
snake please
answer woo
these demons were Vermin I'd expect more
from a mage of eliz's ability right
let's search the
house it's a trap maybe it's a trap
that's why it's so easy
I'm silly today I'm silly every
day bro what is going
on
sometimes they get me good they're
killing me killing me
good where my K-pop fans
at still killing me
[Music]
me see what you can
find yay she's so
hot wait
what does this count as like a little
statue to my like
thing I want to talk to you can I
not no oh
okay what
I can't
exit what the book on the
table
book on the
table ah this one oh no this one today
Master Elias called at my
door I had trouble with my words so I
showed him my
carvings he said he could see my pain in
them the pain of a lonely
man who had learned
to hate the
world and yet our mother Lilith found me
beautiful he said there are others like
me as
well and together we will build the new
world you see Lil as your
mommy that's why there's a statue here
what a dumb mess cult followers am I
right am I right kfp
here's what I found burning Hells we're
too late Elias is long gone this gbar is
our Summoner how can you be
certain isn't it obvious Elias finds
gbar Alone friendless full of anger so
he plays him like a
fidd love and a part in his Grand
delusion then he gives him tools to
express his
anger haven't we practiced that very
perceptive somebody question know how
long Gambar has St in
this yeah now you change your your
answer Eric what's in your
contract okay
shiny special sounds when they
drop it's also
better damn it but it also looks really
cute I might want to change my looks
with that
one but it it's just a tiny bit better
so it's not even worth my time to put it
on and put the sockets on and everything
so whatever what
if up or down or both is down but oh
mother thank you for opening my
eyes your hatred fills my
heart I cannot stop my hands from
working so fulfilling isn't it gamber
you poor
for gamber gamber we all knew he would
fall for the kind of cult
[\h__\h] that mother offers
he was always a weak
link a weakling one might
say no hope for a guy like
Gambar let him live the life that he has
chosen so it may be
Nice Shot o nice
aim BR
SW pack I love flipping things over and
shooting things
down look at all these statues bro wait
why did he make so many did gamber make
all of these is that the implication is
he
insane maybe he likes her BBA because
they are they're very
um they stand out to
me limited Lil
merch it's his Shrine his little Shrine
thank you for sending Master Elias to
show me the way way I long for the day
when we stand by your
side and set the cleansing fire he's
there let's kill
him is that Lil too what the [\h__\h] that's
not
Lil there's a small L on top of L cute
gamb what the [\h__\h] did Master Elias send
you master
Elias well yes in fact he did our is a
very important Mission we have something
for the master but we had heard he was
with you do you know where he is liar
dirty pigs born
liar the master has all he
needs he's cray cray oh oh he's cray
cray to me oh oh he's CR
you already
done Master elas hear me your enemies
are here I should play them
hard things are too easy a very long
time for
this but honestly those few moments
where I do
accidentally lose like like 90% of my HP
for a moment those would end really
badly your y a proper
demon I'm excited bring it
on oh you're almost dead oh it's Gambar
and the guy okay
okay that's it that's it
really I'm just spamming my attacks
brain
empty look at all these unused pots on
the
ground
nice hey he looks like the the
mi mi byai the the the the
guy what's his name
[Music]
again hatle Towers yeah hi hatle Towers
sorry for hurting you
it was an
accident what happens
now wait but why would alah summon
Lilith tell me about
it is he insane you mean yeah that's
what I really exceptional Mage he would
plunge Through Fire and shite in search
of the truth and very often found it
whatever truth he has found in Lilith
only he can say the why of it
[Music]
the scholars of orbe devote their lives
to the study of forbidden knowledge to
serve the light we must know the
darkness or some other silly
platitude I wrote to the Abott seeking
insights on
Lis his silence is most
unusual the man never misses a chance to
speak bad news first gar was expecting
someone it seems El liias has turned
others to his Madness taught them to
summon too ad wager you heard Gambar the
master has all he needs they're about to
do something
drastic and the good
news Elias gave us a gift remember this
demon he sent to kill us it is unique it
requires constant feeding human
sacrifices in fact oh no if I cut open
his belly someone inside might hold a
clue tell us where it came from
literally I must have it brought to
gardu for
examination make yourself useful and
head for the or Monastery see what's
keeping that Bloody Abit all
right we'll
do oh I reached level 30 he enchantment
slot unlocked
M Quest complete
thanks one more into Inferno
then level 30 is in demand yippee oh
wait so wait uh how do I open the
enchantment slot thing
again I do also want to probably go
to he wants to go here
G
okay a second
one and the last
one uh what should I put in
and oh thanks uh enemies take 25%
increased burning damage from you while
standing in fire wall see that's
good Inferno oh oh Inferno can't go
in yeah I think I'll put the firewall in
there okay
should I end it should I play more it's
already 1 p.m.
22 I play
more I want to play more it's so chill
I'm just
chilling uh you cooking today no
I don't know I don't really have
anything I'm just going to make a
sandwich and that will be my dinner cuz
I already had like the burger the
disappointing burger and some
fries before the
stream so I'm good with just eating a
sandwich and maybe salad I have some
leftover
salad girl dinner
yeah quite the girl dinner
indeed winner winner girl
dinner I want to fight some things but
you guys look
like enemies that are not worth
it there's a little dungeon there maybe
I'll check it
out oh there's a
beach
pretty Seaside the is this
big or is it also a small
one
oh slay all enemies in the secluded
Grotto H it kind of looks the same just
Miron it's just
Miron no wait no never mind there's a
little bit more to it but it's like
still the same ground pattern and stuff
I guess now in act three they offer me a
little bit
bigger uh optional dungeons thank
you acid reuse yeah
recycling did you guys see he little
tangent did you guys see
uh the Nintendo Direct that shows the
new Donkey Kong World in Universe
Studios Nintendo
World I still haven't been able to go to
Nintendo World cuz the time when we went
to Universal
Studios with myth and
Quon we didn't get
in cuz we were too
late disappoint
one day I want to
go but it's in Osaka so
normally I don't really I don't really
end up in otaka these days normally have
to go out of my way to go there and it's
it's pretty
far like I can take Ain consen but even
with a shin
consen pretty
far pretty long time and if I want to be
there early like either I go there
the night
before and
then be early in the
morning or I leave early morning with
the shinon and then I got to really
leave early morning and then still I
would
arrive
probably still kind of late I feel like
what I should do is stay a night in
Osaka go there the night before I want
to go to Nintendo World
yeah cuz the thought of waking up like
at 5 a.m. to ride maybe the first chin
conson at 6:00 a.m. or whatever
frog
nah I hate that
thought stay in the USA Hotel oh I'm
sure just like Disney hotels those are
[\h__\h] expensive
I've never stayed in a Disney hotel
either I know that like
American Disney lands like the one in is
it in California or in Florida in any
case they have like hug huge and many
Disney hotels
right well oh
that's a Time window for many so I have
to watch for Easter
oh is it not a good system the fast pass
woohoo loot loot loot loot
loot
nice
niceas I think I killed everyone in here
right travel to the murky depths what I
think it's
cleared oh wait there's a bit more up
there since everyone is using fast pass
it's not really any better no I think it
is is I actually some of my IRL
friends went to Japan recently and
uh they went to Osaka to usj and they
posted a video in
their Instagram story where they just
passed hundreds of people in the waiting
line in
usj for some
attraction so worked out for them quite
nicely and I think they even said they
accidentally uh went on like a national
holiday or
so they didn't even intend to do
so poor people yeah I'm I also I don't
know I think I never used a fast pass
before I always want
to somehow I don't know I don't know how
it works
and the people I go with I guess usually
also don't
know I think when we went with myth we
also didn't have fast passes I don't
know I don't think we knew what we were
doing at Disney it's almost required now
I don't know Disney man all these like
Parks they sound fun and all but good
that we wrecked here I suppose managed
to make it to these caves without the I
think about spending half of my day in
from the looks of it waiting lines we
aren't the first ones to wash up here
some of the others want to head further
in see if maybe there's something to be
found I don't like it we need to get to
K bardu and let them know we've lost the
idol
but I do want to go again I definitely
want to see Nintendo World at least once
in my
lifetime or in its lifetime because I'm
a phoenix and I'm going to outlive
it spending yeah not just not even just
the money that you spend for it but I
remember when we went to usj with myth
and
quason H me uh a couple of us like we
split up some of us stayed in line to
get um like chos and
drinks and we had like 2 hours or so
until we had to go to an
attraction and we thought oh we'll be
fine we'll be fine
but me and I think it was me CI and GAA
most of the time we were in the
line together and we legit spent two
[\h__\h] hours that were so
exhausting it was I guess one of the
more popular food stands I guess there
was something
there I don't remember anymore what it
was but something
instagrammable aesthetically pleasing
this place is way bigger than I
thought but we really didn't expect it
to go that slow it was just like barely
moving most of the
time so exhausting man it just felt so
stupid and then you you you stand in it
for like an hour and you start
wondering like now now I've been in here
now I got to commit since I've been in
this line for so so long I have to
commit otherwise it would be a waste
surely it will be
soon over but no then it's not but then
then you commit even more and then you
even more so can't give
up and I I do think I remember the drink
SL food whatever we got really didn't
live up
to it uh taking two hours to get
it but at least we had a lot of time to
talk a lot of time
[Music]
kind of jealous the I think the gamer
girls the whole Japan gamer girls got to
check out the museum right before
opening made that video on it I think
that was some kind of like sponsored
work deal or
whatever I wish I wish I could like do
that with Nintendo World or so
man but the museum would have also been
cool to see before opening
especially this place is actually
surprisingly long
and uh
[Music]
demanding don't know which direction to
go I feel like I need to go back and
check out this path
first isn't that a corpse pile
indicator I'll
go get a group together next time you're
there for usj for Nintendo World yeah I
wonder if somebody wants to go with me
oh it was a [\h__\h]
GRE
oh damn it I should have got that
earlier well maybe there's still enough
enemies
here quick more more more oh more more
more
[Music]
more a did it end
I think it
ended adakin bolt
crawler is
dead didn't you dropped me an Elixir
thank
you wow wow wow wow I wonder how much
money I made in
total dog go really busy picking up all
the
money oh oh oh There was a another wave
oh [\h__\h] oh no
oh wait did I fail the
Mastery
no radiant chest is that did I fail I'm
not
sure I might have failed the mastering I
was distracted I wanted to run down to
find more enemies while I was
greedy oh well
okay the
heck okay that was definitely necessary
to go there let's
continue going
deeper it was greedy of me the greed got
to me maybe that was on purpose quite
the bit bait I got
baited did you buy vessel of hat no not
yet but I want to I'm just kind of I
want to finish the main story
first and if I finish that then I'll buy
the
DLC otherwise you know there's still a
chance that I might drop the game before
I even play the DLC I'm not sure I'm
really enjoying it
but I don't know if you guys are
enjoying it that much I mean you're here
right but the people who aren't here are
not enjoying it I
suppose but I'm enjoying
it but for now I'll
just play a little longer and we'll see
where it
goes and you know what awaits us if we
do keep on going although I wonder cuz
like it's actually pretty long do you
really have to finish the story to play
the
DLC
oh the chest is a COR o what no you the
you're the
[Music]
guy
uh you can technically skip the campaign
technically would you also like
level uh like skip the levels and go to
the like max level or so
[Music]
cuz I'm thinking like are the girls who
were interested in the DLC really
willing to finish the whole story cuz I
realized it's like pretty
long if you skip you start at one level
one they can just create a new character
and start right away with the expansion
yeah but then they're level
[Music]
one I don't
know yeah the world scales to them I
guess but but then still they don't have
like all the skills and stuff
M geeky did say that she would want to
finish the main story first but like I
don't know if she's aware how much game
there
is what did I come here for for selling
[Music]
things my skill is unmatched you'll see
haven't been looking at what I've
been Gathering a
[Music]
bagger give me intelligence gloves or
nothing same with
boots this one I kind of want to wear
but
[Music]
adventurous guls of Retribution 22
intelligence oh there we go this enemies
have 10% chance to be stunned for 2
seconds when they when they see you cuz
you're so gorgeous no when they hit you
you deal
27 okay cool cool cool cool cool nice
nice nice uh
ma should have sold it maybe I should
have sold
it I still have good good amount of
money good
Salvage good
salvage or good
Salvage becomes an eternal character
when the season
ends oh finding free intelligence
[Music]
but it doesn't have the uh in cool
down I guess it's better I should switch
to the helm
probably and perhaps of it put another
socket
[Music]
in wait legendary want
who uses wands I can also use wands
right if I want to do I have the
choice I do but right now I'm using
staffs so I can use a staff or a wand or
or like the wand with the orb and the
book also
[Music]
if you want
to a dagger too yeah I did in the
beginning but people said I wasn't using
it I guess so cuz I wasn't attacking
from
closly wait did I want to keep that ring
I don't remember
69 armor 22
intelligence
whatever plenty worth
keeping
oh uh 23 22
54 this one's already got two sockets
though plenty worth
keeping
hey 24
intelligence you have 8% increased Dodge
chance successful Dodges you mean when I
press space bar I have to press space
bar but then I could restore 15% of my
maximum
life okay I can use this one that at
least makes more sense than the size ice
armor
maybe
mhm rare
step nice nice nice okay okay we got
some new stuff we got some new stuff
um let's wear these
things
and you must help me out
here
nice um might need to add some slots on
something
right Gem Gem Gem Gem Gem Gem
guy gem lady
nice uh what happened with
these okay uh these I want to add to any
[Music]
armor I
guess and um
uh I think this was like
that why is there one left
over where was that or did I have one in
my
inventory Forge awaits your return yeah
but wouldn't I I still have an empty
slot oh
weird okay all back to
Perfection let me finish the dungeon and
I think I'll uh end the gaming session
once I'm done with this dungeon because
it took quite a
while thank you for the membership
renewal
thank you also be bad come
on we look at at the new cosmetic
options sure sure you want to see my
trans work options you're a
fashionista just like
me thinking about the most important
things in life
fashion I get it I get it one more month
until I get
RGB no no no you mean gold right gold is
first then
RGB sorry RGB is one more
year not so fast little
chicken we're in no rush
RGB one day you have to stay with
me I think I'll go down
first a there is the last corpse pile
then I shouldn't have gone down
something in my God told me no no no no
down is where the corpse
is go up
first I need to trust my
instincts they always prove me
right Dr signant okay cool
cool just going to finish looking around
the dungeon a up here even though it
already says I cleared
it but maybe my white chicken is better
than RGB
chicken
well people may have
some
preferences some people have complained
about the Golden
Chicken but you must
move
on I know I know you got so used to your
body after a
while you feel like this best represents
you but it's time for a change I love
the me too me too keep sake what's this
room this party is it was worth coming
back
here there's so much going on they
wanted to kick me
out wow wow that's just they don't stop
coming and they don't stop
coming why
n there we go oh eternal torment event
oh wait it was a Oh was this a
thing was this a
thing it was a thing a whole thing an
event I didn't know this did I do the
Mastery I feel like I was fast
enough even in dungeons huh this was a
huge thing compared to the tiny ones we
went into until
now I did not what the heck oh I should
have should I focused more on the bone
masses I was focusing more on the
enemies
around that it was spawning
seemingly
bruh no leave me alone leave me alone
leave me alone I want to log out
somewhere which I guess I can still like
make my way there to the next
destination
you think this detour was worth it I
want to kill some mobs and I definitely
[Music]
did yeah I got a kitty I paid 100 in
game 100,000 in-game
monies which isn't too
much in this economy
oh we're here that was fast we're almost
there there we
go oh looks nice here
too
pretty oops sorry this place has been
taken it reeks of forbidden spells oh is
this not a peaceful place to log out at
uh lorath n how bizarre it is to hear
from you your Charming Apprentice
arrived just this morning with equally
disturbing news but he made no mention
of you am I to assume you did not send
him please join us at orb as soon as you
are able
H
misunderstandings in this corner
[Music]
what is happening oh it's another
dungeon oh yeah okay we're coming back
here is there a waypoint no or maybe
here and I'm missing
it feel like there should be a waypoint
here it's not a long
one you can lo out wherever and'll spawn
you back in town
oh but but I want to choose the town
that I spawn in I'll go to cat
bardu oh it looks like
Shy cuz of the
[Music]
teos I could play even longer it's only
been 5 hours man I want to play longer
but I started kind of late today
huh I'm so deep in the
Diablo feeling even though I don't out
sometimes I do want to play
more this is a nice place to log out at
taking a little bath right my little
do you like the bath yeah shake shake
shake I like when dogs go like
oh but we're supposed to look at the
trans do I have to go to the uh armor
person for
that can't just do it on my
own where where where do you do that
again ah here
wardrobe I was I was kind of eyeing uh
this
piece th
boob I do really like this set
though I want
this there's still so
many oh this is like a upgraded
version
NY okay let's let's do
this oh that's kind of
nice the blue white is kind of clean
looking ooh if I do all of my armor in
that color I might look naked if you're
really far
[Music]
away What's this called wanderous
tunic blending in I'm camouflaging
myself camouflaging no but I do want to
[Music]
maybe go for something more fresh
looking was it this or was it uh this
one
blue I think I want just sandals for
this one but they don't have
color
okay oh I don't have wander
gloves how about
these and then what for the head
something oh that's the that looks cool
but I want
something
less
obstructive actually this might look
good in that blue
looks so
mysterious
pretty but now I don't look like a fire
Mage
[Music]
H camouflage
I kind of like this look too to be
honest it's
fine yeah it's kind of cool I look I'm
like I'm blending
in it's kind of
smooth wow under the
poop okay uh confirm
should I change my hair but it's not
visible here so
whatever I
want one day one day that would be a
reason to get the DLC earlier but you
know oh I do look cool I like this nude
beige colors
[Music]
love yes I'm nude that's a K-Pop song
again by the way in case you did not
recognize
it okay I guess I should end it I'm sad
I have separation anxiety I'm
chilling I'm
[Music]
chilling to
bed you can keep going I can of course I
can I know I
[Music]
can but this sexy lady she's got to go
go she's got to go and read super chats
look at her look at those beautiful
colors it actually looks
so
fashionable wow I Stand Out by not
standing out I Stand Out by being so
beige and
nude I miss thumbnail La what do you
mean Miss I'm here
beautiful so beautiful
squishy
okay I don't want to
go exit diabo for are you sure no oh but
then I can't go just take take it take
my
yes it hesitated you to click the stream
No it should make you click it even
faster all right let's go
to why not go
here oh my arms embarrassing
you saw no you see
nothing I want to see you more playing
yeah me too next week maybe although I
don't know next week I might not have
time for many streams as I said I'll be
gone for like half of the
week so
cannot stream too
[Music]
much soorry I'm picking a
bgm for you
guys how about these oops what the heck
[Music]
how peaceful after all that we've been
through with
Lilith oh my God Cron's going to play
tunic in 4 hours if you guys are awake
you need to go support her
help her with the golden path although
she probably is still far away from
it that's her thir tunic stream already
already that's not
enough it's only a bir tunic stream
cor is going to have a mental breakdown
from the game I hope so because
like I had it
too and it's part of it it's part of the
experience you'll feel even more
accomplished if you get through
it
yeah all right Super Chat though reading
time
inscription is the one to read I think
I'm pretty sure I know I know I
know I wish I could play tunic again for
the first
[Music]
time such a good
game this yeah yeah that's I I know
that's why it's so much because I did
the Super Chat go thing take out 47 d d
thanks for the r of chat I can be a pain
in Wild's neck so here are funds for the
pain why why you're not pain in my neck
it might not help much but uh no we love
you and hope your body eggs go away no
more while we suffering please please
dedicate my kiss to unknown who streams
Mirage every day
unone thank you so much
yeah I don't think my pain will ever go
away but I would appreciate um if I did
myself the favor of buying a new bed I
think I need to buy a new bed that's the
problem with like buying beds where the
mattress is in the bed like it's the bed
and all you put on top is a Topper
thingy because if you do feel like you
want to switch the mattress you have to
switch the whole
bed [\h__\h]
I've had this bed for a while though but
recently it's just
been like in combination with the
Pillow pretty
bad I don't know
maybe I'm just overall maybe I'm just
getting old maybe it's just the
age cuz like I've been using like I've
been circling I've been going through
several pillows that I
own like some were fine before but now
they pain me
[Music]
so I don't know maybe my body is just
getting
worse Continental bed you mean you mean
from Continental
hotels what what does that mean
Continental
bed talk like you're 50 well maybe I
am I feel like I'm 50
[Music]
I don't think my pillow is overused or
so I wasn't getting any sleep Beyond 6
hours and got aches in my NE sh after I
got new pill pain away yeah but like how
many [\h__\h] pillows am I supposed to
try out until I find the right
one I know I've tried different types
too like the foamy ones and like fluffy
ones and no
it would help to stop trying so hard to
cuddle with the cats no no no no no no
you don't no you don't
understand no you you don't get it
Casper Casper pill have a Casper
Casper wait I heard that did I hear that
before Casper
P oh that looks comfortable
wait it comes in a interesting
container W this looks really
comfortable wait it is it on Amazon on
like German Amazon Casper
pillow
yeah Casper sleeping pillow are they all
the same or do they have
different can there's a king pillow and
there's a hybrid pillow standard no
that's the color essential pillow hybrid
pillow original King pillow sleeping
pillow there a back cusher nice for when
I want to sit up wow I'm a fan already
this looks
promising sleep snow foam pillow oh my
God which one do I get maybe I'll get
two different ones in any
case I do think I wanted to get an extra
pillow anyway
for um guests also I I have like in
total I have plenty of pillows but I
want more good
pillows which ones the Casper owners
which ones do you have the
OG or original King
pillow wow medium soft
feel wow oh it's a bit uh higher than
the standard one it
seems wow wow
wow wow I'm excited I'm
excited add to
basket which other one should I
get Casper sleeping
pillow I'm looking at Casper sleeping
pillows should look it up too they look
good should I try one of the foam
pillows that they have it's 226 but it
doesn't have
Prime I want
[Music]
Prime just want to try out no but like I
want a different one
too H hybrid
pillow hybrid hi
bird medium feel three layers of soft
fiber and support of foam all in
one
H best for S sleepers what did it say
for the other one sorry I'm looking at
pillows
now ah the the standard ones says any
sleep
style a that's a stand one I bought the
I'm I'm buying the original what does it
say also any sleep
[Music]
style standard this okay I'll get a
standard one what so
the original one is medium soft
feel
uh me it's the same is it ah no it's
just it's the same feeling but it's a
different size I think it's a little bit
finner the standard I do think I need a
like a finner one General
[Music]
oh but this one doesn't have
Prime it's only honestly best if you
sleep on your side you mean this pillow
and
particular I do mostly sleep on my side
and on my tummy
recently it's not good but and then like
at some point point at the end of my
sleep cycle I end up on my back which is
best anyway but I can't fall asleep on
my back when I'm already super sleepy
then I like ending up on my
back it's
weird I think I'll get the hybrid pillow
to
150o there's also an Casper essential Co
cooling hybrid pillow wow I want I'm
going to collect all these
pillows and the snow foam and the hybrid
snow King pillow
wow okay I'm going to get the this foamy
one stand yeah okay okay well I'm so
excited I'm going to look forward to
sleeping hopefully it won't disappoint
me I'm going to cry
so that's 280 bucks
for for uh
pillows for two pillows in total but if
they're good then it'll be so worth
it yeah the next Vite merch did get
revealed it's the second one out of nine
it's a it's a name
tag pin
thing it's a bit silly but it's
cute it adds to your full attire I think
if you go to concerts and uh conventions
and stuff you might want to get
[Music]
this do they have a refund policy well
I'm buying on Amazon so I'm pretty sure
I can easily send it back if I wanted
to okay thank you for that really for
the people who brought it up I
appreciate
it okay here we go
continueing green R just
another P
Papa mattress probably more important
mattress is important too but I do
notice that recently especially my neck
has been [\h__\h] and the pillow is just
not doing it for me anymore maybe my
spine has just in this past year gone
much
worse especially in the upper
region and this is the result of it
chocolate Insomniac lunchbox meatball
deino motion e fan M sauce than for the
pinky that is a goal we're fighting
for was it about eating you oh
yeah tur D XO 77 d new persona d alen D
jaob 47 D Tiara asalan dang am d Eden XL
d r
Oma Tracy
H oh
I I auto failed your name again doesn't
even say Garza anymore maral jro
rer
snowy
uel Legion a Nova floresa D Jo W thanks
for the
[Music]
pinky I volunteer for
tribute hope you have a good stream M
thank you so much for your donation I
shall eat you when you're
ready right now you're golden this is
kind of it would be poisonous for me to
eat
you I guess at some point after RGB we
got to Circle back to making you guys
[Music]
edible
otherwise going to get hungry in
here AR d g dun game 8 910 d r d green
bird D FR D can't take D
so
unknown the gamer CR
timp
ASM coton thanks for the pinky can we
pay to get
eaten of
course sounds like a good deal to me
hell yeah I love my
business uh
model so
genius FL D Dragon Days D Tree Barber
D
um yeah I heard something about that too
but I don't know how it works I was
worried too Milly Sprite d m d game 8910
D the g d red D just another D Robbie s
d unknown
thank
you I'm going to get so many massages
next week [\h__\h]
yeah I need to call them and make more
appointments bar G uel
you jack Red Wing thanks for the
pinky
stretchy I'm stretching I'm stretching
I'm
[Music]
stretching instead of hydration check we
should do stretch
check thank you for the
[Music]
pinky Rachel vermil
s
evil Triple j26 G mark p m
and Phil weel D Tiara D SW swadd D skunk
face D valdian thanks for the red super
chat oh love me boss simple as love me
boss simple as see you in 2 months when
I will have ranked up IRL
or wait when you rank up what's the next
position if you're already a
tanker what's it going to how do you
what's the what's the
[Music]
order two months huh so by the end of
the year oh no maybe in January no wa
this was ah no by end of December that
means you're ranked up because cuz this
was sent at the end of October let's go
super
tager I'm
excited maybe maybe your tank will be
able to go underwater underwater
tanker two
tanks thank you valdian good luck
M Cody koi Dan snowy thank you Dan I
hope you don't have to work so much
overtime
anymore it's not fair m is d thank you
Row in the boat d hogy d thank
you thank you thank you oh more card
games I love card games thank you for
the recommendation the
bazaar maybe I'll get into it one day
Walter bonam D David Gonzalez D you have
more D 77
d m thank you
and T thanks for the pinky can I come to
Canada on vacation we don't have beaches
but we have forests and snow and
mountains and bears and lots of stuff
yeah I already I think I talked about
this on stream that just sounds like
Austria to
me but I do think I want to go to Canada
at some point when I if I have like a
good reason or a good
time and stuff maybe maybe someone to
visit or
[Music]
so maybe one
day for like some camping
trip in the wilderness cuz
Canadian
uh the outdoors really beautiful from
the video that I've seen not clamping no
hiking and camping over
Canadian mountains slash valleys slash I
want to do I want to I want to I want to
kayak
also want to do
everything yeah maybe in the
summer and then yeah somebody should
teach me how to fish I want to fish I
want to do all of it I'll go camping and
Canada hiking and and kaying and
fishing and maybe I'll hug a
bear while I'm at it you can rent a
cottage oh yeah oh no right maybe I'll
just get one of those super cool pretty
airn beans in Canada somewhere I'll look
for a really nice cute Airbnb in the in
in on in the middle of nowhere I don't
know how I'm going to get there but can
crony
Drive she can drive right from what I
know know or can she I don't
know need too maybe I should get my
license
then oh she can okay then we
good she got a license recently oh let's
[\h__\h]
go ah that actually sounds really nice
sounds like a really nice
idea H it sounds so peaceful and
fun and then and then making grilling
something by the
fire making camping
[Music]
Foods grilling sausages cracking an
egg yum
s'mores how you and her had a long talk
about when she got her license really
[Music]
[\h__\h] camping
block yeah and this bgm will be playing
in the background the birds and the bees
will be playing this for us and the
beers the beers the Bears will be on the
Bongos they make the d d
sounds like a Disney movie it will be
like a Disney movie a blow up some
snakes and make them into
balloons that's not Disney though that's
um whatever Shrek
was close
[Music]
enough Canada surely just like a Disney
movie are you saying
that
sarcastically shk his streamworks there
you go yeah all right Tanaka I got a
whole plan now are you ready I'm going
to
Canada but I don't know if I have time
for it in
2025 but in the next let's say in the
next four years or
so Tom P dun simply but angry thanks for
the red ch
angry
kiss choco meteor thank
you
[Music]
finish it's go why I don't
know wherever the Airbnb will lead
me the nice
Airbnb okay next is little goody to
shoes which was a really sweet game I
[Music]
know diesel D cotton gravy D Steph sings
D hey yo wait what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] wasn't Freo my love
interest did I pursue dude Steph are you
in the
chat Steph says in her Super Chat so
excited to see you play lgts my
wonderful friend and irel Idol Phoebe is
the voice of
Freya I'm so elated to see my Kam just
COI make sure you stuck up on pretzels
okay right cuz she sells the pretzels
right oh my
God oh my God
so we had one voice actress in the chat
and the other one was is your
friend
Mia The
Coincidence y Ken
stamps yway D FL of fancy D meta
magician thank you dun
oh wait that sounded like you're one of
the team but I'm not sure no maybe not
tiar asalan dangun Ash thank you dangun
for the advice
also it's a it's a Hidden Gem for
sure
ring
Bruce zor 787
d uh M D Anthony web D oo tubes d
how do I read
this
translate
oh it's just
n oh n d Cruz D Rachel
dun Rachel Vermilion dun
G thank you Richard G happy Halloween
Papa thank you and space waterful
than I'm catching up
guys we're we're we're we're we're we're
in
November at least in jst the next stream
would be November ah and that one I
don't have to read Because those are the
polar words ones
we're till no no no no no no no no I I
don't I'm not worried about
that I'm going to be reading those while
I make the
Polaroids yes uh but those are a lot
holy [\h__\h] is it more than last time no
right how much was it last time six
let's see wait how many pinkies is this
pinkies that's probably less I think it
was over 100 last time okay
[Music]
manageable I'm surprised there were so
many I'm I'm glad you guys wanted to get
more of the polo warts even though it
was the templates from last year I'm
glad we can reuse them did I miss the
light Po no Daisy it was a a
rerun um I offered a rerun
on last year's Halloween Polaroids in
this
stream so maybe you missed it but like
it's not completely new
[Music]
ones if you don't the re ones how can
you get a full set
uhhuh that's your mission I
see didn't have the money that's okay
honestly you guys got to you know save
up for some things anyway perhaps for
the V collab and perhaps for another
[Music]
thing the V I'm just going to say the V
collab might not be the only
thing
that I will have to throw at you this
month this month
yes
yes but don't
[Music]
worry like doesn't have to be like I'm
sure there's
like pre-order windows that are Beyond
to this
month I'm sorry I'm
sorry
yeah in exchange for that I don't think
I really have anything in particular for
like
Christmas and New Years I don't think I
really have anything
[Music]
M no I really I don't I don't think I
have anything
[Music]
um Advent
calendar not looking so good right
[Music]
now I don't think it's going to
happen
um yeah
I was uh I was kind of
awaiting commands from management
because like first year I did it
completely on like my account right and
then second year
they while I was still helping out a lot
they took over right with
like some of the
organization and they paid for the
assets
yeah uh so I assumed this was going to
happen this year again but the answer
now was
no um there's not going to be an advent
calendar at least not from their side so
if I wanted to do one it would have to
be
completely like covered by me
again I don't know going back back to
that after it was once taken care of I'm
not sure about that I there's still
enough time gyy barely if I wanted to
set it up I'd have to start
now but I don't
know I don't know if I want
to like deal with all of that again this
year running after people and trying to
organize like videos and
[Music]
stuff I know that it was like a nice
thing uh to look forward to each day at
least like the people that were aware
the fans that were aware of the
[Music]
calendar yeah there's at least more
members now so that should
like I mean Justice Advent are
definitely going to be
like you
know uh very active I'm
sure
but I don't know what to
[Music]
do yeah
yeah the old one says see in
2024 you could do 12 days of christas n
then then I feel like actually we can't
even
fit n it
depends I don't know I mean the team
that worked on it last year and the year
before they're like they're motivated
and they'd like to do it again but then
it would all be on me
again I don't know I don't
know I have to think about it cuz like I
literally just was told about it
today sorry we are not dealing with this
this year so not make calendar Focus all
the effort into just one Christmas
project no like I feel like if no if
anything it's got to be the calendar
like I it kind of became a tradition now
that we did it twice in a
[Music]
row if I do it then I won't be doing
puppets I'm sick of the
puppets I don't want to make another
puppet I don't want to
[Music]
they're going to haunt me they're going
to come to life and they're going to
haunt me that the best
part well yeah but it's also
like I feel like if it wasn't me doing
it uh like the whole project then maybe
more eyes would be on it
[Music]
so like I don't know if it's like worth
it you
[Music]
know you
know I don't know I kind of want to do
it I don't want to disappoint
the people who are looking forward to
[Music]
it we are chat Christmas via is like
more stressful to
me almost yeah yeah if I'm if I'm the
one planning it that it's more
stressful just still a ho in X
re that could be the final
[Music]
but I don't want to be the one planning
it I I don't know VR is like making me
sick like really stressful hot heavy uh
uncomfortable sick and I'm not I don't
know I'm not the best in like the
technical aspect when it comes to
troubleshooting and stuff like
that now also I don't want to boss
people around I already feel so evil
delegate all responsibility to a
kohai all of it onto one
Kai now I don't know if there's anything
planned for Christmas from management
side at all I don't remember ah maybe I
remember one thing I don't know
but I don't I don't think there's
anything planned that
involves all of
us but even all of us if I say if I
invite everybody to VR collab not like
everybody going to show up
anyway so all of us is definitely
difficult uh
regardless yeah [\h__\h] I'm going to think
about it one night I'm going to sleep
over it
ah ke R thank
you going to sleep a night over and then
tomorrow I'll make my decision
tomorrow's my day off anyway I got to
make some decisions
anyway
yeah sounds good sounds good
[Music]
well it might not be as stressful
as uh it
seems might be okay I just need to
perhaps see it a bit
[Music]
more uh how to
say how to say
I need I need I need to take the stick
out of my
ass what I mean with that is like in
previous years I really wanted uh fans
like every fan to
um like get something get their Oshi out
of the
calendar and so I also tried to make it
like even and organized groups so that
everything is like relatively balanced
as much as
possible but like if I don't try so hard
and I just say
Okay whoever wants to
participate bring it on let's work
together but I'm not going to like run
too much after people that will make it
less stressful but I I generally want it
to be
like everybody
but if I if I try to see it a bit more
casually
maybe uh yeah that could
[Music]
work so this
n but then I'll have to I'll have to
figure out how to take over the domain
again look at that
all right all right all
right it's not at 100% yes yet but I'll
think about it I don't think I'm on
[Music]
it I'm going to read the Eden
Eternal super
chatos
from the Stream
kada Saves
Christmas no it didn't need to be
saved I'm saving the Advent calendar if
anything but yeah what if you get list
to voice act anyone that's
[Music]
missing I don't think that
will really spark Joy
enough Jacob 47 James Finn 87
D what the heck why are you guys' names
so
interestingly
synergized Jacob 47 and James Finn
87 weird is that your cousin
Jacob Ty d zly d Jak Monkey D spim D for
the rent of chair taxes okay here you go
oh yeah the guil tax says thank you
thank you I paid them yesterday you pay
me I pay Austrian government thank
you thank
you naan cotton than of the pinky for an
example this itself is a TI thank you I
appreciate every
TI thank you so much for the
donation as you should to your boss and
Overlord takanashi
kiar your Guild Master whenever she
wants to
[Music]
be
c ah yeah yeah people have been sending
me those ca boxes for the fashion items
they got some good stuff in
it boohoo 723
[Music]
D Ki how did your breakout roll as Le
were jenings of MMO infamy influence
your career
path yeah it gave me a big breakout you
know a big breakout on my skin too from
all the stress man but ever since people
have forgotten about my past and see me
as a completely different person so it's
less stressful these days yeah people
don't know that my past life is Leroy
Jenkins because I'm a YouTuber now
thankfully people don't know there's
people who of course attempt to figure
it all out but they will never
understand even though I'm saying it
live on stream right now I will I will
personally put in uh a virus on their
brains and they will it will destroy all
the memory of what they just heard so it
will be fine
[Music]
be worked worked
no the one
H tricker was revived and is currently
playable the [\h__\h] are you talking
about
when wait do you mean the mobile version
do you mean the mobile version
[Music]
wait this website
works level 400 the
ranking play trickster decom download
game
client is this how how e
how
when it's notop
Mal
[Music]
no Trickster
ah okay even the mobile version was shut
down in
[Music]
2024 I don't understand there's
like conflicting information read their
next Super Chat oh [\h__\h] did I get
baited h i Li trixer is not still active
their website is and I was gas La by
what the [\h__\h] me
too tster it's a [\h__\h]
Mirage it's a [\h__\h]
[Music]
Mirage yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
going under confused Obsession I still
wonder if I was made for you if I could
only see oh please
oh Persona calculated perfect for you
pretending like it's me
[Music]
f
don't what I need do
[Music]
you like you for long
now you me on
I I don't even know what to do with this
man good play you par my me
my
Mir Mir sping disg on and on and on and
on and on this
[Music]
Mir I'm not even writing lyrics this
must be my best known memorized song
that I
[Music]
have I do everything
I be the king and queen of
new I'm begging you to see I'm you you
all of me it seems like everyone wants
it all around run on and on keep me
captive Escape my way you know to PR job
I'm just perect I don't break me shave
me you never see what I want what I need
or do you no no you no follow through
like you now
ah you s me on a mirage i t you up iness
I don't even know what to do with
thism be good playing your part my
Mir my
Mir the light dis and and and and
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
yeah you make me fall in
love make
[Music]
me I don't even know what to do with
this m tell me the crusted big play a
part by here fuing go
[Music]
my I don't even know what to do with
this me the play part my
[Music]
Mir
Mir and and and and
[Music]
holy
[\h__\h] that's so fun the Speedy part SP
why this guys on and on cuz they it's
spread up
[Applause]
yeah yeah I'm better now thank you no
I'm I'm not my head hurts now from
shaking so much that's so much fun oh my
God can't believe they sped it up but
it's still 4 minutes and 8 seconds long
how do they do this
magic it's so
good every time somebody mentions or
creates a mirage Euro beat Mirage will
from now on automatically
play so [\h__\h] hype I can't I can't
even I can't even my head
[Music]
hurts okay looking for the top D you
have more D wait
that was so
[Music]
fun M eight than pinky fun c t you and K
you great together maybe I should marry
just kidding I really actually see her
more as a sister like we do some weird
flirting
but and it makes me feel really nervous
uh but I see her really just as like a
small little like fun energetic sister
she wants her so bad as a sister
sister
wife nah she already has wives many
wives I really like the
vibe that I feel you know she she feels
like
family and a really a cool popular
friend that I want to be a friend
of she's so
fun yeah so I don't I hope people don't
misunderstand I'm not trying to like
romance her I'm not going I'm not taking
the gigy route
actually not at all the rising is just
for fun if there is rising it's just for
fun but it it gives me conflicting
feelings actually cuz to me she's my
sister yeah maybe one day after whole
life you can experience a final
fantasies 14s right story even if it
isn't no wait
X a you mean okay because it's kind of
different even if it isn't the MMO
experience you're looking for oh since
it's November any plans for the usual
calendar the usual
calendar
interesting see you're also asking this
question so people want to
know well already talked about it so you
got your answer I'm thinking about
[Music]
it yeah py
D hope you enjoyed
[Music]
Carta it was fun did you like the the
new SSS
version then did you like did you like
down thank you for wrapping orange I
appreciate
it fancy
r e thank
you there's one that I can't read
[Music]
thank you D moonat
moonat is this moon dog but
disguised is this
oneg doesn't have a members icon is this
your second
account ah your pie see got bonked what
oh your alt I like your alt your alt
should be here more
often thank you t d l d unknown thanks
for the pinky so true thank you always
true I'm not even going to question what
it is what it was about I'm just going
to say yeah everything I say is
true and space wonderful thanks for two
pinkies so I did watch both reasons
seasons of R op just as I said I would
and I got to say season one was mad but
season 2 was okay overall all right I do
like Gandalf Tom uh Caleb bmore and
Prince Duran the others were interesting
too I was entertained and I admittedly
enjoyed
it but it's the weakest Lo Rings content
for sure are you
[Music]
sure I'm sure there now what about the
golum game
huh if we're talking about lot of drinks
content you're in uh you're including
games and stuff
too OG loaded Rings is Peak 10 out of 10
Hobbit is really good at five out of 10
rings of power had good action and the
plots kept me interested but I got to
give season 1 5 out of 10 and season 2 6
out of 10 okay I mean that's fine don't
regret it don't worry I'm just being
honest to you sorry no that's not even
like so bad like you
know what Golem
game
huh what do you mean what do you are you
guys
pretending anyway thank you don't worry
about it I'm glad you watched I'm glad
you gave it a chance instead of just
being so stubborn thank
[Music]
you uh also thank you how do I pronounce
your name raill or
r or
R
rail thank you don't don't go back to
silent lurking you can write in the chat
you don't have to send super chats to
communicate uh you
know I'd love to see you in the chat too
but thank you for being around
just reacting now while he's still here
but I'll read the Super Chat properly
when I get to it which isn't so far off
anymore oh my God catching up I'm
catching up let's
[Music]
go so I guess I'll go tomorrow I'll do
some Moab and I'll uh make some more
appointments and uh I need to call
maybe
my phone provider and stuff need to do
some stuff hope I I hope I stay on top
of it instead of forever watching
Breaking bed in bed with my
cats
mhm yeah it work yeah sorry chy tomorrow
for sure tomorrow for sure I'm so
useless I I I just I can't I
can't no but
[Music]
you chy said anyway he wouldn't be able
to work on it these past days until uh I
think tonight or
so so it's not it's not not too
bad it'll be fine it'll be fine so I'll
think about if I'll really just eat a
sandwich or if I'll find something else
to eat but I'll leave you guys behind
hope you guys had
[Music]
fun had fun that we did me too ah I like
diao you know what even if um
I I wonder even if I end up not like
finding Holo members to play the DLC
with I wonder if we could kind of like
team up if there's any people who have
or who are planning to get the
DLC and haven't really gone through the
content yet I don't know no maybe not I
don't know ideally it should be with
members
but there were some motivated members I
just need to cuz I don't know they
probably already forgot about it I need
to bring it up to
them but don't if you don't have the DLC
yet don't get it yet
cuz I'm I'm mainly aiming to play for uh
play with the members if anything with
the Ian members or like whatever H
members it's really expensive so don't
get for
nothing I'm sure they're happy to be
reminded you think
so it's too heavy for my PC yeah even
lags for me when I'm in the city for
example
crazy get it for the cat yeah do it for
the
[Music]
cat okay oh
I'm going to
[Music]
go it's midnight oh no Cinderella time
y thank you for watching hope you
[Music]
enjoyed should we go listen to it one
more time in the loading screen instead
of the ending screen
did you notice I'm separating them again
instead of using the same screen for
both I just likeed it so much I wanted
to see
it they want to get hype it's just so
good it's just so good G we
say
opening listen to Mir you will beat
[Music]
[Applause]
going I Wonder If I Was Made For You
with I could only
see please oh make me up
you perfectly for you
pretending yet I'm why you never what I
want what I need oh do you do
you
[Music]
follow throw you up into shreds I don't
even know what to do with this m tell me
to cross it be good play you my
Mir sing
[Music]
[Applause]
woing you to I'm you you're all me it
seems like everyone wants it around
around keeping
[Music]
me I break me shap
me you'll never see what I want what I
need do
you
[Music]
no me I you I don't even know what to do
with this tell me to Cross play
[Music]
my light and and and
and me me
[Applause]
[Music]
me I'm off thing
oh is it because I'm playing it
through is it off S the whole
time
[Music]
[Applause]
bro that's
[Music]
weird this I'm lost
yeah cuz I'm playing it for OBS I
[Music]
guess yo it's so good
I'm remixing it even further I
guess by delaying it there's like I see
that sometimes on like YouTube some
people like manipulate songs like this
song but the uh L the vocals start one
second later or
so must be
foreigners
bye-bye go I'll watch crony
later if you want