foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I don't know
foreign
[Music]
hello
howdy
everybody and welcome to Among Us with
whole life English and Indonesia
[Applause]
well you have gathered here today to
present to you a new feature that just
was updated in Among Us for the whole
life Cosmic Cube
[Applause]
then you can like get outfits from
selected members from Whole Life en ID
and Japan this these streams are not
sponsored but we just really want to
show you so good look at everything
[Music]
wow
we ask everyone to introduce themselves
and they can also show off their sexy
outfit Wilder introducing themselves all
right
let's go we might get kicked out of the
room eventually but let's just start oh
let's start with
hello everybody wearing anything uh
number one detective I'm naked
um
[Applause]
she will have some sick outfits some
sick trip right yeah yeah yeah
okay below um we have Anya at least in
the Discord so Anya introduction
yourself please hello everyone I'm
shirakamian today nice to meet you guys
in the nation hello
hi okay next we have Kaleo primary
hi I can't really I'm having some
trouble with the choppy audio which is
why I'm not screaming but guess what
also my mommy hooked up my Wi-Fi which
means I'll be streaming in 480p which to
be honest why even why even [\h__\h]
bother why even bother okay Mom I'm here
to get some whole swag As a sheriff
let's party
[Applause]
[Music]
Amelia one of the selected people you
can get the outfits of hi gouda hello
yes we're officially in the Among Us
lore now we're right
now
you can have so many imposters of
yourself do you even know who who is you
anymore I love it there are many
sharklings around
there's one right here right next to you
is cool please introduce yourself
I love you
uh who is
Shawn Mendes
[Laughter]
[Music]
we're going to be crazy
yeah
[Music]
it seems like an imposter
the whole outfit it has to be meals it's
suspicious
all right whatever it's close enough to
calliope
and then we have Muna who is also part
of the people whose outfit you can get
in the game hi Muna
hi everyone
from Hawaii Indonesia generation one
nice to meet you you're wearing your own
hair oh yes yes
I feel like right now I'm wearing a
scientist outfit right now I feel like
I'm I'm doing a touring love in the
Among Us
yeah
okay okay and then we have Mommy hi
Mommy
I'm nice I'm chocolate ice cream today
chocolate ice cream we're working on it
at the right mommy yeah yeah
oh yeah
who are you going for what outfit do you
want
ah the pepper is closest on the tree
yeah understandable all right and then
we have a baby
[Music]
today I'm cosplaying as sexy naked money
in your area hello
[Music]
good what the heck that was really cool
wow yeah okay
hello hello I am I will be the second
today
oh my God yeah
it sounds fun at least the organizer of
today's events the sponsor of today's
event
Chihuahua
[Applause]
[Laughter]
of course of course that happened one
second I will open a new room that
timing was amazing yeah that time it was
amazing the fact that that happened on
your turn yeah yeah
true a new code is in the Discord chat
please please go get it and don't make
it seem to the yeah
um huh how do I get one set I thought
it's gonna be I thought they're gonna
automatically censor it ah hello oh
thank God comedy gold
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
yeah a really sexy combination
look at that my clothes are so cool oh
my God
[Applause]
looking good I can also do like
I can do so much I can do this and
[Music]
um I will now change the row settings we
will have everything included we'll have
scientists in case you don't know the
scientists can see the vitals at any
time no not anytime well there's a
countdown but you can see if someone's
dead before finding the body and then we
have the engineer engineer can uh is a
crewmate who can jump into the vents so
you can
yeah or you can maybe find some other
imposters because of that
um
[Music]
very spicy and now we have the guardian
angel which I thought was really useful
because the guardian angel is the ghost
of the first crewmate that dies who can
then go on to protect others from death
and I only have last but not least the
shape shifter this one is that that
calls for a lot of
fun
Shape Shifter can be only an imposter
but that imposter can change the looks
of themselves even the name so if the
shapeshifter is me I can change to I
don't know Anya and even have her name
and her outfit and I can kill people as
her other people will think wow that was
Anya oh my God what if I was the one who
found you instead there will be two
onions
but just so you know all of these rolls
are not 100 so it's not guaranteed that
you that they will be in the coming game
but you know it might happen to you
I guess
wow
okay so this is like my first time I'm
using the proximity
[Laughter]
it's a loud shut up
laughs
foreign
[Music]
don't bother me don't bother me no no no
no I was gonna say I trust you but never
mind
[Music]
that is not that is not the LIE
um
wait where was it the um where where was
the body Armory yeah
I'm nowhere near there I was in the
tower of people in the room I think or
was it Ollie oh
I was on my way back
yeah I mean Phoenix tastes good right
what wait wait
everybody saw me in the shower so I'm
safe
yeah she was pretty busy the whole time
so yeah shower she was pretty busy the
whole time I would say
hello
what are you gonna choose
I can hear you uh it's the the corpse is
in the Armory right yes because like uh
like in the beginning of the game I saw
Muna in the armory but like that was the
beginning I was in the back room when it
was for now well she got killed fast
anybody want to step up and be like yo
I'm something
I have no idea though I didn't you can
uh if if you are you were telling me
that um I was in a Armory you can ask a
gura because I saw Guru also in uh
nearby there in the kitchen sky
[Music]
that sounds suspicious
dang
no one was ejected I'm so
so cold
foreign
huh
oh
what
who wants
huh oh
um okay
why why the why the door automatically
close
uh
um
[Music]
ego sip
scary
scary scary
oh
electrical
[Music]
um yeah
this
[Music]
oh p l something I don't know I have no
idea scary
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
I
like scary scary scary
no no no no no no no no
no
oh my God come on man oh my god oh is
that is dead lights out lights out it
was lights out at the kitchen
a kitchen kitchen
uh me and Maury Senpai we were nearby
electrical I was going to the viewing
deck I was with a roommate and Kelly
Senpai I mean I went to the armor and
put guns away I passed by I passed by I
think it was Watson oh and
and gura in records yeah I can I say
that last time I saw zado they were in
the main hall with Kobo Cobo
I was the thing about global because uh
she she telling me on the previous one
it was me well I definitely like far
away from the kitchen and now uh
she left
do you have anything that you want to
defend Cobble yeah
so any last words
was like in the in front of the fan yeah
sure just uh see herself I think like
just what she said and then after that I
go up
I saw you before right near the lounge
that was beginning though that was the
very beginning
oh no I I after that I go up
I go after killing her you mean there's
something oh my God
we have like we have little short time
uh choose uh who's you're gonna I don't
know I'm still not sure but I have
enough information I don't know I have
no idea
everyone
laughs
I don't know
[Music]
I don't even know I don't know guys at
the very beginning
okay I'm gonna
I'm just gonna make a sandwich
tomato soup
and this
wow no meat in the burger
can't relate to
okay
I think it should be um
kind of scary though I don't trust
anybody here I have no idea I was just
like following oh hello what the heck I
uh
I'm just trying to you know carefully
download stuff don't mind me if anybody
sees me don't kill me I'm just a
downloader
I'm just uh I'm just a what
okay I'm just a downloader trying to do
my thing and there's nothing um I'm not
hostile
maybe if I say um
okay
like if I if I say I'm not hostile then
I'll be like you know people be like oh
okay killer
let's go I'm done
[Music]
who killed her
that's insane Watson is dead uh I found
the body
oh is that it was like the previous
corpse that I found last time yeah oh oh
um okay so I was in the front
um of the ship and I was doing the tasks
that were up there and then Watson came
in and we chased each other around for a
little bit and I was like don't don't do
this to me Watson she laughed she was
like I'm Gonna Get You he he and then I
was like haha very funny and so then we
did our tasks
came in right after while I was figuring
out how to do the mini game I was like
how do you do this then mume ran in and
was like hey he hates he and doing
things and then I walk out and watch
this dead body is there
all right can you explain yourself
because you would have passed Watson if
you were entering the front of the ship
you would have passed Watson how did you
not see her well I I don't know but I
did pass I want to say I
pad we people people didn't
have to stab me yeah
by asking that
I'm not gonna point fingers at you
immediately I just want to know what
your Alibi is putting fingers at me no
no I'm not I just want to know what your
Alibi is because I Watson left and then
you came in and I walked past you and
Watson's dead bodies on the ground I
just want to know what that's about why
do you remember so much Kelly I'm I'm
just surprised I got a lot just I don't
I can't remember right now listen here's
the deal so the amount of time that
passed in between me entering the room
seeing Watson leave and mume entering
and me going outside was so short
uh-huh it was like no time at all you
would have passed her I just I just want
to remind you that we have 10 seconds
left so I think if if you don't have one
I'm gonna choose I'm sorry I have to
vote for a roommate I just don't believe
it
we make poor decisions sometimes now I'm
just like messing with Cali
I'm messing with Cali you know it's to
spice things up I don't even I don't
even know who did it I was too busy
downloading stuff
oh
[Music]
surprise guys I actually can afford the
outfit I just chose not to
nice Zoo
[Music]
down yeah
guys should I wear clothes
no that was the only time I've ever done
something legitimately
that was cool
Amelia wants some detective outfits
yeah
thanks are you guys ready for another
round yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my God
a lot of people are here
um oh um okay
cool
spicy
and yeah guys should I um should I keep
myself undressed hold on four excuse me
please don't kill me yeah please don't
kill me Kelly do you think I should like
wear clothes or not
nah you look great just like that it's
very muddy and Senpai thank you that's
what I thought all right then thanks for
the feedback yeah yeah you're welcome
okay let's see oh we can head across
thanks man appreciate that good looking
out
okay
well two in the kitchen hello hi
hello hello hi
oh you're gonna be in the toilets spicy
spices
[Music]
hello hi
it seems easier to remember people when
like you hear their voice I think I
can't remember colors
just not my style
I don't know
hi you're not gonna hurt me right there
are a lot of people in here I'm just
doing my tasks
there's a lot of really safe
um
yeah
a lot of people hanging out in the
shower yeah what was the last one
oh hello
excuse me if anybody kills me well I'm
doing towels I'm never gonna drink
across why not ah just put this stuff
away yeah okay we have to pull it over
the thing
okay I'm done with the tables
love you you're gonna kill me
if we combine your hats with my your
head with my body put your head on my
body
now
found all we did where
um that was crazy so I don't know the
map super well but I left the shower so
I put away all of the washcloths from
the shower yeah and then I walked up and
I turned right and I went down that long
hallway and found Ollie's body right in
the middle of there but I didn't see
anyone coming down from there so I'm
kind of thing oh so like above the
shower house
to the right a record all the way to the
archives
you remember well let's see
um Renee was busy doing things around
the shower um also rained could have
killed me pretty close I know right I
think girl was in the shower as well but
she like went down to the left
that's not what I saw you uh do we have
like uh like you said who's gonna be
delayed
because because if if it's really if
it's raining if she already killed only
probably she cannot kill you
right but I mean Renee could have killed
me several times and she didn't so here
I can vouch for me she was trying to
tell me a joke and then I ran away from
her oh yeah also could have killed me
but didn't so I went the opposite I had
no idea because I didn't see Ollie at
all and I was like at the left side
whole time yeah it was mostly down below
hey Muna what do you have against me why
are you stressing me out huh something
no I'm just like saying uh so Paul is
saying that you are nearby the the place
I just like oh true I'm true you were
also there by the way but I I don't
remember I saw Muna Senpai in the
middle-ish or on the left side oh by the
way no info we got no info
I'm skipping oh okay
foreign
okay
[Music]
this Spider-Man actors rotoscoped into
Mario Kart what is this oh
many many people
I hope I'll still be alive by the time
um Kiara manages to tell me her joke
or better yet she's probably the one I'm
gonna be the one who to kill me if
that's not romantic I don't know what it
is
yeah yeah tell me the joke now
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah you put your head on my body and we
can become one
[Laughter]
I'm spicy
nice okay I don't I don't want to do
calms because I can't like literally I'm
just gonna
be you know what you call it like the
weights dead weights
together thank you
safe you fixed it right here
we're all here except me
but I'm innocent
but I'm innocence
why are you why are you like all whisper
like that whoever that was
I'm gonna die aren't I
ah oh God
oh what
what
I can't go from there okay
you're so sweet
I've been telling her oh hello
you know like this is really scary bang
bang bang sound you know
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
what
oh okay whatever that means
oh
hmm I have no idea what that means
uh but I'm just gonna like do my best
though
um
thank you oh so that's what you do
okay and then
I will be done
yeah it's not my first time in this map
I did practice well I was like you know
for me you
[Music]
oh my God where
no
no too small they killed her off
they killed her off where was she I have
a very bottom of the armory
um
anybody else
I was on the way actually I was on the
way to the kitchen so any any sooner I
would have found the body but I'm from
the engine room like from the main hall
I saw you I saw you at the right side of
the map going up yeah sure because I was
doing tests at the cargo bay you know
there's the test oh okay cool
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'll explain my route I went cargo bay
uh for the you know small thing and then
I went to the showers because you know
that those are a two-part task after the
shower I went towards the main hall
engine room communication because I have
tests in kitchen and viewing deck and
then I was about to turn to the Armory
and then bomb that body found so you
were pretty close by I was pretty close
by I know I saw rainy yeah
went past me and it was the best voice
it was like way back the one I saw the
soonest was mermaid
and I was like I went like what
what well we also interesting
interesting
wait is that a fish I forgot about that
oh [\h__\h]
um
what
rainy with said a voice
[Music]
hello
um
I'm kind of scared now
myself
I'm kind of scared now not going to lie
oh thank you whoever fixed that it's
certainly not me
[Music]
cute
cute humming
please don't disturb me I'm just making
a sandwich
hello I'm sorry for sounding hostile I
swear I was just like trying to protect
my life
it's me hi thank you
what
huh
the house right no no
weird
[Music]
hello
I think it's pretty nice that people are
really scared of me that way
hmm
I can do everything without being
disturbed without having to suss anyone
without having to be to be scared
because people are afraid of me anyways
I smell
who's that
um here and then I saw you
what's happening what's happening what's
happening what's happening
okay
that's real Muna though
okay there was Zetta somewhere around
here I'm gonna say something okay
oh really but I have the thing here
electrical maze uh
[Music]
on your safe on your safe we're doing
the same test for the Senpai it's so
confusing because Anya's like wearing
the exact same thing as Zeta like not
not exact but like what movement why are
you so afraid of me
why is she so afraid of me I didn't do
nothing what the hell
well it's yes that's a little bit quiet
this time around you know
is that kind of quiet he said raise that
thing hey Kiara there you go
hi Anya hi hi
[Music]
I haven't really done anything much huh
YouTube
have you guys streamed illusion at how
many times have you guys streamed
illusion night today I wonder
I'm trying to catch people in the eyes
hello
hmm
anybody
anybody not dead preferably
hello
back
what where where oh oh shoot
[Music]
wait where
I was I was just doing the stinky
electrical test with Anya and I ran into
it raining and mummy
[Music]
um
that's uh technically that's true I I
keep thinking while I think this three a
two Row in the back is always you guys
always spots salsa but rainy why yeah
bring it you're always there
what where was The Buddy
huh I don't even know where it wasn't me
it wasn't even me reporting I don't know
where the body is this time
guys
where was it
wait I want to ask uh Arena where are
you at I'm at Medical I came from cargo
bay
um what with Muna Muna was like going
from bottom to up I saw her in the cargo
bay
and where was the body I literally have
no idea nobody mentioned about that how
about Watson
for a little bit but then I was down by
electrical like down the ladder that's
where I was coming up when it was
reported
I don't know why
I'm so serious why is see all I want to
ask why is mume so always so afraid of
me or is she just afraid of everybody in
general um
scares me my body for me last time the
body
so do we have an answer where the body
was I missed it probably yeah where's
the body was I was gonna see
the body both the body is
[Music]
I don't know what should I choose uh
like dude you got like 10 seconds 10
seconds and then you just like say like
oh yeah
you know so now we just needed
I don't even know
um you're beating around the bush
laughs
poor Mommy
oh hey
I want to take a bath in the coin so I
can be rich
hello hello hello
hello
there why no Muna and the left
what
Muna I just saw you on the right but
huh
hello hello
Muna Muna did you see me before uh up
there
I saw it I was in the carpet
um
we're gonna keep haunting you
until you say something when you're
alone and someone's going to be like oh
man
talking to herself
[Music]
you tell her Ollie
oh my God there's a dead oh my God
no no no no no
no
hey Watson you're not free from this
either stop pretending like you're doing
things
[Music]
foreign
of me
so I didn't know so somebody was
pretending to be you I did see right
yeah
um
[Music]
I was like a while together she could
have killed me so I think she's fine
okay
we already voted one out so there should
only be one imposter left there is a
couple of times
but but she didn't kill me neither
[Music]
can anyone vouch for Ahmed and say like
she's safe I was with Gouda and I didn't
kill her
I didn't kill her maybe you were on
cooldown well hopefully we don't die
no one was ejected
dude I swear I saw her I said oh God I'm
so annoyed wait where's the where's my
ghost homies
homies where are you
yeah it's kind of like it's really odd
because like they're always like trying
so hard to frame me so I was just like
thinking maybe it's somebody that's
actually like good at the game you know
and then that thing with Muna was real
weird
oh here is I think
no no right away run away run away
[Laughter]
[Music]
contradiction
there
yeah but very quiet
oh you wow
wow
I wonder why I wonder why people kept
aggressively trying to frame me you know
it's pretty hard to watch yeah it was
really hard to watch I was barely doing
nothing you know easy to do
yeah and it's like I kept like I was
like alive and then I saw something I
wasn't supposed to see and then you just
killed me on the spots
[Music]
okay okay
nice maybe if I buy some clothes I won't
be so so bad like is the naked ones
discrimination no evidence
[Music]
maybe if I wear clothes people will be
like oh maybe it's not her I know okay
I have a question on there because I
heard you in the in the selection screen
where you choose where to go next I
heard you say something that sounded
like something
because I felt like you might have been
acting yeah was that what you were doing
um
so you were like aware that we would
hear you and you were on purpose saying
something that only a crewmate would say
[Music]
wearing clothes
oh yeah congratulations
everybody's got the boring [\h__\h] oh man
hello hi hi I have clothes
organizer and I only get the boring [\h__\h]
I'm crewmate with no roll me too [\h__\h]
you too
can I trust you
no always baby okay if you say so
I'm gonna die
and our practice runs I did kill you as
the Imposter yeah you got imposters so
much in the practice I'm sorry but you
know yeah no worries uh
no more race
it's always in the it's always the off
stream stuff you know materials what
is
[Music]
oh I'm trying to Oh I wanna I wanna play
with this
uh we passed each other in the kitchen
and I'm from the communications Armory
kitchen I saw viewing deck alien gura
everywhere
yeah yeah
I saw her I saw her in the shower but
then I saw Callie from the left side I
think
you went to the left side so she was
yeah she went to the left side yeah she
was in the shower I saw her in the
shower Cali do you have an alibi maybe I
was going out to get service I did pass
you Watson I was worried you were gonna
follow me outside but you didn't and you
probably weren't that worried since
you're outside
actually right by the body because uh I
was the one who reported it I was coming
up the ladder I couldn't help because it
was really dark and then I really
yeah
you went up I went up no I went I didn't
see you go up yes
no no I'm skipping I'm skipping the body
so I'm gonna vote for Zeta lights were
out right lights were out oh that's
amazing
[Music]
I don't know like someone going up but
they didn't
I'm just gonna like skip
don't kill me YouTube don't do it I
won't do it almost gone okay I almost
spawn hello excuse me don't I'm just I'm
just trying to like I'm just a signal
catcher I'm trying to download from my
mobile connection you know so we don't
really have fast internet over here it's
worse than the Wi-Fi you know like when
the Wi-Fi then the wireless service is
actually from the phone you know one of
those like old service times
you download MP3 and it takes like what
it takes what I don't know
like 15 minutes or so
oh man hello uh
[Music]
hello
hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
okay
then oh
what was that
luckily I'm near the lights
thank you Rainey where's the thank you
okay I don't even know where I'm
supposed to go okay I need to go here
hello everyone
oh no please man I'm just doing cable
things I like cables I don't believe me
alone
hard time following
me
why is it always lights dude come on I'm
not gonna fix it I am gonna fix it
probably
um let's hope we'll fix the lights
ah it's Zetta
huh
oh trash
I have no idea how to do this
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
I just found Anya's body in the bathroom
and I'm pretty sure Zeta and somebody
else versus us here okay
where's the where's the body uh anybody
who knows which room is in bath or
showers or no wait what the [\h__\h] Lounge
showers Lounge which one yeah it could
be bathroom stalls are
um though let's wear out that's a day
where
um yeah the last time well last time I
went near the shower and main hall is I
saw Ollie
and I think I think did anybody see Anya
with anyone no lights were out yeah
think oh yeah she alone in the
huh right side then
I think it's uh probably Kiara and Zeta
what what the [\h__\h]
no can't pass me so many times and she
didn't kill me okay yeah
listen to me I'm always us when I'm a
crewmate and when I'm not a crewmate I'm
uh nuts us so keep that in mind now
you're sassing me which means I'm a
crewmate it's always like this it's not
gonna work I didn't
well then I say it's what
why aren't you providing an alibi
instead of Defending yourself huh
it's included room where like she would
have killed me
[Music]
I'm gonna skip I don't know I'm gonna
skip because I don't know
um foreign
[Music]
okay oh sorry I don't want to stay
together because I have tasks bye
now that the lights are back on sorry I
don't want to stay together
[Music]
because I have tasks I'm sorry
yeah please see okay listen see I might
not be like you know uh doing anything
like that but at least I'm contributing
and watch some shop don't kill me
don't I'm not I'm uh doing a thingy
e
is the thingy killing me
uh no I was just putting in the code
okay
good to know
I'm gonna stay with you no I don't want
to stay with you Chris here
I would have killed you already I'm
turning my cool down to about to be up
oh no
no
please don't kill me I'm innocent
I of course don't kill me I'm innocent
oh okay it's Zetta for sure I'm voting
oh really why why
okay
you you said you you found a buddy three
times a row now yeah because I just
happened to be a detective who's really
good at spotting bodies
one says some scary things but I don't
know man
Rayna could I have killed you or would I
have uh healed that body if I was with
you and in that room for like over 30
seconds
um I don't know uh you want me to be
honest um what you said was oh just
kidding I was just waiting for my cool
down to you know I was already in the
room doing the task before you got there
no I don't know I don't know
oh
uh give an alibi to Jetta
no
no no but anybody can give Alabama
running away from the body because Reina
and I were both up in the room like in
the meeting room and then as I went down
I was with Raina the whole time and then
we saw Zeta pass Us in that hallway
[Music]
30 seconds 30 seconds
aren't I sassy
finish your tasks
10 seconds who
I voted for Zeta but maybe it's wrong I
went for Jenna too but I want to vote
for Zetta because you know
she didn't even do anything
rev Zetta no hard feelings
yeah family meeting
family meeting what oh
I'm almost
shut up
this will be the death of me
you know why you don't open the door
cause I suck
foreign
Watson watch me clean the vent
and maybe kill me in the process task
here okay
ready Let's Stay Together
okay
are you doing a task in here or
something
no
no then what are you doing are you just
waiting to kill one of us
yeah okay
all right all right have fun
all right
good luck
look
did you guys eat breakfast or dinner or
what
[Music]
um
I don't know how to get up there me
neither maybe up from here
[Music]
yeah if I die I'll let it be known that
Cobo and Zeta both voted for me
oh no no no I don't want to be I don't
want to Stack nine four okay good luck
oh no
uh yeah
also I'm done with my tasks let's go
let's go to the emergency meeting and
talk about who couldn't finish their
press okay
hey
and welcome back I'm safe let's just
stay together we can stay up together oh
oh wait she's gonna have to do a detour
she's gonna have to do a detour
what what are your friends
[Music]
oh sorry sorry sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I know she's alive she's alive never
mind
[Music]
trust me bro trust me bro it's almond
trust me thrill okay it's Kiara
why are you calling a bow I was just
doing my electrical thing
you just didn't have an opportunity to
kill anybody did you what what you
didn't have an opportunity to kill
everybody
I'm telling you it's on the dressy
probably Kobo to be honest because she
was like Raina and I were together and
Kobo was not doing any tasks and she was
just following us trying to wait until
one of us was like separated
what were you doing recently
I was just following them why are you
done with your task or no my last task
is in electrical
um
then why did you go up to where we were
Ollie Ollie yeah you're usually so good
with numbers but why did you mess up why
did you keep messing up that number
thing I had to do the keypad thing for
you
true that was
that was so cool but went over to that
side but what's on that side too right
like you know I was on the other side so
I was just being stupid
I'm sorry
wait so why do we call this emergency
meeting in the first place just because
because we wanted to develop you off yes
let's go
let's believe it's not me
I'm gonna um I'm gonna vote for Ollie
because I kind of feel bad for her
because nobody ever susses her wait what
the [\h__\h] ing him
that's so nice of you raymie thank you
for assessing me finally
one day I will get that impossible
okay
it's not Army
see I feel no I feel good
but not voting for AMI
why why do you keep closing the doors
I swear I hate this game I hate
thank you
well my tasks are done
hmm
where is everybody
I have clothes bruh
foreign
even not doing what the [\h__\h]
I'm so tired
hello yeah but wait
[Music]
where are you
oh I don't hear them anymore
what
wait that's so scary I don't hear them
anymore
hello
let's find the others
let's find the others well for
why why why why why why would she say
that
why
ah this is so annoying
what do I keep having to close these I
mean open these
foreign
okay
okay okay
[Music]
hmm
I don't know
swiping card stream
[Music]
okay there
I'm just gonna
it's gonna I don't know
okay
is it time for image I don't know
ah it's so annoying stop it I swear to
God I hope you never have a good night's
sleep
okay
open the Hundred Doors what
what happened
task
oh task done
okay
I'm thank you oh my God
[Music]
was so spot on
she's a real detective yeah
he was kind of funny not gonna lie yeah
I'm so scared potato
that's just her personality it's not
that she's yeah that's just her
personality yeah
I
believed you
okay
sure sure
[Music]
oh wow
hello
please don't mess with me
I am just a little baby
I am I'm gonna check myself what
she's gonna what
okay let's her back on
I'm gonna do my test like a normal human
being what six
five
I'm so dumb
ah six five
bro I don't know what zero
no
I've never
before
huh
what
three
oh
my God so oh it was the other way around
it was the other way around oh my God
that's so confusing
huh
no like the arrows are just like really
confusing
huh
oh my God this this stupid task
s
[Music]
oh I'm so salty yeah I'm salty too they
got some good players like no man I was
I was like doing like this safe opening
thing and I it was just like it took me
so long to understand she really wants
to die oh and then somebody killed me
while I was trying to do it I'm just
terrifying because she just doesn't say
it she doesn't say anything she just
doesn't it
though I want to be killed though um
Cobble
[Music]
[Laughter]
I found the body in front of
Communications between Communications
and Communications and I was oh I was uh
um
the last time I saw Cali was somewhere
near MMA with nine seconds nine seconds
to kill as many people as you can okay
thank you
[Music]
foreign
like I never I've never seen that task
before and like the right and left is so
confusing
God
stupid safe
I'm so I'm not gonna lie I'm not gonna
pretend I'm not salty oh what's this
test oh what
oh I gotta make it straight ah I see
that's pretty cool but the Airship test
is actually really really nice
so messed up I have used the safe before
it's just
oh my gosh [\h__\h] sorry
dad
oh
yeah so annoying
wow but you know uh seriously like the I
like the Airship I never really have a
chance to like do Airship that much but
uh it's nice because all uh all of the
tasks are like I feel my heart is so
Doki Doki
yeah when I'm a ghost where
okay
I was with uh
wait who don't get your body though
there's three bones
an alibi for for Oli and gura because I
saw them and we were we were near the
kitchen and go to security and
electrical we haven't go to medical and
cargo bay yet
for a while so
I'll buy
um
I want to us and also why Kiara is not
screaming at all let's go yeah what do
you mean let's go okay usually when when
she was the crew matched she always
wanted to cut me off and then scream I
feel like me and Kelly Sim I always die
early yeah but that's okay
you know sorry focus on tasks
[Music]
let's see
oh shoot
ah
what the [\h__\h]
no I'm scared for my life I don't know
what to trust anymore
okay I have tossed through time to do
some ghosty tasks hello Kelly
hi Rainey hey are you upset doing my
tasks so we can with you
Ryan
okay she sounds upset I am upset I just
want to do my tests
that's the least I can do
oh hi hi rifle so cute
yeah
okay now we go to the very left what are
we gonna do oh download stuff I love
downloading stuff
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
rifles just like in Russell
okay I need to upload data on here
game hi what's up perfect signal let's
go oh my God imagine having oh yeah you
know good [\h__\h] let's go oh God what's
happening crash course yeah that's none
of my business so
wait what well here what's here I just
like wipe this clean
[Music]
okay and then I need to go to the
records and like store that stuff and
then I'll be I mean I know that Kobo is
bruh okay
okay I'll put this here thank you and
then you
I'll put this a soup here let's go to
our tests to our tasks they're just cute
okay let's go
and then boom
oh that's it and I have to fix the
wiring and then I'll be done with my
tasks well I'm so delicious most
diligent P file 2022 in Hall alive
yes
this is kind of like therapeutic
actually when you get killed oh yeah I
am done with my task let's go I'm gonna
watch people now
I'm gonna watch people
either
[Music]
hi what's up it's Watson and Muna
yeah do the lights do the lights
everything is close
yeah need the electrical thingy
yeah I need to fix this one
oh hello
this just go out again
okay then let's see
hello
we fixed the light anomaly and what do
we do I mean I can just only like pick
up people observe that's what I like to
say observe hello
what is me
yeah
[Music]
over there alone on the left side
I tried to help you
oh what if I hold like an emergency
is here
she's like she's haunted by so many ah
nope
are you the Imposter
one
oh she's going around
someone said I'll be very happy
it wasn't yeah I saw I saw Muna Senpai
going towards where Ollie was and that
was the last time I saw her
oh really on your way there or over
there
[Music]
I'll defend yourself
yeah
it really went to check if anyone's
you're the last one left and you want to
try to vote people out
why
are you doing anything shark also not
saying anything yeah I didn't know
what is it called what are they called
imposter the one consumer skin skin
consumers whoa
[Music]
the tasks is that it I thought it was
over you know what yes I'm done with my
task anyways so like maybe I can just go
chat with the girls you guys can vote me
out because that's what you guys want
um
[Music]
five seconds oh God
[Applause]
what can we ask anyways
I don't know
oh it's me now uh I will I guess
Watson's smart enough
what's an angora you will be able to
sniff the people right
yeah
bye girl please just just just go just
go just go to the meeting place just go
meeting please I think just someone has
to present someone has to press it or if
so because yeah and now like yeah it's
gonna end
ask
Gora
I'm done with myself
oh man
[Music]
1.5
okay not bad
what is that weird who is breathing
Ollie I'm gonna kill you the second time
okay
oh my God she's just happy for winning
guys
every time that Kobo is the Imposter
it's incredibly difficult that should
tell you whenever people are dying
really fast it's definitely Kobo
a
she saw the crime scene went goes to the
emergency meeting and then Ahmed Changes
Everything by sussing the innocent ones
yeah yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
I was right with you Kiara salty
I take it out too early for like one
last round I want to play again
next time
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go
where is Kitchen
in my soul
[Music]
what do I do where am I so sad
I hate this game so much
awesome great fantastic
wait when is when is the cool down it
hasn't even been like 20 seconds or
whatever
or do or does Killers just not come with
cooldowns in the first
um
[Music]
oh
no no I thought it was your body I
thought it was uh no rain eggs raining
is dead so here's what I found I was
picking up all of the towels and [\h__\h] in
the shower and I said I hope gura
doesn't kill me a girl is fine I don't
think that she did it but I went to the
left okay
um we are in the same room and
um the people I saw were you gura Senpai
and Zeta yeah okay well let me tell you
where I found the body first before you
start pointing fingers okay listen to me
because I didn't even tell you where I
found the body you just immediately
jumped yeah
from the left of the shower walked up
and in that photo room we're all like
it's like a dark room I guess that's
where I found the body I didn't see that
there was a dead body in there because
the lights were out until it said before
I clicked report and I guess Renee was
killed in the dark room so yes that's
all I have to say about that I literally
was just cleaning up the shower was
anybody down there electrical
nobody asked about electrical
electricals I was at electrical showers
I was at electrical and I saw no one
yeah I saw that uh but I was so bigger
no you weren't you wait where
electrical I have my I was at the bottom
right of electricity I walked at the
bottom
so not having clothes this was the right
decision I feel like no I didn't finish
picking him up I thought I did but it
wouldn't let me put them inside of the
hamper thing so I still have to grab a
couple towels I I I am suffering with
only because I was in the electrical I
saw I was in the electron I was in the
middle I was in the middle bottom and
she said he was in yeah
that was that was way too fast it might
be exactly
[Music]
too much I'm gonna do my task
s
oh in here
okay I'm gonna focus on my task
Oh wrong place
I'm gonna protect I'm gonna protect Muna
uh hopefully she doesn't die until you
know because I'm my priority is my task
where's Muna
hello
okay damn it did you see that happen I
saw that happen oh is that uh hopefully
you see it said hopefully you see it
whoever it was
oh there were two people in there there
were so many people in there I don't
know yeah
yeah well it do be among us
okay I'm just screaming because people
said I I scream um when I'm a crewmate
I saw
yeah
you know Kelly is a Kelly's really
popular because she actually like
analyzes stuff
[Music]
yeah she's kind of good
I didn't even have like 10 seconds of
gameplay I'm so mad I know me too
every time
I
wish your partner I feel like I do is
super bloodthirsty except for Uranus
yeah I'm just here to have fun yeah
[Music]
um
you can still save people raining true
true I'm flying to like protect you now
because she does things this is us
what are you waiting for yeah
oh my God that's a Full House
rip crazy Mio
okay well time to do my tasks yeah this
task was what killed me cheese
[Music]
if you can't help people yeah
I don't know who's the other one though
I don't know who the other one is
[Music]
foreign
she finished the alarm and then she
walked to the right side I need to
finish my tasks
Etc
and then I will protect Muna or
something
elimination
tells me that that's the result the
showers
what if there's a
I know
um
[Music]
innocent she always like speaks a lot
it's more like met it's it's kind of
meta though if you say that but you know
hmm
what
if it's the shape shift
[Music]
yo good job I did nothing but you know
good job
in terms of gameplay holy crap
it's not just their manga slide
you guys figured it out heck yeah
thank you
that was a great job
they are music I have music I'm sorry
that was my alarm sorry okay
it's anyone who didn't get imposter
every single time maybe yeah
um yeah it's always always Predators man
no I do a terrible job with imposter
anyway
we're like too strong anymore
yeah this game is like never end I feel
like I want to play it until I got a
major imposter
yeah
I wouldn't mind playing more but I'm
just worried about the ID members
because it's like you know two ways
for me it's fine because I usually sleep
at morning
what about three minutes
I feel fine if you want to but um
[Music]
okay one more
oh
my God why every [\h__\h] time thank you
so much
oh my God I like this room yes hello
Making burgers my favorite thing to do
um uh oh wrong way wrong way wrong way
oh hello
please like if you're imposter you
understand how I feel I had like 10
seconds of gameplay please let me live a
little bit longer
you know that's like my single request
if anybody's imposter let me live just a
little bit longer I barely had 10
seconds of gameplay in the past two
rounds so you know if you're imposter
anybody imposter fixed lights oh shoot
man
man huh use work oh tour
whoopsie
I thought what was that button I don't
know
uh I have to go to the showers okay
oh no what do I do
oh I need to kill them all oh no I need
to kill them all but how am I gonna kill
them
oh
it was in the hallways it wasn't a mean
Hall actually yeah okay I yeah so uh I
was I was I actually uh saw her through
the showers I went to electrical a
little bit then I went back to the main
hall and guess this I actually met
another Ollie so if you guys said
anything like oh my God
no there was actually a doppelganger and
I actually met her she was chasing me
down
she was chasing down and you know what
even if you guys
don't mind
I think I think I think I'm gonna skip
because I don't know I don't know I
don't have I don't have anyone either
she's desperate whenever she's just like
this
and whenever she tries to defend herself
always just like very very desperate
yeah yeah
and loved me woke me up because I'll do
the tasks easier that way anyways I can
just fly now you staying
I have no info
[Music]
what happened
oh my God how are we gonna kill all
these people oh no oh how am I gonna
kill them
I thought was there oh no
but you know like for real though Cali
always gets killed off first like I feel
so bad okay
yeah no worries you know what I had like
10 seconds of gameplay like last round I
had like a minute of gameplay last round
too so you know I'm not gonna kill
people off
all right
or am I
that's what that's what an innocent
would say that's what an innocent that
is pretending to be an imposter would
say they would be like ooh my cooldown's
running out but then yeah I mean me yeah
like it would be like I don't know my
cooldown is running out I'm gonna kill
you but then they just like do nothing
different than an actual imposter they
would just like kill you and not say
anything and act innocent like oh I
don't know or like not speak at all you
know
oh perfect signals
oh hey Muna you gonna kill me off
I'm like so hostile for no reason
I'm like searching for
hi Shorkie disappeared hi Ollie hi
Isaiah yeah
what do you think it's probably a
doppelganger for real
I'm just like I'm just like you know
like reappearing and disappearing
oh I need to is this it yeah
[Music]
it wasn't good
oh Dolly got the pretty name plate I
want it me I mean I have I have an alibi
oh yeah you know so I was I was on the
first I wasn't security we drain it if
but anyway I was the Imposter I've been
I've been with Renee uh for like a
couple of seconds I'm not killing her at
all so if and then I got time
yo the thing is I passed I passed both I
passed at least Gora I passed at least
gorilla like girls like was heading
towards the showers I think or the main
hall I don't really remember to the
right and then I think Ollie was asking
like have you seen gura or something and
then it was like also and then there was
also Zetta or something but there was
like a bunch of people there
show me a magic trick I feel like Yeah I
wanted to show a magic trick like I'm
not accusing anybody I'm just telling
what I saw okay
I mean um yeah I mean uh
okay I don't know yeah um
no Ollie's fine I was alone
I was around Muna a lot but she never
killed me but who says it can't be the
cooldown speaker nothing to say for
yourself I'm vouching for Ollie I mean
and then I also saw Anya that if you're
up for like a long time yeah but the
thing is I don't know Anya Anya was also
there but Anya is also there but girls
also dead
I don't know hmm
I don't know
if muna's alive I haven't heard Ollie
say anything I don't know because
everything will be used against me so
I'll just because because
I want to go to records to do another
see Ali's always saying things like oh
yeah you can vote me off or whatever
whenever you know
whenever she's innocent she always says
things like that
it's like uh it's pretty much like meta
it's a lot of meta gaming but
uh and I don't know there's no rules
against it so I'm just like saying it
that way
but trying to see me clean the vents
because I actually have a Vent cleaning
sure
wait did you see it oh you want to hear
something crazy no so if somebody says
uh if you saw somebody and they say I
got the Vent cleaning they're lying
all right
hi there
hi hi that actually makes sense you're
right yeah like if somebody ever says
that you know they're lying obviously
I'm afraid it does hey I know who did it
who is it oh no lights out
she's like I know who did it and
disappeared
classic Army
I feel like being outside is Hey Hey Hey
where's zombie hey Ami sorry lights were
out I couldn't hear what you said
what can you guys come with me for a
second Raiders trying to kill me
ah come here I'm gonna kill you
[Applause]
are you following me ah cause I'm gonna
try to kill you
hi
Marina I think I saw your
you saw me wait I need to do tasks
it is I can't play around too much yeah
you know who it is you know what it is
yeah but you keep doing the Cliffhanger
what is it what's the answer
she wasn't doing anything okay noted
I trust my wife what do you think I
wouldn't trust my wife I trust my wife I
said during the time she killed me and
trampled Over My Dead Body
hmm
you can't know that you're not a
doppelganger oh yeah yeah I'm Zita
oh there we go
I couldn't see it because it will lights
out
like can can I can I shower in peace
please I'm I'm I'm I'm naked right now
so please don't approach me thank you
and now I'm dressed
um I need to go the spicy electrical
this is the first time getting this task
in um in the Airship you know there's
something like that in the skill but
ask
[Music]
where is what
hmm
detour time
[Music]
I'm just gonna go through the lounge I'm
gonna call it okay
um muna's alone upstairs by the way oh
no she's no longer alone
lights
it's like oh moon is down there up there
oh never mind she's no longer up there
what happened
I want to say
it's cool
because I like previously when I was the
Imposter with kobu
um and I died before her I was like
following her to try to cheer her on and
I saw her she would go to that you know
that place uh the Electrical uh where
there's like one task but it takes
literally one second to do it and when
she was the Imposter she would stand
there for ages thinking about what to do
next and I literally caught her doing
that thing now but like she was there I
said hi I ran away because I was
wondering well she's always there when
she's planning something I know no one
died but that's because she's a very
hesitant killer she did that before too
I was watching her and she passed gouda
alone a million times and she just would
not kill gura for whatever reason she's
very hesitant and she goes always always
sort of electrical to
as if she's doing that task but it takes
one second and she waited one minute
there believe me trust me bro I will we
don't have any proof of it
because the only thing the only thing
that's like for me suspicious is that uh
she's she's being like awfully quiet she
hasn't really said anything up until
like in the discussion at all do you
have a defense first yeah do you have a
defense for yourself like why are you so
quiet or you know
um I'm always quiet from the beginning
alibi
what if I really
do my tasks
mommy gonna be so that aggressive I'm
gonna
stand in front of I did I did it after
you too and I know it takes one second
I'm just I'm just gonna say Ollie and
Watson are always together
yeah yeah okay I'm gonna fold stories
yes
how was your imposter friend too
two rounds ago
she's cheated
I don't think it's raining oh oh hi holy
shock of course it's not me what do you
think
[Laughter]
God in 4k talking about me I'm gonna
kill you off
Zeta where are you I'm gonna kill you
[Laughter]
Zeta
I think
she doesn't even believe I'm the
Imposter
hello
by the way oh yeah what what hello
what's up I don't know she's she says
Luna says
[Music]
guys guys want to go to the meeting room
with me meeting room please upstairs
with me I need to do finish my task okay
okay okay we're gonna come wait do we
need power or no
they don't think we can all go because
there's like a little elevator thingy
yeah yeah yeah I think that's like
oh I don't think we can get on at the
same time
so we're all here
nice
um
nice I'm gonna go first
tweak where are you going are you going
yes doing my test doing my task if I die
it's Muna just kidding
I don't know if they can hear me from
there but
oh she's not here
I'm safer
it's like if I die it's her
something dramatic you would say in the
movies
ah notice
wait what where is everybody
[Music]
oh
seven four three
[Music]
oh come on
please hello hello yeah go to the other
side please thank you
[Music]
now we can finally be alone so I can
show you a magic trick
uh yeah look yeah
[Applause]
are you looking yeah
why do you sound like the machine
why do you sound like that machine what
are you trying to show me
you see it I don't know what are you
doing at what are you what am I looking
at
I'm gonna see my magic trick no
oh well I'm too good
yeah you want to go over there because
then we can only go alone I guess so
did we just come back from killing
someone
no okay we're gonna check down here
where was that oops where was it okay
okay
in the cargo bay and she was about to
vent because she thinks she's cool
um and then I saw a red body
don't you see that um I was from the Gap
room and I passed by when you just got
the electricity and then go to the
shower and then I go to records again I
was in shout it was earlier
I I saw I saw I saw I think it was Kiara
and then Zeta is from the shower too and
we passed away right okay
[Music]
where is where is the location of the
body
I don't know what do you think
no but it's um in the cargo bay between
the door of medical Bay Reyna and Zeta
which way were you guys going through
the showers like to the left or towards
I was with you awesome oh sorry sorry
for me we came from the top to the
bottom from my glasses couldn't go the
other way or you saw her going with you
in that direction
I didn't see her at all which is the
problem what yeah
literally I saw I saw like um I was in a
break I wasn't breaking and I go to the
Gap room and then I got through the
record I go down I saw Zeta and then
Kiara and then uh Zeta and Kiara I think
there goes some of them going to the up
to go into the record and then after so
after that I saw okay if it's not more
if it's not and she's just faking being
an
engineering
I mean you always say it's mean
would you say your brain cannot handle
that kind of skill
we will see we'll see if the game ends
now
if it doesn't
no it's not me I think Watson can vouch
from me I think
bye
[Music]
but I'm just gonna be real I hope this
is last game because I'm like actually
recovering I'm so sick
gravity
[Music]
[Applause]
that was fun
I'm born to be a crewmate
imposter
that was fun guys
[Music]
that's pretty good so proud oh my God
okay
a great a great round
excellent I think now
as much as I want to continue playing I
don't wanna you know force me yeah yeah
maybe another time we don't even need to
play on stream to be honest just
together
yeah
I know right yeah
we already have a full Cali costume
though and I'm wearing it so nice
December 20th to get all the Halloween
stuff yeah so hurry up
hat
[Music]
ERS
let's go Gamers all right
I want to hear a goodbyes from everyone
if that's okay
um
[Music]
real goodbye yes
let's start from the top again I'm there
how was it today oh yeah it was pretty
fun I won an imposter round and then won
all the crewmate rounds or pretty much
all of them so it's you know pretty good
day pretty good game thank you for
inviting me Kiara thank you for setting
it up uh yeah thank you guys for playing
thank you for always sussing me even
doing almost never with me
it's like your reflex now but okay I
just want to see your reaction that's
how I kissed you okay
yeah it was so much fun
um I didn't get impulsive but it's fine
it's crazy
together thank you
[Music]
oh yeah that's me whoopsies
um yeah so I think I'm just born to be
crewmate I don't like playing imposter
anyway so I had a good round
um really only one super good play in
the beginning and then everyone gangs up
on your point that's fine
whenever you like explained something it
was really easy to listen to you and
like yeah I feel convincing and you are
not lying oh my God
I just gotta work on my longevity in the
game
I do
could also right I didn't but I made
sure to be the damnedest best teammate
that I possibly could oh yeah
honestly haven't been relieved I was
scared to see what happens if it's like
especially like shapeshifter
all of you
oh my God that's terrifying I wanted to
thank God I really want to be a shift
there I haven't got that yeah
well well if you guys want to look like
good on go get the Cosmic Cube
over the world
yeah yeah
Cobo killer killer give us a statement
about your actions today how many times
were you imposter
a lot three times
[Applause]
[Music]
in these collabs there's always like one
person who gets it off yeah
I only got it quite a bit too right like
twice yeah I want to say sorry for uh
groups who are being posted together
with me because I cannot
um I don't know why but I play on this
room like uh there's
maybe pressure
yeah yeah yeah sure so I'm not that like
I felt that you you seemed very precious
you're sorry
if I if I silent for a long time because
uh first I I don't really uh can make a
good execute yeah I will buy maybe in
Bahasa Indonesia it's so easy but
um I don't know that's fine you can
always use that as the excuse me I use
that with the JP no English please
Japanese sorry
yeah so that's okay you did a good job
being imposter Kobo you're really good
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
it was actually pretty funny because I
thought the reverse psychology would
work it did not
but I thought if I actually reverse
psychology guys like twice which means
if I actually asked us and say oh I've
actually says
Ah Ali's just messing around but nah but
that's what I was thinking
all right
gravity
pulling her in maybe maybe it will fix
itself in a little bit Yeah and uh I
actually want to thank yours invite
especially because uh organizing the
source of collabs it's like a big castle
and well all the most utmost respect
thank you for accommodating all of us
yeah Kiara thank you
[Music]
we had a good reason to play among us
again after a long long time it was fun
Bruno for a second and go to oh mama is
not here anymore
oh hello yeah I start the stream naked
in the end the stream naked even though
I unlocked the outfit but thank you for
inviting me to the collab it was really
fun playing with you guys was fun suit
to all the crewmates and also the
Imposter you guys were great yeah
[Music]
hopefully we can play again in the
future
[Music]
it was so much fun I got a few imposters
how many
you're free uh two or three I don't
remember yeah
it was fun thank you for those who've
been in love with me and thank you for
hosting it and I want to apologize
because my stream died six times oh my
God what how did you survive okay
it is fun yeah
pretty good
I think Zeta killed me more than any
other member yeah
[Music]
she can't talk well with that being said
I'm sure she had fun too yeah and uh
are you able to talk
don't talk
no voice
[Music]
okay okay
beautiful outfit out for now Muna you
did it
[Music]
thank you next time
you have fun Muna I have fun uh actually
uh the first time I'm doing uh
the to become an imposter with I mean
it's really fun
everyone
[Laughter]
yeah
if I make it a list it's probably
Amaze is the one who can like talk a lot
that make me you know
so that's usually the person that's
aggressive protective Sheriff um
[Music]
I think I got to hear from everybody I'm
glad that we all came together for
another big en ID collab I think the
last one was Mario
a year ago yeah it's a long time yeah
it was a very very long time ago you can
try it again
yeah
[Music]
let's do it I'm coming to watch Power
streams today thank you
I'm having so much fun
yeah and I really don't have anything
else to say besides good job everybody
hope you had fun and yeah see you again
soon sometime
[Music]
[Applause]
okay muted foreign
[Music]
foreign