[Music]
hello hello hello
[Applause]
[Music]
hello Mary marry Among Us
Among
Us what if you
Mar welcome everybody to the uh
Christmas or Holan holly Day Among Us
stream we have gathered here today with
so many lovely cute girls and we're
going to have fun choking and stabbing
each other
right
[Music]
VI let's go awesome well we're going to
um do it without proximity chat by the
way guys uh because you know we have
some first timers here I think it's
Advent girls's first time Among Us here
first
Tim not yeah we'll find out how they act
when when they're impostor we can't tell
yet like for others maybe we already
know a tell but for these newbies we
don't know what is their tell maybe
that's maybe you could tell us would you
be so kind in your introduction to tell
me what your tell
is please nah you got to find that out
that information is classified going
need a little cash money up front first
we try well okay then let's start with
introductions let's start with the only
one who's a real as astronaut
here h Hello Amilia Watson number one
astronaut
detective yeah I like Among Us so I'm
excited to play Let's
Go point out because maybe there's some
new viewers at this point who don't
understand why is am able to wear her
own clothes in the game and why am I
wearing p is wearing Min clothes am do
you want to explain H yes we have uh had
a collab with Among Us where you could
get a few uh Hol live outfits and items
in the Among Us shop but I don't think
it's available anymore it was kind of a
little time
thing time too bad if you missed out me
and WEA are ping right
now keyboard slam you guys are actually
you guys are in a room oh
yeah the
keyboard keyboard slam I know no that's
what it looks like code looking like a
slam oh you're giving them hints you're
giving and slam welcome to the slam jam
please join there we go get some
fertilizer who calm
spam all right I guess that's
[Laughter]
more oh you have spam color too M yummy
you had a Spam color that was amazing
nice box oh well while we're at Callie's
uh you know bullying her for her name
Callie please introduce yourself so we
know that's really
you if you
insist it's me K life english's
hardworking
Shinigami uh I'm in a place with very
terrible internet so I can't stream my
POV but I'm very excited to be here with
all of these lovely ladies as a sheriff
completing my tasks and making sure that
we win the day let's go yes you wouldn't
kill anybody she is now known as
[Laughter]
but yeah I'm so happy you're joining
even though you can't like stream
properly thank you so much dead beats
they trained me well I wanted to show
off my new skills that the dead
beats with members fairly recently oh we
got to watch out she's good at the
game thanks the dead Beast would you
just ask us how you kill people in this
game okay I guess I didn't help at all
that you played it recently it was
unhelpful well okay moving on to fun
where is she where is she I can't find
her oh I'm in hiding you can't vote me
as the impostor if I'm hiding
right there is fa from Hol live English
promise hello hello I'm here does it
feel does it feel like normal now like
it still feels weird to me to hear that
introduction
promise yeah I think so fresh still it
is it is still pretty fresh but I like
it I think it's boat yeah not boats I
feel like everyone's been traumatized by
boats
recently what's with this current Trend
in the whole lot English of watching
school days what's going
on last year we finally got it yeah it
was PR
[Music]
good
yes
the it there's a staircase did you know
there's a
staircas
IA have no idea what these girls are
talking about good I'm so confused I
wish I it's too cursed it's nice that
everybody is having fun school days and
all that it's fun a jolly season it is
great piece of Cinema yeah all right
Iris our number one Christmas lover
hello yes you're number one Christmas
lover here hi Iris it's Iris from H live
English promise
your kill people I love this game but I
I I really suck at being imposter but
yeah so so yosu yeah but I'll do my best
you are you really bad at it I don't
remember I I was horrible imposter last
time I played this I screwed up she gets
impure maybe you just need a better mate
to work with cuz you're dumb d m oh
bit of a poopy
head there's use what you're talking
about the lobby will fall apart it's no
problem let's take our time okay yeah by
the way have you guys speaking of Iris
have you guys all seen the yesterday and
today's episodes of of the H Ian Advent
calendar cuz I was very involved in them
I was very involved in them yes just and
they were both in
3D both space yep so Iris why did you do
it oh it's cuz you know we needed some
light to bring up the Christmas spirit
you know what better light than actual
fire right yeah oh that makes sense you
know it was my whole plan so that I I
could become the Christmas tree in order
to become the Christmas tree you needed
to burn the actual Christmas tree first
true you took Christmas trees that's
kind
of it is the master plan it's pretty
late yes
very it was
fire indeed fire fire light the fire
fire fire light the
fire
fire y everybody's uh joining in again
in the lobby I think I'm coming I got my
name I freed C spam he doesn't exist
anym she's more com spam I'm sad is it
going to hide the code if I have
streamer mode
on yes yes yes it's hidden for me it
does it's hidden people self
introduction please Hi H bomu I'm clu
sparkling Jem of H English Advent and
today I'm a space Rock but that doesn't
mean you're allowed to Stellar Stellar
me out of the ship so I am not sus I am
nice
wow okay that was pretty good you could
be nice
us no no that doesn't work here doesn't
work
here man so you have to prove yourself
prove the truth
you can't fool us people you're sus dang
already you're already sus already
why I agree I think I think it's her
yeah yeah I think it's
[Music]
Mo okay let's move on to foro
police I'ma I'm Hua I'm not H
I'm together we Mo don't laugh don't
laugh
okay your voice okay Mo Coco but
sometimes I become a dragon sometimes
you know but as long as you know I'm not
Chihuahua I'm not Hua I'm
Mak and together we make the best crew
mate you know G dogs we a great crew
mate not an impos kind of unfair it's
kind of unfair yeah you're impostor it's
too it's two of you
guys the
best I think I think we should vote them
out right away every time that's kind
ofation let's not do that but indeed as
a crew mate they might be very helpful
cuz it's two brains for one I guess
who's on the keyboard who's controlling
controll I'm the legs you're the brains
uh I'm also the the pointer
finger yeah nice looking for
[Music]
that'll be nice to see one one day they
will play separately but today is not
today isn't this game on mobile maybe
somebody could play on mobile I was
thinking I don't know if it
quite I think there
isect really it doesn't work on this
[Music]
side well okay and then now we stop PE
how
imposter hi
darling devilish Diva
Raven I'm an imposter today because I'm
pretending to be M and I guess
so be yourself oh my gosh fake it till
you make
it we're we're a nice couple no so
aren't we
how ironic but I should be running away
from
you I don't want your child
narissa even if honeyworks made a song
about our child I don't want
[Music]
it okay and
then
please
Oria from H life English Pro what H life
English promise um please don't arrest
me I'm gonna be a very good egg for
today uh CA even if I want to be an
impostor I never get it I almost never
get it so you can trust me I believe her
I trust her 100% I trust yes I trust her
100% I trust everyone
100% everyone only says the truth today
I look so kind pretty high none of none
of us will get imposter probably yeah
probably
that's how many how many imposters are
we doing I set it to two two we're n
people I don't know should I do three I
don't
[Music]
know
okay and I I have in case you're
interested uh two long tasks and five
short tasks uh as well as two common
tasks I don't remember what common tasks
were that's
suspicious what you don't you don't
remember oh yeah cuz imposters don't do
tasks well it's been too long rolls or
something right like you can do stuff
now or
something like rolls RS oh yeah wasn't
there something besides crew mate now
like um uh likees those help the
Imposter like the Spy or something like
that not imp
help
yeah keep them on that's fun okay I
don't know how does that work though I
don't know I've never beginning so wait
yeah there's four roles there I don't
know you girls can probably see them in
the settings uh on the on the computer
here there's a scientist who can access
a portable vitals panel so they can
check at any point of time if there's
somebody dead so they always see the
status of the crew and then there's an
engineer who can use the vents even
though they're not an impostor but then
you might be sused and you have to be
like I'm not the impostor I just vent
because I can oh that's pretty cool
really and then the guardian angel uh is
the ghost of the very first one of us
that
dies oh is that how it works the first
person that dies yeah something like
that the guardian it says the guardi
angel is the ghost of the first Dead
crew mate they can temporarily shield
and protect other living crew mates I am
so I guess if you're the first one that
dies you become the guardian angel and
then you can protect somebody else so
that they don't die yeah if you do it
properly and well timed you'll be able
to prevent imposters from killing their
victims sounds amazing me throwing so
that I can become the
guardan
a already
are and then there's a shape shifter who
can who can change the appearance and
disguise themselves as other crew mates
why would you do that though that just
confuses everyone
The Imposter or make the Imposter harder
to find too because then you know the
Imposter can say I'm the engineer or oh
no I'm the shave you know like please I
promise I'm not a murderer it doesn't
say that it's only impostor but why
would why would why would a crew mate do
this I don't know why would turn that
one off but I like the other ones yeah
should I should I keep them or should I
impost oh it is okay yeah it just
doesn't say so so wait there's only one
imposter is only one imposter The Shape
Shifter is that how it works uh I can
set how many there will be I can say
two I can say we want two or I can say
we I want one or zero I can set it in
the
settings but if I do one then only one
of the uh imposters will be Shape
Shifter but only 50% chance the one will
be oh yeah I can I can make it higher
too that we have one for sure I feel
default is good
right okay okay default then let's keep
the rolls then let's we're going
straight to
the before
we before we go um can we have the
visual tasks off because if we have it
on it might be too easy visual tasks
off yes very good okay and before start
I'm Tak I organized this thing the logos
and the thumbnails are commissioned by
me
[Music]
so don't kill me because I I pay for
this okay don't kill
me we
right byebye byebye okay
byebye
okay we're good crew mate oh where is
what
wow
okay wait Somebody went off into
nothing let's do our task what art art
tasks good question oh there's something
shiny over there what's that what's this
wait what is this I just used it what is
this I just used it cool where am I
going wa what up there a b
Communications CR
Senai what the
heck the heck what is going on we
magician I a wizard what is going on
already saved
us Senai than you that was frightening
oh gosh oh gosh oh my gosh what is
I don't know what's happening why am I
here help what am I
doing I'll break it I'll break it oh
I'll break it is helping it good oh did
it good that was is a
goldome oh
God something I trust
everyone they would hurt us they what
right do you know what's going on
oh no
[Music]
bye I'll miss you bye the only real you
guys tell the only real astronaut you
know what that means we don't have a
chance of getting back to our own
Planet unbelievable so who saw Watson no
I didn't see her at all I did I didn't
see her I see at
all who who reported just now me I did
tell us about it did tell us about it
where was the body so I was going around
Communications um trying to figure out
the mushrooms and went not and I went
down uh the the little zipline and then
in the storage room Amy was dead storage
room storage
room we saw around the Buro yeah so that
checks out you saw
me wait so F was also in the storage
area no no we were at the mushrooms and
we were having problems with that and
crony Senpai was around and then crony
Senpai went down before was there too
yeah yeah Moco was chasing me
around I don't know what's going on I
have mushroom problems
yeah I had like a meat problem I don't
know like it I suddenly turned into like
a a lighter pink and there was like a
chunk of meat chasing
me
puff and then they change into people or
something like that what do do is that
just an effect to freak you out or does
it do something I know I don't know I
think it I think the the the mushroom
like if you touch it or something um it
hides the the people so you can just
like kill them and run away and they
would be able it swaps my skin or
something like
that me why do you know that hot yeah
yeah my skin got swapped as well yeah me
too
and then I had a little worm next to me
for a moment and then poof it was gone
and the light was back
on weird I I don't know what what goes
on in this m I don't know I feel like I
trusted cron Senpai and now I feel like
I don't trust crony s talking huh H I
will say I passed by and I was actually
running away from crony cuz it felt like
she was chasing me didn't
you are you you you followed
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
me
goodbye I don't know the fact that she
had like her own like um name oh oops
okay I'm going to go back to where we
were cuz I don't know where else to go
there's some seats there Oh I thought
that was a body I got scared no over
here a cafeteria engine is this like oh
my gosh is that oh what this what's this
oh let's do that oh seashell seash by
the seashell seashell seashell by the
seash wait is this sea sea by the seaa
sea sea Sals by the seaa sea sea cells
by the sea is that done no M at the top
oh I didn't missed it it's so big we
didn't see
it
oh kind of we were happy last time in
the Splash Zone now I'm kind of scared
here garbage garbage
oh wait wait I just saw Nissa like 5
seconds ago though Nissa is in the South
part of the map with the lab in the
hallway I don't know this
map um wait how do I look at oh I saw
narissa around like next to the
greenhouse when I was green she's above
the greenh
house I saw her walking around I didn't
see anyone near her I didn't see anyone
else yeah I only saw Marissa when we
went up to Communications and that was
the last time I saw
her we didn't see anyone except for the
site and I think she's scared us I ran
away instantly I'm will be honest I
don't trust anyone who voted for crony
in the last round seems like the
imposters were trying to get her out
because she wait wait wait wait is
Dead's there's a
double would K by tell us before huh us
something important when we're going to
stop but yeah I want to kill her who did
it there's only there's
only Among Us really oh that's true
there's two imposters still crony could
have been an imposter though honestly
like I don't
know it doesn't say who oh it doesn't
say oh yeah I wouldn't put it behind her
if she self-reported because look at her
look at her um her icon like she it's
all why why are you of her for no reason
I don't know I feel you wouldn't be this
suspicious unless you were the impostor
and you're sure not I swear to God I'm
not I I I I said out right that I saw
like narissa pass by just 5 seconds ago
before I I didn't see when I saw Nissa I
didn't see you though uh no I was pass I
passed by her when she was going
greenhouse and I I'm currently at the
meeting room I went the opposite
direction that's why I think she was
like stuck on a that bivo and Iris seni
are suspicious I think so too wait why I
swear I'm not you doing I'm not I was
walking around I was in the LA the LA
wait where's my the lab and then the was
on like the 10 seconds I'm voting bio I
was I I don't have enough I'm
going I swear it's not me is not me uhoh
bye
oh my
God we get
him thought we won yeah
tomb excuse me you didn't even notice I
was dead guys we
best literally Iris passed me and biu
killed me immediately
oh good te self report good team you
two thank you
yeah impr was surprised well you know
what we learned from that because Callie
was pretty quiet was The Quiet One
quiet not The Quiet One True fooled me
Cy fooled me too
straty I was just confused cuz like my
voting was super rushed I was like what
wait why am I suspicious all of
a everybody pointing at
each peer pressure peer you don't have
to vote if you don't know I know I you
don't have to
vote Iris out that was so weird I
thought it needed to be like majority
vote to even get anyone off I thought
too I enough to kill me it was it was
only a little bit of us left so two was
enough
people already
[Music]
died we're strong at this we're good
pretty good doing our tasks weren't you
the ones
[Music]
who I guess we're sus no matter what SCE
can't be
[Laughter]
helped well that was a good first round
let's let's try to beit for an extended
voting time oh
sure yeah uh it's currently 90 seconds
should we do 120 or at least yeah at
least 120 120 is the max okay should
good Chad says apparently we can vote or
skip the vote if you're not confident
like who it
is confident was pretty
[Laughter]
confident pretty confident voting out
all yeah
I well now you should now you know then
you maybe cannot trust your
confidence
yeah all right then let's start another
round even though this is really fun
here thank you crony for finding
this see you on the other show bye bye
see you guys bye here we go wait
is oh no I don't know how to do this I
don't know how to do this what kind of
where it the Irish Senai that's also
going to be uh which Senai are we going
to pick up M I'm going to go here hey
this I know this part oh okay we got to
do this part and then oh gosh but where
do I go Aon I said the mushrooms is it a
task I'm doing a task I'm doing a task
somebody comes by it's again I don't
know what to do is there a vent get her
I don't know what to do I'll just run
away from the part someone will see me
how do I do the mushroom gone it's
gone I'm going to
sabotage oh I don't know how to
sabotage I'm going to go down this let's
go down there okay down
here what should I do violence should I
just go violence violence next next next
Senpai I see violence yeah a bble to
bble deserves
it this oh that's the vent oh it doesn't
look like that no one's
around okay where' you go where you go
where you go where where you go where
you go where' you go oh up the stairs
you went oh up the stairs I follow was
it Irish Senpai Irish Senpai is on our
team is Irish Senpai good at killing
people cuz I think that'll be good huh
oh this is the lookout oh I can look out
in security let's find somebody trying
violence I'm
trying uh Sur
where are you where are you where are
you are you somebody was here ponai
again let's get Pony s oh that's a bad
time that's a bad timing oh here is the
meeting spot W oh my goodness oh gosh M
did you shape shift no no no no you did
no no no no should I shap shift into
someone no wa now you
can't now go maybe maybe soon I could
shap shift into the cor Senai oh let's
do that let's do that I'm going to go up
here again but crony Senpai is the only
Senai we seen what if we meet crony
Senpai then that be scary oh there's a
body we got to P our weight no not again
come on
yeah
leave what I'll break it down for you oh
happen I did all my tasks you guys could
see me I think some of you saw me
watering things in the the mushroom
place I moved some storage around
roasted some marshmallows went up to do
my tasks in the communication room and
what do I find Watson dead middle of the
floor I didn't see anyone leave though
was anyone near Communications recently
where is commun top right take a little
like a what is it the zip wi the zipline
zipline we would a little bit but we
didn't see mine I just went up there lad
yeah I was just in the jungle
area yeah I know there was there was
like oh oh okay these white white things
are okay yeah the line you can go up and
down but yeah I wasn't there yet um in
the bottom right um there was a lot of
shape shifting I don't know who is who
yeah yeah there was a lot of what
happened with that the mushroom is that
the mushroom stuff working on everyone
well everybody everybody got a skin
shift right confusion that we don't know
who is who and then we can't prove like
oh that person was there or whatever but
we all look different not like each
other right so it's not shape shifting
it's just it's just the mushroom
[Music]
power is that somebody doing it or is
that oh by the way I just want to say I
haven't used it yet but I am the
engineer mushroom it does it
okay I can vent but I'm not the The
Imposter just saying I didn't use it
that sounds I wonder recently was anyone
around upper engine Lookout or mining
pit because the Imposter may have tried
to escape by going down the ladders I
will check it out I was walking that way
but I didn't see
anyone okay I've been down over in the
left area for the whole time doing my
tasks so I haven't even gone over there
yet sea I haven't been up there yet I
have tasks and communication like I was
going to go up I'm currently passing I
was passing by the greenhouse I was
going to go up but and then you see
anybody run past well no I didn't hard
to tell still at least hard to tell yeah
but bio was kind of
quiet just saying actually bio passed by
me and didn't kill me
so me this is the first time I'm doing
task I can tell you I've been doing
water with narissa and then I did the
marshmallow thing and and I the video
game I shot as
and I haven't been up there yet so I I
do have Fass up
there okay we'll see we'll see
inconclusive but keep your eyes open
yeah maybe don't don't go alone don't go
around alone guys go with a buddy I
don't we don't need a buddy a wait
that
[Music]
together that was close what do you mean
what what am I going to do I don't know
the tasks I have to do
something I don't know I don't think I
should just vent I think I should shap I
think you should get away from Panic
okay we did a task here I'm doing my
task I'm doing my task I could I could
kill someone okay we got to wait okay
don't think just kill time to kill time
to kill It's Time to Kill don't just
kill wake a wake a what's down here is
there a sire okay next sire I'm not
going to takeen out I'm going to kill
them we're demon dogs not chickens yeah
where the sire
sire scared me okay no no I'm going to
I'm going to what are you going to do
you said down there I'm going to out I'm
shifting into Fest here we go here we
go what we I'm going to kill I'm going
to kill I'm going to kill I'm going to
do it don't
the okay okay oh we're going up here I'm
going up here and Senai we're not going
to run to Senpai we're not going to
Runo okay we got we got to go we got to
go we got to
go but I was F some oh then we
good we're good deep
breath
she was a little bit suspicious though
she was pass her going down the ladders
from communication to the lower part she
I see her maybe went to communication
where'd you find her so I was going up
the ladder to the communication and I
didn't really see her body but um I saw
the the vent which is the plant kind of
opening up and then closing they
vent yeah they vented to wherever it is
from
Communications does anyone know where
where the vents from Communications
connect they can go anywhere right I
think all the vents can only usually I
don't know in Old Maps usually vents
only connect to certain other vents I
should have checked and then I could
have told you but too bad no
idea I I can kind of say I think crony
is not self-reporting at least because
like I feel like I was I was running
around with her a little bit alone she
could yeah and she didn't and then I saw
Cali running around I think we were
alone for a little bit but she may have
been on cool down as well but she yeah
she was coming down from that she was
she was coming down from that area yeah
I told you I cross with her oh okay but
yeah and Cory said someone vented
h
H where are you a good question we were
at the beach the beach we're just kind
of going around but we don't really I
don't know what's going on the map here
we're just trying to get the tab it will
show you where you are oh tab where yeah
hit tab the map will pop up there's also
the map icon on the top the map icon
right yeah the top
right I see a map but I don't understand
it it has a lot of marks on it yeah
a lot of marks that is that is it
exclamation
marks a lot of marks on it have some x's
on
[Laughter]
it know marks I mean I don't see so many
marks on my map yeah did we mess up
imposter see maybe does a previous
imposter want to tell us what they saw
like Kelly yeah Kelly I saw some x's
with circles on and I clicked them
[Music]
do you have anything to say to defend
yourself we just doing our
tasks get we
[Music]
everybody what happened to the
Buddies
[Music]
goodbye I hope we don't regret
that
well I'm too
Hest I'm too honest I was so good my are
you proud of
me we're not good doing like this we're
meant to guard and protect too honest
okay I'm not good at this sabotage wait
how do I do this press the buttons
there's so many stuff what am I supposed
to do I don't know what I'm doing haunt
I'll haunt how do I
haunt what does haunting do
what what does haunting do haunting
oh I don't know what's going on smooth
chocolate yeah why she I thought she was
going
[Laughter]
toer you're the one who BW it I thought
I was doing well okay how do I sabotage
my doing good until Nissa got in the way
she did putting us on the spot how how
sabot toys you must learn to lie and
detect I can't do that
is we're not detectives we're foral God
whoops how how how press the buttons I
am how do I sabatage you can't sabotage
well that makes
sense what am I supposed to do here
press the sabotage button there's an
arrow press the sabotage button press
now I can sabotage sabotage sabotage Sab
sabotage sabotage sabotage
sabotage that you now wa
more let's go haunt
[Music]
Nissa you're so close to tasting your
[Laughter]
blood who who's dead Kellie
wait I just saw her at least
I body that name too you know
the the left ladder um you can check the
map you can check the map and see
exactly I good at it I don't know was
she just with me at around like yeah I
saw everyone Communications I was
getting some stuff done there and also
the lookout and then I went down and she
mov
fast and then
died is there anyone around there in the
lookout right now I'm in the mining I
was around I think when everyone was
around can I type in here yeah we all
went to Communications home everyone not
say
anything so mean to to vot us uh who was
it like R Rissa
and I think they were around like
Communications and like Lookout and then
everyone else went to the other coms
um I too I'm sorry FAA but it seemed you
were being just um you know a little
very cautious I don't know if you were
careful about being stacked killed but
you the radio like where everyone was
trying to fix it
oh well you needed to go do the other
thing right to fix it I was the first
one there in the radio and I tried to
put in the code but I think you have to
put in a second code
yeah also I had two tasks that I did in
Communications I think the problem is
that we really don't I was I was in
Lookout I was putting the code in I
think it was the first to
arrive was
happening I thought I would go to the
other one and I saw C was like doing the
code at that point as well so she was
like she already arrived and then I left
her alone there I was about to go up to
the other communication thingy but then
uh it was already fixed so then I went
back and I saw I think I saw crony again
or so yeah but I didn't see fa and I
didn't see Iris at all I saw you Kiara
saw all of you guys I don't know I don't
know I saw all of you guys in
Communications I I was I was alone for a
while and she didn't kill
me yeah I
[Music]
saw down I didn't I was going to the
greenhous what did I Wrong um I ended up
in the lookout because I got and I was
very aren't we
all
[Music]
yeah oh my gosh I didn't know you that
kind
of I don't know I I I don't know either
I'm going disappointed in
your you're going to
skip
skipping
good luck crew
mates saage sabotage sabage sabage
sabotage that's us okay everything saage
[Music]
mushrooms
sorry I can't get through
saage okay I'll sabotage again in a
moment so that fin oh fin got out okay
sabotage sabotage Sab
Sab oh is it's over here hey is this oh
is this where find
aai Senai I'm going to make it difficult
for fin
Senpai assist assist how where is Iris
Senai oh I did it I did it I did it
h i go to Iris Iris here we go here we
go
okay learn from IR make sure to continue
sabotaging okay I Senai might be too
busy h yeah I sort of left the whole job
to her H
yeah well you know that's part of a
senpai's job right I guess yeah wa what
oh be careful because the sabotage it
interferes with ohoops
good to know don't get in her way don't
sabotage IR Senai just sabotage
everybody
else not going to do
[Music]
anything why they stop they're
waiting that was a good plan maybe now F
simp by
trusting okay I'm not going in sabotage
so I don't get into Irish senpai's wave
okay
okay yeah she needs to win everyone's
trust huh yeah she playing the long game
but if they finish the tasks then
it's
hi what why uh hello hello why help I
think n is trying to kill me ah you are
so I can't believe you I was not I
checked everyone's vitals and I decided
to go back to the meeting area
and I saw her and I got a little scared
so I ran back but then she chilled so I
thought it was cool but then she hit the
emergency meeting button my surprise no
the thing is there's a little bit of a
back story I was running around and the
only back story yeah I my task what do
you mean
backstory I was running I was you know I
I I was running around crony alone she
didn't kill me I was running around FAA
alone she didn't kill me I kind and then
I found you and you kind of followed me
and now I think if it's not cron if it's
not fa I follow you what do you mean I
ran into you and then I ran back to the
meeting area you are so fake
K I was also around crony and she did
not kill me either even though she could
have and as I was doing tasks I could
have killed crony too and I didn't which
I would have if I had the opportunity to
if I
was tell me everybody tell me I guess I
have to tell me FAA what are the
remaining tasks that you have I'm done
with tasks and I was Tak with Iris I
yeah sorry if you felt like I was
chasing you
yes definitely you were like stick to me
like yeah I have I have a task to do at
the dock okay and then I have one at the
cafeteria then do it and then we win
task win let's go guys we have to do it
also I think people who are done with
the task can um let's just wait in the
meeting area or follow yeah I mean we
have to do the test we can't just wait
in
the done
with think I do think Marissa is a
little bitsa you and me Let's Stay
Together or not we're staying together
now I'll actually tag along with you
guys if that's okay just to see if I
Wason is there wait then maybe you twoo
are the imposters no I'm my
Tas I kill me it is kind of scary oh my
God I didn't kill you when you were
around yeah what the he oh you two
didn't kill each other because you're
both oh my
God on the blue women yeah let's just
all stay together and we'll see what the
blue women do oh my God we follow IR
does anyone else have
no no I'm all done oh yeah we should
follow Iris we should pressure her
follow do that totally follow me Iris
yeah nice hey who voted for me
me wait am I getting okay okay good you
better you little you keep my
please don't kill me
okay
I to oh I have to go like this I see oh
oh There ah I but now it's
tough that's not my fault though all
right how can we help how can we help
sabotage to help
[Music]
oh
who was
it excuse me I it was desk what who was
the imp imp though Iris I wonder who was
it was
[Music]
Iris doing so good you put us on the
spot know what I'm
doing I'm sorry I was suspicious of you
fa I'm sorry I was suspicious of you
wait F why didn't you kill me for long I
wanted to keep someone on my
side and because crony was susing Faun
in the beginning I was like maybe I
should keep her on my side and kill cron
[Music]
instead like I I saw that Iris was uh
going into the same room as uh narissa
was so I was kind of waiting outside the
room to see I saw I saw I was like oh no
I think she sus I was trying to kill I
was trying to kill you actually um I
when you were inside the lab I I was
following you and I was going to kill
you I youing weirdly and you were like
running away and then Marissa comes in
right away like oh never mind I can't
kill
you well a little bit
too
um there's only there's only me
[Music]
that's yeah I can't I can't believe you
suspected
me I
panicking
pcking all well it ends well hopefully
when we're together alone in the moldes
nothing I won't kill
you don't found me in the ocean please
I'm missing Molly Molly mly Molly oh
sorry I was stuck join us let me just
I'm here sorry join us um I don't want
to like you know make any hard rules
because you know you just kill whoever
is conveniently there but please do not
kill am right away next
[Music]
round being a
ghost no no no we need our we need our
space on out to do her job yeah kill me
first I love being the
ghost no pressure yeah no
pressure okay we complete I changed one
thing I changed that the votes uh you
can't see who
voted hard for me to try to vote
someone let's
go see you later
bye
wait the coate task task task task task
task what is the task there is a task oh
uh that's a
Prett pretty cute done okay let's find
for tasks tab oh if we go to the what
the mar then why was Callie some by
saying do they have exes on them why why
I'm scared of
NOA let's go oh it's pretty here okay
fishing oh I like this fish fish fish
big fish I got it has lots of eyes
pretty eyes four eyes but not wearing
glasses fish fish fish kind of like a
banana fish oh it's a big
one no the fish
no wait I have to cook the fish I'm
really scared a wait if Nissa comes here
then it should be good fish fish fish oh
10 seconds I cooking cooking M I want
the one on the on the left okay the big
one that's mine of course you want that
one oh it's done I have to flip it not
quite done M you can have the middle one
I think that's the second most the most
delicious one
what wait do I have them the
burning thought you know that's oh
that's not our body
no hello oh for moment I thought you
were dead
again oh no
no
well hope is dead I just saw her alive
like less than 30 seconds ago it must
have just happened I just found it in
the meeting room but I was up in the
drop ship if you look at the map and
then I went down and I found her body
there and bi was up there and F was up
there and people look like she came from
down below so I'm a little sus austral
you because I knew no one would kill you
so I thought it'd be safer with
you story F was following the both of us
though so I'm kind of s of F I was just
making sure no funny business was going
on who was around I saw Iris alive like
less than 30 seconds before she was
found dead like I it felt like like 10
seconds before so I'm I'm like What's
Happening that was a really fast I only
passed by in that area it was like bioo
and fauna and that's it I think in that
area specifically I like coming from
that
direction I saw I know for storage room
and then I was using the
zipline and like wasn't taking the zip
line up with me
what oh well people would you like to
defend yourself um I was following Amit
because I no one was going to kill Amy
so I thought Amy was the safest bed but
Amy saw you didn't she not following her
but coming from a different direction no
I was following this entire time
you the was running away from you so I
didn't always see you well I was
following you the entire do you want to
kill her why you is her cute this is a
k t I've done one task so far it was
asteroids I haven't done the rest
because asteroids I was following yeah
the asteroids the video game didn't you
do asteroids in the last one to yeah I
have what is the asteroids one
like straight commun I mean I will
do are we going to skip or B boo out I
feel like she's using her cute way
really the last time too I don't want to
die
again by the way Iris I don't know if
you know but you mut oh it's because
she's dead oh never
mind she is dead I just wanted to make
sure she joins the conversation you
[Music]
know if I die is or F sus one of them
out if I
go byebye
people
are I didn't even vote for her I voted I
just
skipped I didn't vote for you people it
wasn't me oh thank you I just like
saying byebye that's awesome what you
mean byebye people byee we skipped it we
skipped it
bye well I think we know that Nissa is
okay right I don't
know is burning her face is burning
that's why I'm running I am running
rning oh it's the wrong oh okaya oh wait
here with Nissa I think she's safe I
trust Nissa this time we'll find
out okay we're not going to die now I
think we're safe what are we
doing what are we
doing
mushrooms mushrooms
what are we waiting
for that's what we Wai rist on no race
this on I watched her
kill oh
[Music]
I knew
it dead I'm so confused we waiting for
May sh maybe that's a
sh no that makes it so much worse I went
I know it's not bi boo because I went
down because I saw bi boo pass us we
were both waiting to get into the
kitchen because last round Fu Moko and I
were frying fish together right so as I
was waiting I went to get beo cuz I was
like Advent together strong and then
when I came back it was right in front
of the kitchen it was right in front of
the kitchen where is where the death
just happened and I saw someone running
up to the Splash Zone so where was
everybody and don't lie I Splash wa you
found which which of the two bodies did
I don't I don't know where I don't know
where
it then I have something add I was just
up at the very top of the
communications and there was crony and
there was fauna first there was fauna
and me and everything was cool then
crony joined I left and now fauna is
dead okay can you confirm this crony um
after I was uh doing the ladder task I
went down to the zipline again after
that was done so I didn't really see you
saw Kiara up there yeah I saw Kiara and
f up there and then after I was done
with the ladder I went down the zip line
and I couldn't see anything else aside
from that maybe someone vent I'm not
really sure cuz it's kind of a short
time maybe you vented who
killed I mean I
know I know I my alibi really quick and
I saw bi Boo and we were alone and she
didn't come after me or anything but I
was in the Splash Zone in the beginning
I collected shells and then I left okay
where where were you though at the time
of the murder got it just I reported it
immediately and I saw bio and she didn't
hurt me and then I went back to storage
okay and then crony fa and kiata were
over in Communications yeah so Watson
where were you I was at the
laboratory I I am SS of am because Iris
was around
me on me yeah I am too and now so now
I'm s it seems trying to someone off no
cuz the last the last murder the
everyone who was present we know that it
was in FA now and obviously iris is dead
so it's only you were bio but I know
where bi was at time of the murder
forgetting that the first round I
reported the body and both bio and fer
were with me and none of them said that
they B even said that she was following
me the whole time but she didn't see me
kill anyone huh h CR trust me
me I trust you I
trust really
quiet self
reported no okay I don't know Kar is
really suspicious sorry I angel
hope okay uh can I I can do my tasks
right uh I guess I can't eat fish
fish
why cuz it burnt is that why oh is this
n rac's fish now maybe it's the RAC fish
okay what was that
sound oh I don't think we can really I
don't have a physical body anymore but
sure it's pretty
nice
okay they Che for us did you hear them
but we're dead we're dead that's kind
It's Kind yeah oh that's the drop
ship course if we look at our map we can
see where our tasks are right oh we're
close to them good good good something
here one oh no okay I'll read them out
four 5 9
35 okay yeah
I she sh
[Music]
rans where we going
to oh that's that's
scary what's this spin spin opposite way
oh can you don't see I just I don't know
I see ever I push it
cool
WI
[Music]
why why
why done okay where's the other
task almost done oh my gosh that's scary
it doesn't matter we're dead true things
are so scary if you're dad oh it doesn't
doesn't matter question mark I I think
we should
help okay we have the stuff can we
help can we help
no we're
dead we have to melt down in 40 seconds
well I can't do anything about that it's
stop okay uhoh uhoh
uhoh do our tasks
okay might be but we can still be
helpful what are we
doing maybe is not
good where is our tasks H we have oh we
have one in the drop ship huh drop ship
oh I guess there's big arrows that we
should follow to huh yeah
ah I got
the
huh
no I I wanted to check if anyone and
Rees is dead oh yeah I didn't I was
wondering too I I think Kara is safe
yeah cuz we just did the emergency thing
together yeah and then I'mma joined
right when we
finished both of you guys are I both
were the Oster and you were going to
kill me
no I I really because the first death
was Iris and me and Iris were the ones
that were closest to each other
and yeah that I'm scared I know it's not
kiar because Kiara didn't kill me or
anything I still have threee tasks left
by the way but wait so why did why did
you just call him
meeting because I was wondering if
anyone di because we're about to finish
our tasks and you don't want us to
finish our Tas I was too quiet and I was
scared if anyone was going to die and I
thought like might as well chat and like
Kelly what were you doing I went down to
mushrooms mhm and what's the last task
you did the Sorting the mushrooms into
the jars and the crystals
okay ask me any questions you want but
if you talk out too so
question what's the last task you
did um I don't remember I was in the I
almost sent it I can't have chat I can't
even um I know this sounds supicious
I'm I'm going to vote for a i think yeah
you're the Imposter you're just you
called the Mee him because we're so
close to finishing our tasks that you're
scared I real I'm scared of dying was
my I mean I saw cie and she didn't kill
me I was running away from you guys your
arm cuz I thought it was my arm arm why
you cring your
arm I'm resing my hand there guys if you
guys vote for me you're wrong just so
you know that's
s I'm gonna vote for Kelly
[Music]
K I saw you I saw kiar and bi together
and you guys didn't die so unless you're
both the
impostor no we're not uhhuh that's
exactly what an imposter would
say well well if there if there was two
imposters alive we would lose by now so
there's only one oh okay was
using waet it crony sire we got crony
sire and
now I don't know I don't know okay got
it I think we just Skip and continue
doing our tasks unless you guys are if I
was the Imposter i' try to vote one of
you guys out right now and then I'd
probably
win I'm going to skip you guys are wrong
regret your
decision I'll miss you yeah
right is
it do this we got to do to the drop ship
drop
ship that's a part no
[Music]
what oh garbage
garbage do a laugh R is okay not not
this it's not this it's not
this
[Music]
let's
G it
was whacky it wasn't me
[Music]
God that was
wild quiet again that's her tell she was
quiet oh you turned into fun I see see
we thought Kelly some was quiet too but
you know I thought maybe I'm so sorry
how do I ever redeem myself to you it's
too late it's too late
I can't even believe me yeah
I my I'm not a real
[Music]
amling I tried to protect her and now
I'm the one that killed
her yeah I can't trust P I'm sorry I
can't believe I got imposter twice why
so good at lying why is everyone so good
at lying
Japanese Among
[Music]
Us
practice I warned you guys and you
didn't listen to
me damn it and I still didn't get
impostor single time
man maybe next time we still got more
time
right there's a little more time then
let's go next
round
oh I saw I saw by the way the ghosts uh
were going in their own channel did you
have fun
yes recommend it it was fun I don't know
why crony was probably too guilty
[Laughter]
to oh wait there's a dead voice I didn't
even
know voice CH I was like why isn't she
joining I was like probably because she
feels guilty oh no I don't feel guilty
at
allty at all
you don't feel any shame I thinky just
randomly get voted off too cuz I don't
remember like
everybody maybe
next I told you to believe me see oh it
was actually good what I did thank God
she was right you were so right easy way
to tell easy one to tell if if Callie is
imposter she's quiet when she's imposter
yeah now now we know impost byebye bye
you are the Imp
wait wait did we just hear a missa you
are
the that's just Senpai being silly that
would make sense Senai is pretty silly
why would she say that though if she
wasn't that's a thing that we' say by
accident is better than that
yeah emergency
meeting I tried to hide behind
garbage oh that's it okay oh we did it
together oh we're going to R some
marshmallow that's what kie was talking
about I thought she was just being
silly he's Among
Us okay no
no can we do it again can we do it again
no I can't do it again
[Music]
not I'm going to play video games the
world might die but it's okay it's
okay she wants to do the Tas to maybe
this is our game stay away yeah our game
I'm good at it are we yes 19 20 20 good
done
if we look at the map we can see the
time oh there's something
here there's a lot of a lot of people
around why do you can't get was that
what I needed is that it is it done are
we over what am I supposed to do go down
look at the tasks I feel like somebody
is chasing me jump jump on it I did
okay keep moving I'm trying but go down
there's a task over there I'm trying to
get to it you can go around you oh
mushroom
mushroom I didn't even see I didn't even
see I didn't even really see I didn't
see I thought was chasing me did I see
no no no no it wasn't me I was where
were you where were you when you pressed
it
who pressed it I I pressed
it my God I was so in my T my God I went
up to the top right the communication
and I was just Tangen thing and doing a
task and suddenly I see a dead body but
on the same spot I think I saw at least
one more person maybe another maybe two
people I think so Kiara Iris fuo and
then I just came into the room and I saw
Callie outside we just destroyed the
musroom body I just the moment went up
the ladder all of a sudden we went I was
also in Communications we went the line
with but almost the same time and then I
was trying to go in the way to the
mushroom door but I got rid of the
mushrooms
but uh maybe it's you killed by accident
maybe it's just am by being
silly uhhuh wait
what wait I'm me you were there right
when I reported right no I I just walked
into the room like after cie she was
already in there like alive and you guys
were all doing doing the power thing or
whatever and I was also starting to do
the power thing putting in the code but
then you guys finished it and then
somebody reported Call's body so I
didn't even see it wait so you're saying
besides me there was cie and
you there were like two other people
inside the
[Music]
communications the other side the
mushroom wall but I don't know yeah I
just went up the
ladder
yeah that's why there was one other
person
there she the Imposter saw purple yeah
purple see what we no the purple's beo I
we do have something to report
yeah we
heard are
and we were thinking maybe this am being
Sil thing that we we would do that but
now she was saying it to someone else
and now Amai is trying to can we have
someone who hasn't talked talk please me
me me yes so um I was at communications
I saw a bunch of people there and I was
trying to like uh do my task and like I
was still on the task when it happened
so I didn't really see anything oh so
you were also in Communications mm
okay wait you were there even now when
when I reported you were still
there um yeah yeah oh so you were one of
the other people I saw then but I wasn't
sure who am I seeing oh I voted for
what I remember this I will remember
this but
oh doing it as a
joke we were in
[Music]
uhoh it's my Senai it's my Senpai for
sure it's am my S it has to be am okay
let's do our
task yeah it's am by hi
hi watch out watch out watch out
there what I should we go in the other
let's go in the ghost chat I don't is
this GH are we the first ghost
what what wait wait
[Laughter]
what a crowd of people communication
wait
did
oh
gosh yeah up w see The Quiet Ones it's
always the quiet ones I knew hasn't said
anything last
round we're both
innocent susing am right because of her
statement but in the
end I said that on
purpose yeah
thought just being silly
h of vote for
[Music]
Fu I'm sorry oh my God this is what
happened okay next we we got to go
[Music]
next don't give it to the blue people
okay oh
no I don't know what I'm
doing well first we got to get somebody
on their own I ran into the wall I need
my task this thing whatever it is
um I don't know if this is the best
place to kill somebody let's go up
there let's kill cie kill death kill
death right I'm getting my task what is
this oh 2 4819 quickly quickly quickly
819 we did it no 0 five 09 581 wait 09
somebody's here8 1 done is that does
this do ra oh I don't know no M no
should I get do it do it do
it okay how do we else go out yes V
here where am I where am
I I I ran up because of the
communications thing was down and she
was right there in Communications in
front of the the thingy anyone else
I was at the other I
was I was down by the dock I was in the
labs me um oh yeah I just met crony in
the labs
yeah Iris and I are doing the other
cast didn't kill each other I think
we're
safe what
narissa were you I was down by the dock
I I figured that you probably all were
going there and I wanted to keep doing
my tasks so I just went down and I was
doing a sand castle and then I was
checking since yeah don't the um I
passed I passed the T yeah they
disappear but if you pass them you can
still do them oh okay yeah I was
checking manually okay or if you just
still like remember where they were
before it went down
yeahor
reactor what task you doing at the re
we're doing our task we're just trying
to
find doesn't want to use the map I don't
like the map I like finding the little
yellow mark on the the screen it's more
fun
marshmallow emphasizing in the
yellow what actually haven't done that
yet is so cute it's a little Among Us
uhsh we did that the
last
yeah so inconclusive but what task were
you
doing who yeah the marshmallows are
nowhere near the
Rea that was that was before yeah but
what were you doing today huh we doing a
bunch of in the Rea what what were you
doing what were you doing in the reactor
yeah what were you doing in the reactor
kind of to
I for now I'll give you guys the benefit
of the doubt thank you please don't kill
us
again
for get to play No
Bully no bu
bu you almost threw us under the there I
had the marshmallow oh we did that last
I was say we did the
marshmallow this it was no and we
already said reactive R you to say we
said
reactive don't be too quiet I'm say
something say something don't be too
quiet oh you're too quiet say
something tell this is what happens when
you tell us
to but we go make so we keep up the cuz
every we kind of like oh get her get
her I don't know what to
do I don't know what to do I don't
know okay don't step up it doesn't do
anything we can't
kill I'm going up here where are we I'm
going to do the the I'm not killing here
there's two what task can I say I'm
doing here I don't know what uh uh go
find the fish task where go back there
go back there what we're familiar with
those tasks I don't know these tasks
this go ride it ride ride get
her I don't know if this is a task get
one second and there's a task here I did
thisas I did this task I'm doing the
communications the spinny one okay I'm
doing the spinny one okay get Thea now
that's the next
task what
is she pulling her away yeah is she
don't stay here M we were here last time
please if we stay here it's going to be
suspicious I looking
foras I am looking for oh I am looking
for tasks what is going if somebody
walks by you got to kill them okay CR
Senai what's in here the greenhouse
somebody
oh
we're doing the water and can in the
greenhous it
wasar killed don't believe her did you
see I I saw people kill am I am medic I
am medic I can see people's vital yeah
and I can see you kill am is that how it
works I am I am magic I can see people's
vital I have three battery charges every
round to see how many people are alive
this is the first time I have I
saw we should
say's it's hard for me because I had
just I had just seen biu and but I did
not see kiata and I was going down and
she didn't follow me so she might have
realized she was alone with a but uh
bioo also when she killed me
self-reported and then immediately this
is literally the first time I've got
this scientist and I have this is the
first time I played it so how would I
know that I have three charges of
scientist to check
V where is the body time in a while all
the body is up the stairs
communication I
sawara you wasn't you probably just
looked up some guide about those no I
didn't this is the first time I have
whatever scientist whatever I can check
people's well I was I was so often alone
with others and I didn't kill them so
why would I you know can somebody vouch
for me cuz I think I was Al alone
together with a lot of people
come
on I was alone with for a while but I
was not alone with Kiara yeah I saw Kara
for like a split second I'm
sorry s times alone and I saw crony
several times I think alone and I saw
narissa like maybe one or two times
alone yeah it felt like um either Kiara
or fauna was going to kill me cuz like
they were just kind of walking around so
I stuck around one of them then to make
sure I didn't get killed um it would
kind of check out if Kiara was the
instant I saw the kill I believe I
believe wow okay
who's goodbye forever thanks forever uh
what was it I I love you or I'm than
you how many do I need to
[Music]
kill you guys voting me me out but I
guess you'll you'll no you're running
down the
clock it's so sad I I was always with
you
guys love
[Applause]
you
goodby I will go up like a phoenix and I
will rise like a
phoenix good luck guys good luck guys I
what am I doing
killing do I have fake tasks to do cuz
that would be handy right like a fake
task map yeah is that what these are the
yellow marks can
we is that what those are yellow kill no
I hover the button over the kill and
when I tell you to kill you kill
K I'm your older sister listen to me
there
I'm doing a spinning task until someone
gets here and then I'll kill them what
if nobody ever comes here the tasks are
done are the tasks almost done I don't
know got to go fast we got to go fast
quick quick quick I'm going I'm going
I'm going they're going to finish the
task if we don't hurry
up where are they where are
they come close to us I'm going to fix
no no no no that's not a task that's a
bad task get NOA get where
she you missed the opportunity we just
need to kill okay where I guess I guess
I only have that chance H yeah one
chance quickly where are you where are
you I doing my
best what was
that not the
time not the
time I'm worried I'm doing my best I'm
going to I'm going
to what are we doing right now you're
running I'm trying to think of a plan to
save when they start accusing me of
stuff we're in the greenhouse okay doing
the flower task we didn't say that last
time right we didn't so we can still use
it okay right oh go who's around us no
one's around us this this is something
weird somebody I need to kill
someone I'm
thirsty for
death are
[Music]
you
lonely somebody I blood where are
M can you run faster I am
trying where are you where are you we're
alone for too long that's not I'm tell
you to fix this okay okay somebody some
oh
no well where were
we Green
House hello the Emer oh no I I CU I I I
believe it's F what what because like
when we were going to when comms were
down we were going up I see I see like
um many of us were going up I think it
was like I think I saw fa beu
um TR F out I don't know where going and
we were all going up to comms but then I
see F coming down from comms ignoring
the fact that comms you have to do the
bottom one first we're just trying to do
the tasks and you I thought everybody
else is going to do to if you were at
the top you would do the top one but
we're just counting on you we're
focusing on our task yeah you can't see
the tasks on the map when comms are down
yeah you see yeah you can but if you
walk around you can find
them that's what we did last time
too earlier why I
deed every talking at once and I can't
hear
anything that's how we play a without
the M we depend on you did this time
what's what's a task you did what's the
task
theen why' you you you come came back
down from comms even though comms is
sabotaged all the way back down to the
greenhouse the greenhouse is
pretty green Greenhouse is
pretty you got a
[Laughter]
r who are the cutest
puppies are
[Music]
wow Liars look at the little
[Laughter]
Li don't be like Ave mistake byebye not
like by goodbye byebye come on F Go cast
your
boat yeah don't don't um delay your
death it's yeah it's inevitable it's
time to
go byebye
[Applause]
puppies
we're good at this we're so good at
this really Gooding out
iris from the reactor too even the last
round when when we almost voted them out
cuz they didn't know what they were
doing
Rea that made me 80% sure and then I saw
them going down from P so oh
yeah what we crew we'll do the
exact
yes I'm so sorry it's
okay you were just trying to survive I
understand I think out of this whole
group of people me and foku are like the
worst Liars so was a good
combination I was doing my B you Bast my
b so bad oh it's hard to
lie M makes me laugh and I love to you
see see I I had the good the good life
you know I did the marshmallows and then
she goes oh we did that last
time and being
a oh my god well at least I finally got
imposter do we don't want to do one more
round
yeah hide and SE for the last game CH
the hide andek hide andek hide
andek hide andek sounds fun it's like
hideand-seek like how you'd really hide
and
seek for hide and seek wasn't there an
actual setting for hide and seek though
yeah there there is there is Compu uh
you might have to make a new
room um if you can't change it in the
settings um on the computer yeah then
you might have to make a new room is
it yeah no I don't think you can change
it
here okay then I'll make a new
one it's kind of like it's pretty much
like playing tag
cute um any preferred
map let's do the original the OG yeah
yeah yeah okay yi
yi
nice I'll send you the link in the group
the code in the
group okay there you this one's chaotic
but really funny thank you never done it
before oh it's fine and it's a short
game too
so let's go
perfect man this scary this one this is
like the only time I actually want to be
impos hide and
seek I never want to be impost ever
again for
this we don't have to mute for this oh
no I don't think so right you
just we could if you accident I guess we
can mute if we're
done uh we don't have to
right
[Music]
not
wait we can we can hide in V oh is there
only
one is this
like we better
hide we can
really
slow we have three minutes to hide
left 3 minutes to hide she's in the med
Bay oh gosh over
to
she wait
what oh
[Music]
[Applause]
man everybody's clumping
together look look
out where is she right now where' she go
oh my
[Music]
[Applause]
God is
that wait how does this
work I need name tags do your best CR
hear the music come close to you when
she's close by
that's crony where's
crony
oh that's fun that's so quick too that
was so another w
w for both the impostor and the the the
the crew
mates can we increase the speed for both
crew mates yeah I want to but also I I
uh I think I have to make a new Lobby
because I don't think I can change the
amount of uh secr
oh there's only one
sneaker yeah it's fine to leave it at
one we just need the speed up so we're
all running really
fast okay
Max let's go this is how it should
[Music]
Beez yumy let's
go to go
that I think so
oh I'm going to be Unleashed for
my why are there okay oh God where do I
go
don't do your task task task God I don't
see them I see tasks but I don't know
what I really want to finish those
sorry it's all
good
why do I
have I'm scar I'm scared I'm scared I'm
scared I hear I hear the base we got to
win we got to win this I can't find you
guys what heck everyone oh it's so
[Music]
fast task task taskas the
task quickly not
I'm not even near
[Laughter]
[Music]
you terrifying screams
here
[Music]
louder going louder and louder yeah it's
so chaotic going to get in
trouble the moment you hear the guitar
IFI you're
like so
sweaty God my eyes are
[Music]
spinning who's who's you're going to be
even faster in the final round I'm alive
okay should I
do
chicken get one more
minute don't because it's going to show
your
location it shows do you guys know where
location it shows location there's a
there's a red dot uh that indicates
where the crew I have
it I should have bodies I see dead
bodies I see dead
[Music]
people does she see me from map or
when she gets
[Music]
closer
amazing I just didn't really see her on
the screen that often so thank God
everybody was
so
[Music]
that was close teleporting across the
map could even one
more
[Music]
more nothing is scary who is it this
time let's go who is
[Music]
it have fun r r
does doing tasks do anything like we
could get an early Tas then if we do if
we finish them all yeah we could get
lucky and proactive with the hide it's
hide and seek you got to hide not
not why can't I oh
no got to go got to go got to go I was
about to get the thing I'm
sorry
was on you guys on you guys damn
it I I do wonder if doing tasks is even
worth it I know
righty
bait you ran past you R
past
so so fast
going going to the cafeteria wait can
we might be a little
unfair okay I felt that was the wrong
direction okay let's do our
task should we I'm too scared to move
around whenever I do task
[Music]
is 4K
only has only three
left what is the danger meter ah come on
guys one more one more
minute good hiding spot
she very good Pace
oh 30 30
seconds keep on going keep on
going keep going keep going really good
hiding spot yeah that
[Music]
was so L all
the oh no
[Music]
whoops
fast is there
overtime it's so fast I
[Music]
can't pre oh
man go
go 30 seconds do
[Music]
seconds Phoenix getting to
her don't get suckle the
walls you have 10
seconds you can do
[Applause]
[Music]
it my she won't get you oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
no seconds
[Laughter]
wasit was amazing
the clest
ever time at the end of the day really
slippery yeah really
slippery oh my God that was
exciting exting I'm I'm pretty exhausted
from that but we can do another one if
you want I'm down for one
more
actually you know wait wait oh no before
Oh I want to I want
to so fast
yeah oh good okay never
[Music]
mind how do you how do you kill people
the whole time um there's a kill button
so don't you worry okay oh my God no way
I don't want to be here no the she has
awaken she has awakened
I'm coming for you nobody's using my
hiding spot
right don't use my hiding
spot that no that wasn't your hiding
spot that a rampage there were two
people there I only saw one
person
overl does the music get louder for me
too I feel like it does I know it gets
louder oh when you're near someone
really even for
imposter you little get out of
there get out of there you little
oh my gosh what's going
[Music]
onary
where are
they
[Music]
hiding H oh no that's okay that's the
stack I still got time I still got
time I saw someone where is
she that hiding
spot oh I again
[Music]
stop being
so oh my God that was no no I haven't
found anyone in my CES you passed by
[Music]
somebody someone's here no oh
where are
you hello I'm all
alone no hints no help oh what was that
there was some button popping up there
the use button
[Music]
yes
I didn't even see you that's lame what
the
he see you I saw you that's all that
matters
no oh
no oh one more one more more
run no no no no minute still one more
minute they're literally right there
run you can throw just run just run just
run
[Music]
[Applause]
run wow
doie doie we doing the
[Music]
bestes mama M that was wow was fun that
was fun that was merry I'm too excited
to say anything so let's start with the
with the goodbyes from anybody but me um
I'm it please no yeah this is really fun
I'm glad we could get together and have
like a little Christmas Among Us
celebration the perfect holiday SE
holiday game right
yeah just Redwood toy and some blood
when I think of Christmas I think of
Among Us viol and
ornaments it's pretty festive the colors
this makes me want to play this makes me
want to play project winter
yeah F yeah I know
[Music]
C wow thank you I'm sorry you died so
of that's okay it's still fun call what
about you you had some good good kills
today it was nice getting to dust off
the old Scythe for once and get back in
the game for a little bit that was
nice yeah I had a great time with
everybody here everybody here is fun to
talk to fun to argue with in a fun way
really in a fun way yeah in a fun
way about it we should argue more often
yeah let's do
it no no I can't maybe not yeah no we
just stay titty but within among us we
can argue as much as we want right and
then outside of Among Us
you know we're different people among us
changes us but only what happens in
Among Us among
us all right and please please tell me
about your experience today science
Rules science science what science
science science Rules and statement
thanks
great interesting interesting I don't
quite understand but I agree oh I don't
think Kiara knows about Bill it's all
right don't worry about
it don't worry about
it'll okay IR Mrs Mrs Santa Claus Mrs
Chris yes yeah know this was fun I'm
glad I was able to Li better this time
yeah good liing need to learn
from never suspect yeah everyone
everyone was great I love how bad F was
at
L tell their first time you can tell
first time I
was the same me when
I wor was always like that it's great I
love it
thank you very much that was fun they
were so lucky cuz like in that one round
they were about to be voted off and I
thought I was going to be alone but then
somehow somehow they survived they
survive we couldn't sa you
C no it's okay we couldn't save each
other even if we wanted
to yeah well thank you Iris and then
people what about you I was happy to be
able to kill people I wish I was able to
kill more people but I will satisfied
with the amount of people I was able to
kill this time that's the spirit thank
you for your service that's the spirit
that's the Christmas spirit let's go
let's
go it
was J again I'm so sorry be it's
okay what stays in Among Us stays Among
Us don't worry
exactly
[Music]
well we Ln a lot of things today we're
really good at lying right yeah that was
it that was the wi yes yeah and uh we
have fun we we yelled a bit we screamed
a bit and we did a lot of
lying yeah but most importantly we had
[Music]
fun true let's
play yeah when I saw I was imposter with
F I knew I knew that you weren't going
to be good at
lying we have to do
our
we yeah it's all good it's
funny I had so much fun thank you so
much for putting it together kiaha
I
I'm sad I had to be the impostor I don't
like it brings me no
joy murdering me what you mean no oh but
you were so good though you were good at
it with over right away me yeah you guys
are Mur blue women women are scar wom
blue
women say it it's the blue people the
the avatars I always say it
mhm yes yeah thank you you're welcome
I'm glad you had a good time let's
continue this in the mes yeah
peacefully the other Blue Woman
quason yeah it was a lot of fun I'm kind
of surprised that I actually got
impostor twice uh because I never get
imposter yeah I never get these R let's
go yeah and thank you for organizing it
it was a lot of
fun I love among
us I guess you know there was all sorts
of drama but like we said earlier what
happens Among Us stays Among
Us wow
beautiful well said Thank You
Quon well yeah that's pretty much it um
but Christmas is not over yet I think
there's still members that have like
special streams upcoming so check him
out everybody and I just want to make
one quick announcement about the whole
Ian Advent calendar some people may
already know but the last day the 25th
day will be delayed a little bit so uh a
few days uh the it's out of my hands out
of my power now but please check back on
it next week we'll all tweet about it
when it is finally up uh so stay tuned
stay excited and thank you for spending
Christmas with
us viewers I say to you viewers thank
you for spending it with us and thank
you to the girls for spending it also
with us thank you for getting together
at this
time thank you Merry Christmas
[Music]
everyone we're going to stick around
okay byebye
byebye
byby thank
you I Among Us I I think I really do
think he did very well I think we did
too not just our best we do well right R
what do you think R
is that was wild it was
wild do
dot dot dot no wins though did we lose
every
time I don't know I just feel like I won
every round in my heart it was fun it
was fun so we R in the end yeah
ba we did amazing thank you thank
[Music]
you is scary well you know we picked to
be imposter for a reason when I say kill
kill them
okay you know we have to put in some
good effort right I guess yeah you only
get one chance to chill two two two
kill two you only get one chance to
chill
RS it's been a very very fun day today
tomorrow it's Christmas Eve and you know
we have something special we have D Dad
we're going to be spending Christmas
with
you are you
right well we have something special
plan so we hope that you'll be there
with us live but if your familyes AR
know oh no this is my ran then please
please go with your spend time with them
but if you can even just for a
moment please doing
okay and then for the numbers of our
doggy P we have a special to be
continued afterwards too so don't forget
okay but I more importantly our
friends you know what today means
right the day before Christmas
Eve us it today we announce something
else
why the last schedule of the
year now I don't want to alarm you we
going have some fun it's
alarming maybe a bit
alarming so you wanted to to talk about
it a
bit okay are you ready I don't know if
you're ready but try to ready
okay
deep
breath okay I'm going to do
this okay three two
one on last schedule of the
Year take maybe a bit a closer look
we'll post it later
but what is that what is that Monday
it's the only time of the year where the
sea
and it's the Sea episode of L morning
Rin so we're going to have a very
special Christmas
day all
together I'm done we kind of have a bit
of a special present for you do you
think that we wouldn't have a present
for you ran so we thought we give it to
you on Christmas
morning and that present is a brand new
song cover of a song that we really love
called White
Love by speed be you know it's a famous
song we hope you look forward to it we
really really did our best and a lot of
effort it's a little bit of a different
form thiso
right and then afterward thank you so
much R for giving us your very precious
special Christmas Memories we're going
to all talk about our best Christmas
memor Coy Christmas evening together
yeah so we hope you'll join us around
the fireplace for a nice cozy Christmas
Day evening yeah
at Tuesday you know we we we're going to
be a little bit busy so we thought you
know Tuesday we can kind of take it a
little bit easy and just chat all
together read some super
chats and then in the evening we have
our white love after party we talk all
to talk about feelings what it was like
recording it what what we like the best
about it the the meaning of the song you
know those kind of lot to talk about but
the next morning or not really the
morning
uh just after midnight on Wednesday
early morning we're going to be watching
SAS ninja
[Music]
boy
we're going to be watching a show called
s a live broadcast and it is at the end
of every year in Japan but we're going
to be watching it live this year live um
on a Japanese service it might be a
little bit
trick overseas ring what but it's
something that horrible really really
enjoy we get very pumped up for it we
are hoping that maybe it this some
Japanese Roans that wanted to watch it
then we could watch it all together cuz
we're going to watch it anyway maybe and
we more fun together yeah we get so
pumped
[Music]
up let's
okay we have the last H wining of the
Year followed by
white we're going to continue continue
the visual Marvel White Album a game
that we both really really like and the
rough f are You' kind of decided um some
interesting choices for us uh last time
things you know our our girlfriend Yuki
she really really loves us and now she's
become a big famous Idol and her Senpai
Dina's kind of like seems to be kind of
interested in us in a suspicious way uh
she invited us on a date and the rans
you said yes let's go on that date I
know Yuki just saw us but we also saw
her having a out on a with the produ S
what's that about suspicious imp I TR I
trust you I trust you but we'll see how
how everything goes things can still be
fixed
[Music]
right you wanted to watch a silly
Christmas movie R so I chose a silly
Christmas movie chose one of those
Christmas movies after school days can
watch a silly Christmas movie it's it's
a bit after Christmas but we'll still be
in the Christmas sper
okay yeah and this one called excited
the princess switch Yeah why' you pick
this one it look cute that's why it look
cute yeah it's not going to it's nothing
like school days right probably not
nothing like Sask probably not I don't
think there's any stuff to to H and say
how oh yeah to jump
in clear Domin
completely
[Music]
dominated and then in the evening we're
going to be having specialday te party
with
Callie her Channel I'm really excited
enjoy some te warm cozy times it's going
to be fun and then I'm
Friday I think things are going to be a
little different there a
a I have to find out what that is and
then we meet up with all of again for a
very special year and WRA up time this
time we just be chatting withan talking
about the year how things went you know
our feelings and excitement for the new
year those kind of things and then
Saturday finally we'll get some good
Mario Kart 8 Deluxe practice because
well we need
it
again rest on
Saturday because Sunday Sunday Sunday
wow it's start very early
hi know there
[Music]
a the end of the
yearing we've been invited to be part of
the to show
2023 what is a to
to is like a collection of all the best
Clips some clips that maybe you
submitted uh some other categories
favorite moments of the Year best
moments of the year and will'll be there
along with some JP somebody looking all
over the best moment the best of the
best yeah so please join us that will be
on the official Whole Life channel
official Channel our channel channel uh
we would have written it onto this
schedule but there was no space
whoops but that's okay because after
that we're going to be doing a and
retrospec
[Music]
we're going to be doing uh very very
early in the morning we're going to be
doing a year and retrospect talk but it
will be sort of similar probably to what
we talk with a but this time it will be
in Japanese
japanes
of course we'll have English as well do
our best we'll do our best but sometimes
we get carried away H yeah it's a
learning process and then after that
we're going to be watching the Hol life
countdown all together on our Channel
rans it might be a little bit early but
we hope that you'll be there I'm super
excited to see what our Senai are doing
can watch all together
too but well will be in the new year but
we're still not there yet we're still
not there with the slow pokes huh yeah
but that's okay because that means we
still have a lot of partying to do a lot
of partying and we're going to be
starting out our New Year's party with
Mario Kart 8 Deluxe with you we'll play
all together hopefully we can get better
with your help watch out we're going to
beat you going to beat you yeah you
better not drive right past us you
better not stop at the Finish Line
either
okay and then well I don't know if you
can see it that well oh maybe
can't covered up by me a little bit
there we have a rock party to end the
year with and this time it's on
archives New Year's
countown Rock and Roll
Party intense
we'll be spending the very last moment
of 2023 with you the very first moment
as well and is not on the schedule but
there will be a stream directly after
that can't go to bed once it it's
midnight no yeah really morning okay
yeah got it and then there's also
morning but forget about that for next
[Laughter]
schedule it's going to be a really fun
time time this starts at 10 p.m. P 1
a.m. ET 6 a.m.
GMT 3:00 p.m. DST
yes but we will post the big schedule so
you can look at it properly and be able
to use your eyes to see all the
information very shortly so please take
a look at the YouTube Community page or
Twitter for that
okay sounds like I won't get any sleep
I'm sorry B it might be a little bit
rough but you know sleep something that
we can get in the new year new year we
have a full year to do that this year is
almost over we have to stay
awake
right more like fun fun I was going to
say you can't spell rough without fun
but huh four it spells
four are you excited R
is are you
we're going to have a super amazing end
of the year all
together it's going to be amazing it's
going to be fun thank you so much the
end let's say goodbye to 2023 in the
best way possible
together I'm looking forward to it so
much it's going to be amazing that's for
thank you so much we're joining us today
but but don't
forget tomorrow Christmas together with
you
okay we're going to do our best okay
yeah thank you so
much we can't wait for this next
upcoming
week thank you so
much well we'll see you tomorrow on
Christmas evil
King thank you so much
[Music]
byee
e
[Music]