[Music]
T
yeay
What a great sound! Welcome to Arisaba.
Wow!
This building is super cool.
Thank you everyone for your hard work. Wait,
did your seniors build this? Yes, it's all Jor
Ade.  This is so cool that they made it,
and it's a real building,
and it's so real, and there's this building, too,
and there's this weird
zombie thing, and you know, the one that I couldn't hear.  I
just saw it, where is this
? Yes, a dog named Borobulu
has this building. It's from Indonesia. It's amazing.
It's a famous shield. Oh, it's a famous building. Ah, one
after another.
Oh, this is dangerous.  For now, let's
go up to the top.
OK
[Music]
Oh, wow,
that's amazing. Looks beautiful. Apparently, Apo-chan is already inside. I see, I
guess she's been waiting for that. Oh, that's an
amazing jump.  It looks like it's being
used by a lot of buffs who can fly really high
Is this here? And then there's the quiz.
Yes, I wonder if it's Kanade-chan. Why is this
red and white? I know it's red and white.
Eori-senpai's colors are pretty close, but that's
not it.  No, Kokki or something like that
is Indonesia's flag color.Oh
yeah, that's right.My senior was holding it in his hand,
so yeah, yeah, I see.Let's
go in.Yes, I can almost see his name.
Not from there that you can see, but from below.
That's dangerous, so I understand it's from below. It's
dangerous from there. Yes, be
careful, be careful, that's amazing.
What's this? What did you do now? Well,
um.  This is Indonesian magic. It
's amazing. So get off here.
Oh
hello.
[Music]
Maga
Where is Akoba-chan? Oh,
wow, that's it.  It looks like it's
huge and spacious.
Everyone did their best.
[Music]
Eh,
Boi Boi Boi, Me
[Music]
Go, go, OK,
havejustJust
as
[Music]
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, I'll be the director today.
Be Senkyu
[Music]  ]
[Music]
Oh, I'm fine with the briefs here. Oh,
well, today we have 5 mini-games.
First of all, let's hunt for treasure.
But I can't do it yet
[Music]
No, but for now, the rules for Resin
are to look for treasure,
oh, my seniors do it.
[Music] I
'll do it outside of Bobble, not inside Bobble. No, no, yes.
[Music]
Yes, that's all.
Yes.
Yes, I'll do the cashier hunt tomorrow. I
read the rules. Oh yeah, and then there's Hae and Sans. I
just remember the left part
.
Well, for now, I
'll explain it to Japan, thank you very much.Each
pair will be on stage
to show their presence.Yes, this
will take place on a regular basis, so all the
talents will have to give a brief initial introduction in advance.  I need to learn some of the questions.
What the heck? Easy, easy, no problem. No
problem. Oh, no problem. Teams will earn
emeralds based on how well they follow the instructions. Yeah,
yeah.
Oh, I understand. I
'm fine with Japanese. Well, I don't need to explain English, Indonesian, etc.
Anything is fine. Yes,
that's okay. I'm a genius.
Yes, it's no problem. Hey, I'm fine.  I don't have any questions?
Yes, it's okay, it's okay
Genius TE
[Music]
Indonesia, uh, genius, genius, no
, no, no, no,
Tigger,
Eretz,
go Indonesian.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I want to practice hard, I want to do it. I'm following you, so I'm going to do it here. I'm going to stand here and say it's okay.
Stand here, I'm going to cheat.  I brought the paper
soBofyouhavetogo
THthesamecomm Um,
please listen to the same command.Okay
, there are 3 stages.Look at this.  Let's
do it, yes, yes, yes, uh, did you remember the words?
[Music] What, what? Eh, what's up? Do you remember? Kirima [Music]
joh
[Music] I
'll give you the command
startwiththefirst
comok
o  do it after I kada uhm Please
do it after the countdown
Ok Ok
okay then Maju
Saka 3
Towa
Maju
Boro
But is this a sign?
Yes, I
[Music]
Real
G
simonimasu
[Music]
[Music] Let's
turn it again
[Music] Really?
No, no, no, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, just move, don't worry about it, I
want it.
[Music]
Yeah, are you okay?
That's the first command. The keyboard is so weird.
Oh
yeah, yeah, that's the next command. Yes, yes,
please go back to the first place. I see. Yes, yes, that's the beginning.  Is
n't this the first time? Well, I can't do it. The
other spaces are fine.
[Music] That's okay. The
next one is going to be difficult. Please
leave it to me.
Oh, listen to
me.
Hohehe, I tried my best, yes, I tried my best to
get rid of the bugs, but it was originally 2 jumps, 2 jumps,
yay, 3 jumps. Was it
no good?
[Music] Bear, it's
going to be a game like this. Oh, I
get it.
Well, it was 3. I can
go,
oh, and no hints.  [
Music]
Yay,
nice, yay, yay,
and uhm, it's stage 2, right
stage
let's go men
let's go men Okay
Jinko
Luaka Boku
[Music]
Nice,
nice,
nice, yes, let's
do it on Stage 3. Yes, yes, please listen to me.
[Music]
Three
Tsuwa
ga
Omaka
[Music]
Na-chan is right.  I
made a mistake
[Music] Take-
senpai Senpai-senpai
[
Music] [Music]
[Music]
What the heck
Oh, I
can hear
you.
[Music] It's
no good and it's so bad. Do you
have any questions? E
question
is okay. Okay, it's okay.
Yeah, the next mini-game is a bit difficult,
but please follow me.
What, what, next?  Game What's the next game? Hey
,
what, what, here, here,
here, oh, it's so big here.
Hey, what's this? Yes, it's blue. What's this?
Fighting, well, it looks like fighting.
Yeah yeah.
[Music]
Yeah, this is the one that changes colors.
Well, I'll explain the rules.
[Music]
Yeah, this
is a game called Ron.
Yeah, yeah, this is a game called Ron. Yeah, yeah, the team consists of Uruka and Foreman.
Yeah,
yeah, Foreman is a colorful guy.  Go to the floor where the
wool comes out and use the full cutter to cut off the wool from above.
Yes, the Urukatta should cut off the upper wool
so that Perman can step on the sucked hole with the team's color. Yes.
By destroying Yes, you can also drop your opponent's Aman into the world.
[Music] It's going to be
a bit tough without an opponent, so I
'll join in.
[Music] Leave it
to Senpai, leave it to Senpai.  There is one
more color left in the color of the chim.The other chim
wins.Yes, I understand.This is yes.If I
drop it, I lose, right?
Well, this is it.Yes, this is the upper floor.And
And this is lower floor lower floor
Yeah, let's do it. It's
a little hard to explain, but let's do it. Let's
play the game. Either way, let's do
it. Youbetheor [Music]  Oh yeah, here's Shia.
[Music]
Scissors, yeah, yeah, the body should not get blocked, uh,
when it becomes a forman.  It's
okay to bring a block, okay,
but I don't need it right now. I'll
do it here.
[Music] I'm going to
drop Ogo-senpai. It's
no good.
Do your best, Senpai, do your best.
Do your best. I'm sure the sky is the enemy's block.  I can destroy it,
but I feel like my senior was only able to destroy the white one
[Music]
Puur
PUDIA
[Music]
When I asked if it was okay, I realized that
Chim alone is not enough.  That
's
right,
and if
A-chan falls, Temu will
lose, so try not to fall.
[Music]
Why are you holding Ha in both hands?  Let's
do it, let's do it, let's do it,
Austin, let's
do this. Oh, that's right. And Kanade-chan,
Kanade-chan, press F1, press F1, oh
yeah, it's
going to be difficult, nothing.
I ah, we're going to do it here. I see.  Let's pretend it's
not
there Okay Okay Easy
Drop this here It's upside down
[Music]
What
happened to the team
Kill
Fufu
[Music]
What happened?  I won the combo with
[Applause]
[Music] I
want to switch
[Music]
Sui, I'm looking forward to
doing everything I can with
white. Back to white. I
picked up white
than
[Music]
knowyou
Oh, uh, ka and boswitch, okay
have
the
[music] oh,
where
takeAndHoldItLikeme
HoldIt
[music]
inak
It doesn't have to be FF.
Fuswa
[Music]
Scary,
scary, scary
[Music]
Come on, come on
WOWketchupand
mustketchupandmust
YumROUTVS
[Music]
Hey, I fell a little,
yeah,
that's it. Yeah, I'm pretty much dead. Yeah, that
's the course.
Nice
[Music]
Oh from
Bom28for
YELL
20Ithinkwehave24on
[Music]
RedIthinkwe
dothat
Me
AgainnotlikeMaybe
wrongTwoF
[Music]
[Music] It's
a shame
[Music]
Ta
oh
Yes, there are 6 people.
Well, there are 3 people on the top and 3 on the bottom.
Well, actually, there are 6 people on the top, 6 people on the bottom. Oh no, no, that's
right. All of them are 6 on the top, 6 on the bottom, and 6 on there,
so there are 12 people participating.  I see. That seems like a difficult thing to do.
[Music]
Oh,
Chichimasu.
Ah, it
's okay. Have you put the scissors back? Okay, okay.
Next game. I'm
not a kid. I'm a kid. Yeah.  The
kids are here, mallets. Go, that's
amazing.
Please touch the bed.
[Music]
Okay, after this, I'll play
chess with you and
ask you to move your luggage.
[Music] It's
almost there
.
[Music]
Ok,
ok, I can put in a little bit.  Just put it in and do
n't have any weapons.
[Music]
Okay, but before that, let's
try to see if we can use the group voice. Yes, I
know how to use it. I don't know. Did you use it?  Is
n't
it tomorrow? [Music] Yeah, but since I'm talking now, I can download it. It's not like I'm going to download a new one. No, no, no, it's the same thing. Yes, take it. [Music] Is this it? Yes, press B.
Yes.  And ah,
ah, I see.
[Music]
Password
Paa, are you
making one? Hey, there's something in there. What's this, what's this? It's
all VC, this is
it. Oh, here
it is.
Well, you and your
group
also understand
[Music]
I
wantneedknow
somethingLetmeknowi
iwantTRANSforImake
youfeellikenot
sayingsaying
WellIwouldlove
Thank you.Iyaka-
chan's actual performance was with her partner from her team.  I'm
going to join the group chat.
Someone has to create a group,
but maybe Kubo-chan doesn't know how to do it.
Well, anyway, I'll explain the rules of Maze Fight.The
Maze Fight team is
made up of a fighter and a navigator.The
navigator moves up by one size.  The
navigator's job is
to help the fighter defeat the other fighter. The
team with the most fighters will advance to the final round.
Ah, well, the point is, the fighter is important.
If the fighter dies, it
's the end of the team.
But if the navigator dies, well, I
can't help you, but the team
is still okay. Is it okay? Do you
have any questions? It's okay. It's
okay.  Oh
[Music]
Looks like it's going to be tough.
Yeah has
[Music]
helphashelp
the
FIGHTERTHE
[Music]
TEINtheTESAthenavig
Help
[Music]
theDieThe
Aerun
[Music]
NavigatorITU
Navigator
yesanDIABIG
[Music]
It's okay, it's okay
Oh, if you're really in it, uh, bring me a sword.
What is cedar?  If
that fighter survives until the end, it will
add to the overall value of this event, so there is a lot of
pressure.
KJFight
[Music]
jadiIH
Why, why go,
Komokomo Senpai can fight. You're strong. You're strong too. No, Kobo-senpai is
cute, so he's strong and cute. Doesn't that make sense? It's okay, I can
go, yes, I can fight. Tell,
yes, I'm going. Yes,
thank you, yes.
Oh, Kanade-chan, what's going on? This
is the last game, and up until this point, you
can earn those emeralds.  I'm
going to go home with that sword for this battle with emeralds.I see, if I
didn't have that many emeralds, it would be fine.I think the only thing I can do is use those small fry, so
yeah, that's right, so I'll fight with that.Can I
buy weapons that I bought with diamonds?Diamonds, yes.  I'll
buy it. If Deka-chan is
going to be that navigator, then yes, that weapon has already
been decided.
This is the only weapon that
we have. We'll have to work hard if our only senior dies.
If you do
n't have it, then it's okay, okay, Ishii. Yeah, I'll have to get rich first.
Okay, please bring me some erotic stuff.
Just the fighter,
okay. Good luck. I don't have that equipment for Leatherite.
Sorry.  I forgot,
but now this is here, this is
here, please throw it away and
put it on. [Music] There's no place to put it.
Garbage, garbage,
garbage Are you okay now? It's okay,
okay. Well then, Hey-chan,
come on over here.
Oh, this is the navigator's place. Ice cream, and this is food. Bring me some food, and I'm
going to go ahead.
from ah, it's moving below
here
Dako I see, yes, oh,
ah, let's move on to the group chat
[Music]
oh, thank you very much, thank you, please, I'll
leave for now and make an opening. I'll
wait.
[Music]
Bige normal Eori-senpai
here.
Senpai, I can't hear you. Is it
okay to attack from here? I'm a fighter. Boy,
kefa,
ah, ah,
punch
me. I don't know how to fight.
Hey, this boy is going to come in. Let's go let's
go
[music]
Leg go cabo
cabo
[music]
Oh oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
Lego, you can't leave this place,
no, I can't
guess that
from here, I ca
n't go.
Or
Eddie,
oh
no, oh, oh, okay,
okay, please, please, okay, please, yes, oh, I see.
Ori
-Senpupoperi Senior, no, no, it's close, so
yes Yes,
see
Yes, fight fight Go Go Go Go
Chikushi  Let's
go
Maji Marais [Music] Go, you're not doing anything,
you're not doing anything.  That's what Niki-senpai is saying
.
[Applause]
Okay. [Music] I'm here. I
don't have a sword. I don't have a sword.
[Music]
Where is
it?
for
Oh How I'm
Kiki Oh my God yes yes yes
aloo okay yes thank you yes thank you Nono
's food rice rice this food
wait a minute the
food is also here here okay okay
this is fighter I've got food I'm
not okay with roti  Roti roti
is here.It's okay to have a cuppa.Panpan,
one stack, one star,
okay,
star F.Okay,
this is the place to go.
Lady, why don't we go this way
? O pink purpo
oh,
lady
, lady
let's go, F and luck, F1F, wait a minute,
wait a minute, F1, I ca
n't see this
[music]
, no, no F1F,
oh, think, F1.  Ah Okeo
Ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo  It's not
pink yet, no, it's purple, pink,
pink, it's almost pink, it's almost purple
Ai
[Music] It
hurts,
pain, pain, do your best
[Applause] I
see, that's
right Damn F It's difficult Oh, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, I'm falling
[Music]  ] Do
you
want to be a fighter or a navigator?
Navigator, navigator, navigator
is good. Yes, I understand.
Yes, it's difficult. It
's difficult.
[Music]
[Music] Ah, you were good
even though it was a difficult fighter. You were also good at Monkey.
Hey,
PR. I'm
sorry. It's okay.
[Music] You're
cute. It's okay.
[Music]
Oh, let's
put it back here.
Okay, let's play the next game.
[Music]
Okay, Kachan, I've been
aiming for Kachan since she won't come out of the door.
Did you realize that I was aiming for her? This
is called spawn camping. Spawn camping.
Spawn Camping Capin Yeah Wow
Em That was good Oh my goodness
[Music]
thisone
WORKSyougivethemA
WordandTheyjusttry
toasfastaspossible
like one of them
have
[Music] Just
put this back
and it's fine Wakaa
ok color Pink Red one
[Music]
Stick 2 Stereo
Oeja  They even designed the floor, which is so amazing!  wa gore teru ni
uh follow me okay
flow flow
flow
[music] Mua
moona
senpai mu
haisei hello
[music] It
's easy yeah yeah gamma ya
uh one of the pair is given a name for the stage
yes  Well, they have one minute to
set up the scene and the other player
tries to guess what it is.
Oh, the pairs are awarded emeralds based on their turn. I
see.
[Music]
Who's going to make it first?
[Music] I
can't hear you
[Music]
Dako Etka-chan Yes, we're not here Yeah, what should we make? Cat, make it, cat, okay, cat, I-
Su, please leave it to me.  Right here,
okay,
okay, on the floor, on top, whatever, okay, okay, yeah
[Music]
ady
Su
[Music]
2Apple
Bunny
[Applause] I
got it from Bunny.
There's something in this that looks like an ear, so which one
is the cat?
[Music] I
want to make it again. I
want to make it. I want to make it. I
broke this. I
picked it up on the floor.
Thank you, senpai. I bought it.
What is wine wine or wine wine? Um,
this is this, this is this, grass like grass over there,
yeah, yeah, yeah, wine, wine, wine, okay,
okay, wine,
vine bud tree.
Hey, let's go,
come on, let's go,
come on, come on, do your best, I said this
Naaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, let
's go
forSWORD
SWORDohmygod
TallWhatisthis
VitaminCspoonletgo
hormonestrent
[music]
Music]
OSSOWOW
no
waterfall what is this lifeis
hardHardIhave
say
willE
havesee
seeinguplikeVine
there It's
difficult I
made three arrows Naru
Hello, hello, hello, nice, nice,
sorry, sorry, I did it Let's try this too, yes, let's try here, let's try here, let's go, let's
go, um, kana
[Music] I wonder if
Kirao can say it in English
[Music]  ]
Oh, wait, wait, I can't mute it.
Let's go.
[Music]
That's why I can't hear you.
No,
what's antifunden?
Daehun Ah, let's buy the mute, let's go. Yes,
it's fine. That means unmuting.
Okay, okay, yeah,
okay, get ready. I'm going to break it here. Yes, get ready
.
[Music]
321. What's that? Ao,
what are we going to do? Oh, over there.  I'm
just looking at Christmas
Reno Arrow Eh this is a crane fly erotic
Ah Pispics I
said I understood it from Kuspi Chaku-chan
Yoaaaaaaaaaaaaa  I'm
sorry, it's okay, I think the answer could probably
be in Japanese.
[Music]
Hey
be Oh, okay, it's okay
. Thank you. And Lulu, I have
n't decided yet, so please believe me. Yes,
yes, there may be changes.  I don't know, but it's
mostly like this.
Thank you. I
understand. It's easy. That's all. Is it all over?
Or do I still
want to practice?
KAN
[Music]
Thank you for leaving it to me today.  Thank you for practicing
Thank you teacher, yes,
Adore
[applause]
Senkyu, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, we're okay, let's
win, senpai, let's go, yes, it's
okay,
Ojo.  Book
[Music]
SLEhave
things
weird havehelp
Tired
[Music] I
wonder if there's a goodbye
[Music]
[Music] It's
No. 1 Ma
so
[Music]
Ooh Ae
Good luck,
of course, of course,
of course, of
course, what's up? [
Music] Oh, oh, oh, here's the flow.
Remember,
okay,
yes, then look at this, look at this, okay, this is
Jinko,
Jinko, yes, Jinko, Jinko. It's like a person's name, Geo.
Yes, I understand. Okay,
Ronba.
Ronbaronbajika
[Music]
Chandeu
[Music] It's
hard
[Music]
Meao
just o
Ronparonpa
Jinpokopokopokopoko Korekopo
Popopo Oronpa
Ronpa Jinku Jinkopo
Popopopo Okay no no uh Larry Rally Rally Rally Rally
run away o
Rally run away Isee
from eh  What should I run away from?
Run
[music]
Nora
for what?
Eh, rally is
run run run lao control run run oh yeah oh
oran
running rally is easy Rally rally ok
oh ok kelon paropa chichinko chiko ko
lari Okay huh huh
[music]
Ah, I understand, do haa  No, no, yes,
anal
1234 sadoor 5 sasadoa door tiga
tiga ampa ampa ampari marima yes
etsato kari wow once once once is uma
Genius Genius Saka Karikari is a shell Oh
yes Luaka twice twice Oh then the clue is three times
Shiri Makari is five times
Yeah Sakari Saka once
[Music]
Sa 4 times Nice nice nice ma I understand ah yeah
yeah
[Music]
Taifutai I'm a junior
high school student, right? It's not like that.
Ji is 7.
77 I don't know.
Off to 5.
Ochinka Lopa
Lopapo O Rally Rally Rally then uh uh
Rampadore
Kari
Ronpa
Door Kari Yes
Ronpa no jump twice almost no what
okay
[Music]
Well it's okay Throat Length I'm
sure it's still Ririn but it's okay
Yokaze
No  It's okay, thank you. It's
okay. It's okay. It's
so long.
[Music]
[Music] I
went to learn quickly.
[Music]
Oh, no, no.
Good.
[Music] I
hope Momo gets better.
Take a break.
[Music]
Please, Iooooooooooooooooooh
, wait a minute. You're a genius.
You're a genius. You're a genius. Oh, you're a genius. You're a genius. I'm
already a
genius.  Taa, good, good,
okay, next time, let's do it.  It
's wrong,
it's wrong, it's the
wrong right,
left and right, no, it's not right, it's wrong.
Genius
Genius Okay Nice Teach Here Here Here Here Here
Oh, uh, practice, practice, okay, uh,
maju, sakari, seriously,
sasakari,
sasaka,
this is it, yes, ol' saka, yes,
npae
o
[Music]
Wow, ok, maji
sa poko
[music] Maji maji saka, podoa, nice, I
did it, sleep, suri,
sleepi  Where are you going to sleep?
[Music]
Where's your bed? It's so
nice!
Mon Good morning, Ayoyo Ase
Yo, that's right Lepareparepa, Lepareparepa
Lepa Lepareah
Throw
[Music]
Throw Rampa Rampa Yes
Delepa [Music]
Oh yes this is Lepa
Get used to it
[Music]
Losing streak
[Music] It seems like it's going to be a series of hi
japa It's
going to take off.  Turn to the right,
turn to the right, it looks
like a head, easy to remember.
Yes, it's definitely a hatakiri
Ah, the left side is pointing haha, I
see that the left side is pointing, I see.  Karu
runa keru doru te ka ru
back adani
Kiri
[Music]
Kiki
Kiri a times
[Music]
Yes one one
Ohaburakan, oh, Burakan,
wait a minute, hey, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, Burakan,
wait a minute.
Merawana,
Merawana, Merawana Merah, there
was a red block
there, right?
Then I think I'll have to go back to that red bloco
Oh, I see, that's right Yeah, ok,
ok, that's a bad thing, color mela is red, yep,
walong merawan
ok, oh, I didn't hear that,
thank you, I told you, I
won't tell you, it's a secret  Just here,
here, here, just here,
nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Thank you for the cue, thank you, now I don't
have to cheat anymore
Haribachi yada perfect
[Music]
[Music] I
went seriously
Koko and Pukupukukia Senpai Pukupuku
Pukupuku Pokopokopukupuku
Pukupuku and Bokoboko are similar, right? I
remember they are similar.  Wow, please tell me again. I taught you
so much. You're a genius. You're
so talented. Okay, okay, then.
Ha after this
MayI will
rest I have a sore throat SLEtime My
sleep time
No, thank you for taking a rest Louis
No
[Music]
Thank you I suddenly started reading today
Kanakana Ao Inaru
[Music]
Naka
[Music]  ]
Titi-
oh, I guess I should call you Bokoboko-chan
Bokoboko Boko-chan Bokobobo
Boko I'm scared
Bokobokobokobokobokobokoboko-chan
[Music]
Thank you, are you happy?
Poko Poko Chan Boko Boko Senpai Boko Boko Senpai Boko Boko
I often call Kobo-chan Bokobo Abokoboe Bokobo
Bokobo There's a synergy in this.Then the
sense
is similar Teru Bokobo Poko Poko Poko Poko Senpai Pok Poku
Senpai Sparkling Senpai La Senpai Ae
Wow.  Sparkle, oh, sparkle, oh, oh, senpai, oh, oh,
senpai, oh, oh, glitter
Oh, oh, oh, it's
okay to say ``Nononowa'', ``Wawa, wawaso'', ``Wawama'', Kiara becomes Kiara, Kiwa becomes Wawa, Tawawa-senpai Yay [Music] Thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work, I want to come up with a nickname for you, my cousin.
Neomai  Gohan
Rishi
[Music]
Kakashi Yes, it's not a foot, it's not a leg, it's not going to be good.
Is it okay if I stay here?
Tomorrow, I honestly don't know, but
I think I'll be fine. Okay,
thank you very much. It was fun.
Baba, let's do our best.
Baba thanyouBye
[Music]
[Applause]
ByeHV
[music]