[Music]
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
welcome back
first ever full whole life collaboration
yay
[Applause]
i hear a lot of motivated met crewmates
only crewmates of course
nobody sucks
oh let's not talk about it
we're gonna talk about it especially
about you finally it doesn't matter if
you hide behind that little
walk there
just a potted plant
i i see a green root
are you
a vegetable
i just want to mention what happened
before the stream we had a little uh
testing session and uh we just wanted to
play the game seriously for once and
then
after a little while we had no reports
which was kind of just so fanna uh doing
an emergency meeting um just to you know
because she was obviously scared i wish
i was too
um
she reported okay she did an emergency
meeting and then what do we see free
deaths
of course she's not sucks
she made the meeting but turns out she
was the imposter how reckless is that
not to mention she kills so
was so short
[Laughter]
oh my god i'm surprised you even noticed
oh wow
oh i see there's a color that's better
suited to you yes i was
wasn't sure i wasn't sure if i could
enter or not
welcome
okay
it never has counted
[Music]
um so i would like to get some
introductions from everyone and stream
up yet
is everyone's streaming are you
are you ready
are we all ready yeah
are we good okay i have a stream okay
currently okay i hear you guys all
around me
[Music]
a reason why you are not today starting
from amelia girl
oh why i'm not trust today um
okay
um hello everybody i'm amelia hello live
english miss number one detective and um
i'm not wearing pants
that's why you know what's up
i mean there's a lot of stuff
nothing that happened mommy was wearing
pants i'd be more worried you know
okay definitely not sus so next up bae
your introduction please and why not
is about
our council representing chaos everybody
[Laughter]
proximity i'm sorry okay i'm not sucked
because um i got a cute pet look at my
pet oh yeah
you bought that bagel hamster
you bought it with real money
[Music]
oh the
wow that's kind of kind of weird
interesting
right yeah and breathe so the breed's so
different uh definitely not us count
your turn next all right um so yeah um
death is real sus but guess what
everyone i'm not death i'm the sheriff
around these parts and because i'm the
sheriff the sheriff is never suss the
sheriff obviously didn't do it um
some people may say i i shot the sheriff
but i did not shoot the deputy meaning
uh i don't know what that means it just
has something to do with the sheriff and
i'm not i'm not suspect so there you go
how can you be the real whatever you
can't even spell sheriff yeah
now that was because that was because
there wasn't enough room for for me to
spell it correctly all right
[Music]
listen i am definitely
obviously
that that is very necessary yeah the
sheriff
there's only one all right
my name is fauna and i am simply a
potted plant therefore i cannot kill
for today so your deed is done
no no no plant has never killed anyone
little shop of course does it ever
never i remember that musical um
[Music]
um
she's not a believer
[Music]
it's iris live english project help the
trooper slash me singer
uh
i am very excited i
am a hundred percent say so i would
never lie which is why i would never be
suss
yes that that explains everything i
would never
i would never do anything horrible iris
i don't trust their tyrants
iris yes no trash
iris that's not what happened
yesterday
hi
a very very um
good self-introduction while a lot of
people mostly just say hey my name is
this
is
it's just just a newbie newbie you know
what's with a what
oh no no no
shut
oh yes
hello my name is crony oro from
the council and
i am blue
yeah
it seems like your senpai has stolen
your color
but i'm a more royal color royale
okay okay
yeah where's the blue
okay don't look at the color objectively
look at the color that's inside all of
us can i ask why you're wearing a mask
she's right she's right
all right then um uh wait did cronie say
why she's nuts us oh right i'm not sucks
because look at this i'm wearing a mask
i'm doing my uh part
in this situation don't get close to me
you look like a duck
well i tried to social distance but i'm
not suns because i'm doing my part in
the society
and uh
am i the only one that got kicked out
with
i got kicked out did anyone else get
kicked out
everybody got kicked okay
one second inactivity i'm opening lobby
lobby is created code is uh there no
sorry okay
okay wait wait i gotta i gotta hide it i
gotta have it hide it otherwise if we
type it in
by the way hi hi yes everyone everyone
you can hear everyone um
we should have done intros here to be
honest
yeah but you know we had a problem with
the servers last time right like during
the test
uh
yeah that's true
this is just because of our inactivity
it's not a server problem don't worry
it says
rudely interrupted
wait wait it says could not find a room
is what it says
oh wait i mistyped
[Laughter]
there you go
no problem okay
let's see does it work is it possible
yes it works
[Music]
we're
okay
actually i am the guardian of
civilization and i am an apex predator
of the sky and i could kill you if i
wanted to
that's right that's right
that
that is that that is the most nonsense
introduction ever yes
but i don't want to so i won't
okay oh oh there comes a sweet because
you are so peaceful
mhm she's like those berry bushes sweet
but
i take it back i take it back um
i i might not right no taxi back seats
um
the
priestess of the ancient ones i think
and uh
i think yeah sometimes i forget but um
oh
i am not sauced because i'm already dead
look at the the hair a little bit in my
head
[Music]
that makes a lot of sense all right then
thank you ina
next up sanna is not streaming but she's
here so please let us know who you are
[Music]
um hi hi i'm sana sugama from honey life
english council
uh it's been a while hello guys
i have a big limiter on my head
yeah oh
back into the space where you belong
right or actually you're a part of
you should be fine you should be fine if
you get kicked out
i have no reason to
oh um well
i'm very happy to have you here sana
thank you for participating we're really
glad to have you as part of this even if
you're not streaming
[Music]
back soon so we can all look forward to
her streams again
last but not least it is me talking
about live english and uh i am the one
organizing this
and i'm really happy that we could all
get together 11 people is a lot but
we're going to have a lot of fun today
so let's get right into it are you girls
ready to be not suss
[Music]
let's
[Applause]
oh go don't want to be imposter first
round please not imposter for you
[Music]
the crew mate
oh jeez oh my god first round oh my god
i haven't practiced this map so we are
going okay wow i have a lot of hi
hi
what you doing
i don't know i'm pretty good at this
yeah i'm not very good at this either
okay got some stuff to do
uh i kind of wanted to you know go and
you know stab move my butt
oh yeah i have to be careful there's
prox
i'm ready to chat
oh let's go to the vet okay i'm pretty
sure we weren't able to like talk in the
vet i think me and where's bae i had to
look for baby
[Laughter]
hearing kelly's screams
was
beautiful okay let's get out of here
okay
what's going on in this map
um
[Music]
oh i can hear i can hear them i can hear
them
i can't hear them
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god
hello
absolutely ballsy coming out the first
string with the lights on with multiple
people around what was that about
no
came out
[Music]
it looked like either iris or bay no no
no no no
girl this is a self report it could be
both no
it was right in front of my face oh no
it was great i'm right in front of my
face
no wait hold on i am black screened
again
oh no
no not again
we just got started should we do a new
yeah we can we can do it i know if it's
gonna be any better
try fixing it but
maybe i don't know maybe reinstall among
us or something like that because you
had that before
we can always yeah
yeah we can restart but who should we
kill off
were yeah where did you spawn
where where i spawned yeah records
in the middle thingy there a record okay
uh
gooda where did you spawn i spawned in
the in the i was by myself it was the
room with the folder on the table oh
records okay i resorted to spawn
huh uh where did i spawn let me look at
the map real quick uh and being a
detective i i do not have not really
played this map um i think somewhere
like in the main hall
[Laughter]
okay well me sana and cronie all spawned
in the cargo bay and we were all by
ourselves and we checked the vital
screen down there and cali and two
people were already done yeah they were
already fauna and cali were already dead
so whoever spawned with them there were
two killers no i was died at the same
time i was alone
i was alone i did not see them at all
yeah i'm pretty i spawned alone like in
the beginning right we're talking about
the beginning right yeah all right
uh
i appreciate it what's it
that's true
you guys are making the wrong decision
no
oh my god bae
[Laughter]
[Music]
hi
iris
they made they made the wrong decision
that they killed you when you're so when
you're when i'm so sick
oh my god
oh my god how dare she do that to me i
thought we could do a double kill like i
thought the double kill was the thing so
i was just like
out huh
wait raise the other one
oh yeah yeah basically the other one is
we both blamed guru i think it would
have worked it was just like
she just just went and turned her back
on me
um this is why the relationship does not
work okay what no you can't what's it
wait no i don't think she can hear us
yeah only bank can hear us only the
watson can hear us
only bacon here
yeah i'm gonna go home i'm going to go
home like oh my god bae oh my god
where is she where is she where is she
i have to do those i'm going to do other
tasks uh yes myself
i'm i'm not i'm not useful i'm i'm dead
already
oh yeah i could sabotage
[Music]
you know you can hear me uh if you kill
me now you can hear me
how dare you betray your partner
we were actually a thing in this in this
round
i thought oh this is why
this is why the divorce is happening
it's not my fault it's big right now
it's not my fault the betrayal is strong
um test it out again
why
i'll do that yeah
kind of me yeah you've got clothes in
here oh my god
you can count on me absolutely
ridiculous yep hey baby
of course i told you guys it's her yeah
i just can't trust you anymore
i can't
[Laughter]
a message very important stuff yeah
obviously i need to i need to
convey something
okay all right i should i should do
something
all right let's get let's get electrical
down
okay
look there's someone
oh there's still a lot of them how many
more are alive
i saw three of them okay where are the
other ghosts
oh okay they're doing tasks
i know you can hear me
i know you can hear the whisper okay
maybe i'm not whispering but
the voices
of the betrayed
i want you to feel guilty
i want to hypnotize you into thinking
that maybe you are actually guilty oh
i knew it yeah of course of course
walking around alone
yep
yep yep and i was running from here
i was the least suss of them all and
they just out me out including bae
um
i mean
oh you voted oh good good sana good sana
good sanna
yeah
i i praise you i praise you
wait raise you up high cause i mean you
deserve it you deserve it
thank you for voting for bae thank you
okay
i'm gonna go i'm gonna go hunt bae oh
sheriff howdy to quit playing around
yeah yeah yeah howdy how's it going
howdy are you doing your tasks i wanna
maybe maybe you know uh distract you
from doing the tasks you know [\h__\h] to me
now iris you can't do anything to me you
can't do anything we're both ghosts
i have iron focus iron
we have a bit of a a relationship um she
took my life and i didn't think that was
really cool cash money um especially
like gucci
gucci no no we're gucci we're gucci
right sharon
that's a word for it
oh no biz the x the x and already yeah
we we we got together for this round and
then and then we just yeah she betrayed
me
oh there we go here we go there's sana
um
i have found this buddy but i have
absolutely no clues because i was
running around a little still have a
chance i
meant
yes so who's done get her out
but i think that's something that an
imposter can do like show that yeah
it's big i think they can fake it
i think cronie can vouch for me that i'm
not obsessed right crony what do you
think i mustn't look at it well i i know
that watson and sauna were definitely
safe because the killings took place
when uh all of us were still around
and
people who are considered suspicious to
me would be
then we'll just check we should end the
game early yeah um
uh
first and see if the oh no no you just
fold her down just follow her pull her
to the floor
is definitely in the clear because i was
with her
you have to end it early guys
that's kind of suspicious
i thought it was
[Music]
[Applause]
this is not good
we were this close this close
yeah interesting
vote next time
um okay i don't know oh i'm in the cargo
okay hi
hi sana
[Music]
i want them to hurry up and
get bear out of here and this end this
round you know we need to be we need to
be quick
yes watson watson actually you just have
to amelia actually did vote for bay so
oh
there's all
when i was impostor i'm crew now so you
know we want to end this game quickly um
by voting
you're trying to ignore us but in your
mind you're just like oh no the chaos
[Music]
i'm not
but you know i i'm i want to do
something besides just float around so
i want to do something
somewhere that'll take us far far away
far far away oh no
please don't don't tiara
well we'll see when they if we see bay's
body on our way back up
we've seen facebook i was with her for a
little while but she could have been on
cooldown
i don't know
is there a cooldown like when you spawn
in okay where is bay
um
oh
good good sheriff you're very very
where is everyone this is such a huge
map i'm too used to like the the default
map
i'm just like trying to find oh there
you are there yeah i know that there's
nobody around you can just whisper you
can talk to yourself babe all right
oh never mind there's mom
i just noticed
his name was mom
um yeah
make sure to make sure you remember to
sabotage
kind of like you know don't forget your
bento remember to sabotage babe
don't forget your don't forget your
sabotage um
yep
you're so annoying oh what what you just
said
oh that was not that was not a
hitorigoto right that was not you just
talking to yourself that was a message
to me huh boy
she just called me a knife
[Music]
the
i left her and i ran around because i'm
dying
i watched it all happen we can hear you
now
we can hear you loud and clear if you
have been with me i couldn't find anyone
oh my god
is doing her best
where have you been just now but no no
not now it's two cents
yes voter down butter down
let's make this quick though so that ina
can come back yes let's make it quick we
want to make it quick quick
[Music]
she wasn't really doing her tasks she
was just walking around my tummy was
really rumbling
i mean were you doing tasks yes
what were you doing what was the last
task you did i have a good one did she
practice his math kind of overrated so i
haven't really practiced what's the
matter
i wouldn't be able
was your
had to go to the other side to input it
yeah that is at the
um
i think it's between
storage and like developing room the
question question question
that was a short imposter round kiara
[Music]
was the one who reported the body too
right that's an imposter though this is
my second body i'm recording yes
sharp reproductive that's true
that's true
okay good good good for voters
[Music]
we will rock you yeah
well done ladies um well done oh oh hi
oh my god i haven't heard you guys in a
long time
yeah
i'm sure they heard us loud and clear
though
yeah oh [\h__\h] yeah definitely
um
looks like i don't know my screen though
she has i don't know if it's freaking
out
i thought we
[Laughter]
i thought i could do a double kill and
that's why i killed him
and then i thought we could just put the
blame on on girl like if we put if we
both put the blame on girl we could be
in the clear but but bae was like oh
it's iris and i'm just like what
what i thought we were a team
so yeah ever since then i'm feeling
prophecy mm-hmm
[Music]
i thought this would be the round the
imposter
says that she's getting that connection
i'm gonna try to open one new lobby okay
okay okay hey
all right um with me
leave
okay
i'm just gonna open up
oh yeah
um
new lobby okay
just gotta make sure i hide the screen
wait
hello hello hello okay good good good
good
we are here
we should get the that connection
no no i was able to get in one try
okay um
[Music]
yeah me too
ladies cheers
[Music]
why would you put the blame on me
what
i've been the previous round right i
think it's because you
are so uh
experienced to experience say it first
and i always think whoever says it first
is suspicious uh
usually i feel like imposters are
usually very quiet like they try not to
talk because they don't wanna unless
they're very experienced in that sense
yeah
quiet people are usually the ones that
are into the room be like all right so
who did it
[Music]
hi
hi everyone's just like uh you
you
you did it
oh i think it's cute like oh no wait i
think you're good
all right which one of you suckers is
the imposter um it's probably you callie
it's probably you
oh so it's cali
it's callie uh is kelly is kelly looking
in the future already she's looking in
the future
okay thank you for the
promotion oh
i'm a cool kid too
sorry about the fox by the way yesterday
um yeah it's okay i mean apologize to
the followers
you can't
i thought yeah you know you won't won't
you won't get revenge or anything right
yeah it was kind of hard she pushed the
fox down the hole no i didn't
smashing their buttons
it did not do that it just
it wanted to jump into the hole and i
tried to pull it back with the fleece
i cannot believe it
what what if it was your child that you
pushed down the hole huh
no no no it was it was an adoption and
you know it doesn't matter anymore right
because you know isn't getting it
doesn't matter anymore you you also ate
your own child right you ate your own
child i know you did
okay
i really hope it works
really hope it works in this chord until
now is here okay okay
otherwise she's been she's gonna be in
silence the whole time that's true
hello
hello maybe we should make i'll let ina
make the room maybe ah oh that's a good
idea try that you could try that
if this one doesn't work
this one doesn't work it works for me oh
my god wait let me try
but we can
we can let inna try about this
no it's not your fault
this is the curse the en curse is just
kicking in
[Music]
because i got the same error uh when i
tried to creating the lobby before the
stream many times
just try again again
i mean angels do get nerfed in this game
that's true
that's why that's why my ping is not
that not that good
it's because i'm half angel guys
the angel side of me is nerfing me in
this game
yes
oh hide the screen when typing code
that's right yes
is there a new code oh yeah no right
i'm having trouble making the room too
so it's just like
the servers
yeah
maybe maybe we can try i i don't really
think it's closer but let's try maybe an
asian server
we can
we can try
do you want to try you know or should
maybe someone else you guys can try it
someone else is going to try making it
okay i'll make one i ate in asia
okay
okay gotcha
okay code is
oh wait are should we not be saying this
on stream
i'm not saying it okay the code is code
the code is dakota's code okay b o
[Music]
did you get the first try yeah i guess
it was the server no if yes
end up block screen again just just go
on without me it's fine
oh no
we don't wanna
yeah
oh
this is a full en collab and it would
not be full without you around
oh yay
[Music]
party
thank you servers
[Music]
start in the kitchen let's turn take out
the trash this is heavy trash
okay
um
oh wait why are there pistols right next
to the really we can take what's this
for this is sus it's very sus to take
take a pistol that's that's so sass what
wait i can i take all of them what
i don't get it
you take all four
oh wait oh we place it here why do what
what's with this task
ira is so innocent oh i should have made
my name that like that last time i was
just i was obsessed i should have
changed it but i don't know i just
really like the whole iris so sus name
you know
communications
i haven't met anyone yet oops there
sorry redo redo
i was so innocent
we can shoot now i don't know
no i put away the all the guns somewhere
else so sadly no i don't think we have
any on us
i hope this is a very peaceful game i
haven't met anyone
which means i have no chances of getting
killed since oh oh oh oh oh oh
holy [\h__\h] the only one i can say about
that the only thing i can say about that
is that i heard kelly's voice close by
for a moment but
that was like i i didn't even see her
close by i only found the body like a
few moments later
[Music]
area but i wasn't i wasn't doing
anything i was like looking for a task
to do well why were you not doing tasks
i don't think you're done with tasks we
just got started there's a lot of tasks
i doubt it it's a bit i don't know how
to play this game
i saw her coming up towards me and i was
in the armory which is on the bottom of
the kill cali passed by me
that's very funny hahaha time to kill
hahaha
please
me e94 and cali spawn together but kelly
went off pretty
um yeah i was pretty sure we didn't i
was pretty long
she went straight first for the kill
doing my tasks if if oh really you just
said that you did you weren't doing any
tasks now you said you weren't doing the
tasks
oh god i don't want to play the [\h__\h]
game
okay
calm down i will if you really don't
know how to play the game i will give
you a tip now a serious tip press tab to
open the map so you can run around while
seeing the tasks and that makes a very
easy tab tab
i was like i was like looking back and
forth between the map
did you vote
[Music]
that's enough to throw me out really is
it
yup we're good we're good no one
really says for now okay
let's go i have never been to the brig
let's go to the break hi
hi
okay i'm gonna go do some tasks
it's interesting how we have to climb oh
we have hands guys besides the whole
killing animation we actually have hands
oh trash that's a lot of trash
okay
this is a very very peaceful game
haven't met anyone what's this
oh wait
uh
um
7 11. oh wait
one
six two
okay there we go uh oh
crash course uh-oh we need to turn this
ship around
okay
[Music]
i'm not familiar with this map one where
where is the where where do we go
[Music]
don't you oh with the sun okay thank you
thank you thank you mother nature
oh we can use this to go on the other
side
there's a huge pencil here i just
noticed
what's with the huge pencil okay let's
do tasks
ah
feels good to be
a crewmate very very peaceful game and i
haven't seen any dead bodies
[Music]
oh did you did you did you finish your
tasks and just uh no no i have one
yeah this is a very huge map i'm getting
there yeah
i'm starting to think that cali is
probably sauce
yeah oh my god i thought she was
knowing she was like i don't know what
to do oh
oh oh oh
which one of you just closed the toilet
door
as she went inside the toilet stall the
suspect
so into the toilet
[Music]
uh to the very very bottom decided to
kill me right after going to the toilet
right after the toilet
um because when i found that halo
oh that
i sounds convincing
i don't know
oh she's so convincing at trade and
acting like acting like an innocent enos
innocent okay very good acting and plus
acting
i don't know what to
i wasn't looking no i wasn't looking at
chat i was just talking to them so they
didn't have to listen to nothing
she's walking around completely slightly
kind of like
i was trying to sauce
i'm pleasure you could kill me you
probably love it where were you which
means
where are you i was also in i was in
there
but i didn't go up i came from the other
side someone's in the bathroom um
there's a better proposition whoever's
in the bathroom
posters let me spawn back in while i see
you come out no
yes the genius the genius was running
around with sana at one point
lost
maybe i should raise cronies
i don't know well fauna says for now
okay
so uh imposter is gonna win you guys are
gonna win this one
[Music]
why are you me out
this is going to be an imposter wrench
oh i can shower as a ghost
i'm a dirty ghost guys
very dirty ghosts i
what okay
i can shower as a ghost
oh wait where's the where are the
imposters where i i need to go haunt
enough
yes cali is very sus definitely very sus
i'm glad to
i'm surprised nobody voted her out yet
after that so i feel like the
the first meeting kind of gave it away
but everyone was voting um
who is my brother yeah everyone was not
was skipping votes i'm just like okay i
guess i'll skip too but
i mean
honestly i thought kelly was successful
in the beginning so i think it's calina
definitely caleb
oh you're very good at it
you're very good at playing an innocent
face yeah that's so soft
what happened
oh
nobody knows this fabian nobody does
here do we do we look at this
[Music]
um right yeah
records area how do i back up i'm dead
um when i was above the rankings area i
saw kelly so i wanted to say hi so i
followed her and
the next moment she completely
disappeared i went i went into all other
like like uh
ways to look for her but she disappeared
and there was a vent right where she
disappeared so but until you walk down
the road man you can vouch for me i went
down to the bottom and tried to actually
i'm not
[Laughter]
[Music]
let
i
she just wants me to get thrown out
has a sheriff
imposter tactic is sounding a little
desperate
[Music]
it's intense
i'm not so sure
[Music]
you don't have to vote i just want to
mention it
no we should you guys should totally
vote
[Music]
i'm surprised nobody's voting for callie
maybe she's a sheriff oh yeah that's
true
we can't do that i'm just saying you
were sussing me last time but it wasn't
me either let's try records
oh hey faye
i don't think you can hear me this time
fullness us now it's cali sauce it was
always kelly's sauce babe
it was always cali
it's hard to tell with chiata because
this is these are the toilet stalls
in the box
um
oh you heard that that's what i heard i
only heard that i only heard the taco
duchies in a box what were you saying
before that
no no nothing
something that you don't want to you
know what
i'm curious of the continuation of this
uh
it was i was just saying tankodachis oh
tank odachi's in advance
he was saying oh there's someone in the
box looks like yeah tenkodachi's
[Laughter]
oh nice one no no in inaudible
did cali kill you
yeah okay yeah yeah i'm surprised people
are not voting her off she was just from
the beginning
if she's a sheriff i guess we can't we
can't hang a bit i'll get the hang of it
yeah do a good job sure
you have a good hang of it yeah you're
getting the hang of it people are not
voting
i'm slowly getting the hang of how this
game goes
yes yes
she found the body
that was me boys
found her in the kitchen
walking around doing my normal
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
of course yeah you were totally doing
that you were totally doing that kelly
[Music]
are you kidding me and sheriff needs to
go on retirement i'm loving this
this is beautiful
it is time for cali it is time for the
sheriff to retire
what have you guys been doing yeah
nina's so safe right now yeah
like
no one's standing up for me when i when
i like literally why would i could have
killed you if you guys were alone but i
did [\h__\h] nothing anyone who would
vouch for me is there anyone listen
[Music]
why are you pointing the finger at me
i don't think i can vote no you haven't
seen me
no
well
why can't you vote the other impossible
because i'm so unsure
oh there we go
[Music]
you know went and
backstabbed the sheriff
but at this point everyone had something
about someone vouching for them except
kelly except callie this is one task at
the records that i don't know what to do
okay let's go to the main hall
uh i do have oh okay at least i'm a
ghost i can go through walls now
what's this
huh
oh
this is a this is a phone okay
uploading wow the connection is bad look
at that wi-fi bar
uh-huh oh yeah wait wait a sec this is
taking forever so just let me let me do
this
let me do my thing if i've been a ghost
for quite a while this whole stream
i want to stay alive stand alive
how do i get married
i don't know what they're doing all
right
i'll try walking down
[Music]
social distancing
does not exist in this game
hey fauna
i know you can't say anything now
because others are around you killed me
right after the
disappointed right now oh babe hamster
is going haywire right now yeah okay
here we go guys
we've been here hopefully everyone's
gathered everyone's together i finished
all my tests
i got the button wrong what button mina
what button
the what the kill button you got the
kill button right kill myself
okay so for example
electrical
[Music]
wait wait here's where oh wait i did
have
oh never mind they turn off lights and i
can't see that happening because there's
oh okay there they're going wrong
yes you will yes you will i'm here just
kidding hold on let me try this again
yeah i put those away
yeah there's a lot of weapons here oh
hammer
hammer time
okay
um
how's the sheriff doing how is impostor
i'm trying to figure out how to sabotage
things silence
[Laughter]
sabotage because i'm getting different
answers from everyone
just just press the the sabotage button
on the bottom of the screen
below click on the area on the map you
want to sabotage the icons with the
cross and then our door sabotage yep and
then there's also the light sabotage
that easy yeah yeah you just press press
click click click the icon so you don't
even need to go anywhere no no you just
click on the icons yeah so you can you
can basically uh play around with all
the doors in the game yep
wow yep just like a remote control
yep
no problems no problems for the sheriff
than pastor sheriff
[Music]
oh
now
i'm assuming they're probably going to
vote out
that was so soft
and then the nmkr is going to
kept saying that she was lost and i
thought that it was
suspicious
[Music]
know
that
and then i had a great card
that was good
she's very good
this is her first round
voted out and going with my gut feeling
i'm gonna go my guts too even today
everyone votes for each other has been
really quiet
[Music]
no those eggs on your head
what are you gonna crack before i die
i'm going to
main hall
oh they're already sabotaging again
hello hello
hello nina is a very good imposter
that's what we learned today
just one more person
[Music]
yeah this is your first round and you're
like just going around oh oh be careful
babe careful baby okay she got it don't
get close why did you no we don't no we
don't no no no don't get this don't get
them don't
[Music]
oh my god oh my gosh she's such
not that was not your boy's victory that
was definitely ina right there hello
hello no
really
using the i don't know how to play the
game cards
[Music]
hey yeah so i have a question so when
you're imposter and you're like going
pretending to do tasks etc can others
tell if there isn't really a task there
to do
um no
you know what
but
like if you're doing certain like if
you're asking to do tasks that should be
probably longer because there's really
long tasks that kind of can't stand out
that you're
done so quickly
someone
who's got these codes
[Music]
okay
oh we gotta hide the screen
i'm sorry guys no problem
no problem new code is out there now
okay thank you
there we go oh very smooth
smooth entrance okay
oh i can't wait
anymore yeah you can't use that card
anymore i can't i don't know i don't
know this game ever played on this map
before
give us a statement of how you were able
to hide your imposter-ness for so long
um she was very good i think i blended
in with the crowd you know even if i
could make the kill i i waited for my
chance i was patient yeah
i stuck around being like uh
oh sorry
i still don't know
[Music]
yeah i got
watched was so genuine
not to kill me two times i knew it
kiara you're always suspicious oh yeah
sorry
asked you not to kill me and you said
okay
those were my last words those last
words
last words you heard before she did what
she did
okay
[Laughter]
yeah everyone's here
everyone's here we don't have a holster
are you sure okay
let's go all right let's do this let's
go
how recent is this map victory i'm never
going to be the impression
yep
oh i wish i was an imposter for once
i wish i was too i want to play i wish i
wish you were an imposter
no that wasn't that doesn't count that
does not count
okay
um oh i can't get to the other side
okay let's go around
a huge map
it's gonna go this down this way
oh is it shower time oh it's shower time
i want someone uh can someone watch me
shower this proves my innocence right
oh that was quick
[Music]
oh
what did she do excuse me hello can i
have the floor please she was walking
out explain herself electrical
after excuse me taking off kiara's ahead
excuse me i have a question
was the shark near the washroom no
questions at this time okay i saw
and then i saw guru was also in the room
that kiara went that was quick
i don't know that doesn't mean it wasn't
inna i watched it
for me
[Music]
you were by yourself in electrical
because i was humming no no no no no i
was honest berries and cream tuna
[Music]
with the folder on the table and i went
right down to electrical i don't
remember how what happened never stop by
the washroom that's pretty sunny i
forgot that everyone can hear me since
i'm not a ghost
i just knew every time every time you
were innocent you would do something in
the washroom
she wasn't in the washroom
[Music]
we just spawned it i don't know i'm
pretty
i'm pretty convinced can i can i have a
roommate to stink because you didn't
shower
so this is basically
can i have a moment wait there's no
enemies
i don't know
flopped her story she's gone from meek
and shy to very suddenly very demanding
of the room's attention
which could mean she is obvious i don't
know
i walked in on you
i don't know i don't know
[Music]
okay please i would love to have of
course
okay i'm assuming it's probably gura
probably gura
i don't know ina eno is very good at
this game too though so i can't just
like
oh yeah let's go main hall
um
can someone watch me shower you wanna
you wanna watch me shower okay yeah oh
yeah
yeah oh yes oh
hot steamy shower
oh
[Laughter]
oh so does that mean it's probably gross
oh it's probably gorgeous
i don't know but then uh you know scary
goodbye
careful
okay let's go oh bathroom stall really
there's there's something to do in the
bathroom still what do we do in the
bathroom stall
sometimes you have a um what do you call
it
a plunger oh
yeah what do i do with this wait what i
have how much i don't get how to do this
what
oops
what's that noise
[Music]
i keep getting it
exited out of the game screen
oh there we go okay i see i see i don't
get it oh there we go
um
plunger go plunge plunge
plunging oh is this a safe
that's a kind of sauce huh
i don't get it what
i haven't really used a lot any of these
locker keys in a long time
come on wait what um zero oh
three
and then
five
zero
three
and five
there we go
ah i keep getting exited out of the
screen
okay i have to do this again seriously
okay um
crash course i'll be on this side then
oh hi
[Music]
what
are you going
i don't know i'm going to the spot
the thing right i don't know no it's not
this way we're we're definitely not this
okay okay you know what i'm just gonna
do my tasks too
uh
let's try again
zero
two
six
[Music]
finally okay
uh-oh this is bad news
i'm assuming nobody's on the right side
or the left side
let's go to the left side
we're gonna we're gonna crash at this
rate
oh is nobody on this side really it's
this side oh wait
one four three three nine
okay okay okay got it yep i got it
uh i thought everyone was on the right
side and the left side please listen to
me yeah what's up wait wait that's
i don't know can the impostor sabotage
like you know how just then we had like
the left side and the right side the
code thingy huh
right do we have to enter at the same
time is that why no i don't think so i i
just came i was alone that's why i i
thought everyone was on the other side
and i was trying to get there and i was
like wait i'm lost and i ended up being
on the on the right side of the map
okay and then i i just entered the club
both sides really you did i answered the
code on the right side and it said it
was okay and enough was also there so i
went back to the left side to do it but
it said the right one
girl's been trying to find the right
opportunity
she's been acting kind of sucks
yeah i kept telling her not to follow me
and she just kept saying
no i was trying to i was trying to keep
an eye on you just in case you know you
go for that kill you know yeah she was
saying she's trying to frame ina
okay how is it okay that ena keeps watch
of you for protection but it's not okay
if i do that i don't know
when on the very first round when i
reported when i reported ina absolutely
flipped her story and went from the
super meek i don't know where i'm going
to suddenly
super loud and embarrassing as if she's
trying to protect herself
to be honest i don't trust either of you
so
okay that's fair
oh really i walked past what both y'all
were a little suspicious oh okay okay um
is that you're suspicious of both of us
and not one versus the other thing
yeah she went to go do a task and she
ignored me and i yeah and i'm at the top
just
suspicious about gura was because i kept
bumping into her every time uh it was
just three of us in total so if one
person uh left it would just be two of
us
and i kept having that situation
because you were being left alone with
ina and i want you to be in
and i wanted somebody to be
my watch
um
so wait are we still gonna be skipping
this try going together then
are we skipping are we skipping i'm
paying for now there's some reason i
don't know
put my vote on guru i don't know yeah i
mean i don't know both inna and cronie
were like gurus so i'm just please be
mindful of inna
i don't know i think the imposter too
rounds it around put it on
[Music]
she forgot to talk um
okay
okay oh thank god i can go on here
let's use it and get those
tasks done
i
we have huge hands by the way i noticed
that how huge our hands are
hi
oh no we're good i'm we're good we're
cool we both showered together we
showered together right
oh yeah yeah and we showered together
we're good i wish i was there
i mean we took a shower last time
[Music]
yep
uh girl that's scary no i'm gonna i'm
gonna stay away stay away
from the apex furniture yeah i'm safe oh
[\h__\h] oh
lights
okay
hello
i'm gonna get those lights off
oh wait not this way
um
this is electrical right
is nobody around to oh wait lights are
back oh lights are back never mind
um
oh this part this part
we're all here yeah we're all good
there's a lot of people right yeah
there's a lot of people electrical power
yeah the electrical's back on right it's
back two more tasks i have to do here
it's so itchy
itchy where where is itchy you want me
to scratch it for you no with my horns
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh maybe i should do my tasks i should
do my tests
um are you are you still playing the i
don't i don't know this game card or is
it
[Music]
wow this armory is very
very scary okay
um let's
get the viewing deck there's something
in the viewing deck i'm stuck in here oh
wait
nevermind insert card
oh seriously we have this in this map
too
oh my god
oh okay thank god
[Music]
oh yeah and i saw her doing the carding
and okay
yeah it seems like she's in the clear so
trust me now
so i'm pretty sure she's in the cli too
who's in the club is also in the clear
we saw each other and didn't kill each
other so
as well
so girl you really could have killed me
i think
that it's ina though
maybe you see her doing this i mean i've
ran into so many people have excuse me
is your name no it's not let me answer
the question thank you the microphone is
in my hand uh because at the very
beginning of the match i was singing the
berries and cream song and i went into
electrical and right down there ina
beheaded that person
the stories changed get out okay no it
didn't story
[Music]
showers i'm just like yeah yeah iris
isn't in the clear uh-huh
if it turns out that it's not ina
i don't know i still
i mean
you guys see cronies following
i don't know i'm just like yeah i
haven't seen them good afternoon
but last time i saw crony
she wasn't with like nearby guru though
oh so that was when the lights were
turned out pretty sure i saw a girl
all right well i don't know what to do
so i'm going to skip freaking out
there's definitely still two imposters
you found the body yeah
where'd you find it
yeah where the mannequins are
oh
watson why would you yeah
[Music]
didn't accuse her of killing you just
said she was more suspicious but now i
absolutely love her
is my mic cutting out she i absolutely
did i not accuse
all right i'll be quiet this time
it didn't cut out
okay
it just got out
let's go
okay
oh inna
hello
um the kill cooldown is not
not yet right um my next task is in the
viewing deck you know
yeah what what's where's your next task
mine's actually a medical but medical
okay good you can
you can go to medical go go ahead go
ahead
i'm scared i'm scared of being right
next to her okay um
after last time i'm just like okay i'm
not gonna stick around ina too long just
in case
okay
there we go
yes i knew it oh my god you told me
i knew she was a little i was just like
oh my god i i need to stay keep a safe
distance uh-oh find my body especially
oh
my god
oh my god we gotta vote
[Music]
iris leading ina behind went into the
room to the left of the engine room and
then only came out
i'm gonna go see that body that ena just
left in there and lo and behold there
was the body of iris oh thank you for
checking the camera it's very convincing
very wonderfully
[Laughter]
never voted against you but i'm sorry
i'll be honest i thought i was going to
um
not last the very first trial but i
turned it around i think that was good
enough for this round
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh is
well it is true that bae did notice that
she wasn't talking at all i'm just like
[Laughter]
violence
[Music]
let's get those tasks done shall we
almost done almost done
just a couple more
wanna contribute
that sauna
oh my god my mouse come on what what's
wrong with my mouse
there we go
okay
meeting room at least it's much easier
to do tasks once you're a ghost
so many wires okay
hmm i wonder where everyone is
where is everybody where's
where's mame
the silent killer
run cali run
[Music]
she will deplete our health and
stab us if we try to get close to her
with her sweet fake hate or
[Music]
facade let's get her off beat shelley
i am so scared
you won't be able to sing alone if we're
around
[Music]
well you're alone now you gotta
you're gonna have to
kill at least
a good amount of people
[Music]
oh this is where the other one was okay
meep
[Music]
it was so funny
[Laughter]
there's a time limit
[Applause]
[Music]
unless we would have done all the tasks
a good way is just keep quiet if you're
imposter just stay quiet
[Music]
against you
i'm sorry too i'm sorry girl you were
acting pretty suspicious nina was just
too convincing
oh you're not helping
oh my god
[Laughter]
yeah we can't even if venus is crew i'm
just like maybe we should just vote
she's just too strong she's too strong
this is the wrist
[Music]
the wrist
is high in the next round
can i ask you one one question in the in
the better pruning settings does
everyone have impostors here dead uh
checked because it didn't work last
round what yeah
it's checked for me yeah i can hear you
i'm i'm more curious about the private
talking vents is that working because
i've never like i mean i'm i guess i
died surely but that's disabled okay i
think so yeah but only the hopes can
change it yeah
[Music]
the individual meetings
is this supposed to be like bathroom
music
music is that what you just said
[Music]
music
i'm gonna take a sip
[Music]
uh
definitely me all right cool
i wish i was imposter all right
where are we
you can choose where you spawn
yeah you can you can choose fun
[Music]
okay i'm gonna try to be the the oh wait
if both of us act like
if both of us act like eno it's not
gonna it's not gonna progress that far
and we're just going to win by task so i
have to be
aggressive aggressive
no i don't know oh
stuff to do here
yep
tasks
oh where do i go where'd it go
okay
oh lights are off lights are off how do
i get to electrical i really don't know
this map i don't know this map
ah
where's the electrical light switch
this wait wait
i really don't know how to turn it back
on where is it
and i seriously don't know where to turn
this back on i i
and why is nobody here oh is there any
on it's not maybe it's not even in here
what i don't even know how to turn on
hello hi
[Music]
okay
let's go to the vault oh
he's doing stuff
oh
i'll stay here
uh
oh wait what backup tool change how to
change
one two
and six
hi
i just got it okay there we go there we
go got it yep i just got it
um i have one i don't want to go
and you don't want to be alone
and we could stick around
at the end yeah wait uh my last task
nine
it's
[Music]
go oh really only one person can go yeah
oh okay
underwear
why isn't someone right about now
oh boy
okay
oh okay wait where is the worst event i
don't oh there it is
the body's right there i shouldn't be
doing that okay where am i right now i
don't know
[Music]
i
how do we turn up how do we turn back on
electric do you know how
sana mommy
okay
uh
oh treasure chest i did not know there
was a treasure chest here
okay
let's get oh
they're all here oh you can hear them
okay
i'm in the kitchen uh
what sort of tasks are there in the
kitchen oh my god
wait oh hi
trash can get done
it's impossible
no matter how many times you pull the
trash doesn't it doesn't do anything
no i just didn't but
oh so this is oh
okay okay i can't
ah this is the the card opening i can't
open the door
damn it little door
ah
oh this is a door
can you open this door
i love how kiara says that and as soon
as you see that there's a report
holy totally
totally interesting
because she's been doing tasks alone and
i keep on running into her and i can
vouch for her uh
as a detective
of the law i clear cali and gouda
from being imposters as i was with oh me
too
we're actually done
i've been alone quite a long time
i did see watson at the end i was trying
to open the door i couldn't open it
this is a stupid card no the card key
the card key to open the door was just
like it's really hard to open
some fingers
yeah i do
who killed you seriously
i did uh wait
i feel like i'm able to talk to santa
but i'm not
i saw
[Music]
i have nothing to base my conjecture on
yeah
[Music]
she's talking to you right now huh she's
a ghost and you killed her oh
i see you on this extra talk oh no
oh yeah i don't know there's nothing to
base it on so
i'm just gonna skip it yeah but why
would watson
yeah i think i'm gonna skip but i'm able
to play minecraft
sure
i have a couple more tasks left though i
have a couple more tasks
and so one of them is
[Music]
okay
okay this feels good um
i wonder if
i wonder i i gotta i gotta
stay quiet stay quiet
oh oh
[Music]
gotta get this back up
i found rey in the shower
that's a nasty place
oh no this is the worst place to die
a wet rat eela oh i smell it girl we
were alone and she could have killed me
but she just went off and she at least
finished she was kindly happy and i went
on my way i saw tiara and we were on the
left side of the map so this kill
couldn't have been kiara but i think it
was the other imposter who might i
didn't even see you the other imposter
because
where did you see me i don't know i was
trying to get to the whatever it was
sabotage i forgot it was crash course or
whatever
i was in records but i didn't say
anything i didn't see anyone records
mm-hmm i think it was records and
records
no seriously i just walked into records
that was so loud
i just walked into records and i was
trying to or i don't know the round i
don't know if those records it might
have been the room next to it i was
trying to go towards the other side um
does it have the
table with the folder on it that's the
wrecking room
yeah like i walked in from
wait i'm not so sure anymore uh i'm
pretty i thought it was recording i'm
not too sure anymore i really don't know
[Laughter]
[Music]
i really don't know i think i thought it
was records it might not be records if
you didn't see me but i'm pretty i
thought it was records it's like
describing
i don't remember anymore it was but i'm
pretty sure it was records uh like
i've been there
no it's not no i take my vote i don't
even know where where are the showers i
don't even know where the showers are
pretty close to the shower it's just
pretty close
and who are you looking for
with the
huh i don't even know where the showers
are wait
i don't know
showers you haven't heard a lot from
mumei or ina
yeah isn't it close
oh i was all the way okay i spawned in
kitchen with mummy and then i went to do
my task in the uh the bottom left thing
of course called uh so our suspects are
iris and kiara got it
seriously like the duck thing i've been
like the most productive
good gouda can vote vouch for me right
i mean you didn't kill me yeah and we
were up there at the top
room where it's really easy to kill
people blonde didn't
and the sheriff's got the same family i
didn't lie though i'm sorry no seriously
what no i'm not lying i'm seriously i'm
i'm so honest
hmm
you have like a whole bunch of like uh
deductions in a robe
okay
now how do i fix electrical oh oh this
is
this is electrical oh
okay
let's get this back up
there we go
lights are down yep i fixed the lights i
already fixed lights
okay
um
now let's go
to
oh hyena
i don't like that why are you two
following me no no no no i have some
stuff to do wait i'm keeping watch on
iris oh okay
yeah yeah
okay
oh hi
hello
keep your distance please please
this is i don't know where showing it
this way uh i have to go into the cargo
room if anyone wants to get it
nothing nothing no no no no um
why were you thanking ina iris no
nothing nothing
now we know who it is
all right interesting let's uh i guess
we'll vote i'm interesting oh yeah
that sounds about right nothing what no
come on hold on hold on wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait kiara's dead yeah
i need to you need to hear me out right
now okay so i was doing my favorite task
the potty task right elbow deep in the
toilet
um and
uh kiara came in
and ena came in
tiara is now dead i was the one that
found the irish's body because i left
because kiara and e and i said ha ha i
did the sucky toilet okay guys bye bye
and then i stumbled onto iris's body and
now kiara is dead i was with um i was
with ina and iris and kiara and i left
and i saw callie and then now kiara's
dead so
that will tell you
um
yeah i think that's uh
i think it's either who are we voting
for uh i have no idea what we're voting
for i have no idea
okay okay just just vote just vote me
off if if i'm if if the game doesn't end
then well
i'm voting enough just because it was
it was literally
me
i don't know i'm trying to think
it was true kiara and anna and literally
seconds afterwards unless somebody came
in between them
yeah
i think it's i
yeah it's definitely both of them but we
got to be strategic about who we vote
off
if there's one for each of us and then
[Music]
skip
it yes
what the heck
[Music]
emergency meeting
okay
[Music]
i hear i hear things
i'm hearing things
okay
oh i'm surprised that the ghost voices
are not as loud as i originally thought
they were
[Music]
i better not make any wrongs
oh just one more come on
come on uh damn it
i don't think that i don't think i'm
gonna make it
someone's standing by on the button
[Music]
um um last words awesome last words that
was that was fine i'm sorry i'm sorry
ina i i totally forgot about proximity
chat
that was pretty funny though
[Music]
good virus good virus good virus see you
in another life
yeah enjoy the vacuum of space really
we're not inspired
yeah no i have wings i can fly i'll be
fine
she'll probably be okay yep
never mind that's dark
oh god
yeah well you know what um
regardless of where you fly after this i
hope you learned your lesson
[Laughter]
i feel bad i feel bad yeah i feel guilty
um i will i learned my lesson i'll be
i'll be so
such a good i'll be a good girl the rest
of this year so please good citizen i'll
be a good girl yes all right
you off with a warning
oh just a warning is it just a warning
if it's just a warning i'd be i'd be
very grateful if we can i can stay on
the ship a little longer
yeah
sure but we're gonna have to tie it
together we're gonna have to put a leash
on you or some kind of yeah yeah you
could put put a leash on me anytime
anytime um i'll be obedient very
obedient
you seem very willing that's very
as well what
what how could that be
i'm just trying to be a good
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm not going anywhere i'm not going
anywhere
[Music]
that
that was fun but oh my god
if only i didn't say that we would have
been clear oh my god
this
[Music]
good fun
my dream came true i loved because i
love playing classical free times
it kind of gets questionable when you
get it three times people don't even
like trust off the bats
it's harder as the games go along yeah
yeah three times in a row what's the
what are the possibilities yeah
yeah
i feel like i feel like
it keeps giving impostor to like the
same people
yeah i was really surprised that like
you would assume that you would assume
that the reaper would be like the number
one killer of everyone but i'm actually
just the task master like they're all
like
did you like the passions
when i when i saw you callie you were so
scared of death
right
because
i don't like yeah exactly we'll see
that's the thing is death can't die so
when the prospect of death dying becomes
a thing it's quite frightening
oh scary
i think we got a lot of really golden
moments out of this stream i'm looking
forward to all the clips to see the
other point of view oh yes
i'm really excited to see everyone's
point of views yeah yeah
it's really fun to hear ghosts though
yeah the proximity chat is great
yeah iris you almost blew our cover i'm
sorry i'm so sorry i i thought they
couldn't hear me in my head now yeah i
was like i was like okay if we get a
double kill like like this is good but i
couldn't say anything so i was just
trailing you around yeah it was just
like ah yeah i didn't know if you were
on cooldown no no i that's why i like i
i thought we were going to do a double
kill too that's how i was like around
and then i killed someone and then i see
you went somewhere else it's like oh no
no the double kill and then i think yeah
because yeah someone saw me event or
kiara saw me event right so
yeah yeah thank you for the cover though
yeah if only if only i kept my mouth
shut we would have won
did i kill all of council really i
killed a lot
yeah that round how many people did you
kill anything now do you want to talk
about it
it's a coincidence it's a coincidence
but you know at the same time like you
know the senpai's i i can't i can't go
and kill my senpai's right away off the
bat right
all right
no it's just a coincidence so true pure
coincidence and look at fauna just
becoming a potted plant right here
anyways i like that i like that way of
life
good one
i'm gonna go through everyone from top
to bottom again to give a good bye one
by one and maybe tell me your favorite
moment from today or your favorite kill
or whatever so let's start with amelia
watson
oh uh wait what are we doing oh goodbye
and your favorite times
your favorite kill from today
okay uh thank you guys for watching uh
thank you kiara for uh setting it up
again and organizing everything and my
favorite moment
uh i really liked messing with cali that
was fun
i gotta admit that was pretty good
you mean i mean uh saying that she's the
imposter what happened no she would just
outright say things like like i'd be
like are you gonna kill me she'd be like
yeah you're lucky my cooldown is off and
like run away
[Music]
that's another one for the archives for
me okay well thank you amelia next up
bails
um
thanks for coming guys i hope everyone
had fun thank you kiara for organizing
again so powerful
[Music]
we were trying
it's chaotic
it's even more chaotic when chaos is not
there and that's that's the sad thing
i'll have a cold irish very soon
how what
what
i'm not wait i i don't need to wait
right yeah i mean you can
any time get a room right here everybody
really guys
[Music]
all right ladies
now let's dial it back just a little bit
give me your goodbyes
my favorite moment has to be um when i
was trying to hold up the the cell phone
to get the cell service on the deck
where anyone could have killed me and i
saw sana come up behind me oh and i was
like holy [\h__\h] this is where i die and
then she was like
hey callie and she just walked away and
she's like no i have to do my task here
and i was like okay so we just switched
spaces and we like watched out for each
other it was kind of cool it's a bonding
moment i was like oh
i'm just excited to explore yeah yeah
it was really fun
thank you next up fauna
hello thank you everyone for watching
and thank you kiara for organizing
everything it was a lot of work and i
really appreciate it um my favorite
moment was not being the imposter
oh
yeah i don't know i think pressure is
not being impossible too
[Music]
being impostor is just so much pressure
and like
and especially with the proximity chat
you can't really say anything because
because it
yeah i should do whatever i wanted
i wanted to get into that situation
unfortunately it didn't happen today so
yeah well thank you fun i'm glad you
enjoyed it next up
how salty are you
i'm fine i'm fine i'm saying i was
talking my chat though about like how i
don't usually i don't know have
conversations i don't talk like this
usually like accusatory whether it's in
a game or not it's like it feels very
draining uh mentally i guess
he always hangs on
my favorite moments were
uh and i'm asking clippers please uh the
various perfectly cut screams with the
proximity chat
specifically
one round where everybody was terrified
of me and every time somebody would walk
by me it would just be blood curdling
screams
i'd like to see a perfectly cut screams
uh complacement of some sort if there
are enough people
you have a good one too
for putting this together thank you
okay yeah thank you so much for
organizing this wonderful collab camera
i love among us to bits
so i'm so glad i was able to do this and
i i i would go for among us like off
stream anytime if we had enough people
like that's how much i like it yeah but
yeah it was a lot of fun and being
impostor was great pressure but great
and my favorite moments have to be yeah
killing a lot of people that was fun um
and also like
well personally for a moment that really
didn't have much to do with me um i
really liked how cali you know when she
found fauna's body was like it was
pretty boys
and just kind of outing yourself out
yeah that was so i i found that
hilarious
[Laughter]
oh god i need to be careful with how i
say word
was my personal favorite but yes very
fun game thank you so much yes she was
obsessed all the time
good kills when you're uh
imposter though because i was playing
safe i was like okay if i get all the
air girls and maybe the other imposter
can go on a killing spree oh yeah i was
assuming when i was in position i was
like oh you know probably i'm probably
gonna have to be aggressive so that's
why i went on killing and killing yeah
aggression is the way to go
i was trying to clear my name and that
was how i got out trying too hard to
clear my name but i'm just kidding
i was yelling in her ear the whole time
really just laughing a ghost in my ear
okay crony next doll
oh
sorry um
what was i was i gonna say oh yeah thank
you
oh no no thank you so much for arranging
this it's
that's fine
yeah free media
the freebie
thank you so much to kiara
uh for arranging this i really love this
game and
it's been fun i think my favorite moment
was
uh
well every moment was pretty funny but
whatever the
the proximity chat exploded whenever a
meeting happened
and
the first time when the meeting happened
everybody was screaming and i didn't
even know what was going on but that was
funny so thank you for that
yeah that was so much fun had fun thank
you cronie
next time
hello
thank you kiara for organizing
everything everyone says that
while you're waiting
[Music]
i'm blushing thank you please continue
uh i think one of my favorite parts that
i experienced was i spawned where ena
were with ina
and i turned her and i said wouldn't it
be something if you're the imposter
three times in a row
yeah that really would be she just
walked away
[Laughter]
[Music]
i was like i was like yeah it would be
really funny
it's absolutely drenched in sweat
oh
[Music]
well then you know your goodbye and your
your favorite moments who was your
favorite kill maybe
oh
who felt the best putting a knife
through their stomach
well um it's gonna be half
there's there's been a lot of good kills
but i think it's gonna have to go with
uh
uh cronie in the wasn't the first game
or something where she was like please
don't kill me and i was like okay
[Laughter]
you could have just said sure but
[Music]
cronie would make a good impact i mean
she misheard it if you got
i want to see evil in here who knows yes
this would be very scary and
intimidating though because callie was
every time when i was sussing callie
like she was like so intimidating to me
i was so scared she was yelling at me oh
i'm sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay thank you very much for organizing
the collab cara um i'm really happy to
play a game with you guys again it's
been a while me too
it missed your voice
my favorite movement is like
we're so happy you were here today sanam
we're waiting
waiting for you to come back i did think
about my favorite moment as uh
pretty much every time i heard cali
scream but now my favorite moment
spending time with all of you guys
[Music]
[Laughter]
you should next time next time you
should uh leave me leave me alive
because i
believe everything you guys say i just
[Music]
all right well um uh for me my favorite
moment one i had so many but i guess the
one that stayed in my head now is um i
think it was in this in the
round before the last round where uh
everyone was sussing
gouda and she was just trying to speak
but then like i was really mad and then
ahmed was like well i'm gonna follow you
to see if you're really innocent and i
was like chilling with inna as ghosts
and we were just talking about the
better curling uh just we're standing
there together as ghosts and then ahmed
and guna ran into the room having a huge
fight like disgusting
[Music]
you know like watching a kindergarten
fight on
kindergarten fighting
good that was good they were running in
circles yelling at each other it was so
funny
oh man um but yeah uh um it was it was a
i'm really glad this all worked out fine
in the end uh you know i had some
troubles in the beginning but i'm so
relieved
i'm sorry about no no no no no no no
it's all good
it worked out for sure as the
that everyone organizat fun and and no
hold on scuff was that present today
not as president as usual yes definitely
yeah thank you no problem
thank you for appreciating i'm sure
there's some some among us who are a
little bit tired of this among us game
but uh i think with proximity voice chat
mod it made it a whole lot more
interesting and kind of refreshing so
yes
yes definitely it was a blast i'll kill
you we could do this sometime again
yeah i want to do this again this is so
fun i don't mind hell yeah
yeah with everybody do it yeah
[Music]
one more thing i kind of want to do is
like because i organized the en id mario
kart tournament now that we are
11 years we could do the full en mario
kart tournament
can we do races with 11 people like not
12 by 11 is it just one of the one of
the people are gonna be bots is that
what it is
yeah one of them might be a bot i think
or you can just leave that one out i
think oh okay
okay
[Music]
is it time for another training arc for
mario
let's do it let's do it time to unlock
all the parts well it is uh past 5 a.m
for me so i hope we can yeah
[Music]
um i have an announcement for next
weekend that we will be having another
lab
yeah
what for help yeah
[Music]
yeah the halloween collab
details are secret for now but uh yeah
now you guys mark it down lock it down
exciting your calendars boys girls and
friends
yes i need to report yeah
the organizers amazing not even directed
to the pun i'm just really saying it's
genuinely going to be amazing
amazing
council to hope and oh english let's do
english
okay three
two
one
[Music]
we're ending our streams right yeah okay
bye
oh i love that thank you
darkness will fade away
light will guide your way
hope has descended and you are not alone
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
your darkness
i'm here
[Music]
[Applause]
i was a pretty good imposter today
wasn't i
council keller let's go
virus