[Music]
do
hello hello hello hello hello
welcome how are you guys
welcome to the stream hello
uh it's been a while since the last fire
emblem stream
since i i i had to fix some things
since the last time and i moved from one
place to another place
and actually then i moved to another
place
i moved two times since the last
uh fire and palm street
and yeah
but oops now
i think everything is stable at least
for a little while
[Music]
everything should be stable for for the
meantime
and i have finally returned to play
fire and blam
[Music]
and i will try to stream
quite long today
we're like still at the very beginning
of the game i've only done
one real battle like one real battle
which actually went fine if you guys
remember
so the last time i tried doing fire
emblem i
did not save because we didn't really do
anything
so we should start off
anyway i privated those streams anyway
and that's why i also reused the
thumbnail
because i didn't want to have the
thumbnail go to waste
thank you for the new members and thank
you for the super chats by the way i
really appreciate it
and also maybe
you made me out of the cat that is true
i did that
it was like in between my legs too maybe
today
during the stream we might
reach maybe 300k
subscribers
itself
here i am again
and i i really haven't played this in a
while so
i i actually yeah i feel like my memory
of the game is not so much
there anymore
but let's continue shall we
fight for idol god
here we go story time
i think this one we saw before muchu
in the mist what mutiny
uh is the audio too loud do you hear
audio
is
okay a little low that's better that's
better than too high let's leave it
there
i like this little little um storybook
storytelling chapters in between
okay please bear with me i might have
forgotten a lot of things
by she's behind me now
yo yo yo
yo
but someone said i can jump too how can
i
how can i jump oh
it's okay we saw some of this last time
but we really didn't make any progress
so whatever
someone's birthday is coming up wasn't
it ferdinand
oh wait
you guys
uh at my at my most energetic state
right now gotta drink some dr pepper
what
[Music]
foreign
what did she just say in the end i
didn't read it
grab that ferdinand wasn't it fernand or
the other guy the other a servant
sylvain
yeah yeah yeah yeah my orange hair
friend
yes you're very welcome let's have a
talk later
let's drink something together
okay so here we go
[Music]
what so i think i read this before but i
don't know what it says
[Music]
oh okay so what what
i guess we're going to go i think last
time i did the
seminars first did i
but then i think some people said don't
do it yet or something but i did it
anyway
should i just go exploring first okay
i don't know there was some reason why i
should go exploring first and then
and then i was so surprised last time
that you're actually in my room what the
hell
well we should talk
the last time i said i had forgotten
this time we said i should have listened
more intently
yeah this time she likes it
i love you selfies
okay so first we do some exploring
and some fishing and so on because uh if
i if i saw it correctly
then we have a bit what
we have a fishing event and [\h__\h]
was there something here now
wow wow uh and last time
i said i wanna i wanna marry uh
one of mary's office and people keep on
hinting to me
i saw your hints guys i read too much i
like comments and stuff and people
people try to tell me that it's not
really
not really easy or not possible
i'm not sure but i'm gonna try anyway
oh thank you for the super jen you're
gonna sleep okay
you are welcome to watch the archive
later
don't worry about it this is why i
always prefer to
to watch archive myself
no okay so ah yeah last time we went in
here first
we checked out our our seeds
okay harvest
take that those vegetables professor
level up
nice plant
oh whatever i i don't care
i don't care but take this
very carefully selected seeds indeed
then cultivate with some
poor hermit water
and bye and then we talked to this cutie
pie
yeah you know what right now
uh probably they don't i won't have to
have these flowers here
but like in in this season
right now in japan
there's these red spider lilies
in season have you ever seen those
before guys they look so
so
i've never seen them in any other
country before
you don't know them oh google google red
spider lily
i wonder if uh if they exist
in other countries i already already
seen like people taking photos
with the with those spider lilies
online let's do some fishing
hello wait i should let me take that
first
wow
oh yeah i think it signifies death
does it how do we fish again
oh i wasn't supposed to well when was i
supposed i was supposed to ah
yeah perfect but that uh how do i see if
it's a rare fish again
we don't have enough bait what what
where's my bait
where's on my bait pawn snail there we
go that's bait right
here
you have a quest bring it up
bring in some reinforcement the
reinforcements along might give you an
advantage in battle try talking to the
battalion guild master it
ah okay i guess so just have to talk to
someone right
no problem oh they're so adorable
huh
can i fish again
okay now let's give me a good fish
no ah wait was it the red one that i was
supposed to
react to is it a red one or something
else
ah that's oh [\h__\h] damn it i think that's
it
it was the red one god damn it
ah see it's been such a long time i
don't remember
oh wow oh well
does she not doubt that is there
anything above red was there not a
golden fish or something
damn it
[Music]
don't know what you're talking about i
don't wanna i don't wanna
waste too much time with dialogue this
time
because uh what
what am i doing cooking together oh yeah
why not
we did that last time because i wanna do
some progress today i mean i i totally
enjoy like
playing this game like slowly um but
[Music]
we want some progress
i have to look otherwise i don't know
when you're done talking
wow thank you bernie she's so
cute okay that's that
now i think we can eat with someone
oh yes edo guide and
i think last time i did also the same
thing i want to eat with
lis lisi lis lai sifia how do you say
her name i wonder
let's share a meal itadakimasu
they're they're like the cutest girls in
the game
i want to eat pancakes today today
pancakes with like berries and ice cream
i really want to eat something sweet
right now
yeah that is that it can i talk with you
no
[Music]
yes yes when you drop something on the
floor and you it's uh it hasn't passed
three seconds yet then you can still eat
it even if it's like dropped in the mud
no problem
hmm
okay i think we're done here
is that a bait poultry
oh wait where did we go
let's follow the red the red sign
i feel like you guys remember when i had
like some
audio crackling too i feel like i even
figured out
how to fix that figure out so many
things
you know you just gotta step by step
some things don't work maybe but then
you figure out everything
eventually and ow
yo bird bunny uh leonie hello leonie
orange hell buddy
[Music]
you can open the game capture window but
you can even open the sound capture
window i don't know
but once i open that even though without
opening it place the sound but
when you open the sound
capture thingy then it actually will
stop to capture the the crackling sound
i feel like it did that like instantly i
opened up the sound capture window
and then it's gone
hello there top fishing spots eh
whoa what
is that just like
sorry i'm not really reading the text
right now
anything else here now i kind of have
no plan maybe
first the other one
[Music]
how do you know how did you know
to learn the various troubles plaguing
the people of the monastery
to help solve them all you'll have to
become close with many different people
okie dokie
yeah so many quests
she's so hot it's just sexy
there's always so much to do
we back
when did that just happen
weird oh well sylvain sylvain i want to
tell you about
since you and i will love girls so much
you know there's a girl called
calliope murray she's so beautiful she's
so hot
oh you gotta check her out someday but
remember she's mine okay
felix uh
who was felix again maybe he's at the
training ground
oh i didn't i don't know
no problem you're looking for a guy not
for a girl are you sure about that
the way i know you you must be looking
for
a girl no
oh
horses
wait where's that thing that i just saw
i hear
oh horsey oh hey marianne
did you also not get so much sleep
tonight again
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
that's so nostalgic oh my god
give me g did you have anything to tell
me
[Music]
let's go to the red to the red sign
where is it how do i get there
how do i see that the big map is there a
big map
it must be here straight okay
said r ah i forgot
i forgot so many things
let's go
hilda where's hilda i heard hilda is
here
plus one plus five
oh plus one plus one plus five plus two
which one should i go
by the series holy monks
oh damn
there's so many different patterns what
stride strike what what stride with
stride
let's try it at this one
[Music]
you get a job then you get a job and you
get a job and you get a job
replenish what does replenishing mean
[Music]
i can heal them a battalion whose
endurance is reduced to zero will
withdraw
providing no benefits until the
replenished uh until replenished at the
battalion guild
[Music]
okay
huh
nice okay we now have two
i have two on edelgard oh
since you're a girl after all but in the
translation it says since you're a
professor after all
interesting translation choice
i wonder why they did that
some people said they want me to point
out these mistakes but they usually
don't pay so much
attention
okay what next talk to this boy
gatekeeper
creme de la creme
yeah why do you guys like gatekeepers so
much
did i talk to everyone oh no
what's so special about kevin
i heard you the creme de la creme
[Music]
i'm a force of nature
it's an overstatement i'm i'm not yeah
no no no no
that's not true that's not true thank
you for the super dad
yo bird you look like you're out of
here
maybe she secretly likes girls
train with me no
okay ah ferdinand we didn't talk to my
boy ferdinand
hello where's my boyfriend
is that him what does he look like again
that owl scared me eh
he looks like god
and where is he
[Music]
why can't he be here too is that still
the same map
it should be right his name is ferdinand
von aykiel
[Music]
try the classroom yeah see i'm in a
different place now
right where is he
i want to talk to my lord and savior
he is that
hello
the classroom is he shouldn't he be here
mostly moss is this a different area
again
no
are you guys talking about ferdinand
when i care
yeah i can't find him is it okay if i
don't talk to him
maybe some somewhere else again
there should be someone here too
lawrence a very german name again
i didn't talk to you either be on your
uh what am i like blind or something
oh you have to talk to ferdinand pandaya
so you can remember foreign
you don't trust the western church what
about the southern church
well i mean i guess that's that seems to
be it i can't find the others
oh god
there's some cute girls here
hello oh
god damn it i wanna sing
hello
you're like thinking way too negative
you're already thinking of the death
of this dude why why why why why
calm down someone said ned to me
no stop where is everyone
[Music]
oh
whoa whoa you're covering up the statues
with the text how am i supposed to look
at it
it's you
[Music]
where's everyone why can't i find anyone
yeah are they sitting here
where are all the cute girls there's a
ingrid and this is
please let's slice twice if y'all
may be here does that still count as the
same place
that are to make it ah
i guess there's one oh yeah one is here
ingrid hello english
that's it did she just give me a
question
i didn't know there's a big is that said
all right
now i finally figured out how to see the
big map
cute
[Music]
just like me you would never get lost
obviously
why is that uh why is there such a
sparkling
thingy go away
yep
would you like to read a note from the
advice box
[Music]
each month people will proud approach
the console with their concerns select
responses that satisfy them
oh and your support points will increase
okay
what 30 seconds when i was in the
greenhouse early a female student
fled from me as if in terror why did she
do that i was only tending the flowers
scout what does that mean goddammit
try making small talk
but you are indeed very scary is not
satisfied
then find your own answer
oh that was a quest oh nice
oh can i do this anytime yeah
find your own answer if you're not happy
with my answer then why did you ask in
the first place huh
there's a lot of people here who want to
talk to me
[Music]
okay who wants to talk to me here
wooden flask spotted eat nuts
nuts
that's like the same questions
breathtaking you say that seeing me
[Music]
indeed i must agree
i must agree i'm indeed breathtaking
[Laughter]
hello ah wife
number two
[Music]
you're breathtaking thank you thank you
chad
thank you for the super chat
oh good night
[Music]
i can't do the big map i guess because
it's so small
okay someone is here the monk wants to
talk to me
okay
i wanna fight i wanna battle
when are we going to battle we just do a
little bit more talking and then we
teach them some stuff
because i'm a professor okay
now why does everyone want to go to war
says the person who just said i want to
battle but
yeah for what
[Music]
oh no oh god damn it
god damn it can't do it right now
damn it
one more thing here
monastery and find it for him you should
try looking near the captain's quarters
that gel this occupant
[Music]
i already picked it up
use the gift option to increase your
support points but with others by giving
them things they like a gift
will also increase the ali's motivation
okay you may sometimes find lost items
around the monastery
use the last item option to return them
to the honors and
increase support points as with gifts
and ali's motivation will also increase
okie dokie will do
i pick up everything i see that's what i
gotta do right
no problem
okay one more person over there
hello who's here
thomas do you want to talk to me thomas
sensei
she can be difficult eh really
oh man that's a lot of information i
don't think we want that right now
did you just army okay
i think here we are done
manuela has a quest for me when i have
activity points again
then we try one last time to find
ferdinand from ayakia
oh my god but which one of those dots is
he
act one with one with the dots
one of the dots alrighty there's one
with dots here
you were there all along
is
it will guard should we give this to
idle guard
by the way where is it okay did i speak
to idol guard today i only ate with her
[Music]
good luck with that she seems very
strong
hello logan's i was also looking for you
nice
abuse of that kind is no better than
slavery a proper noble most guarded
people from centuries when you think
i don't want to really give you anything
do i have something that belongs to you
i don't think so
oh i see one more one more person wants
to talk to me
lawrence is a good boy really
well what makes you say that
okay something is here
are you
okay are we finally ready no way does he
still still want more
me
they all want to talk to me
i'm busy i got so many duties okay
who is it this time
hello
[Music]
you're buying all the games that i'm
playing
nice
well what what what did the conversation
give me huh
okay are we done
hmm seems so this is my room right
this is my room oh yeah as long as you
are in here it's probably my ring
you must try harder from now on
i'm trying monty kyle
okay so
[Music]
what
looks the same
wait do i have any special outfits oh
yeah oh yeah but i prefer this
outfit anyway
how do we continue again is it written
here
ah finish exploring ow
yes
i think it's time for battle or first at
instruct
manually and then we battle i know you
all want to see some battles one one
more second
you know guide uh
[Music]
what are we teaching her again
axe and authority okay
good what's up farty again which one is
this one
one more and one more
perfect
hey wait wait wait it oh i have one more
session
we have one more authority
let's do ferdinand
it some budding towns are worth getting
it what you mean
some other that that are not recommended
oh he's almost full
good job good job pregnant
but some more
and some writing for the future
i think that's it
so i can only do this with the smileys
right
uh he's reason and authority
reason
there you go there you go
wow
and authority really authority
all right i guess
and that was weird
is really useful
reason and faith all right we shall
teach you about reason and faith let me
tell you
the only thing you need to believe in
is the kfp
empire i don't have enough all that
that's it right we can lecture
goals i think we've done we did our also
set grip tasks before so we can just
leave those
no let's do it
okay oh guys i added some new uh
emotes yesterday some
text emotes and one angry emote
and the kfb bucket so whenever i say kfb
kfb you can go and spam that bucket
been trying to i've been trying to win
the heart of this girl oh me too
i know what you're talking about but
none of the fancy gifts or sweet things
i tell her have worked
do you know any secret dating tricks
that i can use to win her height
[Music]
i think both of these are good
but for your for your specific
case i would say stay away for a little
while
[Music]
you're welcome always ask me for advice
on how to get girls just ask me
i'm really good
you know what again you yeah what
you know jousting is a popular sport in
fairgrounds the ladies love a guy who
can joust
speaking of let's polish up my writing
and land skills
huh
no
yes no yes okay
good luck with that
hope no one says no one is sleeping in
my classroom
lauren's birthday whatever whatever take
it
is there anyone who would not like
flowers
oh the hairy horses again
next time we gotta change the thing
bam
i think we're finally ready for some
battles my friends
wow i won't forget all i've learned
well you definitely have a better bigger
brain than me i forget everything in
three seconds
i really like but she's in love with the
apprentice of death how should i
approach her
do not approach me
do not
you can work for me
okay i think the only thing oh wait what
about certifications
should i should we go to battle or to
certifications
oh are you approaching me
[Music]
yeah don't i don't quite understand this
fighter i guess
this intense music for studying
oh wait was that the wrong one
oh wait i thought i was doing this for
idle guard
you got that man
that luck eh
i didn't want to do that it's fine
no but if i choose no
then what did i do this for she passed
yeah i guess she did was that not so uh
was that weird do you play read visual
novels ah no i don't
you mean visual novels are the ones with
with the
with the like text and the pictures i
mean i did play
one or two before i'm just gonna go with
yes
i passed yeah i actually thought i was
doing this for idle guard for some
reason
feminine okay so
oh i was really not supposed to pass huh
so for him
do we do soldier it seems uh
makes more sense
okay how do you guys know
i mean it did say like not a red text
that's like his
past um
petra seems like she'll be a mermaidian
you better pass nice
then the music is so dramatic i have
success
yes
okay that's it let's go battle
so we did this one right or did we not
it did we do this one
i think we did now we're gonna do this
one
battle in the mountains
i didn't save now i saved
let's go let's go let's see how much
i've forgotten
i know we need to stay together
i know i should have some of the other
members
do the finishing blow
what do i do here though
um do i do anything
switch your units okay
but like oh i don't want you in here
i don't see this
how do i get a different one now bring
them out oh okay okay okay
okay fight i already saved
you guys keep on saying save even though
five seconds ago
in front of your eyes i saved
every time you're like save save saves
it but already saved man i already saved
and you just saw
it how many times do you want me to save
say it again okay
what the hell okay fight
let's go route
the enemy let's go
play a face
okay so there's some people here there's
some people here there's some people
here
how do i see like a can i see like a
bigger version of the map
oh my god oh we are in two teams
yeah oh yeah we are into teams
oh damn it was that was i supposed to
like choose
who is on which side or no
what does even what does route the enemy
even mean
where am i supposed to go can i just
battle in two teams
or like i bring them over to one side
destroy oh it needs to strike oh well
okay
well now let's go
let's see if i remember
you guys told me i need to like wait for
them to
come to me but i don't wanna
uh wait what was second a bracelet
i forgot how it works it wait
wait wait how does it work again
how do i sing how did i see it
wait she's a fighter now i gotta use the
axe or no
ah this is what i want to see and then
uh wait how do i switch the attack
[Music]
could you change the camera oh sure like
this
ah oh
i can only do it with the sword ah
well let's just go for that then
rap strike
don't use skills too much okay
[Music]
here
my name is
convoy what was that again don't think
we needed
so what's going on on this side huh
you're so far away from the enemies
oh let's come here to the front
oh damn it there's not like
i only have one close battle
guy here yep
rally
that is a a very um
sensitive team
oh my god casper is going to eh
is casper supposed to carry this team
you're stronger than this and show me oh
my god i gotta like heal you every turn
don't i
he's level one oh my god was i supposed
to like
change where everyone starts out
now i don't have permadeath active nice
fat and unfunded
let's finish that enemy off with bernie
or something
oh man everyone wants to everyone keeps
missing on
ferdinand
yes yes the pointy end indeed
oh nice i'm a bit scared for the left
side i'm really quite scared
survive you're strong
do i have a healer on my side oh god i
don't have a healer on my side
oh my god this team is strong but they
don't have a healer or a caster and this
team has like every
every caster every every
like everything but no real
good close you know
close fights person
but wait this is the healer right maybe
with bernie we do some
and she cannot yeah
oh she can uh-huh
come on bernie save this team
carry this team you're gonna like help
us out here oh okay well maybe the
caster can do something
this dude maybe oh really it's
you're also too far away how close does
she have to get
oh god damn it well i guess
yeah attack
oh i'll heal first
one to two tiles is he gonna be so close
not
[Music]
if he available he's gonna die
hey any better idea
go for it okay which one though does it
matter
smash don't miss
don't miss oh thank god
[Music]
i'm gonna wait for the rest to come to
us to be honest
so yeah
um
wait i hope that is not too much of a
stupid idea but
this team is so weak they have to come
to me i'm not gonna come to them
now let's move on here
that's a good idea okie dokie
[Music]
pilot let's do some fighting
oh i didn't even check my skill
i did not check my skill oopsie
[Music]
oh you need some you gotta heal yourself
vulnerability
oh there's an enemy right here
okay let's do this it'll finish him
nice
okay sylvain
let's go get this dude shall we
oh
another nice kill hmm
level up congratulations
nice song okay fairly non fun
i agree let's go fellainand
oh yeah 10 past lands here we
go bam
not bad not bad radio can i am ready
none from ikea
oh don't get too close oh [\h__\h] pastor
casper survive no don't hit me again
goodbye my friend so now we only have
a long distance attack beeps left
oh my god ah this grip is
weak
oh damn it
what did i hurt your ears did i scream
too loud well
a healer uh archer a caster and a caster
and they got like a [\h__\h] ton of enemies
in front of them
oh my god even that dude
are they gonna get wiped
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
move in move in the caster
fall back
uh fall back hmm
[Music]
um
it
do you have a choice the trees are
trees oh well
i'll get in there next time
okay you go in here
and you go in here
wait but can they can they not attack me
when i'm in the trees
[Music]
nani nani
we just gotta do our best to go with
this team over to the other side is that
possible you gotta go uh go all the way
here home
oof okay this means
we have to move forward there's no other
choice
we have to move
wait
let me then let me go here and then
attack him from behind
does that have any effect by the way on
on
like if i attack someone from i know
they look at me
right away that would have been cool if
it had any effect
we gotta move forward we gotta save the
other team before they all
die and get wiped
what what are you saying
wait is there no other way to get there
no
okay uh
death is coming dab is coming
no no no no benny
nice bernie
survive ha ha ha ha
stay alive stay alive
okay bernie this is okay we can still
heal you don't worry we all got your
back
oh
oh bad enough fun
we'll be fine
i'll kill you for that stupid piece of
[\h__\h]
i'll kill you
look at us
you killed ferdinand
my room feels so hot right now
divine pose now we're gonna we're not
gonna be
like that we gotta move on this is
this is a challenge we will survive
you guys remember the first the the
training battle
where i had like what one unit left or
something i don't know it's always a
struggle but
we will do it no this is not with
permadeath it's all fun
bernie run run what
what what what
[Music]
are we back are we back hello
moshimos i just killed one enemy i don't
know if you saw that but bernie killed
one enemy
we should be back don't know why that's
happening
hide your ass
assist physique what's the difference
between physic and heel
[Music]
yeah i can't see it because my head is
in the way
ah huh
what is physics ah physic is range tail
okay please heal bernie please
for the love of god we need bernie so
much
sorry for the small disconnects but only
small disconnects i think
it's not that bad can you attack this
dude or
oh
oh well you can thank god
come on please wait are they gonna
oh [\h__\h]
oh
thank god say bye
oh god no no not bernie what the hell is
wrong with you
why you gotta pick on bernie mastered
skills for noble
oh nice not i mean
bernie
okay you will regret
what you have done to my baby girl
[Music]
bastard
pain pain makes bernie stronger
man i know how that feels yeah should we
finish him off with
bernie again or not we do we know
dorothea if she can
but she gotta go
[Music]
nice okay
he shall attack it is there a chance
he'll die
[Music]
he'll be fine right he'll be fine oh
wait
nosferatu wins what's the wind then
hallelujah okay first wave first wave
is done and we have lost uh one link
of this weak ass team oh bernie
bernie you just stay there be safe
where are we here we're coming for you
to save you
um my wish
well
attack
ah battalion level up
[Music]
i can't do much right
they all gotta go behind uh violet
she's got the knight she's got the
knight
enemy face uh-oh
they keep coming they keep coming yeah
new emotes
use them use them thank you
don't do the mistake of writing danke
scheisse
that means thank [\h__\h] please write thank
you soon that means thank you
although i like that i like the the
sound of that but
can you attack him from where you are
yeah okay awesome
go hubert nine nine nine nine nine
[Music]
how about a heel for yourself wait what
yeah and
what i'm so confused
[Music]
can he not heal himself i'm confused
healers can't heal themselves
wha what
what that is ridiculous
what that that was ridiculous
he's an eye on them
[Music]
okay well i don't know i don't really
want to get closer to those
dudes but i also don't um
[Music]
do we have any should we just wait
stay in the trees okay ah i'm scared
[Music]
i
move forward
actually here's an item
i gotta buy more of these healing items
can i buy them at the marketplace
actually you could use a heel tool
whatever
oh human don't die don't die
oh [\h__\h] yes okay
[\h__\h] nine nine nine nine nine nine
it's indeed harder than i expected holy
[\h__\h] no no
okay bernie take it this one hit
save us
okay this side is fine i'm not worried
about this side
and
okay okay okay we survived this face
okay first of all heal him
i like that dramatic sound there
then yeah bye
okay how about
can you attack from that yeah or where
you should
uh what if she can one hit someone
oh yeah okay go for that dude
nice
[Music]
is almost dead oh nice
let's go for this one die
yes welcome to the membership thank you
for joining
[Music]
okay and you will finish him i hope
oh thank god
hallelujah we survived
the struggle the skunk nice
it was a good choice to stay in the
bushes thank you guys
we saved the bullion thank god
[Music]
thank god
okay now this side
did you go here the brushes are kind of
in the way oh yeah attack
uh huh
let's finish it off with petra maybe
what it did
i can't ah oh i can speed up the process
okay
wait i should some of them need some
healing
okay
you'll be fine as long as you don't miss
you'll be fine thank you for the shot
i had it coming i had it coming i had it
coming
[Music]
did she also miss did she also miss
against
it's fine it's fine it's fine it's fine
oh stage complete
we're done mvp by them
[Music]
oh thank god what do i do
what what do i do just wait
[Music]
well sacrifices have to be made
what game is this fire emblem three
houses
instruct manually shall we
it's all good again everyone is alive my
wife
and back okay don't mind it's just a
small small disconnect
and back
who do i uh
who else do i add to this
thing
[Music]
huh bernie
okay
and then instruct
let's see casper oh only casper and
sylvain
okay
axe and brawling well you died quite
early on the battlefield you definitely
need to learn some things well that's it
already
surveying you have survived i thought
ferdinand would
survive and you die but oh well man what
man of the people
skill goal is man of the people does
that mean lance and horse
lens and horse
all right i guess
no worries yeah ah it's all right as
long as it's just such
a short disconnect so i'm not too
bothered by it
horsey i i won some
when i was a young young phoenix i
i went to like a horse camp for one week
before
yeah but only that one time i wanted to
do it again and again but
horse riding is kind of expensive kind
of an expensive hobby
so i could never afford it after that
what do we do do we do more lansi
[Music]
yeah it's really expensive but i have
like uh
one or two friends actually right now
maybe only one friend who has a horse
but she's like people who own horses
they're like so
uh how do you say they're so
um they're like don't touch my horse
they're like really really connected
with their horses
and really uh emotionally attached to
them
yeah protective yeah yeah yeah so
usually they they won't let you ride
their horse
but i understand i mean it's expensive
to own a horse in the first place
i get it but i want to ride a horse too
oh speaking like i think it's fine now
yeah begin lecture
huh another must know how to ride a
horse yeah we're talking about it just
now to be certain and should know how to
wear the lens
as that is the most obvious weapon of
choice for a writer oh really
i guess so yeah lanceland's writing
battle things yeah
as a noble among nobles it seems natural
that i focus on these skills i love this
guy
and so now he has focus on lands and
writing skills but now he wants to focus
on that on lands and writing skills to
act that's the same thing
let's do it whatever so same thing
ferdinand from
ikea
would like to speak with me it i'm sorry
that i
i'm sorry that i let you die so easily i
i mean you kind of let me down like
i thought you were not going to miss so
i'm i'm sorry
is it about something else
it's
[Music]
i fell for it what i don't know why are
you asking me
ah i fell uh i fell for it
eh i
i don't know doesn't really make much
sense
that is what you say when you meet the
maid of yourself
okay this
well i mean it
yeah it's like when when someone pranks
you
what is it what is it let me tell you a
good
good german word it's shy set
yeah you have something on your face
it's like a drawing underneath your eye
your cheeks are on your face oh my god
don't confuse her
i don't know you're enthusiastic i guess
[Music]
tell me about it
she just said in japanese i can't take
my clothes off
she just said in japanese she can take
her clothes off
hell yeah i would love to
she likes it
she just said in japanese come to my
room tonight
what is this translation mistake go be
more direct in english what the hell
i'll teach you some things privately
tonight
we don't need to speak we only
[Music]
is
is she flirting with me i i'm interested
in someone else though
hi hi i don't know me
hey bronx
what do you mean bottom left support
love is not seen
okay so even though i let her die on the
battlefield she really likes me she
wants to spend the night with me
wow i should let everyone die on the
battlefield if that's their reaction
good job girls i want to fly too
flying and horse riding best combination
ever
okay here we go every guy's birthday
what i want to buy her flowers for a
thousand gold not for 200.
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear educard
but i wanna buy uh no i i want to buy
the the vulneries
i have to buy them for for each member
well she has three out of three
she has none buy
buy ah i can buy them at three stacks
[Music]
vulnerability
bernie is like always getting hit let's
buy her some more
vulnerability
uh
oh you need also much vulnerary
do you have have you checked your
supports no what do you mean what are
you talking about
i guess that's all right
uh what else do i need get bernie a new
bell
true how do i get that again
what armory
and you guys said that
um the most expensive one isn't
necessarily
necessarily the one i want to get so not
steel but we should get iron because
steel is
there was a reason and i i forgot but i
i know i shall buy
iron
training sword is there nothing but uh
but i guess she attacks with magic
mostly so it doesn't matter um
mini bow bow is good
well she can have that too now she has
four
anything else maybe for him
iron lance or javelin
can't be thrown let's buy that [\h__\h]
and an iron lens hell yeah
sell bullions oh yeah oh yeah
and wait who has the bullion ah you have
one
cell this is a weird way to sell this
[\h__\h]
large billion nice
buy shields from the supply shop they
act as accessories for units
okie dokie do i need one for every unit
oh wait what where
item shop right no
no maybe just the front front uh
yeah yeah
let's get an iron shield wait i get oops
one okay awesome idle guard gets one too
uh-huh do i have to equip them
ferdinand take the iron shield
no need for shield
they reduce speed
uh ah well who should get one then
is it fine if it's only those two
fasteners shouldn't get shields like
petra
oh petra is a fast unit
means we're already so are they are just
too slow
thank you okay okay sword uses okay
and anything else i want to sell
[Music]
oh she has a letter shield oh
should i sell it
i had kfc today nice ah
i only ate something small today like a
small bread i wanna eat something
ah give the letter shield to petra okey
dokey
oh i think for now let's find out
then let's explore yes
selfish it's office
hello you must try harder for me you
told me that last time
is that the only thing you can tell me i
love you
so cute
okay where do we go where do we come
from where do we go
cotton angel
and ah
hey no one really wants to talk to me
why do they not want to talk to me
i thought it was always gonna be like so
many is it not always that many people
who want to talk to me
i can't see it maybe it's better if i
put myself here
where
[Music]
only once a month ah oh that's actually
good like because
that took so much time mission
assistance
do we want her to join yeah sure
thank you i wanna oops up
i mean i mean i do want to record you
but not right now
yeah yeah sorry sorry sorry what
but like i'll skip or something
riding boots she likes riding right so
if they give her writing boots
she'll be happy right
is she a healer she's a healer
take it you're welcome i love you pretty
girl
bye bye bye bye
wait now i should be able to do the
manuela quest right
marianne is a badass swordmaster she's
not supposed to see
let's see if he is way better as a
healer or what
i'm going on both of them is there a
maximum of
recruitments i can do i feel like i read
somewhere before that there's no maximum
here
just teach me
i would say sword right
let's go
i can get the whole school on my side
nice
why did she give me carrots and cabbage
i want chicken
oops no bye bye bye bye and
yeah well is that already it
is
what is that that time that
time thing is supposed to mean
oh planting and eating oh that's right
that's right
where's the dining hall
half a carrot pickle actually i really
like carrots
today's special but now i'm in the way
again
[Music]
i shouldn't always eat with the same
people right
petra already loves me hello
um i wanna eat this cutie
i mean is catherine gonna stay here or
is he gonna leave again
pick those who have no motivation
this peeps this you mean this free
thank you for the super chat thank you
i will read every super chat at the end
of the stream again
oh i fought
it wait so the the smileys mean how
motivated they are
and uh the arrows mean they would like
the food huh
ah but then still i should take someone
from here like
because they like the food right okay
well maybe catherine because i've never
ate the food before before
and
huh
of the heat of food
well you i guess
casper is sad oh well oh well
oh but i wanna eat with girls
among the three of you grew stronger
hell yeah
i can't argue that logic i'm sorry
casper
i'm sorry maybe i can cook something
with him no
no okay who wants to teach me cooking
this time let's see this
invincible
strength for the rest of the month let's
do it
did i use up my activity points now
do i have no more activity puns no
[Music]
no where do i see my activity points
again
[Music]
he seems fine
on top of screen are the zero
okay i wanna go fishing
i know no actually no i want to go
planting and then we
continue i guess with the story or the
fighting or whatever
hi petra
tonight right tonight konya
i'll see you tonight
actually like i really think she's hot
i do i do see quite the charm in her
uh yeah
she is hot
okay am i am i ready i think i'm ready
hi rubble oops no no no
no food yeah one foot two
what what's going on why is it so gold
why is it so gold
it's golden hey ah hey
[Music]
what do i do with that can i do it again
wrong face
i got them in
ground sell it for gold ah
okay can i do one more
give me a red fish are they gone now
blue
blue i guess i oh damn it i missed
my reflex just pushed a ah
oh god damn it okay one more time
blue
blue okay i'll take it otherwise it's
gone completely
excellent excellent excellent
wait caledonian crayfish i think we can
do one more time
do
[Music]
was there only one golden fish in there
yeah fish gotcha
why was it still going i thought it was
only like three times
okay bye bye
what do i do with the fish oh i never
looked in here
i wanted to do something with you
actually
i want to i think unequip
and then give you the other one right
wait how do i give you the other one
ah support
that's so cute and with this music in
the background i feel like they're going
to start kissing
please don't shoot any birds at all
[Music]
never settle for being the bird
beat the arrow instead
i'm not birth and arrow
what wow that was that wow that was so
deep i i learned so many things
i learned so much
[Music]
foreign
calm down bernie calm down no panic
always come
[Music]
hey ferdinand is so sweet
well i mean i also generally prefer to
stay
in my home
did you guys have an image of me that i
would be the one like who loves to go
outside i wonder
did you guys think kiara is the type of
who loves to go outside and have fun
probably you all have that image yeah
right
um it depends
uh on where i am i guess
depending on the country there's so much
more fun things to do
outside and i've i've lived in
[Music]
i've spent my life in more than one
country and uh
i have to say depending on which country
i am in i prefer going
outside i prefer staying inside and also
right now
of course you're supposed to stay inside
and i wanted to do so many things this
year
but um i had to to pretty much give up
on
all of them but now i have whole life so
there's also no need to go outside
i'll just stay inside forever but i mean
being able to you know work from home
like this
is such a dream come true
you know
how the [\h__\h] did you just spray your
waist fell in
wrist ferdinand you're stronger than
that how did you do
he'll protect you trust him
he's a good protector
okay bernie who do you want to talk to
petra okay
[Music]
oh yeah thank you two would get along
well
why why are you facing her with your
back
she talks she's talking so much
in japanese but the english translation
is just like i do not have that no
she just said i only have two eyes in
my head i don't have eyes in my back
not on my blah blah and i i sensed your
aura in the back something like that she
says
that was the translation so
indeed
me oh they're really weird those two are
really weird and awkward
foreign
yeah yeah this is not how you tell
people to be friends yeah uh
what a weird conversation petra needs to
have get some more social skills for
sure
okay anyway um
[Music]
how do i uh did they just automatically
re
re-equip the lava shield i want to give
her the other shield
treat no i don't know
maybe on maybe when we are like on the
battlefield
what else do we do i think we can
move on mo balikana
what's next oh instructions
oh instruct let's do some quick
instruction
instruction only petrol okay
petra my friend in bed
let's teach you some flying let's teach
you some sorting
you're welcome the more there you go
wow yeah i'm such a good teacher
i have i'm teach i teach you all the
things
people are calling me a thief but i
would never be doing bad things
it is because i'm moving very quickly
without my enemies noticing this is why
i must be learning the bow and sword
focus on sword and both skills to access
the fifa assassin
what about the flying though what about
them no wow you guys are very strict
some say yes i'm saying no no thief
i mean i feel like she fits like design
wise the role of a thief
but what about flying i was teaching her
flying
he hasn't both are good
[Music]
i like how the the new emoji is getting
a
good use out of this what a we had a
great also good job
[Music]
okay
what's next fighting oh another weekend
exploring this time we should we shall
sing in the core
yes okay this is the first thing we do
where do we do it again
uh probably the cathedral yes
let me sing
[Music]
let's see how this works oh
i want to sing with hilda but i guess
dorothea would gain some
motivation from that
i can choose more than one oh 39
okay let's sing beautiful friends
yes
[Music]
let's go
yes nice singing i didn't hear anyone
sing except myself but okay
if you call that singing
[Music]
we need a karaoke stream again soon but
as you maybe know i'm
streaming from my manager's pc right now
i feel kind of embarrassed doing a
karaoke stream in this situation
oh no actually wrong yeah i'm using my
manager's internet but my pc
yeah yeah yeah i brought my pc over but
i currently don't have internet in my
new
house so
yeah i don't have internet
what what does that arrow mean on the
right the the
the the orange era
yeah i don't know i don't have i only
have like my portable wi-fi right now
but that's not good enough for streaming
upvote orange era is more effective
but do i want to go for people who are
already in my
team or for people who are not in
recruited yet
for people who are going to recruit in
the future maybe
but i've already eaten with her so many
times so maybe
hilda i think i also ate with mercedes
before maybe
okay
so one for my team and one from not
recruited yet
although i feel like i've eaten with
hilda before too
oh yeah [\h__\h] i cannot even recruit hilda
from what i've heard
ah goddammit that was a waste
ah although i mean everyone told me
about that but then there was some
some other comments that said it
actually
actually you can but like how
there's there's a way
well well uh can we do one more thing
one one activity point well then let's
cook something and
[Music]
wait do we get this skill for the rest
of the month for the rest of the week
because we already got plus one strength
for the rest of the month does that get
like
switched out if i cook again uh more
meals oh i can eat more than once
oh
are the special i can only eat once
and the full menu i can eat any time
oh you know i really don't know who i
want to recruit in the future
but
who do i want to recruit
[Music]
maybe these two
mercedes what does mercedes do
all right let's do this tour oh wait
where's [\h__\h]
should we do this too
ah she's a healer what does annette do
oh okay
let's go ah she's a mage
benny what does she wait what are you
eating are you eating lasagna
i want lasagna ah
oh man now i really really really want
some lasagna
i wonder i wonder if there's any place
where i can have lasagna here
yes okay
i think we're done with the free time
right
sorry if i made a mistake but i think
we're fighting now
you're curious to know how bernie
leather is doing go for a visit i guess
sooner
or later
how do i know which one belongs to which
wait does it does it does it disappear
after the month
you missed a few things god damn it
what's going on
uh yeah i mean but some like one item
said something like idle card but
some others didn't say much
you still have the last time okay okay
okay it won't disappear okay okey-dokey
then let's do it next time
ah oh oh so if you try to give it back
and it does not belong to the person
you just get it back and keep on looking
um
oh she's cute what's that you singing in
the greenhouse eh
what's she singing
[Music]
unmarried
and she's like so chaotic chaotic energy
okie dokie end of the month that was
quick
hey it's all about already been two
hours it doesn't feel like i've been
streaming for two hours
more music on heist instead
i will continue our marketplace fix the
weapons
but someone said that right now it's not
really worth fixing my weapons yet oh
yeah i have not
unlocked it so that's that
and but wait some something else
check sort of oh yeah
hmm
oh bye love
what
we we don't want her to do that right
do we chances of passing hundred percent
hundred percent
do it
we just gave her a different class my
other call
wait can once i do this
is she automatically a mermaid then like
can i keep on switching and stuff
she'll quit like crazy oh hell yeah
but isn't that like supposed to be
especially swift with high avoidance
so isn't that like a faster class who
shouldn't be wearing uh
oh you can switch okay well let's just
do it
but if i want to switch do i have to
like do this certification thing again
or can i just do it anytime
passed
do i want to
[Music]
yeah i think that's it
okay mission
your house must help the knights of
saras suppress
lord lornada's rebellion at castle
gaspard
though you're told to not not to expect
combat the deep fog at mcdread
way back that way sets you ill at ease
so
they tell us we'll probably not fight
but we'll probably fight huh
well here we go
buy torches here i'm saving okay guys
don't tell me to save again i'm saving
training vows for units with nowhere
okay okay i think
they all have one though
[Music]
what are you talking about
damn nice sword
mega
foreign
oh story time
what the king of fergus was murdered by
the people of dusker
why was the king targeted
your child is like dead wake up chad
suddenly they're all awake
japan bros where are you at
okay
taking a second
wow what a surprise what a surprise
certain terrain will have effects on the
unit occupying at first for instance
razor universe evasion and defense move
your units to adventist terrain
and prepare to meet the enemy okay i'm
always prepared i'm always ready let's
go
let's try not to die we brought another
healer right
and the blue haired chick so we have two
healers
okay let's see map
where are we
what
where are they oh can i not see them
because of the fog ah
the one time i'm so smart to check the
map i just don't see [\h__\h]
no mommy in it
oh what do i do
torch is needed ah
[Music]
for everyone
it's in the convoy how does this work
just the people you have in the front
but they send it to the convoy
safe shut up i just saved
it i know what ah
does she have a full inventory ah
oh yeah buy little it's wow they're
expensive
600 gold taco
oh wait sorry you won't be in the front
bedroom
[Music]
uh and then we'll give one torch to
sylvain
wait how do i give the one in the convoy
how do i switch
inventory items
trade no ah
i don't get it item
trade
oh okay oh now i can take the
uh uh the iron shield
take ah
[Music]
yeah okay and
sylvain
you uh you can take a torch too
ah wait can i take one or do i have to
take like all of the three
i guess i have to take all of the free
okay equip it do i have to do one more
then do i have to equip it or is it fine
now
battalions
is already battalions fine
i could can i give him oh i can give him
a
battalion take that
it's fine okay well now save
our finish
do you need that not this one
planish
okay
now let's go units
oh yeah i want to bring with marianne
i have to let leave someone home huh
i mean she's a better heel than linhart
should i switch her out for lyn height
uh
the other way around ditch casper do you
think we need two healers
oh man i'm sorry casper
oh okay okay
okay
fight
map i already saw the map i already saw
the map i didn't see [\h__\h] because it's
foggy
cool safe
um
i already saved two times before the
battle
[Music]
wait for them to enter your field of
view okay love visibility maps
on battlefields with thick fog your
units will only be able to see enemies
that are close by proceed with caution
against movement will be cut short if it
is interrupted by an enemy
okay but i have torches you can earn a
reward if your allies do not suffer
heavy losses
does that mean if i do not have someone
die
be careful not to let your alleys flee
eh flee
[Music]
i mean fleeing use torch how how do i
use turrets
do i use torch
[Music]
what do i do do i use these
oh i cannot use them
eat torch what just use it
like items ah
now
should i have moved
move first okay
put how long does it
work
it counts as my action here
oh there's someone there
does she have a torch yeah
three turns is it really worth it
wait after this map no oh
hey i will never use it again
[Music]
um
okay
it's the only required map
with fog ah oh i don't have to do like
other maps that have fog yeah
ellie face already damn
oh that's what you mean with ellie oh
ally not alec
ah there's a fog maker okay
us see you in there i don't see enemies
accept that one
but i want him to come to me right
can i just wait just wait here
but can i tell everyone to wait wait
with one click or
do i have to really tell anyone
single-handedly
[Music]
gotta be aggressive this map what they
told me to like chill
just go way faster oh oh oh
where but where to this dude
okay i shall go
um
[Music]
into the fog oh
we'll see what happens but they're
coming at me anyway no
us
go can you heal green units oh i wonder
probably yeah oh they found enemies
well i'll just fight this dude but he's
like
ah range should i i probably should stay
with my allies though right
hey they went that way i wanted to go up
meanwhile
[Music]
i think i probably should go with them
god damn it well it's okay
california they're fine your eyes will
be fine you could split up okay can i
undo everything i just did
it can i undo
what i just did
[Music]
here
today bring them one healer
no go left ah
let's leave them one healer
from two groups oh okay
i'm so undecided
fine oh he missed
when they got some fancy attacks
but someone said kevin is fine alone
where did you come from
one percent it did i have one percent
chance of quitting and they actually
crit nice
you're doing great buddy thank you
ally face fight captain
and she's hot can i recruit catherine
would she be even that strong if i
recruit her too
would she be nerfed when i recruit her
she's strong
am i can't oh
let's try to get closer to her not on it
for [\h__\h] sake
yeah it'll guard kind of blocks off a
lot of people i want to have
indocard why you do this to me
[Music]
um
you can require her later it great
captain kyle
hey hey
i'll see why ah story thing i guess huh
hodo
[Music]
can we check from there no
um
[Music]
not bad okay we're
clear here there's no more enemies but
should we move on
up there where should we go i see
nothing
like the torch what did the torch even
do for me
i don't see [\h__\h]
[Music]
follow the world what road this road
oh wait there is a road
huh go left okie dokie
[Music]
did i just do the same thing
well now we're already close to that
group down there again
use a torch
again i'll waste it diving how many
times can i do it
are they carrying torches too
hmm
now i shall use it again ah
[Music]
i see them well then i guess you
just if she has it activated then i
don't need to activate it with everyone
else because now i already see so many
enemies
[Music]
i have seen what
needed to be seen i am
awake i'm woke
[Music]
stay safe there
nice
did you just one hit that dude
down
damn i have oh damn another one head
oh holy macaroni
[Music]
double crit
no damage what's to get we're so strong
what the hell
we're one hitting everyone
needs to be nerfed oh petra
my petra baby she got to stay alive so
we can spend the night together
and now that that's nothing like that i
don't think i
i don't think i deserve the child bottom
left if she invites me
if she she is bottom left okay
petra is bottom left like she invited me
to stay over
and get naked she actually said she'll
take her clothes off for me she did say
that okay
it's not me
oh maybe i should have used the weaker
attack and let someone else finish it
oh well
hmm
i'll leave this to you ferdinand from
iager go girlfriend
what
what thank you for the superjohn thank
you so much
you'll finish it in archive thank you
hope you enjoy it
later
yes oh wait
why are you taking care of that dude
oh kill my alleys oh
oh oh [\h__\h] he's almost dead
stay alive to the membership
she has a hot outfit damn
okay well i guess that should have moved
actually a little while
yep it i have one two one left here
okay i'm ready
is that dude so strong god we gotta help
him
is that okay are we fine
damn it they're not gonna flee right
because they talk to them about don't
let your allies flee
okay uh actually i think i should send
you someone to help now
oh wait you should probably shouldn't be
there
oops no yeah but
i'll send you some help uh how about
do would you like some sylvain now he's
so far away
oh they're also far away i'll send you
sylvain okay
take good care of him
uh he could even attack
oh
welcome to the live museum
welcome to kfp kfb kfb
kfb kfp
[Music]
can't you also attack from there no
what if we move her
here attack
yeah let's go
bernie nice
level up blood before nice bernie
the fog is lifting as a result ah it was
that dude
oh
what
dad what a cool cutscene
and the fog is gone
uh we weren't really the ones hiding it
was kind of
you but okay
you twist the story around the way you
wanted to
that's all right i guess
let's fight oh maybe it is
can i heal her right away
oh let's go there wait
where's my healer you are my healer
right
can you do like a healing thank you
weird game logic
fairly nand leading the team
as always carrying the team huh
whoops what
what you got here
why is edelgard so from the back oh look
at that dude maybe she can finish him
alone
now he can just try to follow me i guess
or
ah he's so far away
let's stay with the team ah
wait i didn't even get to move all my
units didn't i
it's not like a limited i thought i can
move all of them in every in every move
fairly nun's bag must hurt from caring
he deserves a good massage
go catherine
wow they look scary
let's go by left
let's go here and then have petra
i want to hide her in the bush oh well
wait
ferdinand go here
healer go here
[Music]
balance come closer yourself and not
bottom edo guide
come closer
oh this is moving
ah sylvain i wanted to send him down
there
is he even still necessary down there
and i invited marianne to join but she's
like all on her own the whole time
what did you bring me here folks she
must be thinking
what am i here for you don't need to
heal them yet they seem fine
okay
can you go here
she hasn't bad enough already
she's used to it yeah she probably
appreciated that
interesting interesting you guys seem to
know her well
this is the worst field trip school
field trip
yeah seems like uh oh no not
how dare you attack my snape
boy my slivering boy
what is that what is that effect
speed
[Music]
okay snape i said snape
um wait
you stay here assist and heal uh no
physic physic the [\h__\h] out of bailout
come on
a debuff and she can't move she can't
move it but she's surrounded anyway so
that's all right
uh you do him
now you haven't done much edelgard
in this fight but what was what was
gambit again
i forgot what gambit was is that
what does that do does it attack like
together
[Music]
let's do it special attack but not on
the 2 hp guy
stride gives me more movement
do i need that right now
let's just attack normally
ah [\h__\h] i want to check out the other
attack
oh no damage weak ass
boy
okay bernie you can finish it off again
do you want to finish it off bernie like
one of them
bernie's finishing off a lot of things
here
yeah bernie must be mvp this round
[Music]
a special attacks that can heal or
stagger opponents
wait a gambit's also something i can
change or
[\h__\h] i should have left her the basket
oh well
building on it
[Music]
okay just leave it to petra
okay
move wait actually
he could use some heel but oh well
okay let's go am i done
oh
[Music]
attacking bernie again
that's not fair oh my god bernie
look catherine going all in is she even
went
back home
okay they're not moving huh
well we gotta come at them
that's all right oops
building on oh he can't move oh [\h__\h]
god dammit ferdinand get your [\h__\h]
together
we need you oh you can also cannot move
can i get rid of that buff somehow
that debuff
next turn it's over it'll run out ah
okay
a debuff removal spell on some units
later now hold on
and wait am i not done i think i'm
just i can't just end it there
go make it end
missing i didn't really miss a lot in
this game
[Music]
by the way guys i i didn't do a members
only stream this week yet so i was
thinking
[Music]
maybe tomorrow
but tomorrow like we have to collab
stream
and uh oh there's only him left
tomorrow we have to collab stream
and uh i also wanted to do a normal
stream but um
should also do a also uh
i don't feel blight or blitzed obliged
do it every week really i'm not sure
because i wanted to do um
i want the next members only stream i
wanted to do either like a movie watch
along or a german lesson
but i don't feel quite ready to do a
german lesson yet because i want to do
some perfect
some more preparation for that but we're
also going to do some
more preparation for the collaboration
tomorrow
[Music]
again bernie damn
damn burning getting all the kills all
the bow broke
just do whatever you like let's do a
movie then
um for the movie i was actually also
[Music]
kind of waiting on something
so i'm actually also i know like
normally movie is like the easiest thing
oh is he strong
[Music]
that's not bad and that's the only move
he can do he's like
one against five million oh there's one
more down there okay well katherine will
take care of that
is there much more down there oh no only
one
well good luck my friend
i shall show you how it stands with my
wife edel guy
yeah yeah i wanted to lord of the rings
movie watch along with you guys
lord of the rings is on netflix isn't it
it is right so we can all i think
probably most of you guys have netflix
otherwise you can probably just watch it
somewhere else
extended edition entire trilogy in one
go
[Music]
big
no no no one movie per stream
well maybe i wanted to prepare something
for
that but maybe uh maybe it's fine
actually can you go here and attack from
there yeah
[Music]
yep
i wonder if netflix has the extended one
i'll check it out once we're going to uh
get into that
i don't even need to move all these
peeps july
seems fine i can just leave everyone
else in the on the field here
let's see what happens
here comes the horses what idol guard is
carrying
oh
is that all you got
attacking catherine you coward you fool
oh
damn
they be on the move
we shall finish
one one really
okay oh oh critical oh it's over what
the
what clappy clappy
nice
[Music]
did not suffer heavy losses so you
earned a reward
yeah only only one person died and from
that's from the allies allies right
nobody died from my side did they
or did oh wait did did ferdinand die
or was that a different battle
what goddess icon you can't carry
anymore it's like what is called this
icon
yeah well i guess the torch can be sent
to the convoy now
stage complete
ah that was a different battle okay the
pain is still so strong and so
deep deep in my veins that ferdinand
died
once that i feel like he died in this
battle
still not over it thanks for the efforts
of battle of all of your allies
motivation chris nice
say yokoyani
what kind of movies do you like oh
fantasy
adventure kind of movies or like movies
that are like
middle middle age medieval stuff or like
historical movies i also really like
like like on i i really like movies on
british history
i really love them um
um vikings recently
i'm like pretty much at the end of
vikings but
i don't know why but suddenly stopped
watching i'm not really at the end but i
stopped watching for some reason
okay i gotta finish
that's how it is
[Music]
you want to kill the gods you want to
eliminate the gods edogard
what the [\h__\h] yeah that's taking it a
bit far i would say but
since i want to be friends with you i'm
going to say agreed
i'm a good liar it seems
like
i guess we're eliminating god wait does
this mean we're eliminating surface i
feel like she's a goddess i don't want
to eliminate the surface
honestly i'm like really i'm really
undecided about that now
i was like in the beginning in the
beginning i was like i'm gonna marry
edelgard
but then i was like i'm gonna marry
sophis but then people are like
um that's not so possible
but now other girls feel more
interesting to me than edelgard
yeah there's too many i'm just gonna see
what happens
i mean marrying is not something
obligatory right
i don't have to marry oh
my students deserve the brains they're
fighting so hard
how do you say that and but well i mean
we'll probably marry someone i kind of
want to marry like
sophie's but i guess i but how yeah
some i read some people saying i i i'm
on the wrong route but how do i
i only had three route routes routes to
choose
i've already been like loki spoiler like
something about a church route route
route
don't tell me but it's not it's not
it's not completely impossible right
uh well i had i had a choice between
like three houses
i never had the choice to join the
church
root oh [\h__\h] church route
very hard
[Music]
i don't necessarily want to join the
church but if there's such pretty
leaders in the church
um you can count on us
[Music]
uh maybe we end the stream here for
today
i feel like there's like not much going
on today anyway
maybe we ended here i go eat and i do
the super chat reading in a different
uh stream because it doesn't i feel like
it's not so much today anyway
so i can just combine it with another
stream
lasagna i really want to eat lasagna
new month started right
that looks like a cult ritual
beautiful though beautiful drawings
[Music]
it just repeated the same thing in
japanese don't worry
all righty i mean we did some progress
but did like i personally feel like we
did some progress
i mean we did one month now didn't we
that was one month
am i still going too slow is it still
gonna take like uh
two years project like two years real
time for me to finish the game
one chapter per stream is good really
one month is
okay if that's good progress then here's
some flowers
casper you disappointed me today but oh
well
friday night okay we will end it after i
spoke to ferdinand
well yeah she's a good student
foreign
good that you mentioned again that
you're from a noble house thank you for
reminding me
fatty nan von ayer
well i didn't have the choice to say
you're superior
i like you though
yes demonstrate it
i can't stop you
[Music]
is he mad at me
okay okay i'm timeless i'm eternal so i
shall keep your time
oh he's gonna be scared and run away huh
i oh it was me it was me lasagna fans
thank you
oh yeah i guess it wasn't too bad he he
seems to
like me more now even though i feel like
i didn't make the best choices
it doesn't stop the game just did one
stop
[Music]
they want to steal from us
foreign
she's
oh
[Music]
um
hmm by the way you guys said i cannot
recruit hilda but what about
le la laisse fia lucifia it's
my birthday it's it's my birthday
i got a birthday gift from erdogan oh
oh oh i got so many things
i can okay and i want to i want to
recruit and marry
lots of fear every every every fire and
blam stream
i decide on a different wife
well uh how do i
how do i safe and
[Music]
sit how am i safe how do i save
[Applause]
what did i do
us well
did i i didn't say fred double save
better
okay everyone and thank you for coming
today and i hope you enjoyed the stream
i hope you enjoyed the progress
we will do maybe a fire emblem streams
weekly or maybe two times per week we
will see
and tomorrow is the collaboration on
gura's channel
and then actually after that the club
then is lifted
i have a i have a collaboration with a
senpai plant next week by the way
and tomorrow after the collaboration on
gura's channel i'll
i'll be doing some stream but i'm not
sure what yet either membership or
public i don't
i have no idea but now i shall eat
lasagna
[Music]
mina
wait is it is it one month
tomorrow or one month already today
since i actually isn't it like
in wait isn't it one month in three
hours for me
oh wait two days oh wait wait wait wait
wait wait today because i thought i
debuted on a saturday
but eh wait when did i debut
i've i have no idea how time works one
one two three it's exactly four weeks
for me now
eh
oh wait the ah i'm confused
i'm confused by the well it's almost one
month
yeah yeah yeah ah
in two days oh oh well
[Music]
i want to thank whatever for watching
today and
see you tomorrow or maybe if i'm
spontaneous maybe i'll do something else
later i don't know
i'm spontaneous you never know what to
expect from me
so thank you for watching and
uh let me check one more last thing
yeah i feel like uh
[Music]
i feel like possibly off stream we might
reach
300 that's kind of lame one i want to
reach that on stream
maybe i i'll think about something
thanks for watching and in german we say
auf wiedersehen
[Music]
so
foreign