[Music]
reflection going under confused
Obsession I still wonder if I was made
for you if I could only
see oh please oh make me up
person for you pretending
it's me
[Music]
soing want what I need oh do
you do
you follow through you purs but
now you sold me on a I to you up into
shreds I don't even know what to do with
this man tell me the be good
[Music]
play don't
do I'd be the king and queen of
new you to see I'm you you all of me it
seems like everyone wants it all around
running around on and on keeping me
captive Escape my way you say I'm way
too fragile I'm just your perfect Idol
break me sh
me you never see what I want what I need
oh do
[Music]
you you sold me on a mirage I to you up
into
I don't even know what to do with this
man tell me it be good play A Part my
[Music]
Mir
and you make me fall in love
[Music]
you me on a i you shred I don't even
know what to do with this tell me the be
good play A Part my
[Music]
Mir dis on and on and on this Mir
I'm part
[Music]