[Music]
This program is
sponsored by the following sponsors.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] Good
evening everyone, it's okay. The characters
are okay. Don't worry. I
decorated the Christmas tree.
[Music] There
were decorations.One year ago for Christmas,
all of us in English
made
them together.Oh yeah, on VRChat.At that time, we
put them up for fishing, and they looked like this
[Music]  I
feel
like I'd like to do this talk one day before Christmas
is a special interview feature for English-speaking countries.The
purpose is to
let overseas people know more about Japanese talent through live interpretation.
Spoiler wise, today's guest is an angel.
[Music]
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
It was postponed once, but I'm glad it
went well today1
[Music] It's
gotten a lot better compared to a week ago. Yeah,
at first I was
like, ``It's pretty good.'' It's
really good.
[Music]
Super Idol  Kanata-senpai
SS
No, that's
right.
Let's get started right away. You've
already introduced yourself, so I think that's fine.
Thank you, Senpai. Thank you very much.
[Music]  I'll
do my best with an English conversation book.English
conversation OKOkFrom my quiet birth and career
I
Englishconversation
What kind of things do you write?
[Music] There
are a lot of curves.Oh, I say that often.Huh?Is it
true that it's often said in English?It's
not Escape Famicom, it's
not Krysian.  Yes, that's English.
[Laughs]
OK,
OK [Laughs] Let's rely on each other.
[Music]
What are you doing these days?
Lately, I've been
playing games.  It
's still the same now, I'm practicing so much for that live on December 27th, and when I
buy it, it's a different world for the third anniversary live.I
was doing it, but it might be Tiara tomorrow.I'm glad you
told me that.Thankyou
Chiara-sensei.I'm
happy.Thank you,
Senkyu.  That's right. I was
practicing long tones, and I
heard that you're good at [music], but
I'm already practicing the longest long tones I've ever done.
How do you
keep your breath from becoming red when you make it last for 10 or 12 seconds? This
is Mr. Hodoshi.
[Music
] I wonder what kind of song makes it last that long. [Music]
I'd love to hear it.  Check it out
Hello, I'm curious
[Music]
Hello from afar
Yay
Hello
OK OK I wanted to show you this It's
amazing
Um
, there are people on camera, and there's a chicken on the camera,
and
staff.
[Music]
That's amazing, thank you for this. How did you
find Hololive in the first place and what made you want to join again?
[Music]
Hololive is about things like YouTube's
recommendation feature, Ack
Tan, Aqua-senpai, Marin,
and the captain.  I used to watch senpai and stuff like that,
but then I realized
that I really like Hololive, and if they
didn't stream it every day, it wouldn't be enough.When I was
getting close to that, there was an audition for the 4th generation.  I
thought I had to do it myself,
so maybe I can adjust it a little bit.
[Music] I
did it.
It's interesting. I
feel like most of the guests so far have had a slightly different flow.  It's not like I'm
watching a lot of people on YouTube
[music],
but it's like I'm
picking up something from a different place, and it
feels like the flow is a little different.  It was
around the time that Holo Live became extremely popular on YouTube and I had no
choice but to notice it.Recommended.Recommended.
[Music]
Since I first saw it as a fan.
It's the same, it
's the same, it's the
same, it's the same, it's completely the same, I was a fan at first,
and from there I
went to auditions over and over again, and it
seems like there were a lot of them, and even if I didn't get in, I still got in.
If I take it just one more time and fail, then if
I fail, I'm
not going to try anymore, and I'm like, ``I wonder if I can
make it.'' If I
could do it, I wouldn't have been able to do it.  I was
watching it as a fan, but now that I'm
at this concert, I
wonder how I felt,
because my perspective has changed.
Ah, at first, I was
like, oh, so many female idols.  I
used to watch Hello! Project because I like it,
but I was
worried that the seniors would be scary in this girl's world, so I
timidly entered and found that everyone was so nice.I
was really surprised.It's
true that
there are weapons.
[Music]
Phantom Swallow
Senpai Morning I wonder
if you were thinking about Morning Musume
Karata-senpai I do
n't have an adult senior who's scary for my daughter
[Music]
There's a word in English that says it's scary even if you don't do anything with your face, but there's also a word in English that says you look scary even if you do
n't make a face.
That's right, since we were 1st generation students. We
had our own Discord, so there
weren't any Japanese members like Descoin mixed in, so that's right.
There weren't that many seniors either.  It
's true that at first we didn't have a chance to really talk, and I was told that I couldn't talk unless I went through my manager. Mottainai [Music] Is there anything you wanted to convey to people overseas that you couldn't say due to the language barrier? Yes.
There are two voyeurs, but one is that
I speak too fast. I
can't be heard because I speak so fast. I
think it's okay for the person wearing it, but
today I'm speaking very slowly.
[Music] It's
fast, but it's okay.  Saying
[Music]  I'm
glad it's
true. And one more thing:
I
used to do a lot of endurance broadcasts, but when I was
doing endurance races, there were a
lot of things like opening and closing JST at dawn in Japan, so I gradually started to
go overseas.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
[Music] I
think I have conveyed what I wanted to say.
Thank you. If you have
anything to say, please contact me. English English Conversation  All you
have to do is use that instinct. [Music] I wish I could keep going forever. I'm
sure it's nice weather. [Music] What is it? Games, karaoke, chats, etc.  I've
never heard of it, but I'm curious. I
still watch the streams of stupid people. I watch them, I watch them
a lot. I have
a little more time than before to not be able to watch them.
Sorry, but when I'm doing that work, I'm
also watching someone else's SuperChat reading.
[Laughs]
[Music] I think the thing I
like to look back at the most around here is
chatting, rather than looking back at my own broadcasts.
Which of the gals do you like on your own stream? Is there a
game? Then
Tominaga said the last one, but now
[Music]
Who's in it now?
[Music] I've
been playing it for a while.
Eh, okay.
[Music]
[Music] I'm
sorry, I'm sorry. Sometimes I
don't want to do something when I'm invited, but I'll
wait even if it's just for one day. But just for one day. Finally, it will
take hours to install it.
Well, it's
so lenient, I do
n't like it.I've
never lost a lot of games until I debuted, so I'm
playing cool with that 10.  I
admired it and now I can do it, so
it's my favorite.
[Music] I'm not
very good at it, but when I sell it well at the end, everyone is so
happy, isn't it?
[Music]
OkOkOk
NEXT
Yeah, well, it
seems like I have a few nicknames for my shoulder-senpai, like
Gorilla and Pipi.  I also wanted to hear about the origin of Tenshin's heels and the
wall.
[Music]
Before I knew it, the gorilla was...  I was
told that the grip strength is
getting stronger and stronger, which is probably the
cause.That's
all.It's
from Gorilla Lass, and it's that idol, so it's
cute, but I feel like I'm sorry,
but
Note Gorilla
is Gap Moe.
Gap is also  Why? Don't
act like it's a gorilla.
Yeah, well, the gorilla is. Yeah,
I know the Phi Phi angel, but why
? This is the cat.  I
used PowerPoint for my first broadcast, and from there I was called a PP angel,
so even now, people still say that overseas diary
is ppt.
Okay, okay, okay, this has always been the
case. At that time,
Canadian senior, it was no surprise that I
made my debut.  I
feel like everything was pretty normal, but I think the whole thing was interesting because Kanda-senpai suddenly started using PowerPoint.  I'm
glad you're doing well. Well, I spent a month making it, so when I made it for a month, people said it looked like a presentation from that black company. [Laughs] It was a little good, I'm glad. Well, everyone seems to have a little bit of a breast.
Well, I have the misconception that it looks like I don't have any breasts, but they are actually very large.When I hide my breasts, it's normal to see them from the front.  I
think I'll give it to you, but be kind.
But it happens often when it's in 3D.
Well, you can see it from the side. Even when I
looked from the side, there was nothing. It's
actually big, but
everyone says they like it smaller, so I'm
crushing it.
Yes, it looks like it's
crushed. There's some kind of
tape
on it. Yeah, it looks like a towel.
Cosplayer. Cosplayer. I've
been wondering when I'll start showing you the
PNG of those breasts.  You've
been broadcasting with it on your chest, haven't you? Lately, it's been
easy to understand. At that time, you
took off your towel. Yes,
yes, yes, yes. As expected of Chiara.
[Music]
Does anyone know where that name comes from?
[Music] I
don't know. It's
true that Pipiti has various meanings.
[Music]
OkOk
[Music] I
feel like Karata-senpai.
[Music]
[Music] I see.
Everybody's saying ``Pyonpyon'' Copy ``I do
n't know what to say. I
mean, I
have a lot of excuses, even for myself in my head.
[Laughter]
[Music] Is that
okay? Please go ahead, go ahead,
Aken OK OK.
[Music]
What only you can see
doesn't exist.
Let's show it to everyone someday.
[Laughs]
Who's to say? Give it to me.
It's different.
[Music]
Everyone imagines the
true appearance of that senior. The
real appearance is
[Music]
Speaking of Perfect Perfect Power Perfect Power Angel.
For the next question, I'd
like to see a clipping.
[Music]  Let's
take a look. By the way, when you play that one, you can
hear Kaneda-senpai's voice, too.
[Music]
And the last part might have been a dub.
Wait a minute, let's
take a look at the mistake.
But it's okay, OK!
[Music] I
may not be able to get a grip strength meter right away,
but I
'd like you to measure your current grip strength on a live broadcast. This is it. I wonder if this is your
first time. You're
being serious.
Wait, I'm getting leg cramps.  Maybe I'm in trouble. My
arms are strong, but my legs
are weak. My legs are weak.
Well, I can't hear with my right hand, so I
'd like to go from the left. I'm really weak.
By the way, it's
true. Hmm. Are you ready?
[Music]
[Laughter] Let's
raise the baby and the new baby.
Show us that.
[Music] Is that
dangerous? I'd like to show it to you all.
Um,
metoo,
uh, October.  At the end of Angel Day on the 4th
[laughter]
This one
went up. That
's right, that right hand. His
dominant
hand is
higher than the average for boys, so it
's probably about the same.  I've
been doing a lot of muscle training, but
recently I've been doing a little bit of muscle training.I
guess that's it.
What I like about my senior
is, you know, something like that in this cut-through, like how she's a
cute idol or something like that.  I
like how the shop doesn't bother me.
This is the real truth, so I
wish I was
this strong. Lately, people are asking me to be this strong. I've been
thinking about my grip strength, so I've
been training my grip.  I've been
doing grips to train my grip strength, and I thought that
if I dropped to 30 or something,
everyone would
despair.
[Music]
Next time...
Well, let's do it, but I
also lost to Ayame-senpai in arm wrestling just because of my grip strength.
Yeah, it's quite different,
right? Well, it's just my ability to escape.
[Music] I
used my hands to hold that tiara's head.  You
might be able to crush an
apple.
If you can crush an apple, you have to be about 70 kilograms
.
[Laughs] That's
cool. Someday, I'll give
everyone that hand-squeezed juice.  I
can't do apples so I can sell them, but I can
go to all the oranges, right? I
can do it with oranges, right?
Tiara too. It's
impossible to make a character, even though there are only 10.
[Music]
Kiara
is orange, but
please don't crush it. It's
fun to be rough with it.  This person once
mashed a potato.He
puffed it up.The
soft potato was
in the lunch box for the recording.
When I tried to eat it, it crumbled,
but Captain Noel happened to be sitting next to me and saw
it.It's normal to be able to crush a soft potato.I guess so.  No, it's
like fries. It's
not that bad, but you know,
boiled potatoes. Well,
that's all 5. 1. Yeah, I see.
1.
[Music] That's 1.
Leaving that aside, she's a
cute and cute idol, so let's get back to this.Okay,
this person is also a-ha-ha-ne-um.About the cutout,
though.It seems that
her
senior's
grip strength has been a hot topic for a long time, so she cut it out and
aired it.
[Music] I
'm training with Win
Well, lately I've been doing it a little bit, but
up until then, my
grip strength was a bit like a talent and I hadn't
done anything about it, but now I'm like that.1012  She
weighed 35 kg at the age of 35.
What led you to measure that?
We measure women at school, measure their academic ability, and we don't do that.
Really, when you
think about things like height, like measuring physical fitness, you
measure nervousness, but I don't think that's the case.  [
Laughs] The
fact that I have such strong grip in my hands makes me wonder
if there's some kind of anger hidden inside of me. I
don't even realize it, so someday my anger will explode.
There's also a possibility that Canada will wake up and wake up. I don't know. It'll
explode, or the
clothes on my chest will explode, and my
muscles will come out.
Well, that's okay, but there's also a possibility of that happening, isn't it
? That's
cool.
Good-looking guys are cool, aren't they?
That wall stinks. I
understand the reason for that wall. What's your plan? He's got a little muscle.
Hey, what's that? I wonder if it's a boy.
Women also
exercise a lot, so it's a little bit.  I've
seen it turn into a wall.
Well, well, well, that's true, but it
does happen, but it's a
body type that people don't see.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Just kidding.
There are a few.
[Music]
You
are into the same idol group as Kihara,
or rather, I don't know if it's true now that you're into it,
but I'd like to know which block you liked.
First of all,
I really like Hello Project, so I
'm going to go with my daughter.  hey  There were
quite
a lot of them, but I
liked Eri-chan.
Seriously,
Sarada was also really cute. I loved her so
cute. I only found out about her after graduation,
but I
still like her. Also, Sayumi Michishige
[Music]
Lately, I've been
loving Gian.  Eririn Eririn
came first, and you know, just before that, there was
that Saiyan Ho-chan,
Kamen Spear and Michishige Sayumi.  I
thought she liked pretty girls,
but she's
a bit of a cool type, so it
's
a bit confusing, but I was
asked
about her charisma, and her aura.But at that time, I think
Haruka Kudo was my favorite because of her ingenuity.
Tayo
[Music] I
bought a photo book, and
now I'm
selling it on Instagram
[Laughs]
[Music]
Kudo
Haruka
SIDED,
except for Mori Musume.
Other than who I like, for example, the cute
continuation of Airi-chan, that's
lucky because Airi-chan is the only one doing that kind of activity right now.
[Music] I
liked Pudding-chan from Juice Juice.
[Music]
What happened to
Eh, Eucalyptus?  That's
right, Karin
is relaxed, and that's amazing.
No, I really love it. I still love it.
Being able to capture someone like me who can dance.
Dance with you and Psycho are really good. I want you
to see it. Kanana-senpai
[Music] I'm
definitely going to go. Umm,
my Japanese friends that I've made over the last five years or so are
like, "When I'm addicted to Carrboro, I'm like...  There aren't really any
people who like it, and it's
like, ``I don't know how to sing Hello Project at karaoke.'' Well, I
get it. It's
lonely. We're
already a group of geniuses. I
know, I know, if we continued as the four of us.
It's amazing how much I can't help but wonder what would have happened, but the
fact that S/mileage is still the same. It
was a world war that I wanted to see a little bit of.
[Music] I
wonder what Sakichi is doing now.
I know what you're saying, but I've been
trying to find out what you're doing right now.But,
yeah, yeah, yeah, but yeah, but yeah, listen
to me, that thing that's been coming out every day since Sakichi graduated.  The
princess became that mold, right?
Yeah, well, right now, she's
in a different group under a different name, but it's not a secret,
but, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, I
never thought something like that would happen.  I
didn't think so, but I said that on
Kanyon's
new Twitter account, about
a year ago. I said, "I
don't care about anything," but when I did that, I
got a follow pack. It's probably a
lie,
really.
terrible  I
thought he noticed me,
so I tried to write a
reply or something,
but when I edited it, he
replied back to me.
But his
voice was dangerous. No, he was
screaming. He was really screaming.  It's
really good, but it doesn't end there.
[Music]
Well, after a while,
[laughter] The
streamer
seemed to understand me, like DMs and things like that.  Apparently, I
felt like I wanted to stream something,
so I would like to ask for some
advice on streaming, advice on equipment, etc.,
uh, how to stream games, and that
sort of thing.Well,
this is Kanon Fukuda from Kanyon.  Okay, that
's a lie, you can't say that, I
thought to myself.How can I reply to this?I'm going to make a mess of it.I'm
screaming and I wonder if they'll find out I'm
replying to this, so I stopped thinking.I was so
nervous.
I want you to know that I'm rooting for you,
but it feels like it's too good of a deal.If it
gets too much, I'll think it's over and I'll
never get a reply.I was
really confused, but somehow I
managed to do it.  It's like
[Music] It's
just a dream.
Ah, I'm sorry, I haven't spoken English in a long time.
[Music] It's an
official program, right? It's an official program. That
's right, that's right. I
was like, ``
Yes,'' but for a moment.  I was
really nervous during the recording,
so I couldn't understand it anymore, and
after it was over, I
thought I'd be able to say hello, but it was really just a moment.
Wow,
Komaki is different.
Well, I guess it's good that it was just that moment.
On the contrary, it was almost time to go home.
Hmm, maybe that feeling was good on the other hand. I was already
excited.
[Music]
Morning Musume
Ireallylegeone
so
mazingSODhoundo
toryer
doingaft
haveanyyoursepty
NEWSThat
program,
Kageda-senpai is an action
live.I had the opportunity to do something like this.It
's true.It was a dream, wasn't it?It's awesome.It
would be great if I could meet more of the Hello Project members.I
really want to meet them.  Nice to meet you.
[Laughs]
By the way, I've always wanted to talk to you
about this, but
there's one thing I've left unsaid. You may know me.
No, but my favorite book was Berry's Kobo. It
's Berry's Kobo
.
Actually, I was
at the Berry's Kobo, erm, Nikon Nico Nico's
headquarters. I happened to be performing at a place called Nico Nico's headquarters, and I
happened to be performing at Nico Nico's headquarters.  I
went to look at the place where those goods were being sold,
and I'm telling you, I
went to look at the goods by myself, and I thought it was a toilet.
When I was about to go to the bathroom, the members of Berry's Kobo
came out.
[Music]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, wait a
minute, Bear. Hey, wait, it's not Misako. It was
there. Well, well, that's what everyone is saying, right?  They've already come out!
Don't say it first. The
first one to come out was Risako, and after that,
two more people came out, but I
caught Risako's eyes and
thought maybe I shouldn't look at them.  I'd
like to
look away, but as a single person, it's kind of weird.
I
go to a lot of concerts, but I
don't dare to look at little Risako.
Iyarisako isn't small, but Risako is
big.
But really, I couldn't go to the toilet for a while after that, so I
finally put up with it.I put up with it.Of course,
Idols just fixed their bangs, though.
Even so, I couldn't get in. Is
this the guy that normal people go to? He didn't seem to be in the best,
right? Come on, come on, get my
toilet ready. Seriously,
Cao Cao is so embarrassed.
As an idol, he's a
fan.  It would be the worst if it happened there It's already
a bit of a propaganda,
but
please be
careful I'll get really angry Seriously,
where's the risk?
Smoked food is in God You
see
[Music]
[Laughter]
Last single Eh,
recently, Saki-chan, what?
Not recently, not recently, about eight years ago, but it was the last single,
so recently, the last single.
Because I said that,
I thought it was the first one.I wasn't that much of an adult.Oh
yeah, but when it came to romance stories, I was
doing the one I was doing at NicoNico Headquarters.  I was
watching a live show at this headquarters that was being played and was doing, and at that time, I was
thinking, ``It's so small, so it's so small.'' I think it's smiling. It's
crazy. I can't stop. I'll
continue to do it later.
Later, backstage
talk.  If I were in Japan, I could
talk about salt, about lifting my legs, etc.
[Music] This
is Niconico's headquarters.
See you next time. But I don't have a problem with this question. This was only half of the story. I haven't read the second half.
What was your life like? Do you still
go to concerts? I
don't go to concerts. I was an
elementary school student or junior high school student when I liked those idols. I was a stay-
at-home nerd. I
watched TV.  Or YouTube, or something like that, I've never
looked up an image and thought it was cute.
[Music]
But seeing something
blue at Niconico's headquarters is already a miracle. It's
crazy, isn't it? I
was really happy.
That's right, you're such an idiot. I
can't stand it.
[Music]
[Laughter] I
feel like I crushed your
throat. What do you mean when I heard that you've sucked your cheeks
?
[Laughter]
That's right. Um,
originally.  I
had a desire to suck her cheeks and all, but
during a certain broadcast, I
had the opportunity to take a bath with a real marine, and I didn't want to get dirty with that drool.
So, I said something about wanting to let him smoke in the bath,
and
then he made a recording of me and
made fun of me, and for a moment, I felt
like I was sloppy and tried to smoke,
but he
really didn't like it.  It's been put in storage. The
audio hasn't been made public. I
'm desperately trying to get the fan listeners to stop saying it's too creepy, but I'm sure they're yelling at me a lot.  I did
n't release it.I was told that it was over LINE.When I say I didn't release it over LINE, it was a recording.66Ah,
I don't regret recording it.That's why.Does
such a thing exist?
Actually, it does.
This
[Music]
Question. This question
was also sent to me by a listener, a senior listener from Canada,
but I
thought I had to ask this one, and Mainichi Senpai, a
senior from Canada. As expected of a cat.
[Music]
Mr. Lister asked me this question.  I'm
surprised that you told me not to release this.Ah,
well,
there are some people who want to hear it, but
at that time, they just
give me a break and say it's too gross.
Well, okay, let's make it public.I
laughed at my hand, but I wonder
what it was like for someone like me to feel so disgusting.Those
breasts, so big you could touch them with your upper arms,
felt so stinging.  There's a
difference in perception of how disgusting it was.
[Music]
[Laughs] I
thought that's what it was.
But I kind of want to go back to six months.
No, it's okay, Kiara Kiara. I
haven't smoked
Yokai Hops since then.  I sealed her as a woman,
so it's okay. Are you satisfied? It's
beautiful. I
was satisfied. Yes, I broke her [ __ ].
Of course it's OK.  I
remember
[Music]
Senpai,
uh, this is what I just said on Discord,
and this is what I just smoked,
on Twitter.
Hey,
Miko-senpai's this is cute.
[Music] Isn't it
cute? I don't
understand why it's like that.  I
don't understand why I have to do that, because I think it's cute. Is there ever a time when you want to suck a baby's cheek or something like that?  It's
still a long way to go if you don't know her cheeks.She
looks cute, but the
act of doing it does
n't really matter to anyone.When I
asked her if she could smoke it, she
said yes.She asked me to smoke it.It's
delicious.She
said she wanted some Hoppies.  Yes, that's
what I
wanted to say, but on the contrary, that's what it came from.
[Laughs]
Especially for overseas viewers, I
'd like you to tell me something that you probably don't know about Kanagata-senpai. I wonder what it is.  Is
there something that you don't know about Oku?
Maybe everyone already knows that it's very powerful.
Yeah, that's right. I guess that's the question that
Mr. List
sent me.
If you ask him about this in the question, he'll tell you.
Maybe that's why I included it, but
what else
?Baseball It might have been that,
really.Baseball.Well, I like baseball.Ah, that's surprising.Perhaps
not everyone knows about
baseball.
Ever since I was little, that mom has taken me
to the stadium, and I think I've gone to the right side a total of about 100 times.I
like the
Central League
in general, but my mom
is a Hanshin fan.Hanshin
Hanshin  And yes, I'm a
Central League
Tigers fan.
[Music]
The Hanshin Tigers, huh?
The Hanshin Tigers exist. They
exist.
As for the Central League, I don't
know anything about this story, so it's a little
difficult.
But yes, my mother likes the Hanshin Tigers,
right? The
Hanshin Tigers are
like the Hello Project in the Central League. It's
hard to count them in Hello! Project, they're Yankees. They're
old men. They're the same even if they're just like that.
In Japanese baseball, there are 12 teams, the
Central League, or the
Central League, which is split up like the Central League, and
these 6 teams basically compete against each other for 69 teams. I guess it's
still Hello! Project
[laughs]  It
's a professional team from Osaka
Anshin Tigers
Saitama's leagues are all from Osaka. Yeah, that's
wrong. There's Tokyo, there's Tokyo,
there's Yokohama, there
's Hiroshima, and
the seniors like everyone in the Central League. That's
right.
If I had to choose just one person, I'd like Kosuke Fukudome. He's a
baseball player who is very popular in Japan, and
has a unique personality.
There are people who know how to hit. If you
try to imitate Kosuke Fukudome's way of hitting, you
can do it.
But I know because I went to the Cups.
Maybe if I go overseas, I've
been to the Major Leagues.  Shine
Ah, I see, okay, okay, that
doesn't mean anything, but
[Music] I'll
convert
[Music]
Gal Gal
Eh, I can play baseball by myself.
No, I've never played it.
Baseball is so much
like an office. Finally,
finally, finally, I've
finally reached the speed quiz.
Speed quiz.
Well, I wonder where it is. Are you
ready? Are you going to come out? Ok, it's
cold. Which do you prefer?
Rice or
noodles
?
[Music] I
see.
I do
n't like Instagram or pink orange juice.
But seriously, if those
hands
had that strong grip.
Maybe we should climb a mountain. Let's go mountain.
[Music]
Vegetables to put pineapple on pizza.
Washing dishes or something sweet.
Dad, Teti.
Coincidences happen.
Kitty.
Titi, rather than TT.
[Laughs]
Go to sleep.  Is it time to be naked or wear clothes?
[Music]
Wearing pajamas
Favorite events: Halloween, Christmas,
flower fields, etc.
[Music]
And Christmas, New Year's Eve, New Year's Eve
7 or Family Mart or
Lawson
[Music]
Family Mart
Message OK
[Music] I'll
walk the distance of one station from my living room, but I
'll take the train
[Applause] The
monster's
blood type is
bby
[Music] The
color of the dance parts
isPants
Flaming
Pink Flamingo
[Applause  ] You're
wearing pants like that, aren't you?
[Laughs]
[Music]
Why should I be born? It's so
nostalgic.
You're you, you're different, you're different too This is already
starting to look blue Did everyone have this?The
blue axolotl
was really a vision [Music]It
was a communication deviceIt was Fubuki-senpai's appearance.
[Laughs] It
broke my heart that it
was real.
[Music] There
's an interesting project with that app. You
can't see the hammer. It's so loud. It's so
small. It
all looks the same.
Eh, blue and white look the same. Just count them. They're similar. You'll
see.
Look, look, look, there's already one. That
purple is a
little purple.
[Music]
[Music] There's
more drumming.
[Music] It
was really long.  That's right.
How many hours
did it take? I wonder how many hours it took, but it was three days.
I'm so
picky
[Music] I'm
sure it's
worth it [Music] It's going to pay off! It's already turning out to be an epic story
[Music]
This is it, right?
[Music] I guess I'm
overflowing with unnecessary emotions.
Shibusawa sneaks back. I
still don't know the
words to describe this kunoichi I don't know yet
Happening Happening This
[Music]
Emotions are
within my reach, but I'm moved.  It's not in the dictionary yet.
Congratulations. Please wait. I
won't shoot. I can't
shoot. I'm scared.
My head was shaking. I'm
waiting for a while.
About 3,200 animals.
[Music] [
Applause] [
Music]
Please do it.
Name: I
think it's gargling.
[Music]
3200122 How many hours?
How many percent?
927 hours. 27 hours. It's too
heavy. Give me a name. It's heavy. What I'm
carrying on my back is too heavy.
[Music] That
's good. That
's good. Really, but Senpai. It's
not at all for me.  I don't understand that feeling.
Well, when the axolotl came out on the Micro,
I was
n't interested at all. Everyone was
trying to get the Blue Pulp, but I was
n't interested in the regular version.
[Laughs] I was
thinking, ``I'm doing this again today,'' and I'm like, ``
Why would you do something like that
to yourself, why would it hurt you so much?'' Well, when I think
about it calmly, I
wonder why.  [
Music] It
's the spirit of gacha, isn't it? I do
n't know what to call it, but it's
betting, gambling, candles,
etc. It's gambling, it's about putting your feelings at
risk.  It's
not about money, it's about cutting down on time in your life. That's what I mean.
[Music]
Things like this have happened. Yes, I was
nostalgic and had a question about it.
Well, first of all, I
just touched on it a little bit.  Why was
the axolotl photographed by Kanata-senpai
? Why was it so important? I
started broadcasting it with a slightly more casual attitude than the axolotl itself, and the
probability was 1 in 1200.
Even in the first year of 1200, it did
n't come out.That
's why I didn't really intend to be durable at first, so I
started with a casual feeling, but it did
n't work out so much that I couldn't stop.  I'll
do it until it comes out Well, that's right. I understand that.
From the beginning of the middle, I know that it won't end until it comes out. Well, I'll do it. You
know, this is a story where we talk a lot but don't say much.  I was
able to do it without thinking about it, and it
wasn't that hard to do with that axolotl, so I divided the strings,
right? So it was
n't that hard,
but the hardest part was the fight against Sans from Undertale, which
was really tough.  I've
never played that one, but I
know it's a 3 o'clock character, but the battle in 3rd year
takes so long. It's
difficult, and
everyone, probably
even someone playing it for the first time,
can complete it in 56 hours.  I
think it took me about 30 hours,
so
no, it's difficult, probably
because it's a game, and I'm not used to it, but it
took so long.
That battle wasn't that
round.  I
wonder if
it's a shooting game, a shooting game.
Yeah, I
thought it was a painstaking process. It's
not a basic one.
Yeah, once.  If you
get it right, it's over. A-chan, it's
difficult, but as I
said in the comments, there were probably a lot of people who did it for about 10 hours. It's hard,
but I kept trying.
When I made it to 3 hours, I
felt a great sense of accomplishment.  I can't help but cry.
[Music]
I see.
Kiyohara-chan is also going to play Undertale again. I wonder if she'll
do it someday, but I'll
be there to support her.
[Music]
That's it.  If I remember
correctly, Flare-senpai was pushing him a lot.
[Laughs] I
really like Sans-senpai.
[Music]
Yeah, but he's cool after all. He
's a cool, cool character. He's a
bone-and-bone character here, too.
But he's
really cool, after all. The
story.
It's a character that you fall in love with when you play it.I'll
play it in 1963 or 2014.Ah, my
brother, you see,
it's around 20232324.  I'm
looking forward to hearing from you on LINE, so
please wash your hands.By
the way,
who is Kanata-kun?  That
's right. It's a
really easy-to-understand
character. It's
a photo, it's a photo, it's a photo. I feel
like he might have gone somewhere. I was
looking for him.
[Music]
Hololive
members
also love to stream. I don't really love it. I'm
reading this next time. I'm
not the immune type, but I'm glad I
was kidding.
You're so nostalgic. Yeah, right?
At the host club like this.  I
was planning on having a lot of girls come and play with me when I waited for the convection, but
that was my intention, but no
one came at all, and I was the only one who didn't
come.  We
talked for about 30 minutes by myself. That's
a bit of a
heartbreak, isn't it?
Since Host Club Canada went out of business,
Kanta-kun is already
on the streets. Now, hmm,
sad. Let's have
fun again someday.
[Music]
Thank you, please tell me.  About Tekanako Kanata-kun, I
wanted to meet you, I love you, and I wish
I could have met him while he was still alive.I'm
sure
he's
crying when he reads this, too.Karata-
senpai has no confidence in himself either.  I'm
also involved in writing
and composing songs, but when it comes to songwriting and
composing, I'm not as good at writing lyrics.
[Music] Writing
lyrics is a lot of trouble, and I have to rewrite them over and over again, like when it comes to
Japanese artists,
back numbers, and
Mr. Yonezu.  Well, I look at the lyrics of various people and
learn a little about how to express them.I compose the music, I write the
songs quite a bit.  It's like trying to come
up with a sound that makes you feel good, so it's kind of intuitive, but I've
gotten so much help from so many people that I
think I should study it a little more.
Oh, well, the song that's
being featured heavily right now is a song by the 4th generation members
called Miracle Musubi, which I
wrote and composed.
[Music]
Are you interested in songwriting? I've
always wanted to try it,
but I
think my bigger dream is to ask the artists I admire.  Right now, I'm making my own songs.
Maybe on the 27th, the
songs I've made will look something like this, but I
guess someday I'll
make a Holomen song.  I don't have to
put it on a CD or something, so
I'd like to give it a try OK OK
[Music]
I don't have that kind of talent,
so I don't think I have anything like that. I wrote the
lyrics in English once.  I
tried writing the lyrics as a joke, or rather as a content for that broadcast, but when it comes to
English, even though I'm fluent in English, when it comes to lyrics, I
can't write them very well.If it was in
German, I feel like I'd say something like that, but it's
just a little bit better.  It's
weird.
Everyone understands it,
so it's fine if they just put one line in there, but
sometimes they put German in between English songs, or in anime songs,
but it's
usually weird German, but I hope
everyone admires it.  Also, I was thinking about,
for example, what kind of German is that?
[Music] The
correct
line is
Attack on Titan
[Music]
That's not the only one, but there are other songs as well.
Now that you mention it, what's the name of that anime
?
[Music]
Tanya Senki, yeah, yeah, that's also from Germany. That's
right, but even if it's not just the lyrics of that song, it
's probably a Japanese anime or game.  The names of the characters are
pretty
good, too. I did something like Atelier, and the
Atelier
series
has a lot of German names in it, which always
makes me laugh.
Yeah, that's right.
When I add German to that song, I
consult Tiara.
Please
[Music]
Next up is the
real thing.
[Laughs]
How did you overcome that?
Why are you laughing? There
were a lot of walls, right?
As I said earlier,
there were a lot of them up until my debut.  I had never played a video game
before, so I
couldn't get used to playing it,
and
there was a time when I felt like I was really bad at it, and even now.  I'm
not that good at it, but I did
n't know anything about this activity as a streamer, so there were
times when I wasn't really good at speaking at first,
but I
learned a lot.  I've
done a lot of research on things like binge watching my seniors' streams to see if they'll find it fun when I talk about what they're doing, and I've watched my own streams over and over again.
But Kanata-senpai is
really
good at talking, and every time I listen to his stream, I think to myself, ``
This is the
style of stream of the Japanese members,''
and I really admire him.He
just
keeps talking and
talks about everything.  I think you're really good at it. I'm so
happy. Thank you
very much. At first, I was
n't very good at speaking, but when it comes to collaborations, I
can't speak much.
Lately, there have
been times when things haven't gone well at all.What have you been doing?
Lately, I've been in a bit of a
class, no, no, no, no, it's not like that,
but you're such a
kind person, and now you're really, really bad.Even
though I've gotten angry,
[laughter]
Really, it's better than in the past.  It makes
me so happy to think that I can
now speak that language.
When I'm talking to you, you
're smiling, but I wonder
if you
understand.Sometimes you understand, but you don't really understand.It
feels good, it feels good, right
?
However, in the comments, you say that you're a good
clone, and
say whether you've grown or not.
Thank you everyone.
[Music] Let's get
into it.
Thank you very much, sir.
Yes, thank you very
much. Thank you very much. This is the next and final question, but even after that, there are things that make me happy, so I'm still happy.  What is
Senpai?
Hololive is a
serious story.
If it wasn't serious, it would
be a gathering of pushers, but it
feels like a gathering of cute girls, but
seriously, it's a
place that really changed my life. Hmm.
After all,
I'm like this quite a lot, too.
Even when I came overseas,
there were people who supported me and knew about my situation,
but I was often sick.  There
were a lot of times before my debut where I felt like things weren't going well or something, but now that I've been able to
review Neko's live performance and have so many people support me
and sing, I'm really,
really happy.  As I spend my days, I
want to give back a lot to Hololive.
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
For those of you who want to hear the song now, there
will be a performance.After that, I'll
probably say buy and sell, or say bye-bye now,
but yeah,
that's right.
Well, I had a lot of fun talking with that guy-senpai all day today.Also, I'm
planning to have an off-line meeting in Japan again, so yeah, I'd
like to hang out.
[Music]
And then there's the character stuff.  I just
wanted to let you know, but with this stream, I
still have a bit of a sore throat. There's a possibility that I'll take a little more rest. I'll
take a break, but thank you. It was fun. Do
n't overdo it, don't overdo it.
But also, uh, that holotalk the other day.
Well, since it was our 2nd anniversary, we put out some goods the other day,
but I don't know if the pre-order period for shoes is about 2 days left, but since it's over, if you're interested, check out this
one.
Description Column It's listed in the description column of this stream,
so
please support Holotalk.
That
[Music] I
'm selling mugs. Everyone,
put your name on the mug that's right in front of me.  It's a T-shirt that looks like something from a band's
tour.
[Music] There
's also an acrylic stand, but it's
really stylish.
Thank you. It's
great. Everyone, take a look.
Well,
there's a JP bar,
so it's kind of nice. Well, it's
a little bit too much to have it made in that studio or something. That
's right, it's luxurious and luxurious. I don't want to liven it
up. That's
right. Actually, it's Levitt's
song that everyone wants me to sing.  Actually,
I was recruiting for something, and I
heard about it on the internet.Well,
at that time, I didn't say it was Holotalk,
but I
received a lot of requests, and I was like, ``Holotalk.''  There were some
songs that I just couldn't sing,
and there were some rights issues that would be difficult to get right away,
so
I'd like you to sing a song of your choice.  Is
there anything you want to say? Dear Senpai, if you
have something to
say, let's do it. Everyone, let's talk a little bit about everyone. It's very, very
special. I think today I've become even more in love with you,
so I'll continue to do so.
Thank you for your support of the Hololion, that counter, and the tiara. We
get along well, and this time, it looks like we're going to have a little fun with the dog.
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
Those seniors,
seniors
[Music] I
can say [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]  [
Music]
[Music] It's
not now. It's a
declaration that I'm just sleeping while traveling.
Be a hero to me.
[Music] That's
cool.
You
can't rely on me.
That's true. Even now, I'm lost.
Can
you take my hand? It's a gift. I'm bored. Just like you were my hero, it's not now. I
'm on the verge of being so hot. I can't do anything about the limits lurking inside me. Tangled
up in my impulses, look, I
realize that there's so much baggage that hurts.
Where are you going
carrying this on your back? Why don't you leave it with me for a while?
[Music]
No one
knows who's right, me who just believes in you, or you who just believes in it.
[Music]  A
world just for us It's a
gift take
Oh yeah I'm
sorry
Miss Miss Miss Miss
Service Star Restart It's okay
Sommer Pom Pom
Pom Pom It's
good to hear it one more time I'll make it I'm
sorry Look, it's no good
Canada-senpai Thank you from the beginning Okok
[Music] If
it's now  No, it's
just a sleeping justice that's flickering around.
Now
I want to be my hero.
[Music] That's
cool. I wonder
if I can't rely on you?
That's right. Even now, I'm
lost.
Could you please take my hand?
[Music]
Just like you were my hero, it's not now. There's a
limit lurking in me, right in front of my eyes, and I
can't do anything about it.
Those of you who are tied up in impulses and realize, why don't you carry so much baggage on
your back and leave it with me for a while?
[Music]
Who's right, me who always believes, or you who just believes?
[Music]  It's a
world just for us, it's a
gift-take
Once we complement
each other, I want to dream the same dream [Music] You're an enclosure, and I feel
like it's not my fault for tormenting you and leaving you alone.
I'm sorry, but what you should see is that
now is the time for me to help you.  Do
n't hold me back, I want you to believe in me. It's
not now. I
can't do anything to keep it from lurking in my eyes. I'm
driven by an impulse, and
now I'm
starting to realize it.
Don't pray Where are you going with so much baggage on your back?
Just leave it to me.
This is on
your
forehead.
[Music]
La la la la la la la
[Music] La la la la
la
[
Music] La
la  ]