[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [
Applause] [
Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] I
can complete it. I'll
never finish this challenge for the rest of my life. Please
say something properly first.
Can I hear you? Eh, why are you late? It's okay. I can hear you.
This
is okay. The game's sound is probably too loud. It's probably too small, so you probably
can't hear it. I'll
put it on the microphone. It's okay. It's
okay.
It's okay. Just take it slow.
Slow down.  You can take your
time. We're a man and a
woman, so let's
introduce ourselves.
From the bottom,
from the bottom.
Thank you. It's an
angry operation.
[Music]
[Music] [Music
] [
Music] [Music] I'm really happy [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]  [
Music]
But yeah, it
seems like this is the first time we're meeting at a free ad. Thank you very much. Thank you for your time today.
Tiara is closer to the microphone, so I'm sorry. It's so
loud.  It's
not Supers, it's super,
whatever. This is fine. It's
not Mario Party Superstars, it's
normal. I'm
downloading it, so wait a minute. What's
okay?
This is fine. If it's Maripa, anything is
fine.
Please,
me and that Chiara-chan are in the middle of the microphone,
so even if we move a little further away, it's
the same with the earphones.The
shovel speaks quietly in the family hall.  The men and
women of Lifere
Takamori are talking.It's an echo.Yes, it
's a flare that Freire doesn't know.It's my
first time with Calliope-chan.It's my
first time, but we ate together a while ago and we've gotten to
know each other, so let's go together today.  Let's do our
best to liven it up. Senpai gave us a treat.
[Music]
Hearing that he's going to call me by his nickname, Neuchi, and
Flair said that Neuchi wants to eat yakiniku.
So I went to have some good yakiniku, so I treated myself to it.It's
said to be very like, but it's a place
where you go alone.It's
not like I went there with everyone.What is
like?There's a solo yakiniku restaurant called like.
But for some reason,
when everyone wrote Gyukaku, I
intentionally wrote a little like,
and a lot of
people started picking up likes.
But, since I'm
curious about Yakiniku by myself, I'll go look for it next time.
When I want to eat Yakiniku in a light and easy way, it's a
restaurant that I highly recommend. And the
leader was calm too. He
asked me if it's okay or not.
And
everyone is a little scared. By the way, I
chose Starz, and it's okay, but I
wonder if they'll crack the game.
Today's stream is
going crazy.  I do
n't have a pass. Can I bring another cap? Is
it okay anytime? 4
[Music] I
have a book. I came here at the last minute.
Hey, I heard that you'll be back
at 9 o'clock after eating a lot of delicious Yakiniku. [
Music]  ]
But at the end, there was a really delicious,
sparkly one with money on it. How do you
say it in English?
[Music] I
was surprised. Let's take a look. Hey, when I
bake it.  I
thought it would be black, but it wasn't
. Hey, everyone was just drinking.
[Music]
Hello, hello everyone.
Actually, this
Noefre Takamori has
been around for many months now. I want to do it with everyone.
Thank you, you're a
genius.
[Music]
[Music] It
seems like you use Daisy a lot like me.
Oh yeah, you can use Daisy for that. Even
if I give it to you this time, I always use electronics. My house and Mari
always use the curtains.  I feel like
when it comes to Daisy, it's
easy to win when it comes to emotional problems.I
feel like she always wins, but I don't know
what's going on.This time, I
heard that Aonokai-chan is quite strong, right?  I
decided to ask him to carry that handicap, right?
[Laughter]
[Music]
By the way, I loaded it earlier, but
if it looks like this, maybe it will be reset.
Today's Noel.
How about the switch? I just loaded everything.
[Music]
[Applause] It
doesn't have to be English today, except for English
. If you
keep talking, you'll
end up saying simple English.  Yes, it's
really easy to learn. You can say things like the weather, so you
can pronounce it well. You
won't be embarrassed. It's
really good. You'll be surprised
when you go home. You'll be able to speak English like that.  I
can't speak when I'm using something like that, but my
senpai just kind of
suddenly
said OK, so I'm
really, really happy.
Actually, I can't speak at all.
There's no sound in the game, right?
Is it on? Everyone, I
can hear when I can.  But
since I haven't touched OBS, I guess it doesn't look like wood. I don't know. It does
n't have it in it, so I can
hear it cracking a bit, but I guess it's just
a little bit.
But I guess I'll try it here.
Maybe it doesn't make sense.Then, the
sound is low, so you can clearly see it.Here,
here
[Music] It
's not touched, it's not touched, it
's 0.
Hey, let's
turn it up, this is the offset, and
if we raise the offset, there's a lag.  [
Music]
Even if I give it up, it
doesn't come in. I wonder if it doesn't come in. I wonder if this is
different. It's not that. It's probably OBS.
OBS
[Music] [
Music] I wonder if it
's
[Music]
[Laughter]
Eh, I don't know what to do. Eh, it's like
Mario. Mario
is me.
But if Kiara is going to use Daisy, I think I
'll use Yoshi.
By the way, I feel like the leader can move this.
Okay, uhm, I made a mistake.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, use that.  That's
fine,
Noel, I
'll play it with the Joy-Cons and the Leader Joy-Cons. Yes,
even if I play with just one device, everyone's battery will be low.
But it's okay. It's good that the four of you
know what it's like.
But this is the controller. I
pressed LR.
[Music] It's
okay on the left.
Okay, this isn't my response. I'm
not lying, really.
Okay, this is fine. I
loaded it, but I think it's just because it has that yellow-green color.
OK
[Music] I
'm a guest, so I'm
not part of the team, right? I
took a picture. So, leave it to me for
a while.
Absolutely.  I'm
definitely going to do something weird, I'm not looking at this and that.
[Music] I
can't skip this. I
understand the rules of adventure. I'm
not a beginner.
Yeah, I've
been saying this on a regular basis again,
Catherine is boy yes Yingling
[laughter] I've
been getting excited about Catherine's stories,
but there's a stage, and
this
isn't the first time.
[music]
[laughter]
Why don't you go out of your way to make it a little smaller? I've
done some stages where I'm curious about Kani-chan, but
other than that, I've never done anything like this. Is it okay to do this? It's
been decided
[Music]
45 minutes  It's written in , but it's always going to be long.
Which one is better?
Hmm
[Music]
15 is fine
.
So I'll go with this. I guess
this should also be normal.
[Music]
What happens when you go to Don Quijote?
[Laughs]
Everyone saw that muscat in Don Quijote,
that Pengri, and then it
became a letter.
[Laughs]
This
forest is a lost forest where everyone walks the same path round and round.
A long time ago, there was a once-in-a-millennium
battle to determine the superstar,
but unfortunately the superstar
was never chosen.  I'm
not going to explain. I want to be here today to
decide who will be the once-in-a-millennium superstar. Yes,
I'll be. I'm
really motivated. I'll
go first because I have preparations to make. It's over,
Tenjin. It's
over.
Regards, Pinocchio.
Pinocchio Pinocchio
Yes.  Okay - Is this your
first time
? It's fine at home, but this is your first time in this forest.
The two of you are taller. Yay!
[Applause] It
's your
first time. First time.
[Laughter] [Music
]
[Music]
Well, for the
first time after we had dinner, I was
talking to Hari-chan,
and I thought she was really cute, and I thought she was pretty cool,
but it wasn't like that at all. She was
kind and cute, I'm
sure.  Today, I'm
sure he'll give in kindly.
[Laughs] He'll
write me a letter. That's
right. He's the one who will take it easy.
[Music] There
's a
rule: If you're doing well at first, you'll be fine at the end.
Because you lose, yeah, that's how you always
do it. At first, you keep losing, so that's how you put up your preventive measures. They
say it's lactic acid, but I use it all the time.  It
starts out pretty bad when you're playing it.
I, uh, I
don't have this game.
[Laughs]
[Music]
By the way, how much do you want to get? I think it's 20. Just
hurry. Yeah, it's
pointless if you don't have coins.
At first, it's okay to do something like 1 or 2. It's
okay to go round and round. It's better not to go too far.
First item
[Music]
Similar dice and warp blocks
[Music] It's
kind of
like this.  I'm about to give it to myself. I
haven't dropped the flag that I feel like I'll be left behind. So, bye
everyone.
[Music]
But
if you go in such a hurry, you might not be able to buy it tomorrow. That's
it, this is it.
This is on the other side, oh, the
game starts here, there, there, here, here, it's all over, this
is my first mini-game, the
left side is cut off.  Let's
get along well. I
wonder if we can get along well. Let
's talk about plus and minus.
First, we'll be on
the beach.
[Music]
I'm in my 4th year. We
're close to the beehive. Okay, you
're being mean.
Touch two, two,
then take one. I'm
thinking ahead. I
don't have time. 123
[Music] I
can't move my head, so anything is
fine. I'll
touch two here. [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] Eh, wait, temporary.
Karinkochi
[laughter] is a
loser.
That's right. He's
strong. He's strong
enough to say he's good at it. Well,
give up. He's smart
though.  It seems like
Kai-chan really thought about it that much
. I
think he did.
Why were there three of us
? The number of money.
It feels like my turn has changed. Does that mean I
can't do it this turn?
[Music]
Normal.  Go I'm
going normally Yeah, it's 1st position
It's not much I
want money It's
amazing
OK
[Music]
Even if it's slow, it's the
number of stars in the end So I
bought it
Mr. Perfect, you're so
smart I'll buy this item  It's an
item. Even
though I
bought it, even though I bought it, I
want money.
Hello Lucky is amazing too.
Mr. Perfect
[Music]
The four of us are at peace again.
Love & Peace. This is a close-up thing. There's a
photo in the middle
[Music]  ]
[Music]
OK OK Is
this peace? It's
not peace. It
's a commemorative photo.
Noefre Takamori Yay.
[Applause] It's
like a cake. They weren't there
for a long time.
Is that okay? That's
funny.  Congratulations
and congratulations, thank you. The weather is
such and such a frog. I
bought that first one. I
think I'll
go home. I can only go home. I
can't help but look pale.
This is where the war begins. OK,
take away Chiara's star. Eh, this
is my first time doing something like this. No, no, it's my
first time.  Even if things go well,
I've never had success at first. I'll
do my best. I'm
close.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Alright, alright, I do
n't have any money, so I'm really looking for money. Hang on.
When I go up, it's blue.When I go down, I cry.Aren't you crying? Yes, I'm
baking.
Wow, please give me back my love. Wow, things are
going really well.
Baby 34
[Music]
No. 34 It's
far away.
Change the direction of the arrow.
[Music]
Next  The color of the star is
next.Even if I
go over there and get hit, it doesn't matter either way.Just to make
sure others don't get hurt, there's also a frog.Hmmm,
but it'll
change again on the next turn.It'll change a little.
C That's it, right Donkey. So Carly-chan is
getting closer. I
think I'll change it. OK. I'll
make it a star. I'll
fight and fight with the trees. It'll
be easier here and there. But if I stop this, it'll
be faster to stop.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Laughs]
[Music]
All the things I lose are the ones
I run away from.
Harry
[Music]
[Laughs]
As long as we're on the right team, we can
win
infinitely. It's true that we can't go. I've
turned over.
Hey,
uh, I'm up to the 11th place star. Let's
roll the dice. I can
reach the dog. 1, 1, 1, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, can I reach it?  No, I don't think
so. [Music] [Music] I think I'll buy it. I'll buy it when someone else will use it. It's too bad. I don't think it's suitable for Chiara today. But I have to go home next turn.  What's the point of
going home? It's woof,
wan, that someone uses the dice.
The key is probably the
rain.
[Laughter] [Music]
[Music]
Maybe there's a use for it once in a while. I don't know, but
lukewarm dice only roll 1 or 2.  I'll get rid of it,
but it
won't be of much use
[Music]
Good, it's better to do it alone,
no, it's too much. Yo, it's a mistake to be thrown
around so many times. I can't let this go to the goal.  It seems like they're
buying their abilities. Eh,
everyone should be a little ok. It's
not about teamwork. I'm
not confident anymore. Let's
go to the number one man and woman.
[Music] [
Laughter] [Applause]
[Music]
Eh, on the train.  It didn't look like I was going to be able to do it at all, but even though I was
practicing so well, I was
outclassed at the time of practice.But
everyone, this
is so bad, I'm so happy, but I can take this away.  It's just because
it's a care, so there's still one from last time, so it's
okay.
Yes, it means we can take a picture of two people. Is
this close to Noel? It's passed that.
How is it passing? I
can borrow it.
Well, it's a little bit.
[Applause]
Double  Use dice or something.
Oh, Ok, Ok, 3 coins, ah, 3 coins. I'll
give you that. I'll
cry.
[Music] You
just passed.
Shall I use your one-man whistle?
Oh, that's nice.
Vanish. Anyway,
Noel is trying to collect money, right? Amo was just right.
If it was a perfect fit, it
would be written down.
[Music]
[Laughter]
That's right. [Laughter] Don't be silly.
[Music] I
'm with you.  Oh, it's scary, I'm alone again
[Music]
Thorns of danger, this is the worst
Noel hides like this, okay
,
okay, okay, I can go This is
scary, hey,
this is it  I
forgot. The
last time it moved
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Oh, it's already here
Wait, it's farther away
[Music] I'm
going for a walk
[Music]
I just want some dice.
But hey, I have a lot of money,
right now, I'm really in this situation. I do
n't understand, I'm not used to it. It's my
first time to be a winner. I'm crazy, Marie, and I'm
strong, but there
are kids and stars.  The
first one was unlucky as usual,
but
[Music] You
can get money. If you
get free money, it's
50 coins.
In the explanation, I said, ``If
the government or something is going to take a lot of money, then it
's sparkling.''
Well, she has this kind of leeway.
How much are you asking?
[Music]
[Laughter] If you ask
for too much money, it'll be 7 or something.
You say you're not going to go there anyway.
[Music]
Claire's crying, okay.
This is the thing where I can take as much money as I want at the front, and
that's it for us.The
people behind the scenes will
come later.Maybe
if we bump into each other, I'll
collect some of
your coins.  If there's a lot, I'd like to win.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
Stop it, don't be
silly.
There's a factory park, so I'll buy it now. Things will go
well like this. Today's Chiara is strong.
No matter what's going on, Sari-chan
has 80 tickets too.
[Applause]
It's okay, someday,
aren't you winning a little too much? Even if you
lose to everyone, it's
okay. It's about
time. It's not good. This is okay, but from now on,
everyone.  I'm sorry, I'll stop, I'll
stop. There's something about the battery being low. I do
n't understand. It doesn't
seem like it's something else, right?
[Music]  It
's not far away.Also, I'm far away, but I can get one,
so everyone, it's time to get it, and the
stars are happening too.
[Music]
Only the coins you
can get. Take what you want.
Hmm,
ok. It's
true, it's getting a little scarce, so ok.
[Music]
[Laughs]
There are a lot of them
[Music] I guess the
items here are a little different. Ah, I
'm standing there waiting. It'll be after 22. Hey, I'm
going home. I want one. I can finally buy one.
All 1.
Nice, yes.
End.  I'm
already being targeted, so I
want everyone else to get it
too. Even though I'm so beaten up, I didn't expect to be a star.
No
,this is
flying. It's
crazy.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause] I'm
so sorry, I should go home.
So, I'm
going home. I'm going home.
Sorry.
[Music] I see. I have to hide. I move and hide under the towel. Just a little bit, just a little bit. There's a bit of a lag. [Laughter] [Music]
[Laughs] I'm
scared if I don't go back.
Soccer ball Takamori. This is my
government. No,
just like that.
[Music] I
want a little more, but that's fine. I think that's fine. I
always
lose, so someone else is in charge.
I'm already doing that.  Who's doing it for me?
Go up to your waist. You can roll the dice.
How far do you want to go? It doesn't matter.
It's OK to go in the safe direction.
Okay, number 4.
What are you doing?
[Laughs]  If
I have the next chance, I'll just have to
stay somewhere and
get a star, so I guess I have no choice
but to take them with me. There
's a square that can be taken, so maybe I'll have a
companion who'll involve me somehow. I
guess
Noel is nearby.  I
can't go up, no, I can turn. There's an arrow at the top. Oh, I
can't go. Ha, but Little Red Riding Hood. If I don't have it, I can
do the math and go back.
[Music] It
seems like only 1 comes out in those cases.
[Laughs]
Well,
there's a certain point, so
if we don't catch up here, it's definitely a
one-one
cycle.If you don't use the whistle, you won't use it, you won't make it.It's kind.[Music] [Music] It's running all alone.  I don't think so. I don't want to
switch places with Pitta Recycle and Noel, but
there might be a chance for a warp block. I
don't know who I'll switch places with
[laughter]
Fate
[Music]
This is a fixed point.
It's expensive. It's expensive. I'm
angry and can't afford the strong wind. It's
not fun.
What do you like? In Japanese
[Music]
What are you doing? You
saw Takamori's fixed point. It
's okay. You
're on time.
[Laughs] I see.
This is the kind of thing where you're good at practice, but you're trying to get caught
in the actual performance.I can't keep up with the people who seem to be good at it.There are people who are good at it, so it's just luck and I almost
never miss a thing.However, I
feel like I was pushed.
Where's everyone?
It's over there.
[Music] I ca
n't see it at all.
Everyone
can't see what other people are doing.
[Laughs]
So, where's
Starba now? The song is below Noel
.  I see, if you take out 12, it'll be at the bottom.
Ah, that's right, that's right. I'll
go normally. Normally, no
, no. I
got 19.
[Music]
Scary,
scary. I like it half price.
Little Red Riding Hood.
[Music]
Really
Now, I wonder if there's 1 or 2, 1 or 3. Then
what actually happened to make it so low? I do
n't know if it's a curse or something. Is
n't this good? I'll give it to you. Yeah.  It
disappears, Wow, why the
sudden light bulb!
[Music]
Hey, thank you, this is a bad situation.
If I win here, I have no choice but to win in the game. Whether I
win or not, if it's not big, I'll
be that one, that one, that one.
Maybe I'll play the Man one. That's cool. I want money in the mini-game. I
want coffee. Oh,
but here it is. Is it money or items? I
wonder
what's coming. The weather.
[Laughs]
[Music]  ] The
person with the most coins at the end gets a star. Well, you get a star. I do
n't know if it's a coin or not. I bought a game. Do I have to keep hitting one coin a lot? [
Music]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] You're
too cute
[Laughter]
[Music] I guess I
'll repay you sometime next time
[Laughter] I'll
repay you so much I'll
reach you right now I'll fly
to the stars
Even if I'm
taken away, I'll always be here  1st place isn't bad.
Star is also 1st place. He
's a regular customer. I
guess he's a customer who always comes.
Last year, I've
known this person all my life. He
's always here.
He's here again. I'm tired of his face.  wearing  I
want it.
[Applause]
Maybe it's a machine. It
was
opened. There was a thing that put a cup on it. I don't
really know what was in it in the first place. Well,
no, no, no, no. Anything is fine. Is this
okay? It doesn't
matter. I'll
guess.
[Music]
Money.  I'll run out, so I guess I'll just
buy some mushrooms.Okay,
okay, okay, what kind of senior is this?I
can use it for 3 stars.Wow,
time.I
want Alice's money.
Hey, that's
right.
[Music] Wow, there wasn't much of it.
Damn it.
Who's on top?
[Music] I don't know
what to do.
Where's the man who's full of things? If he
uses a monster to get close to the other person, he'll
do it alone.  Also,
Noll-senpai, I wonder if I'll use that next time.
11 huh?
Maybe I'll go for a yard, or maybe I'll get one. I'm
aiming for
it.
[Music] The
perfect
way to use it is like this. Ah,
do you want money?  The
person who stops exactly right gets the money.
Now I know.
On the other hand, if you're a star, you
can call me and get the money.
[Music]
Kani-chan, who keeps coming back so many times, tries to be as
self-centered as possible.  You should just take the money there.
That Cali-chan
is better than us. Yeah,
OK.
[Music]
[Laughter]
That's twice as much. The
situation is so great that we're finally number 4.  Do
n't give up just yet. Don't give up!
Hurry up!
[Music]
Ah, but the next third star is
Kari-chan's
time is dangerous. If we
do a lot of happenings, the
chances of getting a lower will go up.
Oh, and what's left? 5 more turns.
Thank you for the hidden block. It's a
card that gives you a voice. There was a card. Oh,
the money will increase, yes, yes, but this will also
increase. I'm sure the
battle will be OK. Yeah,
there's a chance for a reversal.
Even if I'm alive, there's no point in
doing anything about this, so I'll just go. I want to look at the map and see where I can reach it. 1234 I guess I can only go up. I
can only go up. It's a
key. I can go up, too.  I don't really need it right now,
because either way, I
'm aiming for something that has a certain value [Music] in the back of the item shop.Hmm, what I
don't need
are mushrooms.
Here you go, this is a good box for happenings.
This doesn't matter.
The arrow has changed.
On the contrary, it's now easier to go to the left.
[Music]
[Music] That
's fine. [Music] But, the chairman has broken down. There
's nothing we can do about it.
Tax payments.
Senpai, you've already
given yourself some leeway. Well, there are three.
[Music] The
hidden block is the one you found earlier, Kari-chan. It's
better to just get it, even if you
throw away one die.
[Music]
Lucky Girl,
nothing.
Wait, game. Ah, I was surprised. I
thought the Koopa Trout would stop, but no one has stopped yet.
[Music]
OkGoogle
OkOk It'll
probably get faster if I do that. I'll
do my best, but maybe
this will help.  I don't think I've ever understood that. I have
n't seen the one I bought. But at the
same time, Mom.
[Music]
Alright, let's buy this Tiara-chan already.
No, it's okay, I'll buy it on the next turn. I don't need it
right now. I can walk there.
But I can't buy it anymore. It's close today.
No, this dog is passing by. Which way
are you looking?
This one is right in front of me.
Chang's face:
What are you
going to do? It seems like there's something to do with money. It's going to
be a big deal. [Music] [Music] [Music] When I woke up this morning, I felt like today was going to be a good day. That's
unusual.
[Music] I
ate some delicious short greens.
Even though I have delicious ribs, I'm staying in a scary place Even though I have
money, I
can't get the star
Anzai-sensei,
I wanted it, congratulations, congratulations,
next, next, it
's the last spurt, where are you all going? I
can't write
[laughing] It's
strong, strong, dark.
Yes, this looks sad.
Even though I want time to practice, I'll make sure of it.
[Music]
Oh
[Music] I'm
only getting money, but I do
n't have much. Is this something else? It's something else.  I
think it's a different program.
Ah, what, what, I found a mushroom. Ah, OK. I
feel like I found it.
[Music] I see.
[Music] I
guess I
just have to survive. In the end, ah, I see. I have to run away from the one I found.
Bikan beer. Ah, here we
come. -
Goku  It
's a game,
huh?
[Laughs] That's awesome. I think I'll
actually use it. I
'll retire from there.
[Music]
That's it.
[Laughs]
[Music]
Thank you.
5 stars is a big deal, but this is it.
Since the meat was taken away, I
had a lot more.
Yay, you've
got about that much, so
even if you distribute it,
where are you going next
? There's no one who has the warp thing. There's a
lot of gold there. This time, Chiara has a lot of money.  It's
going to fall somewhere close to you
[Music] I
feel like I'm always going to fail at this. It's really
good. From now on, I'm OK too. [Music] [Music] [Music] All I have to do is win this game.
That's what I mean. Let's go to the hot springs here. [Laughs] [Music] I hope it doesn't end there. It's nice in the game. Well, sometimes it's the start. There are stars, but the basics are strong. [Music] Ah, happenings.
What do you
mean by reverse cycle?  What's that?
[Laughs]
Oh, it's true, I can't help it, but I'll get it. It's
not bad.
[Music]
Buy it. It
's okay to buy it this turn. It
's on the 90th floor.
[Music]
Buy it here and
get it next time.  If you
put it out, it's a
chance [Music] Ah, that's going to change, but that's not the case at all. You'll be back on the next turn. This doesn't really make any sense. [Music] Really? I don't think I liked this that much. I wonder if they're going
to take my money. It's
ruined.  If you can jump, you
definitely have to fall.
OK, OK. I see. It's
okay to clear. OK. It's going to
crush you a bit.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Did you
slip and fall? At
first, Kari-chan was the one who did that.
He said he was really good at Super Mario Party.
[Music] I
said we always lose, so
today we're winning, so that's what I mean.
Yeah, it's the same as usual. What should I do about this?
Hmm, it doesn't make any sense anyway.  It's close,
but
it's different, but it
's open for everyone.
Yeah, it
's just me. I
passed it once. If I go there, I
'll pass it. Things I don't need, things I do
n't need.  It's
probably too much tea, but everyone's already
going to take the next one, so it's okay, it's okay.
[Laughter]
Things like this happen.  I wonder
if it will happen.
Should I use Dokkan here?
Where will the best and final place be? Will it
be near Kari-chan?
Exchange it here.
0%
But it feels like one chance will come on the left side. But I
don't know. That side.
[Music]
Oh well.  It's close but that turn  It's fourteen,
so it's
impossible.
Hello, you're right next door. Ah,
ah,
[music]
What the hell
? You're playing the entertainment of rich people.
What's more, you're doing so-and-
so here, and you
can even get coins. [Music]
[Music] I want to understand this. I'll go. I've never been solo. It's okay. I can't see anything fun. Wait a minute. Thank you.
Eh,
it's different from the previous practice. I
didn't listen. I did it.
[Music] I was
surprised. You
can accelerate.
[Music] There
were other ways to use that, but I hope that my boyfriend
somehow
manages to get it. I
won't ask.  I don't need it, I
don't need it
[Music]
How much is it? [Music] How are we going to fight?
[Applause]
[Music] It's
going the other way, it
's too much This is too much
[Music]
[Music]  There's
still a turnaround. It's
that far away. It's
surprisingly far away.
[Music] It was a
big deal, but I didn't need a big bang.
This is what you see.
[Music]
[Music] You're a
genius. You're
really hiding your worth now, and you
don't have much of a voice.
[Music]  I'm not
listening to you begging for your life. I'll
leave it to you, Merry
[Music]
In the end
Well, Hanepuri-chan was very kind just now,
thank you
[Music]
Thank you.  Is there
no choice but to buy it and get the money?
No, there are only two squares left, so I
think I'll definitely get it to 100%, but I'm going to use it in case I get one,
so this is the only place I have.
[Music] I
went to the trouble of buying it.  It's a
waste
because I have no choice but to use it. It's a waste to use it for just one square. I
probably used up all the items. I
thought I won today.
[Music] I wonder
what happened to the bonus. A lot of
lucky squares stopped.  A lot of
happenings
stopped. A lot of items. I didn't
think there would be a reversal at the end.
But now it's no surprise that anyone could buy it.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] For now,
let's
go to the whirlpool.  It's the opposite. It
feels good to have one different thing. It feels good.
OK, totally OK.
[Applause]
Who is that? Huh? That's
right. I
buy a lot of images of people winning.
[Music]
Happenings
Happenings that have stopped
[Music] It
was decided from the beginning, right? That
happened to me. Who won this time? What's
left behind?
[Music]
Ah, I'm
so happy
. Eh, I'm the happiest I've been since I started this live show.  I wonder if
that's enough?
[Music]
But, I
never expected to catch up.
But the mini-game was the best. It
was hot. Congratulations on your
good sleep. I
'm sorry that you had too much time.  I
suddenly apologized, and when I
said it wasn't the winner's line, it
was just a blue devil.
[Music]
[Applause] I
ate some delicious Yakiniku, Mario, and I
bought a party, so that's good.
Every year,
I had a fun start. It's a
great opportunity.  Is everyone going to give their impressions one by one?
Well then, from Claire to me, I
thought the first half was already over,
but it was a little more so. But it was fun, so I
thought it would be fun, but before I knew it, I
had moved up to 2nd place.
Thank you very much
[Music]
[Laughter] It's
famous among KFP that I always lose and have no choice but to lose, but today I was
shown that that's different.
[Music]
That's right, it's finally time to
make reservations, but that's not a bad thing.  I think,
uhm...
[Laughter]
[Music]
That
's not a problem because it was fun.
Yay.
Well then, Noel-san, who became an autograph before I knew it, is
fine. It was a little bit at first.  I was
a little confused at first because it was my first time collaborating on a game like this in my new house,
but
everyone was kind enough to watch over me, and the
listeners were also surprised.  It's always
been kind. It was really fun. We had some food and
yakiniku. It was a great
memory. Let's do something again next time. It's
really
difficult to do collaborations, but let's do it
online.
Hey, let's play again.  I
feel like we've
become good friends, and after this, we're
like Noel Senpai's Ham-chan.
[Music] I wonder if I
want to see Popo-chan. That
emoji looks like a muscle.
And that
Muscle Roots emoji in the bathroom
is that
Viking.
[Laughs]
[Music]
[  Music]
[Laughter] He's the
Grim Reaper, so he's been
cut down and taken away.
So what should we do to end it? When will it
fall into the dungeon and core?  I'm
tightening it. It's going to fall. Is that okay?
Okay, okay.
Thank you for the open apartment.
[Music]
[Applause]