[Music]
do
hey everyone
are you ready i prepared something
special
i prepared something special are you
ready
okay free try
try it
[Music]
hello
do you like this layout
do you like it
yay i
put in an effort so you
better put in effort as well into
learning in german all right
here is my effort
i also picked out a new background music
this one is not made for me it's just a
random free btm
that i picked out but i thought we
needed something
different everything is fresh
as fresh as the apple down there thanks
to everyone who
gave me an apple before before the
lesson
[Laughter]
i can't eat so many [\h__\h] apples who
do you think i am
at least fry them for me for god's sake
[Music]
anyway welcome to the first
the first fried apples are good the
first
german deutsche
german lesson but i have promised you
previously when i opened the memberships
i promised you guys i will give you
german lessons because
i guess i could have done this publicly
too
and maybe one day i will give a special
public german lesson
uh but i don't know why i just felt like
i wanted
my members to have something really
special yeah
yeah yeah yeah so
first of all uh
i'm gonna teach you this uh seriously
because there is no
no half-assed things when it comes to
takanashi kiara actually that's a lie
most of the things i do are quite
half-assed
but not today not today
um you guys have paid for this and i
will give you the good stuff
to get i will i will teach you some good
old german i'm serious because
i know it's funnier to teach you some
stupid swear words
but i don't know i don't want to
if i if i need to teach you in german
then i want to teach you properly but
also i don't
i don't know like any grammar rules
oh so we're gonna leave out the grammar
and you just have to like
figure it out yourself yeah
should be fine uh
so first of all my dear children
you will call me either
[Music]
miss teacher
or
[Music]
oh wait wait a second first of all i
have to learn english
there was a difference one is married
and one is not married right miss
says miss miss miss is not married right
and mrs is married or something like
that right
oh why why did i write queen that's not
even in german
miss what mrs
is married miss is sing okay
uh but in german it doesn't matter so
it means both oh i guess oh there's one
more word that's similar it's called fly
line but it's more like a
a cute way uh to call like a little
lady or like a child
that you want to address politely frau
is just uh i mean i guess you wouldn't
address someone
under 16
with frau however in good schools
for some reason every child gets
addressed by the teacher with afrau
or hair and then the last name
or the first name whatever if it's a bad
school then they just call each other by
the first day
in many cases at least in my experience
oh by the way the other the other
uh uh i'm not a good teacher let me tell
you that
in the beginning i'm not a good teacher
i'm probably going to lose track many
times
[Laughter]
but yeah the other misses or miss
is frow and
[Music]
stop correcting me in the super chat
today everything i
say is correct okay shut up
and mister is
should i write it down for you yes i
will
yeah okay
[Music]
this is like uh he's not i don't know if
he's here
but yeah that would be mr hook
uh in german they would probably
pronounce it
in in in japanese it's like they add a
little f
a slight f in there but it's
[Music]
did you write that down everyone
you better not forget it hold on i might
leave this one like
uh so you don't forget it i might leave
this
here oh perfect okay
i'm serious you better write it down
take a photo after each lesson
and send it to me on twitter as a reply
got it
you know
actually for real we could do that that
could be like a promotion for
my for my lessons to you and maybe we
get more more students
for real do that after each lesson
you take a photo of what you learned and
send it to my twitter
okay i might retweet some of those if
they look pretty okay
if they look messy then no
all right that's a good idea that's a
cute idea we should get like some
hashtag too
ah but then people will find out i guess
it's okay to find out what we learned
oh okay okay i'll think about the
hashtag maybe
okay moving on
let's let's teach you some important
uh phrases yeah
this is how you answer me always this is
yes nine
you never say this to me okay i only say
this to you when you ask me for some
stupid favors
it's no okay
[Music]
okay
by the way wait did this font have
smaller yeah yeah it does by the way uh
in german language
every how do you how do you call that
every [\h__\h] every
uh like um
[Music]
google translate is my assistant's
teacher
and actually no i use a different
website for that but
one second every noun every noun
yeah yeah every noun
[Music]
every noun it has a the first letter is
a
big so also with
so actually it's supposed to be like
that also every name
but i think that's the same in english
yeah
[Music]
so and the beginning of each sentence of
course
so this is correct okay
correct your notes you better be writing
notes
however it is yeah and nine no no no
don't capitalize them
i did but you don't
i just wrote it big because i know y'all
have
have have eye problems you probably
don't see this correctly
making his biggest yeah okay okay
by the way is the vgm too quiet or is it
good balanced
is it is it okay yeah or nine
okay now after this
important yes and no
uh i'll give you one more
[Music]
this is also an option maybe
it's flight repeat after me
[Music]
he
uh will you stream tomorrow
flight are you saying yeah
cute beautiful
call it a minute
hike
[Music]
but let's delete that okay beautiful we
have some
basics down now next basics
[Laughter]
uh hello this one is easy
it's hello hello hello
hello this is a really basic greeting
uh it's not very polite it's not
impolite it's nothing
it's just like how you would say hello
in english
[Music]
then there's also and probably a lot of
you have heard this before
it's like a polite way of saying hello
but it's also directly translated to
good day
and then there's oops wait you don't
even see that do you wait a second what
where is that oh oh my god what happened
one second it's too pink better
okay perfect beautiful beautiful
[Music]
uh then there's variations
like good morgen
does anyone know what good morgan means
[Music]
probably for the most of you it's a good
good morning and not a good attack
[Music]
yeah correct and you get a plus
good morning is good morgan correct
yes does anyone know what this
you probably don't see one second i'll
fix it in one what this means guten
abend does someone know what that means
correct correct good job
it's good evening [\h__\h]
yeah correct
good time
all of those people who answered that
are cheating
because they're probably german
themselves
yes i'm teaching you language what's
your problem
what's your problem huh
uh i have a
one more important greeting
um but it's hard to write that on my
keyboard because my keyboard
is japanese right now
one second let me google
[Music]
and then i'll copy that
i'll copy that one second because my in
german we have some letters
that you and in the english language
don't use and that is like that
on top of those you put two dots and
then you have
e oh and you don't do it you don't do it
with the e
you do it with the air
[Music]
if you put two dots it turns into a
and it's kind of hard to say for many
for many people it's hard to pronounce
but the chat is already writing them so
you can like copy them or whatever write
it down in your notes
so there's a greeting uh i think
in germany maybe it's only used in the
in the southern part of germany and very
much in austria
which is totally not where i'm from uh
but
this this greeting is very polite and
we uh we like to use it in the south
or in austria to say
hello at any time of the day it means uh
directly translated it means greet the
god
but uh we don't mean to greet the god so
we're just greeting you actually that's
in some way you would be calling the
person
in front of you god but no i don't know
uh even people who are not religious
say this yeah scott coy scott and oh
have you noticed
there's this letter here uh after the
u with the two dots there's a letter
that looks like a b
what could this be this is not a b
b looks like this this letter
uh let me
let me save this okay greet the god but
okay
i should i should so that people don't
misunderstand it's actually just
uh good greetings or something like that
you know yeah that letter
is um it's like uh
i need to like let me copy that
[Music]
one second you students think you're
smart or something stop it
i'm the teacher i'll teach you
have no patience no chill unbelievable
shut the hell up so this
is a s it means it's a
sharp s and
if you can't write it you would write it
out because you have a different
keyboard or something or some people
just do it for fun some people um
are too stupid to figure out at what
even german people
some people just don't know when to use
the sharp s
so they would uh just write double s
and you know there's words which have
double s in it for example like essen
which means eat
is it too much information asm which
means eat
but just because you have two s in it
doesn't mean that you would normally put
a shaft
s in it no no no no no no no no no no
a word where you would uh
say where would you where you put in the
shaft is s
for example uh
but anything else
this word if you don't write it with the
if the shot is s
then you look pretty stupid but you
could you could write it as if this
means
street by the way you could write it as
you could write it like that but it
looks
weird to most people it looks weird each
time
yeah so um if you don't have the right
keyboard it's always okay to just write
double
s but and also it's too hard to remember
from many of you probably in the
beginning so whatever
oh yes for the word for fun
is also normally written with a shaft as
s
but many people just write it like this
too
but remember not every word
with two s's
is also written as like this no no no no
no
nine nine nine nine nine nine nine okay
[Music]
so i'll leave that here for a little
while okay
okay oh by the way there is no
capital letter for this but also there
is never
a situation where you would need a
capital
s because uh it's just not used like
that it's always usually in the middle
or at the end of the word but never in
the beginning of the word so you also
never need a capital
uh chavez s teacher i got a pp
no you have to wait until the break for
[\h__\h] sake
oh my god i tell you every time
to go peeing at the break
you have 10 minutes break before the
lesson and then it's the one [\h__\h]
hour for the lesson
and then you have a [\h__\h] break again
and you tell me you can't [\h__\h] hold
it in
or time manage you know you learn many
things in school and some of these
things
you don't even realize you're supposed
to learn some things you learn outside
of the lesson maybe in the breaks or
in some other way and one of these
things is time
management it's not so hard it's not so
hard to learn that
and many times i tell you idiots and i
know what you're doing in the toilet
i know you're not most of the time
you're not even going to the toilet
you just want to escape from this lesson
but
excuse me why would you want to escape
from this lesson excuse me why
do you not enjoy the privilege of being
able to go to school
do you not appreciate this privilege do
you not appreciate that your parents
pay for your tuition huh you know how
hard your family works for that
unbelievable you are all spoiled
children
unbelievable so sit the [\h__\h] down and if
you need to pee for real
you either wait for the break or you pee
yourself now
okay thank you
okay song continuing
we got some greetings down um
important greetings
did you understand what it was just
talking about
[Music]
huh
no toilet in between the lessons
okay have you written everything down
can i delete
uh can i arrange the chalkboard
[Music]
what is it
did you get everything down
i shouldn't even be asking you this i'm
spoiling you by asking you this you
should be you should be writing this
down
as soon as i'm writing it down okay so
next time i'm not gonna ask you it will
be away like swoosh
and then it's gone okay
next step
[Music]
this one is easy it means
guess what name
but you capitalize this because it's uh
an uh what was it again a noun a noun
this is a noun
so we have to capitalize it
yeah it's the noun for name
name repeat after me
name
very well and
if you want to say mine and my name is
something something you say mine
this is easy for english speakers
because it sounds exactly
like mine yeah and that's also what it
means
[Music]
so this looks almost like the english
version
easy mai or ah okay
my name is something something
got it repeat after me
[Music]
i highly doubt that your name is kiara
okay correct yourself
one more time mine name
east now what is your name
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
wonderful wonderful wonderful
yo okay
so and
then you can say um
v que esta this
means how are you but
informal understand
write that [\h__\h] down writing down the
pronunciation well if you can't remember
it yeah go ahead
it shouldn't be that difficult though uh
we get this here is made up
made up out of these words how
going is you
but it means how are you all right
repeat after me
get s
dia you don't have to say
you just say like dia pretty much and
the the h in the kid is the
silent okay
v good esther
[Music]
good job good job
nice very nice it means how are you
there's a
polite version of this
[Music]
now it means the same thing but this is
polite
uh i may explain to you polite speech
in a separate stream but
german has um not as much polite forms
as japanese
in some way maybe yeah
no well i know there's a lot of polite
speech in german
compared to english there's much more
but uh well i guess we'll
i'll leave it here but we'll mainly uh
this by the way means it's the same as
above i don't know if you guys use that
for now we'll just uh go mostly with
informal speech
oh yeah if you talk to me you should
probably
use the polite one you should ask me
and i would say good because i'm with
all of you together today
it makes me happy
just kidding i'm not not happy about you
being here or anything like that
okay now um
actually before we should add something
in here
after you say your name you might want
to ask
the other person what their name is so
you could make it easy uh and say
owns dinah and which means
and yours or
you make it complicated we all love our
lives being complicated don't we
you could say the heist
oops oh [\h__\h] i don't have that letter do
i have it somewhere here
god damn it do i have it copied yes i do
okay
this one has a sharpest s in it it looks
[\h__\h] weird if you write it out like
that so remember to put the shaft s
in there okay be high stool
this is what oops
what's your name
so after i say my name is
kiara i ask you
or or or um
[Music]
yes very well good job or
polite one always gotta be polite okay
v heisen oops
hi sen now this is complicated again
because the verb the the verb changes
as well basically
the word see when it's written uh
and the word c itself is like uh a
plural form uh of
of like you would say uh
okay here goes kiara explaining grammar
when german is her first language um
i you would for example say uh
they okay it's steak they
like to go ice eating this
normally this is how you see but for
the polite speech polite addresses
in german you use this plural like you
you talk to the person
as if they were plural just as in
uh did i write it yeah
normally means
uh for example
uh eska felt in the niche and this also
means day
yeah so you talk to the
person you want to talk to politely talk
to them as if there were more than one
person however
however normally if you use
the actual word day you wouldn't
capitalize it
you would write it just uh just like
that inanen
but if you write if you
see my mom already looking at losing
track
but but it implies
speech as an address to a person
uh you capitalize it normally you don't
capitalize it if you use it the way it's
supposed to be used
do you understand firsthand here
[Laughter]
yeah yeah this is not so important right
now i just wanted to
um somehow roughly explain
okay uh where was i where was i
behind the heisen c this is just uh
the polite way to
uh formal the formal way to say uh
what's your name
[Music]
okay we can almost have a conversation
do you remember what we wrote before
this
you have it written down right so i say
guten tag repeat after me
[Music]
mine
and yours
[Music]
now i will teach you the answer to that
question
one second
good
[Music]
good good
means guess what it means good
remember this web this was also in the
greeting wasn't it like guten tag
guten avent good mor again
so easy to remember but just as good
you would say make it is
[Music]
good means
i am fine sorry
i am fine
[Music]
you could also say
which means bad ah
mia ass fleshed
[Music]
i feel bad or i'm not fine
ah repeat after me
mia get as good
repeat after me
get as good
[Music]
then repeat after me meal get as flat
but i'm feeling actually fine so
everything's cool
good job good job yay
good job my dear students good job i
don't hear you
but i hope you're pronouncing it
correctly
by the way is the pronunciation of the
of the ch
difficult for you
[Music]
i hope not um many
people when they like to make fun of uh
german
they like to over pronounce this
uh these letters this letter combination
you don't have to go like
although in switzerland they like to do
that
but normally you can just say it softly
like um
[Music]
you're like a cat imagine you're a cat
and then someone picks you up and you
don't like them
you go like but now do they softer
[Music]
okay
okay good job let me drink some water
hydration check everyone
vasa is water by the way
although many of you i told you you
can't pee yet so you shouldn't drink too
much
either pee yourself or
go in the brick i told you i told you
yes vasa yes yes yes yes yes we
shouldn't learn this word yet but
you write it like that it's water
but anyway let's delete that okay
uh what else could you say if if um
if i ask you how you are how you feeling
what else could you say um you could say
[Music]
so
that means it's like
i don't know how to translate that to
english
[Music]
it's like a it's like
i'm a right but not quite all right
is that fine to say yeah yeah yeah i use
it i use it a lot
you could scout
i would i would say it when i'm not
exactly good but i'm not exactly
bad or when i'm actually feeling bad
but i i'm too lazy or too annoyed
to tell the other person more about it
because if i say i feel bad
then they would always ask me like
why and so i just say esquito so
don't ask me questions oh by the way
this is important
in english in english language
i have noticed that
everyone asks how are you
and they don't expect an answer the
answer to how are you is often how are
you
[Laughter]
or it's just like a greeting in english
however
in in german that's why i always i
always reply when someone asks me how
are you even that even though they don't
accept uh
an answer was that was a very confusing
thing for me when i learned english
but in german language if you ask
someone how they are
uh you get an answer and sometimes you
get a very detailed answer
and it's it's also um expected of you
to ask everyone how they are if you see
them for the first time today
or if you talk to them for the first
time today you should always ask them
how they are and
normally they're just going to say good
or bad
uh but that normally it ends there
but yeah don't ignore the question yeah
i think it's a very european thing
too yeah i don't understand why in
english language you ask this question
and you don't want to hear an answer
then why the [\h__\h] do you ask me
yeah yeah yeah yeah so
i ask you and you tell me the answer
everyone
we get estia tell me honestly
we get esther
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] why are you feeling just
mad
what the hell what happened
it's good well what's your problem
what the [\h__\h] is your problem why are
you feeling so so
it's 6 a.m i love how
i'm teaching you a language and this is
like we're in school and it's like
actually in a
at a really early time
just like school although 6 am 6 6am
when i went to school it was like
the time where i would uh get up because
uh
my school usually was pretty far away
would take me a long time i would also
have to do my makeup and [\h__\h] and even
when
even when school starts at 7 15 i would
always get up at 6.
it was horrible horrible i hated getting
up at 6.
that was so [\h__\h] horrible
especially in winter when it wasn't even
bright outside what the [\h__\h]
you get up and you get out of your
apartment and still not bright oh my god
oh it's so depressing and every time i
would ask myself
why do we have to go to school this
early why can't school start at 10 or
something i could
i could get much more sleep and i could
concentrate much better
and then i heard stuff like uh the human
brain
doesn't actually really start working
until like later
in the day so why do we start at six
or like okay 8 a.m when we start so
early doesn't make sense but but for you
guys
there's time difference so what can i do
about it don't complain to me about it
i can't do anything about it
not my fault that you live so far away
from me
move over no don't that's creepy
okay we can pretty much have a basic
conversation now
[Music]
next question uh can i delete that [\h__\h]
did you write that [\h__\h] down everyone
yeah
as you write that [\h__\h] down
okay where you better
nine to top sneak ups clue nine nine
nine
sorry the super shot made me laugh much
more than this
and i should have oh yeah i'll delete
that
[Music]
oops this one can stay ah
actually let's see that let's leave that
and
continue here okay we continue with this
serious german lesson
no the lesson is not over shut up
sit down next
is
[Music]
this means where are you from
or vulvon stew
this means where do you
live and maybe you have noticed
[Music]
in english both seem to be translated to
wear
[Music]
however actually wool hair means
it's like two words together it's like
wool and hair
and that means where from so actually
it's not the same translation
got it
so this is like and you could all you
could even say
vulcan yeah and now it's a more direct
translation
like it fits to the english translation
better now it's exactly
uh vo is where comst is actually
come and do is you
and here is from from
and volvo is where leave
you directly translated understand
[Music]
[Laughter]
repeat after me boo
comes to hair
[Music]
boo comes to her
good and repeat after me
wants to do
[Music]
good job
you all come from such random places all
over the world you can look up what your
country means in german but for example
america is america
and japan is
japan and
germany i think the germans know what
their country means in german
uh
anything you want to know any country
spain
[Music]
canada is canada
brazil is brazilian
[Music]
netherlands is nidaland
this is even saw on the chocolate yeah
oh yeah
and so on philippines is uh
[Music]
oh you got me there
okay i think that's correct
fairbands is filipinian i think right
right i'm correct right germans help me
out
[Music]
with ph the [\h__\h]
this never happens
[Music]
i don't know man i don't i'm confused
okay i'm confused too many words
[Laughter]
anyway get the rest from google get the
rest from google i
i'm not going to tell you i have a very
goddamn country on this world
so i would say
ich komme house
[Music]
is
repeat after me and then add your own
country
if you already looked it up on google
[Music]
each comment
all right you didn't repeat after me i
didn't hear your voice
i know you're just writing that in the
chat down i told you to repeat after me
say it say it out loud
okay i think now i heard a few more
people although there's still some
people
who apparently it's too much words uh
too much work to say this
one sentence apparently god damn it
[Music]
is
well
good job everyone good job good job good
job
good job
so
[Music]
we put that there
and then
let's let's write down here
[Music]
upstate
we continue i'm teaching you in german
in a serious way
so next thing
um
[Music]
you have to find out how old the other
person is
to figure out if they're legal or not
how old are you
[Music]
what now this is an important question
important question by the way
in many countries you are um
legal i suppose uh or are allowed to
drink alcohol and whatever
with 21 right i think in japan and in
america
it's with 21 both legal age and drinking
age i guess
yeah this is crazy where i'm
from alcohol and smoking
is from 16 years old and you're illegal
when you're 18 years old
[Music]
although not every alcohol is allowed
with a 16. and as if 16 wasn't early
enough
most of there are so many children who
already smoke and drink when they're 12
or 11 or whatever it's absolutely
ridiculous i tell you
i tell you it's [\h__\h] ridiculous don't
drink or smoke before you're you're
actually in that legal age i know it's
i know it's like in so many like i feel
like this is all over the world everyone
just drinks and smokes whenever
oh although i think for america 21
is pretty late wait wait the actual
drinking
you can't oh you can't legally drink
beer before you're 21
that i mean i don't like alcohol but
that sounds to me like it's pretty late
for smoking generally i wish i wish
smoking was
uh later than 16.
i feel like 16 is too early for smoking
but it doesn't matter it doesn't matter
which
age you make it legal uh
because they're just gonna smoke
whenever the [\h__\h] they want these stupid
children stupid [\h__\h] children
i for myself have never smoked in my
whole life
[Music]
never and i didn't even think about it
because it's disgusting
[Music]
yeah 18 18 seems like an okay
age for that but i feel like 16 is too
early
i don't know man 16 for drinking and now
uh drinking and smoking
but it's not every alcohol by the way i
think i already said that oh yeah that's
ridiculous don't you think it's
ridiculous
anyway we are pistol v
art beast
by the way the polite form of this would
be
v alt
c this is the same
but formal
but you have to capitalize uh the s
because otherwise now good example if
you don't capitalize this
it would mean how old are they
oops if you don't capitalize the s
[Music]
because i'll teach you one more thing in
a moment
i don't want to teach you the numbers
right now so you'll you'll not really
get the answer to this question yet
because there's a lot of numbers
there's a lot of numbers i'll teach you
the numbers in a different
stream
[Music]
we add cincy i for myself
um
[Music]
how do you say eternal but timeless
let's say
[Music]
um
sounds so weird but i guess it means
eternal just how how our
me and your eternal love
[Music]
is
okay so this answer is only for me all
of you
all of you idiots are not eternal
ha ha ha ha you will die at some point
i will never die for real ha ha
suck it
you will find out the answer to this in
the next stream
[Music]
what else
i think we're pretty much at the end
because our lesson was
uh shouldn't be longer than one hour i
think all of your brains already seem to
stop working
[Music]
so what did we learn today everyone
we learned how to say a greeting
[Music]
we said guten tag good morning
let me tell you one more ah let's say
let me teach you the goodbyes
[Music]
one goodbye you already know all of you
yes let me hear you say it
the one thing we always say at the end
of our streams
yes correct alf
[Music]
do you capitalize that do you
i don't think so oh
this is not i i i guess it's a noun
yeah in this case it's a noun you can
venezine can just be a verb but in this
case it's a noun
because directly translated it means
on
[Music]
a reunion or something like that
but it means like see you again seeing
you
again
oh you say oops okay yeah okay i don't
god damn it i don't have an u on my
keyboard
[Music]
one second i got it kiss
oops this is very formal
the auf wiedersehen is more uh i mean
the alfida zine is very formal the juice
is not very formal it's
quite informal but we use it most of the
time
and this means just goodbye
informal auf wiedersehen yeah i would
say that's
it's pretty formal and it means to you
again
if you want to say see you never again
you could say
[Music]
it means see you never again
just kidding but no we don't want to use
this
no no no uh
one more thing that's useful is
and here we have the goot again which
means
good yes correct means
good night
this is both informal and formal i mean
you use it in
in any situation you know
[Music]
so at the end of the day when you
are in bed with your imaginary lover
you look at them and say good enough
and then you close your eyes the next
morning you wake up
you look around and well it was all
imaginary so of course there's no one to
say
good morning to oh well too bad
sad good enough
oh and of course we have
[Music]
thank you oops i don't have it
struggle the struggle
wait i i have it again
these stupid letters show up here
i have it i have it
[Music]
there we go this means
thank you very much while danke only
means thanks okay
[Music]
did you write that down now we have to
repeat all of these
repeat after me
[Music]
juice
good
[Music]
is
uh you are welcome
however bitter
bitter can mean you're welcome but also
it can
mean
[Music]
please you can say
that could you please pass me the salt
but you can also say
[Music]
you're welcome i'll i i i i like to do
that
or whatever
[Music]
okay there is no salt to pass
god damn it god damn it that's a good
thing that's a good thing
okay we learned so many things good job
good times applaud yourself
applaud yourself
[Music]
you concentrated for a whole hour and
learned
german for a whole hour now you think
you could go to the toilet now but no
we will do a super chat reading
for the members only
a test
um okay
am i not testing you the whole time
maybe one day we can
or next time oh you could write me an
essay at some point oh yeah
[Music]
do they say that in english too german
teachers like to say that
when students hear that on the bell and
they want to leave
teacher is like
[Music]
a club and a collab is uh in what
one two three two hours
so no problem no problem wait two hours
it's a nine right yeah should be fine
what is the hashtag for the notes okay
everyone
uh all the notes shall be
[Music]
sent to me on twitter
with the hashtag
[Music]
this is uh i have to make it bigger
here
wonderful everyone
send me your notes hopefully they're
written nicely and
readable otherwise i cannot grade your
homework send me a notes
at hashtag deutschmachiana
on twitter i will make a tweet um after
after uh the stream actually i want to
take a screenshot
one second let me take a screenshot
[Music]
[Laughter]
stay still i got that whatever this is
okay
i always use a snipping tool
probably should use something else for
that
[Music]
okay thank you now we shall proceed to
the super chat reading
should we stay on the screen because
it's so pretty
i'll do a close-up of me now
okay i will read only the ones from this
stream and the others will be uh uh read
another time
[Music]
hope you enjoyed today's lesson i hope
you enjoyed it
i enjoyed it that was actually fun
although i
have to be honest i started to stream
without really uh
knowing what exactly i'm gonna teach you
so that was that was pretty spontaneous
for the next time these were just the
basics but for the next time i should
probably um
like decide beforehand what exactly i
want to teach you
if we keep this going you might
eventually really end up being able to
speak
german quite well hmm
[Music]
if you're actually gonna be serious with
it as serious as i am
[Music]
okay super chat time here we go
um deal of 67 thank you shin
looking for the top donkey shin do you
have 67
thank you well next is dan kashan or so
many apples
sha
how dare you not be there just kidding
thank you though thank you
hope you come later do you love 67 thank
you shane wild next is tankishan
big game of three 11 thank you soon vega
for 311
deal of 67.
wild next is thank you very much
it's always the same people mix it up a
little bit
do you love 67
i like how you try to change it to
german but it's wrong
[Music]
side question
a favorite german artist
i'm not very cultured in that matter
unfortunately
the favorite german artist oh no idea
but mozart for the win who is a not an
artist in that in that sense but no time
[\h__\h] yet
[Music]
cough drop in german is
who's then bomb
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
exactly although i'm the only one rating
you guys in this
in this lesson i rate you
you may not rate me
[Music]
by the way in in germany austria and so
on
there is no abcdef for the notes
we given einstein
and in germany sx
so the six is the worst one
in austria there is no six there's only
five one to five
so we give one to five and one is the
best one here
we don't give the letters we give
numbers
[Music]
[Laughter]
now here we got it going here's finally
new people probably this is where the
stream started
[Music]
ranspi dankeshen oh by the way
honey garlic fried chicken [\h__\h] yes
29 thank you wild nexus
headstand 29 do you love 67
[Music]
oh actually uh i requested a bunch of
um square enix games
i don't have the permission yet but i
did request a bunch of them a bunch of
them are already bought
so i hope i get permission for them
but once i get permission for all these
games
one day there might be a final fantasy
yes yes yes
[Music]
i mean there's many ways to say it
you could say like
you could say there's many ways to say
it you could say chef
you could say
[Music]
most people probably say chef all the
other ones are too long
they're correct but they're too long you
could say
you could say
you could say yeah
it's like boss
[Music]
most people say chef
wait i want to read that message though
today the kfb
learns german from our phoenix let's
open our books and listen to kiara as
the good little chicks we are
those that misbehave shall be fried
right away whom them kfp
to class yay
well said well said thank
[Music]
thank you so much that is very very very
generous of you thank you
let's make a good first impression thank
you for the apple as well
[Music]
thank you thank you
looking for the top function
[Music]
looking for the top
there you go the german you were asking
for
[Music]
thank you so condemned
b
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you oh
should i always eat apples now when i
get red super jets
[Music]
sapphire
foreign
and yes it's going to be archived it
will be archived so you can look back on
it
[Music]
what's the german version of choose
smooch
i mean the sound the sound you mean the
sound
or the word kiss is kus
k-u-s-s
[Music]
a smooch is a [\h__\h] although i think
maybe that's
uh mostly used in austria and south
germany
it's [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
the sound of a kiss though oh
maybe schmutz no wait that's that's more
the sound of eating
both i guess actually yeah
[Music]
h m a t z
there's not really there's not really a
written
sound for kissing is it is there
oh yeah maybe like mwah what m-u-a
i can't think of anything else
[Music]
there is no help as teaching also kiara
skips grammar
that's because i i grew up learning
german i mean in school i also learned
german grammar but
i mean it just came natural to me so i
didn't really pay much attention
it's also not not hard but now i don't
remember like the rules if i had to
teach you guys
i mean i can try at some point but do
you want to learn german grammar
are you sure that you want to learn
german grammar
do you want to learn uh
the the articles for every [\h__\h]
german word
you know that we have this thing with
daddy does
[Music]
for example the apple is there
upfa but
[Music]
the
pizza is
[Music]
yeah we have gender and gendered nouns
like articles
are you sure you want to learn that from
me i don't think you want to learn that
i haven't oh for people who are actually
studying
german right now in school or whatever
that's actually
fun that you have an extra lesson with
me now
oh my god you guys know what someone
told me
someone told me that their friends told
them
that um they had a
japanese class i guess yeah japanese
class
the student was not japanese but they
had a japanese class and their teacher
[Music]
never mind i can't tell them now mine i
just realized i can't tell that story
never mind
i just mixed something up
sweating nervously
[Music]
[Laughter]
cliffhanger
you and i can't tell you anyway
anyway
[Music]
watson's concoction kestrel
a tongue twister
looking for the top thank you
friendly neighborhood lesbian
wow if i remember correctly the rule is
that the shaft is s the one that looks
like a b
comes after a long vocal an umlaut or
a diff thong what the [\h__\h] is that
[Music]
i don't know might be correct whatever
you just said
might be correct
[Music]
a combination of vowels
anyway i don't know if that is correct i
can't guarantee that chi bro isotope
thank you darren wade general beckham
thank you
i can't remember how you said crew squad
could you repeat
[Music]
two sisters reminding me so friend and
i'm wondering if that's as creepy in
german as it sounds in english
[Laughter]
[Music]
people never flirt with me so i can't
really
judge that very much but
[Music]
sad
that does sound it's not a good pickup
line
if someone would say that to me
i would say [\h__\h] you
[Music]
that's uh you look like my next
girlfriend
is what he he wrote in german
yeah it's not a really good pick-up one
maybe something like um
the shout-outs as opposed to
[Music]
you look like you fell from heaven
okay i'm bad with pick-up lines that
that one goes differently
doesn't that sound different that's
different right how do you say that one
[Music]
i'm not good with okay honestly if you
want to flirt with me just say
you're sexy kiara you're [\h__\h] sexy
just tell me that and i'm happy
oh tell me you're beautiful
okay how how to hit on kiara
look into her eyes deeply she'll
probably look away
and be embarrassed now you
you you put your hand on her chin
and hold it so she's forced to look
straight
at you now
you stare at her say nothing and
kyara will be like
what the [\h__\h] is it and then you say
[Music]
your eyes look like the universe
yeah you maybe thought that i would say
something stupid right now but that
that's actually
genuinely what i like to hear
[Music]
and then you kiss
just kidding don't kiss me
[Music]
okay enough of that
till of 67 ancient eggs are redundant
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
can you say this line with angry angry
kiara sound
eh
[Music]
i would never say such a thing because
balchemist is kind of a lame
lame swear word i would never use that
[Music]
did that sound angry i tried
if i'm angry i'm more like
[Music]
i'd have a fake chance again
yes that was
much more aggressive than what that
super chat wrote
[Laughter]
[Music]
that was pretty bad that was pretty bad
don't be scared of me
that's hot can i ask him
no nine
i remember the only stream clips allowed
because that needs to be clipped
[Music]
no i guess not i'm sorry
should probably shouldn't be clipped
ninth sorry
um i'll just ask me to say that again
in the public stream
[Music]
is it always silent art it's not really
that silent
it's more like it's like a sloppy
pronunciation
uh but it's no problem to say it like
it's not
everyone talks like that the r gets kind
of lost here and there
so when i say my miner my
miner there's r at the end but you
pronounce it like it's an a
at the end you know miner
but it's not always silent
um sorry i need to hurry up
[Music]
turkish thank you soon
foreign how do you say please release
the streams archive for everyone rather
than keeping it members only
in german you're on fire today i think
everyone should get to see this
should i should i do that i don't know
i mean i want to keep it as something
special between you and me
wait like a month
[Music]
should i wait and then release it i know
callie does the same thing
[Music]
like after a month would you would you
have a problem with that everyone i i
don't want to decide right now but what
about you guys
[Music]
nine
yeah yeah yeah
nine nine nine yeah yeah
keep it from members only
maybe only the first lesson and
everything after that
no just the first lesson to give them a
taste of what they're getting
so just in case i ended up making this
one public
hello hello
non-members you better join now you
better join
now right now why aren't you not a
member yet you idiot
okay that's a preview lesson very good
very good okay that could be a thing
okay stonks
sell the archive for ten dollars
no okay that's a good idea yeah maybe
maybe just the first one i'll i'll
public
uh i'll put public done in the future
sometime soon
thank you guys for your input
[Music]
foreign
german um and um means the exact
opposite one is driving over something
and the other one means driving around
something which one you say
depends on the i guess cell depends on
the pronunciation
that's true that's true actually you can
say
[Music]
i i drove over a human being
or you say is
have it mentioned
[Music]
um then mentioned
you would change it a little bit in that
in that
sentence you would change the word a
little bit i guess or the order of the
word
but yeah basically you're right that's
funny
[Music]
like driving over something or driving
around something
it's a life and death situation but in
german it's just about the pronunciation
or like not the pronunciation but more
like where you put
the uh the accent but how do i say that
which part of the word you use
[Music]
stress yes stress thank you emphasize
yes exactly
[Music]
oh good job was that google translated
or was it actually your own knowledge
if that was your own knowledge good job
thank you
inclusive foreign
[Music]
you have to write without the uh without
the r with two dots just
that you would use for freud line kiara
but for frau piana
you don't need those two dots
[Music]
no there is no equivalent for lol in
germany we just also say lol some people
even say it out loud
[Music]
now let me refresh
and then we should be done
i need to prepare uh minecraft because i
i didn't check yet if the thing is fixed
so after i'm done here i need to fix the
minecraft thing
because i have a collab with cali after
this i hope everyone will be there
[Music]
very good i love how you all are using
the german you just learned
oh okay there we go milter thank you
logical paradox
99.99
[Music]
to to yanked recently and your streams
have really helped me feel better
oh damn one day i'll have to do that too
before i went to japan this year
i i went to the doctor and
the doctor told me not right now but
sometime soon i should think
start thinking about when i wanted they
don't hurt yet
but i should already start thinking
about doing it
before it starts hurting she told me but
i don't want to do it
i don't no no no no no no
no thank you
[Music]
what getting my wisdom teeth out was
actually pretty awesome i had the best
nap doing it
what
damn but afterwards must have hurt a lot
no
i'm too scared
[Music]
yeah probably will hurt a lot later no
anyway taking a class like this for the
first time in years was actually really
fun
what's your favorite funny sounding word
in german funny
[Music]
asking me these kind of questions out of
nowhere i have no idea
funny funny
probably sounding weird
[Music]
i can just tell you that there is one
funny sounding city
in austria there's a city called
[\h__\h] not [\h__\h] but
written as [\h__\h]
but it's a [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
we have a city in austria where
it it's called [\h__\h]
don't misunderstand don't get it wrong
[Music]
foreign
have you ever fathered about playing any
other fire emblem games after beating
three houses
i never thought of it but yeah i would i
guess but probably not on stream
mistral dankeshin wilson 97 in danger
sharon paul m dankeshen
berendick thank you in three days you
have a german test oh my god yes this
clown is studying totally
cute anime girls are the best thank you
soon kill you and dance deluded sprite
thank you
very do you love much dankeshen
could we get prakiara as an official
outfit
yoona you know designed the the this
and drew the thumbnail oh
so i don't think this will ever be an
official outfit
but you're welcome to draw fan art of
this specific outfit
if you would like to
[Music]
dance
thank you
[Music]
answered the question because i don't
really have a favorite
german artist sorry about that
uncultured burp some might say
[Music]
question andrew thank you snoop dogg kfc
can you say something in german dalek
you mean uh
which one uh austrian dialect
again speak but i'm australian don't get
it wrong
i'm not it's not like i'm austrian or
something i can speak austrian dialect
but uh
[Music]
if you ask me to speak it out of nowhere
that's a bit difficult um
[Music]
what should i say you're late
how dare you be late to the lesson
[Music]
yeah that's a dialect word
how much different is austria from
germany by the way i've never really
left the country so i've never been to
austria
it's pretty much the same just better
and too much sky dankeshen kazuma duncan
[Music]
looking for the top as a thank you for
uh the german i guess thank you
[Music]
thank you oh another red super chat
thank you as well thank you
[Music]
i want the apple give me the apple hum
m my nose keeps on being itchy why is my
nose so
itchy
in german you would say
my nose is itching
[Music]
is
i like putting how you wrote that down
just from hearing it
[Music]
you
being itchy
just gonna drop this here because i
probably won't be able to watch oh thank
you anyway oh
[\h__\h] that was a different stream
goddammit it's it's me
mixing up again with the collab stream
that's coming up
seoul gundam thank you 67
tickets
[Music]
days
oh one last one for looking for the top
thank you lots of salted germans
okay
[Music]
hmm
in the end i'm from australia so i don't
know what the [\h__\h] i'm talking about i
don't know what the [\h__\h] you guys are
talking about
i don't even know german why did you
guys listen to me this was all [\h__\h]
i'm
australian i don't know german and thank
you for coming today today's lesson
this was everything i could tell you
i am australian mate a
kangaroo koala spider
called crocodile thank you everyone
and i'll see you later at the
collab with kelly well what it is
uh thank you and at the end of every
stream we say
i have a surprise for you at the end of
every stream we say
[Music]
you very super chat patrick
and what do you mean you don't hear
music
oh [\h__\h] wait oh god dammit
[Music]
hey
you