[Music]
so
okay
[Music]
happy easter
there go my cats
hello
happy easter kfp
uh
hello
yay yes as always now
these are my painting gloves now so
they are dirty by default now yeah and
it's okay because today we'll be
painting so there will be lots of dirty
stuff
yes hello happy easter let me actually
put down the
uh one second we did it wrong wrong
order here satisfactionary
animation here we go
[Music]
there we go that's better
so
uh welcome uh everybody we are
celebrating easter today by draw a
painting
and decorating
easter eggs uh
i will be uh today i have my table on
this side so i'll probably be looking
over to this side a lot
uh
and my microphone is over there so yeah
it might sound weird and but but but i
prepared a lot for this setup
um i prepared
many things wait let me put on my other
glove too i'm only wearing one glove um
for easter we used to um
paint
eggs
yes
and
uh
even we did that and additionally
something else or we did just uh or we
just did uh left the painting to someone
else but i also remember then hiding the
eggs and the eggs and and uh chocolate
and all kinds of things somewhere in the
in a garden or in a park and then going
to look uh for it yes so land for all
god
i need to get rid of these cat hairs i
don't want them sticking to my eggs
so
um i have many things prepared uh i can
also put on here this is the wrong
outfit but
wrong outfit but let me pull on my wish
hi putting on my my sleeves
[Music]
that's that's my record
i got it recalled recently
[Music]
i got it recorded recently
oh no she's
just sitting there
recently um
she's just she's just very active um
uh raccoon's name is um a bonkers as i
told you before
[\h__\h] is now lucas i love you but
no no no no
she likes the plastic
[Laughter]
ah no it's a record they do not see the
colors my cats are different colors
no no you need to go you need to go get
off the table
i love you so much one second i mean
i love you too i love you too my sweet
sweet cherry pie my sweet raccoon oh man
why are you so hyper right now
you say that's just how raccoons do it
oh yeah i understand raccoons raccoons
be like that yeah very very um
um active and they do whatever the hell
they want
yes i have a raccoon
yeah okay you're not gonna get on my
table anymore mrs
raccoon
bonkers app she's absolutely bonkers
yeah i am no no my cats are blue and
orange but this is my raccoon um anyway
uh she better not come back she usually
doesn't do that
my cats don't do that either
suddenly i was like what the [\h__\h] that
never happened before
[Laughter]
oh man
oh man she was like really um
well she wanted some love you know
but that's okay we will not let that
uh keep us from doing stuff where was i
um
where was that what was i doing what was
i saying
so i got some things to decorate today
this is just um i just wanted the basket
it didn't come with these but i wanted
to eat these so
uh and see what's inside so can i eat
them right now i've been waiting to eat
them i bought them
yesterday i've been waiting to eat them
i know they're um illegal
in america
it's chocolate guys how can it be
illegal
you guys are just crazy over there
let me eat this but the the thing about
this chocolate is the reason reason why
i like it so much it's not necessarily
because of what's inside actually it's
not at all because of what's inside it's
because
i um open it with gloves
ah there we go
it's because the chocolate is so good
i took them out
yeah yeah they're choking and whatever
but but there's so many other things you
can choke on too like people's actual
hands so
are we gonna say hands are
illegal now
[Music]
and they're illegal
because they can choke people
and many other toys of course as well so
but the chocolate is so good and the the
company makes a lot of other chocolate
as well of course but i don't know they
taste similar but this one has a really
specific balance of
of flavors oh is my raccoon again
raccoon and but do you want the
chocolate too i better turn off this
camera i'll show you what was inside in
a moment let's let's celebrate easter by
eating uh an uber rashong's eye we call
it uber rashu's eye surprise egg
[Music]
raccoon
bonkers
could say meow
what is it what did i i gave you so much
attention today already i gave her so
much attention today i swear i swear
i swear i gave her even a snack
even a snack yeah yeah i gave her her
favorite snack
um
we don't talk about bunkers now anymore
okay i want to eat my my chocolate egg
fish
diet
i haven't eaten this in a long time
bonkers is on standby on the floor
[Music]
oh my god it's so good
oh
[Music]
now sorry i kept it a secret
that i have a raccoon but
actually i
i am i brought it back
yesterday
when i was with my mom
yeah i am she has a lot of crazy animals
living there
um
[Music]
is on the table good that the camera is
not on
she will
eventually calm down i'm sure
um and then go somewhere else and sleep
um because she also likes to sleep very
much just like my cats they're very
very much in sync
[Music]
she's very interested in my setup
she's just doing um
she's literally on on my table now
making a pose like
telling me to draw me like my french
girls draw her like my french girls
oh
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh that was so good
oh the chocolate is so good
[Music]
okay
can my cats please leave the room i will
oh my god go
my cats and my raccoons please all of
you
please leave the room
[Music]
okay
um
my cats and my raccoons have left the
room i have the
situation under control
at least for now
[Music]
all right so
here i have the egg
[Music]
shall we see
what the chocobo present is inside
i want to see
what is it oh it looks like a dog no
it's an ice bear
[Music]
why is it a nice bear
why why why
oh my god there's apparently
there's apparently a phone game
where you can like uh
use the ice bear
if you take a picture from the
iceberg or something what a pull out
there of course wow
i'm gonna put it together
it has three parts
three parts
[Music]
we're putting the buttons together
but
and
[Music]
not very good with my hands right now
oh sheesh
oh the head moves
[Music]
it looks like this okay
well who needs that i really just want
it because of the chocolate i have
another one we can eat it later
okay
okay and then there was oh yeah i was i
don't remember what i was saying i was
saying that i only bought the basket
because i wanted the basket to put my
own eggs in there
but it comes with you know easter
chocolate
now we can put it here as reservation uh
this is a decoration
[Music]
chicken a chick
an easter chick
some more bunnies
[Music]
some more easter chicks with liver
uh some some shells eggshells on its
head
a green bunny
another chicken
and some eggs
i have
a lot of chocolate
yes okay now what else do i have i have
uh
colors
um
and
i have
here eggs now these are
because i am a big brain
artist these are made out of plastic so
they will not
break
i can grab them pretty tightly and they
will not break
genius and they come with
these little
strings
that
i can attach to them and then hang them
on you know like bushes in the garden
and so on which i won't be doing
but
uh in order to um dry them it might be
useful because i actually built a
station you don't see it but i built a
station where i can hang them up
very well prepared today and actually
these came with um
[Music]
these came with some pens
but i don't know if they're good if
they're any good also it's just a couple
colors just six colors i have way more
acrylics
so
i will try them but they're tiny
i mean that might be good i don't know
maybe for some detail work or or some
groundwork i don't know we can try them
i guess
uh so we have uh how many eggs that one
does oh oh and those those uh
those thingies to hang them up for like
also for christmas trees
so that will be useful
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve eggs it's 12 eggs
[Music]
and and i have some also some some
normal pens i like this
[Music]
um and and i have some cute cute
stickers from um from when i left japan
i
i bought some stickers
uh because i thought maybe i'll gift it
to someone but now i ended up you i'm
gonna use it myself look at these cat
stickers
from daiso daiso daiso has really good
100 yen shop and
that's cats and that's that's that's
owls i don't know i like owls
look at them
i want more stickers
[Music]
it's so cute look at those owls
sticker sheets and they're sparkly these
are sparkles so they're more fancy
sparkly and gold they have some you see
that gold
shininess
yeah
so we can also use these um these are
all i found so
and of course i have some brushes so
um
the last time i did something like this
is probably a million years ago
so i don't even really
uh remember any patterns but i mean
there's a lot of patterns on the
internet so
i can have the internet as my cheat
sheet
cheat sheet
a show
uh do you have anything to hold egg my
hands
um
yeah
it's gonna be okay
is their eggs
[Music]
but but at least i can hang them up to
let them dry um but yes i am the egg
holder
i am
the one and only egg holder now let me
get some inspiration here there we go
okay so we can do all kinds of things we
can do stripes we can do hearts we can
do zigzag we can do wavy stuff we can do
dots we can do all kinds of things so so
i want to start with one we're probably
not gonna do all 12 of them maybe five i
don't know five five sounds like a good
number to me
um i'm the keeper of eggs yes
yes behold my eggs i'm not gonna use hot
glue my glue gun is still broken
yeah so okay um um
this angle is like and you really need
to lean in to have you guys see it like
i'm leaning my arms onto the table
um
so that you guys see something see
there's already a hole there perfect
no let's start with a pattern
are you guys is there anyone in the chat
who's also painting eggs alongside me
probably not you should you should be
painting eggs
really draw egg on the egg no no no no
no
i didn't stab the eggs they came like
this
you're painting eggs through you what
does that mean
oh you mean you can't control me you
can't control me chiada is under control
i have myself under control
[Music]
ain't a raccoon dick
no
okay i'm i'm the only one painting
that's okay
but you're going to be watching them
yet
um
what kind of pattern do we want i think
we want let's start with something
simple let's start with a zigzag
so i will first because i don't want to
mess up too much
i will first draw
like the pattern with this
[Music]
erasable pen
you don't even see it i tried my best to
set this up
yeah maybe until here
that should be good
let's see
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah that's better okay
okay professional setup for
these kinds of streams getting better
and better and better
trust me
yeah um
today is officially easter i hope you
guys hear me while i'm like turning away
from the microphone today is officially
easter
but i wanted to do an easter stream do
you guys hear me well
ever since last year
an easter painting stream oh i heard my
raccoon meowing
yes i'm left-handed yes i'm legend
distant kiana
sounds good okay yeah if you guys
remember last year i was like oh we
should have oh [\h__\h]
we should have um
we should have done an easter egg
painting stream why didn't it just
[\h__\h] erase that doesn't work
i should have done an easter egg
painting stream but then it was too late
and so i was like next year we will 100
do it so here i am finally doing it so
proud of me show per hour
okay so we'll repeat
we'll repeat the zigzag
a few times
[Music]
sure we can do this a little bit messier
are you guys seeing what i'm doing oh
yeah i think you are
yeah yeah looks good it looks
good
oh yeah and yesterday
i was with my
my family i was with my sister and my
mom we were visiting my mom
um
so when's my day off
yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah and we i mean
we didn't really celebrate it's like
we're not we don't really celebrate
easter but it was just a reason to to
meet up i guess
and
the first topic
first topic of the day was talking about
my playthrough
of
starship titanic because the whole
family was kind of watching it
and was excited about it it's a bit
blurry yeah probably that's probably
better that way
my mom was like she said she was getting
a little bit frustrated watching because
you know
um that's that's how backstage feel when
you don't do exactly what they want you
to do but i said mom i was trying my
best to cut
it was like the whole freaking family
was backseating me
for better or for worse
but i asked my mom
um
why
did you did you play it like for a
really long time well why did it feel
like you were playing it for a really
long time she said yeah
yeah yeah you can in theory if you know
everything you can finish it and then
two to four hours but
um
uh yeah back then
back then in the good old days
um there was no easy access
to
uh
you know walkthroughs and guides and all
that
meow
meow too you're not allowed in my room
anymore for today no no
um
and and uh yeah yeah yeah so and that
made me think yeah wow
where are you going very cool it has a
life of its own
that made me think holy [\h__\h]
could it be that
back in the day
you know like when when the internet was
not something everyone had yet maybe or
were guides were just not so common yet
maybe games were something more
appreciated like even shorter games were
played for like a really long amount of
time probably you know like this one
game my mom said she was playing it for
months
but those riddles i mean you saw without
a guide without any help if you're
really supposed to solve everything on
your own in a game that that takes two
hours if you know everything can take
you months and months that's why i felt
like it was a much longer game but in
reality it really wasn't
it really isn't like but it can be when
you have no no guides but yeah as i said
i was thinking
probably uh games were more appreciated
back in the day
you got more out of a game because you
would be playing it for much much longer
which is i think pretty cool
so i think
we're gonna i'm gonna draw
look at this messy pattern that's okay
yeah beautiful beautiful
it just flops out
it just flops out of my hands
it's so light it's really damn light
ah
i just realized
it has a hole here
if i had anything thin enough
stick it through
and like hold it like that you know
[Music]
what
could i have
i don't have any chopsticks but even
chopsticks would probably be too thick
uh a toothpick i do have two things
just make sure a raccoon doesn't come by
i'll turn up the camera a chapstick
could be helpful
i'll be rv
[Music]
hello
do
[Music]
oh man
oh man i feel so bad
they were both not but all three of them
were sitting in front of my my room's
door
uh
looking at me
they're just waiting there for the whole
stream
oh i feel so bad and this bunker is just
still super hyper and when i walked out
of my room she zoomed for the room and
ran after me also it's really stinky out
there i think bonkers had a
really mean poop
a really mean poop man
oh
the chapstick is actually too thin
um
so
but i guess it kind of works i'll i'll
still get a little bit
dirty but
see because it's like in theory uh
it it will go through completely but i
have to stop it with my own fingers okay
um also
what's up i got some water
but
and i'll try out the the pens first so
maybe i guess
but they're so tiny i feel like with my
little with a brush i'll be faster
so
[\h__\h] the pens
um what color kfp what color
[Music]
oh yeah no that's an alpaca mug
i love that mug yeah i have it for a
long time
that one and there's a i have a pink
version that's uh orange okay that's a i
have a pink version that's a sheep has a
it's the same mug but it has a sheep
face i think i have that one from west
from daiso too no no i'm not sure it
doesn't stay on the bottom anymore
but i i probably bought it in japan
orange orange and orange and blue
blue dark blue like my colors
orange and orange and green like my hair
maybe the turquoise or something like
that
okay
that means
that means we need this orange
and we need
a turquoise i don't really i don't
really have a turquoise um but i'll go
i'll go with these colors these two
colors are nice
and maybe we'll add like a middle middle
line of white line
uh on top of the zigzag sounds good
sounds good i don't have um
[Music]
you know it would be nice to have a
thingy to
put the colors on
um
how about
we'll put it on here
oh put it on here
let me open this up
[Music]
anything anything works
in my
uh in my until year kiana's actually
here
okay we start we start with some pink
[Music]
a pink that's orange as far as i know
that is orange how much do we need these
tubes are so tiny but i have like almost
every color
i bought like a huge set
hey i love atelier games so i like
calling myself atelier kiara atelier
alchemist
or at the alchemist of kfp
not much of an alchemist
how do you say it in english
okay
let's get started let's get started
[Music]
it makes poopy sounds when i let out the
color
oh my god
okay
okay fully prepared this is this is way
better prepared than the last
art session that we had because the last
art session wasn't supposed to be an art
session it was supposed to be a hot glue
session session all right
i'm sticking in the
egg and now oh there's a cat hair in
there
how lovely
let's get started um
i'll i wish i had thicker
thingies
bigger thicker
i don't have anything
this is so awkward to hold
it's really awkward to hold but whatever
we'll get through it now [\h__\h] it i'm
just gonna hold it like this now
at least for now i need a i need a good
cream
[Music]
for lucky people it will um
dry fast
so yeah um
i i was with my family
we didn't really do much um i arrived
and my mom showed me
an update of her garden and oh my god
she did so much since the last time i
came
and when i say garden it's a huge
a lot
a huge lot that was originally like it
looked like a freaking forest back there
and
ever since she got it she was working on
you know getting rid of the trees and
all the
like there was so much [\h__\h] back there
um that needed to be gotten rid of
like i don't know
trash and
like it was like a ruin back there
ruined in the forest
really messy a lot of work for someone
to do it alone
and mostly my mom was always working
alone on it
uh sometimes she she got help
so
yeah
uh
oh yeah yeah choppy she's actually yeah
she chops the wood and all that
uh
yeah it's a lot of work and she like she
made paths out of out of the all the
wood that she chopped she would make
paths like she would throw it in one of
those things that makes everything small
and she would make paths out of that and
she built like uh like square fields for
planting like planters huge blenders
that are like two
two by two square meters or so maybe
two yeah two square meters maybe uh
maybe three square camera experience i'm
not sure but she made a lot of them and
then she showed me all the veggies and
oh my god she has like pretty much every
[\h__\h] veggie i can imagine
besides potatoes she said potatoes are a
pain in the ass because they
take it foul
really easily
um
and then that
that kind of
um
the other veggies will get foul as well
and so on but she has like she has
zucchinis she has broccoli she has the
white broccoli that i hate
and she has
tomatoes all kinds of tomatoes she has
bell peppers she has chilies she has
salad she has
i don't know
freaking million different things
[Music]
so many things it's incredible i was
saying yo you can like you never need to
go to the supermarket again eventually
no
okay this is difficult because i have no
grip and it keeps on moving no
when i
see
you see i need to get my hands dirty
okay
okay i'm getting my hands dirty i guess
[Music]
okay i can't use this i need to
yeah yeah we're getting our hands dirty
i
i don't mind it's just gloves we can get
new gloves so
yeah and she was very proudly updating
me about her garden
oh yeah also a lot of fruit as well oh
and and pumpkins pumpkins yeah
um and fruits and flowers and
uh yeah she said that once she's done
with that and she's pretty close to
being done i would say then she will
um build
by herself and maybe with the help of my
brother so she'll build a shed for the
chickens yeah
she really needs those chickens
sorry
i need to show you what i'm doing
you're not seeing it
scoozy are you saying it yeah okay
[Music]
yeah she wants chickens
and
later very much later she also wants
some
what are they called goats yeah goats
or like goat milk and goat cheese maybe
yeah maybe she can make cheese
yeah
so she updated me about that and it was
looking it was looking amazing oh and
she updated me about she has a tiny tiny
tiny tiny tiny tiny pond
and recently
a frog started laying its eggs in it and
it looks disgusting by the way it looks
like someone for a wrap in the pond in
green
um it looks disgusting but there were
already
a lot of
tadpoles that were already uh hatched
and swimming around there
yeah yeah yeah so i was looking at the
tadpoles and it reminded me of that
video the korean video that i saw the
other day of of some korean guy raising
some tadpoles it was really cute
and supposedly there is one frog in that
tiny pond but i didn't see the frog
yeah but that's cute
and my my brother and my sister
they gifted my mom you know one of those
um really tacky garden frogs like out of
out of
porcelain
or porcelain or something like that or
or i don't even know what it's made out
of but
yeah they give the terror one of those
in the store
no it's not a stone it was also with
color and all that uh green a green frog
and my mom was like really not um
liking it because she doesn't like tacky
stuff
[Music]
but
yes he was like threatening that you
throw the frog
on the ground and break it into pieces
but then my sister said i will buy a new
one for you if you do that and i do it
again and again and again
your mom doesn't want to be part of
their system
but
yeah
my sister will not give back
she will not stop
yeah
look we already have two layers
going pretty fast and i'm doing it
pretty thinly so it dries pretty fast
it's not a huge mess
it's not so bad
[Music]
is this is a
forever therapeutic actually
no
phoenix egg
yes
and then we ate some with some cake
and
uh
and then we played
a game that my brother is very addicted
to and my bro and my mom always play it
together when my brother is over at my
mom's place
it's
surprisingly
not much of a game
considering how you know
my family likes to play a lot of like
cool games but they they always play
geo guesser
you make the time pass
and
my brother and my mom are like a really
good team
when playing that game at this point
yeah they
my brother really is
so good at it and so into it
takes it really seriously
so they wanted my help
because they said hey you can get help
us get gold
uh in a in a in geo guest or japan
and i was like oh oh okay so i helped
them with a round of japan but i
actually ended up not being much of help
because
well
i mean
i
mean the thing is
that
i don't know if you guys ever played
geocache before but if you
uh it's basically like google maps and
you have to like get set in a random
spot somewhere in the world and you have
to guess where you are um
on the on the world map um but you know
car car plates are censored
so you have to look at the houses and
the vegetation
the plants
and
uh road signs to try to figure out where
you are
so the thing is like anything anything
helpful
to roughly say
where you are is mostly like written on
like big blue uh signs on uh on a
on a what's it called the the autobahn
what's it called again in
english um the big road the highway yeah
highway signs usually it's written on
highway signs in japan highway signs
always have an english writing
underneath
the japanese writings so
they can read it without me in theory oh
what am i using
um but yeah
[Music]
it was it was fun helping them anyway
i'll use a smaller brush because this
one's kind of messy i need better
brushes
i need better brushes oh well
okay
oh yeah it's so stiff
[Music]
it's so stiff
i'll do my best here
yeah that works good can i do you mind
if i look at it closely
i gotta get some
uh clean lines here
so so uh we ended up not getting gold we
got only silver
because like one time we were set um in
like an eye in a tiny tiny tiny island
in
okinawa um
[Music]
and
i think it said
no
yeah i think it said something like
kagushima somewhere and i was like oh
that's kagoshima i don't know where
kagoshima so i told them to you know go
put the marker on kagoshima but but but
then uh
we were so far off because
i didn't know
they had like so many tiny islands so
far away there were also kagoshima
considered kagoshima like really far
away
yeah yeah so i [\h__\h] the whole rating
up with that
um i couldn't help that much and most of
the most of the areas were like in
really remote
areas in japan
that i have i don't really know much
about
and then there's also like the thing
with like so many
names of places in japan are repeated
uh
like
somewhere across the country like for
example there was like i think
uh
a place called hamada or haneda
i was like
i mean that sounds like a place that
japan would have at least 20 tons 20 20
cities that are called that
[Music]
they had high expectations but
i ended up not being very helpful
hello
[Music]
i need to
learn
japanese
geography
to help out more
yeah i'm sorry i couldn't be of much
help but then we tried some other like
categories for example we tried it was a
category um that's uh like you get set
somewhere in the world
randomly but it's always a spot where
there's a cat on the on the picture
so it's like just a random cat either
walking across the street or sitting on
the balcony of a house or your land
landed in the middle of a cat cafe or
something
uh yeah and some some of them you can't
even move when you're some some of the
cat cafe places you can't even leave the
cat cafe so it's really difficult to
find out where you are
um or it's just yeah randomly outside
and then you try to um go from where the
cat is
and find some important signs or
something that tell you where you are
that was cute
i was cute finding where the cats live
cats all over the world
then we also tried a map that was um
famous
famous sites all over the world
and that one was ridiculous because
there was only five sites so in one
round there's five places that you have
to guess and it was the most obvious it
started with the [\h__\h] eiffel tower
who doesn't know where the eiffel tower
is
uh
and then
yeah you know we went for the first
round easily and then we were like let's
do another round this one was too easy
and then we figured out oh [\h__\h] there's
only five places in this category
they were showing us the exact same
places
no i think
maybe it wasn't famous sites maybe it
was fair no it was famous movie spots
famous movie spots and one of them was
in paris and all that
and yeah it was uh it only had five so
that was kind of lame it was
anti-climactic
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
so
[Music]
yeah we played geo guesser for an hour
or so
and then we just had some more
cake and chitchat
and then my mom started cooking the
dinner
which was not particularly easter
related easter themed it was just just a
normal dinner
and then i
already very pretty soonish had to leave
because
the drive home was very very long
yeah
it wasn't much but i think my mom was
uh happy
to have us anyway
and i was so tired that i got
to fall asleep really early
i fell asleep like at half past one
which is really early for me you know me
[Music]
oh cat hairs
yeah yeah yeah half past one i just i
just was like dead tired
[Music]
let gasp
look guys
yeah yeah
[Music]
what else what else
i brought some of the
leftover food home with me so i'm gonna
eat that today and after having a
discussion with my mom about it i
decided i am for real now 100
i'm gonna get an aquarium
i was thinking a little bit about you
know not getting an aquarium but like
trying kind of like a terrarium to get
frogs and all that but but i decided
i'll get an aquarium after all because i
um
have found some help
yeah yeah
aquarium yes yes and and and i'm looking
forward to um showing it off to my
visitors
um
you know there's some
live english girls who want to visit me
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
in the summer time probably
and show them my fancy
aquarium my fish and also it's gonna be
tv for my cats and my raccoon
you're gonna enjoy that it's basically
cat tv
[Music]
i wanted one for a while i thought it
would look really cool in my apartment
um
not that i'm like really extremely
interested in fish
but i just thought it's not only
like an additional pet but it's also a
good way to decorate and fill up my
empty ass apartment
[Music]
they won't jump into the water it's
usually close and they won't even be
able to reach it anyway don't worry
they won't be able to reach it
no no no no
yeah but i was always kind of afraid
because
it seems like a lot of work and it is it
is kind of a lot of work you have to
like switch the water and all that a lot
um
but it's okay i have a plan now
i have a plan so i'm confident
i am motivated
yes
okay i think
i'm done with the green
[Music]
there we go
don't look at it from too close just
look at it from afar and then it looks
okay
i did just a thin layer of green and
orange so now i want to do
a
white
layer
yeah
yes yes yes yes yes
yes
okay
okay and then we're done with the first
egg
i just want to go around the zigzag
because you can still see the line the
the sketchy line
i don't want to fix that
aside yeah
[Music]
have you guys seen my weekly schedule
i put up my weekly schedule
on twitter and on the community board
have you seen it
[Music]
it's looking like an exciting week i was
motivated so i did my schedule earlier
motivated and i also have like
everything already
set in stone
and it's not on the schedule but there
will be this week
the new song
[Music]
yes finally finally it will be on
energy's channel and one week later
we're also doing um the
the gaming collab
[Music]
there we go
yeah spanish as well we're doing a
spanish snack box review uh actually on
tuesday tomorrow is my day off
and on tuesday i'm doing a snack box
review for spain
i'm curious what we're gonna get inside
very curious
and
then we have
very early in the morning for me but it
was my suggestion because you know we're
dealing with free time zones indonesia
ian and
me
so
i said let's do it in the morning time
for me
it's a
it's
yeah
when i was trying to figure out a time
that works for us it was kind of
kind of the only option
yeah
and i did i didn't want the others to
wake up at a weird weird ass time
because it was my idea
i should have thought of that earlier
like that i have like the time zones all
over the globe that was uh i didn't fake
it through early enough
um
[Music]
so we're doing monopoly
will not believe the girls
only because i i never
had a proper collab with ollie before
and recently i've been thinking damn
ollie is actually such a sweetheart so
i should collab with her
[Music]
there's there's just not many
not many people
that
in hollow that so openly are so
supportive and hyped like she's a hype
woman of all the whole life members and
and then she's so sweet like
oh i really want to like appreciate that
and you know for being so supportive of
no matter what like you know
once i once i got verified on on twitter
i gotta did you guys know when you're
verified you get like an extra um
category in your replies
um there's like a notification right and
then there's one for replies only and
then there's one for
um replies and reactions from other
verified people
yeah so that actually makes it easier to
see at least some of the other homo life
members and filtered through not all of
them are verified
so i can't see all of them easily but
only
is uh
oh he's verified
uh so i i often see ollie liking and
retweeting my stuff
yeah
like usually usually in my verified
uh
tab
it's usually
braided only
[Music]
yeah and and seeing that so
so clearly
made me
realize how how supportive both of them
are towards me and that made me really
happy
yeah
i say thank you today that oliver being
so sweet
[Music]
because not everyone does that you know
it's not it's not a given
i need to be more
accurate here i'm so messy
[Music]
cute egg i think this color combination
is really nice it's like kind of very
springish
i think
yeah it's an alpaca mug i collect alpaca
things
deserves loves and good friends thank
you you too
[Music]
oh did you know ollie has a original
song coming out tomorrow
[Music]
it is your first original
he's been
putting out
like really
nice content these days trying her best
working hard
[Music]
let's support her back the way she
supports kfp
[Music]
good for her
i think her is i can imagine her
original song being a really really
really energetic one
because like what else would it be it's
ollie
i think a really energetic song
should be her first original and then
and then um i forgot what uh i forgot
what the genre was called but you know
coronet's new original song that genre
would fit her well she's here only how
did you know i'm talking about you
[Laughter]
how did you know
what did she say i didn't see and i
don't have my hands free right now can't
scroll back up
[Music]
only
you know ever since i got ever since i
got verified i can see so clearly in my
verified tab that you als always are
like
like liking and retweeting my things and
that you're so supportive and it made me
really really happy to see that because
like you know not not everyone does that
it's usually always you and dana who are
in my verified tab
and that made me really happy so so yeah
i'm also looking forward to our collab
and and also looking forward to your um
original song
you're working so hard only and i want
to give some of the support back to you
that you'll give to me
is she dying right now i wonder
she's probably dying the way i know her
is she okay
ah
i
does it say she's hyperventilating
oh my god
oli don't die
don't die
oh no
i killed ollie but she's a zombie
it's okay right
only happy easter you probably don't
celebrate it i don't really sell it
right it either but anyway happy easter
it's already dead
she was born dead
[Music]
ollie if you want to thank me back let
me win in monopoly
just kidding you don't have to
it's okay don't let me don't let me win
i don't i don't it's not like i
desperately need that win or anything
[Music]
yeah
why are we why are these brushes are so
[\h__\h]
the brushes are crap
all right gotta look at it at the end
closely
let me take a good close look at ya
crush her ollie don't
don't motivate her to crush me no no
no no no no
i think if i look at her with like pnp
and i's
she can't do anything against my power
but full true unleashed power
she doesn't want to make her senpai sad
speaking of volley
is it still going on that huge apex
tournament or did it end like i only saw
like a little bit like really just a
tiny bit of it
is it over
[Music]
it ended who won
no idea
ah someone from niji another
[Music]
who is really good at apex
[Laughter]
really
they're all super good at apex though i
suppose
yeah yeah it was not only uh
and i
participated though did you see a
monster example for example was
participating too
and wasn't there was there some
i feel like there was maybe some one
more
one more i don't think a little better
no better sampler was participating
yeah i sure
but uh they had none i think non-whole
life members in their team i don't know
who they were but i didn't really look
at the tournament to be honest i just
looked at
um to as is a
aqua team for like five minutes trying
to understand what's going on
but i never played ibex before so
i really
i really don't know anything about it
[Music]
how many teams was there
you know aqua simple had like 100k
people watching us crazy
[Music]
thing
20 teams
wow
or 20 teams
wow well now that apex tournament arc is
over
what's it gonna be next huh
okay i was focusing on the top line
uh it looks so busy
i don't like these brushes they're very
stiff
very stiff brushes
[Music]
but i guess they do their job
i think this one this one the zigzag
just takes so much time we're gonna do
an easier one next time
we're gonna do
just straight lines
and maybe some
maybe some polka dots
i don't know
[Music]
i messed up the pattern here what the
hell
but the white really covers up the the
mess nicely though
it's still messy but it fixes some parts
okay
i'm done
[Music]
my first
easter egg
yeah
there it goes let me try to
attach these things to it so i can hang
it up
[Music]
tamago
they have different colors these strings
so cute i want the green one
or the white one that's okay whatever i
get and then i need
one of these
[Music]
happy easter to you too
no paint me you're just a white egg
though
there's not much painting to do
let me decorate you so how how how how
this is uh this is like this
i think
i know how to do it
i still no
no wait that's not it
how do you how do you do this
i think it goes through here
[Music]
and then
like this
you see that
my gloves are gonna look like eofy's
clothes after this
and we squeeze those together
[Music]
squeeze it
into
into the egg
[Music]
wait
okay
oh nice
you could also use these as i don't know
fancy fashionable earrings or as a
necklace
or as a christmas tree decoration
lovely
[Music]
nice
eggnog oh no actually
it doesn't really need drying anymore
let me put it into the basket
into the basket you go
oh
it's an egg in the basket isn't that
comfortable
you like that don't you
on the blanket too egg in a blanket
me yes of course i'm gonna use them as
earrings totally
okay
that took us way too much time
let's um
let's make a simple one and let's play
basketball with this egg
[Applause]
it doesn't have the right bounce
oh there you go i'm gonna be more and
more aggressive
fun very fun
uh 10 out of 10 bounciness
okay color ksp i would say blue light
blue
what do you think
light blue
with
with pink light blue with pink dots or
lines or something like that so we're
gonna first
uh paint the whole egg
in glue
there's some orange on my brush
[Music]
and i actually um still have a lot of
you know the other colors so
surprisingly
i don't end up using that much
dip the egg oh that would make it so
easy if i could just dip it
into the blue color
i shall but i can't it's not that easy
[Music]
okay
blue with blue and white clouds oh that
sounds so cute let me do that because i
have a lot of uh white leftover right
now oh that is so cute
yes i want to do that
okay let me start here though let me
just start uh
holding it like this and then painting
one side
thinly a thin coat so it dries fast
huh
yeah yeah that sounds cute right
[Music]
hold the egg gently
oh it's kind of watery [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh dear
oh it's very watery because i washed the
brush
that's okay
uh but that needs some time to
it gives you the watercolor effect
though i like it
[Music]
don't touch
this is really confusing to me you know
as a child uh of course i understood
that
bunnies don't lay eggs but the fact that
uh easter is always like a combination
of eggs
and bunnies
and the easter bunny brings the egg or
hides the egg and all that that whole
thing always like [\h__\h] up my mind you
know what i mean like what why is it a
bunny why is it not a chicken or a bird
or so it's so confusing i think for a
child that's really confusing
right
i would
[Music]
it's just a blue egg not every blue egg
is
[Music]
oh this is so much faster if i don't
have to follow any lines thank you for
the person who gave me this beautiful
idea of doing it with clouds
this will be a speeding
but it will still look fabulous
[Music]
oh i didn't talk about the rest of my
schedule uh i was at uh monopoly and
then we have
wait what was after monopoly
i think it was already uh
a portal was it portal
okay i can't touch it i can't twist it
i touched it i touched it
yeah
i'm playing portal one in preparation
for my collab with cobalt i told her as
well that she might wanna play portal
one before we collab not because portal
2 needs you to play portal 1 but just
because you know
it kind of makes sense so maybe she will
play it too
um
before our collab we are gonna
collab
not immediately after
um
not like on the day of her collab band
being lifted but very soon after
we're gonna do portal 2 as a collab game
yeah yeah
and she she seems very excited about it
[Music]
um i could use the toothpick for once
okay there we go
um i need this to dry a little bit
i'm sticking it
onto my i have a style styrofoam foam
thingy board over there where i'm
putting the eggs and
letting them dry so while we're waiting
for that to dry a little bit we could
you know be actually effective and do
another egg
um this one
i wanted to be pink i have an idea we're
gonna make a pink and then add uh white
uh
dots and whatever
so i'm gonna paint the whole egg
uh pink which will also be fairly fast i
think
smart smart smart
sounds good yeah this one will be baby
pink
in this cute color
[Music]
okay so
it's gonna be kind of watery again
[\h__\h] i only brought one toothpick i'm so
smart
well the bird's eggs oh
you gave me that idea to wait that would
have been cute because i will make five
and we're five i want to make five eggs
[Music]
[\h__\h]
but in theory that does look like it
could be my egg and the blue one could
be reyna's egg
and then this one the pink one could be
lily's egg
so we're still actually we can still
switch it up and say it is exactly what
it's gonna be
okay
okay okay
and what color would silva's egg be
like green green and
yellow
very similar to mine
green and yellow because that's her o.g
outfit
right she has like um kind of almost
neon green
colors
[Music]
ah maybe some red
yeah green yellow or red
we can try to make it work yeah
okay
let me drink some water
i'm like
when i'm like looking over there i'm
like screaming i'm trying to scream to
reach the microphone but it's kind of
not good for my voice
red at the top
okay
the name of the medium oh i'm sorry
myanmar i don't have the title i have it
from audio stock um
yeah there is no title sorry
i got it from audio stock
all right
pink
[Music]
although i have a pink that actually
looks more like her pink
but it's okay
i started using this so
um
let me hold it differently
i'm holding
it like this okay
okay
oh and uh yeah i started um properly
learning hangul korean writing korean
writing system
and
it's a bit tough because my brain
is not helping me much here
it's uh
like it's it's supposedly easy but i
need to repeat it several times to
actually remember it properly
and then then
i i should be able to
have it in my head until the duolingo uh
session because they're doing the late
do a lingo korean
this week
and i want to be able to
not
need to rely on duolingo for korean
writing
learning
this time
so i'm using a different application to
learn it
and
you know it's pretty good
so i'm confident that i can learn it but
[Music]
brain
very slow
my brain very slow
i don't have the brain capacity anymore
that i used to have back in
back in the good old times when i
learned japanese
[Laughter]
yeah you get older and you have a
tougher time learning languages
[Music]
but i will not give up i want to
get to a level where i can have a
normal like everyday conversation just
you know like hello how are you what's
your name where are you from
yes please i want to order this you know
stuff like that that's all i want and i
think i think that's manageable
[Music]
okay it's pretty much done
uh
uh-huh
[Music]
yeah
uh where do i let you let your rest
because i only brought one too like i
think the other one is it
[Music]
don't go anywhere
don't
[Music]
stop stop move
don't worry this is a this is a table
that can be messed up don't worry about
it
[Music]
okay this is maybe not the best
technique to draw an egg
um egg on the run i have a tissue
just stay on here
okay
stop good egg
let me thank you but
okay
okay whatever just i'll leave you like
this is the other one done
it feels them
look at these baby eggs
[Music]
okay it's drying look at my gloves it's
getting i'm looking like an artist i
look like an artist
artistic
[Music]
beautiful
okay
and now we're gonna paint some clouds
i think it's dry it's kind of shiny but
it's dry elsa is very messy don't don't
don't you dare criticize me
i'm trying my best to in a short amount
of time
just celebrating easter on my own
and yeah
i like the watercoloring look let's just
say it has a watercolor look
the sky is um
it looks like that totally
ah this isn't raining right i mean
clouds don't really
[Music]
also really make sense but it's okay
it's gonna be her egg okay
maybe i should gift it to her when when
i see her in the maldives i'll be like
here there we go
actually don't tell elena don't tell
dana um
i was shopping the other day
and
i
i was going all out i was like and when
i was in such a shopping mood i was in a
little shopping spree
and then i saw
i saw some necklaces
and they had letters starting letters
capital letters
and i wanted to buy one for me and one
for aina
you know like a club
and i asked i asked the store lady
if she has um an r
and she looked through his stock
and she said nah she has no r but the
whole time she was looking for like she
had it was like two three minutes or so
when she was looking for all the
necklaces one by one and what what
letter it is um
and and the whole time i was like yeah
baby is this this is a weird present
maybe ah
it's probably weird right maybe i
shouldn't i don't know what to do
and then the moment she told me there is
no r i was weirdly relieved but i do
want to get something for her
yeah
i'll think about it
[Music]
yeah i mean the whole vacation is
already like a couple's vacation
because like people go to the maldives
for
um for fruit for like usually for
honeymoon
no it's gonna be very romantic oh i can
imagine imagine we walk into a room and
i know these hotels like to do this a
lot and then on the bed there's like
something shaped in the shape of a heart
like either rose petals or you know
towels shaped like a heart i can totally
see that
[Music]
present
we might even do streams during the
vacation
i'm so excited oh my god it's gonna be
next month oh [\h__\h]
oh i can't wait for the sunshine and the
beautiful clear water oh my
clear water and the fishes and our
amazing room that we booked
[Music]
it's gonna be a dream come true
clouds are pretty easy to draw
thank god
[Music]
here we go i think i'm done
look
[Music]
i mean it's not that cute though what
else can i add that's like that like
every baby can't talk anymore maybe like
some some dark blue feathers
maybe some dark blue feathers yeah i
think that could be good
um
stop rolling
i think this this color
like this
darker blue
people patterns is like a little bit too
intricate right now
okay it's just a tiny bit these acrylic
colors really
um are
very
giving
[Music]
okay do our hair sitting on the clouds
oh that would be so cute but these
brushes are so [\h__\h]
they're like
wide brushes
i don't think i can do that properly
um
sorry
i can put some of the cat stickers on
the egg doll
and maybe maybe some heart stickers and
some music stickers there's some music
stickers there
[Music]
now i'm going all out
i'm going all out now
i'll get better
god dammit i got so much color
[Music]
oh dear
oh does that even look like a feather
[Music]
maybe from a distance
no it's kind of messed up
what's happening
what's
happening
it's kind of it's kind of messed up on
you
[Music]
let's try another one
ah this looks okay
[Music]
that looks like a feather
that actually looks like a feather
[Music]
okay
uh here
[Music]
ah
one more one more one more one more
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] brush man
so useless this brush
[Music]
it's so
um
[Music]
oh what the [\h__\h] is this
ah
i'm having a crisis right now
let me wash it maybe
maybe it will um get a better shape then
that looks like a
looks better that looks better
[Music]
okay i think i might might have saved it
one more feather somewhere maybe oh no
it's actually pretty balanced now okay
look at this egg
everybody look at the lady egg
don't look too close to here
hi
hi hi hi hi hi
[Music]
yes
it's done but let me fix the top a
little bit
i don't think
she would um
even if she would if i would give it to
her she would probably just like fake
her happiness it's
probably not something i
should give to her it's not very
impressive
but she'll get a picture of it that's
for sure
but now it's so [\h__\h] up i don't want
to give it to her i want to give her a
high quality gift
but not this
i fixed the top though now let me um put
this on one of these hangers
[Music]
this came with some really nice
accessories so i'm very glad that i got
this
set
didn't test out the
pens though
so
we're gonna
close
this
thing on this thingy
[Music]
yeah
wonderful
i'm
[Music]
another one for the basketball
yes beautiful spot okay
[Music]
okay
and figure out what we could add to the
oh maybe uh some black
stripes
black
[Music]
black black stripes
black and maybe a dark purple
in some way
okay
ah both
or hearts you know i kind of wanted
sunglasses
oh like as a pattern
that would be
orange though
let me
[Music]
i guess we can do a pattern
of
the orange glasses and maybe
red uh black
stripes ah i have an idea i have an idea
i have an idea i have an idea i have an
idea how i'm gonna do it
a black
and a flashy we already have some orange
let me reuse the orange i have a
different orange too but
yeah let's use this one and the black
[Music]
not too much
alright now here we have our perfectly
dried pink egg
now
we start with the black lines
i think i wanted to go like um
diogonelli across
the egg
but kind of straight
hmm
let me dry the the brush
there we go okay
let's hope this goes well
let's hope that because the black is a
strong contrast so if i if it looks
messy it will stand out a lot
[Music]
okay let's see what we can
do [\h__\h]
look at this brush look what this brush
does this is what i'm dealing with
[Music]
okay
okay that's that is bold
oh that is very bold
[Music]
um
i reached
the bottom
okay so kind of like this i want to
continue making some stripes
it's some strong color it's okay it's
okay
by the way
i
did it
i did it the other day
my
super
new fancy
airfryer arrived
yes
yes i did it
i got myself an air fryer
oh my god
[Music]
yeah um i am convinced i have been
convinced by videos and by reina of
course
[Music]
the brush is so [\h__\h]
i'll even use an editing pen
and i want to use it uh for some cooking
streams too
yeah i was thinking it would be kind of
fun to have a stream where um
like an off collab
where we just throw all kinds of things
into the airfryer and then we taste test
it
and we say if it worked well and maybe
maybe with a camera of course
what the [\h__\h] this brush
what you see is it's like all over the
place it makes no straight lines uh
relate air fryer
experimentation
cooking stream
of an air fryer because we can also do
that from the office
don't need to
uh
[Music]
don't need to go into the kitchen for
that and i think that will be a little
bit more safe
congratulations on your effort thank you
i saw this video
of someone making these really fluffy
amazing
sugar glazed donuts in an air fryer like
okay the sugar glazing comes afterwards
the airfryer doesn't do that but you can
make some really nice fluffy donuts in
there oh my god
and that's just one of the million
things you can make and that's so basic
even
i think that line is okay this looks
very bold oh dear
[Music]
i mean that's no
i wouldn't have done an egg like this
if it wasn't for you know trying to do
something horritory themed
but okay
we're we're too deep in it now we cannot
escape
[Music]
donuts man
you guys can of course send me
suggestions
of what you want me to make in an air
fryer
[Music]
i didn't unpack it yet by the way and i
didn't test it out yet
[Music]
but once i do
i will let you guys know
i will maybe i'll test it out this week
oh my god
this line is messy
[Music]
i don't even know if i can make that
shape properly the shape of the glasses
with this [\h__\h] brush this is the
smallest brush i have
it's so crappy
[Music]
look at that
okay this is the last line
last black one
[Music]
maybe just
maybe i should just
do
[Music]
orange dots or so
i don't know
[Music]
her thingy kind of looks a little bit
like
an owl doesn't it like because it's so
thick i could use one of my owl stickers
maybe
now i don't want to try i don't want to
try those glasses
[Music]
i have a bad feeling about maybe just
one
per per stripe
or pink area
[Music]
okay it's messy but who cares
okay
[Music]
yeah it looks like this now
it doesn't look like a [\h__\h] easter
egg the colors are so not easter anymore
it's simple
what is this why is there black on an
easter egg it makes no sense
okay
[Music]
a kinky pink egg
it's not kinky
it's gonna look good with the rest lined
up i don't know about that but let's
hope for the best
i
like my cup thank you
[Music]
okay
dry my brush
my unbehaved bad bad brush away
maybe i wonder if these work because
there's a laser orange one maybe these
work on top of the color that i already
painted because i would have more
control over this one i think
right they look like where where is it
here
like this
[Music]
let me try
yes they work
um
they're kind of see-through
but actually that's good because her
glasses are kind of see-through too
right like transparent
orange but transparent
[Music]
you want to see it looks it looks um
actually it has like a good effect
like okay the shape is not perfect but
see
it's it uh layers on top of the pink
pretty well
okay so we're gonna do that all across
the egg
like us
[Music]
tamago is there
well by the way today after this stream
we have a members only stream as well
which i didn't set up yet but
i will do it after this one is over
[Music]
i messed this one up
whatever
only happy accidents there are no
mistakes only happy accidents right
yes yes yes
yeah we are going to play
a new memories only game that i got
permission for
finally something new because we really
have only so
such such a little choice of members
only games that we can choose from
and i was like looking for members only
games particularly
and found one that i thought would be
nice to play together i mean it's not a
game we can play together but you can
watch me play it okay
while we chit chat
[Music]
yes yes
very relaxing game
uh what was it called
uh
poundscaper or something like that
[Music]
yeah okay
oh you know what all the owls we can put
on the moon egg
yes yes yes we'll make a brown egg and
just put a [\h__\h] ton of owl stickers on
it and then we call it the day
oh no what do i do i want them to be
connected so starting out i started out
i started out here
and i went and connected them
but then here
see there's a big height difference it
won't connect anymore it's so high and
here's so low
i'm so stupid
[Music]
yeah i'll just kind of tilt the glasses
gotta do what you gotta do to make it
work
[Music]
there we go
very connected with a [\h__\h] eggman this
looks like crap
[Music]
looks much much cooler
much more badass
you know what you you'll get a special
pink
thingy
actually i don't even need them i'm not
hanging them anywhere to dry so whatever
i guess i don't need them there you go
let's put you let's put you here
okay that looks
weird that design is weird
i don't know what i was thinking
much i need some water i'm drying
i'm i'm i'm drying
i'm drying
i'll be
just sand
sooner or later
dusty
floating
but my cats still need me so i need to
supply
[Music]
bondage egg
no one just because of the black stripes
come on
i don't want to turn into sand no no can
i eat the other the other um surprise
egg
let's take a little break to eat the
other surprise egg and then we'll make
two more eggs we'll make a sweater egg
and a chihuahua egg and okay well
mermaid egg
let me eat surprise egg oh yeah that's
so hot
holy [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
are you saying i guess
i have a godiva bunny oh maybe you sit
in the back i also have a lint
bunny
yeah lint bunnies are very popular gifts
for
uh easter
open up
kfp
give me your chocolate
[Music]
oh yeah
oh that's a good stuff
[Music]
milka bunny did you know makeup bunnies
are recycled into
into christmas
chocolate figures
the ones that don't get sold
[Music]
yeah yeah
you didn't
i mean i'm sure there's some fresh ones
but
they keep on recycling the ones that
aren't sold apparently
ah unknown shocking
[Music]
they don't taste old so just eat it
so good
i'm almost done i ate half of it
hmm
[Music]
um
okay
i'm putting my gloves back on
want to see what's inside
[Music]
is that a smurf is that a smurf
it's a smooth
[Music]
what is that location
i can't open it
[Music]
there's like some some location thingies
and oh my god let me put what's her name
smurfina or something like that can i
even show this
i dropped her legs
smurfina smurfette
smurfina would have been better what the
hell
[Music]
nothing fits man
this should fit
it's not oh i think it worked okay this
is just a quick one
i won't show it longer than this oh oh
are those bags
shopping bags
yeah
huh
[Music]
just shocking
oh this is also like you can apparently
also use that in that kind of phone game
there's a oh there's a kinder
kinder application kidney.com app
hashtag not sponsored
but apparently there's a phone app
and then you can like read a qr code
this is like real life gotcha you have
to buy the gacha things in real life in
order to get to use them in the game
what
yes she has like these shopping bags
that you're supposed to attach to her
it's
weird
i can't they won't fit in her hand i
don't know what i'm doing wrong okay but
whatever she's cute she's cute but she
will probably land in the trash
afterwards
at least i got to eat one of my favorite
chocolates again for the first time in a
long long long time
you may not characterize
maybe i should melt her in the airfryer
so that was like a good idea
okay get those cat hairs where where
would i always come from
get those cat hairs so i can make
another egg
[Music]
okay we're gonna do the lumi egg i think
cause that one's so i think easier
next egg clap clap next egg
club club club club
are you guys ready for the mummy egg
it could we could make it really cursed
but no i'm going to make a cute
moment
or so everything's shaking
brown brown brown brown brown
is this brown okay
i think it's okay
there's so much left over colors though
like so many color blobs i just
put on too much thinking i will use it
but i'm not using it all right i'm not
gonna use so much of the brown
clean the brush clean the brush
[Music]
yeah make it curse i don't know i want
to put those i want to put those um
uh stickers that i showed you in the
beginning onto it because i have i
literally have owl stickers
would be such a waste to not use them
don't you think
why is it that the pink doesn't come off
but okay maybe the brown is gonna
overpower it
[Music]
hopefully
let's go brown egg
oh
is that luma's brown it looks very
yellow
look at more coats maybe
[Music]
that's good you turned yourself over
that's actually pretty helpful
i dropped the ink
you gotta be careful
oh can you turn yourself again
[Music]
i gotta continue kiwi with meme
we played kiwi the other day on her
channel
but we didn't get really far
i somehow thought that
we could finish the whole game in one
stream and i might
we could if we wanted to
but it was actually
[Music]
using quite a lot of brain power
and no need to force
uh
us to do a six hour stream right to
finish it even for six hours we probably
wouldn't have finished it because it
took us it took us two hours for
one season and there's four seasons
right
i'm gonna let it dry and prepare
prepare the other egg
[Music]
the other egg the last egg will be
the sobato eggs i'm gonna try to put
some more effort into this one
um so the colors are going to be
a bright green a bright orange
now let me put look up a picture of
subaru
[Music]
yeah yeah some
some red um
actually not yellow and not orange no no
we don't need orange
we just need a bright
green
some blue light blue
and
some white
and some
[Music]
i mean it's like something in between
red and orange
the stripes of the the edges of her
shirts and that's more
i think it's more on the red side
[Music]
well i can mix the rest of my orange
because i don't need it anymore anyway
okay i'm gonna make this egg look like
super you watch it learn you watch and
learn maybe i should make some outlines
so i want to
we're gonna make
we're gonna make stripes
just like the t-shirt
and then on the top of the egg we're
going to have uh
something that maybe
will resemble
a
hat perhaps i'll try
okay so
ah
yeah we'll do straps like this
[Music]
okay straps like this
on the top
we'll have
a round
[Music]
and maybe
maybe one side
[Music]
and have like the
the front part of the cap
see what i'm doing here
[Music]
i deserve a picture maybe from her 3d or
something
because like i i see that the bottom of
her cap is blue but what is the top of
her cap does someone know
[Music]
[\h__\h]
i
wonder i mean we don't
isn't it red it's
there's some red on it but it's it's not
only red so it doesn't necessarily
guarantee that everything is red
now i'm looking on google for references
but
uh although i mean we can't 100
recreate it so maybe it's not so
important maybe we'll just have um
we'll have
until the middle the cap will be red and
then
the cap will be white
and then this part i'll just i'll just
make it blue because you know we need
some more blue elements
and then the straps will be
uh light green white light green white
so i don't have to even paint
part of the
egg
and then
[Music]
then i'm gonna cover the stripes
with
some
orange red color okay
sounds like a plan
sounds like a freaking plan let's do
this
i got
[Music]
i'll use a big brush
and it actually can be a little bit wet
because i want to thin out the color the
green color that i have
[Music]
i will start
here
it looks
uh it should be a little bit more
yellowish but it's okay
okay
[Music]
oh yeah that's good
the watercolor effect
the watery effect makes it
more bright
[Music]
okay
one side done is actually pretty fast
who would have known if you if you draw
a sketch on the egg beforehand
you will know what you're doing and then
it will look better at the end
that'll work cleanly with outlines
sorry you're probably not seeing most of
the work i'm doing
[Music]
i keep on forgetting that you guys don't
see it
this is good this is very very good
[Music]
okay green scraps are done
only three green stripes thankfully i
don't have to uh make the white stripes
white because they're already white
um now
i'm gonna do the the red part i'm gonna
mix some red
into my orange blob that i already have
from before
okay
i'm mixing colors
so creative wow
should i use the big one
i'm gonna use the big one but i want
this one to be dry
this has to be properly dry
this one's hat is red
and white at the top
oh okay even on the extended part but i
think i'm gonna make it blue anyway
i think i'm gonna make it blue because
you know the i want that blue color
to show up somewhere
but thank you for looking it up
that drink looks delicious
do you want to drink it afterwards after
i'm done
you probably shouldn't but i don't
really i don't really recommend it uh
right mixing the orange with the red
[Music]
yeah it gives me a good in between color
like a like a blood orange color oh
black orange is also one of the things
that my mom is um planting by the way
blood orange so cool
i told my mom that um once she has her
first harvest i want
a good part of that
uh
harvest especially the fruits harvest
[Music]
[\h__\h] i said i was gonna do it in blue
but i ended up making it orange okay
whatever i guess no balloons
[Music]
i guess no blue it is
i dropped my egg
it's okay it's all good egg is safe
[Music]
okay no problem no problem no problem no
problem
it just and
what's what's that saying
[Music]
just and i don't know
advance maybe
[Music]
overcome
adapt
adjust overcome maybe
[Music]
i'm looking at the chat in a moment
there we go
adapt improvise improvise adapt overcome
that's what i'm doing
now you can see the pen kind of shine
through the the sketch that i did on the
egg
oh wow
[Music]
look
the same color
i wanted to
fill the stripes
the lines in between oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
um
it looks like milk tea almost at this
point
almost looks like milk tea
now let me try to show you guys what i'm
doing
[Music]
ah the brush is shaped again
wonderful
thanks for nothing
could have actually gone with one of the
pens for this one
oh well
[Music]
oh wow that's okay
i don't know what to do with the bottom
though right down the bottom is empty
maybe it's just a blue
blob
i guess
[Music]
because we didn't use the color blue yet
in the whole thing duck feet
ah that would be cute
[Music]
we need that blue color somewhere and
duck feet would be like a yellow
[Music]
although a line around the head should
also be um blue
[Music]
all right
are you seeing what i'm doing yeah okay
what else oh
what else happened because i want to
tell you
nothing really besides the airfryer and
me going to see my mom
know what else happened
[Music]
oh my mom also
um gave me i guess she was reminded
because of that stream where
that i did with mumi where i told her
that i once
was uh riding on um
on a
what was that bird called again
strauss uh
what is that tall bird called again
champions
it just looks like this because of the
gloves
ostrich yeah yeah ostrich i was riding
on an ostrich let me lean back a little
bit
and uh yeah my mom suddenly
on discord sent me a picture
of you know
child kiara
riding on an ostrich
she was like
she immediately had it
and sent it to me on discord
so
uh that was during the stream and i
think
it uh made her look for the other photos
of my childhood so um when i arrived at
her place she
showed them to me some of them i've seen
before some of them i actually haven't
yeah so we were looking at some pictures
of our childhood me and my brother and
my sister
and my mom told me to take them home the
ones where i was on
but some of them
some of them are really
painful to look at because
like most of them were photos that my
mom took um but there were some school
photos
you know school portraits that you have
to take
and
oh i always look so
bad in those
and i gave them to my mom to like
never never show them to me again i
wanted her to exile
the photos
the portraits oh
there's like
there's like a couple of the ones of the
face before i cut myself bangs
you know with like a huge forehand
that are so embarrassing to look at and
then there's there was one
where i was like already like you know
teenager
and
had my bangs and i looked i started to
look like an edgy emo wannabe emo kid
because of the
because of the bangs
they are really long and really thick
and um
yeah
that photo was okay because then when my
forehead was covered up
but all the old school photos from
before
oh no but it did make me remember some
kids that i
you know that i went to school with and
like how
which which ones i liked which ones i
didn't like and all that
yeah
very
nostalgic doesn't go past the eyebrows
oh hell yeah they do i mean they even do
now but you can see my eyebrows through
them
so i guess they're not that thick
anymore
you guys have a look at your
pictures from like
your time as a child
baby pictures i got some baby pictures
too
and
i really barely have any color left one
of the pictures
uh that i saw from my brother
was
him as a child lying on the ground with
with our um one of you know the very
first cats that i previously mentioned
that small cat that died as a kitten
it was on his back and i was like oh
i
i never saw a picture from him before
and that was the first time
and since you know i had the cat that i
saw him again and
it made me feel so no
i don't know
emotional happy
it was not really a clear picture i just
saw like the back side of the cat
like it was clinging on to my brother
when he was on the ground
but you could see that
kitten fluffiness
the fur was so like a kitten fluffy fur
you know what i mean
could tell like how the texture was
through the picture
[Music]
yeah
all right this is what it's looking like
there's some
some smudge there
by accident probably when the egg rolled
over
unfortunate
[Music]
i've never seen easter egg what
maybe you guys over there don't really
have that tradition huh
that's okay
all right we'll add that blue blob and
the blue line on the side of the cap and
then i gotta say
it looks
perfectly like a subaru egg
actually that must be my
my best egg that i've done today that
i've created today
and i've
popped out of my
hands
all right some blue here
just a circle
[Music]
just a
circle that's all i want here
[Music]
wonderful
wonderful okay okay so we have this
circle there
we gotta outline the cap
and then we got it
[Music]
yeah okay okay
it's about an egg very cute yes i could
sell this
i could sell this for a thousand bucks
try to hatch your own survivor
yeah
okay all the super new egg is done
oh i think
maybe let me try to fix the
let me try to put some white color over
the smudge that i got maybe i can fix it
i don't want this egg to be dirty
somebody will say so
super duper is actually pretty stacil
i don't want her to be dirty
i want to do her justice so
let's try to cover it up
oh yeah that works
[Music]
okay you can't see anymore you can't
notice
i want to give it eyes i almost want to
give it eyes and hair and everything now
ah
i want to give the cap
an outline
um in the middle
[Music]
what a gorgeous egg
i wanna do
[Music]
slightly
yeah okay that's fine you see what i did
there
okay
mr butter is finished
look at this perfect egg
[Music]
now we only have one more egg left
to do which is moment and we have the
base for it there you go brown egg
and i want to use the stickers
see my owl stickers that i showed before
i can put some cute owls on it
yes
[Music]
yeah
and before this will be the cutest egg
out of all of them because i didn't mess
it up with my messy lines but i just put
some cute stickers on it
cheat stickers
but they're so cute and i finally get a
use for them
ah
aren't they lovely
can you go to daiso and buy me some of
my cute stickers i don't really have a
use for them but
paint some berries oh that's a good idea
i'll do that i have some
the red is kind of messed up now but
okay i'll get some new colors um
i don't know which one to put on it
[Music]
i don't know which one to go for
all these are so adorable i'll call this
one
[Music]
and the purple one
oh they're so cute
[Music]
oh there's a there's an owl with a hat
and one with a ribbon on top of its edge
[Music]
this one
oh cute i'm so happy using these owls
let's oh that one looks funny
i'm feeling very girly right now
and one more one more
a small one
i have an extra small please
oh my gosh
oh this one is
small okay
okay okay so we have some some owl
stickers
okay it actually looks kind of scuffed
no it's okay it's okay it's gonna be
okay i uh oh wait i can use mine my red
pen for the berries
[Music]
all right
let's see if that
covers nicely oh yeah that works
[Music]
minecraft style berries i'm probably
gonna draw them like cherries
i will add like a
[Music]
brown
uh
uh what do you call it the top
the the part that you the part that you
rip off
[Music]
you know what i saw today on on social
media randomly because of an
advertisement
i saw there's a louis vuitton
um
[Music]
game that's you know kind of like a
platforming game there's a louis vuitton
platforming game and i'm like what are
you doing making a game what the [\h__\h]
it actually looks pretty cute
but i wouldn't i wouldn't play it on
stream i was just saying it's freaking
weird look at that louis vuitton game
yeah
it doesn't even fit their style like
it's so cute like
like
cutesy style
i think it's a free game maybe
i was really surprised to see that
[Music]
maybe
maybe there's gamer is
working for the company
yeah hell yeah
wasn't there final fantasy there was
wasn't there final fantasy louis vuitton
collab yeah maybe they really
have gamers in their team
[Music]
yeah i remember that
that was really cool though because they
didn't they dress up the final fantasy
14 characters in louis vuitton clubs
like
didn't didn't they do that yeah like no
yeah lightning
modeled for louis vuitton and looked
[\h__\h] hot in it
what a great model
man
yeah i remember that
wasn't she carrying some bags or
something from louis vuitton
yeah yeah
yeah you know what i'm just going to use
the putty here because it depends on the
the brushes are just going to mess up
everything so
this is more accurate
i know it's green is fine
green
look perfect
[Music]
nice
all right there we go
that's actually pretty cute with the
cherries in between
i don't know
but
i'm real embarrassed about the base of
this because the color makes the
streakiness really stand out
but actually
actually we're finished oh my god
i did
five eggs
wait let me let me put them nicely
together
and maybe some that i didn't make to
make it look
nice although the one from me
it doesn't quite i want it to look more
like me let me add some dark blue we're
not done we're not done i take it back
[Music]
let me add some dark blue
make it look a little bit monkey like
chihuahua
either
dots or
outlines
oh
[Music]
hmm
okay this is what i'm doing
[Music]
i'm going to try to be fast but with the
pin it's much easier thank god i have a
dark blue pen
[Music]
wait a minute
shut the wait a minute
and then all we gotta do is hide it in
some garden and have you guys find it
oh speaking of gardens and you i was i
was thinking looking at my mom's
garden and her telling me all the things
she still has to do i was thinking oh
man i wish i could just
tell you guys where she lives have you
all come over or at least 10 people that
would already be like such a huge help
to her 10 of you strong people
helping her to um you know rip out the
weeds and all that because there's like
still so much to do there
help her with some of the gardening
the groundwork
yeah it's really exhausting
i wish i could just send you guys over
to her
wouldn't that be
lovely wouldn't that be great
but no of course that's not possible
i know i know you guys would volunteer
to do that that's
that's the thing
but i don't
don't want you guys to see
you
know you could if you go there you might
accidentally find some
pictures of my childhood and then you'll
see and you see how embarrassing i look
like
no that's not really the problem you
know it's impossible
oh yeah
so when i was about to buy an air fryer
i was so um
motivated and like
i was like yes air fryers are great so
i was thinking about getting my mom one
right i told you guys
so
i told my mom mom you think do you think
an airfryer would be helpful for you
and
i told her that you basically have to
use no oil only just like one one little
spritzer
[Music]
and uh
so i was like that sounds like you're
agreeing
you know that that you want one so i put
it into my into my basket
uh
in my amazon basket and i i literally
order it and i show my mom the
screenshot and she's like
[Music]
what are you doing
you should buy one for yourself but not
for me i don't i don't really need one
that badly
like or or like yeah i don't know she
wasn't
[Music]
so i cancelled the airfryer
i just got an airfryer for myself she
said she said uh
i need a coffee machine more than an air
fryer so i was like okay okay okay i
don't really know much about coffee
machines what what coffee machine do you
need what's a good one then she was like
nah never mind i just i'll just deal
with my
with my old coffee machine
mom
tells me things that she needs but then
she doesn't accept it
[Music]
mommy
but i really i literally don't know [\h__\h]
about coffee machines because i don't
drink coffee
[Music]
okay look at this does it look more like
me
doesn't look more like me now with the
blue lines um
not necessarily
i think the green should have really
been more turquoise but when we were
making this egg we were not really
trying to make it look like me
but okay it's gonna look more detailed
and that's that's okay
i'm not showing you what i'm doing guys
because i'm trying to get a better grip
of the egg i'm sorry
but this way i could also work faster
[Music]
was there anything else i wanted to talk
about is there anything i'm forgetting
that you guys know i should be talking
about
oh my mom and my sister
um
[Music]
why did this come up did my mom bring
this up i'm not sure
they
um
[Music]
my mom was kind of curious so we were
talking about some whole life members
like we were talking about super my mom
my mom is really um
um convinced that subato is a great
person i was like yeah yeah she's so
sweet and i love her she's so energetic
she's a great collab partner and then
somehow we came to the um
to the topic of that
of that mama looney
my mom saw it and then my sister got
curious and she was like what are you
talking about i want to see it
so i showed her
and my sister was digging it but my mom
was kind of like
[Music]
isn't just a little bit too much and i
said no mom this is good this is good
this is this is by far not too much you
don't know you don't know what is too
much there's
there is you know um this is this is
great i like this this is aesthetic ah
yeah i said aesthetically pleasing
and my mom and my sister was laughing
about it
then my sister was digging through
don't tell us tomorrow she's going to
get a heart attack if martin when he
hears this
she's going to be so embarrassed but um
[Music]
my sister was looking for
mama luna's art
um
yeah
i was in a car ride
what did bro tony say bro
bro my brother was busy driving
the car that we were sitting in
so he didn't have time to look at it but
i saw my sister sending the artwork to
my brother on whatsapp
[Music]
so that he could look at it later or
something
what the hell
[Music]
i mean
i mean i personally am all for you know
spreading
that beautiful art that mama looney does
[Music]
but okay there we go i did all the lines
that looks actually much cleaner now
[Music]
there we go
okay cozy
now we're gonna add some some other
things
this is gonna be my easter basket
[Music]
oh lovely
nice and comfy
there we go
oh that is just
perfect i'm gonna leave that okay there
we go
my easter basket
ah
my easter basket is finished
[Music]
left side we have the dewy egg
a pink a light pink egg with a strong
contrast
er with the black lines but we keep her
her dorky personality by adding some
flashy orange glasses that she likes to
use
on the top right we have the moomay egg
also known as the moomeg
it is a simple brown egg but also girly
because of the flashy cute sparkly
owl stickers
um
and giving it more personality by adding
the
berries that she likes so very much
indeed
on the um bottom right we have the
uh the dreamy dreamy elena egg you may
not see it very well but it is a
combination of feathers because she
makes me go to heaven
no clowns because she makes me go to
heaven and the dark blue
uh feathers that she has
very harmonizing egg
it is very soft and beautiful indeed now
on the left side we have the takanashi
kiyara egg
originally it wasn't supposed to be a
takanasi cadet but it ended up being a
takanashikirak because every everything
that chia touches becomes chiada as we
all know
and it is oh [\h__\h] i missed the line
i just realized i just saw this one
we want it to be perfect after all
because kiara is also perfect
there we go
did you guys notice that
way too distracted by all the beautiful
eggs
we have a kiana egg with the
orange green colors of her hair as well
as the white lines in between to
um
you know give it a nice say so touch
that she also always embodies with her
beautiful say so close
and um to finish it off and give it a
sharp look some sharp edges we have the
dark blue lines
um on the
outer lines indeed
and in the middle we have none other but
the subaru egg which i must say came out
beautifully accurate
even with a perfect
hat
on top of the egg as you can see here
that is 100 subaru
so in character the lines if you look at
it i think you will easily notice a
resemblance with her fashionable sporty
t-shirt and at the bottom we have a blue
blob because
why not as a nice color finisher to add
a little bit more life to it and these
are the world famous horotoni eggs
coming soon to your museums and art
galleries make sure to look at them
they're not for sale they're just to
look at and be amazed by
and with that i wish you happy easter
happy easter everybody
yeah
that was that was a cute usual cute
thing to do i think something oh wait
suddenly the sound is so weird in my
headphones oh my god what's happening
i think it's because i rolled onto my
uh onto my cable with my chair
holy [\h__\h] do i sound different to you i
sound different to myself but that's
probably just
just because of some
uh
weird connection thing going on holy
[\h__\h] that's crazy
i can be that loud in my ears
but only if i roll onto the table that's
crazy
oh
[Music]
oh my god i'm so dehydrated now let me
take off my gloves
all right
[Music]
i made some
cute eggs and i
was creative
for once
it feels nice to you know let out some
creativity out
let out some creativity let out let out
some creativity on stream
show my creative side although it's
really just messy
yeah i'm really just doing well doing
everything so messy oh my god my
headphones are like
dying
there you go okay now it's all good
push up
i shout that was fun thank you
fish tank reflections and why
did you mean the aquarium that i'm gonna
get like later than i talked about
but why would that be online
why would that be on my stream
i mean it wasn't
it was a topic when i talked about it
with my family that i could if i ever
need to you know
go
to idle meeting time i could switch to a
different camera that shows my aquarium
but that sounds very complicated to set
up
although i could just use a record
pre-recorded video but that's also not
fun
i mean it's an idea but not really
necessary
yes painting on the surface that's round
and
oval
yeah thank you for pointing that out
that is actually kind of difficult
and um
[Music]
maybe if i
maybe if i had something that you know
like a stick that actually fit perfectly
in that little hole
uh then i would have
had more control over how the egg moves
without touching it all the time
that would have been nice but i only had
things that were too thick or too thin
what happened to broncos and broncos is
in the usual room
oh but i can open the door again now
she probably won't come now but
yeah now now she's probably not
interested anymore now that the camera
is off
[Music]
do
okay
[Music]
they are
they were chilling outside
my room and uh actually sleeping
yeah they're calm again
but now the camera is off so wait just
one moment i'm moving my camera around
more into the middle
uh uh uh uh oh i'm moving so much
there we go
now it's in the middle of my screen
again camera mode okay
kitties no raccoon raccoon being bad
um
no i mean you know i think
i think the stream is going to be fine
i mean what would if i would not be fine
i just have a raccoon there's no problem
there
um
i mean raising a raccoon is quite
difficult but
because there's such
[\h__\h]
i might just leave it like that
i mean at this point what does it matter
[Music]
oh yeah for people who don't know at the
very beginning of the stream a raccoon
jumped into in front of the camera
um and it was um a secret that i didn't
want to let out yet that i had a raccoon
i wanted to keep it a surprise until
later you know
just keep keep some content for later
surprise i want to announce i have a
raccoon now it's my third pet
[Music]
it's all good i know i'm not harsh on
myself don't worry about it
it's surprising that it took so long for
my raccoon to come out in the first
place
it's actually quite impressive
[Music]
yeah
my raccoon is
although my raccoon is usually actually
um
like when it comes to strangers or not
even strangers even friends coming to my
place
uh my raccoon my bonkers gets very shy
and runs away and hides in the bedroom
um
you know
so but i guess there was only a camera
and the and bungas didn't see it as a
didn't see it as a person but little did
bonkers know there were 5 000 people
watching
if bonkers would have known that she
would have never come in front of the
camera yeah bonkers already has fan out
on twitter
of course bonkers has fan art on twitter
bonkers is famous now
oh i saw some other cute art now too
oh
wait where's the bunker's art where is
the bonkers art
[Music]
that's not bonkers that's cristina
montanita
[Music]
ah now i see something
yes
um
this is
this is what happened
[Laughter]
thank you choco cookie
congratulations bonkers on your debut
[Music]
i must i cannot emphasize enough uh
chunkers and smoovie
are different animals
they are not the same
living being
uh bonkers is someone else
[Laughter]
just so you know but yet in the speech
she was so uh uh stubbornly staying on
my table too
even though i was pushing her off
so stubborn
okay i'm gonna take a picture of the
eggs later by the way and put it on
twitter
um so that you guys have a clear look
and that the other toy members will see
it too hopefully
i will however now read um super chats i
think a little bit
and not too much though because i need a
little bit of a break before the members
stream
[Music]
welcome bankers to the family yes
and welcome welcome indeed
it's so nice to have so many
fluff balls around me sorry there's a
cat uh raccoon hair
who knows at this point it could be
anything
in my mouth
[Music]
no no it could not be a skunk
no
technical or important donation
[Music]
thanks for the pinky
no no so interesting now should we
switch to the
to my other office screen it will look
like a mess at first don't be surprised
equia
wait wait wait wait
there we go
let me fix the chat
hearts of trash i say
raccoon is not
no
[Music]
no trash
nice y'all
okay
and this one let me cut the
that part
[Music]
i had
i had today again recently i'm making
this a lot i'm really into making
banana blueberry not only blueberry but
uh any berry banana berry chocolate
pancakes these days
yeah i ran out of um blueberries so
i put uh a mix of frozen berries after
warming it up of course
on the pancakes today i ran out of fresh
berries
wait
no i didn't i forgot i bought
strawberries i didn't use them i'm gonna
eat them today for dessert
and hopefully if they're still good
tomorrow i'm gonna eat them tomorrow too
i bought like premium strawberries yo
and i forgot about them i knew i would
forget about them i bought them on
friday
and then i was like yeah might not be
around on saturday march but i'll eat
them on sunday and of course i forgot
today sunday and i forgot god damn it
i forgot my strawberries i need to eat
them before they go
[Music]
stream on screen
here we go we're starting windbreaker
now i actually don't have the console
yet but i'm confident that i'll get it
until the weekend
yeah i'm sure i'll get it until the
weekend it'll be fine strawberry oh good
idea that's a good idea too
strapping on me because i made banana i
made banana milk the other i could make
banana strawberry milk oh
oh my god
[Music]
more water i'm drinking so much water i
hope i don't by accident drink the
the paint water oh and now we're reading
super chat so if you're not here for
that you can leave but a lot of people
also stay for my super chat readings
because they're all so fun
and i chitchat a lot in between
[Music]
okay
paint water yummy yummy
drink the paint water for content
the thing is like i can't really show me
drinking it so
i could just be fooling you
putting it somewhere else besides my
mouth
and then show you the empty glass and be
like i drank it
[Music]
chunkers
i'll need an audition for bonkers huh
on my table but yeah this is a weekly
schedule please uh
enjoy
put it out a little bit early so you
guys can plan i'm looking forward to fun
week i think this is a good looking week
um
i have to do some other stuff in that
week too
i also have like two doctors
appointments and i need to still record
some vocals and
uh this and that and not go crazy um
so
there's a slight chance that maybe one
of the wind waker streams will get
cancelled maybe
um but that's okay that's okay i just
don't want to stress myself out too much
but yeah
busy busy
amazing any news on a ttrpg no nothing
at this point i feel like
we could we could just um
fade it out and never talk about it
again
it's been too long
but i don't know it's cali's choice
yeah it's kyle's choice if she wants to
do it like last episode or so that's i'm
totally fine with that
[Music]
welcome new egg welcome and happy easter
eggs joining on easter just makes so
much sense
join us new eggs
remember stream right after this one
actually so it would be perfect timing
perfect timing
[Music]
i think a lot of people already forgot
about it so
but of course you would want like a
proper end to it
right
i get that
but i think a lot of people already
forgot about it
[Music]
friday yeah friday 10 p.m
is a korean study
i will try to
have hunger down
by then or at least partially
so that duolingo can't confuse the hell
out of me anymore
yeah time scraper that's great
all right i'm going to start reading
super chats where do i have to start
[Music]
again unarchived rebroadcast starship
titanic
i think starship titanic right that's
where we start
i think
i think until then i was caught up
hallelujah but that's still actually
quite a lot
[Music]
nice to see you guys yeah happy easter
full of sun
okay
the
starship starship thumbnail
i
i was surprised by the limp
a pretty damn good sim stream
[Music]
uh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
what what is happening what did i do
[Music]
i just did some weird setting
okay you didn't see that
[Music]
okay a pretty good sims 4 stream
a pretty good one
versus this super unknown game
streamed back to back
[Music]
now guess which one
had more
views this one
and i think i know why
do you think do you guys
know why
you guys know why i think i know why
i think
it's it is obviously just because people
thought it was about star wars
right
looking at the
looking at the thumbnail starship oh
star wars game
obviously
and people love space
all those things
i mean
i don't care but it's just for me funny
to see
how
a thumbnail can really
you know change the way
things are
um
[Music]
you got to
it is um
something that i will have to continue
studying
and
observing
[Music]
it's not a clickbait i played it on on
easter friday
so i was in a bunny suit
[Music]
what is there
to click bait there is no click bait
there i was in a bunny suit because it
was easter
easter
[Music]
nothing wrong with it it was actually on
topic
okay
i did see the cover of sparks
yes
yes i was so happy to see it
thank you very much
[Music]
i think uh
was that the only one or was there
another one before
i think that might be
the sorry i'm playing with the egg
that might be the first
spark sun cover did i pull up the
instrumental somewhere did i
was that released was the
[Music]
what the song
because if i didn't then how did they
get the they might have tried to create
them themselves created themselves like
because that's actually possible you can
try to filter out the voice
[Music]
instrumentalism
is that official
it sounded very
[Music]
um you know like the original hmm
anyway front for the audition for the
red super chat tangent i need to tell
you something i'm so hyped for dokomi
that i actually get really nervous oh
can you imagine yes i bet you can you go
on a con and you see your aussie on
stage you'll cheat for her and swoosh so
much with those pen lights while
screaming your soul or vocal chords out
while listening to her singing and maybe
maybe you can talk to your aussie on
meet and greet
if you don't forget how to talk that's
so crazy only thinking about it makes me
[\h__\h]
i must have passed out sorry what i
actually wanted to say was i'm grateful
to get a chance this year and thank you
for participating again and dokomi love
your kiwawa thank you
yeah it's it's um it's a pleasure for me
to be able to go to dokomi again and
give you know the german and non-german
kfp people a chance again who wanted to
be there last year but weren't able to
go there last year but i wasn't able to
go this year and i know how it feels um
especially for the meet and greet for
concerts like going to like
concerts of idol groups that i like
oh let me change the pgm by the way um
it wouldn't really apply like concerts
wouldn't make me nervous i would just be
super hyped and excited to
you know
vibe to my
idol groups concert
but meet and greet i mean i never had a
like a one-on-one meet and greet just
you know handshake events but that oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah the short amount of
time
makes you feel so pressured
so but you guys have way more time with
me than i had with the idols that i went
to a handshake event with two four
[Music]
so
you guys have more time but even then
it's a short amount of time i think last
year we had like one minute per person
and
that i guess sounds like long enough but
that one minute is over really quickly
especially considering that i always
offered everybody who came in
um at the end to take a quick photo a
quick selfie and that took up quite some
time
um wasn't it free was it free oh it was
free but it felt like one minute
i think yeah okay okay it was three
minutes but it felt like one minute um
three minutes just sounds like a lot but
it's really short
really short um
once you once you get into a
conversation it's really [\h__\h] short
so you guys should think about what you
want to talk about i think last year uh
a lot of the people who came to my meet
and greets
didn't really think through what they
wanted to talk about
and
basically just
came in sat down and if it weren't for
me they would have been quiet
but i immediately
knew what was up and would usually be
like oh what's your name where you from
how long are you watching my streams oh
one year oh my god thank you for being a
fan for so long and so on you know
uh oh
that is called an airport oh
it was both the most awesome and awkward
thing oh yeah i can imagine yes
[Music]
brain empty style no i would personally
appreciate if you guys would
not go in totally brain empty style
um and i also think
it's a bit
way a waste if i do all the talking you
should tell me it's a meet and greet you
should tell me you know what you feel
and all that uh put your super chats
into words i guess
so
uh everyone who's coming to the
convention and the meet and greet please
think about what you're gonna say to me
i would appreciate it
you can bring notes yes
i write a damn script that's okay
that's okay that's you know um
when i went to handshake events say
there was not much time so there was not
much to remember but it's very important
to not go completely blank and then
forget because if there's so much time
pressure then you might forget what you
wanted to say
yeah yeah and thanks for the super chats
more and more thank you for a fro
looking forward to having you with
dokomim
[Applause]
thank you
monkey and evans l
evans
[Music]
i'm so happy to see you again
i heard you're going to come back and
help me find the rest of my friends who
you are aren't you who ah well i'm
definitely coming back to see you this
month
i love you
don't forget about you
for the pinky you have to know does this
have to deal with the events of
april 15 uh
1912 voice is just some amazing
coincidence as i said on stream it was a
coincidence
a weird coincidence indeed
but it was a coincidence
that the titanic starship titanic stream
i forgot to leave the thumbnail on
oopsie
let me put it
back yeah
that was a coincidence that was a puke
window and the coincidence that the the
dates that i chose to stream this was a
coincidence
a funny one though kind of funny
oh thank you for the pinky duck thank
you for the red super chat
oh you were so helpful holy [\h__\h]
a bar but i like to order a
non-alcoholic titanic title later for
the cute phoenix sitting at the bar and
a rise of firecracker for the p gate
with the extra crushed chimpkin
no crush jim can please that's that's so
brutal boss can i dedicate my kiana kiss
to p gate thank you
to pig aid
i should turn this down just kidding
pj is fine
i think it's fine
be good paid
there you go
ah it was his birthday
oh i think i may have seen that
happy birthday birthday oh no it's today
i feel like i saw something on
twitter
happy birthday
happy birthday happy birthday
[Music]
nice congratulations
thank you both of you for your support
love
love you too
thank you the game recreation
this super will be my last super for a
while because i'm going to dokomi
wait i already knew that right i know i
know there's one there was one korean
person telling me they were going to
dookumi was it pong or was it someone
else do we have two people
also i saw during your collab with
mother fauna that you want to swap cats
like that tv show i have cats at home
they're not with you i mean but i mean i
guess
show me pictures of your cats i want to
see
but that's so oh my god
that's so amazing you're going to
welcome me
i hope you can get into the meet and
greet keep your eyes open so that you
can make it
um i will let you guys know i will
inform you guys once the applications or
whatever is open
restraining members only today yes i am
yes i am i need to put up the
reservation i'm sorry
i'm sorry oh my god um this stream will
be over
uh at the latest in one hour so that i
can take a break
yeah there's no no information yet
i don't know it for sure either how
we're gonna do it
so please just be patient
remember stream is in three hours from
now
[Music]
so paul thank you no no comes
looking for it
uh please have a safe trip to
germany um
very exciting is it your first time in
germany probably right
oh
there's a
there's some good restaurants there even
little good korean restaurants but if
you're there i guess you should probably
eat a german food actually i tell
i tell all the europeans who are going
to dokomi to eat japanese food there
because they have really great japanese
food but you as a korean you probably
have really good japanese food in korea
anyway as well
and you have great korean food obviously
too so when you go to germany to
dobomite you should just eat german food
yeah yeah
[Music]
and um then you'll be able to go to
restaurants that aren't
fully crowded
and overfilled overflowing with people
because all the all the japanese and the
korean restaurants are
filled to the brim
dark iron thank you for the red super
chat it just is a happy smiley but that
means you're happy watching my stream
right and i am happy too thank
[Music]
thank you
thank you very much
stopped with ribs yes exactly
[Music]
ah let me try to read this now uh no i
can't read all of them i can't read part
of this korean name
i think the the the square was m right
and then e that's a is it me
me
now that that one like a snake i didn't
learn yet
but the one next to it is the e again
and then that's a knee and the one that
looks like a h is uh that was a e i
think
so
something
let me look it up
let's see if i was wrong maybe i was
wrong
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
no yes
yeah the middle one i couldn't read i
guess that's the r the snake is an r
mini
[Music]
i was able to read the first one and the
last one
soon the day will come when i don't need
papago anymore
nice
those are easy
i feel smart
i remembered it i need to practice
though
[Music]
thank you
for next time
should we start singing so long and
thanks for all the fish
or shall we sing so long and thanks for
all the chicken
are you referencing to
uh
sound of music so long and thanks for
all the fish it doesn't sound quite
accurate
thank you felix for the red super chat
why the fish
the game was all about chicken it's a
hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy ref oh
[\h__\h] once again i'm not getting a
reference but we are gonna do you know
what we haven't seen a movie in a while
so the next to after today uh so in two
weeks time the members stream will be a
hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy members
only stream because i think i need some
something um where i don't need to do
much anyway
yeah we're going to watch it after that
go watch it i miss you watching long
spanking i don't want to do them too
much because i know it's a little bit
low effort
but they're also fun you know and i
i haven't seen many movies in my
lifetime apparently i've missed out on a
lot of good movies
so yeah it's nice to experience them for
the first time with you guys so felix i
hope you will be there too
because you seem to know the movie but
it'll be it will be nice to watch it
together right thank you felix
[Music]
you know she does a lot of public ones
and i think they're for her like as a
public one they're they are they work
good as like filler streams i think
um yeah but for members only since i
don't do them that often i do them once
every two weeks
uh
generally of course i would also like to
have them
all be special but with the lack of
games
you know
i can only do like very limited things
in memphis only and i can do like
singing streams and maybe some you know
creative stuff like i did today but a
lot of these ideas like the creative
ideas i kind of want to keep for public
streams too
it's difficult to decide what to do
um but at the moment at least for today
we have a new game for the first time in
a long time
[Music]
for you thank you thank you thank you
for your very generous donation
[Music]
phoenix fire thank you
you were warning me here to save
frequently in different slots especially
in parrot puzzles you were warning me
but i didn't see it oh man we suffered
we suffered but thank you doug for
helping out so much you finished the
whole game in order to help me and it
was really really good
optimus prime
[Music]
uh
zombie duncan
such an obnoxious animal
i think it
made me even more certain that i will
never get a parrot in real life i lived
with a family before with a host family
that had a whole room filled with birds
i don't think they have parrots though
normal birds are okay but they're out
they they all noisy to keep as a pet
really noisy
not really a pet i would want
[Music]
like there's some noise in you and then
you can't even do as much with them like
you can with cats hats are noisy somehow
a little bit sometimes depending on how
you raise them too
well you can do so much more with them
you can hug them
and play with them and all that i mean
you can play a little bit with birds too
maybe but still
yeah i don't know
oh not a great scream of that that's
true
yeah they can be insanely cute i know
i've seen like really cute bird videos
but i wouldn't keep them as a pet yeah
sure you can hug birds but they're so
tiny so [\h__\h] tiny there's not much to
hug
and i can't face plant a bird
i can face plant a cat and have the
fluff all over my face
but with birds it doesn't cover my face
a very common pet background from the
loudest thing ever
they're coming really they're not really
common here
seen real parrots
probably yeah
oh you mean because they're really big
i guess there are some big birds yeah
i guess so
but like i mean
try taking care of one of those men
sounds tough
my raccoons raccoons have a lot of
fair to face planting two yes
of course i face my raccoon what a
question is that what kind of question
is that huh of course i do
[Music]
where was the cocoon packaging
ac
thank you
for your first ever super chat duncan
jacob 47 out thank you
[Music]
pirates
yeah already uh it's in the works i
already have a sketch from the artist
at this time i went with an artist that
i thought would probably be able to
finish it in in a very short deadline
um but for the others i'm gonna plan
ahead more
yeah
do you think it will need to be problem
i think
we're just going to leave
maybe i'll ask my manager
for the pinkie
jimkins this is what i endured the last
few days to test this game for full
playability
this is how much we chimpkins love our
boss now she understands i really
understand
i understood before that you love me but
now now i know there's so much
dedication there
holy [\h__\h] thank you so much it was
really great that
someone tested out like the full game
because if i did that then i would know
you know then i would know how the
game's story and all that goes
and i would have probably gone crazy
just testing it by trying to solve the
riddles on my own
we gotta let the chickens do the hard
work
and i just lean back and let you
let you tell me what to do
businesswoman
this is how we do it
[Music]
but thank you for helping as well
logical paradox
is
[Music]
you today
your the stuff you made is so cool i
kind of want to use it in my stream
somehow
but i'm not sure how
[Music]
thank you
thank you so much
i love your pixel art it's really cool
i'm gonna see more of your work
very mysterious suddenly joins twitter
and puts up cool pixel art of kiwawa
did you guys see i retweeted it it's the
the one that painted like a kfp city
with skyscrapers with the the one before
that was also really cute i thought i
could if i if i was the type of person
to use stream alerts i thought
um the other one that they did could be
used as a stream alert thingy like
popping up
whenever you know we have a member join
or something like that and i kind of
want to start doing that just in order
to use that
[Music]
that one was so cute
the smaller one hmm
all right yeah but we already have a brb
screen but i guess i could switch it i
don't know but that one says super chats
oh i guess that could be i don't know
i don't know
any reason you don't use it
just because
i mean i also personally just don't like
having alerts pop up constantly on the
screen
it's just i don't know i feel like it's
cleaner this way i mean my screen here
my office is already pretty messy a lot
of stuff coming going on already but
with alerts it would be even messier
i don't really like it but if it's
maybe just for members
then
maybe
i could tolerate it maybe
yeah i think it's distracting especially
if they have sound too
like i sometimes really rarely i watch
some twitch streams really rarely i just
peek into it
and it's like a constant
we won't
we
i'm using like i don't know farting
sounds and throwing up sounds and weird
[\h__\h]
sounds like from the alerts and i'm like
[Music]
how do you even manage to talk and have
a conversation when there's constant
noises going on there holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i mean i'm sure that it can be fun
adding like funny alerts and every time
i mean a lot of people probably do
certain things to get these alerts to
happen because they are funny and that
motivates them to donate more or
subscribe or whatever
but holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
with the sounds it's really obnoxious
i
i can't imagine doing that on my stream
[Music]
oh me channel
i don't know i'm too used to
the way youtube streams are
um
people who come from twitch to youtube
must be like
what is this why is it so quiet why is
why is everything so calm here
they must feel like something's missing
maybe
[Music]
yeah
onion alert for every red super no thank
you
no thank you
[Music]
no
yeah yeah yeah youtube is getting hit by
a barrage of things that kills anything
they say
yeah i can't i i see them being
interrupted while they're talking so
many times like it
that's so disrupting don't you think
but to each their own
oh yeah he only uses them too but if
only i didn't think it was that
disruptive
it's not that
like powerful like overpowering
yet
and i mean ollie is generally a chaotic
energetic person so even if it was it
kind of fits her stream maybe
[Music]
yeah
man ollie is louder anyway
[Music]
yeah it's relatively quiet yeah yeah
yeah
uh where was i
um
congratulations on beating starship
titanic i didn't really know what to
expect when you finally got the chance
to play it but i've been looking forward
to this for a long time and it was a
blast thank you
[Music]
yeah i think for me
uh
i just wanted to play it because it's
like a really nostalgic game for me and
i want to share some kind of
things with you guys that feel nostalgic
to me because i think it's kind of
personal
and yeah it feels it feels like we're
getting intimate
you know by sharing personal things
and yeah that's that's nice i like that
like we're bonding we're bonding
even though it was a bit painful
but it's it's um it's a bonding
experience um and thinking back we'll be
like huh wasn't that funny when we
played that old ass 1998 game
and tried our best to solve it together
and then just said [\h__\h] it and use
guides all the time
[Music]
that was the first time that i played a
game on my stream
while using a guide and i partially feel
ashamed that's not how obviously not how
you should stream games
um
but for this one i had to make an
exception
i would have gone insane
yeah
[Music]
i would have gotten insane and you guys
would have gone insane too because i'm
really not good with like puzzle games
and
yeah my brain will just go like
[Music]
you know that um sound of
uh phones or tvs or something that don't
work
not working signal
yeah portal um
we're gonna be fine
i know it's a puzzle game but
we're gonna be fine i'm sure
[Music]
i'm gonna be fine
i have you guys at least you guys
probably a lot of you guys probably
played portal already
with titanic starship titanic it was
like
two people in the chat that played it
so
at least that played it recently so that
they could help
with portal
you guys are gonna be able to help me
much more
it's more physics-based puzzles that's
cool
that's okay
[Music]
yeah we did some super liminal too
and that was also like
physical puzzles no
hmm
that was fun super lemon was so cool
[Music]
and what was that
did i read the whole thing thank you
jacob 47 out for your pinky
sleep forever etc thanks for the
thinking
thank you for your parts on in the
one-on-one collab with fauna oh you're
funna you're sampling huh fun of them
that's why i feel like i don't know your
name i have been waiting since your
debut month for a collab between my two
favorite v tubers
my two favorite idols and my two
favorite anime girls what thank you for
everything you do this week's schedule
rocks
oh of course it's always nice to have
your favorites club that's nice good for
you
you're welcome
nice oh i'm happy for you
thank you soon for supporting both of us
yeah yeah
i feel like um
i feel like
we have potential for more but
yeah it was fun though
the
the gaming part was fun and and uh
chit chatting was fun too i'm glad i got
to play clubhouse games again this was
fun fun fun fun he got some nice wins
too
didn't lose by a huge margin no no it
was 5'5 at the end so
big success i would say
[Music]
and tanaka
congratulations on getting a nice phone
as someone that likes to play older
games from time to time it was really
nice to see this was something different
for sure thank you for the stream
potential thank you for watching yeah
very very different from what i usually
play
you guys know i usually stray from older
games uh but
this one i mean it had 3d
so
what i don't really like to see that
much is older games for like 2d and
pixely and all that but this one was
okay actually it's pretty pretty looking
good
i would say for 1998
and it had a big plus big bonus because
of the nostalgia
and my mom playing it
[Music]
but i would say it's retro right so
finally a good retro really old retro
game on my channel
thank you for watching cyrex i'm glad
you enjoyed it daisy as well thank you
for the pinkies since i know you
probably won't read the book
hitchhiker's guide to galaxy movie
watching yes you're doing it i promise
yeah i won't be reading the book anytime
soon but
you know maybe maybe one day when i'm in
a in a rocking chair maybe i'll start
reading some books that i missed out on
who knows never say never
the guy nicholas duncan the game of
korean duncan thank you i'm here thank
you for the thinking
good job now if we can expand into space
and maybe next time read the sentence
and sentences in the guide to the end
what do you mean i i read them to the
end but i just didn't know that the
order was that important for some things
and i also didn't i legit just didn't
want to full on
read the whole thing from beginning to
end i was trying to you know just
just you know look peek over just use a
few hints and trying to do it myself
partially at least partially but
when i tried to do that i realized holy
[\h__\h] it's not working what am i missing
and then i had to look closer and closer
and start from the beginning and all
that and
i feel bad about that
i feel bad about using it so much i
didn't do anything man we didn't do
anything even though forgot it's still a
hard game yeah a little bit yeah
um
schneider thanks for the pinky great
cover and gameplay through have you
considered maybe trying out
vtm swan song it's a western rpg set in
the same universe as the tt approaching
and releasing in may
and i thought it might interest you
based on the trailers
the same world as our ttrpg
[Music]
oh i looked it up on google
it looks so dark
wow
um
i have to say the world of darkness
world is not really like
something i really dig that much
mmm like vampires and all that
i don't know what you think vampires are
kind of tacky
except battle senpai
murder senpai is an exception but the
whole like vampire
thing with like you know the vampire
movies twilight you know stuff like that
and looking from
judging from the google pictures that
i'm seeing it also looks kind of tacky
um
yeah i don't know
no not tacky but edgy maybe edgy is what
i'm trying to say
trying to be very edgy
tacky edgy
oh sorry manuel it looks kind of cool
though maybe if i watch a
trailer maybe it can
um
catch my interest
i'll keep the tab open
but it looks very edgy and tacky so far
twilight ruined vampires
yeah
[Music]
they might they may have yeah yeah
they may have uh getting getting
husky again
[Music]
that was a vampire
and yeah i know i did a cover of a song
called vampire but that was just a cute
[\h__\h] song
you're just so cute
[Music]
and it didn't look or sound edgy
anyway whatever
you're trying to catch me on my double
standards huh
looking for the top down dominique
for the pinky original music let's go
yes let's go
thank you gd
i'm doing my best to put out a good
amount of music
this year
um but it's still it still feels
like it's not that much yeah there's
like
a long process of creating
in between each song
and i can't do too many things at once
it takes so much time i'm sorry
i want to do more if i could i would
rather it's not vampire or anything
let's just get this out what does that
mean
violet is not vampire or anything
i don't don't know what that means
i mean are you saying that not all
vampires are like twilight vampires well
i mean sure
yeah
uh
[Music]
oh
i would like to dedicate oh oh you're
dedicating it to someone out to myself
i would like to dedicate a second kiss
to other kiana who keeps inspiring you
to push hard and not quit we are proud
of our hard-working aussie
thank you
yeah the
there's the one that's pushing and the
one that's um
pulling pulling into the darkness and to
be honest it's getting kind of strong
that kiana
recently
oh but the other chiara the the positive
one is um very much trying hard to
to keep kiara
above above water
yeah
trying very hard but it's getting
difficult
i kind of want to take like a break but
i'm still powering through
no time for break
maladies is
a low-key break
still trying to create content but
i'm gonna get a good good uh chill break
i think
yeah
yeah yeah i'm just trying to power
through until then
[Music]
very motivating mo maldives vacation is
quite a big motivation
thank you jim tracy duncan oh let me
read this the first one is b
[Music]
i didn't don't learn
the middle ones yet and also when i
learned the last one so i only can read
the first one
b
b and something that ends with it
okay let me try to analyze this yeah i
see an m
i see an e
and i see a r
a snake
so that's me
meat
and then
chop chop
i see the b
i see the the o
the j i didn't learn yet
hold up
and the t
the t t i didn't learn yet either but i
learned that
okay
[Music]
very interesting
it makes sense it really makes a lot of
sense
[Music]
i'm learning yeah
and i need to analyze like how they're
built it makes a lot of sense
[Music]
yeah
pepsi dancing
calling burgers
thank you
oh
that's one of the reason my brother
known as that sucks day oh
[Music]
oh what is your birthday
was the 15th of your birthday colin
happy belated birthday
the gamer created
[Music]
it's cool seeing you getting this down
i'm trying i'm trying i'm trying but you
know need some patience need some
patience i'm old
[Music]
okay we're gonna read the ones from the
unarchived uh
rebroadcast of my kada okay
this one
i was actually on the road when this was
happening so
every now and then i peeked into
the stream and i saw you guys vibing and
made me really happy even though i
wasn't really there you guys are still
um you know
hyping it up and that made me happy
thank you so much thank you
um
[Music]
hope it was fun for you guys a second
time or first time
thank you very much kian's missing
earring
um
see i saw you guys pointed it out but i
think
ah
there should be one
i'm pretty sure
i have it in my 3d model
uh
i think i even pointed it out before
like hey it's missing it can you add it
and then they added it i think
i think um but it might just be
that picture
that didn't have it perhaps
but it supposedly has it
yeah the badge is funny um
because the badge isn't supposed to be
there when i have the sword and the
shield out i know
but it's okay i mean for that picture
to show off everything nicely i think
it's okay to
be out just for for that moment
your singing was amazing black eyed peas
ankle was so fun thank you
maybe the angle it could be the angle
yeah
my face
you stop pointing out everything
it's okay it's okay
it's
difficult to you know recreate
everything perfectly but
i mean
i pointed out some things myself
to the
team
to have some things fixed
and uh
eventually
i might get like a little bit of an
updated version
but mostly it was okay
yeah
yeah for that picture they um
you know got rid of the black spats
spots
because that's like a promotional
picture where they did some after
editing and all that
but whenever i use my my model it will
always have the
spots
the black pants always unfortunately
[Music]
sorry
ah
reminder to update the hotodory picture
frame
to what so the picture that is your
profile picture the the mama loading
picture
no
i can't i can't put that up there
[\h__\h]
is doing long names the fetch thing to
do today
thank you yes it is the game recruit
damage and shadow pencil duncan derek
seattle
diesel
um
[Music]
thank you
really
i guess
i guess i can actually
all these pictures are prepared um by
not by me though
by the way um
[Music]
we can add her eventually no stress
seconds
[Music]
down thank you max for the first time
it's 2 a.m and i can't remember the last
time i've enjoyed a karaoke stream so
much you sound like you're having so
much fun and i can't help but have fun
with you thanks so much kimono thank you
it was definitely one of my
one of the karaokes i had the most fun
with i think
i was listening
um
while i was traveling uh and i heard
some
some notes that
uh
sounded really bad though so
the nervosity and a little bit of a lack
of practice kind of messed up some songs
but overall it was just fun
it was just fun for me
i want to do another one old butt gold
cut out
i want to sing more
old songs from 1980s
and after
yeah i want to see more of those hey
yes
[Music]
oh my god why am i so
drying out today
[Music]
oh my god i keep on drinking water i
really need to go to an island meeting
that code thank you for the pinky
i need a pencil she's gotta be cute and
she's gonna be fetched and she's gonna
be larger than life and she is wait what
melody is that supposed to be
i need a potential i need a
i need a hero
[Music]
no way where is the melody where's the
melody ah
that'll be cute she's gonna be features
i know i know i know i know i know i
forgot the melody
[Music]
i don't know anymore
[\h__\h] that was such a good song though
i want to sing more songs from
that lady
bonnie taylor was that her
thank you very much that is very helpful
i'm holding up a hero
till the end of them i don't know
anymore
[Music]
thank
thank you for the pinky
pinky for the boss who is now turning
pink
why
why why why why why why what was i
thinking then
some cute song
i didn't sing any pink songs
[Music]
oh just because i was blessing
oh
[Music]
madonna you screwed me over
one too many times
god damn it
madonna i thought you were a good
christian girl
cemetery thanks for the pink uh super
chat sticker no more comes on
thank you
[Music]
my homes she's got me spending ooh
spending all you super chats on me
for the pinkie
humps and lumps are nice potential
voices divine
[Music]
i can read your name now without looking
up on papago
[Music]
thank you for the pink super chat but
the super chat message i have to look up
that one looks complicated
what is this one
[Music]
come on
we're done with these super chats thank
you soon everybody
we have caught up with today's stream
but i want to take a break down hey i
want food
[Music]
i have oh i have leftovers from
yesterday nice
speed yeah uh my my fruit is not doing
so well right now i need a break uh
we're gonna um play a town scraper later
i'm gonna put up the reservation i'm
gonna make a thumbnail quickly or just
reuse it from there
and yeah immediately after the stream
i'm gonna put up the reservation
[Music]
are you trying to say sounds
good enjoy your food thank you
looking forward to it yeah
you guys should
also get the game and then make a town
alongside me i think it's a it looks
like a really
really pretty chilling
chill
uh relaxing game i think a lot of you
guys would enjoy it
already did oh
what food did you eat
oh
hot pork chicken
which is um
our pepper guys bell pepper red
red bell pepper chicken with spatula
which is uh those those noodles that i
made before that are not really noodles
[Music]
as i said it's not really an easter dish
but
it was one of my favorite dishes when i
lived with my mommy
i'm gonna eat that now of course it was
some
vegan chicken
[Music]
yeah i need a break i'm i'm tired maybe
i'll take a nap i shouldn't take a nap i
woke up at a good time to the extra i
got a full
really um refreshing sleep amount of
sleep you know how i said recently
um i can't sleep as much as i used to
but tonight i slept a lot
and i slept early yeah i think i got
like eight or nine hours or eight and a
half hours maybe
which was really nice and i woke up
before eleven
amazing
before 11 but naturally not even trying
to wake myself up at a certain time
i could have woken up before nine if i
wanted to
but i didn't need to
yeah
rocking four hours of sleep why are you
not sleeping are you doing it for me
you shouldn't please sleep oh my god go
sleep now you can watch the members
stream another day
it's not members participation anyway
you better go sleep now
[Music]
why what did you do with our attention
well it's on time sometimes you know
sometimes it happens
[Music]
ah
oh you're doing it for
your parents
okay that's okay
i guess it's not because of me
catching up with youngsters when you're
behind is tough though
oh i saw the meme that you posted on
your community by the way it was it was
suggested to me in my youtube feed
thank you
for your support
[Music]
i got up early for your streams
are you from
the north american
area
i i make so many of you
live a healthy lifestyle because you
guys are so used to waking up at like 9
00 a.m or even earlier of your pst to
watch my streams
wow
actually living a healthy life waking up
early you guys have so much time for the
rest of the day if my stream isn't 9
hours long
but then you can accomplish so many
things isn't that amazing
[Music]
yes
living very healthy yeah you should
thank me
[Music]
yeah sca on the other side is pure
suffering
i mean i'm not forcing you but i'm very
happy that there's so people who try
their best to watch me or you guys
should just watch the archive though
okay
all right i'm gonna go now
i really need to go to an idol meeting
i'll read the rest of the super chats um
in the snack box stream
so thank you everybody for coming today
i'll put up a photo of the eggs i'm so
proud of them now
i think they look okay
i'm looking at them now and i think
together as a as a group they look
pretty cute
yeah
yeah i'm good with them
oh thank you thank you guys for uh
celebrating easter with me
just got back sorry but there will be a
members only stream in two hours that
you can watch
thank you for the fun time today
[Music]
um
yeah
thank you thank you guys and in german
we say
thank you
thank you very much
yeah
forehead austin
[Music]
see you later or on tuesday
thank you
[Music]
i'm