[Music]
foreign
thank you
kick it again
hey girl
hi hello hello
ladies hello girl to my right side and
my left side
kitty kitty Girls
Girls Girls Girls Girls
hi girls in the chat
hi we're all girls here right everybody
yeah everyone's flying on the girls
sleepover right yeah no girl stalkers
here right exactly right girls here for
girls talk
you are stalking the girls while we are
talking with the girls
[Music]
the
lack of space was actually clever and
intentional yes
uh well okay even if you're not a girl
you're welcome of course but there might
be many things that you wouldn't
understand but we will help you get it
right maybe you can learn today you
don't never understand us girls
don't get it they just wouldn't get it I
know never understand me
because they will understand we can
truly care freely talk about anything
yeah another one you hear is like
question mark question mark question
mark
oh that's a good point
I can take notes and Google it later
you'll still be confused
yeah well I'll try our best guys to make
you understand but
um first I was really surprised that
everybody was so interested in this so
now you're getting it so try to keep up
with us okay
friends I think this started because we
talked about hair removal
how did we even get to that topic
they're done I don't know I feel like
I've actually talked about Hair Removal
really talked about it in the Halloween
collab too did we we did with Cali
I don't even remember what we talked
about but I vaguely remember this oh
well we're not gonna We're not gonna
start right away with the hair removal
topic but it is on the topic list we
have a couple of topics and
um well we have also some pictures
prepared to look at uh yeah I'm gonna
have this little little girls talk right
now so oh oh let me introduce you to my
girls then uh on my right side who's
who's that girl
[Music]
I'm on the right hello
wait am I yes you're right my they're
right sorry
later they're right I just realized yes
I meant like you know that girl over
there
mommy yeah
I want myself to introduce yourself
please
um tell me what makes you a girl
[Music]
um I like rainbows and unicorns what
really
cute
very cute okay so then another girl on
that side what's that green girl there
I am green girl fauna
hello hello what makes you a girl
that's a deep philosophical question no
you can't just ask that so casually
hmm okay but I've always felt it deeply
in my soul you felt it I know what it is
you like flowers yeah I like flowers yes
oh okay then um let me actually uh jump
right into this little question but um
we're gonna go move my last because she
wanted to cheat off of our answers yes
copy the homework yes
um well I'll start then so I'm takanasi
kiwawa
um and and the question that I've asked
the girls beforehand and I'll also
answer is uh what's the girliest thing
about you
ah think think think my Luna is thinking
me and fauna will ask well that's a hard
question I don't know if I have an
answer prepared anymore okay
um well I think
um there could be many things but what's
the girliest About Me
Maybe other people would
have an easier time answering that than
me but one thing I guess I could say is
girly about me is
my
manner not now the way I the way I
move my hands and so on when I talk well
maybe and my bad mannerisms yeah not
matters that's right mannerisms
and also I mean of course this doesn't
mean that uh your Girling just because
you have cats but I feel like me having
cats somehow and the the
the way I treat my cats all about that I
think is kind of girly and also crazy
cat lady style but
let's just say it's girly and
just to throw
a very specific one out there uh I don't
at least I didn't have to I didn't used
to have many like
tools for
construction at home
and then um when we like had to do stuff
in my home like put out pictures and so
on and Furniture uh
I I had to like get some stuff you know
and so I got the cutest freaking Hammer
ever
it's a really small Hammer but it's pink
and it has flowers on it
cute yeah it's cute and so every time
when someone comes by to help me like
put some furniture together and they're
like okay well do you have a hammer I'm
like of course I have a hammer and I
bring the hammer and it's always like
something that I laugh about yeah but it
works though it's just kind of small but
I'm smaller than the usual Hammer but it
works and then I just talked about this
like two days ago but
um we were we were in need of a
what do you call it again like the the
thing the water scale which is not
called water scale in English actually
but you use it to see if something's
straight
oh
um
okay yeah so I didn't have one and you
know what I what I brought out instead
to fix it to get a level that replaces
it
was it like lip gloss or something no no
because I think lip gloss is not you
know it's not liquid enough
so I got like a little uh from Louis
Vuitton I got like little small perfume
testers yeah the samplers
no because they're relatively small and
they're clear see fruit and very liquidy
and and it has a little like bubble
inside too so you could see it if it's
level or not yeah it works
so stuff like that I would say it's kind
of girly
did you think of something
um I feel like most things about me are
pretty girly
[Music]
my appearance the way I dress myself I
like to be very girly I like frilly
things I like skirts and dresses
I like to style my hair I like to wear
makeup
I think me and Luma can probably confirm
that yeah is the girliest in terms of
like appearance right very parallel
but you're the girliest I would say in
terms of appearance where I don't know
we have different styles I would think
but but when I when I first met you
fauna uh you know when we were at umez
uh back then I think I told you anyway
but
I used to dress and all that like you I
used to do my hair like you I used to
dress like you so I felt like I saw
myself in you
I remember you saying that
yeah yeah well well I mean
I mean I I feel like I kind of grew up a
bit but for you I feel like it still
fits
yeah well I feel like I will never grow
out of it because it's like my whole
life like ever since I was a little girl
I've always loved like any excuse to
dress up like I loved Halloween I loved
any any chance to wear something fun and
frilly and that never really went away
okay so your appearance you would say is
the the girliest thing about you
probably but another thing and I think I
share this with mume he's like
I feel like girls often can be very like
indecisive and talk around what they
really want yeah yeah it's like the
thing it's like where do you want to go
out to eat and it's like oh I don't know
anywhere is fine it's like that kind of
thing oh that's as someone who ends up
always having to take the lead in like
group activities that's actually
annoying because no one ever says like
what they want to do
I know it's annoying
oh my gosh hearing YouTube I was
questioning myself I was thinking am I
really a girl because I I wasn't
relating most of what you were saying
but then that one right there that's
that's probably that's that's copying
isn't it that's causing fauna's homework
well maybe maybe there's some humans who
could tell us what's girly about mummy
maybe they know something oh
just like girly about me like guys
I'm sorry this is trying too hard is
that a girl thing trying to watch insane
like cute
me too that's also my answer moving cute
uh and then I I of course we can all say
your voice but I guess that's not really
like you know an an attribute
um but one thing that maybe you were
forced to do the mermaid but I want to
say because it made me feel like you to
a girly
um when I when I met two girls
in Japan
you two and Bales I hope I can say this
but I thought it was cute so I'm gonna
say maybe you already said it anyway but
um
you all have matching nails and and hair
accessories
oh
oh yeah we had matching bows bad
matching ribbons yeah I think we did
mentioned
and they all had the same hair accessory
and and Nails uh also so cute like they
got their nails done in Japan so cute oh
my gosh I have a story about my nails oh
later okay
can already talk about that no tell me
that tell me
I okay so yeah I got gel nails for the
first time in Japan and they often put
you know like little charms and
accessories on them yes so I back home I
went to a nail salon because I wanted
new gel nails because they you know
whatever
they didn't know they weren't falling
off they were super stuck but they grew
out and it would be too hard to fill it
in or you know whatever if I wore new
ones and it took them nearly two hours
to get the charms off oh because they
were so badly glued on not badly they
were just super glued on
yeah and it was so painful because they
had to file it and they had to like pull
it with pliers and stuff and I have like
YouTube
cried we watched videos of people
removing Japanese gel nail charms and it
was just it was too much glue like there
was no way that was coming off did they
not try to dissolve the glue I feel like
they did they did they tried dissolving
the glue and it wasn't working
I'm trying to find like a picture to
show people what Japanese gel nails are
usually like uh
there's that oh man I told them I was
like you know this could be a form of
torture because it's like ripping nails
off almost oh my God no
but that's fine I'm a tough girl
like girls go through yeah I'm a tough
girl
your nail pain I can also have a really
tough head too
pain tolerance maybe in certain parts
like on my head for sure because when I
was younger mother Al was really bad at
brushing her hair
oh no it was like she'd pull my hair and
stuff so I got used to it so now I've
never had pain when people do stuff to
my hair damn
okay uh I'll keep that in mind
here
oh sure
but that's not a good idea girls talk
off collab
it should be doing each other's hair and
then I guess we can't be rough with each
other
oh
wait whenever I go to the hair salon
they're always like it does this hurt or
they'll make a mistake where they're
like they tug it super hard and I'm like
it's fine
oh that happens sometimes but I always
even if I am in pain I always lie and
say it's fine oh of course you can feel
bad there's a picture the water's too
hot I'm like oh it's fine
water going to my ears oh it's fun I
won't get an infection don't worry now
you get a fruit you're cleaning but yeah
here's just a sample of
um how they could look like but these
are pretty like childish I guess but
um they put like a lot of accessories on
top right and they're really cute and
there's so many different variations and
I never I actually so here's the thing
when I saw you girls with nails I was
kind of jelly because I have never
gotten my nails done before never yeah
not even like normal manicure
before
never never so you paint your own Nails
I don't do that either I mean I've
painted my nails before but oh that's
the last time I did that is like years
ago
I don't don't do that and I guess that
makes me less girly no we have to we
should go
together
I'm into it now I wasn't really doing
anything before like the gel nails and
stuff and now I I want to get them but
even though it was so painful to remove
them
oh I didn't get charms this time I'm
never getting charms again okay so the
chocolate were the painful thing about
it yeah that was the only painful thing
getting them off but yeah years ago oh
this is kind of girly but also kind of
gross is that okay okay bring it on okay
a few years ago I was wearing these new
boots that I got and they were stylish I
wasn't used to wearing stylish boots but
I was walking around a lot in them and
it really hurt but I just dealt with it
and I ended up with giant like bruises
under my nails like my toenails that's
like not really girly but something we
deal with a lot yeah yeah
the blisters so I had purple big toes
and I have purple big toes for a year
and so I ended it because they have to
it has to grow out
it snuck under your nail
um so I did get pedicures that year
because I got like black nail polish on
my toes to hide the
the bruising of my nails that happened
to me but instead of it being shoe
related trauma I dropped my switch
joy-con directly onto my big toe and
closed it and it was just Bruce for like
a year until it grew out
oh yeah that reminds me of hair to paint
my toes that I might do something can I
give you girls a life hack a girl life
hack yes please you know I never wear
like
pumps kind of high heels
pumps pump pumps
because I always fall out of them I feel
like they're so hard to walk in like I
can walk in high heels as long as they
have a strap or so
right let me look up what a pump is real
quick I think I know what it is I guess
it's just like a high heel of normal I
mean they also come with no strap yeah
let's say you want to wear a high heel
but it doesn't have like a strap around
the ankle or so you just keep on falling
out of it so there's one life hack next
time you go to Japan you need to get
this
okay let me show you
[Music]
okay this is really bad quality but okay
you can't even see it but it's like a
see-through strap plastic strap that you
wrap around
um like the middle of your of your foot
basically you see it oh yeah I don't I
don't see it but yeah you don't see it
that's why it's so good oh
I see it yeah yeah so that you will not
fall out of your shoes and it will also
not ruin the whole look yay oh this
might be where I lose the girly points I
never wear high heels
uncomfortable and I never wear them
because I am okay that makes me earlier
than I don't want you to call her though
so I also don't want to wear them
I have so many high heels I wear them
all the time and then people keep on
telling me like
I thought it was not really hard to walk
in but actually surprisingly
uh a lot of high heels are for me very
easy to walk in you just get used to it
and then
it's really not a big deal did you start
from a younger age I never was I never
had opportunity to wear them so oh no
maybe I haven't tried them in a long
time maybe I should try it again
[Music]
platform shoes oh yeah I love flowers
yeah I like platform shoes too but you
didn't want to be taller though
well yeah I don't want to but sometimes
the platform shoe is like so cute and
fashionable and then it's worth being
taller true so true so true all right
all right sometimes they can be part of
the look sometimes I think we are all
imposing on others yeah also knife your
legs and you post your better so you
know
um
we're gonna start with the first topic
um with pictures now the main topic
and I asked the girls to prepare
pictures of their skin care products
yeah so we're gonna talk about those and
about also I guess skin problems and
struggles and all that and maybe the
tips and life hacks and whatever
skincare that's something that non-girls
can definitely relate to as well so
what's up hey hey hey Okay who wants to
start
[Music]
all right here is here is fauna's
collection of skin care and she
currently it is
[Music]
um tell me what I wanna point out
I feel like they sort of fell for the
Korean beauty Trend yeah
there's a lot of nice skin care
um help me talk me for your process and
what is what from the top left what is
that sort of arranged in order somewhere
inside the top uh it's like double
cleansing which I actually like because
uh the first top one is like an
oil-based cleanser and this makes sense
to me just because of like wait you
don't mean the bomb you mean this
[Music]
yeah yeah so it's oil based so in the
one below it is water-based so use them
both because the oil-based one will
dissolve oil and then the water-based
one will dissolve water so together you
can dissolve all the impurities on your
face to get super squeaky clean but the
top one also is really handy because it
removes makeup really well
I also use it as my makeup remover do
you do this like in the morning or
morning and evening or morning evening
okay
I'm not always good about doing
everything but I always do at least
those two and so those Brands were where
are those from
[Music]
um I they're both I got them but wait
should we say where we bought them sure
if you wanna sponsorship
Glam what's that they're just oh it's
like a retailer for Korean skincare oh
so cold Glam yeah like South Korea
in the future how about that yeah please
do just spend too much money on your
website so please
so for how long have you been using
these two
uh I actually used to use different ones
and then they were they stopped carrying
them and I'm kind of sad because the
other ones I had wearing marshmallow
scented but these are nice too I've used
them
maybe six months now oh okay okay okay
what's next to that
um that's a toner I should have two
toners I don't know I like them both so
I use them only I know Tony moly yeah I
like that one a lot because the big one
it makes my skin feel like super super
soft it's calling Mochi and it makes
your skin feel like emoji
oh the left one seems like more like
serious yeah I think it is it's meant to
be like pH balancing which I don't know
sometimes I feel like this skincare is
kind of a
scam but I don't know maybe you will
have to explain to the people what a
toner is please
uh my toe in a drive and no it's
supposed to like balance your skin right
you use it after you wash your face to
like balance and hydrate your skin it
also can remove excess impurities that
are left over
okay how do you apply those with your
finger with a cotton pad and I just use
my hands me too me too
okay so did you also get those from that
website
yes damn damn they gotta sponsor us
okay then oh I see something called
retinol I've I've been I've used that
before too but not the same
um thingy yeah retinol is like a pretty
good ingredient I think it like has a
lot of research behind it so yes you can
sort of feel like it will maybe actually
do something yes it's good um for like
turning over your skin cells like it
increases the turnover rate so it can
help with like anti-aging but it can
also help just in general with the
quality of your skin and like acne and
stuff if it increases the rate of your
skin turnover she sounds like like a
professional who's trying to sell me
something at the college dermatologist
stuff is like kind of a marketing scam
and it maybe doesn't do anything so I
like try to buy stuff that actually has
ingredients that actually do things yeah
yeah
things that you know are very well known
to be good already yeah
okay I see some cool again yeah this one
is like collagen which is also just
supposed to help like as you age yes
your skin loses collagen yes so if you I
guess you can put some more on top of it
to help help again keep you looking
youthful more more just kind of try to
save our face for as long as we can yeah
yeah and it like yeah and it just
increases like the elasticity in your
skin you use all these two before the
makeup too or well I use these only at
night oh before sleeping
sleeping okay okay
I guess a facial mask that you use
sometimes yeah yeah I use this one
sometimes this one's an exfoliator and
it's a chemical exfoliator which I read
is better than a physical exfoliator at
least if you have sensitive excuse me
explain us the difference please
so like a chemical exfoliator is like
chemical based so we'll have chemicals
that basically eat away the dead skin on
your face and then a physical exfoliator
will be something that has like really
fine grains like sugar is really common
and it will like buff away the dead skin
on your face I thought that a chemical
one is more gentle for your skin
um ironic I've heard that Sugar ones can
actually cause like micro abrasions in
your skin can be bad for you potentially
so I don't use sugar scrub even though
they're really common
like a chemical based exfoliator okay
and I really like this one this one
definitely does stuff like I can tell
the difference you shouldn't use it
every day because yes of course of
course keep all your skin away okay and
then we have something green of aloe and
green tea amazing you've got all those
important stuff
this one is my most beloved used it for
like five years I feel like I feel like
at this point it's just a moisturizer
but it's it has no oil in it oil can
make my skin break out so this one is
like it's very sensitive very I like it
a lot it is cheap this one is not
expensive this one doesn't look like
it's from Korea either what is this yeah
it's not this is an American brand I
think never heard of it never yeah it's
like natural one but it's very I like it
when do you use this one miss fauna I
use this one well sometimes at night my
skin feels like it has too much stuff on
it because I just put all of this on it
so sometimes I don't use it I use it in
the morning
sometimes at night too okay so that's
your current skin routine uh would you
say overall you're happy with it
oh no can anyone ever be truly happy
with no skin no no no I'm not happy
either yeah
maybe I don't know how can we achieve
Perfect Skin is it even possible
but it's it's all right I've been trying
to like not go like Overkill with skin
care problems these skincare products
these days because like yeah of course
you can try using like 10 different
products at the same time but I wonder
maybe it is actually better to not like
slap too much on your face all this
yeah so I just try to tone it down yeah
okay well we'll talk about like skin
care problems after we're done like
introducing all the products that we're
using but next I'm gonna go with a
mumma's products okay
[Laughter]
tell us about your selection of products
here okay so mine were chosen not based
on my own research but the research of
others like a dermatologist
well a dermatologist told me some stuff
and then I watched most of the stuff I
have I have because it has good reviews
or I saw someone in a video use it okay
well that's fine that's totally very
valid please make me talk me through
your process and your thoughts and all
that all right first I clean my face
with CeraVe wow well foamy facial
cleanser and I use it because actually
my dermatologist recommended it years
ago yeah that looks like something a
dermatologist would recommend yeah that
dermatologist
the name what comes from like ceramide
which is the all the ingredients in it
I don't know moisturizing I didn't ask
anything the dermatologist like opened a
cabinet and it was just full of
different CeraVe products
he was sponsored
amazing
no like the ingredient in my toner so I
think it's a good one it's simple it's
not cute because yeah I also realized
maybe I'm using too many things so
that's honestly mostly what I've been
using now but I also use vitamin C serum
very good very good this is the same as
retinol I think it might be is it I
don't think it's different because I
have I think different products for that
but isn't the thing with like vitamin C
if you put that on your face actually oh
aren't you like supposed to not really
um go out unless you put um some some
sunscreen sunscreen yeah because
otherwise if you put vitamin C products
on your skin you're gonna like burn
right yeah yeah
right next to it yeah sorry yes this
isn't an order sorry yeah hey you're
getting it you're getting it you're
doing it right yeah yeah yeah I have
vitamin C Sarah
um but also I think I do the serum
usually at night I don't usually put it
on the morning
but that's my because I'm lazy I think
that's normal I think that's fun
I see yeah I have SPF please because my
face is like
naturally and naturally red like it gets
really red mmm no I don't like that so
I'm trying to make it less red oh well
sunscreen in general
not only in summer it's just always
important right I never put it on but
you're supposed to put it on all the
time even when it's not like super sunny
and even in Winter you should put it on
apparently I have it in my in my makeup
so I'm always yeah
that's so helpful though because like uh
I feel like for the longest time I felt
like the the sunscreens that I was
getting my hands on would kind of mess
up my
um my base and so on and like oh you
can't really put it on top of your
makeup either so there's a lot of makeup
foundations that come with the sunscreen
protection and that's so such a life
of creators for thinking smart thank you
yeah this one I if I wear it I probably
won't wear makeup it's really watery but
like it Blends in well it just yeah I
don't know it does mess up the base of
it
is a Japanese brand right
[Music]
okay what we have next to it
I think that's a toner
are you sure is it
is that
Korean ice cream I think so
toner and it's too small to read what is
the one next to it oh that one's a
moisturizing cream so these we can use
before makeup too
yeah although I have a different
moisturizing cream right now but I
couldn't find a picture of it
but I usually do that one's that one's
not even really what I have it's the
same brand the moisturizing cream
it's also strong so I usually do it at
night
you you bought these only because
another like persons that they're using
no yeah I watched one video or someone
talked about skin care they only used
four products so I bought the four Pro
oh no actually it was a makeup video it
was a girl who was doing makeup and she
said she used these things before she
did makeup not the moisturizers she's
the toner and then she used the serum
over there that's right now now so
you've got those from another video from
another Creator and now maybe there's
some people in the chat who will copy
this from you so he would keep on like
yeah really giving it to the next people
by the way I looked up reviews and I
look up the stuff about I don't just go
straight to the buy page you know
people I saw girlies and I have been
enjoying them but who knows there could
be better stuff out there because I
haven't tried very much since I think
those are the only serums and toners
I've ever used so who what do I know
[Music]
might not work for you exactly
I mostly just do skincare at night
because my dermatologist once told me to
focus that night like I watched my I I
try I tried to get myself to wash my
face in the morning like properly not
just water and cleanser but yeah I think
that's important because in the night
you like well your skin regenerates but
it also I guess it like sweats and all
that gets dirty from the pillow blah
blah blah so it's important in the
morning I changed my pillow sheets
recently because I think that the cotton
like I think I had too much oil or
something coming off my face at night
because
I looked at it I was like trying to
figure out is there something else I can
do to like reduce the redness in my face
and so I got bamboo pillow sheets and
I've noticed a difference and they stay
cool too like they don't get us warm so
I don't really have to flip my pillow or
anything that's really interesting yeah
I tried silk before because my hair
would tangle sometimes when I was
sleeping
but I didn't like how it felt but the
bamboo is pretty nice okay maybe this
can be some advice for some people it's
interesting yeah okay what's the last
thing this is serum again
oh yes it's a serum I'm not sure what it
does
but it feels nice it makes my skin feel
nice
proposed okay I also have a feeling a
clean gal
clean girl clean girl no skin
smell a little bit weird ah
I feel like my propellant serum smells a
bit weird but just a tiny bit it has a
smell I don't know if it's weird though
this might be off topic but do you guys
know about like the recent makeup trends
and stuff
because I wonder if it's the same all
around the world I feel like in the US
now this clean girl aesthetic is taking
off or maybe it has a cleaner aesthetic
you don't mean just like bare face like
natural aesthetic yeah but it's cool
yeah it's makeup it's just to make it
look like you're not wearing makeup
there's a certain way they do eyebrows
I've seen it well here's the thing I go
to civilization duties where there's
lots of gals and they follow a lot of
them follow the recent Trends that's
where I see it and stuff it makes me
feel weird because I'm like I'm not my
face doesn't look that clean but then I
realized oh they're wearing makeup and
I'm not wearing makeup yeah it just
doesn't look like they're wearing makeup
well the the no makeup look that can
fool people who don't know
especially guys especially guys think
that they're not wearing makeup and they
think that's what's natural but let me
tell you guys it's it's if it might be
makeup it is
nice it might be makeup or or that
person is just really blessed yeah
there are people that just have really
nice skin and naturally yes or maybe
they're getting all like the craziest
skincare treatments
no what's that I think they take they
take like
your blood plasma out of your arm and
then they like micro needle your face
with the blood coming from your arm and
then it's like supposed to oh
I don't think anyone needs to have this
done but
Kim Kardashian did it there's no way
well she's full of
yeah almost hurt me all the Kardashians
are full of I'm looking up before
and after
I think who was that who I talked to
from Japanese members I talked to my
chat about it before but I I mentioned
the Kardashians to them and they had no
idea who they were even after I showed
them the pictures of them they're like
so isn't that like a a beautiful
life to have where no one knows the
Kardashians maybe that's just me
yeah I feel you can't escape them yeah
it's hard even like even someone like me
I don't get like I like makeup here but
I don't really look for that kind of
content or whatever the Kardashian
because Kardashians have Brands and
stuff but I still see I I somehow run
into things about them and I'm like I
really don't need to yeah I found a
picture oh my God I do everything now
um what picture uh do you want me to
I'll send it to you sure you can't share
it though oh I can't share what is it
because it's a specific it's a person
this is secret girl stuff don't look
guys
let's work
right I guess it also looks like someone
just put jam on their face like
strawberry jam let's discuss it's
disgusting at the same time though but
if I think that that's blood then that's
disgusting
uh no way is there even like what is I I
wanted I wanted to find a before and
after is that a Kardashian lady
yeah yes I think so who is this
[Laughter]
she sent the picture of Kim Kardashian
with like blood on her face basically
but smiling
smiling that could be it has her own
blood
[Laughter]
I know someone one who like recently
they got a skincare treatment there was
like a CO2 laser on their face
and this person she looked really scary
after she got it done immediately but
then like a couple weeks later her skin
did look so good even without makeup
toys that's like a CO2 laser skin care
treatment
CO2 let me go let's see a little two
laser treatment
look at this
sorry it might be scary I think yeah all
your skin peels off afterwards that
looks so painful oh God please don't
Google that guys anyway all right
really good
afternoon
well okay um I'll show you my skincare
it's not much because
um as I said I tried to tone it down so
here we go
um currently on the left side I'm using
this
um foam cleanser uh it's from rituals
I think that brand is everywhere
I don't think I've heard of it rituals
it's a nice um phone there's lots in it
and just for a little bit a tiny dot of
of the cleanser there's like so much
coming on out of it so many bubbles than
I currently use
um this is casually I don't think it's a
toner but it's like
uh something to put on your face before
makeup this Japanese one
um yeah yeah just to give it some
moisturizing and I have like some some
eye creams like one from Nivea and one
from bioderma I guess I use whatever I
find in my
um pocket that day it doesn't matter
what do eye creams do again it
get rid of the the puffiness and perhaps
the wrinkles or like prevent the
wrinkles and so on
so I think pretty important around the
eyes so I have some specific ones for
that
and and then uh here on this area we
have some masks like this one the green
one I just used is a it's a tiny like
Castle mask that I bought in Japan the
other day because like it's really
popular right now I think this one this
is Tiny capsule mask you can buy them
one by one and I tested it out just now
I can say it it was pretty good of
course my skin has improved by 300
percent of course
no I don't really feel a big difference
but you know every now and then putting
on a mask because nice the one below is
a big
um rituals mask it's like powder inside
so you mix it like
um with some water and then you put it
on your face oh interesting I've wanted
to get something like that I like that
because
um you can just like uh how to say
measure yourself how much you want
because I feel like a lot of these
pre-packed pack masks they have either
too much now usually I always have too
much in it and then I don't know what to
do with the rest of it yes we use it out
and then rub it on my body yeah wherever
just don't go to waste yeah don't waste
it the mask below I really like this one
because it's like a like um I think like
earth-based it's like a gray mask and it
feels like it's really natural and good
for my face that one really makes my
face feel amazing afterwards
so big recommend I forgot my night cream
because it's currently in Japan I left
it I left it there I know
but my night cream is just another Nivea
night cream
um for preventing wrinkles and stuff and
specifically for night time but I don't
use much however now here we go
um who wants some TMI
I used to have
really bad skin I mean I still kind of
do but in my school years and even after
school years I used to have really bad
skin and it bothered me so much and
um nothing no products would work so
before the stream we talked a little bit
about hormonal acting and I said let's
talk about this during stream because I
guess I guess that was probably hormonal
acne because I was able to fix it
eventually
guess how
[Music]
how how
he then guess you just had medication
yes medication but
um what I got was
so this is really girls talk okay I got
the pill for my skin
um
birth control
yeah so I I read and I heard from
friends in school and so on that
um a lot of people just take birth
control specifically for that there's
like different types of birth control
and when you want one you go to the
doctor and you say you want that one for
the purpose of your skin then it will
then they will like specifically give
you the the birth control that is
focused on fixing your skin it's more
about that than about other things so I
started taking that and oh my God it
changed my life I had the worst skin
forever I had so many pimples all the
time but then I started taking that and
it I I it changed my life it changed my
life
it changed my life for real so I guess
that's hormonal right
yeah yeah
it's interesting because I've heard of
people like they'll take the pill for
other stuff but then get really bad skin
like they'll have acne problems so it
depends which one yeah exactly can be
the other way around and if that happens
then you just go back to the doctor and
said well that up my skin can I
get a different one you just have to
change it you know uh well then you
girls told me before the stream you
started talking about something for
hormonal acne what was that
um yeah so I had pretty bad acne too and
I know that it runs in my family because
my mom she said like oh yeah when I was
your age I also suddenly developed like
really bad like hormonal acne and sure
enough I did too when I reached the age
she was talking about but
luckily my mom had like tried many
different treatments already and I
figured well she's my mom so whatever
worked for her probably will work for me
yeah probably similar skin type yeah I
tried a different medicine
um it's called spironolactone and
bronolactone what's that
tone and um only women can take it
because it's basically like blocks
testosterone production I'm sorry to the
boys because testosterone causes acne
and release
yeah women also have testosterone it's a
lesser amount yeah and that's why when
you get hormonal acne it's often like on
your chin or along your jaw because
that's where the testosterone is
concentrated that's why men also grow
beards ah in that area at least you can
hide it then I guess but maybe beards
also making a bit worse
yeah because of Shaving as well but I've
had most of my pimples always on my
forehead and on my on my cheeks and this
is really embarrassing because I I was
scared to wear a swimsuit
um but a little bit on my upper back a
little bit
But but so because I had this was not
the only reason this was one of the
reasons why I got myself bangs was
because of my pimples on my forehead
yeah
the one that said this I don't want
to show my forehead also because it was
too big and everyone made fun of my big
forehead so I one day after coming home
crying I went to the bathroom and I took
some scissors and I cut myself my own
bangs and they were horrible but
eventually I figured out how to style
them nicely and since then I have never
shown my forehead again basically
[Music]
mention a different one too you girls
so not acetone
Accutane stuff it was um it's a more
powerful acne medication do you take
that with me
um I took it before when I was younger
because everyone or most people in my
family took it at one point I had the
least severe issue but I just wanted
I wanted to get rid of it and like
because I had it I also had like upper
back oh that was pretty I didn't like
that so
[Music]
I'm so handfuls because normally you
know we don't talk about problems like
that but it's just a realistic problem
that everybody has and there's no need
to like hide it or so feel embarrassed
about it right yeah everybody has
pimples yeah Accutane Accutane really
worked but oh my gosh does it dry out
your skin but that doesn't know guys can
use too for example yes yeah yeah there
you go guys it can have really bad side
effects though I was too scared to take
it my dermatologist also said that was
an option for me but I was too scared
because of the the side effects but
again you don't have to take it for very
long like you could even just take it
sometimes for like six months and then
you could never have acne again really
it's like that power for me it cleared
away like most of my acne for years yeah
but I've been having the same the same
thing if Anna mentioned later on but
it's not too bad like I wouldn't I don't
think I would take a medication for it
again I think you I just um good skin
care and maybe I don't know I'm gonna
figure it out but not it's not too bad
as bad enough well actually I have I
might need to go need to go to the
dermatologist and ask for something like
that because actually after years of
taking the birth control I recently ran
out of and I was too lazy to go to the
doctor to get more so I stopped taking
it and now my skin is starting to get
I don't need her anymore please
leave me alone my mom's getting mad it's
like everyone's always like oh my God
only teenagers
such a struggle man yeah I know I'm a
teenager again basically no it's not bad
it's not as bad as when I was a teenager
but
oh well so I might have to find or go
back to the doctor and get the birth
control again but the thing is like I'm
actually kind of happy like not taking
it because it reduces the things I have
to take
oh yeah I stopped taking like the one I
was taking for my skin just because
it was I don't know it was annoying and
I feel like it isn't that much but maybe
it did
well if you think about it I guess the
it's probably healthier for me right to
not take it too long because doesn't it
have like effects on other things in my
body too
I think it's a pen wasn't there
something about burp control being like
I don't know what was that I keep have
you ever unfolded the paper of all the
side effects
when I was like pretty young I was also
put on it because of my body I have
really bad pain yeah
it helps yeah
TMI again but I've also noticed that
it's more painful now to um you know the
monthly thing you know yes yeah yeah
stay home from school because the pain
was so bad like yeah I have to like yeah
and I have a high pain tolerance too but
it is really bad me too helps after my
second Hospital trip because I was in so
much pain yeah that was basically I was
told like this it'll help and it did
help it made a huge difference but then
at one point I like I didn't like it
because I didn't I didn't like taking it
every day because I forget and stuff
yeah and then and then I get like it was
a few years later I had the worst pain I
had to go to the hospital again because
I hadn't been taking it but yeah okay
that's like next level though oh my God
no I couldn't do anything I was like
screaming and pain it was so bad
but oh first I remember the last time it
happened I was like in a group with
people like I was like at school right
and I like started noticing it I was
like tearing up and I was I was laughing
like it's so funny that like that this
pain is exists in like an hour later I
was in so much pain that I had to go
but no and it's okay I haven't had that
since it's been I haven't had that since
and the one thing we can say that at
least
um
this helps us with is uh or used to help
us with in school at least we could
always use the excuse you know to not go
to a sports class or to swimming every
time they were swimming because I'm I'm
a really really bad swimmer and I could
never hold uh catch up with like the
others in my class I was like like a
little bird drowning in the water all
the time so eventually I felt too much
pressure going to swimming class because
every time in summer they would let make
us go swim instead of normal you know
indoor so so I always said oh oopsie
totally do I got my thing so
that's how I got out of swim parties I
didn't want to go to
I just said that's something yeah we can
use them for something good Yes actually
if you have a male teacher if you're
just not if you don't want to do
anything you can just say sorry I'm
having girl problems today you can't say
anything about it you can't die hello
you don't even have to specify what kind
of girl problem you're having yeah
maybe we just lost like we were we had a
crush on someone and that person started
dating someone else so maybe something
like that you know many girls problems
there are in school yeah I watched a
notebook and I specified I'm emotional I
need two days off of homework please
why
is that
I watched the notebook or another
romantic movie
elements when you even made that movie
sad sorry that doesn't matter okay okay
I don't know what you're talking about
oh you don't know the notebook that's
like the uh I that's like
um do you know what it is
yeah I haven't seen it it's like the
romance movie it's the romance movie of
the 2000s I think but I don't even
remember what it was about or what
happened so that's why I was wondering
what made it sad interesting I don't
think they're like crying in the rain
like holding each other's faces
the movie poster isn't it yeah yeah I
think so why are they doing that I know
it's a drama I have to watch it with my
members then
I'm sorry Kiara's memory
and Gosling
yeah
oh what's her name oh I forgot the
actress's name but she's also another
stuff because she's an actress oh
hey one more
um skin care tip uh when you have a
pimple that you need to get rid of as
soon as fast as possible there's one
thing that I found worked for me back in
the day you know those like
um round see-through patches yeah yeah
hmm those really work for me
I don't use them anymore but they used
to always work really well
I was using them but I noticed that I'd
start to get another pimple like around
where it covered so even though it would
help the one that I had yeah it would
adhesive was irritating your skin or
something yeah yeah I don't use them now
but it did make a difference for the one
that I already was there
I guess you just gotta put those on your
whole face
I feel like it helps at least like to
stop picking at it you know that's true
to the sticker on you won't pick at it
and you can wrap makeup on top of it but
I felt like it still stood out very much
yeah then it's like you have a circle on
your face yeah
it's almost better to not put makeup on
top of it than it stands out less
somehow yeah yeah my opinion no oh wow
oh wow okay
nothing let's talk about makeup
because you do have pimples you can
always just put makeup
yeah
and it's okay to use like concealer or
whatever if you have like issues like
that when you want to hide it you don't
feel comfortable yeah I mean if you do
it well
um I think it doesn't really necessarily
stand out at all so um
I felt bad for guys because I think they
should I think I think it were concealer
to hide actions yeah right we like dark
circles you know it's never advertised
for them it really seems like an option
but I think it should be
this time
um
okay
again
these are things I found in actually
just a singular video I believe and to
copy an exact makeup look make it really
easy to do yourself there huh I do make
it very easy for myself but the first
one is foundation and it's a light tint
or whatever and I like it because uh
well if my Skin's not too bad it works
pretty well because it will not cover
pimples or acne is not strong enough but
it kind of has this like uh what's the
word
um
like gooey gooey yeah yeah which I like
like it makes your skin glow and stuff
um oh I forgot to put my concealer I
have Nars concealer okay so now it's
that is the only brand I would recognize
out of all these oh yeah I don't know
what any of these are again
from a video but I do have Nars
concealer which is like probably
the most expensive thing I have
um but it works really well do you agree
do you guys put your concealer on first
before the foundation or after
Foundation
I start I used to do it after but I've
started doing it before now and if I if
I use that Foundation like that specific
one
I do after because how am I supposed to
know what I need to conceal exactly
before I put it in both ways I think
both ways can work but I'm also an after
type of person yeah actually well you
see I have the other the cushion
Foundation there too I don't use that as
much anymore the Michelle button yeah
that one has insane coverage so I put
that one on first and then after if I
need to put concealer I'll put on
concealer
that one's crazy with the coverage but
hot stuff oh that's perfume I got that
in Japan like years ago and I still have
it well it lasted a long time
that's not really makeup but I guess
we'll we'll keep it there as interesting
too and now if you want to smash
don't smell like lemonade you're not
sure
your acrylic
if you ordered my birthday merch you
want your let's see just now like more
and this might be really up but
uh for someone who has maybe a
girlfriend you know and you want to give
her a present yeah
oh no no no no no you looked like her
sense
but you could also recommend this to her
it smells pretty nice
I think we may recommend it
might be like maybe you can just I mean
I guess basically you know if you don't
know what to give to your girlfriend uh
because you don't know any of these
products and you're looking for you know
on a recommended perfume that someone
you know has good taste
and Bae and I were with TOA and she
showed us her perfume that she liked
yeah and she handed one that was citrusy
and I was like oh I like how this one
smells but I kept it to myself and she
said this is gross
[Music]
yeah like when I think about this
perfume I'm thinking to myself
I told Osama would not like this it's
too fruity for her she would think it's
gross she would think I'm gross so I
don't know if I can recommend this
because I just have that in my mind oh I
but I definitely also like in terms of
perfume I don't wear that often but when
I do I go for like like flowering like
sweet scents rather than like adult ones
like my mom the stuff that she used I
would never use it like because when I
have that on myself I tried it before
when I was you know I like a teenager
like 13 14 and I go for my mom's closet
and I try her perfume I'm like it was
disgusting but I guess this makes me
feel like more adult more mature so I'm
gonna wear this even though I hated it
but um
[Music]
I prefer the the girly rather than woman
lighter ones ready for it yet I guess
[Music]
well we're not ready one day maybe we'll
wear those kind of perfumes but not yet
that day is not now maybe tell me about
your mascara
[Music]
topic with makeup when is finding a good
mascara is so hard I think yeah this
one's this one's okay but I actually I
have another thing that I didn't put in
there I got this serum that makes your
eyelashes grow more but I haven't been
using it regularly so it's not really
working but I was using it before and it
ended up making eyelashes grow where
they shouldn't grow or really
inconvenient spots so I had to Puff them
out
if you like or it have like one
abnormally long eyelash like trimmed it
because it looks so weird that's why
it's scary you know like the the inner
part of your eye there's one that was
just too far down there and it was just
a singular one so I had to pluck it out
but oh my God but it does work also
people use it on their eyebrows yeah
thicker eyebrows yeah I don't do that
but when I was used I was using it more
like
um like last summer and it definitely
made a difference but I haven't been
doing it as much anyways I think having
longer lashes also solves the issue of
finding the right mascara
yeah but this is okay can I say one
thing I don't know if you girls ever
tried that but I've noticed in times
when I've lived in Japan all the
Japanese girls that have been around
with uh they almost all of them are
doing like eyelash extensions
and I feel like the whole process of it
I don't really want to do it because it
feels like scary I don't want them to do
something so close to my eyes and like
that yeah you mean like the you mean the
ones that stand for days not false
lashes right
um
yeah yes I think the ones where they
just add more really close to your eyes
They Like Glue them on there forever
yeah yeah yeah yeah no that's been a big
thing here and I see it and it's
interesting like there's a girl I had in
a class at civilization duties and she
had them but she wouldn't always wear
makeup so it's like when she had a
makeup on like it went really well you
know with the with the makeup oh she
wasn't wearing makeup she just got these
huge long eyelashes okay I guess it's
like less natural type because the ones
I saw in Japan look more natural but
still like even without putting on
mascara their lashes look so beautiful
but like not too much like fake
beautiful but I see it takes a lot of
work from you I think but I wouldn't do
it I don't know I don't think I'd be
nervous about getting infected
um I just like I don't want to keep
adding like more and more things to do
you know like more and more things to
keep up with like oh now go get eyelash
extensions every month though now also
remember it's too much it's too much
that's true
I don't want to keep just upping the
standard on myself you know just get the
serum I use
eyelashes everywhere yeah
and so you like this one
all right give your volume or length for
ah
does it make it makes it darker
flying pig is a bit of length I think
and then that's up there that's your
eyeliner eyeliner yeah I like brown
eyeliner that's like a pen right not the
liquid one yeah that one's a pen I like
to smudge it a little bit
I have a liquid eyeliner girl what about
you fauna
yeah also liquid I used to be liquid you
used to buy liquid you wear like a glass
of water or so
I'm good I hope you're not liquid
anymore I can touch you now yeah being
solved pretty nice yeah not having
people go through but
but uh what was I gonna say oh yeah I
used to like doing winged eyeliner and
stuff like dark wings and stuff but I
have I'm very out of practice because I
don't wear makeup as much as I used to
everybody always tells me that I have
like eyelines eyeliner on fleek all the
time I've been told this for years and
it depends like uh maybe when I met you
girls um I might have done like a less
um like standout one but I've been
always told that my eyelines don't blink
I think some myth member has told me
that before too maybe gouda or so but
I'm really good because I've been doing
that for like years now and and oh my
God I must say I'm like really good at
it I don't even put that much effort
into it it just flows out of my hand out
of my ankle of my hands what do you call
the ankle feeling your wrist
hey cool your hand that's a good phrase
his makeup one day you know I wish
sometimes for these kind of ideas I wish
you really were not like so virtual
because I wish we could like really do
our makeup you know yeah
next time but I know you gotta and fauna
your eyeliner is yes on fleek you know
who else's eyeliner is honestly cool
crony is crony's really good at eyeliner
yeah
[Music]
I'll have very nice like I don't know
it's perfect it was terrible like makeup
on fleek or her eyeliner just the
eyeliner she's no she's good at makeup
she's really stylish she is stylish yeah
it's kind of the like intimidating kind
of style stylish where it's kind of
minimal you know
it's minimal but you can tell that she
like it's very thoughtful I like the
brands it's like I'm so curious I need
to check her out I need to bring her to
the girls tongue
[Music]
because I feel like whenever I put on
blush it always like
um Turned out spotty on my face just let
me tell my faces so I just don't use it
anymore I don't use it either I feel
like actually like I like it on like
other girls when they uses them I was
like oh that's cute they're gonna kill
blush but on myself I feel like I I try
to
um not overload my face now I guess with
your stuff I just do a little bit but it
also depends what I use if I use that if
I use them
foundate the lighter Foundation I
probably won't use it but if I use the
one that has more coverage I probably
will do a little bit
yeah but the one with more coverage
makes me break out more even when I am
on my face before I do makeup it's like
penetrates it I think as long as you
remove it properly it should be fine not
for me for me it well it causes a very
specific type of acne that I never get
otherwise and it's on my cheeks and it's
it's like my skin is still smooth it
just gets a red dots maybe it gets
irritated well yeah I mean yeah anyways
[Music]
it was cute I like the colors
yeah they're natural I like the middle
one
yeah I use the middle one on the outer
side oh my eyeball oh yeah or sometimes
I even take it so doing eyeliner I take
the darkest eyeshadow and just do
eyeliner with that I like that
yeah nice my current makeup
I don't know much about makeup it'll
probably stay like this for a while
until I see another video
thing on your lips
I do I do I didn't I forgot I forgot
about I need to do lip tint
lip oh I just heard Lipton the iced tea
lifted
yeah
I specific uh brand that you use for
that
no it probably won't be
I love Lipton iced tea ma'am it's called
benefit oh Ben a tint and Nintendo it is
the brand right yeah benefits the brand
and benefit is the product
yeah yes yes for people who don't know
it's kind of like a liquid uh that's not
a lipstick it's like you put some red
liquid on your lips and it's just
supposed to create some kind of grad
graduate gradient right yeah yeah a
gradient yeah but for me
um
sometimes I just don't use it I
sometimes have a hard time using lip
products because my lips get really dry
I have a really bad uh Habit of biting
my lips
okay I don't bite but I like rip off the
skin of my lips oh yeah I do I do really
[Music]
sometimes but it's really dry but it's
like a like a cycle That Never Ends like
I ripped in a tear and then it grows
back but weirdly and then I rip again
we'll just put on ChapStick because I'm
like oh but you know when I put on lip
balm that's supposed to help with that
it makes it worse lip balm makes it
worse for me really yeah I try to
remember to put Vaseline on at night
I still bite I still rip rip and tear I
think
so if you bite then your lips already
have probably a red color and you don't
need the lip tint
enough
but even but even if you don't like make
it go so far that it bleeds
um I think I saw girls do that before
they would like kind of bite into the
lips to give it a red look but that's
really just that momentarily isn't it
yeah well for me if I if I put lip tint
on and I have like you know a rip it's
dark it makes the rip a lot darker so it
sticks out more yeah yeah I know what
you're talking about yeah okay okay see
I I knew this was already gonna these
pictures were gonna take us so much time
that we don't have time for all the
other topics so let's move on next one
let's look at Thanos makeup
that oh that lipstick looks nice
so cute
I don't really actively watch those like
makeup YouTubers but when sometimes when
I watch them they always have like these
two faced products and so on and some
other products that I see here like
colourpop and I'm almost like I can't
get my hands on those but I always
wonder about them so can you bring me
some girls next time we meet bring me
some of this good stuff I haven't I Love
Too Faced they have so much cute stuff
okay let's start from the left here
okay that's a tinted moisturizer some
kind of like a foundation or a BB cream
yeah so it's a little bit lighter than
like full coverage Foundation
I wish I could just go with BB cream
just call it a day I wish I could
yeah I did that and then I have some
backup from concealer there
Foundation
[Music]
yeah it's a I mean it's honest similar
it is a concealer but it's very liquidy
I like it it doesn't make my skin like
crease you know
nice you have to try it one day
mm-hmm what's this one the powder
setting powder yeah what's what brand
uh Kat Von D
oh and oh
I've heard of that the setting powder
actually do stuff I have setting powder
but I never use it yes but my skin is
always like really wet after I put on
the Tinted Moisturizer in the concealer
so if I don't set it it will just like
wipe right off wait a minute you can use
powder I have it but I didn't know if it
made a difference
don't you feel like your makeup like
gets like messed up all the time all the
time touch it then it goes on your
fingers and so on don't just stop I
don't use makeup very much but I think
well I mean if I wear makeup when do I
wear makeup
but I try it dries eventually right
you probably just like got wiped off
also I feel like if you put on the the
powder it also like kind of gives
everything a more smooth look like it
brings the concealer and the foundation
together and I like I like The Dewy look
of my foundation so maybe so I haven't
used it with that but also I don't know
I just didn't know what it did
I didn't see a difference I guess it's
more of what
um wait when I met you you were not
using a powder now
I didn't bring it with me
I wish I didn't have to use powder but I
feel like it would go everywhere my
makeup would go everywhere and yeah
wipe right off yeah to be fair I mean
when I take my mask off I noticed makeup
and stuff isn't it normal okay well on
the mask I still can't make up even even
with powder that's like inevitable but
especially if you don't use powder oh my
God it must have been like full of
makeup oh no it wasn't though it was a
normal don't look around my nose you
know yeah the nose especially yeah
wait that's like the most interesting
thing to me that you don't use it oh
well let's go on let's go on
um that's an eyeliner liquid eyeliner
from Urban Decay oh everybody another
brand I've heard of all these like
American brands that I can't get my
hands on and all the influencers use
this stuff so much fun like just
shopping for makeup for you
I'll bring you some next time we meet
wait what's that what's that um that big
um store where they sell all the makeup
yeah
[Music]
oh my we went to Sephora it was me and
they fauna and Cali in Japan no no no no
no no no uh met up in the states and I
was everyone knew exactly what they were
doing I was so jealous like I wanted to
get stuff I didn't know what to get and
like like Cali is so efficient at
shopping fauna you were really you know
what you wanted they knew what she
wanted I was just there I was like oh my
gosh I hope by the time if we go I'll do
more research beforehand because it
ended up getting nothing because I
didn't know what to do oh I tried to
help more next time you no you are
you're on a mission don't worry don't
worry
I have to learn what is that is that a
eyebrow thingy this is actually a brown
eyeliner oh I you probably okay I know
you know this technique Kiara so it's
combined with there's also white
eyeliner next to it you see
yeah so I use the technique
I actually blur it out with a little bit
of Shadow so it's not super defined if I
do the black eyeliner on top like cat
eye emo God
the white eyeline eyeliner for the
waterline yeah
wait you put it on the waterline yeah
yeah it's a little bit under so you
don't mean the wet part right
oh I used to do black eyeliner
yeah I could I never could
that's why you put that it's like that
it's kind of like a it's like a soft the
that pencil is really soft yeah oh yeah
not pen yeah the salt like crayon yeah
I draw under but I like I do the trick
where I extend my eyes exactly
you would know you mean like look at you
look at the like the screens and stay
still uh you mean like like around
around here right
yeah yeah okay I got the corner you like
extended a little bit so it makes your
eye look bigger like the anime
we may have a similar gold but different
techniques though we have different
techniques I know differently
and this what's this song this one um
what's it called this mascara that has a
yabe name but this is okay it's like
very popular here and I see it what is
it what kind of name it's a yeah
s-e-x yeah
but what's the full name of this brand
better than sex
when you said you don't know a good
mascara I feel like this one is really
really good I've used it for years
I'll bring it to you it's a synonym for
gender
a synonym for oh yes
it's an okay word to say but I also is
that what they is that what they mean in
the name of this mascara I don't know
probably not but
this ain't nothing very you could say
but I also never say it on stream
because you know better than either of
the two main categories into which
humans and most other living things are
divided on the base of what their
reproductive functions
is the name that's the name you just got
that out of your brain data bank right I
got it out of Google
[Music]
no
the plagiarism
okay I'm so stupid it's like you're
sponsored oh my God I had a long Too
Faced I can't this is that looks pretty
that one I actually bought it at the off
collab we were talking about oh it's
like a clumping lip gloss I don't always
use it
the tingling one
yeah yeah oh god oh it doesn't hurt that
bad I mean it doesn't hurt at all but I
think
it doesn't yeah
damn everybody at least you know you
guys remember when when that thing was
um trending where you put like a sucking
cup or so on your lips yeah
the things that girls come up with
sometime I swear oh man that's gross
they were moving to be all like
saliva like Brews
there'd be like a yeah trailer it's just
too much too much much you know too much
is that you have a bronzer or a
highlighter uh this is glitter ah it's
very pretty glitter I like to put lots
of glitter on uh-huh where on around
your eyes or where
um yeah I put it like under my eye like
in the corner in the corner and then
also on top of my lid okay okay when you
don't use highlighter
no I don't I think I think highlight a
little bit you don't have to overdo it
but a little bit of highlight on your
cheekbones I think would like give your
face more less flatness with let make it
look like more how to say
um
oh that actually actually also would add
to like a glossy dewy look though a
highlighter
I like highlighters
uh any of your yeah what's the colors
inside that one like lots of pink tones
oh I should have showed you yeah yeah
it smells like brown Shades me with
makeup palettes like most of them always
have the same kind of colors so boring
yeah
need more colors more different colors
but I I like only do the same colors I
never experiment I do the same makeup
every day
[Music]
or gold I like like golden golden colors
too oh yeah oh this palette also smells
like peaches yeah nice
that's good stuff it's cute oh okay so
that was fauna's makeup let me show mine
next
and although yeah
yeah I took a real picture again oh yeah
you have a real picture okay
I have the same eyelash curler thingy I
mean they all like this movie
of the same color they're using black no
or silver
okay so after putting on that you know
that moisturizing shirt before I start
with my
um this Foundation I'm currently using
the Bobbi Brown Foundation but no
particular reason I just ran up out of
my Japanese one it's a good one though I
like this one and it does have SPF
something what's that 15
you know that's 15.
but better than nothing I guess and then
I put on a liquid concealer you see how
it's been used a lot um
yeah this is normal this is what's
supposed to look like
and I finished it off with some
sometimes
um I use either like uh like white
powder just because
the other powders I find are all too
dark but here I was lucky I found a
really light color for once I put that
on on top of it to make everything
become one then I go to this can make
it's a cheap Japanese brand but I just
always go for this one
um this is a little bit of a Shader I
put it around my nose a little bit and
uh under my chin under my jawline
but I I don't do it like around my
cheekbones like all the YouTube
yeah
it always gets it turns out trust the
process yeah for myself yeah it's very
sloppy but I think under the jawline is
really easy to put it there you can't
really mess it up
and then uh this what do you think this
is
I don't know
um
I don't know either it's
um eyebrow mascara oh in like a light
brown color yeah
you know and then here eyeliner eyeliner
is uh this one's Maybelline too this is
my this is liquid but it's like it comes
out of a like a pen shaped brush thingy
yeah it's really good I've had one very
similar from Maybelline before when I
used to do winged eyeliner it's really
good and then I use we're currently I
use a Bobby Brown mascara and oh this is
this is glitter for under the eyes some
this is really good glitter I got this
one in Korea oh good stuff good glitter
ah and then I don't always or I actually
rarely use this palette I just put it
there because
I used to have it's Urban Decay right
yeah I used to have uh an Urban Decay
eyeshadow palette not that one but wait
I want to look at the colors of that one
I'm gonna google it these are like more
golden ones yeah honey they're called
honey so what I do normally the only
thing I use eyeshadow for most of the
time is maybe just a really slight tiny
coat of
um like a light golden or brown or so on
top of my Lids but most of the time I
ignore that and when I do more like on
the lower lid right the red fauna yes I
do the thing to make my eyes pop yeah
the Japanese girls all do it so you know
I like it I've been doing that for years
and then uh I do that like oh do you
mean like that like the what's it called
it's like the egg Yo song yes yes yes
yeah I actually don't do that quite that
technique but I want to but I feel like
every time I try it it doesn't look
right
but I'm used to show me how to do it
properly hell yeah I've been doing it
for years and then I I add some
highlighter this is a highlighter
palette I put some on my cheekbones a
tiny bit on my chin a tiny bit on my
nose and then around my eyes you know to
make them even more pop and one of my
favorite lip products is this one uh I
think it's also from Maybelline they
have like so many colors and this is
kind of like a liquid one but it it
turns out matte and it stays
there this is the one thing even with my
up lips my dry ass lips this one
is just perfect for the whole day for 24
hours and it doesn't mess up when you
eat and so on like oh my god dude they
still sell these in all kinds of colors
so I really recommend this one this is
so good so good so good yeah I got a
matte yeah it's not that one but it
stays but it stays too well oh my God I
didn't when I got it I didn't think it'd
be so strong I guess so I was like this
might not be for me so try taking it off
I cannot get it off it thank goodness I
tried it on like after I had already
been out like I took a shower it was
still there I tried yeah rubbing it like
it took so long yeah this one's like
that kind of
ah I'm gonna I think I'm just I'm really
bad at applying lip stuff oh yeah I I
don't know it is difficult it can be
difficult yeah she always go with like a
gloss because you can't really mess that
up yeah that's why I do the tint because
yeah I can't get the shape
and everything I use 10 sometimes too I
just didn't have it here on the picture
I lost my tint somehow I think I left it
in Japan too
um oh but yeah this is nice you can just
smudge it and then there you go finish
sometimes it's fun to try to change the
shape of your lips a little bit with
lipstick though
oh yeah sometimes uh what do you call
that the the middle of your top lip what
do you call that yeah the Cupid's bow
yeah sometimes I fill it out
I do that too sometimes it's cute
sometimes
I've seen people do that but I assume it
would like
smell or you know fade really quickly no
not at work it doesn't a good one look I
feel like like one of those that I have
this this one does it really well I feel
like the one that I am
yeah make the lips more round at the top
too it can look pretty cute
you wouldn't understand chat you
you can also like on your lower lip
sometimes I like I don't feel the edge
out so much like I but I make the middle
part a little more full so it makes your
lips yeah like kind of smaller but more
full in the center
good stuff all right that's like our
daily go-to makeup I guess yeah you're
welcome to copy our products guys
kick coffee copy what I copied if you
want to
okay let's let's throw in one more topic
I think you can squeeze in one more
topic
um
you can choose between
uh the hair on our heads or the hair on
our bodies
which ones do you want to talk about
I'm a fun way with either haha I'm doing
that kind of thing I'm gonna do the girl
thing too I'm okay with either okay okay
well I think the chat wants to hear
about body hair
but like specifically what I'm trying to
point towards is hair removal me and Mum
I talked about it before but we need to
check up on on fauna what she's like
doing about that kind of stuff so uh
I'll I'll start I'll say
um that I had like kind of like
issues with how how thick uh some not
all of my but some of my body hairs
where it was a TMI team my team I
um but like even for example
this is really embarrassing but we'll
all talk about it okay you guys better
talk about it too
let's just say like uh uh our arm
armpits for example you know when I was
ashamed when I was younger it would
still shine through okay I think a lot
of people can maybe relate to that mine
too okay yeah okay
yeah even though you just shaved it you
can see yeah yeah because the hair grows
grows from below your skin so if your
skin is like light and your hair is
darker you can see the hair you mean the
dots yeah but I don't understand when I
was younger because like I feel like my
my school friends they didn't have this
issue
I feel like they all had like beautiful
armpits so I tried like so many things
and at some point you know I was young
okay I was a little young struggling
teenager one thing I would do is I would
go so far as to put makeup on my armpits
oh no in summer like when when or when
we would like uh in in sports class or
wherever whenever it would feel like my
armpits would be looked at too much I
put put some foundation and some powder
on my armpits right I was I was that
frustrated and desperate about it
wow so uh eventually I thought this
can't keep on going like this so I
looked at other Solutions
um I tried one time I tried this like
hair removal cream that you put on your
like legs for example you wait a bit and
then supposed to fall out
and you know I guess it worked a little
bit but it didn't really work that well
so I gave up on that next thing I tried
is those
um is it also called an epilator in
English
oh yeah oh I've never used those I've
heard of it it's like a messy hair out
that goes with electric and goes and
then rips yeah it rips your hair out
it's like it rolls over your skin you
like move it over your legs for example
and then it rips it out and it hurts
[Music]
so much
so desperate so I was like well what
else can I do because this one I guess
at least kind of
helps but it hurted so much that I could
not use it anywhere besides my my shins
um like even on the sides of my legs it
would hurt so way too much only on my
shins I could really use it and on my
knees was not possible on the armpits so
after a while I was like well this
doesn't really help me either so what I
did next this solved my problems but
also was expensive and painful
I
went to a two year long procedure not
laser hair removal I did something
that's like one level above that somehow
a lot of people don't know about it
seems It's like removal with
light and heat I guess
um two years sorry yeah because like I
could
um there was like a cycle of hair growth
right there there is a cycle of hair
growth so you go once and then you can't
just go the next day to do more because
they take some time until the next one
show up but you go once and gets rid of
rid of some of them forever forever
though and unlike laser which comes back
after a few months I think and then I
think laser is also supposed to be
forever no no there's two different
types there's two different types it's
the ones that where it stays away for a
long time but then there's the one
that's more expensive that is gone
forever and I did that one but it hurts
so much and it it takes a long time it
took me like two years because I had to
keep on coming like once per month I
think for a long time and I did it in a
lot of areas and well now I must say
uh my armpit problem is gone and I am
more or less happy
yeah I really want to have that done I
don't shave uh anymore by the way
that's how how you know how good that
was yeah I've been I think I'm I'm gonna
do that oh I wanna do that I want to go
together fauna sure so it hurts so much
though girls like especially although
like I would cry at the sessions and the
lady would tell me that it's like
um she has not seen anyone who has
suffered as much as me with this
apparently I suffered extra much and the
lighter your skin is and the darker and
thicker your hair is the more it will
hurt
oh
so good luck with that
my I'm pretty light like
we're all pretty pretty like just look
at our color if you take a screenshot
put it into Photoshop and you color pick
our skin because it's almost like pure
white yeah
it works better too the more contrast
you have though between your skin and
your hair color that's your laser can
see it that's true yeah but it will hurt
more too and has any one of you tried
waxing before because I haven't been
there yet I've only I've had my eyebrows
waxed once that was awesome
what I did just once though because my
friend my best friend always got her
eyebrows waxed and I was like I've never
done that I feel like I should do that
why but not not all of them off oh not
like the whole eyebrows
okay I bought the whole span yeah just
like to shape them
okay it's like a small area yeah okay
it wasn't bad but I was just kind of
like I mean it's easy enough to just
like pluck it or use I have like one of
those little electric thing used
[Music]
I didn't think it was necessary I
started getting my eyebrows threaded
because they told me about it oh that's
so interesting tell me about it yeah
it's good it's nice I mean I mean it
doesn't hurt that much it's like
plucking your eyebrows but just a few at
once and a super fast or at least the
lady who did mine it takes like five
minutes how much does it cost and how
often do we have to do it
um I've only done it a few times and I
did wait a little bit I think you go
maybe once a month
[Music]
explain threading for the people
oh it's hard to explain I still don't
fully get it but let me Google it guys
you take a string yeah and it wraps or
like the you wrap your eyebrow hairs
around the string and pluck just
multiple ones at a time it looks really
cool like the technique it does look
cool yeah yeah damn damn but is it yeah
expensive
nope oh
like like
fifteen dollars oh it's for five minutes
but
these kind of things same with like for
example cutting my bangs things that I
can do myself I don't feel like paying
others for so I always put my bags when
I go to a hair salon and they ask me do
I need to like do you want me to cut
your bags I'm like no thanks I'll do it
myself I don't want you to actually like
20 bucks extra for that that could do
that alone
yeah I'm like too lazy to go out of my
way to go do that kind of stuff if I can
just do it myself you know for that
thread anything like me I don't know I
could pluck my own eyebrows it's just
that I get um
I always have trouble with shaping them
because I don't really know what I want
so the lady who does mine she's just
like yeah okay I'll figure it out and
I've been happy every time she does it
it's fast and she shaves them way better
than I can shape them so also it's more
it's more like ten dollars but then you
give a tip you know oh you know I I'm
I'm proud of how I do my eyeliner but
the one thing I to this day cannot
Master is my eyebrows but you know what
I'm like I don't even care because yeah
I had with my bangs anyway I got things
I didn't put makeup on my forehead
[Music]
sometimes you know uh when I show
someone like I I put up my my bangs and
then surprise I'm not wearing makeup on
my forehead so my forehead is like a
little bit more red than the rest of my
face
oh yeah
same thing I'm saving materials you know
lately if I go out I clip my bangs
because they're very in my look at me
very long they're very long we all have
long right
but cut cut
no okay back to the hair removal that's
what we're gonna wanna hear oh tell me
about you oh yeah those girls
so I struggle so much man
yeah I also have the same struggles
actually I have a really embarrassing
story I can share it it's the girls
talk this one in middle school you know
you're in middle school you're going
through puberty everything is hard life
is hard I had
didn't use to grow hair on your body in
puberty yes I had grown some hair on my
arms
to the story I'm gonna so relate sister
let's go yes yes you know what happens
you have hair on your arms and then
um I was in Middle School and I I never
thought about the hair on my arms really
I didn't give it a second thought but I
was in school I was in class I was
wearing short sleeves and this guy in my
class looks at me looks at my arm here
and says dang fauna you the man
they are so mortified so embarrassed but
actually there was such a nice person
there who came to my defense and was
like that's messed up don't say that and
I would kill a person to that person for
defending me otherwise I don't know I
might have been crushed for the rest of
my life but I did after that never wear
short sleeves again until I learned
and I don't like to shave my arms
because I don't know that just feels
weird to me instead I use like
um it's kind of like a sandpaper but
just really soft sandpaper and I just
like use it and buff the hair away and
it gets rid of it
I could wear shorts again
happy that you shared this story because
I have a very similar one
um so this is actually one of the
reasons I guess why I started like
caring so much of a body hair but
um I actually I didn't get it
permanently removed on my arms because
nowadays it's not so bad and uh I
started shaving it too the reason is
because
um this really really really
traumatized me too but uh I also got I
guess I I had some pretty strong dark
arm hair on my arms like I say pretty
strong but I feel like that's more like
in comparison to like some I feel like
in Japan I barely see people with arm
hair you know they just don't grow as
much there and so once upon a time when
I was a young young teenager
um then some many many Japanese people
told me they looked at my arm and they
were like ew it's like like a monkey or
so
[Music]
and that like I never thought about it
till then and then I was like so
embarrassed and I felt so ugly because
of that so I immediately started
um shaving my arm hair but like the
thing is like I was in school at that
time and nobody the other girls in my
school they didn't care Oh nobody there
at all the boys leave her nobody cared
about like body hair back then I think
um I was the only one who started
shaving it uh just because I I started
caring so much about it I felt so blah
um I did that for a couple years I
stopped doing it because I feel like
eventually I think really my arm hair
started thinning out
which is actually kind of a miracle but
um it doesn't bother me anymore and I
think I also just have more confidence I
give less less shits about it yeah I
also also don't like care that much
anymore it's like and like I don't think
most people care like who cares if you
have hair on your arms who cares like
who cares
if your armpits double is visible it's
like who's even really looking that
close no thank you thank you and it's
like you know if someone did care you
wouldn't want to be friends with that
person you know someone who's like
judging other people saying mean things
to people because the things that are
out of their control you wouldn't want
to be that person that that's the person
who needs to hellions themselves change
themselves exactly oh man yeah when
you're young though you don't really
realize that yeah yeah that's harder
when you're young but now it's hard yeah
someone said something to you about your
looks when you're that young and you
feel like you're you that's the first
time you realize like oh wait so that
part about me was bad that was yeah I
didn't know I guess it is ugly and then
you start caring so much about it
so that's actually also one thing I had
with my forehead like everybody this was
like in in
elements it started in elementary school
I was being born for my forehead and
they said
um you you're like you you're bald
already haha and I'm like
um
that's so nitpicky did they think they
were like jealous of something else so
they had to find some weird thing too no
people just suck but it gave me big big
complexes so I I came home crying every
day and then eventually I cut my bags is
there something mermaid that like you
like something similar where someone
told something to you and you then then
you got really worried about it
ah not really look wise
because if we're talking about Middle
School I didn't really talk to anybody
so and people didn't really talk to me
but I did well I didn't realize it was
such an issue until I had a friend who I
did talk to say tell me yeah people
don't think you exist and people think
like you don't like you don't talk it
made me realize you're right I don't
talk I'm very quiet and it made me more
quiet and more stuff that person say
that to you and trying to help you or
trying to do something no it was more of
a um I think it was a I think a little
embarrassed of being friends with
someone who was looked at that way so
they wanted to encourage me to stop
being weird basically
but
can't help no no it didn't help they
didn't really tell me what I could do so
I mean how would they know they're also
a kid but um
yeah that made me yeah made it worse
because I haven't got even more it
smells like wait but if I talk then what
I say is really important isn't it like
I don't know it was a bit I was like
this would be the first impression then
for people right if they don't think I
exist but then I didn't say anything
anyway but I'm trying to think of like
physical stuff I always wore
like I never wore short sleeve stuff
really I like one baggy sweatpants and
well not sure anything just because you
liked it oh yeah just because it feels
comfortable yeah so maybe yeah I did
wear shorts and stuff but I have lighter
body hair so I don't think lucky it was
really noticed but I did get it like I
did start shaving because you know I
knew people were judges I knew the other
kids were judging each other at a
certain age it starts like just being
expected to from you as a girl that you
shave every single piece of body hair
and yeah then you just feel like you
have to go with it yeah otherwise
like no I got too intense because like I
don't know I'd like shave where I really
didn't need to especially if I never
wore short sleeves like I would face my
arms even though I was wearing long
sleeves and yeah yeah but I remember
right when I first realized
like
like similar to you you saw like other
girls when you looked at their armpits I
looked at the other girls aren't 52 so I
was in a changing room or something and
that's when I first realized like I
didn't even notice before that I was
like you know starting to have armpit
hair
and I looked at my friend and she didn't
have any and I was like I freaked out in
that moment like it hit my armpits and
then I went home and told my mom was
like what is this
right it looks like those moments where
you realize that like everyone else is
doing something that you haven't been
doing yeah
ahead of you and you have to catch up
yeah I don't even I guess she already
started me did she search I don't know
if she started shaving or no if I was I
was it was like at the age where you
know that stuff is right about to start
um
well I think nothing's nothing was wrong
with any of us but am I right in the
assumption that we were all kind of like
the shy maybe outside their kind of girl
in school
it sounds like it okay
yeah I feel like probably
out of the all of the whole life and
girls I feel like
99 of us or 90 of us maybe that type I
feel like we we all
um end up here yeah
that makes me even more sad that there
were people in your schools that would
say those things to you if you were
already you know quiet and kept to
yourself like
I don't know I've had people be mean to
them I think me and fine
mommy from what you said it feels like
the reason why you were an outsider or
so was more of you like because of your
shy personality right I think me and
fauna it might be because we were sweeps
dressing up I wasn't
sure
[Music]
Middle School yeah oh did I never tell
you my anime shame as a middle schooler
what animation game yeah I I just picked
up pretty quickly like what was cool and
what wasn't cool so my interests were
definitely not cool so that's also part
I think of why I was quiet in general
but I was ashamed because I liked anime
and in my
school if you liked anime you were a
complete weirdo like something was wrong
with you no you were uh you were like a
pervert if you liked the anime
I always kept it to myself and I always
had this like guilt when I'd watch anime
episodes on YouTube like part one High
School Host Club and I would just have
this awful feeling
because I enjoyed watching
it okay yes I also had that it was when
I went to high school though I think
it's because in Middle School my friends
also liked anime
um but as soon as they got into high
school like my friend suddenly stopped
being interested in anime and they they
liked the they stopped girls
yeah they stopped being interested in
anime instead they liked normal girl
stuff like I don't know what not I felt
a little bit like anime but I couldn't
like it anymore they didn't like anime
boys instead
I they just stopped they didn't care
anymore about anime
I couldn't like it either the opposite
for me because
um starting from uh High School I
started go I started going to like an
art school
so there I was overly more accepted by
people because there were a lot of like
people in the more creative side and who
liked drawing similar stuff that I did
because I was really into drawing I
would the whole time I would draw things
before high school too and they were all
like kiwawa can you drop me can you drop
me something can you drop me like an elf
girl or a song I'm like okay okay that
was like the artist everywhere and then
in art school people finally
um were like nicer to me and more
respectful of me that's also finally
where I felt like me wearing over knee
uh socks and shorts uh skirts and all
that like Japanese fashionless Lisa and
all that looking at fun
um like I didn't have to be so
embarrassed I mean I still definitely
stood out for it but I didn't feel like
so embarrassed about it anymore
I was awesome were we all Art Kids I
guess
in my well in my anti-weave phase I used
to love to draw in middle school and of
course I love to draw now but in high
school I I also thought the drawing was
weird so I like I stopped drawing like
completely because I wanted to fit in
oh I just one more thing too but I like
to draw like
Mickey moose style animals
this is even I guess more childish
yeah I like your drawing like yeah like
bamboo boom boom
I thought you were also like going in
the anime Direction like look do you
check this out well I stopped drawing
because Yeah by looking back my friend
group their their intentions were
whatever they were they told me to stop
because it was weird so I stopped and
then yeah similar I started drawing
again around what the hell oh and I got
into the anime like drawing anime and
stuff
[Music]
um
that's sad like that they make you stop
that's sad they shouldn't be able to
like control you like that I like Drew
but like I drew in private still but I
stopped showing her stopped drawing in
school I'm I'm surprised because even
before high school where I was getting
like more bullied and where I was
definitely The Outsider the only thing
what people would mind like schoolmates
would ever appreciate me for and ever
ask me if something for is about art
like sometimes they would come up to me
and be like hey can you draw me or can
you help me with my art uh project
whatever this and then and And when they
see me drawing something that's the only
time when they're like hey this is nice
when I go up to like in the break time
before the class starts I would like
Draw Something on the on the chalkboard
and that's yeah stuff like that that's
the only time where people would
appreciate appreciate me a little bit
and be like hey that's cool that that's
cool that you have that Talent
so weird looks like different worlds
different yeah different tolerance
levels I'm glad that we can all be more
confident now and especially yeah this
is live I think it makes me feel a lot
more confident yeah you know being here
like I feel like I can I can really be
myself and I can talk about anything and
I have a place
in Japanese yeah at least you realize oh
these things I was supposed to hide are
actually things people like
we're not Outsiders anymore yeah anyone
with anyone who's watching is younger
maybe you're also going through periods
of uncertainty about yourself your
identity
anything like that you can hang in there
and know that conference will hopefully
reach you and you don't have to be
ashamed for anything like that body hair
is natural and normal and you can be a
weave if there's nothing wrong with it
yeah I can't like I still have a
civilization a school setting sort of
thing that I go to and I can assure you
there I've never felt like anybody cares
like nobody people stop caring about how
you dress it's really just time junior
high school well yeah it was a little
right yeah
yeah once you get out of there people
stop caring and if you find people who
do care you just avoid those people
because they're exactly they don't need
to you can find people that
you don't have
other things to worry about it's hard
but you have to get over that that that
one hurdle of you know your teen years
unless you're like maybe lucky sometimes
maybe you're lucky like me I think like
an art school was better and maybe
nowadays compared to back when I was in
junior high school and all that I think
nowadays all these things are a bit more
um acceptable and also I guess if you go
to school where there's school uniforms
then certain things like your your style
your clothing choice will not matter
anymore and all that so that can be a
good thing but overall whatever people
are struggling with there's
um there may be a solution for it but
maybe you don't even need a solution for
it maybe you're just putting these ideas
ideas in your head by other people
criticizing and bullying you
um maybe you don't need to fix
everything that is supposedly wrong with
your body because people think you're
different and that sucks so don't try to
like forcefully fix everything there's
no need for it I accepted my arm hair
now I don't give a about it anymore
but it was definitely understandable to
like worry about these kind of things
for a certain amount of time you know
teen years or or those years where
that's inevitable you go through all
these all these struggles right yeah and
do be like that but so I think this is a
nice segue to the end it's great great
topic where we ended up at is except
it's okay to like have flaws and maybe
they're not even flaws it's just you
know in the end it's just what's what
society says we live in a society
exactly yeah beauty standards are always
changing nothing is definitely seeing
the beauty standards from even a hundred
years ago is stuff that people look down
on today even from the 90s things that
people look down on are now popular
oh and one thing that I was always made
fun of in uh elementary elementary and
Junior High School and so on uh being
too pale people always said I look sick
and I look like a ghost and so on but
then I go to Japan and everyone
appreciates it they're like oh you're so
wow your skin Oh my God it's amazing so
you know one thing that is maybe not
appreciated in one place is more
appreciate than enough in another place
so yeah your your beauty standard might
be elsewhere think about that it's a lot
easier to
to just be yourself than to try to
change to fit whatever Society is
telling you yeah you need to be yeah
grow you have to grow into yourself
right
get used to yourself and accept yourself
yeah so wonderful
we should do this again uh Girls Talk
there's many things to tangent about uh
in the future maybe also with other
members we can like switch we can cycle
we can cycle through because I want you
girls also to come again if you want to
learn a lot
I feel it yeah it's nice to like share
it's nice to share things that we think
are embarrassing and have other people
you know to share the feelings and
realize it's not so strange
hmm I felt very embarrassed about
certain things today like the armpits
sorry but you know
it's an it's an it's a safe place here
to open up
so let's hope it continues to be a safe
place thank you guys for listening to us
and yeah maybe you learned something
nice maybe you can even take some advice
in terms of skincare or whatever we're
happy to help maybe next time we can
have like a corner where we read some
questions or yeah yeah
yeah like oh there's a girl I like how
do I talk to her
sister would love to help you
I might give bad advice but
no who knows maybe maybe it's a girl or
so that's similar to Yuma and then only
you can answer that question or maybe
that the girl that they meet is you is
moving
I'm a human but no it's totally not
about movement but please tell me how to
impress movie how do you how
see I have to think about this well I
think about this don't ask me this time
you'll have time to think about
it okay thank you guys for watching
today uh channels uh of the girls are in
the description obviously maybe they are
are you guys streaming later
I have a membership stream oh okay I I
have no idea
I will I don't know maybe maybe not
maybe tomorrow I have to figure stuff
out I'll have a member stream tomorrow
and also I'll be at Elena's
classroom tomorrow on Dana's channel so
I'll see you guys there first okay
yeah thank you
thank you somehow awkward topics but you
know TMI is good information we like it
feels awesome yeah yeah I felt like we
bonded over having similar problems so
it feels great thank you soon girls
now get out of my room
okay
[Music]
from the poster in the Box
bye bye guys
[Music]
foreign
thank you