[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
do
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
so
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
so
[Applause]
[Music]
cake candy
sorry i'm drinking water wait let me get
my microphone closer sorry moving
oh i'm already feeling
too hot in here
welcome everybody
welcome to
another cooking stream and this one i
think this might be the first one that's
starting on time
uh today i have something special for
you
gingerbread house yeah that's that's a
special thing sorry if you expected
something
more special now but no
um
that is that is the special thing oh
sure
ah
oh god am i peeking let me turn this
down a little bit
am i peeking when i speak like this now
i shouldn't anymore now it should be
okay
uh
[Music]
i prepared this beforehand
um actually the the dough was made
uh no this is not the ikea kit this is
self-made that's why some colors are
different and um i'm not sure how the
conscious con the texture and everything
is because look at that i don't know if
that's um you see that
focus yeah is that normal like this one
is like very grainy
and then the second batch that i put in
um turned out not as grainy
maybe you can see that the difference
wait let me let me show you both
[Music]
sides let's see there's a huge
difference
and it's the same dough uh i don't quite
understand this one also turned out
darker but
it's not the same thickness either which
i also don't understand
that's good
not sure why but we're going to make it
work anyway
um
this is my first time building a
a gingerbread house
and we i already wanted to do this a
while ago
the dough settled yeah maybe it did i
don't know i had them both i had both
like i had two platters with the dough
on it already prepared and i was like
cooling them i was cooling maybe this is
the difference i was cooling one of them
in my fridge
this one
and i was the ones that actually all the
others on this plate also turned out
darker i mean look at look at that it's
like
[Music]
let's see the color difference
black star um
uh anyway uh what was i saying oh yeah i
was i was cooling one platter in the
in the fridge and the other one
on the balcony
for
actually
a long time
it might have been two days but that's
fine like i'm first of all it's still
it's still theoretically it's edible and
i tried
i'm sorry i tried here i tried
nibbling off this one
it's not
it's not necessarily like
disgusting
it's not disgusting at all it just
doesn't taste as sweet as i thought it
would but what what i did is
i don't know should i tell you all of
this now or later
i probably won't won't will be too
focused later so let me tell you now i
um
i i i looked up a recipe to make this
stupid dough after looking for an
already finished dough literally
everywhere like i looked in all the
supermarkets and online but online
couldn't find anything
and one guy the supermarket told me yeah
yeah we don't have that anymore in stock
because the stock was gone weeks ago
of gingerbread though apparently
apparently everyone wanted to make a
[\h__\h] gingerbread house i highly doubt
that but okay
[Music]
so eventually
um
i think it was like one day before the
last time i
planned this stream that was before
christmas um i was like for [\h__\h] sake
i i
i need more time then if i need to make
the dough myself i'm i don't know man i
need more time so i moved the stream to
after christmas and during christmas my
mom came to uh my home and she helped me
make the gingerbread dough although she
was also kind of like
i don't know if that's gonna be that
easy and i'm like mom for real like
hearing that from your mouth is
unexpected what's what is difficult
about gingerbread though and then she
was like
and i'm like
in the end it all turned out to be fun i
got a
gingerbread dough a gingerbread house
specifically for a house not for like
edible like cookie gingerbread uh
cookies you know but specifically for a
house because i thought there's a
difference there and indeed there is
like they're they're made to be more
sturdy i guess also
so that's maybe why it's not that
difficult
why it's not that tasty um
yeah so
yes we speak turkey sometimes
uh so she came over and we
after christmas on on the on the 25th
before my mom left and we made the dough
and then i cut out the pieces and then i
put it on the platter to cool it because
it said i think it said to at least cool
it for eight hours and i ended up
cooling it for two days because
i kind of forgot about it
i mean i didn't necessarily forget about
it but i was like i can do that tomorrow
it should be fine tomorrow it's cooling
anyway
um
but it's okay i mean i'm not planning on
eating this [\h__\h] anyway
and
so i have watched a certain forest fairy
building a gingerbread house and i've
seen her struggle endlessly so i was
like
no i'm not going there so
so
and i'm sorry you may call this cheating
but i don't give a [\h__\h] i'm not gonna
eat this so i will be using this
so what you can't stop me you can't stop
me
we're gonna use a hot glue gun um in the
background you see that package over
there that is 40 sticks of hot glue
actually 40 seeing it in the package is
way more than i thought it would be
[Laughter]
um i also bought many other things
one of the many other things that i
bought was this [\h__\h]
you see this you see this you see this
um it's a decor a cake decoration set
but i thought um i need this because
um you know what it comes with is all
these like the things that you put in
the sugar
the sugar coating because we're still
gonna use it we're just gonna put stop
laughing
i will use the hot glue
[Music]
strom
wait is my pc not my laptop not
connected so wait a second wait a second
wait it should be charging what the [\h__\h]
that's my store
[Music]
anymore shut up now battery optimization
is triggered which may take a few
minutes to begin charging the power
what do you want alienware shut up maybe
even that one should update
one drive shut up okay so
um where was that oh yeah um i will not
be eating it so
i will use the hot glue gun but we will
still
use all the you know the sugar coating
[\h__\h] because
uh we want it to look nice it just has
to look nice it doesn't have to taste
nice
so i also bought oh it's gonna be
all these like
sorry
all these uh little tips for
uh
where is that [\h__\h] um
where did i put them
oh no it's here it's here too
i mean you don't know what this is but
what do they call it what do i call it
see there's like
so many different tips
my shadow shut up
i don't know which one to use maybe 17
or
uh i mean we can use all of them
but i've never used like something like
this either oh how to use poppy that's a
good question how to use piping bag be
careful when cutting the piping bag cut
a small opening at the beginning and
adjust it to the best size
okay
you cut it
put the one of coupler
into the bag
does that sound like proper english to
you
put
no wait you you're reading something
else put the one coupler put the one off
coupler into the bag cut off the extra
part
here
and then put the stainless steel on
decorating
tips yeah okay
sure screw up another card
i will be doing a lot of screwing up
don't worry how to use tape use the tape
connected
connect the piping bag for what
what
use use the tape to connect the piping
bag
for easy yeah okay use the tape to
connect okay this one was an okay
sentence it's just me reading it weirdly
uh okay we'll get to that later but you
guys think i can do this i don't know
how to do this like i'm worried about
making a proper um sugar
sugar whatever schnitzel
sugar snow thingy whatever
um it's easy
yeah apparently i need like three three
or two egg whites and then
i just i just hit it good i i will use
my kitchenaid and we'll hit it good
until it's like fairly stiff i guess um
although we don't have to worry too much
about the consistency i guess because
we're not gonna use it to glue
anything
yeah the icing icing icing sugar and
water for glue what
no
egg whites right what the [\h__\h] egg
whites
and for glue don't worry we only need
this
yeah and then
and then for decoration is this all i
got uh i have
these thingies these are kind of long
long and thin
could be good
um
then we have smaller ones we have these
things
so also very colorful these are smaller
i was thinking about you know what what
what could what we need like small and
big things you know plastic reflection
there's nothing reflecting in that
plastic
yeah uh and then uh i already opened
this one yesterday night i couldn't hold
back anymore oh my god there's a cat
[Music]
[Laughter]
i think it was because she heard these
these sounds from the plastic she wanted
to see if there's a snack
baby
you didn't see her right that was
stronger
i mean girl you're always welcome but
right now i'm busy also she's kind of
zooming right now which is a prop
they're both zooming they're running for
the apartment right now
anyway so i opened this one already but
uh these are um well do you guys have
these overseas
there like all kinds of shapes there
they're interesting shapes
[Music]
don't no running right now there's a lot
of cables on the ground chunkers
[Music]
she's playing with my hand sorry
there she goes there she goes
oh my god oh
oh my god okay okay my cats will calm
down in about five minutes they're
having like a little bit of a moment
okay
chunk is already sitting down she's
already exhausted at this point this
movie is still running
um
[Laughter]
oh oh wonderful do you see that cat hair
you see that you see that oh yeah that's
totally um uh turquoise
as it should be
anyway
uh so i guess we'll just start first by
putting together
and then we'll worry about the
decorating afterwards we'll put this
faint out but i also got smarties of
course because smarties seem to be like
a base opponent
uh yeah
yeah thank you
this one will turn on i think
immediately after i i i i
attached it to the electricity to the
method no chunkers i did okay yeah stay
down there that's that's good i dare you
can i turn off the camera for one moment
[Music]
okay let me get those hot glue sticks
i wonder if this will be easy or
difficult
but i think we're already making it
easier by uh
by not like by using the hot glue
we're already winning can you feel let's
go
okay i don't think we need that many but
whatever
okay and then we stick it into the hot
glue gun yes is that a good yeah yeah i
bought the right size did that
what
did i yes yes oh god that was that was
close that was a close one okay
okay and then we attach it here chunkers
you might want to leave this area
[Music]
otherwise i'll have to put some hot glue
on you as well
[Music]
um i have a
tripod between my legs right now because
that is the only way to position this
[\h__\h]
this is the one problem that um i was
worried about when getting
a new tripod a different different
tripod
it's because you know the stupid stance
the legs they're gonna be in between my
legs
and that's
really not helpful also let me let me
see how how stable
this camera yeah it's pretty stable i'm
shaking it yeah actually this time i
didn't use tape at all to attach it to
this tripod um i used
what's the name i used uh
sorry i need to communicate i used
what's called uh
uh
[Music]
i didn't use hot glue
no
not a zip tie but like a like a you know
the round thing
[Music]
uh i used several
uh
rubber bands yeah rubber bands thank you
rubber bands and surprisingly
it's more stable than the [\h__\h] tape
i didn't use cream
okay
um
yeah rubber bands it's super stable i i
i bought a new tripod if you were out of
the loop i bought a new tripod oh wait
it's already getting hot is it
[Music]
i think it's getting there i don't have
to turn it on right it's already on
um
uh
you go away for now
space here
okay
uh what was i saying oh yeah i bought a
new tripod because after the last
cooking stream you guys were like oh my
god and i was like oh my god and then we
were like oh my god and then um
someone recommended me a new tripod and
i was like okay i'm just still getting
this one now even though it's not the
best solution but for now okay
and then before the stream i was trying
to put together the tripod but
i don't know if it's me or if they sent
me the wrong thing but it's not exactly
how it's supposed to be so but okay for
this stream it's okay because actually
you know i bought a tripod where you can
like um like you could like extend it
this way and then have the camera like
face down from here
um but thankfully for this stream i
don't need it we can have this angle
it's actually better so
my cat looks like she's dying on the
floor you're cute
i wish i could show you but she's you
know pretty famous and she prefers to
not show her internet
reads
her face on the internet too much i got
so many cat hairs on my on my hands now
dear lord
see normally my cats don't intrude when
i stream but yeah right now chunkers
wants to be close to me okay and we will
not
stop her from doing that
okay where where do we where do i even
start where do i even start okay this
camera let's go let's do this uh
oh my god my camera is also gonna like
my camera is not in front of me so just
i i will stop moving a lot probably
i'm sorry for that
um
wait so i think there is no base
i think there is no oh this side is
really soft it's not not very good but
okay
i think ow
and maybe you know this on twitter
maybe you noticed on twitter but i had a
little bit of an accident so we might
want to start with that um
[Music]
um
yeah so that happened um but
why not
when i picked it up
when it was still like right like it's
fresh out of the oven
um i realized oh it's not
as
as hard as i thought it was so
it it it gets stiffer when it cools down
you know
so we're gonna glue this together
see this would probably not work if uh
it was um
uh wait wait a second let me adjust this
a bit more this would probably not work
if it was uh
if it was the the
you know the other thing the other thing
the other uh icing or whatever blah blah
blah
okay let's try this
is it it should be hot by now come on
get out of there
come on
oh wait i think it wasn't pushed
properly inside yet and now it's now
it's getting hotter okay we have to wait
a little bit longer
oh yeah
it's plugged
it's blood it's blood it's it's um
getting
hot yeah yeah it's it's warm no problem
it's actual glue yes i will not be
eating this don't worry
i mean gingerbread houses usually even
if you make them edible people usually
don't eat them because they they're
supposed to just be decoration and then
when you have them standing there for a
while eventually it's just not
not good anymore i mean at least like
this part is not good maybe the little
little uh decorations you could eat
yeah
[Music]
they're supposed to be edible but who
actually eats them come on
come on don't worry stop this is my
choice okay this is my choice i'm a free
woman
i'm not gonna eat the glue no i'm not
gonna eat any of this
come on get out get out
so difficult
[Laughter]
i repeat myself but i took i made a
a dough that is good for building a
house
and not not very good
like i tasted it it's not even good like
i don't i don't even want to eat it even
if i cook mom
[Laughter]
did you hear that the chocolate what is
it
no she's so cute she's like right next
to me looking at me
she's like mom what are you doing
oh she's so cute and you're so cute
let me go with this [\h__\h]
i'm building a house for you chunkers
although it will be way too small for
you i can't get it out
[Music]
oh there it is
okay okay hold it i dare you i dare you
chunkers i dare you
okay
should be pretty good it should be
pretty good
matsunoda oh the camera is being
a good girl today isn't isn't it no
naughty camera right now
okay
[Music]
okay already stable
let's do the other side
[Music]
okay it was just it didn't come out
because it wasn't hot enough yet
but now it is
uh
uh it was like this
i think
oh
oops
but too high oh god oh god oh god
oh god the shape is not ideal
[Music]
yes it's cool shut up about it
i'm not gonna eat the glue
oh
i'm already exhausted
okay you cool down for now
um now um yeah usually there is no base
so we are going to do a how was it
how did it go
oh yeah yeah these are these are the
roofs i think
um
oh my god this is the roof too and then
this is the side
okay oh my god
oh my god how fun
so like this you know
wait no inside i think it was supposed
to be glued inside
probably
probably inside because it will look
like
i'm just kind of sad that that side is a
different color
but oh well
okay so with the glue this this will
make everything so much easier and at
the end of the stream you're gonna be
like oh she was so smart to use hot glue
the wall is upside down what do you mean
this one no it doesn't matter
i made it so that any side could be
usable
okay let's let's glue this on the inside
i guess
[Music]
let's go
many many glue
much a glue
yes yes
and then
like so
[Music]
nice
nice i'm the smartest person in the
world
hold it support it support it
wait maybe that oh god maybe the angle
oh it already stands it already stands
can't be winning now
meow
it's that easy
it's that easy are you seeing this
forest fairy
are you seeing this
although yeah i think it's a little bit
wrong angle but we can still fix it
the problem is the other wall
is
a quite a bit thicker do you see this
difference
is that sick
is that gonna be a problem
hmm
[Music]
okay let's do this side down what this
is like a speed run gingerbread house
any person
any percent speed
run oh god push it
[Music]
okay
holding
keep
holding on
[Music]
i can't hold anymore
oh are you good are you good i'm good
uh
okay
works
now look at my fixed house
[Music]
so easy
okay oh yeah perfect oh my god this is
the most stable gingerbread house i have
ever seen before
wow
[Music]
let me move this a little bit
wait a second
okay
[Music]
don't fight babies
so now we'll touch this
yeah yeah i know it should be fine but
you see that you see that part there we
just got to put a lot of glue there
and and there's a little bit of a
free space at the bottom too
yeah but it will be fine
yeah it will be fine
okay uh let me prepare this if when i
have to hold it yeah
whatever
uh let's go let's go
lots of cool that's cool lots of glue
we can still add even more glue
afterwards like kind of on the outside
to support it
okay
okay quick quick
uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yes yes
[Music]
everywhere let's go
yep this is how it is when you work with
uh hot glue
we're gonna clean it up later
oh
nice
nice it's so
like stabilized
wow and now we need to see if this works
yeah yes
this is really a speed run we're gonna
have a lot of time for decorating then
that's wonderful
should i glue it to this cutting board
it's not like i need it anymore
now we won't glue it to the cutting
board
okay now
now
wait i move the camera again
a bit more up
see that this by the way that is just uh
flower floor flower fluid flower fluid
flower
uh-huh wow that has quite the thick roof
oh my god
but the size is perfect
okay um
don't overlap too much i guess let me
see how it looks when they're both
together
um
[Music]
like like like so connor
other side other other side kind of fits
better okay
like like this i mean there's some weird
open parts but it will be covered up
later so i am not worried at all so we
need those two sides and then should i
glue the bottom like this side too
over here
it would probably help
should i
overlap one side
one side overlapping doesn't that kind
of look uh weird also because
nah that looks weird because they're the
same size and i would have had to make
one the bigger size
okay
let's do this i'll do the bottom part
too
[Music]
and
that does use a surprising amount of
glue
here
okay okay class to be fast
speed run
oh
[Music]
wow
wow wow
it's already working
[Music]
oh
burnt my finger
i burnt my finger
[Music]
it's okay i'm good
i'm good i'm good
not even the plastic protected me
of course not why would it
why would it should we add like a layer
of uh
hot glue in there if we can reach in
there just you know at least one side
would be better protected
oh yeah i can i can kind of reach
[Music]
no no i'm phoenix
i'm good
go there yes
go there
[Music]
i don't want to do it anymore it's too
heavy
i need to oil this hot glue gun
i can't do it with this hand i need my
left hand
[Music]
i need some water
noodle arms if anything has no fingers
then
that is cool yes it's cool so what
this is why you use icing but i think
everything would be falling apart a
million times i will not be
bullied
by icing like that
i will decide
whether or not my house sticks or not
if i have to force it then i will force
it
[Music]
the gingerbread is real the gingerbread
is real i made the dough with my mom
because i couldn't find any pre-made uh
dough
and only one day after i made the
gingerbread dough with my mom ina told
me that there also
is a gingerbread building house set at
ikea
uh i guess that has pre-made dough
um
is is that pre-made like i looked it up
and it looked like it could have the
pre-made dough already inside
uh but
i mean all the dough was sold out
everywhere else in all other
supermarkets so i'm not sure if ikea
would have had it either but maybe that
because i guess i can't usually have a
lot of stock of everything
and for christmas maybe they would have
more stock of the gingerbread house than
usual
yeah but i found out about it too late i
didn't realize ikea would have it so
it's too late
it's too late for that now let's put on
the second
the second uh roof
[Music]
we want a roof above our heads after all
wait which side was the one that i
wanted to go for
not that it really matters
something really matters but
oh oh that side is fine that side is
fine
i guess i'll use this one better
there will be
like a little bit of an
elevated
part anyway but this side is better
okay
glue let's go
[Music]
go
okay
okay okay
perfect perfect perfect
beautiful
hold it hold it hold it hold it
hold it
is this really good
jenna are you watching this can you put
up a pinned comment that says yes i am
using real glue no i am not planning on
eating it can you can you do that for me
[Music]
i don't have my hands right now my hands
are busy
the amount of questions i got
oh my gosh
i'm not planning on eating it
[Music]
is ramsay here today
he would understand
probably hopefully
maybe not
well you know what let's glue it
together here
[Music]
okay
and then we'll cover like all these
seams with the icing later and that's
when everybody will shut up about the
hot glue but
we might use the hot glue on the on the
decoration sweets decoration as well
i mean i got 40 sticks so i want to get
something out of my 40 hot glue sticks
right
uh
uh wait um genma might not be watching
i have to type it i think wait
oh god my uh
it's almost late now anyway but
but they keep on asking
so i have to deliver oh gordon ramsay is
here boo she didn't make the gingerbread
herself i'm already upset i did i made
it with my mom okay
it's not store-bought okay
i'm going to condemn this house as is
abandoned
what are you talking about this is
sacrilege how are you going to use a
glue gun
pull up your big girl petticoat and fail
like the rest of us there are no
shortcuts in cooking and decorating work
like the rest of us shut up thank you
thank you genma
gemma did put up the comment thank you
while i was reading
gordon ramsay's
jordan jordan ramsey's boo glue is
cheating me me mimi you guys hear that i
hear like a tiny sound that goes almost
like a bird like
me you guys hear that
i hear it
okay so um
now i as you see i have a lot of tiny
decorations in the back
um yeah apparently i could make a tree
i think
it goes
together like this
it doesn't actually work
oh my god it works oh my god oh no it's
about to break
who the [\h__\h] thought of this
who i guess you shouldn't push it in too
hard
okay hey i got a tree it's
da
wait it doesn't stand wait how's it
supposed to stand
oh you know you have to get it all the
way to the bottom otherwise it won't
stand
but it's about to break i was trying to
push it in and it's about to break i
glue it
just glue it
but then at first i'll have to break it
[Music]
unless
no
[Applause]
everything we need to glue together
okay so there goes the glue
on one side
here this is how you make a tree
[Music]
is it the hey way around no that's i
guess how it is yeah okay
and then on the other side
[Music]
i show you oh
good amount of glue oh oh this one is
running out by the way
[Music]
don't burn though don't burn yourself
okay okay oh
nice oh glue is the way to go i'm
telling you guys
[Music]
and now it stands now it stands yeah
honestly like before i baked it i tried
to like push these this just these parts
further apart so that it wouldn't you
know grow together but it did anyway so
this is like they didn't think this one
through that much did they
and i have some other things uh oh yeah
right my mom said you know with the
things that we cut out of the out of the
uh windows she said i should make a
schweinstein
with the schweinstein in english again
um
schweinstein you know the thing that the
santa comes through
on the on the
on the roof a chimney yeah so i guess
that's a good idea we'll make a chimney
look how good it looks oh my god
oh my god my house
who needs a real house and pay rent when
you can just make a freaking gingerbread
house
yes
it will be like lopsided though
because
you know one is not shorter than the
other
unless i force it uh
i don't no
it could work somehow where is the
chimney usually anywhere on the roof
right just anywhere
around the chimney tree on the chimney
chimney top
like so
oh god hold on
stay stay stay stay
staying it's staying
staying not the most ideal way to do it
but it's staying
okay
uh we might want to do the sides before
i do the front again
it but it will it'll be like
i don't feel like that
on it
i guess it
yeah this is the problem that i have now
this is the problem i'm facing i guess
i'll just um
make it straight and then
fill the bottom with icing
[Music]
and it's too late to cut anything at
this point because it's all baked and
i'm not gonna make new things and
i'm not gonna try to create it out of
other things don't worry it's okay
okay
that is this is okay this is okay
i hope it's not too heavy
oh see it's floating
[Music]
bite it at the end
i don't wanna eat this
especially now that there's now that
there is cat hair and glue everywhere
it's too late to eat it now
okay
[Music]
okay okay
okay very much floating
is this how a chimney works i don't have
one i wouldn't know
[Music]
i have the doors too by the way so i
could like have an open door here and
one in the back too because apparently
there's a back door as well
but in theory i could also maybe do this
so then it would solve the problem at
least a little bit
you see that
because otherwise it will now be
like like totally floating
oh i should use one of the doors
yeah i should use one of the doors
yeah yeah yeah
okay okay okay
so that means
i need glue
uh
on the top sides and on the bottom
okay
okey-dokey
girl
[Music]
okay
okay i'm shaking
[Music]
i'm shaking
okay
ah no more glue
[Music]
oh oh it's working though where is the
rest of my here
round two baby
[Music]
okay
so i'll i'll stabilize it a little bit
here
[Music]
there's there's a only air here let's
try to fill it up oh god oh god
oh god no no now the glue is going
everywhere okay never mind we don't need
that much stabilizing it's perfect the
way it is
oh
okay all right
okay
okay that's enough
is it up
which side is prettier uh that side was
broken so this side is better
we will always show it from this side
then
and then
we will add a door here
okay
wow
this is kind of fun
this is kind of fun isn't it
or should i close it
i could be like no
no this house is closed
mine should be open i think opening it
is kind of a
nice touch
i don't know where to attach it
like so
okay i put some glue where it's not even
necessary but okay
no no no no interiors but here we have
it oh god the tree stuck to the table
oh god okay here it is we have a tree we
have
a tree here
[Music]
and there is also some weird animal
that i made
how does it work uh and and and uh and
the snowman
let's make the snowman at least see this
is like this is the snowman and this is
the base it's supposed to be sitting on
this might actually work this one
let's try to connect it see if it breaks
um
nope
doesn't doesn't go in
[Music]
will it stand already
no it won't
see it's like still a little bit too far
out
ah it doesn't work do i have another one
no i don't have another one i only have
this one
do i have to purposefully break it and
then glue it just glue it just glue it
yeah but then first i have to break it
though
i guess i'll break it
[Music]
don't come on the table don't jump up on
the table
can you come here
hi baby
okay so wait uh what's how
doesn't matter
which side was the correct side
she just like
uh
she just stood on two legs with her
front uh
legs on my
chair and she was like what are you
doing
why didn't you go behind me
yeah
mommy's busy right now come back later
you'll get some extra cuddles later okay
cute chunkers
okay show
like this
and then go this part
to the snowman trunks do you want to
build a snowman
junkies
do you want to build a snowman
it doesn't have to be a snowman
okay bye
we're shaking
[Music]
that's a lot of glue because it's uneven
i added some extra glue
oh oh nice nice nice nice noise
yeah
snowman maybe after putting some sugar
coating on it it will look more like a
gloom
wait it does it stands it stands
hallelujah
[Music]
the moment i touch her she like drops
dead on the floor
[Music]
not
he really wants my attention
um
[Music]
wow
sorry excuse me
cat is always priority chunk is cute
okay uh i don't want that tree i got
stars too by the way i don't know where
to put the stars you can put them like
on the floor
um
this i don't need okay i think we're
done
one more thing that's like what the [\h__\h]
is this
uh how would this work again
man
how would this one work again
this was supposed to be a reindeer i
think but no matter how i look at it it
doesn't doesn't look like a reindeer
anymore
[Music]
no whatever i don't want it
[Laughter]
okay um
do i still need glue after this hmm
[Music]
no i think for now we'll turn off the
glue and then put like the sugar coating
everywhere on these edges and all that
and
then we'll try to use that as well
for
uh
putting on the sweets
i do by the way have something this is
supposed to be for some more cookies but
i do also have this we could decorate
the tree
with this
but this isn't really supposed to be
used for the
house but we can use it for the house as
well and i got i got these ones to add
on top of the
on top of the icing as well okay
now the next challenge is to make the
icing
uh
okay so it's basically help me out here
guys it's basically three egg whites and
a little bit like it said like 500 grams
of powdered sugar
and
it's just no i mean it needs it for you
know looking like a gingerbread house
the the coating must be icing not hot
glue
although i when i bought this hot glue
gun i saw that there's like colored hot
glue sticks
like all kinds of colors and they are
even like some of them are even like
like uh they they sparkle
sparks
yeah they got glitter in it so i wanted
to buy that but it would have taken too
long i think
but if i had that then i could fill the
whole roof with that because if it's
colored then it actually looks good i
guess
yeah the icing in the hot cocoa
no what the hell
that's not how it works
oh
stream sparks of hot glue gun
okay then um
um i will uh move away from the
microphone for a moment and try to make
the icing
uh how long do you usually
like
how when do i know it's finished
when do i know it's finished
[Music]
i have a mixture yet i'm using a
kitchenaid but i never used a kitchenaid
before and i never made icing before
even
when it's very ah when it dries it gets
thicker
15 nah
no idea stiff
10 to 15 minutes
no way
[Music]
you won't it's a leap of faith
well okay um i won't use free eggs
though i think i'll only use two eggs
because i i
like i think that's the three eggs is
for if you also have to use it for you
know putting together the whole house so
we probably don't even need that much
and then if we end up needing much more
than we can still make new one i guess
what are you guys doing
what are your cats doing over there
can i put
my headphones on the house
no let me put them here okay and then um
i'll be shouting from a distance i guess
uh
okay
i'm nervous
[Music]
should i write something on the stream
myself
[Music]
okay okay only the egg whites right
uh
[Music]
okay
i know how to separate them
[Music]
yes
what do i do with the yolk you guys want
some
raw egg yolks
[Music]
maybe i'll make some uh
some scrambled eggs afterwards
you want some egg yolk acid yolk
okay number two
crack that egg
[Music]
i'm good at this
it doesn't look like that much even
though there are large size eggs
[Music]
i don't lay eggs
they're not chicken eggs okay they're uh
turkey turkey eggs or so
or ostrich eggs whatever just not
chicken eggs
don't worry i got you bam i got you
okay how do i use this
powder sugar too how much is 500 grams
don't say 500 grams 500 gram i kind of
know that
[Music]
oh i bought this fancy thing for this
purpose where did i put it
no no no you don't go anywhere
go off of my chair this is mommy's chair
it's a mommy's chair
it's mommy's chair
[Music]
wait where do i put that thing
yes
look what i got
here's something like
for the powdered sugar
isn't that smart it also says here
and have what how much uh 500 grams
[Music]
in like a
sugar
powder sugar or anything powdery yeah in
this way because i have learned that if
you don't like put it for a thief
it will hi cats
i don't have time to pet you right now
it's like an egg on my on my
on my hands
one egg
oh yeah you have to put it for a seat
right yeah yeah
okay don't you dare jump on there let me
put the
turn the camera out for a moment please
enjoy the uh mixing asmr for a moment
i hope this will go well
i really hope
um
[Music]
it only goes up to 350.
it's 500 million
that much
oh my god
it's like
this one this one says
500 is a lot oh my that will use up like
maybe almost all of my powder sugar
it is a lot
okay then but 500 was for free eggs
[Music]
why is it sticking
oh my god
give me a second guys
[Music]
uh
okay
[Music]
and when the icing is done
chunkers
okay
it's not 100 your fault because uh
there's like cables everywhere
don't blame her
blame me instead
blame me
now i want to ask so when um
when uh
i have the let's say i have the icing
done how do i put it into the bag stupid
question but just with a spoon or what
where how do people put it into the bag
into the ice
into the icing bag how would i put it in
there
would be spoon for the spatula ah i did
get a spatula with the whole set
okay
i'm i'm i'm forking the sugar right now
because there's a lot of big
clumps of powdered sugar in here hi
smoothie
[Music]
with the glue gun no not everything is
done with the glue gun
[Music]
okay i'm gonna do it now i i'm nervous
but i'm gonna do it though bye bye guys
[Music]
i never used this machine before
i like close it
i don't know
[Music]
anything okay
you repeat
[Music]
oh my god
how do i put the sugar in there there's
like no space i need to like lift it up
every time
[Music]
[Applause]
how
[Music]
in there [\h__\h] this thing
um
[Music]
okay
it's getting pretty thick
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
there's sugar everywhere on the floor
ah
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
is it done
it already looks pretty nice but i don't
know where to stop
[Music]
[Applause]
it has to be pretty stiff right
has to be pretty stiff
but like it shouldn't like just pour
down right
it should kind of
pour very slowly if anything
maybe more
[Music]
yummy
wow
it's so sweet
it's still porous though like i think
it's not stiff enough but aren't we like
doing it for pretty long
oh the machine sounds like alma is that
why you said what are you saying
it doesn't what the hell
don't over mix it it will coat it wise
um
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah that makes a difference
yeah maybe it will attack a bit longer a
tiny bit longer
[Applause]
wait a second
[Music]
we're almost there i think
making some adjustments
[Music]
will it stay like this
or really change its consistency
over time
i'm gonna put it into the bag now
trying to follow the instructions of the
how to use piping bag
so we first put it in the like we don't
cut it yet right we cut it after
everything is already in there right
uh put the one up coupler into the bag
ah
what
one of you mean one of the metal things
should be inside the bag
where is no couple that's something else
wait that's this part
the one off coupler whatever that means
aha
[Music]
uh and i will actually turn off the
didn't turn off the hot glue
[Music]
chunkers is sitting on my chair as if it
hurts
nice asserting dominance on me
i'm so proud of you chunkers can i sit
on the chair huh
[Music]
oh guys it looks it looks gummy
the problem is that the bowl definitely
mirrors
my favorites but reflect
cats go away please cut please
please go away
okay okay
i'll just i'll just uh do it on my on my
lap
moment
putting on my gloves again
[Music]
it's not hers though that is uh that is
true
everything here belongs to cat
you guys also belong to my cat the real
reason why i
created kfp is to have lots of chimpkins
for my cats because my cats are actually
controlling me
[Music]
no cat no go down from the table you're
so lucky that the camera isn't on right
now
junkers junkers
go down
yeah good baby
okay okay
okay okay we're back we're back
everybody
uh
okay we now and this the inner part is
okay to show
um
oh god don't i i won't show you this
part it's kind of difficult
and i will show you how i pour it in i
guess so now we have
this piping bag thingy and i think this
part i was supposed to put in there
mm-hmm then
i'm just going to use
one of these
i have lots of different ones
paint my scissors
[Music]
okay
i'm gonna cut it open
now
there are many different types that make
different shapes and i said i want to
like what was it 17 or 7
both of them are
okay um let's take a look again
let's take a look
i like seven
alex seven
reflection
no
on this it looks reflective but don't
worry you don't see [\h__\h]
i'm checking it
how where does it say the number
wait it doesn't say the number anywhere
you're telling me i have to like look at
the tip of each one of them and then
figure it out myself are you kidding me
okay seven looks like um
[Music]
no these are not it
what's this
bungalow kind of nights and maybe this
one
for this one
and this doesn't know how many tips are
there one two three four five six
one two three four five that's more than
six
wow there's some fancy ones in here
[Music]
like which one didn't i look at yet
can i look at this
what about this one one two three four
five six no that's more
ah
huh this one this one this one is it one
two three four five yeah i think that's
the one okay
uh instructions
how to use piping bag uh okay now wait
should i already put
eh should i already put my icing in
doesn't look like it's in in the
instructions
uh
put the one of coupler into the bag cut
up the extra part uh-huh
cut it off
uh
you mean to cut it up here
[Music]
here
like
this okay
put the what put oh the one of coupler
means that wait are they they're
sticking together
show the weight
there's you have to like these are
sticking together i have to pull them
apart oh wait which part goes inside
this one
this one goes inside ah
[Music]
that's no problem
oh god now it's sticking out is that
okay that's probably not okay
it's sticking out now out of the plastic
is that okay
but wait then you ah ah wait then
where's the the thing that i selected
this is it
does it go like that
oh yeah yeah okay okay so now
and then we'll put that on here uh it's
okay the plastic is a little bit too
short now but that's okay it seems to
work
yeah so like this
okay
and i do have the tape too
do we need the tape
okay i mean it's not it's not tape i
don't know why they call it tape
okay
so we put that on there after we put in
yeah
for easy spraying i'm not gonna be
spraying anything but okay stand here
okay and now now i need a spoon
[Music]
oh
i tasted a little bit of the sugar
i haven't moved in a while have i i
tasted a little bit of the sugar
it's it's nice
pretty nice
this is where the real stream starts
everybody
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah it's it seems to have a nice
consistency now
okay
[Music]
how do you get it in there
and how to use
how do you get it in there properly
honest oh well improvise adapt overcome
uh
oh this is a messy situation
oh god oh god oh god oh no
get in there
[Music]
it is pretty sticky that's a good sign
right
okay
[Music]
i want to get in there as much as
possible so we don't have to open it up
again
preferably all of it
[Music]
do you have any any any tips and tricks
because it's like kind of difficult
[Music]
okay
uh
spoil it i'm trying to add glue
i just winged it okay i'm trying to wing
it too
[Music]
oh oh dear oh there oh oh there oh there
oh dear oh dude
i need another hand
i need
cats help me
what do i have you guys for
[Music]
cats
sorry guys this is taking a little while
but it will look marvelous it will look
divine
[Music]
oh
okay
oh it's already pretty full
[Music]
okay
that must do for now
i've got the decoration over here
and this stuff and then this can go away
and this can go on
[Music]
okay
baby
would you look at that
oh bubble there's a little bit of my
laptop that's okay
look at this
it's
pretty full
pretty old here but it's like
partially on the outside of it as well
it's not really what i wanted uh those
shield
how do i get it to the bottom what
how to use the tape but for me it's like
for me it's like all the way to the top
now all the way everywhere how do i get
it to the bottom
if they use my fingers push it to the
bottom
what a mess though what a mess
ew
ew i'll should i lick it off
oh my god oh oh it's already coming up
oh
whatever ah
sorry are you coming out
wait wait wait
shut the leg
like
[Music]
oh wow this is not how it's supposed to
be
[Music]
ah
oh wait that's barely anything
there's barely anything
okay
it's not
telling me it's not gonna be enough
you have to like spread it i thought it
would make like a nice shape oh god
i thought it would make a nice shape it
doesn't make a nice shape at all
[Music]
so calm down
this is gonna be a messy house
[Music]
we just have to
cover up these parts and then the rest
will do a glue
turn around turn around [\h__\h] this
this
is gonna be a beautiful house
wherever you want it or not why is it
not coming out now
hello
oh god oh it's coming on at the top
[Music]
i want you on this time
i don't know what's going on
i don't know what's going on with go to
the
go to the bottom go to the bottom go to
the bottom go to i dare you go to the
bottom go to the bottom
okay okay
oh god oh god i'm gonna maybe i
shouldn't have put it all in there
okay wait we want all the edges here
right okay
okay
[Music]
this is really how you do it
it looks messy
gotta do the windows i think
why am i doing this with my right hand
huh
okay
i mean for a first try and doing this
all alone
can anyone complain
no
no and we're not eating it so it only
has to look nice but yeah that's what
i'm failing at right now
uh
can we do the dory somehow
see the tip didn't matter at all
turns out the tip didn't
[Music]
matter oh
can you can you just please go to the
bottom again
[Music]
go to the bottom please
okay okay okay
okay okay
stroke it stroke it
stroke it
stroke it nicely
yeah yeah yeah
okay there's still a big chunk at the
top but
just gotta be careful and uh oh how do i
move the house now without touching it
dropping my fingers
[Music]
oh my god yeah my room is so hot
i'm sweating loki
looks beautiful
shouldn't have made fun of the forest
fairy
[Music]
shouldn't have made fun of her this is
karma
[Music]
okay oh my god oh yes
should we cover the whole roof with it
if we can
i wonder if we can if we have enough
honestly i think we do
there's still a little bit in the
in in the
in the bowl i still have a little bit of
bowl we should cover the top here
[Music]
back to the bottom back to the bottom
sorry i'm like 100 focused right now i
can't even look at the camera
i didn't expect the situation to
escalate like this
okay
i think we will do the the the decker
microphone
we will do the decoration with hot glue
i think because this is stressing me out
way more than it should
okay
well we got some sugar coating on my
blue yeti mic now gorgeous beautiful
not exactly where i wanted it to be
i mean it looks cute though doesn't it
i think it looks pretty cute though
[Music]
and which gingerbread house doesn't look
messy huh
how many points out of 10
and why is it 10 out of 10.
[Music]
guys i don't know you might be wondering
why i'm always out of a breath when i'm
doing this it is partially because
i'm like leaning forward and like
stretching out my arms while doing this
so that my body and my head doesn't like
enter the camera angle um and it's it's
pretty
exhausting
to like
always have a tense
body
posture
also it's hot in my room
but this is oh no there's more more
icing on my microphone
oh it's okay it's just it's not my
normal streaming microphone it's just
for for cooking streams
i suppose there's bound to be some [\h__\h]
on my microphone
oh cookie oh god you see that
overlapping bar in my
lick it off do you guys want to lick my
icing
any uh
any any anyone any volunteers to lick my
icing
yes
[Music]
there was no time for putting that
stupid
ring on top of it man
okay i want i want all of that lined
please all of it
[Music]
oh god oh god oh god oh god go back go
back
where's the spoon that i have oh no oh
okay whatever
[Music]
oh god oh god it's spilling
the window
oh my god oh my god
okay
uh
we got all the important parts i think
did i get it on the other side on the
under the roof did i get that part did i
get that for
no i don't think i did okay
okay no problem
oh god oh god oh god i sing
giant hand tight
tie hentai
[Music]
we actually we will have a lot left over
i guess
oh wait it shouldn't only be under the i
guess it shouldn't be under the roof at
all it could just be on the bottom of
the roof
because oh well
oh well extra homework oh god oh god
sorry i got it on the can i get it on
the webcam hopefully not okay it's
everywhere now it's everywhere now
um
i have this thing
oh
[Music]
yes
don't worry about the reflection i don't
see myself in it so we could
okay
it's like a cake thingy
okay it's dropping all over
okay okay
okay okay uh but then i don't i don't
really necessarily need it there do i
i'll just just just do this and and then
we'll spread it
all over there
and now um just uh put this somewhere
put this somewhere
okay okay we're spreading it we're
spreading it we're spreading it
yeah no i don't see myself on it we're
good we're good i don't see myself
do i steal myself
no no
no
there's some hot glue strings
okay we'll cover up the roof i think
that's pretty
uh nice should be it should be good
let me do it on this side
actually i need a bit more i think
once the whole roof is covered
it will look beautiful
i think like as if it's snow snowed
beautifully
did it snow for everyone's christmas
probably not huh
i don't see a reflection shut up about
it
no no you don't it's just like darkened
and bright that's all
that's all you can see
don't worry
did it snow for you i it did for me oh
really like it snowed a little bit in
december surprisingly for me but not on
christmas unfortunately
[Music]
not on actual christmas
that would have been too lucky
when was the last white christmas i had
i wonder
it was 84 years ago
[Music]
i guess like yeah maybe in canada and
like the northern countries where
there's a lot of snow anyway or like on
the mountains i mean in austria and the
mountains it was probably
most likely snowy on christmas as well
oh god i need more icing please
i need more of that icing and i have
some more icing this is such a mess
i should be doing it like this let me
get it from the bowl
nice
okay
uh
a fake
coating
of ice
by the way yesterday i spent my whole
day
um
watching
this show
um i started yesterday by watching the
tutors re-watching it's not my first
time
and at some point i was like
hmm
i kind of want to know more about this
lady
catherine of aragon because i'm a huge
fan of
and berlin
but what do i know of catherine of
aragon and then i found out that there's
this show
uh on on amazon prime or not not on
amazon prime i guess it's on amazon
what's it called stars or whatever um
[Music]
and
sorry uh
it's called the spanish prince wait i
forgot that i forgot the windows here
what the hell i will do those later
the spanish princess you guys know that
show
and that one focuses on how catherine of
aragon
and became
the english queen
how she came from spain
to england and then struggled first of
all to you know first she was married to
a fur tutor
um
but our fortuitor died soon after
because of the plague yes yes
i know my history
thanks to all these shows that i'm
watching
and then she was like but [\h__\h] i want to
be a queen i'm not gonna go back to
spain so she kind of uh
created
uh she kind of made she said i wouldn't
say seduced but she made she made um
a
henry tutor
uh fall in love with her and then
eventually after some struggles
they did get married as we all know
um and and yeah that's where i am and
i've watched the whole [\h__\h] season
yesterday every episode is one hour and
i watched the whole season yesterday
because it was so good that show is
actually really good there's like
millions of shows about the tutors
i was going for amazon i was like oh my
god there is really a lot of movies and
shows about the tutors but i was
watching a whole season how many
episodes does that season have i watched
it in the whole season and one or two or
three episodes of the second as well so
i was watching for like at least 12
hours
yeah but um i was also not feeling so
well yesterday i had some
weird uh tummy ache i think i was
feeling a little bit sick so i was like
okay okay i have a day off i'm just
gonna watch netflix all day and then and
then in the late evening like uh uh
close before midnight i
i recorded the
the little you know piano cover
that i did
yeah
i'm gonna move that house real quick
to this part
okay
yeah but i recommend to show to you guys
i am feeling better yes i'm feeling
wonderful
i'm feeling
wonderful thank you
[Music]
i feel like i'm making an actual house
right now
this part is not good
yeah
just cover it all with icing
yeah anyway the actress for for the
spanish princess for catherine is really
pretty too so now i'm struggling because
she's she's not that pretty in the
tutors
which i guess is because they wanted us
to fawn over and berlin on the tutors on
the show the tutors
the focus was mostly on
um
and berlin although they did cover all
of the lives
here and fangirling tutors right now i'm
i'm geeking
geeking
geeking over the tutors i'm sorry um the
tutors made me really interested in the
history of the tutors uh yeah the show
that you just made me interested in the
history so like after or in the middle
of the episodes i would go on wikipedia
and i would look up all kinds of things
like who is that dude and and what did
that do do and is that really true that
did that really happen
blah blah blah and did you know
that there is a myth now this is not 100
uh confirmed but there is a myth that
catherine from aragon this made me
respect her the the spanish princess
made me respect her so much more oh my
god like she apparently
uh it could be very much true because
her mom did stuff like that too um she
like when there was there was a time
when henry when they were freshly
married and
somewhat freshly married and henry went
to a war in france
alone
and it was ridiculous because the french
people just ran away from them
uh it was not really much of a battle
and in the meantime the scottish the
scottish the scottish king decided now
is a good time to uh take over england
because the throne is empty i like
talking about this it sounds like i'm
smart
although i learned it from the show but
hey still knowledge knowledge
this is when i say you can actually why
you say you can actually learn something
from watching netflix yeah
i mean not everything is true of course
but anyway let me continue
um
oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god why
did i do it like this
um so so the scottish were like okay
let's take over england because henry is
not there right now so who the [\h__\h] will
will uh will
protect england nobody so they started
gathering uh an army and then and then
and then catherine was like hell no what
the [\h__\h] and she sent some some of her
people to the border um and and then and
then and then
and then
and after a while she was like no i
gotta go there too
so
she had even though she was apparently
about seven months pregnant yes oh my
god
seven months pregnant she had an armor
made for herself
that covered her pregnant belly and her
mom apparently did the same
and she went there to you know uh raise
the how do i touch it now like literally
everything is covered now except those
windows
uh yeah what was i saying um what was i
saying
what was i saying what was i saying
oh yeah she went there to raise the
motivation of the people of the english
people and the funny thing is that the
scottish went into that battle with um
uh
5 000 people less
than the english and the scottish people
were mostly like actual actual knights
and warriors while the english army at
that moment was mostly in in in france
so
it was mostly like just random people
from uh
from like you know
uh
from the land uh
what's the word countryside from the
countryside it was just mostly mostly
yeah like an army of normal people and
even uh yeah villagers and and even
women partially apparently get country
people yeah farmers with pointy sticks
and all that um
and so like 5000 people less and not
even a trained army excuse me we thought
that they would lose that it was that
not many not a high chance of winning
there huh
but turns
[Music]
out much was it again
let's say i think it was like 20 000
that 20 30 000 on the scottish side and
25 000 on the english side and
casualties now listen up casualties on
the english side from twenty five
thousand one thousand five hundred
something like that
only
and on the scottish side they totally
obliterated them
they killed like
fifteen thousand twelve thousand fifteen
thousand
can you believe it how the [\h__\h] did they
do that
how did they do that
sorry i'm really nerding out about this
this is really cool
but unbelievable
they didn't even have like prop and a
proper army but they killed like 12 000
on their side while the english people
only had like 1500 casualties the
scottish had 10 times that much and they
managed to kill the king in that battle
the scottish king fell in that battle
yeah
led by catherine of aragon
meanwhile
the english king henry
was uh chilling
in in france uh trying to make it look
like he actually did something too
but
uh
apparently
the french people just like kind of gave
up the moment they saw the english
people and they just kind of ran away
which i think is just hilarious
[Laughter]
and then and then i mean at least in the
show it was funny because
um
henry came back and everyone like was
like of course the english people were
celebrating him like oh my god we won
over france he took over two cities or
whatever
and then and then and then cavalry of
course she respects the king and she
doesn't know yet how it actually went
down there and and she's like oh my king
oh
my lord wow so strong
and and then she finds out that uh they
actually kind of surrendered and didn't
fight and and then she shares her story
to him
that she they actually had a proper war
that was so much more dramatic and so
much more important and and somewhat so
much more of a success
and and and he's like he doesn't want to
admit that she did like
someone something so much more important
than he did but
yeah
oh man she killed a [\h__\h] king
she killed the [\h__\h] scottish i mean
maybe not in in the show it was her but
in reality it was probably someone else
but she was there but they killed the
[\h__\h] scottish king
oh my god so exciting
[Laughter]
so fascinating to me you have no idea i
can't get this like to look pretty oh my
god
[Music]
oh my god
of course of course the king doesn't
want to be like he doesn't want to look
weaker than his
spanish
young wife who who doesn't even really
have any experience in in battle either
her mom
the isabella from aragon i think
i really gotta when i'm done with with
catherine from aragon i really gotta
look up more about isabella because
she's really um fascinating to me as
well
the whole i was like the english i was i
was like the english family so
interesting but now the spanish family
is so interesting to me
yeah because then there's also this
whole arc about joanna um who who became
who is catherine's sister who became the
queen after isabella died and and
everyone else died and it was only
joanna and she was married to philip
from france and blah blah blah oh i'm
such a history nerd
i really [\h__\h] love that kind of stuff
okay i think we're like done with the
roof
oh man
so i'm in the second season now and i'm
really enjoying it
it's on it's on amazon please go watch
it
uh okay we gotta just do the
pick that disgusting thing up here and
just do the windows really quickly
everything's so messy
that was my my
uh day yesterday i spent my time when i
was feeling sick quite nicely
but then uh around midnight i was
feeling a bit better so i recorded um
that song that i promised you the piano
version of
um
the piano version
of sparks i recorded it for you guys
have you guys watched it have you guys
watched it
it's not the same as in my outfit reveal
so you gotta check it out we we adjusted
it a little bit
um so that
we adjusted it so that uh
you know
it would have
uh
oh god oh god
so that it would help that that let's go
let's go after pass tonight although i
sang it in a lower key
because the instrumental kind of asked
for it so instead of it going like
really high at the end it still was
pretty low so
hope you guys like that little touch
of the key change
the rest of the song i think is the same
key but
the bridge ended up being um
a different key kind of
okay are we done with this [\h__\h] this is
such a mess
[Music]
my you don't really see it but there's
like a
flat floor or whatever oh yeah now you
see it on top of my gloves it's just
disgusting all of this is disgusting
okay
um
the thing is
in order to glue anything on top of that
i would have to wait until it's dry
but
maybe
maybe i can glue things on it
right now while it's not dry yet maybe
it will stick
maybe we'll see what do we put on top of
it though
[Music]
let's be creative
this is where um this is where we get
creative let me try those i never ate
those before
let me try let's try them let's take
this pink one
[Music]
i usually
i love sweets but i usually only eat
like um chocolate and cookies and all
that
this kind of stuff i
i only ate when i was like a child
so i'm thinking
putting this here
maybe different colors
[Music]
candy
it looks cute
but will it stick on the sides here oh
too
[Music]
it kind of does
it kind of does want to stick here
[Music]
oh my god it does
could say that
uh
i don't really see that side but okay oh
my god sticks yeah
hot glue salad
no more hot glue
[Music]
oh nice oh let's put it on the top too
oh this is fun this is the fun part
[Music]
ah this is difficult oh well
okay
now i want to put it on on the sides
here too
i'm not sure if that will work
[Music]
wait that's the wrong call like it's
already red there
i feel like a child
does that work oh it works
oh my god
my god
[Music]
all right it's a bit too long here but
that's okay
it stinks oh my gosh
[Music]
oh yeah
are you sure is that really gonna
you know this way i could even eat it
afterwards
because it's not sticking to the
hot glue or anything right now it's
sticking to the icing would you guys eat
this off like would you guys eat the
sticks off of it afterwards
would you guys do it or do you think
this is still disgusting
yes
nope
only for a chill
this is an adorable house thank you
probably
yes i used hot glue to put like the base
together don't judge me stop judging me
yellow
[Music]
not green um
so far nothing has fallen off yet i'm so
proud
okay
wow
[Music]
let me move this a little bit can i
i can't i have to kind of keep it like
that can i turn you around how do i turn
it uh
let me put some things away here so that
i have more space
when a tree is sticking
there is no space for me i just have to
turn around the whole thing this thing
can go though
you can go here oh that will be fun to
clean everything up afterwards
[Music]
i should just turn the the ground part
from now
on and by the way um
i am
i i was watching as you know i was also
watching shit's creek lately
um
you know it sounds weird but it's a
really good show as well
and
oh no not that one
and i have this
i realized i have this problem
that when i like a show very much and i
realized i've reached pretty much the
end of it
i
i avoid watching the last episode
um
so
uh
i stopped i have one more episode left
from the shit's creek but i switched to
the tuners now
i did the same thing with the handmaid's
tale i can relate really you guys do
that too i still don't know how the last
season of the handmaid's tale ended
[Music]
i don't know and i don't want to know i
will wait but the good thing is that for
the handmaid's tale they're still making
um
a new season
i think
my show i don't have the dark red
anymore i have to go this bright red
so once the new season of the handmaid's
tale comes out i will watch the last
episode of the last season
because then i can at least continue
watching it and but it doesn't make
sense so partially part of the reason
why i'm doing it this way is because i
don't want to wait for the next season
too long right but
it ends up being the same i'm still
waiting it's just i haven't watched the
last episode but i just don't want it to
end you know
but
it ends up being the same i i still wait
the same amount of time for the new
season
so stupid
i'm so stupid i don't know why
but this is just how i am
[Music]
i can't believe this actually sticks i
am surprised really
can i put them here as well just put
them everywhere everywhere
although uh
having a little bit of a space problem
here
okay that works
[Music]
did you guys see the news
i mean it was kind of like obvious that
this would happen but ninety and um
the sixth generation
is getting a new
uh new new year's eve outfit i mean i
knew that ninja was gonna get it this
year because the rest of her generation
got it last year so it was like to be
expected
and if you don't if you're not if you
haven't been watching whole life for a
long time then you maybe don't know but
usually uh
whole life members get a new year's
outfit
for new year's uh every year there's
like a bunch of members that get it
and uh
so it was obvious that nana she was
gonna get it because the rest of her gen
got it last year
yeah
but i was surprised that holo
uh x
the icing has ever shut up
i was surprised that holo x was getting
it already because they it has only been
one month
i was pretty surprised about that i
didn't expect it
i think i was informed beforehand but i
i kind of
forgot about it
[Laughter]
yeah surprising isn't it but wow we
already got new outfits from them that's
that's cool that's fun
that's fun
[Music]
well i mean
we got the party outfits very recently i
mean there was supposed to be you
we were supposed to get them earlier but
we got them recently so now it's kind of
like our new year's outfit isn't it
[Music]
it's very it's very fitting for like a
new year's party i would say
our
party dresses
okay i'm scared of things falling apart
now let's let's add um
different things i will add
this my thingies
[Music]
uh
i have not bought smarties in like a
million years
oh my god
smarties
[Music]
smarties oh
so many colors
did they always have so many colors
so now we put
uh
them all on i guess we can cover the
whole roof of it i'm not gonna have
enough smarties
let's just start from the outside and
then hope that we'll have enough
zimba
symbol
[Music]
smarties and m ms which is better
wait it's the same thing
[Music]
oh
i thought smarts and m ms
all right they don't have the m on the
oh there's no m on it
oh
wait wait why did i always think it's
the same thing
i thought it was the same thing
[Laughter]
wait do you guys have smarties over
there i know m m's must be all over the
world right
what about what about smarties
they taste different let me let me try
one then oh no i can't try what if i
don't have enough everyone counts
[Music]
only m ms we have smarties in canada
mmms are chocolate so but these are
chocolate too i think
yes these are chocolate too i ate one
it's just i guess i think i think i know
the difference
besides i think the size being um
generally bigger
the i mean there's probably giant m m's
too but generally smarties are bigger
and
i think um
m ms just that they come with like nuts
inside and all that kind of stuff but
smarties only come like in the original
one i think i have yet to see
smarties with like um
[Music]
with anything else inside than chocolate
smarties have no chocolate but that's
chocolate wait wait
what i just ate was chocolate
[Music]
you made me look again i ate a second
one because of you guys
it's chocolate inside
[Music]
they want smarties
no
see i could decorate it like this too
and instead of doing the whole roof i
don't know but
i probably have enough
okay
we should speed it up kind of though
it's gonna take years
uh-oh there's too much space down here
but not enough space to put smarties
there [\h__\h]
damn it
oh well
no
i think the icing is starting to uh
[Music]
stiffen
i'm getting really hungry by the way the
only thing i had for breakfast
was um
[Music]
you know what that
is no
it's it's like a milk sandwich that's
it's just a snack it's not breakfast
but i ate it for breakfast
because i didn't have the time to eat
anything else have to set up for the
stream
[Music]
and
speed
i said this was a speed run after all
okay
milk sandwich
it's so yummy though i know it sounds
weird but it's so yummy
it's so yummy
i love it so much i could eat it like
every day
where are all the colors
[Music]
it's rigged my smarty box is rigged
okay
i will only do it like that that cause
like i don't really have much space on
on this side so okay this side is done
it's looking cute
come on your tongue
calmly down call me down
okay okay
turn it over here
[Music]
this looks pretty dry
on that side like here it looks super
dry
can it stick anyway
[Music]
oh sorry that was just me not putting it
on properly
let's
all right on this side
[Music]
it just i just wanted to stay like this
until i take one photo
that's all i want
one photo this is like probably not
enough
no okay that's it
um
uh wait
don't
i have more
i put some fresh icing on here yeah
there wasn't that much here to begin
with on that side
[Music]
new year's outfits i'm so excited uh to
be honest i was looking at this at the
silhouette and i wasn't even sure which
one minute she was i recognized rapurazu
obviously i think i recognized louie
because of the feathers if you look at
the hands you can probably
recognize that there might be some
models that have the same hands as in
their original model maybe i didn't look
at that though
um i reckon i think i recognized uh
coyote because of the ears
but i am not sure which one could
and
iroha and nanaji are
so
i
if you guys know did you guys look at
this at the silhouette and and knew
which one is everyone
besides rapudasu and clyoti
because i didn't
and this is usually usually it's so easy
to see
like everybody
did you know no not really oh then i'm
not the only one
that's
good to know
[Music]
i'm so hungry
no
and then a secret member
of holo x
no no no she just she couldn't get it
last year because she was in the middle
of you know
getting a new design
that's why her 3d was delayed as well
but but i'm so happy for her getting a
new outfit
i'm sure her her
her kimono must be
maybe because she really likes to be
like she likes to look like an idol or
or like a
very
she likes to look like a student as well
i think
so it might have some elements of that i
didn't see it yet
nancy would probably show me if i asked
her to
[Music]
but i will not spoiler myself this time
i need to drink water let me drink water
[Music]
this time yeah she um sported me before
um i think you know she got her new
outfit while i was still in japan no
i think
and we were at that moment we were like
a lot in contact
and she may or may have not showed me
beforehand
[Music]
and then i was like yo that's so cute i
love it thank you
for showing me i'm just so curious when
it comes to new outfits
so curious
to find out what it looks like i i just
i just can't hold back the problem is
that i know about these new outfits way
earlier than you guys know
so i'm like oh i could ask them to show
me
should i should i should i or should i
wait like five million weeks until it's
actually getting revealed
oh well i think i think we at least have
enough to cover the whole roof that's a
good
news it is very tempting
[Music]
i feel so so girly and childish by doing
something like this i like it
it's fun
something different again
didn't you have a gingerbread star yes i
do do you want me to put it on there
i don't i don't really wanna i guess i
could like where should i put it though
here
[Music]
that's kind of cute
i guess that's kind of cute
it messes up the order though
okay
i'll just leave some blank space um
[Music]
okay
what i do after these smarties i need i
need to put these ones somewhere
and the other i have two more different
kind of
sweets that uh i could put somewhere so
we're gonna put something here obviously
until
everything is covered in sweets that i
will never eat
and probably end up throwing away the
whole thing into the trash yay
no i might snack on some of these i
might
maybe
maybe i will
[Music]
yes a little bit easier with the fresh
um
uh the fresh icing
makes it
a bit easier
[Music]
okay
we're almost done
[Music]
and
this one
is there there's not enough space for oh
another one is there
alright so let me squeeze a little bit
and then try to squeeze this one in
okay yeah it works
[Music]
not done yet
um
let's try these ones
these ones have an interesting pattern
oh they smell oh i love these i love
these they smell good let me eat one
i do like these
[Music]
i see it
you like these two
they're pretty good yeah um
[Music]
but wait there's no icing here
so if i put icing all over it
but don't we want to see like some like
a little bit of the original gingerbread
too
[Music]
what do you think
put it around the windows
uh-huh yeah maybe
because i don't think we should put it
all over him
[Music]
nothing on the walls leave it as it is
but what did i get this for then i'll
try to put them on
but that looks really um that looks
really dry
oh
what could it could work
it's not the oh
my chat broke it's not the perfect shape
though works
wait maybe only at the bottom because
that maybe looks like you know maybe it
looks like someone has
flowers
out on the on their window um pain
thingy you know what i mean i do see it
i do see it it's like flowers at the
bottom
[Music]
and that way i can eat more of them too
let me turn it around
and we have windows here too
[Music]
yummy
i really normally never eat these kind
of candies i never buy them i never eat
them
[Music]
but now that i have them
i'm digging in
they have the perfect coloring for being
flowers too because it's like
several
colors
in one
corner
nice
[Music]
oh it's really dry
oh they're sticking sticking together
no sticking together
you will be part of this house now
and you will be part of my tummy
now we go here
wait i can't get enough of these this is
my breakfast
[Music]
stick
the green ones are especially
good for this particular illusion yeah
yeah yeah
the red ones they could be like all
kinds of roses and pansies pansies right
that's that's the name of a flower right
or am i misremembering
oh this is perfect i'm in love
[Music]
i don't know where to put these
these are pretty big too
and and the colors are pretty uh
uh
i wait wait wait
[Music]
yes that works
this has a bit of a trouble a bit of
trouble sticking there
but okay
okay um where else ah wait wait good
idea uh
uh can we someone said they want me to
make kfp out of this so this is a little
bit of a challenge but maybe i can ride
kfp here
oh it's a little bit tricky
wait i have an idea
i have an idea
[Music]
put some icing here
no more hot glue
hot glue
is of the past icing is the future
actually it should be the other way
around
but
it's okay
we're relying on icing now because i
don't want to
power up the
hot glue anymore
[Music]
i want this to be kind of like a sign
wait i could use my my sugar pens for
this
[Music]
wait
i could use i got these ones right i
could get these out wait
[Music]
um we have we have
we have red we have green we have blue
and we have orange or yellow yellow i
only want to open up one so i'm gonna go
with red
[Music]
on the icing though i hope it will work
let's see
let's try to write something on top ah
but maybe
oh
stay stay uh it's not it's still too
fresh i think
let's see
[Music]
me tell heck hey
hey
[Music]
the p is a little bit messy
but it works
and i hope this one will stick
will you stick
i think it will
maybe i can put uh one of those on top
as well
chocolate
[Music]
i just put it on top of the candy now
stay stay
let me push it a little bit
for a while
okay
kfb kfb kfb
oh it's falling down
don't fall down
that's a fine establishment you got here
care to um
join us subscribe
youtube channel
and maybe even become a member if you
want to oh god i think i have to wait
but i sing on this one for a while
this will take a little while
now light it on fire what no
this is this is a new kfb branch this is
a gingerbread branch
[Music]
i actually um
i bought this pen for the cookies that i
wanted to make
um but they come in handy now too should
i use them somewhere else as well
now that i already opened it how long
how long can you like keep these open by
the way
off of them how long can i use this
i gotta make the cookies soon i guess
[Music]
okay i think it's good
what do i do with this
[Music]
maybe maybe some
let me try to be creative
you don't really see it well unless it's
on the
on the icing
here's some blood on the windows
oh it's really um this one is really
stiff now
oh god this one
isn't here christmas decoration totally
[Music]
nakakazario
i don't know what exactly this is
supposed to be
but since i open it up i want to use it
we could also
quickly
do something with the snowman because he
needs to be white
[Music]
wait a second
let me get
the icing
[Music]
okay
come here snowman should we only do you
on one side on both sides
i'll do you everywhere
[Music]
do we do this part too so it doesn't
stick out too much
even though that's just the base
yeah let's do it
i'm already doing it anyway
can't stop me now
should i do the sides well there's
already icing on it
let's do it
[Music]
do you want to build a snowman
it doesn't have to be a snowman how do i
how will i hold it okay we only do one
side because otherwise i can't hold it
anymore
[Music]
but i could hold it but i don't want to
hold it
i'm getting a cramp in my right hand
[Music]
we'll have to yay a little bit for this
one maybe
to dry a tiny bit so i can
ride on it
okay tree you stay here good good boy
i want to make the door white
let's make the door white
we still have icing
wow this is fun
once like everything is like there to
decorate like the icing and the candy
that's the most fun part i now
understand why people do this even
though
even if they if maybe many people don't
actually eat it
it's just a fun activity and then it
looks really nice as christmas
decoration
however
christmas is already over
but i still get a use out of it because
i can show you guys and i can make a
stream out of it yeah
oh no this one dropped oh i didn't
notice
you know what i have some fresh uh
icing on here so let me put it on you
and that way you should be able to stick
better
[Music]
yeah
stick
okay
hopefully that sticks now
it cold shut up but the rest oh wait i
still didn't have flowers in the front
flowers in the front
please this one is already dry let me
put fresh icing on it
a bit more please
it's like
i have two professions
house building
and baking
you go you go here
[Music]
rifle material
yeah i can build your house
i will put that on my next time i apply
for a job
if i ever have to apply for a job again
i will put the following things on my
on my labels now on my skills
i will say i can build a house
i can cook
i can engineer
i can be a plumber
can game
i can drive a car i can drive race cars
i can um
i can parkour
i can
[Music]
what else do that i can sword fight
probably
[Music]
i can uh be an alchemist i can do
alchemy according to a
risers atelier
i can make a bomb i know how to make
really [\h__\h] badass great bombs
that blow up the whole world
[Music]
i can build
pickaxes and [\h__\h] and then uh farm
diamonds
i can literally do anything
i can tame an alpaca
i can tame a cat i can tame a wolf
i can tame anything
um damn i'm so multi-skilled i'm like
over
over qualified for literally every job
in this world
minecraft and all the other games i've
played on my channel have taught me so
much i'm so thankful
[Music]
i thought i would be using up all my
candy but now i got so much left over
[Music]
wait i have a good idea
a door handle
[Music]
yeah door handle
oh this is so cute
are you ready tree
uh a
are you ready
how do we do this i only i don't want to
open the other colors so
you'll have a red hat
[Music]
yeah
or red hair or whatever
[Music]
and then we'll have red eyes
and the red nose
and the red mouth
[Laughter]
[Music]
uniform
he'll be the first employee this is
totally a chicken
[Music]
i don't know what that part is supposed
to be oh [\h__\h]
um
i don't know
well
uh
what do i do about that
let's put some more icing on it
no um
i don't know it's it's your legs now
you know one leg
i don't know what this is
[Music]
don't question it
put something on you
i don't know what that
is supposed to look like
but at least you will be decorated and
i'll be using up my candy
[Music]
nice
lady i ate my sneeze [\h__\h] i ate it do
you know that feeling when you're when
you eat your sneeze while you're
sneezing
it's so unsatisfying give me my sneeze
back
give it back get back
you're back
what a weird snowman
i think i'm done
i think i'm done i'm like really happy
with it
it turned out a lot better than i
thought it would
damn
[Music]
found a good shape here
an orange slice orange slice
concealer i will take a nice photo later
when i clean up a little bit
but basically should i oh oh welcome to
what was it called my cribs or mtv what
was that mtv show called cribs mtv cribs
or something
uh let me welcome you to my crib uh
welcome yes so this is a 50 million
dollar mansion
uh that i renovated in order to uh make
a kfp out of it
yeah yeah yeah mtv creams welcome
welcome i'm famous person
so here it says kfp
here we have some christmas decoration
yeah yeah let me give you a tour
are you getting all this coffee are you
getting all this
now here we have an orange slice
that tastes like orange but don't eat it
it belongs to my house
it cost me um about
uh 50 000 bucks this this orange slice
now here we have flower banks on on each
one of the windows
i do have a door i know it's gorgeous
the door
the door is beautiful
i forgot about my [\h__\h] tree
it's it's only brown now i don't know i
don't know how to make it green i'm not
in the mood now
i don't [\h__\h] a tree we don't want the
tree
i have a beautiful door with a door
handle not many people have a door
handle but i do
now we have the beautiful kfp sign did i
mention that
this is definitely not blood uh please
please don't claim it is blood
now we turn it around and we see
we see a beautiful roof this is handmade
by the most professional people
handmade yes even with a star because
i'm a star
not everyone gets to do a mtv cribs show
okay only the only the cool people
oh
wait a second did i did i cover this on
the other side
yes i did i forgot one point one second
please everybody
i forgot one part
shut them up and let me put some fresh
icing on it i forgot that part did you
guys already try to make me notice it
i'm sorry
i hope you didn't
oh my god there's hot glue thingies
i shall
[Music]
that is a lot of icing baby
just how i like it
ice cold
just kidding i like it hot i'm a phoenix
okay let's put uh here you get a special
look into how
how
a professional roof builder
builds a professional roof oh my god not
like that
[Music]
oh my god
i dropped my spaghetti please please
ignore that
it so happens that the snowman is in the
way
kind of rude but okay
[Music]
oh god i keep on touching him
i keep on touching him
i'll get some complaints from my
employees again for touching them oh no
okay oh i'm sorry sorry that was a it's
a very new house okay it's a very new
house so some things have to be
corrected of course of course everything
according to my wish because it was uh
commissioned
yes yes yes so uh here we see a
beautiful roof in all the beautiful
colors we have diamonds we have rubies
we have smurfs my racks we have all of
them all of them
tiger eyes whatever you want
and now we give you a little bit more of
a turn
i must say the neighborhood here is
pretty
pretty bad it's a pretty bad
neighborhood so i'm starting to uh
to kind of make them all leave by
paying their fees to move to different
houses because i want all of them all of
the houses to be mine now here's the
back side yes it's unbelievable i do
have a back entrance for the cool people
the vip people here we have a back
entrance it has no door but don't mind
that it's a totally safe house yes
we have used the door somewhere else
because we like to improvise adapt and
overcome
or adapt and provide an oval overclock
doesn't matter in the end we overcome
now you see that beautiful lining here
wow the detailing here
is gorgeous
we turn that [\h__\h] around one more time
and we see this side with the beautiful
um
what's it called again
what's this called again
[Music]
let me eat that all right
ah beautiful chimney with some boobs if
you look closely you see they have
nipples
you see them
you see them here
nipple
i can even draw on them to make them
more apparent
let me do that real quick
nice detail
they're not in the middle because not
every boob is perfect you know
oh god this one isn't on the bottom
[Music]
[Laughter]
yummy
[Music]
good that i didn't use glue on
everything
so
the chimney
is not functional
um unfortunately
but doesn't matter
inside we have
4k 8k no no over 9000k flat screens in
there
that look like a real fire um
we have a
room
we have a thing down there a fireplace
with a screen yeah yeah so the chimney
doesn't have to be real
and this is just decoration
[Music]
and then of course you have the
beautiful flowers down here again
perfect detail for the for the flower
loving people so that my forest fairy
comes visit me someday eventually
one day i believe in it
and that is it that was my crib stop
eating from my crib stop eating my crib
don't you dare touch it
don't you dare touch it it's my crib
comes in
it's finished
and the first
the first worker
is here to what happened to your face
okay
what happened to his face
[Music]
where did your nose go
didn't you have a nose
oh well that's a working accident i will
not pay for it nope nope sorry that was
me
clancy
[Music]
yay
i still have so much
so many sweets you guys want to come
over and eat them
not yeah
[Music]
it's very cute right
it turned out so so much better than i
thought it would
be me drink some water i'm so out of
breath
[Music]
i like it
i think i'll be having this
standing around until it starts
um
molding
it looks cute thank you
nice touch
already in the chimney who santa
new usual room no this is kfp it says it
here i mean the kfp always comes with a
usual room but this one doesn't have one
yet it only has one room
[Music]
yeah attract ants no i don't think so
um my apartment is pretty and safe i
don't think there is any way for an ant
to enter my apartment in any way
i i have yet to like
the interesting thing is like
even when i have the windows open and
the lights on
not even flies fly into my apartment
that is actually something that
surprised me
normally i always had that issue when i
would have the light on in the night i
would always fly into my apartment in my
old one
but they don't do it here i don't know i
don't know why
you say that
now no an auntie and house yeah
no don't worry don't worry this this one
will be fine they won't smell it the
only
problem we have is that my cats might
try to play with it but i don't think
they'll try to eat it or lick it or
anything my cats are very picky when it
comes to food like i used to have a cat
when i live with my family still um who
would eat raw meat and i think a lot of
cats do like if you offer them like raw
chicken or raw beef or whatever or raw
fish they would eat it right but my cats
they don't
the only thing that they would eat is
raw tuna out of the can out of the tuna
can but they don't like i tried giving
them raw fish and now wrap or raw
chicken from you guys um
and and and all kinds of other food but
they don't give a [\h__\h] about it so they
are really really picky
they are really picky
anyway
we're pretty much done so we are done
i'm just gonna take some nice photos of
this now
and um
as you know i'm i'm not in my usual
setup this is my laptop setup in my
kitchen so i will not be reading the
super chats here but what is my stream
tomorrow sims 4. so i should be able to
read them tomorrow we have sims 4
tomorrow
um i'll be playing with um at least a
council family and if possible also with
the myth family to celebrate
new year's eve
and then besides that i have two
announcements that you already know
about if you follow me on twitter but
on
wednesday first day on the new year's
day
at half past
7 00 p.m japanese standard time uh
so 9 30
a.m gmt plus one so my time
and
and i don't know how late it is in pst
maybe isn't it eight hours behind me so
it would be one half past 1 a.m
uh pst maybe maybe
i will be on the official whole life
channel the whole official live channel
has uh like a like a program that will
go on for like five six hours or so um
until like a little like a few hours
before midnight and then until like i
don't know one or two a.m after midnight
and i will be there for a portion of one
and a half hours the uh i think i did
the same thing last year i'm pretty sure
i did it's called today
and the award of the best like moments
in in that year
um
uh that will uh i'm one of the people
who will be there i think it's like four
four members and but throughout the
whole stream there's like different
sections and different members
participating and i'll be in that one
section for one and a half hours from
seven at jst half five seven pm
um
[Music]
yeah i was there last year and that's
why i recently
for no reason asked you guys for some
ideas for the best moments in hololens
in the past
one year
did you guys maybe guess that it would
be this thing again
because i asked you guys very obviously
but
um did you i knew it did you suspect it
that it would be for this purpose
no reason at all no no no no no no
just for myself yeah i just wanted to
re-re-watch these moments
i didn't
no callie will not be there it's me and
and two japanese members i think and one
id member so one en one ide i think
yeah i'm i'm really happy i get invited
you fell off your little bastard i'll
fix you later and i was i get invited to
these official programs quite a lot
recently there's there's a lot more
following um
in in january i think
and where you will be seeing me
i think it's because i speak fluent
japanese said
i am potential potential with the
entertainment skills
entertainment
and potential enders entertain
[Music]
yeah i'm really happy that i i tried my
best like i had this recording uh for
one of the one of the things that i said
that will be i think in january i had a
recording for that a while ago that was
like at 4am my time
um but i really wanted to do it so i was
like [\h__\h] it yeah
um
[Music]
who likes finger cracking
okay i'm done
oh yeah so anyway please come and check
out the the
best moment of 2021
award show
to see partially what i selected and
what the other members selected and i
think there's maybe also a section where
um the viewers can select
something maybe i'm not sure well it
will be japanese but
yeah but we will be watching moments and
i selected some moments from whole live
english streams as well
so those will be english
yeah
i hope um
i gave them like my selections and i
think those selections plus the ones
from the other members they'll put it in
a pot and then be like which one is best
and then they'll select
that i don't know how exactly they will
select it or or if they will show all of
everything that we all selected
uh but
but please look forward to
my moments that i have chosen to be the
best moments of 2021 although i'm sure
that there might be moments that are
better than the ones that i've selected
but i still like i couldn't think of it
or you guys couldn't think of it your
fault just kidding
so that will be i will be streaming
three times basically on the 31st so the
first one will be that official program
and then later i'll be having the was it
the clip reviews on my channel
i'll be having a kiara only moments clip
reviews
on my channel that i'm currently having
you guys send me clips for on twitter so
if you didn't know about that yet and
you're like i know about one moment that
i really liked in 2021 that i want kiara
to show
then go on twitter and then send me the
url there's a hashtag for it
which was
i forgot
chad probably knows
so i'll be doing that and then
in the evening the event that i am
organizing you're surely entertainment
and potential
presents to you is sponsored by kfb
let's write this one this guy
um
the the whole live english karaoke relay
new years relay um
yay
i did a really last minute i organized
the last minute because i was like
wouldn't it be nice if we did something
like that together
um because we're not doing anything else
like any collabs or so
i was like kind of want to do it so i
didn't expect everyone to participate
but in the end it turns out that
everyone's participating in whole life
english so
it's not that it's like a collab where
we're all there at the same time but
it's kind of a full collab as in it's a
full relay everyone's participating
so
everyone will be having a 45-minute slot
they can go a little bit over time if
they want because we have a 15-minute
break in between anyway so everybody's
allowed to
uh go on longer as long as they don't
overlap
and uh
yeah i'll be the first one i'll be the
top bubata because
you know i'm i'm the one who organizes
it so i feel like i need to be the one
to kick it off
getting kicking it off
as always
so i hope you guys will will see my
slots at least
and then please go on and watch the
others if you can
to support them
yes yes
it uh how long is it going i didn't look
how many hours is it total from
beginning to end did someone like
add it together
[Music]
did someone add it together perhaps
it's wait shouldn't it be 11 hours
because all 11 members participate and
it's uh
or is it 12 hours
i guess it's 12 hours is it 11 hours or
12 hours if everyone gets should it be
11 hours well it would be just 11 hours
why is it 12 hours for some people
should be 11 hours but then ame goes on
longer i had to add gouda at the end
because um uh i wanted amit to be at the
end because she has a kadelka anyway
that she already planned and i was like
okay it would be weird to have you
somewhere in the middle and then you
going on longer when all the others are
still doing it you know what i mean so
let's have amer at the end but then last
minute uh guda said i want to join too
so i was like hmm how do i do this now
oh okay then you go at the end um there
will be a little bit of an announcement
at the end of it
uh and and it will be in the last stream
so now it will be on good stream uh the
announcement the announcement is
regarding all of us
so you might wanna
keep your ears open or your eyes open
for that
even if you miss it you'll probably most
likely see it afterwards on twitter or
on and anyway somewhere
yeah don't worry it's not merchandise
don't worry
don't worry okay
no no no
there is currently other merchandise on
sale though for for a short time of a
period of time if you want to get the
the party dress uh merchandise it will
be
uh on sale for a little while longer a
little while longer so get it before
it's gone if you want it the the party
party outfit merchandise um
yeah so that will be the 31st and i will
take the rest of the day off to
watch more of the spanish princess
for today
so i hope everyone enjoyed this stream
it was a very special stream we usually
don't do um stuff like this i'm always
happy to be able to show you guys a
little bit more special streams i hope
you enjoyed it
oh
[Music]
i think the sneeze is coming back
oh no no it's just leaving me again oh
why you do this to me
thank you everybody for watching thank
you i'll put up a photo on twitter what
did you see in the chat idw
well what did that mean someone in the
chat wrote something of idw am i going
crazy
is for jen already coming no [\h__\h] way
someone write them
like i know nothing
i know absolutely nothing what maybe i i
saw something wrong or you meant
something else
no wouldn't it be too early
i'd be gen free
[Music]
no they opened auditions like a while
ago
okay i might have seen something
different
in the chat
[Music]
chat's spoilering me
thank you for this nintendo thank you
for watching
thank you for spending your time with me
maybe i motivated you guys to make a
beautiful gingerbread house as well
uh
yeah maybe you guys got motivated and
inspired to do this too
hey
[Music]
it was fun making and and i gotta say
the dough wasn't very difficult but like
my mom made it because like she has
really strong hands and she was we
didn't even use the kitchenaid for it
she just used her and she was like wow
wow wow
and and made a beautiful dough and it
turned out like this perfect
absolutely perfect
but i put in the ingredients and i
bought the ingredients and i said which
ingredients come in and i put them in
and then she was she was kneading it
like a cat like a very strong cat
yeah it looked very difficult because
the the the
dough became like so thick and so
that only my kitchenaid or my mom could
have done it so
i'm really thankful for the help and
then we rolled it out with the with the
roller and then i made the shapes out of
it and then i put it into the oven after
two days
and i actually i actually s jitsu
actually we made too much and i have a
ball of this size which would be enough
to make another house i have a ball of
this size in my freezer now because mom
said to put it in the freezer i can use
it next year she said
one year later
i'll be having the same dough
nah i probably throw it out till then
[Music]
not
i could make a second house yeah i'm set
for next year's stream
i guess so
you're scared that the house will break
by my ancestors no
no no i ain't no problem oh no problem
oh no
okay everybody thank you for watching
and in german we say
i'll
[Music]
yay
ta
[Music]
bum
you