DET [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
DET [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] A [Music] [Music] [Music]
DETDET [
Music]
DET [
Music] [
Music]
N
[Music]
DET
[  Music]
[Music]
DET
[
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] DET [Music] [Music] DET [
Music] [Music]
N [
Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
DETDET
[  Music]
[Music]
A
BM ready
Good morning
[Music]
Hello Welcome to
[Applause]
You
forsee
[Music]
EL
likeThankyouGUfor
andouwith
TE  Chim chim chim chim chim chim chim chim chim chim chim chimu chimu gather
together
[applause]
have
[music]
[applause]
[music] [applause]
[music]
andWhatisyourteam
namehave
TE
think
teyyou
Good do your best
[Music]
isTeamname
IYouEnjoy
[Music]
todaybethewinners
Do your best
[Music]
Tethan
Papa
[Music]
Ki Mochi Mochi Mochi Mochi Kochi
Kochi
Who is your team in the sky?
Hey, self-introduction  Yes,
self-introduction, self-introduction, self-care. Sorry,
what's that team name? Yes, that's it.
Wow, please look forward to today. I
guess I'll enjoy it. Yeah, here, here,
okay. Okay, okay, how's that team preparing for that?  Oh, you're almost there,
right? You
can do that picture, ah,
try your best. Llama, you're already good at it. You're good at it, you're good at it. You'll win.
Yeah, and those clothes and costumes are
so cute.  Hey,
Indonesian uniform, maybe. Clothes, Done's clothes. They
look good on
Sasato. [Music] You're cute. Do your best. I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best. I wonder if it's next. Hello. Nya, hello, hello.
[Music]  Let's
do our best TE
[Laughs]
Halo
[Music]
goooooo
herbal
asmenykarHARGsendi
UNSARA
[Music]
so
guyskitakurang
satuiITUkita
treasureHsothefirst
GAMEwillbetreasure
huntsTherewillbe
aroundSPOT
[Music]
so yeah have
aroundforalso
alsoThereishint
Aroundthearethatyou
Find treasure around Bob Inside Silka Inside
Tess Might be inside Hopper too
Good luck  Please
[Music]
OKONE
OneTimetimeforHthe
trewillbe
10 It's only slow,
10 minutes
[Music]
[Applause]
Stand
Hold up, you're so good, you're such a senpai, you're so serious, you're
such a fool.
[Laughs]
[Music]
Hey,
do your
best, where should I press that button?
Thank you for your hard work, too.
]
Te onlyup
[Music]
Oh, I don't know what that is.
[Music] Naknow
Good luck
.
[Laughter]
[Music]
That's it, no, no.
tem
[Music]
harb
[Laughter]
[Music]
rutBlockBLNoWenot
supposed to BREAK
Block
[Laughter]
Oh, good luck  I found a button,
but I don't really understand what it is.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] I'm trying to
laugh at it, but it's not that.
DI
[Laughs] I
feel like it was there, but it wasn't that. I
guess that's it.  This is really
lol lol It's the focus of being here
3 It's this red flower, but I guess I got it right
But it's
8 Good luck! Ah, this is A,
but it's not this.
Hey, what is this human?
Wait and watch
[Music] I
think there's another button around here that
wasn't the one
over there. Where is it? It
looks like there's a Silca box. It should be easy to understand if it's Silca.
Hey, let's go around for a bit.
[Music]
Yeah, I don't know, but I already have the emeralds, so let's play.
Oh, I don't know. It looks like there's no slip-up.
[Music] We
need teamwork, yeah, we
have to work together.  Let's
have fun [Music] Simultaneous press switch [Music] Kachi Shiwa Ao [Music] NoILS I Oh Godoh GOD Oi Iru [Music] gampanggampangOhiya sudah diiludahdiambilo
S [Music]
urinfinish
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
AR
NIBRA
I
[  [Music]
FriendIlovelovei
[Music]
Iwanttock
Her
knowyouguysyouguys
Find
anyar
[Music]
NothereONECloseby
It's okay, it's
okay, it's okay [
Music] It's okay [
Music] [Music]
Yoo
[Music]
How
guys
[Music]
anyYES
jegjeg
[Music]
[Laughter]
Ptake
[Music]
ATTpleas yes Okthank
youthankyouforATTWe
already done the
treasureHSowehaveto
goback
andtotheSIMONsay
[Music]
Let's go inside
pasang
DIADIA
sudah [Music
]
NokokK
kerSD
[Laughter]
[Music]
Ah
HEverybodyareyou
guys
[Music]
AllWho
think next fly
and
[Music]
That's it, it's decided, it's decided
It
's okay, it's okay, it's okay
[Music]  [Music]
Okay, so I made the
rules. One more time.
[Music]
One
more time.
[Music]
Bevel.
All emeralds. Emeralds.
Emeralds. There are emeralds, but if we keep winning.  It
goes on and on, but if
I get that question wrong or that fourth question, I guess that's it.
[Music]
So get ready, let's do our best.
Oh,
then let's get started
.
Oh, I see. Yeah, yeah, other
voices from that group.  That's why I'm making it
right now. Where's that group?
Daimonses' push and groove, ah Simon, Seis's, oh wait, wait, O go,
wait, wait, I'm excited, I'm excited, it's okay, it's like
practice, then it's going to start. It's going to start.
Okay, level 1, okay.
[Music] Wanwa yes buanun uh buan o buan Rampa sorry one more time please Hey hey O then you said Lepareparempar Okay Lempal yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah right uh yeah Don't say this volball ball [Music]
ONE
[  [Music]
Twang
Parampa
Jinji Rampa
Rampa
Nai nice nice like 3
Era
Next Next
Rampa Jin
Korapa Ronpa Majdoa Karimaju Door Kariooo Owa Repare
Jinko
Ronpa Majido Majido wa Owa
Waa Next
Next Next It's going to be long This is going to be long  It's
going to be long. I forgot about the previous one, so next time. Um,
Repa
Jinko
Ronpa.
Oh, hit, hit, hit, oh, it's strong, it's strong, it's strong, it's strong, it's strong, it's strong, it's strong, it's strong.
[Music]
Deya motte yaa oi
Osenkyu Senkyu
Senkyu ja voice group
chat to group chat to get out of group chat ka ani
ania
[Music]
nice
thethinkthinkStand
InTheforStandthan
[Music]
Ah BlindapparentlyOK
sotherleislikeexpl
duringthepracticeso
youguyswillbewillbe
given
progressivecomm
[Applause]
[Music]
oneofyou
failDotime
thefirst
ONE
LtwooneletgoHowIn
Thisgame
[Music]
har
OKOKyouyoutake
backokayOKNEXT
nextyouguysareright
soNextOneis
lempar
johnkTHtwoone
GoingGoingNEXT
LAMPLP32
ONE
Going
FGEHNEXTisLjoh
Ronpamagidore
Kali
Susto
Ah Ah Ah
Ah
[Laughter]
GU
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
for
[  [Music] [
Music] Momo is
okay, okay Stand
[Music]
areyouare
youwillbe
Easy
Slowlywill
give
3GO
NEXTOkOk NEXTNEXT is
johone ONE knowNEXTNEXT
[Music] NEXTNEXTNEXT I don't remember NEXT
]
ONE
LP
right
TurnI
meanasTurn
Rightas
Turn
[Music]
MINGmeans
thattheway
[Music]
same
are
[Music]
ront
okokokokR
like
hadseeup
RunNo
Worrycompliasguys
think
ONT
[Laughs]
BlockAreyoureadyfor
thefirst
onethefirstONEgoing
totellyouis
L3twoone
[Music]
NEXT
WayMOVonMOVONTHE
SECONDONEisL
joh32
[Music]
ONE
backthethd
onetwoone
HNEXT
is32
NEXTGoing
StrongGoingStrong
NEXT
lokKIThreetwoone [
Music] [Laughter] [
Music]
GoingStrongNextOne
is
okp
MA
kiantwoone
GoingStrongGoing
evenStrongerNext
Onelok [Music]
hadapKI
hadapan
[Music] Mtwo [Music] one [Applause]
[Music]
WOKNEXT
NEXT
KI
mul
Kone
[Music]
KukuGUforNextOne
NEXTNEXTGet
positionRPleasethan
younextONE lkp
majuKI Pa
ThreeTwo [
Music] [Music
]
OneLastOneLastOne
LastOne
[Music]
LASTTHE
LAST
GO jkp
majuhadapKI
hadapanmund
Block
mer
Three
two
[Music]
oneOU
byidso
apparently
ARMforg
[Music]
Oto
Thankyouthanyou
thank
[Music]
youis
[Laughter]
Oh Ihave
[Music]
is
the
[Music]
upthanOKAreyouready
CanIJustGiveYouThe
commNowYesOKsoevery
EveryTimethecommand
finyouGUGetBackto
theRBlockandPiupany
youOKthefirst
One2ONE
Easymovingonmoving
on
NEXTJThreetwo
oneNext
One
LPjoh
LP3two
[Music]
oneI
NEXT
Repazin
Pama
DU3to
[Music]  ]
one
NEXT Lapa
J
jongkokLP
majuhadapKIThreetwo
one
[Music]
[Laughter]
back
YouNextOneNextOne
Herewego lar
Kone
[Music]
apparentknow
Do
[Applause]
[Music]
Hey, have you
practiced already?  Did you
do that? Yes, that's good.
Please stand up with the red block
here. Yes, yes, yes, please stand here. Are you ready? Get
ready. Okay, let's
get started. Let's do our best. Let's do our best. Let's start. Let's go!
Let's wait!  Wait and
think about it
Leparepatri
Lele
[Music]
Next next next is uh Renjon
Wago next next
Rampa
Jonko
Romper 3
[Music]
Wago next next O
Rampar
Jonko
Ronpa Majdo Akari 3
Towa
Go Oh
Yes next
Next  Next time Not yet Not yet Not yet Not
yet There's still There's still Not yet Money's not here
Okay, next time, uh,
Lepa
Jonko
Ronpa
Maha
Towa
Gomu uh, this, this, this,
this
[Music]
a
l Hakirihad
Kanan  Three
tow,
go to the baron,
go to the right from here.  Like, I'm not naked. Is it like this? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
No, here, here
[Music] It's
a bit far away,
oh, oh, okay, Kakabo Kabo, here, here,
here, yes, here [
Music]
Bonk, here,
dying
[Music]
Nh, let's do it
here, Nni
build
[Music]
Yo, this is uh
[Music]  [Music]
[Music]
biara
Um, we're gonna be in a group
EXPeveryhasminut
eachandWewillbeat
thetime Um, we
'll do it together
Um, howsay at the same time at the same time
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah minute  Let
's do it, then wait in a minute, um, please
write it in your book. Yeah, yeah, please
write your answer in your book. And Mr. Builder,
um, here's the answer.
[Music]
[Music]  ]
If the answer is yes, please don't shout. Do
n't say it. Write it in a book.
[Music]
Please, look at me, Aja-san.
Don't do that theme page over there.
[Music] [Music
]
[Music]  ] It's
okay if you don't have to wait a minute,
so I
looked at the two of you and I
looked at
you too. Look, there's a skull on this.
[Music]
So what should we do?  I do
n't know if it's okay to leave it as it is. I don't know what to do, so
please stand still. There's a
second one. There is a second one.  2nd thing is
squirrel
senpai is new so I'm
going to take a look at it now
Wait a minute, uh, I'm going to check it out for a second
Hey, please take a look
Oh yeah, where's the chit chat?  I
guess it's just that now I don't
have a problem anymore
[Music]
I don't have anything
[Music] I wonder
if hints are allowed [Music] This is
bad [Music]
[Music]
Ooh [Music] Ooh, I'm going to ask you a question.
Yeah yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
Good luck, good luck, good luck,
good luck If you have any questions, let me know
Good luck
[Music]
Yes, yes, yes, good luck, good luck, good luck [
Music] [
Music]
Good luck,
good luck
[Music]  ]
Hey, do your best, do your best
[Music]
Te game
Stein, then it's going to
start It's starting, it's starting, do your best, it's starting It's starting Hoi Hoi Hoi it's
starting Just one minute it's
starting It's starting Alright alright
Alright Ama
[laughter]
Kita
[Music]
MajustBel
Chia  Well
[Music]
Hey, nyan, nya, it's all over
, it's so cute, I
wrote it, I wrote it, I
changed it, I wrote it, I'm going to check if it's okay Yo,
thank you for this
and
thank you, hey,
it's good, it's good, it's good  Hey, it's
spinning, it's spinning, it's nice. I'll
check it. Okay, okay. [Music] Okay, I checked. I
checked.
[Music]
Okay, yes, I checked.
for
[Music]
BUCK
[  [Music]
Camille
Beer Next Next
Kandekan De
Preparation
[Music]
Jijieto willconfSkate
CheerswhatIwill
confiscateCheers
THANK
YOU
NOwhatthe
[Music]
fuckyouknowYouYou
SORRYSORRY
[Music]
Oh no de da yo
Suisui
I
PE
[Music]
Oh yeah  permipermi
Good luck
[Music]
[Music] It's so good
! ThislikePIDPID
this
[Music]
iest
Okay for
forGU
[Music]
me
Well, let's take a look at it
Oh, it's nice
[Music] That's right,
that's right  So, you're good at it. I'm so
happy. It's too heavy. Biddy is good. You've
done it. You've done it. You've done it. You've done it. You've done it. [Music]
[Applause] Next Next Next Next
Next Toddle
[Music]
1than
[Music]  ]
[Music]
Ta
Do
your best
Hey,
you'll do your best You'll do your
best I do
n't know why this is happening I don't know ThislikeanEG
Good luck thisalsolikean
EGThisisa3DATT
Good luck
[Music]
You
know I'll get better I'll
get better
What is this? It
looks delicious.
Okay,
now [music] Good luck, cute. This looks like an egg.
[Laughs]
Good luck, everyone.
[music]
[music] I'm going to
keep watching it. Oh, are
you done yet?  It's
amazing,
yeah,
isn't it a great telepath? Yeah, yeah, it's
amazing, it's amazing, it's
amazing.  Alright, alright, gabo, everyone gabo, gabo,
te lady,
yoya
[music] Let's go
Mario, it
's starting, it's starting, amaru is
starting
You're a genius, you're a genius, you
're a genius. This is similar. This is a genius. You're a genius. Dore-senpai is amazing. You're a genius. Do
your best. Let's go home.  You
might not have the talent to be good,
good,
OK. Genius is amazing. Genius. That's amazing. That's amazing. That's amazing. That's amazing. That's amazing. That's amazing. That's amazing. That's amazing. Do your best.
[Music]
Hey
Sutams Time Osw Tata
[Music]
[  Music]
Neya
A
[Music]
Indonesia Ran [
Music] Malachi Indonesia Gui [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] Nakane feel [
Music]
BadIfeelBadbecause
Thereisalwaysalotof
stuffhappentoPA
nashiandIhopeandI
hope
[Music]
TheyDENDENHoldHold
grchOnUS
look
[Music]  ]
Superwiththe
timeF
in
Indonesia
What Godzilla is this?  It
's no use
[Music]
[Music] OK OK OK OK I
understand it's so amazingly amazingly easy to understand
what is easy, it's easy.
[Music]
OKKAMmangantidak
mengakuiLetLetCheckOUTTheglasses quick
JJJ No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
[music]
]
Wani Wani
Piro Wani Piro
nextbodyseenthe
[Music]
I
[Music] Let's
start
Kopira I
[Music] I
can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do
it  I do
n't know, it's difficult.
This is oh, this is, oh, this is mine.  niwa
[music] ni lala litre mata desu
this is toms mata ga
KAtams
mgu
NDIA
anj
ITUE
jegDEN
[music]
BLZG
glesman
BU
akdasiak oni wa ani
[music] Gaiya
hi
[music]
hell mitoo meat please
OK
every defun mimu defun oh no
no
mimu everyone mu
neasosomi
OKeveryonethanyouso
forplayingThisgame
Wemvetothenext
GAMEAWRWSowehave3
minutestoplaywith
TeameveryeachROUND
GotFIVEemeralThere will beROUNDSoLetgo tothe [music]  I haven't
done it yet. Where's everyone? Where
's where they've gone? Where's my Ella-senpai? My legs are
fine. I've gone too far. I've gone too far.
Where's the wool now?  I'm on the wool,
right? It's up, right? Where's
the bed? It's down there. The bed is sticky at the bottom. Hey, where are you
? You
're on the second floor of Wool. Oh, here.  I'm
not here, but I'm
here. Where's the bed
? It's downstairs
. Yes, it's white here. Thank you. I
fell asleep.
[Music]
Oh, will
be3.
Will
be
None.  And this is it,
Battle
bleby
GoingGoing
atandforthe
CUTTERarePress
[Music]  It's
forbidden to squat, right
now.
[Music]
PeoplePeople
I'm sorry,
but it's okay to hit me.
[Music]
What color is it?
[Music] It
's
okay, Ajaka, but in Kana.  Are you okay?
If you're going to try hard, then I'll change. It's
okay. I will Change place for this ROUND.
OK, I'll change my place for this ROUND. Ok, I'll do my best. Thank you,
everyone. Good
luck. Bye-bye, Baba-bye Biles. If it's big somewhere, then it's either up or down.
What
color is it? If it's the same, then it's the same. If it's the same, then it's
pink, pink, pink. It wasn't this color,
but is this okay? Yes, yes,
yes, oh, do your best, Kanade-chan, do your best. Yes, you
can hit me.
Okay,
off. Can I see what your
col?
isokkuisYELL, show your colors
[Music]
Leo, tell me
It's okay without that request
[Music]
GrePINKYisgrepink
YELL
[Music]
and
isYGreenandPINKOUT
ONEBR
[Music]
Yeah,
disbanded in BC
[Music]
Good luck
Canaris is cute, pretty,
pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty.
Ha, it's
pretty, it's pretty, it's
pretty, it's pretty cute
Ogoa 5 is 5 I
can't do that.
That
's red. Oh, it's red
. Oh, that's it.
Oh, that fell. Who fell on that? Yoshifu, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's
okay.
Do your best.  It's okay.
[Music] You
did your best. It's
okay
. Next time, next time.
[
Music] There's a lot of greenery. [Music]
Do your best.
[Music]
[Applause]
Next time, do your best.  Do
your best,
do your best,
do your best Yes,
do your best [Music] Yes, do your best
[Music] [Music] Do your best [Music]
[Music]
Do your best I'll
do my best I'll
try my best I'll try my best
[Music] Are you
okay? Are you okay?  It's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
[Music]
Keep moving! The
staff members who are still left are
no good.
[Music]
Green is strong
[Applause]
Brown is slow, but
BR
[Music]
OK
[Music] They're
quite the enemy
[Music]
Nice,
amazing
[Applause]
[Music]
So strong, so strong
ELL
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]
Kukuku
There are so many emeralds
[Music] It's fun to
work hard, it's fun, it's fun
Ah, there are so many emeralds  There's so much to
change about that macaque and sword and stuff like that.
[Music] Good
luck
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I
'll give you my all. [Music] F 3 Where's the red? Where's the red?
[Music]
To
Who fell
[Music]
[Applause]
Nana Nana Nice Nice
Nice Nice Nice
[Music] No
Naina,
do your best,
try your best
[Music] You
can go to Pink
[Music] Wow, there's
so
much left  I'm still there. It's
amazing. No, it's
okay. You've
done a great job. [Music] [Music] [Music] You did great. [Music] You did great. You did a great job. Well done. You're the
last one to survive.
[Music]
That's
great.
[Music]  ]
Awesome
[Music] I guess I'll
go to the strong bottom.
Down here
[Music]
Then, uh, I'll choose a bed, and then I'll put
all my luggage here. I'll put my other luggage here.
Emerald
will be fine. Emerald
will use some kind of item.
[Music] I'll
wait a little while for the rice to come
.
[Music]
What's that? [
Music]
Tade-
chan
[Music]
Mao
, what kind of items do you
want? How about money?
303434 [Music
]  [Music]
What should I do?30
Maybe
[Music]
Kenken Ton
Stonestone SwordSword Yeah Yeah Yeah
Stone Sword
is
[Music]
And Shield Shield I want a shield What kind of potion is
used
by Fashi
to Fai
What kind of potion is it?  Ah, as for
potions,
invisible potions,
etc. Yeah, yeah, yeah, it
's only 3 minutes, but if it's long enough, I'll buy it.Well
then, I
want Fightin Fightin or Navigate, which one do I want?  I don't think
I'm good at gates.
[Music] I
see.
VC, that group, BC. I'll
go in. Well, if I'm navigating,
that's Anobo, Arrow, and Schild. [
Music]
Ino.
[Music] Let's
go in here.  Is Ax okay
?
Shopping
? Opika
wouldlikeONE
SWORD
Shioha
[Music]
If
you wait, I'll do my best. I'm kind of lost,
Easy Easy,
Easy, I'm lost
[Music]
Hey, it's okay, it's okay
Navigator
Oh, yeah, yeah  Yes,
those who believe, yes, those who believe,
Sword and Stone, probably Ax.
Ax is stronger, right? Do you
want Stone Ax and potion? Stone
Ax, and yes, potion
. But in Kana, Bo and Arrow are Bo Arrow,
Shield, Hmm, body.  I guess I don't need a shield.
Well then, that 10 Aro is 3
from Emerald.
I want 1 stack, so 1
stack is Let's go to the 1st stack. It
might be impossible. It's too much. What's that
10 low 10?  Yes,
yes, I think 30 Arrow is good. If I use 3030 Aro, I'll
use about 15 here.
With 30 Aro, 9 Eri-senpai can also use a shield.
Or maybe I can't use a shield. Then I
can't drink potions.  Is it true
? The potion is probably the last one. Yeah, yeah.
Well, first of all, I'm going to buy Bo, Arrow, and Ax.
And the remaining money I'll
probably change as I buy more potions.
[Music]
I want Chopin Shoppin.  I don't
have a pin yet, I don't have a pin, I don't
have a pin yet, I still have to wait a minute, I
don't want to go shopping again, I'm sorry, I want shopping.  I
think
it's just one, uh, give me the money, oh, I'll
take it
[Music]
Oh, give me the money,
give me the money,
please.  I got it.
How much money do you have left? I have 12 of them,
so I guess I can buy a potion. I
think a potion would be good. Or a shield, or something like that. I think a
fi-fi shield would be good.  I think
so. Okay, I'll give you a shield.
Yes, one shield, one shield, please.
Ao,
hey, the money left is 5. I have 5 emeralds
left. If it's 5, I think Arrow will be fine.
Yes.  Ah, do you want Arrow? Yes,
10. Okay, give me 10.
Yes, this is
it. Q. Okay, let's go.
Oh,
but do you have more 46? I
think I probably bought 50, but yeah, 46.
What 46
would Arrow be? From here.  Ade-
chan, please take that VC from me.
What VC? Ah
yes, it's okay. I've already done it. Yes, then, who is this here?
Yes, my body
picked it up. What did I pick up from my senior? There are a lot of arrows.
Yes, there are too many arrows and someone picked them up.
46 Yeah, who is 6
? Who's who?
[Music]
Well, it's pretty good. It's my
fault. I wonder if Ol' VC will be included. Should I
join? Yes.
All shigAll Youallyouisdependon fighte
ifnaig
Navigatorbeideofthe
tempFightwithand
AR
have
Kill
EnemyitemsFall  If you
defeat it and the item
drops, you can take it.It's the enemy's
item.Oh,
and if the Navi dies, the Navi
won't talk.It's okay to fight, but if the
person fighting dies, that's it.  The game
is over. It feels like it's over. If you fall, you
can't talk. You can't talk. The
game is over.
[Music]
Can I get some food?
Satade-chan, um, I'm going to create a group chat. I
guess I have to take it. Then
[Music]
Eh,
okay, wait a minute. No, I don't think I can hear you.
Yeah, wait a minute,
I muted it.
Which tower should I be in? Maybe
we'll come and wait. Not now, maybe not now.
Because those three teams. Yeah, yeah,
we like them. I
see. I'll be watching from here.
Maybe it's from here, that way,
or from here, okay, it's easier to see this way, right? Well then, is it okay from here?
Hello, um, Kanade-chan, here, here, over here, over
there, that's just that staff
staff
[Music]
Just here or right here.
Oh wow, that's amazing
. I
don't think anyone's right now. It's Hine Chimu
and Inaina's Ina and Aanyan.
Who can
fight?
Wow, I'm
excited. I'm so excited.
Wow. And those other navigators are
sold out.  It's okay, okay, I'll
kill you, yeah, yeah, that
's right, that's far away. It's a little far away.
Hey, everyone's far away
Yeah, yeah, it's falling, it's falling,
uhm, I'm
falling,
oh, yeah, I'm falling.
Yes, look, I'll show you
around. Thank you, thank you.
What happened? The
bread is wrong. It wasn't my body that dropped it.
Okay, wow, it's strong. It's heading towards the fire. It's
strong and it's progressing. Yeah, it's
strong.
[Music]
It's awesome, it's great, it's great, it's great
.  Someone is coming and fighting all over the place.
Yeah, I
can't see it, but I can see it from here. I'm
eating my food.
Oh, wow, do your best.
Ah, what a shame. Wow, Reine
won. Reine-senpai won.
Amazing, I can fight with Su-senpai.  Yes,
yes, yes, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I
'll do my best.Okay, let's
go to the bed.Yes,
let's go, Nect, let's go.Then, I
think the place should be red.Here, the
red one is this one.Maybe this one, yeah, yeah,
okay
.  No, I
don't know if it's here or there. I don't know if it's here or there.
Where is Kaade-chan?
[Music]
Oh, where are we
? Can we decide
where we are?
Mochimochi Okay, okay, I'll wait here.
Ai, definitely. Yellow, blue, squirrel, Kanade, Pink. Where's pink? Pink, pink, pink. Maybe it's here. Pink, yeah, there's definitely no pink. Pink,
yellow, blue, maybe
pink. Okay, red, maybe red.  Aka, that's good. Yay, I'll
do my
best. I'll do my best.
Watch this.
[Music] I'll
do my best. I wonder
where you are.
Everyone doesn't have to press F1 on the navigator.
Yeah, that's right. I'll do F1. Oh, I'll do F1. Wow. It's
difficult. Maybe
this is it.  I feel like I shouldn't have done that.
Fighters are okay, fighters are okay, yeah yeah.
So, I'm Jinbi, okay?
Hey, okay, okay, okay, okay.
[Music]
Lady,
okay, let's go. I'm excited and excited. F1 is okay. So I
'll do my best. This is Kuni-senpai.  It's about
to start, I don't want to start, maybe it's not
yet, it's still a long way
[Music] Is it okay to start yet
? I'm going Tedakadakahihihi I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm running away.  I'm lost here. Oh, I'm lost. No
, it's okay, it's
okay. I think it's okay. It's hard. I
think everyone is pretty strong too. They're not coming out.
Why,
why? Run away. Come on. Why? Run away. Hey, I'm
fighting. The
power used by the shield is smart, smart.
Oh, [ __ ], I'm a little stuck. Neeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Okay, I can't see where it is. Ah, I can't see where it is. I
can see
it. I can see it. I can see it. I can't see it. I can't
wait.
What's going on here? It's
moving
so
well. It's so bad. It's so strong. It's so
strong.  Too much
[Music] It's
bad, I
can't hit it at all
Choneku Ku It's
too
far away It's difficult Wow, haha,
try your best Wow, I can't hit that part I can do my best, okay Wow, I'm
using a potion that doesn't have a potion
But that's the one on the right, it's
so close  Oh, I'm running away, I can see you, I'm running away, I'm
running away, I'm running away
[Music] I
can see that armor,
back, back, back
, ah, I can see it, ah, I'm sorry, I
hit you, it's okay, it's okay
, it's okay, I can see it, I can see it, do your best,
try your best
Wow, I'm shaking.
Shaking is amazing.
Shaking, ah, tension, tension,
oh yeah. Well, I've got this much,
so maybe I'll give it to you. Okay, oh, oh, oh,
so much now.  Yes, there's the sword. Let's
do this too.
[Music]
Well then, it's the finale. Yes, the two of us will fight. Yes, yes, yes, we'll do our best with 22 pieces. Yes, we'll do our best with 22 pieces.
Group: Oh, you're green, yeah, yeah,
yeah.
[Music]
This is gray, this is gray, and here it's red, and that's
green, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I
can't really see the color over here, well, it's far away, yeah,
yeah, I can't even use the navigator here, right?
If it's in the middle,
maybe I can do it.  I
see, it's
better to be as close to the red as possible.Easy to hit is
easy to hit, but if you don't progress, you wo
n't be able to fight.Thank you,
welcome, panniers, panniers, wow, lady, lady, lady, wow,
scary, scary, wow, it's okay, you can go, you can go, yes.  I
'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best. Who am I?
Who is my partner? I ca
n't see your name. I'm sure you didn't have a buff. Oh
Reine Reine. Where is that? Reine. I ca
n't see you. I can't see you. Reine is Reine's
place.  But I'm still waiting for my whereabouts Yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, right here, we're here, we're here,
all the way to the middle [music], there's
a lot of oh, oh, they're coming, they're coming, they're coming, they're coming, oh, oh, yellow, yeah, yeah, yeah, uh, from purple, ah, I can see it, it's a little bit, it's a little bit.
Hey,
yo, wow,
hey, this is wow, and
I'm already in the middle, but here it is. Wow, this is dangerous. Oh, I'm still at Apple. It's so
far away.
Fight
and do your best, Ei-senpai. You
did nothing. You
did it. It's amazing.
[Music]
Pa-yuusha-
ya. Yaya! Squirrel-
senpai was too strong. This is strong.
Well, let's do a group voice.  Shall we
go? Yes, yes.
Congratulations.
Thank you. Congratulations. Congratulations. Congratulations.
[Music] forbeone [Music] of after forforthe Hey hey hey, hey, no thanks!
Yes Yes, I
sleep
sleep I'm sleeping. Sleep sleep Yes, slip slip
slip
slip OK
, if you take a picture, it's
still there, so it's still distributed.
After that, I'm going to
go outside.
[Music]
Wait,
wait, here, here, here, here, here, here, here,
here, here,
now, now, let's
go,
okay,
wait,
here, here, here
.  [Music] [
Music]
Yes, it might be okay here or there. It might be
okay if it's over there. Yes, it's
okay.
[Laughs] Let's
take another photo
Otwa
go
ee
[Music]
Kiwa
Thank you, thank you, thank you for your hard work.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I'm
jealous
so jealous [Music] Thank you
for
what the
How
[Music] the GUmeputthe [Music]
music]
indindonesia
F
SAmethe
[music]
GU
pleas
S
mayyou
knowwill
in
guyscoun
DownONE
[laughing]
[music]
mzzcounDowncoun
Downcoundown
ma
[music]
GUin
SATU
[music  ] [
Music] [
Music] na toang
toangtokangkangsail
[Music]
KJBU
JIA
[Music]
La [Music] [Music] [
Applause] Pa
Singdar
jaiDUEKnangbaung
diwangnangbatisKUNG
diwangamparpisang
pisang KUmasak saiimasak
saii
ariang
ariAR
[Music] [
Applause]
guys
[Music]
ー
La
la rabuka
pinto ibuca
pinto
kapin Besra's woman's pot
taani pick up tapantira nya
pinto ga
tira
paci
utapan
as
so
[music]
[clap]
guys
uwaalko
pasa
[music]
n
[  [Music]
Rupama
[Music]
Sari
Poko
[Music]
Erema ni deinai yatena yapparishi
na muwa sorore hayani
PERmusim
SOL
[Music]
PERRatMU
Rmusic
PER
key Wow wow wow wow wow san
ni to
Kankanta
[Music]
Heto
ni
[Music]
Jira thank you
everyand
you
GUdid
[Music] Is
GR a hologram? Oh
wait,
what is it?  [
Music]
nafushi
hororai
life se
ha malaibu e
sryso
[laughing]
[music]
V
hitam
guys PM
what is it 5
[music]
PM official channel
yaatsu
anpan no no no no no Osbye bye
ne
[music]
popipopipo
papipo
[music]  Music] Poppopopopipo Papipa Papi Papapi Papi Papi Papi Papi Papi Papi Papipapipapipapipapipipapipipapipipapipipipipip Pipipipipip Pipipipipip Pipipipipopopipopipopipopopipopopopipip Pipipi Pipipipipipipip Pipipipipipip Pipipipipipipip Pipipipipipipip Papipapipapipapipipipipipipipapipipapipipipipipip
Papapi Papi
Papi Papapi Papi Papi Papi Papi Papi Papipi Papi Papipa Papipa Papapi Papipa Papipa
Papipa Papapipapipapipipipipipipipipi
[Music]
BANGBANGKUN