foreign
[Music]
hi hi hi
I'm nervous
I I actually like
um
fights a couple of people
but before that
I'm gonna introduce myself
foreign
[Music]
I I have I have a video
uh incoming because
apparently the person who
who actually wanted to call uh she
doesn't have time
so
yeah yeah there's a video we just like
go straight into the video
thank you thank you
okay now so
um
why I'm so nervous right now
oh my God I'm so nervous right now
after this
okay let's play the video
it's from I'm gonna I'm gonna
it's from thinking
mom
bye
-bye
[Music]
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday to you
soon
[Music]
how you wanted to get to know me better
it is hard for me to be brave
um
what I would like to play more with you
me too
thank you happy birthday
[Music]
thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
I was
that was really really
I really want to play with you too you
know I really want to play with you too
so
foreign
[Laughter]
no
thank you
let's let's play again let's cook again
[Music]
yeah thank you thank you
wow it's really I've actually like
pretty
um
pretty pretty much
nervous
I am pretty much nervous about because
I'm gonna call Max who's gonna join the
call next you know
um
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
I have
I have lots lots lots
I wonder her snakes her snakes is gonna
be
happy
[Music]
no
what a shame
what is that one
a really really sad you know a really
really sad
I'll figure out it didn't have one
yeah
[Music]
hello hello
hello
[Music]
um
identity foreign
[Laughter]
the hollow life Indonesia
um
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
yeah yeah oh my god
[Music]
um
welcome
so
yeah and what did I hold on I want to
try
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
oh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah let's go let's go
because
[Laughter]
an idol not a comedian
s
hahaha
come on come on
not a comedy app yes yes
[Music]
thank you
happy birthday
guys
thank you
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
bye-bye
donations thank you
I pressed the wrong button on this one
like it
ah oh who's next
hello hello
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
I don't know
ah
um
[Music]
[Applause]
uh what do you like the most about Muna
hoshinova and tell me why okay tell me
why okay um
foreign
okay
perfect
thank you guys
foreign
[Music]
I'm fine
okay
[Laughter]
um yeah
okay yeah
happy birthday
Japanese
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
when you're welcome
eh eh
outside yellow
ah
mushy Mash
hello
[Music]
Indonesia
hello
[Music]
um
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
papaya
wow
[Music]
oh my God
um okay
okay
foreign
[Applause]
what is your first and last impressions
of Muna hashinova
first and last impression impression was
Impressions yeah
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
um
hi
thank you happy birthday to you
oh oh yeah origami oh
also Disney channel thank you
thank you for coming
yay happy birthday happy happy birthday
yeah thank you thank you for uh for
coming into my birthday
is
not comedian okay
yes comedian no no
comedian not comedian
oh the Best comedian okay
rolly
oh ready
ready okay ready okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
a nut oh a comedian
oh okay
best Comedia
oh yes
oh okay okay
happy birthday
okay
[Music]
laughs
[Laughter]
I didn't
[Music]
yay happy birthday
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you for coming to my birthday yeah
thank you I'm just watching you bird out
of your room but I'm standing here to
your room I'm here
can you hear me yeah I can I can hear
you very clearly yeah there is a window
bird so yeah yeah yeah I can hear ouch
I will okay okay come come come come
come yeah
[Music]
got it
go go
I'm blowing the window
thank you thank you actually it's a
little bit cold outside oh I'm sorry I'm
sorry
thank you for inviting me thank you for
coming to us thank you I uh I I'm really
really grateful that you have some time
for me to come this is this is our first
time talking in the Stream but yeah
we had a conversation in Japan yeah this
is the first time to have conversation
on live stream like this is the first
time yeah I'm very glad thank you thank
you
I I have a Rolex game do you want to
play with me
yeah I do but I'm a little bit scary oh
don't be scary okay come to Mama
let's go okay let's go because oh
what number oh well actually
um
uh I think it's it's special for for you
okay actually it's been it's been like a
couple a couple of uh people like doing
the day or two but I kind of want you to
go into their tree
is that okay
okay can you can you try to pretend to
be
like try your best to mimic Muna voice
all right okay it's okay I'm no I'm bad
at the pretending so like a hollow
member so bad so okay I tried it
where are you
I like Indonesia
I didn't know my voice was like that
maybe maybe next time I should I should
make the same like uh Muna I'm gonna
come into into everyone and everyone
become Muna hoshinova it's like it's
like
I see I see yeah can I make her can I
make a effort to pretend like you yes
yes you can
it's a kind of meal feel free to do that
I feel embarrassed first so but that was
quite good it's good actually yeah
everyone is safe it's okay
hahaha
[Laughter]
thank you
yeah thank you it is my best
performance yeah thank you you're my
best performance today
thank you thank you oh my God my my my
face hurt loud name thank you so much
for making my day
yeah thank you
have a good day and have a good year
this year yeah have a good day and have
a good day and hopefully
um you know I I wanna uh I wanna do many
things in Japan next time so please come
to Japan soon yeah I will I will I will
come to Japan soon all right let's um
maybe maybe next time if I go to Japan
again how about we eat go eat together
in some you know
some place that I never been through
oh right yeah but let's let's go to
together yeah
thank you
[Music]
bye bye
so Legend Disney
um
uh huh
my my
my
day I think English is really great you
know right yeah I was surprised at first
when I met her
in Japan she she would have a perfect
English
mm-hmm
wow
Riri
[Music]
her pronunciation is really good yeah
yeah her finances in this so good
so good
I don't I just it doesn't feel like hard
to understand oh
hello
hello happy birthday hello who are these
who are you what are you doing here
what's up guys it's Dr Gladiator hit
that assassin
's videos here
Luna's birthday today happy birthday
Muna thank you thank you thank you no
problem
it's Brian
all right if the birthday girl says so I
guess I'm Brian today I'll I'll be
buying this for today just for the
birthday girl I'll be Brian oh yeah yeah
yeah so
um Brian I mean Axel do you want to play
Rolex with me
yeah sure thing I I had a look at you
know all the questions and so I'm a bit
scared for sure thing you know no it's
not that scared
okay you know we can we can try it out
and see what I get okay
three two one
[Music]
oh please give me something easy
oh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
what's this
what oh
are you ready
what how do I do this okay so pretty
try your best to mimic my voice
that's easier
I have to sound like you right
essentially
for your best that's fine
and you feel a little bit cute
[Laughter]
it's it's remind me of some I don't know
some anime who is a man trying to be
like a girl I don't remember
oh
yeah
can you see donations thank you
or maybe thank you like that donations
thank you Super Chat thank you
[Laughter]
we only gotta have fun thank you so much
it's difficult you know
how's your how's your birthday so far
have you been having a good day I
actually having a really really good day
I sleep well
okay I eat well okay what are you gonna
what are you gonna have for like dinner
or what have you had already eat
uh I'm thinking about maybe a vegetable
soup
oh okay yeah I like to get double soup
no soup is good I like soups I don't
know why like back then I wasn't like a
big fan of soup
As I Grew Older I started liking soup
more and more I'm not too sure why but
soup is good soup is nice soup is like
um a really good option on anything it
is it really is yeah it's like a good
side dish to have with your main meal
and stuff yeah yeah anyways happy
birthday I hope you you know I hope you
get a lot of a lot of lovely wishes a
lot of a lot of lovely Super Chat from
you you know thank you lots of gifts I
hope you received so I know I wanted to
talk about this also I think I invited
you to like this you remember like at
the end of last year I think I invited
you to like a like a song project that I
was thinking about oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah when I get back to when I get back
to Australia I'm gonna start I'm gonna
start planning everything out once again
so uh please wait but it's a little
teaser for you know everyone who's here
today watching sure sure
yeah yes stay excited everyone yeah I
cannot wait happy birthday yes no
problem you're my me that I have a lot
of project incoming them oh don't worry
we all I think we all have a lot of
projects
we'll keep working hard but anyways just
for today have a you know nice day off
enjoy your birthday it's a great one
Muna thank you
yeah about that I think I haven't talked
because I forgot about that one oh what
oh god thank you for reminding me
Brian
oh
I need to follow up all of my project
sure yes
bro
[Music]
again
ah Ben
um
we have another videos guys we have
another video
incoming it's from
let's hear it
thank you happy birthday
thank you yay
[Music]
there there is
if you had a chance to meet Muna what
kind of activities
[Music]
if you could take one part of Muna what
would you take it
foreign
[Music]
anime
is an idol not a comedian yeah
okay
thank you
tell me two false facts and one truth
about yourself that no one knew uh two
false fact one of Truth
um
what's on Twitter how much you love Muna
like a simp
ly
happy birthday thank you enjoy enjoy
your birthday thank you
[Music]
oh yeah
yeah
that is a birthday call from Zeta
[Music]
and that is a vertical from Zeta
thank you
[Music]
she did she do all the roulette I did
to literally do all the roulette
literally
[Music]
thank you so much
oh God
yes yes finally
finally
I wonder I wonder if her snakes
[Music]
amashimashi
hello hello hello
Muna happy birthday
happy birthday
thank you
that's okay oh as soon as you said ha I
was I knew I was
[Laughter]
I have a present for you oh what is it
uh if it's to you bye I'm sorry but uh
hold on I'll send it to you
and then I send it
here you go yeah okay oh okay
oh
I'm sorry this is what my brain thought
of in 20 minutes I'm sorry
just in case in case you need extras
oh there is an x-rays
if you need any extras
um I give those to you
thank you
you're welcome
as soon as I as soon as I finished I
became questioning everything
I don't know why the that you
bring the the yeah
okay
because they're they're heavy I carry
for you oh yeah thank you so much for
caring you're so kind
of surprise thank you so much
no problem
how's your birthday my birthday really
going well so far
yeah it just I don't know maybe like
um I'm sleeping well I have enough of
food
but I'm still nervous about everything
birthdays are so nervous yeah like they
make you so nervous it's
you just should pretend it's not your
birthday yeah it just like it just like
I feel like uh I'm I'm happy that I'm
having a birthday but at the same time I
wish I didn't have a birthday
I understand I feel I feel the same yeah
but I love I love when other people have
birthdays
because I like seeing happy I like to go
happy birthday and I give them something
that I I never know if they'll like it
or not oh yeah yeah anyway
do you want to play rolling with me yes
I would like to yes I'm gonna I'm gonna
spin it okay
yes please oh God we I didn't even look
what the options were but yes I want to
play stuff
oh oh you you got a question three
question question yeah you got a
question tree
so I'm gonna ask you
oh okay okay
if you were given 10 billion to live
together with Muna would you take that
tell me why
wait if I was given money to live with
you yeah like someone giving you like 10
billion to leave it in me would you take
that and I
I would pay to live with you okay why
I don't know it sounds I don't really
not oh I know because I can listen to
you singing when you do karaoke oh
yeah all the time anytime you sing I
listen yeah
actually how about how would like we're
doing a character like every night or or
like at least once per week at night
like we have like one day to do Curry
get together oh that would be great yes
I will destroy my throat but it'll be
worth it
yes if I take the money then I could put
that towards you know uh the doctor
fixing my throat every time
fixing you what
fixing my throat if I like too much too
much listening oh too much singing yeah
Would You karaoke together but I also
can list out I'll listen yeah
yeah yeah yeah I guess that is a good
idea
yeah yes please thank you so much yeah
yeah I hope I
get it soon whether it be online or in
your house
I would love at least I have one one
more uh chance to do with you
[Music]
before before we end I'm just gonna say
I saw like someone
um doing some edit of me and just
singing together and and I think that's
awesome oh I've seen those too but I get
scared to listen because I don't like
hearing myself but it's really cool
though it's really I think I think it's
awesome I just like it's it's rhyme uh
the harmony is fits perfectly that's
what I mean
[Music]
I hope we can sing it together one day
and not just have it edited together
well it would be edited but like in a
different way yeah okay yeah
thank you so much
the rest of your birthday thank you and
also good luck with the treaties wait
oh that's not me
you're not the first one to wish me luck
thank you
okay bye bye
oh
sometimes I miss amazing but I always
remember that moment is like
some maybe like myths
almost forgot I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry
oh my God but she would get it
eventually right
she would get it eventually
[Music]
all right
huh
I mean in Hollow fence right yeah yeah
in a hall of fans you will get it
eventually in a hollow fast
not wrong so good luck with the treaties
right yeah
nurse
what
is this mooners no this is not munners
or not no this is not munners
so so what's your name tell me your name
ah my name
my name is
is it
[Laughter]
nice I I hope you will you will graduate
from the from the from the gang and
become nihongo JoJo level 100
[Laughter]
have like uh I have I have I have made
something but
I I didn't manage to finish it but I
will try to manage I will try to finish
it uh in the near time okay uh so so I
will just uh wish you Happy Birthday for
now and then I will give you the present
letter
before that I want to
um
play with you with a roulette
a Roland yes yes roll it
are you ready
yes yes
what is question for oh okay there is
actually equations you got a question
but do you want do you want me to like I
don't really want to give you the the
questions for
ah okay okay okay sure sure can I just
choose by myself
yes yes sure sure okay I'm gonna choose
by myself
so so
wait hold on
I
want you that's one concerning love
I want you to do the Dare
oh yeah I wanted to do the Dare and
pretend to be monahashi Nova try your
best mimic
foreign
how do I start how do I start uh
Moon
uh
what else why does it sound like a
Mickey Mouse
that there was my munners every time I
watched I watched stream like more more
[Music]
doesn't doesn't like Mickey Mouse
[Laughter]
oh my God okay I did it
oh God okay
I hope your quest to be the sugoi purple
Mitch will be uh realized wait wait how
far are you in Hogwarts oh no well right
now I'm like 30 hours
30 hours that's longer than my working
hour
that's good that's good
[Laughter]
all right it's just really fun it's
really fun thank you so much for writing
happy birthday thank you very much thank
you yeah I hope you have a good health
and stay awesome yay thank you you too
yeah bye-bye to the Moon of fridge bye
bye
[Laughter]
ah
that was frozen everyone
my
Muna fridge illustrator and animator
okay
mushy mush
happy birthday
thank you
my name is
yeah
happy birthday I present for you
important information oh
between
you and I
um
ozora police
and there I own you
what oh
watch out huh please watch out
okay okay
please remember
Harry Potter three
yes foreign
[Laughter]
that name what
I'm gonna say
oh
you you are pecora
[Laughter]
says so
so
now pecora arrest oh my God
Maybe
right
yeah love you
bye one arrest Muna right
yes one two yeah
[Music]
wow
you are like pecora
from my eyes oh no I'm way cooler
kubra yeah I'm cool
hey yes
what's your
name
yes yes
but my heart to coming soon
my heart to beat is fast that's fine
slithering doesn't mean fat people which
is ambitious
ambitious yes
Indonesia and this yes
okay
let's play Roll It
okay play Lauren yeah let's go let's go
start
Ed
oh
do you know like truth or dare
[Music]
um
sing a song for Moana
okay
if I I sing a song for you hi
Happy Birthday song present for you
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday dear Mama
happy birthday to you happy birthday
thank you thank you thank you thank you
so much next time
uh
I want to
eat
spicy food together
thank you happy birthday yeah
next month
how fast welcome to Japan
let's eat spicy food together
yeah
I checked restaurants
thank you happy birthday bye
[Music]
wow
wow wow
[Music]
I miss click again I miss click again
okay okay okay
[Music]
mm-hmm
ing
[Music]
don't feel I I I don't want to kill I
don't want to kill
it just become a challenge yes thank you
but I don't but I think she likes spicy
it's just cheese
after you still
so you have to used to
marshmallows
my smiles
dude I need you back
happy birthday
thank you kudani oh thank you so much
for having a Time
for me yeah I mean of course my my
my Muna senpai
well you said was like my moon
my spicy
spicy
I mean not as not as spicy as your new
outfit oh thank you yeah I really
haven't seen yourself
oh
my God thank you karonio for scumming
it's been a while having talked for like
a long time
I know like I wanted to get back into
Minecraft but
like just haven't gotten the Taffy tried
playing in the new server lately
yeah but I just like I'm stuck with
Minecraft like
um I still like don't know what should I
add in the next one
I mean
yeah that is true you pretty much built
to everything in this yeah it just it
just feels like uh even though I built
Lots in the GP server and uh and the ID
Surfer and so we moved another server
which
I I feel like
should I remake again the building
that's what I think
like why don't you try like building
like a city in the sky kind of thing oh
God that's gonna be hard without Adam
yeah
oh you're starting from scratch too huh
not really
not really yeah not really but but
um I just like use elytra for the
transportation if it's really necessary
wait no we should not be talking about
Minecraft
that later okay yeah we can talk about
that
I'm sorry for the NPC talk
how about how about we do a rolling
oh yeah of course let's do it let's do
it ding
foreign
[Applause]
I'm a little Daredevil okay then can you
say Muna is an idol not a comedian
of course
that's not that's not much of a dare
that's just simply stating the fact no
yeah I know right that is the fact that
is I don't know why someone like the
client about it
yeah that's absurd well
um
Muna is an idol not a comedian
there you go someone who really stated
with a heart like they know that it was
the truth
yeah it is 100 the truth and if they
don't believe you then stomp on him that
is a good idea yeah
that is a really good idea maybe I need
a friend to help me to do so oh yeah I'd
gladly help I jump at the opportunity
I got you fam
thank you thank you thank you for Ronnie
for coming I hope um we can play
together next time outside the Minecraft
thingy
yeah I love you all soon yeah okay yeah
you have a great one have a great day I
hope
um
I hope you have enough time to rest and
I hope the manager doesn't give you a
lot of homework because I know how it's
felt
yeah
you you get you get it man
let's not worry about that now okay you
have a great one that'll be great it
looks awesome thank you
okay bye-bye bye bye
tactic wow wow wow
here we are
[Music]
what's up
okay
okay thank you karani could I ask me
yeah
oh hello
hello
[Music]
happy birthday Muna yeah yeah thank you
then
guys
YouTube
[Music]
oh my God professional streamer indeed
oh yeah
foreign
[Laughter]
uh anyways happy birthday
oh yeah
um
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
uh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
uh
bye guys happy
[Music]
um
wow wow wow
[Music]
hello
this is
[Music]
I
mean
I mean
oh yeah
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah
Minecraft apology
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you so much
thank you yes
[Music]
yeah
thank you
[Music]
wait wait wait
laughs
what can do
it
oh I do
[Music]
foreign
yes
happy birthday
it's been a while
it's been a while Purple Gang
we like
purple yeah
okay
okay okay okay
ah
um
I thought you want to play Charlotte
roulette questions
thank you
question and uh
sharing
English chat
yeah
hey
a Christian challenge
yeah okay okay okay okay okay okay
let's go let's go
do this hahaha
oh
Jenna Adidas
uh
challenges
um
okay okay
foreign
[Music]
arigato
you hear that even even
say that Mona not comedian
yes yes
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
can you hear that
[Laughter]
oh God
[Music]
that was really fun daddy
the whole life Indonesia
is
wow wow
[Music]
let's go
okay okay
[Music]
foreign
oh no hi
hi
hello
happy birthday
thank you
this is this is the very first time that
um we are talking in here right
I
I attend the last year oh yeah that's so
much yeah oh yeah everybody
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
I I remember you mentioned about one
time okay I'll make one
well thank you by the way uh
hey guys let's go
let's go
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
ah Laura
okay
[Music]
um
okay
uh
[Music]
stream
yeah today oh God
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
hola
the real autumn
[Music]
I wonder who is thanks
sitting down
my shimash
hey
hi Mama
hello hi
happy birthday
thank you
for calling me thank you this is this is
our first time right calling like this
thank you for coming
thank you ah mama uh do you want to play
roulette
yeah
hi
what
[Music]
a challenge bye
[Applause]
there five challenge five
um
[Laughter]
the day of five is Plus on Twitter how
much you love Muna like the saint
s
foreign
How can I how can I uh
I love you so much am I the best
daughter and I I love you
I I am I am happy uh that uh
right all right all right
I am happy uh uh guys
[Music]
I'm happy that on YouTube tastes the
world
um foreign
you through this word
um
my daughter is
the best Idol in the world I love you
you so much
ah
foreign
don't worry don't worry
[Music]
um
hi I love you I love you uh
best base Idol I love you
[Music]
of writing in nihongo please no
because
[Music]
I love you
he know
s
hey
[Music]
guys
foreign
[Music]
okay
thank you for coming to my uh birthday
thank you thank you love you thank you
bye bye bye
[Music]
oh well okay wait
ah my God I'm so I'm so actually I'm so
nervous
[Music]
it's naughty mama is single
mom what kind of night
ah
we got
the actual gods
Chef for Mama also
a picture for Mama also
um I see it before but I'm gonna show it
to you guys
I'm gonna show it to you guys
[Music]
it's it's cute
it's cute
so cute
okay okay
let's go next car
once you must
there it is
thank you for coming yeah I think
our first time talking to me and not so
much one by one thank you thank you
but I'm very nervous now don't worry
don't worry I'm nervous too this whole
time yeah
yes not the time do you know that
um actually when I first saw your
um full body
your full body that I I recognize that
you have a transparent
transparent feet
transparent feet hi
foreign
mm-hmm
yeah you're afraid is see-through I just
like wow
[Music]
where is the feet
see true it's sweet too wow
do you want to play Rolex to me
roll it let's go public game became a
game okay
good job
Larry
huh
oh
crystals too question two one
two
um if you could take one part
one part of
the moon to be yours what would you take
and tell me why
foreign
[Music]
what
uh singing voice
singing voice yeah but but natachian is
a mermaid
only chance
yeah
oh thank you
yeah oh Harry's our penguin uh I gave
rerun we prayed together in Japan the
penguin the penguin is on my back right
now I always put it as my bag
it's it's I think it's died now
I think it's Dinah here I'm gonna take a
picture
this is so sad this is actually so sad
like the Penguins
[Music]
Hobby
and
I'm seeing thinking of going to the
Indonesia and next time
um yeah um if you have time I'd like to
you store me around
of course I do have time yeah
oh angry so cute yeah so this is the
yeah and the Penguin that that NATO Chan
like literally giving to me
oh
I'm gonna I'm gonna
[Music]
literally depending on that that not oh
NATO can give it to me and
it's it's become my my backrest this
whole
hey
oh my God yeah
so it's become a background the penguin
it's really really helping me with my
back thank you so much
well done
so the when you are coming to Indonesia
yes please tell me okay especially uh
the exact places where you came because
Indonesia is really big place it's a
really really big place and even like we
have like lots of islands
but if if you're on the same island
that I'm living on I would love to meet
you
and we're gonna have lots of fun
together
thank you yeah thank you all right you
know as soon as I know when I'm growing
okay yeah just just DM me
I will I will make sure to to check on
it too
okay
yeah thank you
well well well
oh
I got okay that is
that is not the time everyone
[Music]
and we have another coloring
hello
[Music]
thank you
cute
[Music]
oh
yeah
happy birthday
[Music]
Japanese so good
ah
good so great
still still a height
so uh
it writes for real pleasure to meet you
the last time you were in Japan
it was really fun yeah it's fun I'm
gonna I'm gonna go in Japan too in a
couple of
again
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
let's hang out again
yeah so I want to go to uh anymore
famous Japanese phrase uh-huh
yeah uh
foreign
what again
do you have a place you want to go no no
no
no I uh so I only only go to Japan for
the for the color festival polite
Festival outside of that I don't have
any plan to go so maybe maybe if
I go the maximum place is
foreign
[Laughter]
uh actually if if um I'm planning to go
to the Japan like going to Japan so my
my plan
I don't have any plan uh watch what I am
interesting to go with but I think I
would like to try another a strawberry
the one that we eating together
that's good that sounds good
um
also I think um I will really like to
try the best onigiri in Japan
[Music]
I hope
I uh I so I tried one onigiri that I got
from the
um the staff in in Japan and I really
like it because it's not from the
company but so yeah it's like a handmade
nigiri I want that
and one more one more do you know that
there is like a cafe
in Wonderland
to do is
[Laughter]
the sounds good
I like food
yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm me too
like two I like to eat me too
[Laughter]
so I'm looking forward to it
can you see me
um
I was happy to give you nearly family
matching t-shirts also like t-shirts
t-shirt
foreign ah
it's a present for you oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
um
so we have like a matching t-shirt that
all of the noria family have so right
now uh
right now kitchen is wearing the
matching t-shirt
let's go let's go
your new question it's too pretty
um
your new costume yeah
our matching teachers now
[Music]
is
again anyway
yeah do you want to play
ah roll it
[Music]
right yes roll it
I'll do that yeah yeah yeah I want to
pray okay
okay
[Music]
ah the challenge
okay 21
sing a song for me okay okay yeah okay
okay one two three happy birthday to you
yay happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday to you yeah
I love you I love you too love you let's
hang out again
yeah yeah
foreign
[Music]
happy birthday happy birthday happy
birthday
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
initiative
let's go
Saturdays
[Music]
thank you thank you
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
wow
[Music]
I know foreign
foreign foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
Chara
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
okay
important
[Music]
Internet America
um
foreign
[Music]
questions
that's your mind
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
huh
technology
[Music]
my fan
foreign
[Music]
ah
yeah
[Music]
oh yeah
foreign
[Music]
I wish I could have called in to hear
your lovely voice but thank you
um still I hope you have a wonderful
birthday I hope this dream is going well
I want to see your March stuff soon yay
yay
um all right I had a question for you
um
everybody knows that the Moon is
actually a giant egg what what will come
out when the egg hatches I don't know
all right thank you thank you
well that is from army guys
yeah that is from Ami mm-hmm
thank you so much and also God Gotta
Give I got a gift from festival and
fauna I'm gonna show from fauna first
thank you happy birthday Mona Senpai
from fauna look at that oh
I look so good
thank you fauna and then we got from
fast forward to us well
thinking like
I just want you now I don't play any
horror game that run quick on this test
so
thank you so much for I don't know is it
meme
oh
thank you password thank you right yeah
well
I'm gonna put it
I'm gonna put it in here
um I'm gonna put it in here yes that's
all everyone thank you so much thank you
so much for uh
I know Daddy
foreign
[Music]
well well
I also learned a lot thanks to this
video hopefully well now you have a
lovely birthday I wish you all the best
sorry for not being able to come live I
am currently busy I know dancing lesson
I get it yeah everybody wish me a happy
birthday okay
see you soon hopefully
uh thank you Kiara thank you so much for
giving me uh the video
Happy Birthday to me yes happy birthday
to me and also good luck with your
treaties all of the meat congratulations
you finally got here pretty uh showcase
I can't wait to meet you guys on the
hollow Fest
thank you well that's all
this all for
I've already rechecked all of it that's
all for today thank you so much everyone
for watching my tatsumachi
um I think Coco cannot wait to to eat
her Foods since you can hear that and
[Music]
Bernard
thank you
I am Moana
from hololive Indonesia generation one
awesome
bye bye
okay bye
[Music]
[Laughter]