so
my cat
smoothie
[Music]
i
has anyone seen
my rat
has
has someone seen my rat
excuse me
has anyone seen my rat
or my mouse
i'm just looking for my
for my rat
i don't know where she is
she was supposed to start streaming
uh half an hour ago
for sure
i'm doing this really spontaneously i
just came to my computer to do a
thumbnail for my ori stream
rat doko
where is she
and this is too
too ironic because
didn't she just do a waiting stream
waiting for callie and it only lasted
two minutes because she did show up
immediately
now that's that's funny to me
because now
where is she
i literally just came to my computer to
make a thumbnail and i saw that she's
really missing for 40 minutes now
it's not like she wasn't just online on
twitter tweeting about something
okay i'm really not prepared for this
when when are you how could you ever be
prepared for something like this
sometimes the job just calls upon you i
haven't even tweeted
let me tweet
i am looking for my rat
uh
where is she peidoko
i need to tweet
spontaneous
stream
[Laughter]
where are you
hey
she's offline on this but let um i could
i could message her and who knows maybe
that would already do the trick i
haven't tried contacting her because
it's not like it's not like uh this is
really a life or a death situation
i just i just was like oh well
i i had a day off today and i was just
doing uh
about to do my thumbnail for tomorrow
and i see this and actually someone
tweeted at me
someone tweeted at me already like 15
minutes after she was uh missing 15.
one five minutes after she was missing
someone was like kiara bae is missing
not really even directly asking for what
i'm doing now but i know that person was
exactly asking for that
wait wait eh
whoopi said play is not doing a stream
like this right now right
i'm misunderstanding that one comment i
think
whole live english members when they go
missing is my job it's my job
kelly must know what why
why kelly
we need some some detective music shall
we go on audio stock
shall we go on a little trip to audio
stock we have probably a lot of time i
don't know i don't know how long it will
take for her to wake up let's go uh
background local uh no background
because this is what bayer's stream
looked like this is kind of a parody
[Laughter]
have you seen my rat
excuse me
have you seen her somewhere
i'm just i'm so lonely
okay so
uh
tanto
let's look for i gotta change my
keyboard i literally just turned on my
pc
tanto
let's see
what maybe something loopable
uh
you guys tell me when she's awake
it's been 43 minutes yo oh this could be
good
i'm just going to be oh it's too loud
sorry
the cell needs to be turned down a
little bit
we might be in it for the long haul so
that's not detective music
[Music]
no this is not it needs to be a bit more
chill
oh oh this one maybe
oh stop
[Music]
where you at
my rat at my flat i hope not
i recently
tried to poison them all
but you are that one rat that just won't
leave me alone i say i don't want you
but my heart really starts for you
my rats
[Music]
if you switch the letters
it also could turn into
art
is stuck
so in reality
[Music]
your art
okay this is good download this one
i don't know what the hell that was
please ignore my
freestyling just looking for my red
excuse me
no no no vlc
i chose you here it goes
snap that finger yeah
is it snipping your finger or snapping
your finger sip snip snipping a thing
all right
a rat is missing and all i see is
all i see is a cat slash bird in her
place
you didn't did you attention
[Music]
why would
why would you
[Music]
how why there's
that's not connected in any way
just because
i'm a cat right now
that that that that doesn't mean that no
no that
that one thing doesn't have anything to
do with the other i eat chicken
exclusively i do not care for rats at
all
rats are not really yummy even no matter
how much barbecue sauce you put on them
i tried i have tried
it really doesn't taste any better i
tried sweet sour sauce i tried that that
what's that sauce called again that
everybody loves uh the one the whites
the the one the the the sour cream sour
cream sour cream i tried that one
i tried gravy because you know gravy
usually saves everything
and but no even gravy couldn't do the
trick
nah
you guys i'm shining so fast my my chat
my real chat isn't working i need to
look at lbs did you eat i didn't eat
casper casper casper casper is
probably still alive
[Music]
casper is still alive out there
yeah yeah anyway should we try uh
writing a message to me
it's almost been an hour there
are you
sleeping
babe raise my rat
where's my rat where's my rat tatooi
eh they got blasted with callie what's
that man did they go drinking the other
day but but but that that doesn't mean
she's drunk right now right
oh
she went flying i think my
my tweet helped and my
my message
i think she got like a ping
and then now she woke up her reply is
let me show you
i found my rat this is nice it's just
about as much of a short stream as hers
was
uh
well
[Music]
i have
what do the what do they fans call
themselves
what is their name again
cheese bits or something like that
what are you guys names
what
i love that well you're welcome
beyblades i woke up hiroshi
wasn't even that difficult
hey are you watching this
[Music]
i'm i'm just
i'm just looking for
my rat
have you seen my rat excuse me sir
excuse me have you seen my rat
would
you like to
um
give a statement on my stream
[Music]
i was waiting for something like this to
happen again it's been quite a long time
since the enough waiting stream and
honestly this was way too easy
this one was way too easy
let's give it i'll give it a try you
don't have to pick up if you sleep for
yourself
[Music]
i saw her in the chat yeah she's aware
she's somewhere oh
hello bae
good morning
weren't you literally just tweeting
only a little tiny while ago
technology is a lie
it's a freaking lie oh are you blaming
it on your alarm clock
it didn't go off
you probably uh didn't set it in the
first place you probably like set a time
and then you didn't press okay
i did that a couple of times before
i oh it said
alarm in three hours
i have that couple times before too
[Music]
you know what you know what you have to
do
you have to eat your phone out of the
window no more phone life
i'm so sad okay i gotta go rescue hold
on um
hold on
oh my god okay yeah
50 minutes late mrs rat
um
i'm so uh
you don't have to apologize to anyone
bae
i'm sorry but you know
nine minutes i'll be good in nine
minutes oh i find this very ironic
didn't you just uh one or two days ago
make a stream about waiting on cali
yeah
so
what does this mean
[Laughter]
ah that we are one and the same um
yeah who who said who's next to you
right now bae is it callie
no okay man it better not be
no
[Music]
what
thank you for messaging me oh you're
welcome you're welcome i'm actually
surprised that dad did the trick it's
way too easy i've been dealing with more
difficult situations like you
know ah no because here's the thing it's
like my alarm didn't go but i was like
you know when you're like kind of awake
and like
i normally
like my body clock normally like is
is not that bad so like i normally still
wake up early but i just zoinked out
was this supposed to be a nap or a full
sleep
full sleep yeah
girl
girl this is
three hours is not a full sleep
it is in this house
what's going on girls you need to take
care of your health have you not learned
something from your senpai's mistakes
from cali's cali herself your big sister
she had issues like that she didn't get
enough sleep she didn't feel well and
she learned from her mistakes she tried
to she started to adjust her that stuff
and she tried to put herself first so
you need to prioritize your health girl
sleep more and if you can't get enough
sleep then you need to stream less a
little bit
yes exactly exactly
yes it is
yes
um oh yeah people wondering what
happened with the that was a scheduled
tweet
oh
that's interesting i was wondering about
that too like how is she not here right
now
yeah i was scheduled to because normally
i wake up
don't trust the tweets guys
don't trust the tweets especially
they're in the morning if they're in the
morning
morning time cannot trust cannot trust
now get yourself some coffee girl and
and put on some clothes or do it naked
whatever not that i care
and go stream but uh don't do this don't
don't force yourself like this and put
get some proper sleep girl yeah
okay
i think i'm turning into an insomniac i
feel oh because i i try
see say okay i was in bed for six hours
i just couldn't sleep ah
yeah no i don't have that too
i tried how do you try
i try i just sleep i like really you're
not you're not watching netflix for
hours like me
no
real real
[Laughter]
[Music]
what are you watching currently tell me
um
trashy reality tv
cheshire reality trashy trashy trashy
reality tv oh no is it like the
kardashians or something like that
uh i'm not gonna name it because i just
called it trashy but it's still very
good
oh you watch reality tv shows uh do you
also watch stuff like the bachelor and
stuff like that like similar stuff
no no no no no no not that one okay did
you know
there there was this this uh reality tv
show um uh which was kind of like the
bachelor but it was like a british guy
who looked like that that prince harry
guy and
and they called in like a couple of
american girls it was many many years
ago and they really seriously made the
girls think that that's harry because he
looked
like a little bit similar but they
didn't really i guess know him that well
anyway so they were
the whole the whole show was about
making them think that his hairy day is
he had like a butler he was arriving in
a helicopter he was living in this huge
castle and stuff like that yeah uh cr
absolutely crazy
i didn't watch it though i just watched
a review
oh
maybe that's something for you
um
yeah you better get going now and i'll
i'll enjoy the rest of my day off
thank you so much
i had a good time good short time
good that i found my rat
oh my god i can't wait to rewatch this
and nothing much happened really but
please go ahead it's short so it's an
easy re-watch
okay all right then
yeah go get some coffee
okay bye bye
bye bye
i told you i didn't eat her
i told your rats don't taste good
you gotta trust it i don't know why you
expected me out of all people
me i'm innocent you guys never believed
me unbelievable
inconceivable
okay then
that's that's all that i needed uh to do
my my work here is done
and in german we say avidazin see you
guys at ori uh first episode tomorrow
bye bye
bye
the cat found the rat the cat found the
rat
[Music]
do
you