[Music]
I guess we started
[Applause]
hi hello hello hello
wow wow all right thank you guys for
joining my the valve collab Marathon
thank you for play
[Music]
you thanks for the game right oh yeah
yeah I never played before I didn't even
play the tutorial I ski skip skip
easy we ski the tutorial yeah we skip a
skiper yeah yeah
I don't know if we need introductions
there's a lot of us here so that might
take like five or 10 minutes yeah but
just maybe for audio check for the
balancing all right fine all right we'll
go down the Discord list I'll go first
hello everybody Amilia Watson and number
one detective from H
[Music]
English hello
everyone SS
[Applause]
Le
Justice
here
hello I'm I guess hello it's different
than my
[Music]
list y
[Laughter]
[Music]
so
good y yay
[Music]
[Applause]
zoron from H life English promise nice
to meet you
[Applause]
[Music]
Alli oh sorry I couldn't tell what
people are
ending okay yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
woo wa here I'm gonna play
[Applause]
Pyro know got a fire today yeah oh yeah
true all right so we are going to split
up into different teams uh I I randomly
what oh what I nothing think so it just
killed
me wait how am I dead why am I not why
am I looking at people I think someone's
cheating anyway anyway you can cheat in
this game no no you can't you
can't are we are we
starting yeah yeah yeah if you're on
Blue Team we'll go into the
other okay okay okay and then the flag
yeah any questions where's the flag
somebody kill where's the flag yeah
should we all go together PR PR okay
blue
team okay okay let's go
together te no I want to be a red team
on okay is it safe I don't trust the
robot I think she'll kill us no fighting
oh no no no it's okay no fighting wa
wait is everyone is everyone coming
[Music]
team blue team wait so red team stays
here or no no red team and blue team
everybody go to the bridge just go
inside the middle outside in the middle
Hey where's the bridge okay
outside there stairs over
here it's
okay okay oh wait that's GG oh crap
there's no username no wait that's can
you use the gun to try the bridge no
fighting no fighting
[Music]
they're all in a
different are we starting I think we
should just start they killed one of us
s just kill them just kill them okay
let's just go come on killing time
up I'll heal you is this working thank
wait I'm the wrong
team hey what's up
guys I doesn't move to the right voice
call are we complet
wow I was left at the other
team oh you were spying kind of well I
didn't mean to I think they wanted me
there oh okay they wanted you there I
want you too sh I I could pretend to be
wait you what I want you to here oh I'm
here I'm here no worries us who I will I
will eating up people I was just being a
spy by accident
I'm
lost where am I hi lost hello lost can
someone pick me up is the machine
gun I exploded even is the flag yeah how
do I all chat oh that's my flag how do I
go I found our flag you found our flag
where's their flag it look like a flag
though
hi running around so energetically a
gigy I'm running
running oh oh crap don't die all right
maybe I should change a different class
wow CeCe really hates me I'm
scared get him get him don't be
[Music]
scared are we are we like in the lead I
can never tell in these games I don't
even think we started is it a I have no
idea what's going on warm
up it's just warm up
Air Blast only good strch right oh
that's you okay that is me hi what is
this guy do hello sexy
ladies oh oh oh oh no stop killing
me we need to capture the flag okay so
we need to get deeper into the system
get him get him
get get get get I'm crap where are you
I I don't know what I I don't know who
this person is but I don't like them of
the enemies but I'm not quite sure I
don't know what this disguise thing my
intelligence has diminished
oh they got the I think that's the flag
oh I think we need to kill
Watson picked up our intelligence are
they all in our base right now yeah yeah
I saw SP here oh we need to
defend they keep going invisible
attack attack attack okay okay I got her
I got her nice go g go how do you run so
much can you even oh there you go I
don't I don't know what happened but I
think I killed someone don't tell my
parents where is
everybody K one okay I'll defend them
okay I'm going to go look for theirs it
must be deep in their their spawn nest
yeah I'll stay in a corner
here can't pick up for intelligence I
need healing I need healing do we have a
Healer at all we do not have a
Healer do the others have a Healer dad
do
haveo they're
healing man oh Dar I don't think they're
in our
team who's this oh hi crony me hi
nice
suit thank you oh you can pick that up
can't find their intelligence oh I think
I found it all right I'm heading in
there just a kill God Dam oh I didn't
mean I thought they meant that we got
some like smartness buff or so no we
don't the flag oh picking of
intelligence means picking up the flag I
I'll defend okay I'm running back okay I
watch I got your back I'm so alive they
got our no you're going the right way
you're going the right way I don't know
what I'm
doing they're shooting me back I'm
trying to shoot I need to reload
though is that my
intelligence
intelligence oh my
go there you
go how
should oh crap
I have no idea where to drop this off do
I bring it to our place I don't know
bring it to the base or something oh
maybe a spawn
point it's okay at least you're still
alive we'll spawn in soon listen yeah
least we
together oh I got it nice you got
it I don't know where I'm going oh yeah
we both have one one now y good good job
d see yeah watch out there's a Watson in
our base oh sorry that's you oh yeah she
killed me we really should get a Healer
huh uh let's
see all right I'm going to go as a
Healer
oh I you know
what I think I'm going to protect the
myself why over
there she she's just miling everyone
she's so surrounded oh
no it's okay you did
great maybe all right I'm away from me
there's an impostor with my name bye
don't trust them kill them kill
them currently dead why is the Sy gun
stuck yay our intelligence has been
picked up which is not a good thing I
learn now we have to stop stop them stop
them this s gun really sucks there's two
of them there's two of them there's two
of them there's two of the hell they're
in there intellig you need healing guys
guys there's two of them I got killed by
F and Liz I'm looking for it dead body
I'm s here your crony so I can
he I can't tell where they are I think
your character
smoking hello any body here oh I need a
mini
map I'm where are they I think we just
made a game we can go from here no this
place is so confusing I'm going
to uh yeah think they're over here come
on we should stick together where are
all of them they gone oh oh
Noone I I died
oh yeah
yeah you need healing I must heal
someone it's part of my
job ohal I cannot heal anymore actually
you can switch Yeah Yeah with scroll
wheel oh where's your intelligence
resupply all right I do not like
medic you don't like medic no I don't
think so I don't think healing is to my
nature I think think I need to stay with
killing yeah I can become a Healer
eventually if we can change the rulle I
don't mind too much oh yeah yeah you can
change you can go with whatever you want
Oh
H you die you can
switch yay
[Music]
yay I'm right behind you
protect me owie I'm not really the Ty to
protect not but that's right oh oh who
shot me I'll protect you
that
[Music]
oh it was it was fa and F killing me
that means free people ganked up on
me all right we're eating hot dogs
tonight oh
that's not
dog I can't walk through all of that oh
crap get her get her get her get her all
right maybe I should go for a machine
gun become a Healer later for you my
lady I'll be the healer that you
deserve oh that's where you go I see
KY what class are you playing the really
fast one that has a bat that bat people
oh
go you a baseball player yeah that's why
you're so bad I'm going for the big guy
now I'm going to intelligence I'm a big
guy with a little ego that's the wrong
place
oh I like the big guys H
hi I just like being fast though they're
shooting me they're shooting
me I thought it was a false spy our
intelligence has been dropped I'm I'm
lost sorry gigy where are you gigy they
dropped the intelligence right by their
spawn I don't know how to protect this
no
no why are they so good
oh I got two
timed I'm trying to protect
our
oh all right I'm going to try to be less
aggressive
now you can change how do you change um
use the comma and then press a random
number comma and a random number yeah
you must make sure they don't they don't
take this wait how do you grab the
intelligence you have to there's a
circle above it and then it
shows can you shoot someone who looks
like a
spy oh crap there's two of them all
right they've invaded us what what the
hell stop
a I like how Cron's just chasing the guy
hey nice job CR
yeah yay now it's
person I don't know who this guy is the
enemies are gone she already together
we're
strong
that's maybe she needs backup okay I'll
you the
healing help help
help yeah you're you're here now yeah
you just got fre people defending
intelligence wait wait guys I got the
intelligence to our base but I got
killed someone pick it up okay uh I'll
stay
here you I I'm in the big open area kind
of the one that has
stairs okay ah I I see it I am I hear
death soon oh and I died okay I here's
three like three people intelligence has
been returned
oh oh God I
see I can't do this
alone they're coming after
me isn't that your go
office I'd like I need to go
back hell
[Laughter]
that's how it
works oh hello B it's really in
intelligence
guys okay their is gone we just have to
we have to get we have to get it again
I'm close to it but I'm alone oh no oh
is there is there even a winning side
right now they're winning they have two
intelligence yeah they have two they win
I'm just uh staying here
then I'll just pull out my switch and
play a game or something can I eat a
salad tonight for
dinner
he good
job help oh okay sorry
the uh spy is evil don't trust the Spy
is
evil they keep on no one here yet sh
it's [\h__\h] oh hey Med kit nice yeah
intelligence is
here is there anybody here oh nice good
job team good job I'm oh oh sorry I
thought you were someone I was about to
shoot oh nice job I think I didn't kill
you right oh crap they showed up there
three of them in
oh no they got our intelligence oh no oh
no they're in our base three of them
intelligence person I don't know where
to
go oh you got the I got intelligence I
got the go go go I'm just going to
[Laughter]
shoot I'm trying to find my way to you
yeah I don't even know where I'm going
help help
help oh
crap oh wait are you one of us
sorry of my body okay I need to bring it
to the intelligence right yeah to the
intelligence room run further inside yes
yes oh
man do damage F hates you I do
it I'm look not that way that come back
come back come back this way up up up up
oh [\h__\h] intelligence too I don't know
where they
are no no don't come back come back come
back back back back back
back she was following me oh never mind
follow giggy giggy understand gg gg
should be this way over here this
iSell that way works too
intelligence let's go okay my character
doesn't have enough like day for this
yeah you
follow follow the sign thank you nice we
did it
[Music]
nice wait
what no we almost
made we got to drop it off no I think uh
you
didn't like literally in that moment end
it by a second I think so they got hours
first cuz they were a little bit faster
carrying it over to I see guess we'll
just go
kill okay it was close you now know
[\h__\h] hates
humans hi I'm here to check you guys I'm
just spectating oh oh
okay hello you guys good now I saw you
running around with the the case for a
long
time
yeah I was trying to find the
intelligence room but I failed it's kind
of it's it is very
confusing yeah I picked it up and it
killed someone which is better than
nothing well you guys need any help or
questions I can
[Music]
help I don't know where I am the game is
very simple yeah
I'm like a lost
child have our intelligence
again take there okay what if I just
Camp
here oh yeah just Camp there yeah let's
just Camp here what they have another
spawn too there's one on the other side
okay we'll we'll camp out at one of them
you guys are all going nice nice yes
teamw teamw makes the kill work yeah
they're strong yeah where is ity come
back I don't know where it is I think we
should stick
together run run run run we'll protect
you we'll protect you I'll defend I
probably die way actually oh they can
come back down and take that yeah Cas
okay never mind ow oh if you're carrying
intelligence you should stay back so you
can
defend okay yeah stay back stay back I'm
just going to keep shooting my missile
oh no oh no
no I kill it I K I think I got it okay I
don't know where to go guys oh shoot oh
shoot I dropped
it trust the queen good nice nice I
don't know where anywhere
[Music]
is that that have dropped it kind of by
their spawn area oh thank you oh
I like how's just standing there I'm
making sure no one takes this
intelligence yeah I think I forgot about
it my brain cells are dropping thank
God they forgot about it they forgot
about it no she came back but it's gone
[Music]
fool I see the red are there
there we have taken okay they're they're
watching from the roof pick up pick it
up
every time I got you my buddy I got you
Raa thank you I want to go grab the yep
yep
intelligence oh
no niy oh there's too many of
them all right they're not even going
for yeah that's good they're going on
the defense
oh maybe they're using it to lure
us they're exped by how good we
are down there yeah we let them win the
last
round why are you down there swimming
you can go through the tunnel here I
don't know the C yeah the tunnel is easy
to but it's stinking there's rat
oh oop sorry
teamwork you guys need a medic they have
a medic
yes okay I can try being medic I'm not
good at it
though don't die don't
die y I'm killing
myself
rocket no all right I'm medic now who
needs healing I'm going to stay here
though
um well if you're just standing there
then follow me and heal me okay I got
you uh where's everyone out of
heels uh I think you you got to like
pick up those little packages on the
ground refill your ammo like this one I
think refill your I see I see oh there's
someone here we are yeah but with your
healing we can do it the enemy has
secured our intelligence we can get our
intelligence too oh crap I'm dead
sorry medic medic was killed medic was
fried I became a
kfp oh healing is infinite you have to
use theun okay gun is infinite all right
I'll stay put in a random area
then where we going someone has our
intelligence too you guys traed you guys
tra oh it's returned oh
no does someone have ours what they had
to I such like this
game I'm going just a lone healer
getting Fri help us
losers and now those we pretty strong we
are pretty strong all right everyone's
at base I guess
no one
wow wait that barely did any
damage to the battle battle Ms battle
Ms heck yeah we need to some fire right
I'm
protect might try to
go he's going
[Music]
thees they're oh my gosh okay I'm
following someone
at the entrance they're inside I blamed
them put a Sentry on the intelligence
game I can't where are we going oh I
think they did they already take the
case oh not yet not
yet
H yeah that is okay this is super messed
up but
uh that's not messed up it's smart
inside the base
I'll just I'll I'll just leave it at the
middle upgrade uh oh thank you we
appreciate the
help thank you
oh nice
nice you should you should you could go
with the the other team into the base
and then it'll help them a
lot wherever they're making sure you're
not a
spy
oh I'll try where go where where are
them
I was all right I'm going with the Enemy
area with anyone who's there no going
with the enemies oh no no no I meant
like if anyone's going in I just can
hear people kill I'm running oh who's
running oh they're right
there
yeah oh everyone has died pretty fast
[Music]
really hates me I bet she loves me
though thank
you seems like you had some practice as
an engineer I can build teleports so I'm
going to put a Teleport into their base
from our
spawn okay wow just give me like few
minutes and it'll be noy Noy no Noy no
don't die no
KY no no
help okay it's okay I'm still I'm okay
I'm okay I'm okay I'll go the other
way I got you it's okay
ra they're in our base they're in our
base it's okay I got a Sentry down
there they're still in our
base a they tell them I'm on the Xbox my
mama said I'm not supposed to be here oh
crap oh no I got sniped help help
help yay yay
no so
tanky
yay is it friend or
fo I just shoot them
anyway they're
underground we'll figure it out
later GG let's go let's
go I don't this yet it's why did you
shoot me can I trust you just in case
you were
[Music]
CC where where is it I'm
I'm I'll keep heing you intelligence to
drop it
off drop it off all the way to the desk
again yeah you know the architect of
this place kind of sucks cuz they put
two enemy factions near each other you
guys I put a teleporter by the main
spawn and if you go into teleporter
it'll take you into their base who are
you can I trust you okay I can trust you
you can trust me okay I'm friend okay oh
we leaving our intelligence at the
bottom
killer how do I take
this I got their intelligence I'm on my
way back good
job
uhoh it's okay it's okay yeah yeah yeah
I think they know they know they know
I'm here they know I'm here watch out sp
sp he right behind
you you're good you're
good where are them all right I'm now
without protection I must stay with
someone where are you you not lady oh
you need heals yeah hey if you go into
this teleporter down right to their base
all right guess we're going
[Music]
together okay okay all right don't die
you have a minute to not die it's fine
fine it's not me but it's them but it's
they're acting as
me which one where this one I
can't I'm just healing
everyone currently the okay where are
you
I'm an enemy base I saw spy behind the
scout who's the Scout on the bridge turn
around we have sec the we got it we got
it oh it's you okay it's me it's me okay
I'm healing who is that thank you okay
no problem making sure that it's not a
SP oh let's go grab the
intelligence can we even teleport back
from here we have think okay come on oh
no no it's a only one way sorry oh
okay be safe everyone me me heal me I'm
healing I'm
healing you have Uber if you have Uber
you be careful they're going to turn you
into a kfp don't worry don't worry it's
me it's
me all right oh my god let's go good job
good
job where's everyone now crazy
girl
oh okay we have to go back we have to go
back Shing yeah
yeah where am I where am I going is the
I don't know just pick a way this way
this way who's this okay oh crap wait
wait she's falling this way I'm healing
I'm healing
y literally
Unstoppable MVP I hear the scrips of the
damn bad Halloween yet
cover my shoulders sh I need to find I
am I am I got both your shoulders
there's an enemy
here good job what is it intelligence oh
my gosh I I don't know I'm not
intelligent enough to figure that one
out let's go let's go they have our
intelligence make sure shoot anyone even
if they look like us at this point
that's a good strategy yeah shoot now
ask
later so
true we did it we did
it let's go to
the
yay thank you for the help Amy oh crap
everyone's gone
you got to go to the other
chats
time
okay did you guys have
fun hates me
yeah so fun what why are you bullying us
h
no you're the target you were just
walking around
are we doing random TMS you walked into
my bullets yeah random okay random you
want us to hit
random yeah random let's go random move
the
hi are you
healing if you're healing I'll something
El yeah so this one uh one side pushes
the cart the other side tries to stop
the cart see how you die I had a heart
attack oh no how do you know if you're
on the pushing defending team uh red is
defending blue is pushing okay I cannot
okay do you want us to move in a
different
voice yeah yeah okay uh blue team or red
team going to the other okay I to follow
someone is in my team so she can't kill
me
anymore wait I I I I left the room by
mistake I mean they K me out I don't
know what happened I'm trying to we can
wait for you I just to come
back I guess we should uh memorize the
map really quick begin that is true we
just
push it's not letting us through this
one oh is someone shooting me or killing
me oh why am I on fire oh no okay but
seems like is kicked out of her group
yeah yeah I'm trying to log in again
okay
Mission begins in 10 seconds can you
like what are we doing again are we
capturing a
flag 3 2
okay wait am I in the right
party do we just te move team move te
okay
bye oh making hello hello my red team
party members welcome I am one of you
[Music]
I'm going to see what you feel
M they about to kill
me that's good don't tell the
cops cops all
right you got itend we need to go to the
next
car is that a
car I found a the car is
moving
okay there's something at the left we
need to jump in there
oh I hear death yeah I hear death
too it's okay I look I look for
death that's
right oh I need help down danger wow it
takes up so much to kill this one guy I
will heal if you fall back here it will
heal you oh no it's okay I'm dead
there's herb though she can use some
healing I use that I'm red now CH I
didn't
realize start hello welcome welcome to
the red team red for blood absolutely no
idea that happened hi hoko we're here en
has yep y are you okay I'm making sure
you're not the Imposter I know where to
go uh I see the car the car is really
wait am I going the right no I'm going
the wrong way it's this way
I'm just following anyone I'm like a
Lost Child hold my
hand okay you're
you're it's coming it's coming Soul oh
there's somebody there I'll heal
[Music]
you I should up be here okay okay I need
healing
you I'm going to go
in uh oh C's behind you
okay I hope I helped a
little I think we'll need a flame
person I'm going to get this orang
gun
gun I'll heal if you need that cilia I
think way be careful no
risks are
dangerous okay I'm here
hom I want something more like the other
side looks kind of safe here on the
other side this is
[Laughter]
hard it's fine oh they're doing well
they're going to next Point get them
away from
next do explode how does it stop I don't
know it's okay it's okay it's okay there
was someone near
you can I shoot the
oh at least there's
attack over time can we use
the
we're
we're yes you
are do she want to die all herbs needs
healing I need come over here by the car
the car the car okay I'm by you by you
to
good over there come over here if you
want
healing wait what color am
red I'm up
here
uhoh healing put death oh dang it's okay
I set them on
fire come over here if you want
healing they Camp they camping push oh
they have to push okay we probably need
Tove move now no I'm seeing right here
oh we got a spy find us they're going to
find us we're going to die yeah yeah
yeah yeah we're not going to make this
we're not going to make we have to jump
it's
okay my way I'm on my way
[Music]
want I'm going to do it
yeah a strategy it's a good strategy
yeah I don't want to hurt
her we need an engineer that is I got
sniped by cilia we didn't started to
become an engineer we started to become
AIC oh they're there defend the pay from
behind there's still 8
minutes so
Angy we can't survive that we can't
survive that
flying
off do I go
hello oh it's coming in
oh
okay try
try you're good to to
[Music]
Y defense is always so hard again again
let's go I'm going to try and do we're
attacking now we're attacking
now okay I'll stay together here done
you our bullets aren't that strong we
should only use it we really need to so
let's focus on healing okay that's very
different from what you said just a
moment ago I'm just going to take out
the gun take out the gun I see
aggressive Target so I need to respond
aggressively yeah you healed
let us
us you got 30 seconds Mission begins in
30 let's just think about our like our
family because we're probably going to
die how do you look at what all the the
do hicke you do on each character like
is there a button to click
but you have to press the Uber and then
attach to someone begins in 10 seconds
10 seconds
what was that oh you got to be attached
to someone and then Uber yeah oh I see
them how do you I've changed character
how do you look at what the character do
uh period and then do numbers just keep
holding the period I already see
them
okay always telling me to kind of get
out for I can't shoot them from
here okay I'm just going to focus I'm
pushing yeah push push push oh we're
dying we're dying we're dying going to
go
and then if you H over the characters
it'll say what they do I'm
cring really like those G
Guns oh we're getting we're getting up
wrong way wrong
way oh I
[Laughter]
stillo
the I'm going back to other voice chat
good luck you guys have question fig it
out Liz thank you
all right they're in the tunnel right
now oh it moves on its own oh that's
it I guess it moves faster if we're
closer to
it oh hi guys it's time for the
gun all right we're on this team
now harder yeah good job good job good
[Music]
job oh good job yeah
come from behind us so careful yeah we
got to be
careful I'll tell you if you're getting
shot at
M from above oh from above above above
stay away from above I'm trying to heal
Elizabeth yeah thank you it's going to
be all just like everyone's a
Healer okay they're up
here they're here they're down here
too nice
[Music]
there got him oh
nib needs healing I need healing there
to the first stop
okay okay healing
you go nice
is there anyone else
there o we have an MP so
far all right I'm just going to
sacrifice
myself no stay safe she will we oh it's
okay I'm
dead watch over for the big
bullets watch for the big bullet
[Music]
okay heing I'm running I'm
running GG's in here careful I'm going
to
die oh I'm dead now I
dead than you system time time it's a
fight between you living I'm
dying oh my go he hard I'm dying he
harder okay can I heing
Elizabeth yeah he can I got Elizabeth
can too thank
you nice all right now we're talking
okay let's over those big bullets let's
over the big bullets oh crap
bomb keep they're doing bombs now watch
out watch out watch out bom Str let see
I keep forgetting we're blue team yeah
me too so used to Red oh someone's
flanking us can I shoot the bombs okay
I'm going to shoot the bomb behind
behind oh I'm from above and above
behind and above shot the
[Music]
bomb good J J good jump good JP good JP
good good good
good I'm dead
[Music]
healing a heal
herb I don't know heal
someone okay I'm on my way I'm on my way
on my way okay careful they're above us
too
who stop pushing the
car think we might have a
spot behind us oh okay I see I'm going
Sho with my gun yeah I'm on my I
need I got a new item
okay long way to run yeah we're trying
to get together with everybody we cannot
make it over there it's okay we're on
our way
[Music]
I try to heal you thank you it's a fight
between healing and
dying indeed it is it always
is can I shoot come back a it come back
a it a ball okay you're good you're
going expl
it I'm following you I'm just making
sure that we can get them from an ankle
[Music]
that was that was another bomb another
bomb another bomb
bombs another bomb go down watch all the
bombs there's a lot of bombs get
W yeah nice one sh you okay move the
thing I have you thank you thank
you someone keep my eye
behind yeah yeah they might flank us
anytime oh they're here in the front in
the
front we're watching behind
you
fine make sure
everybody no it's
fine make sure we he heal the
happies okay we're good we're good stay
behind M go down watch out for bombs
watch bomb in the front bombs in the
front
Okay in the front how big is the they
behind us
oh God I need
help look at this we need to healer we
need a
Healer I'll heal the making sure you're
not a thing okay there is fine okay I'm
healing you I want to shoot
[Music]
everywh let's run
okay keep an
eye am I going to survive I have than
you shall survive and as long as you
know how to love I know you'll stay
alive keep pushing this we got just be
around
it behind us behind us
nice job oh okay goodbye beautiful a
draw good it's fun when you
win all right we're defending
now okay we're defending again let's see
how this goes defending be hard mhm it
is uh hello
I'm going to change the game mode one
more time but if you guys want to go
into the other chat for this round and
then oh sure okay chaos we're number
one
hello hell let's have a party
party come on let's go big wind in
two good G
how to defend
successfully I'm over charged wait let
me just watch in one hour quick I I I
looked up like a guide and was like how
to play this one it was a 2our long
video
God that's a try hard average team for
no I didn't watch it I
mean that's a try Harding video I cannot
believe you try
everyone I thought we were going to
switch game mod oh okay okay
yeah can you I guess while we're
switching game modes we kill everyone
huh
[Music]
each let's
go take him down I don't know come out
guys come on blue team are we playing
again are we I thought we were waiting
[Laughter]
team death match oh well this is working
out though I'll do this of course you
do oh I don't know where I am team death
match I'm a little bit lost I might go
the other way by the way they die
already I love oh there a
sniper where
I can go here wow it feels kind of mean
my how could this happen you've been red
but
shoo oh I don't have enough ammo for
this
actually like your
teammates all my teammates eat my
missiles
[Music]
okay R run run run we're wait is this
the new I'm sorry no no no it's not yet
oh it's the not yet oh we're still
playing oh okay
oops how do I get out of
[Music]
here I thought you were my friends
and would you guys prefer to stay all in
voice chat or still separating for teams
I think
separate separ okay okay okay yeah
otherwise it' be too chaotic and we
wouldn't but every once in a while
getting together is fun
[Music]
too down going to be in a team again oh
wait there's no video oh my God wa
where's the
video I don't like this oh we're three
of the same uh character
F oh no wait how can I
change let's we can go over there oh hi
short what's up
losers the same team we the same team
now
stop what up yeah who's staying in the
which voice chat oh yeah te going to the
second voice CH okay
okay two medic okay not bad
is what is this
game red team
right doing is this Death Match actually
maybe he you to know to come back oh
it's raining what this Death
Mode death I think we just kill each
other all right each other wait you take
damage from the rain I think you you
took fall damage maybe it's cuz you're
stinky Tak damage oh yeah oh I guess so
I'm not taking damage from the rain I'm
Tak I'm dying
everyone I don't know what's going on
but I'm here we team red that's I I
found the blue I found the blue yeah
yeah they're in the Saw s I forgot to
tell you guys it's um it's a king of the
hill objective so you want to get the
control Point yeah yeah oh okay so we
have to stay there okay I I think
everybody hit the all right CCE needs
healing I died to the
Trap I guess you that there you want to
play a game I'm not going to make that
why you should say
it past can kind of make
sense or or I should say I saw that com
[Music]
I need we need
healing
to
I'm I'm trying to K you are getting
points I can't tell
honestly so what do we have to do uh
stay in the Blue Zone to get points I
think or or oh no
okay we need to
heal uhoh behind us
King of the Hill everyone we're waiting
we're winning don't foret there's heal
on the ground we're actually not
winning we just have to stay in the Box
area and not let them kill
us okay we have to minut over
us
nice yeah
[Music]
okay use the saw coverage it helps oh
assuming you don't get hit by
it I'll go heal you if I can get there
I'm don't worry I'm distracting them I'm
distracting
them okay you guys
defend okay we're catching up with 20
seconds I'm going to throw myself at
them
there there's a scout in the Bas crony
or at the at the thing at the at the the
at the flag get
him are we doing pretty well almost half
and half yeah they capturing the they're
capturing the thingy we don't really
getting I'll
come I'm back in the house right oh it's
the end it's the end of the house
oh shoot they have a
medic SC medic good job
CeCe know where we are if we shoot
them don't quick quick they're capturing
the point again they captured it we have
to go back to the point okay go okay oh
oh
here where is it is over here I thought
it right here at the
Sawmill yeah up the stairs up this hill
okay I will just follow you team now
here's the
house oh this
sounds go in the house we definitely
need a Healer near the saw there there m
go in the house
no oh good
job is there a way
go in the house oh no house in the house
watch they'll be in the house go in the
house go in the
house any go in the house oh that's we
got yes that's attack them let's go in
the house in the
house oh there's one hidden I think
Under the
Stairs oh she's dead we're going
to are we just keep healing not the oh
there's AIC on the yeah do keep healing
where the medic someone saw that
[Laughter]
coming why are you fake laughing it's
hey what if that a genuine laughter are
you making fun of my
laugh sorry sorry my bad get the get the
Healer you're outside here
there you go oh behind you
no oh
[Music]
wow help help they're all here it's okay
you got this one maybe we need more than
one Healer just to be safe cuz we are
defend I'm doing my best no I think I
think you should stay as your thing
you're actually pretty good
CeCe I would prefer you to
have
on no they captured It Go
why did I die Elizabeth is why you
die they're going to win they're going
to win kill kill
kill I'll be
healer go in the house go in the house
almost wi so confus
almost we tried I thought
we oh my God blue is a good color that's
why is a good color
okay so we have it's okay we have a
second chance now second chance at Li I
can chance I'll stay behind you okay I
okay so all right now we actually know
the objective so objective I don't know
all right to the center you guys see the
numbers 3 minutes yeah yeah yeah so if
you guys hold one point that point for 3
minutes we're we're D run away run away
run away
wa we're dying we're dying we're dying
I'm trying to get run away
run oh crap that's a bottle the shared
Point yeah Whoever has it makes the time
go down okay okay I did not do
balls all right you
should take my
balls I don't understand that oh right
click the detonate okay I thought I
Wasing balls okay I set them on fire
surely it helps
so
useful te
yes we want to kill blue yeah
nobody's I think this is working well
just stay down damage they know they no
they don't know they don't know balls
they don't know I'm here if you're in
the house come behind the the
[Music]
wood okay
take my it does no damage it's actually
I don't really like
it Go St behind the wood go go away go
away yeah good job good job going away
okay go he go okay I don't like this I
can't go
heal ah there's to many of
them yeah there so many heavy all right
I'm going to I'm tapping in I'm going to
help you guys a little bit okay
mom's coming mom who wants some Pockets
um you are damaged here you
go I am
Hing okay never
mind I tried go go
go oh that's your
[Music]
I'm trying to kill I hit him
once
no they're so
s was nice am I in the wrong team
no wow
nice we so hide we so hide on it I died
oh the lag oh what yeah lagy oh
okay oh God nice I guess I'll uh I'll
chill I actually can't move
now
the oh no never
mind going to have to wait for us I
think I see
oh yeah I I can't move at all so okay
yeah so you guys come here often I'm
also being clicked through
walls no it's okay the game's trying to
Nerf us because we so good yeah they
know we're going to
win
[Music]
yeah so are we
losing I still feel the
lag yeah they're feeling the lag too
it's
okay okay we can we can get the point
here just don't run into the all
hopefully
move Mission be ending
soon oh
Tri hey at least [\h__\h] time down let's go
okay
overtime time on the point I'm trying I
was not letting me
up cled out it's okay we still have
somebody watch out I'm walking I'm
walking there what's
overtime we we got it we got it we got
it we we keep on it the has I'm trying I
I can't I can't move now good luck
everyone not go you are the single
letter oh I can't I
can't I'm like a
plant rubber banding oh my God oh God I
can't to the door
oh this is what it feels like to fast
forward in
time so we wait until the
servering oh I think it's back going
it's fine it's going good yeah it feels
better now okay for me it's like rubber
bending still so like I don't know if
that's the way turn but like yeah yeah
I'm a little
ball weird you weird weird that you
little B maybe May
huh
maybe they don't have it
yet some
time te no I don't know okayed team I
think they they're
capturing I'm fro is this a new game
touch it touch it it's not too late it's
not too late what if what if I change
teams write this
instant look guys I
won all right uh we can go back into all
chat and then uh I think there's like a
sandbox mode we could do and then we'll
just uh yeah and
then thank you thank
you place good good
game G
GG oh that was luy
wait a
minute GG oh I get it now
we never too late never too
late never too late never too late is it
still isn't it still lagging should we
like I can't move at all yeah yeah it's
still lagging the lag has been really
bad can we restart somehow yeah it's for
us it's not lagging it's just stopped
yeah oh it stopped the server
stopped before it kicked us out it
disconnected and now now it's just
nothing's going yeah yeah crony also got
kicked out and for me and 's just like
moving yeah I can't move right now
yeah I see okay yeah um I think I could
reset the server or also I mean we
pretty much played for the amount of
time we were going to play
true was so fast it was fun you guys it
was fun
along with the
[Music]
whole if anything we learned how to
differentiate colors which is yeah I
still do not know how to do that we're
not color blind you guys got better
about it yeah that was
[Applause]
fun thank you I'm looking forward to G
mod thank thank you
thank you so
[Music]
much thank you
byee byebye
byebye byebye
byebye all right I don't know who will
be in Gary's mod but I you can go there
manually for I cannot check and I cannot
redirect so hope you had fun I dang this
game is old I cannot out tab I'm playing
in Window
mode and I'll see you guys for the the
Batman Begins watchong in a few hours
probably like around 4ish hours or three
and a halfish so I'll see you then until
then
[Music]
sh sh sh
for
[Music]