[Music]
true
sleep talking
away
[Music]
he notori
heart Challenger
[Music]
Sparks
favorite night
[Music]
do you
hate all those things
[Music]
[Applause]
first album
point of view
pineapple
[Music]
love Rush
the great Wanderer
[Music]
[Applause]
retrospective
[Music]
tell you
sleep talking
back
[Music]
heart Challenger
Sparks
[Music]
favorite night
give me that
let me know
[Music]
do you
love hate all the same
[Music]
hello
welcome actually
um
is too small actually and now I realize
yes that's that's better but yeah hello
everybody Welcome Back to the collab
relay hey hello
Kelly could you take up your your heels
because I think behind you there will be
something
take off your heels as in like maybe go
a little bit oh I mean I guess I can get
a little yeah aren't the heels like
uncomfortable you know
and I don't want to be barefoot in the
studio
um well they're slippers slippers go
take the slippers
so okay hello welcome we have another
game show here we we
yeah I'm sure time we're doing all the
classics um and all of them homemade
yeah so
what is it what is it what is it gonna
be it is
homemade Family Feud with me
and I used to love that show yeah we're
fighting yes against uh yeah yeah
actually
um you can do teams I was thinking of
maybe doing teams
um but I don't know how to form them uh
how about
um
um uh uh say
DM me DM DM me uh the letter A or the
letter B
what is three people what what if three
people choose B well then we'll do it
again maybe
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah that's what I wanted
there might be like some differences and
rules maybe a little bit oh but yeah
we're gonna go with how it's seemingly
easy to play and
um oh sorry good on my hair is in your
face that's okay it smells nice
[Music]
and uh the questions are indeed hollow
life or YouTuber related questions
yes I just before the stream a little
bit before the stream
um I did some polling and pulling
pulling I show some questions and then
we we chose some I chose some answers I
did like a like a form to collect
everything and then I sorted it out so
that's where we are so if you want to
get started with some family
oh
I'll sit okay okay well well the first
question let me show you
one ah wait yeah you have to buzz when
you think you know the answer
is this on the screen name a common
feature look character beam
okay wait that the first one was kalai
primary there's by the way five answers
the top five if you give me the number
one it will give you five points and if
you give me number two it'll give you
four points Etc but Kelly you're working
in a team anyway so in the end your your
points will be together with your
teammates yes so what do you think is a
common YouTuber character theme
sea creatures
creatures let me see if that is on the
board
no it's not
you're kidding me it's unfortunately not
oh no
then I will go
I will go with number two of the buzzers
next was
oh let's see if cats it's on the board
hey how specific are we supposed to get
with these Kiara's um
I did put together some very similar
ones in some cases
uh let me show you
this is a bit okay yeah with with 100
free votes out of like 300 yeah it's
number one
games
[Music]
congratulations your team now gains Five
Points
here
your teammate is Ina right yeah yeah so
she also gets it
[Music]
okay but there's still four more answers
um should I go by who already buzzed I
think so right okay then I'm it would be
next I mean what do you think what else
is up there on the board
see if Birds is a common theme for
YouTubers
[Music]
um
oh it indeed is
more common than sea creatures
actually well let me wait sorry I'm I'm
scared to show something that you don't
want to see yet
yes okay bird is indeed on
spot number five
19 common votes yeah so you get a two
points I think for your team come
[Music]
nice
okay we have three more answers on the
board last but not least would be Ina
and then everybody gets a chance again
um
what could it be
good campfire
vampires yes that's a good guess let's
see if that is on the board probably not
it is
unfortunately for you that was not on
the board now I will reset the buzzer
and then yeah okay
you our hands are fast on that buzzer
let's see gouda what else do you think
is on the board
doggies she's just going through the
common animals
well
maybe no it is actually not
um
but not in the top five uh actually
surprising the problem is there's like
there there no okay I I won't say it I
think this is this is fine this is fine
it's not on the board next is
um
demon
[Music]
is that on the board let's take a look
everybody
ah
indeed it is congratulations
it was
number three number three
devils and devils and demons together
with 32. that's nice that is three
points for your team congratulations
thanks I can sleep tonight
okay next on the buzzer was Inya what do
you think it is number two
[Music]
take a chance go for it
and try Shrine mate what is it Shrine
mate yeah
[Music]
oh no unfortunately next one is
come on girls pink
YouTuber oh
how do I say this so far you had cat
devil demon that demon demon and bird
what about like uh I'm not oh God how do
you say oh by the way this is not like
what's actually comic book what people
think is common in the end so
oh
why didn't you tell us that before Kiara
you would you ask opinions of people so
um
what did you say something
what would you call like uh like he's an
eye like that kind of virtual digital
girl how would you say that girl Idol
girl I girl
cute girl
choose yours that's what I was gonna say
I don't know how else to say
none of that none of that is on there
unfortunately
next is Maureen Calliope give it a try
let's see can I give you a foundation
yeah go for it yes the team what do you
think of like maybe bunny or something
that could be pretty common
yeah I was gonna say fox though oh yeah
either of them either Fox Maybe
go for a fox okay
[Music]
it is one of this is the last one the
number five all right I'll take it I'll
take some points yes with uh like 16. 16
votes uh it's up there you indeed get
one point for that
yes let's go Point uh wait for team
rainforest yes it's good that you're
staying confident in in your beliefs
yeah okay next is uh
um I'll say the last one is difficult
because it's kind of I'll give you a
hint it's kind of like a different way
of thinking about it than the others
others that you cleared so far are like
very specific
Ally
and this one is not
Mori raises eyebrows at Kiara from over
here
hey let's begin it's just what what you
don't want to clear about it this is
what the people put into the form well
see that's what I said too but I didn't
get Ninja Kiara
you didn't give me you didn't you kept
coming at me what you got [\h__\h] right
I know what are you complaining about
it's not what this is about you
complained about my game Kiara I'm
coming after you I can't help you okay
okay uh yes
I do
idle let's see if that is on the board
it is
in free two one
[Music]
your turn
I'm gonna steal Amazon so I'm gonna try
bunny oh wait no you said it has nothing
to do with the previous one no go ahead
go ahead
I'll leave that for you you can have
that one would you like to lock in that
answer no ma'am I would not no
um
uh
asymmetrical clothing
uneven stockings or gloves or on one
hand or something like that okay oh
that's like it's in some way that is
very specific and very vague interesting
interesting but it's not on the board
unfortunately
next up is sweet sweets oh yeah like
candy scene kind of like uh
everybody's going in the direction that
is not very good so let me just I think
I know what it is I know what it is
unfortunately uh the next one is Maury
the answer is gamer
but when you're going to the vague
Direction it's it's good you mean okay
is that what you mean like yeah it's
like maybe broad like Broadway okay
[Music]
oh my god I didn't even announce it the
color blue blue
no it's not about the colors
unfortunately
singer
it's not singer Amelia Watson
and a girl
[Laughter]
are you doing this uh wait I'm sorry
like normally in family if you you get
like like X like right like like you get
like three chances at a certain point
yeah at a certain point it stops okay
should we stop after this because uh Ena
didn't buzz anyway yeah I have no idea
okay this girl was wrong I'm so sorry
guys I didn't really want to accept this
answer because it's so vague but
unfortunately the last one was animal
like any kind of animals
what what would you like to say
what is the matter
I was definitely gonna guess that
but you said that's too big
when some animals it was the animals
animals
you're allowed to give a big ass what
what I said
[Music]
I said more vague I said that no just go
to the next question okay
we are going to the next question
[Music]
and I'm clearing the buzzers after I
read the question this whole life Ian
Japan ID member is commonly fought as
say so what do the people think clearing
buzzers in three two one
look we are starting with Google
oh uh I'm gonna guess uh
senpai
Sam's pie is sort of senpai up there
let's check let's try and
it is getting the number one
let's go that gives your team five extra
points and you are up to 10.
wow
look at
it
yeah okay oh yeah because the numbers
are the same okay so Sona is not a
possible option anymore let's go for
Cali primor what do you think is do
people think is say so
let's see
uh this is a serious question right it's
not a I think you should also consider
the fact that like most like I could
probably tell you 100 en speaking fans
are voting sometimes they yeah because I
said Ian Japan ID they might be putting
in Japan ID members too but you know
they might be biased towards en members
so they're probably more en members in
here
all right well if you phrase it like
that then I'm gonna have to choose an En
member
um I think that's a good idea okay
and you and you can give this to me I
helped you out here so let's let's be
good again okay
all right I forgive you I forgive you
for making fun of my game is
[Music]
good congratulations
[Laughter]
oh my God
oh my God they're all at 10 let's go
okay next was oh no who do you think who
else could be there
um
think hard
you can also discuss with your teammate
what do you think Guru I was gonna say
aqua
[Music]
English speakers
yeah I'm like I'm like questioning hmm
bonna okay we can lock that in if that's
what you want okay I'll I'll go with
Father all right let me check
oh father is indeed on the board and you
guys are going by order so far because
[Music]
yeah
every time I think I fall I can't help
but to remember her Hitman streams and
like her
they're official
[Music]
yeah probably more safer than some other
oh okay so next was Amber oh wait you're
still gonna get points though uh that's
three points right for your team
and 13. next we have amen go ahead
um Ian member or ID or JP I think anyone
an ID is is going to be yeah
on the board
[Music]
I'm clearing the buzzer in a moment
okay clearing we have one more left okay
oh
oh that might be a good guess I think I
even saw her when I was sorting out the
answers but she's not on the board
unfortunately
yeah
I will I will give everybody a hint
indeed the last one is not an En member
the last one we're missing
you can give a guess
remember
I mean someone who I didn't know was
considered to say so like I mean I guess
now that they say it I guess it probably
is so I never saw her doing anything not
say so I guess I was saying
um
which one do you want to lock in
[Music]
options
I'll go we'll go watch a bit with uh
Cali's yeah
[Music]
I think I saw her mentioned like once or
twice in the I mean
I feel like a lot of Ian fans already
knows a lot of fun
thing okay
do you have a guess
okay
um
I'm gonna go with I am a senpai I am a
senpai I'm a surprise not on the board
what all right we're gonna start fire
emblem
to me
foreign
[Music]
buzzers in three two one
you gotta
Cali please
all right I'm putting my guess on irowa
correct
I was sweating when Emma mentioned you
know how but didn't go for it
I would have yeah but you got it nice
I guess so yeah
yeah I know that I think about it she
really doesn't but it surprised me like
like even if you don't do anything say
so it doesn't necessarily mean that
you're considered as uh you must do
something in particular to be considered
wait what breaks to say so
cursing and talking about looting yeah
yeah probably I think I think okay girls
we we cleared this one with the combined
power good job
did I get the team right it was
yes yes yeah yeah I think Matt is saying
everybody should have 13 but I don't
know really
yeah they're saying the score is wrong I
don't know if it's gaslighting but it
might be true okay
really okay all right we're nice
you can give up two points I don't mind
you guys are trying to screw us over
chat huh that's fun
rainforest Will Rain Supreme I give free
buns for a question that was in the
number five oh okay well thank you guys
for keeping score better than me I'm
nervous you know right now and man
you're doing FICO you know together so
it's fine okay
flash news coming up
okay this whole live YouTuber brought
people into the rabbit hole oh no I'm
clearing buzzers though three two one
[Music]
is on the board
she is on the board I just have to um
first hide the window to find because I
I blacked out everything let me find my
shoes oh there she is she is
do
[Music]
oh that's right
that means Four Points as far as I am
concerned for Callie's team let's go up
to 17. wow congratulations
how do you feel number two what people
think
we brought them in here yes that's
pretty cool wow wow wow thank you for
bringing so many people in let's go
yeah
yeah okay
yeah you'll guess I'm gonna I'm gonna
say Corona Senpai again yeah that's a
really cool
wow correct this
vessel and she is
yeah that's about right with
106. wow it's going it's a lot
that's uh Five Points uh so you are up
to 18. oh my God
okay next up would be amazing
take a good look
yes she is
number three
um oh no not that one no it is
very nice yeah but still good that's two
points
very nice and next one guessing is
make a good guess
[Music]
a reason why I got dragged into the
rabbit hole but is she on the board
[Music]
I know I know it's shocking
um shocking wait sorry I mistake she is
on the board she's the last one okay
there was no way she didn't bring yeah
other people I think it was a really
close one there was one right after her
with one less boat and yeah I thought it
was switched around ah yeah she was my
alarm no no
what was the alarm saying she was
laughing now
[Music]
how does that wake you up yeah because
it's it's it's it's iconic it's loud you
know
yeah perfect way to wake up in the
morning let's not tell that her laugh is
still swapping though
this is like way before TV too so it was
like I was a whole like fan so I was
like her laugh was iconic woke me up
yeah yeah that is indeed okay we have
one more and I'll reset the buses for
you to one
she's nice you know
who you think is the the missing one The
Missing Link
[Music]
she is now before she kissed
it must be the I'm a sketch man
yeah among other things
20 21 22.
22 I think you're up to 22. good wait
come on
let's go to the next question
[Music]
terms that you would only hear in a
vtubers chat
I'm clearing the buzzes in three two one
okay Callie what do you think could be
up there on the board
yeah is it up there oh let me check oh
it
is but it's the the last one Maji I mean
I guess I kind of believe that yeah oh
the reason why it says four here even
though it's the last one is because
there were two of the same amount of
votes that are out there
okay
next is amen
[Music]
that's a pretty common like Japanese one
I mean I guess for
people on this side of the world you'd
really only see it in vtuber chats okay
I know what I think
[Music]
um
whoever's next
feel free to give me the guess I think
it's uh goodbye
is it you know which one is it what's
the the the
Kusa
let's check
that's my correct Sound by the way
[Applause]
yeah really
did I do it wrong again really but now
you're getting four points
uh that's that's 22 what
what be correct right it can't be wrong
23 I think I didn't get a point for
answering uh
oh okay I believe
Sumi Masari I have too many windows open
right now it's okay you're doing good
it's okay we they know we're not good at
math
no it's not a math
it's a multitasking issue okay we have
two more answers up there and they have
the same amount of votes so you will get
wait actually
should I give for toscato because it's
only number four not one point but two
points
you know what I mean because the the
next ones will be giving that is up to
you
that doesn't matter it doesn't matter
it's up to you ah it's whatever and
whatever okay you chat in the end you
just tell me the final challenge
who's next Who's Next you know me yeah
what do you think
baby
[Music]
but it was one of the ones that didn't
make it to the top five
[Music]
yeah
I guessed it she was ready what do you
think uh say so
and we want me is on there indeed and
it's nice
[Applause]
31.31 okay
and then uh
uh last one fill this out for me please
will you
[Music]
know if I should I say buba or Kawaii
so your options
do you think those are so common this
one yeah
well it's in my chat it would be free
[Music]
hmm
a hard one I gotta say
I mean because it's like
you see Kawaii like everywhere right
yeah
but then
I don't know I guess I guess I can't
really relate to people being in chat a
lot because
you have to do that yourself you know
it's okay it hits hard
because of time issues and me wanting to
bring all the questions out this is your
last chance until I clear the board
[Music]
is indeed something that's probably used
a lot in the Japanese chats I don't see
it so much in the enchant
yeah
the last one was oshin
okay
[Music]
I think like from the en audience
probably like most of them didn't hear
about of this world until they joined
this community
it's true yes yes and it's being very
much used at the moment so that was that
next question shall we move on let's go
oh yeah it's the best whole life duo or
couplings
according to you know the people who
voted
yes so I'm clearing the buzzes in three
two one
[Music]
I made it
Cali bank is on my summer
let me see if it's on there I'm
surprised you go for Amazon let's go
it's correct correct
obvious if we chose the other one wait
did I give uh I didn't need to give out
any more points right okay because
nobody got it okay here this one is
just hiding it for a moment but it is
number
three three
oh not five but fifty one
fifty one one there we go Yahoo all
right next is
definitely one that comes to mind for me
as well and it's correct yes
the Amazon was three points for uh Kelly
and mama so that's uh 34 and uh 34. and
then you just got four points right
um Four Points that's twenty seven is
this count correct
chances is correct okay wow there's a
big cats here wow
okay Shirley Dina is next
oh okay girls I'm kind of disappointed
by you guys right now just give me a
minute Kiara give me a minute yeah we're
gonna get there
it was I saw like a few minutes but it's
not in the top five
the gods here coupling of course but
it's not bad
let's go next go next okay
finally oh my God
yeah because it's not of course the boat
was maybe a little bit biased but even
if it wasn't biased I think takamori is
one of the most well-known couples in
Ian yeah that is true that is true so it
is well known okay that gives you Five
Guys
I know I feel that already nine oh my
God
that's that's incredible okay but we
have two of the like bottom ones then
before number five still left over uh
we're resetting right that was amazing
now okay uh three two one
Cali go ahead
all right uh bayeris
ferris ferris
Paris is
m
41. oh my God I'm learning math with the
stream and uh
who could be okay I actually I don't
think you girls are gonna guess the last
one because the last one is a biased
definitely a biased answer
oh I know what it is your child from
view yeah
would it be you and rainy or you and and
uh
involved yeah okay who's the other
person in the room the other person no
no
what do you think your heart wants to
say
what does your heart say what did you do
okay I know I know I know I was gonna
say Kiara and rainy
[Music]
for each other very much yes
definitely biased answer but we'll
forgive it
I think we gotta speed it up a little
bit because I want to do all the
questions we have um five more
oh my God
I don't know if we're gonna have time
but okay well likely to stay whole in
whole life until the end oh okay okay
clearing buzzes and free two one I also
wait this is um uh considering any whole
life member but
the answer is Juicy No actually they're
pretty mixed they're pretty mixed okay
Japan and uh en members only let's go
three two one
uh Marie
senpai
try to try to speed up my my side as
well here there it is
next uh please I'm in
shoot Kelly do you have one do you have
a good one
um I was gonna say maybe Sora
okay yeah yeah yeah I'll go with that is
[Music]
congratulations I do believe she will be
here forever as well yeah that's another
four points and brings you to 48 I think
uh
[Music]
okay if they put their answers in surely
right
Kiara has to be number one you think
Sakura
I don't know I don't know
[Applause]
okay I'll say
ah I'll say koala
yes but I don't even I
don't know
some biased there but still I think I
know he has been very tenacious right
almost yeah I mean totally not ringed
but the others are not really biased so
try to get the others too yeah
um this was for Ina wow wow Five Points
that's 32
and 32 Gouda
yeah bring it on
[Music]
two more for the the Umi c bond baby
are you sure
well now that you said it that way oh my
God I feel like clear just bored
are you sure
who is considered tenacious
star
[Music]
oh
oh that's so interesting what makes you
think she's uh tenacious
I guess I mean yeah she is okay
she is number five
no that's amazing good job out of all
those members that we have she does have
a tenacious story yeah she does yes okay
reciting the buzzer please give me the
last answer Go I mean I don't know
Amelia Watson
ooh uh Cali what do you think I was
gonna go with like two buddies or
something yeah I was gonna maybe say um
wait wait I give you a hint
the last person is a mogus
what last person
um it might be color if you want is it
could I be more
guys
[Music]
yeah I'll continue giving all of them
I have a lot of things to do
yeah I don't think you're leaving
anytime soon even if even if you wanted
to
no I'm not all right let's go to the
next question section thing in
okay well we have eight more minutes oh
no problem no problem best questions
Minecraft
is Minecraft on there oh it is number
one
let's go
so uh uh five points for you girls who's
next
okay
[Music]
um
um um uh Jaguar because uh Jack box
is
[Music]
yay it is the last one number five
uh that's uh that's one point right one
point
or
um that team okay uh next is Ina
Mario Party
[Music]
friendship's destroyed
pretty much intact it was number two so
you're getting four points I think
please next answer please can I go yeah
I think so uh Kelly wait what do you
think I was gonna do super Bunny man but
whatever's gonna say Among Us
oh yeah yeah wow
[Music]
okay okay that's three points man okay
and then we are already moving on let's
go
BB
music yeah okay next last not last we
have a few more who deserves according
to Ian fans the title of gamer of Ian
and let me tell you the answers are not
as biased as you might think
in three two one
Cali go ahead oh no
it's fine it's butter according to the
people the gamer of Ian yes she is
[Music]
if you want me in anything
well didn't we didn't we do a Mario
cart
um back in the the arcade
yeah yeah and she owned us all right oh
well okay next is Ina give it a try
um
I'll say it I'll give you one hint
yes because you're behind too
um there's no more council members
mentioned
oh okay okay I have a chance
Bible
people is people under she's a new
member does she already have the
reputation of a gamer yes she does yeah
building that reputation fast I love
that rock again it's 44
okay okay who's next I'm in I mean I
mean
I'll tell you I voted for you when I
wrote
thank you
[Music]
you know being the game of Yen doesn't
necessarily mean that you have to be you
know the best gamer just a gamer that
that shows that they game a lot yeah
so yeah that gives you uh three points
and good as next I think
okay Bloody Mary
on there
robot maybe maybe
yeah so that's one point okay am I
clearing the buzzer again I think I am
okay uh
universe
I'll tell you the secret yeah it's like
a lot
[Music]
um gura no but it's not on there okay I
know I know
yeah right Kiara yes correct
answer
oh bias
um
no no
not at all see next time we play Family
Feud like this I'm gonna pull all the
fandoms okay
see what comes out then okay we're
moving on I only have two more okay we
also started a bit late so I'll go
through all of them okay because I'm
proud of them
okay okay the next one is who would win
an IRL Sports tournament
or everybody
um this was for everybody but the
answers are
um mostly em and maybe one Japanese
member
yes okay clearing three to one
oh
yes
yes I don't know why why I buzzed in
um just kidding all right
they lift weights
number one congratulations I mean I'm
not great at sports I exercise a lot but
you do exercise you know that's that's
the minimum criteria that many people
don't have
yeah I think that's uh 74 right oh my
God 74. who's next in the buzzer please
go ahead and say something ah ah crony
some of the votes said crony but not
enough next is uh
I'll say bae
oh baby it's considered a sporty girl
she is better
okay two points congratulations
and coupon next I think
uh
uh Miller Watson
Emilia
is she sporty enough to be on the board
am I strong yeah
[Music]
that's true
okay and then we have uh the clearing of
the buzzers three two one oh
okay oh yeah
that would be the last one
someone sporty in the end besides these
people voila
kill
my swimming reps okay thank you
I don't think I would really win a
tournament IRL Sports tournament but you
know I mean you're more fit than a lot
of us
all those dicks because you dance a lot
yeah oh yeah I do okay then we have
reached the last one let's go let's go
name something that uh a YouTuber has on
their desk I think this is very
interesting three two one
their their iPhone
oh
[Music]
technically that
that would probably be an accidentally
that uh if if this was pulled among
YouTubers would probably be up there but
it's called among viewers so they're not
so aware probably
next uh Cali microphone microphone
it is
the number three
[Applause]
feet is an option
on the desk I do not recommend uh
mentioning any body parts
okay next is Nina
um the keyboard keyboard yeah yeah yeah
keyboard is not necessarily something
that only videos happened on the desk so
it is a very very open answer but yes
it's up there
or 54 and um before that was
before that was Cali who got three
points made
it okay who's last is
uh hydration water
cornbread that's awesome
nice one up okay it's
uh number two oh wow
okay but it's not a water bottle though
right now
clearing buzzer three two one
oh
[Music]
boogers dirty dishes dirty dishes
Chad can you just help me out here in
the moment
operating on a different level
closed and you know
um
um help me out here Goomba do you think
controller is a good
answer
um
[Music]
I'll give you a hint yes one is
something that is pretty specific to
streamers to have on their desk
oh it doesn't help
like an audio interface or mixers
oh
yeah
this is so true
wow
I lost track because I wanted to go fast
at the end but I think in any case Cali
and AMA probably won
oh yeah nice job but you you caught up a
bit at the end
[Music]
congratulations thank you for the game
that was stream number two of our collab
relay there's three more to go next one
is on Ian's Channel
to my channel yeah we'll be drawing
we'll be playing garlic phone so there
might need to be some setup time uh yes
okay oh merch
my merch went up off stream please let
me say my merch is on is there now you
can purchase it now it's in the
description or also pinned in the
comments please support me by getting
married nice
and all of our merchandise anyway but
you know everybody
getting redirected so just stay and then
click on the redirect offer to ninoma
okay guys
[Music]
foreign