for
[Music]
t
hello good evening everyone hello
welcome back long time no see finally we
are back
again with Minecraft
hello hello good morning good morning
good afternoon good evening wherever you
are today we are
entering
day day four it's actually should be day
four but um I was like one day late so
this is my third day so
yeah so
good so good long time nosi I just saw
you loging in this afternoon L long time
nosi it's been a while I kind of miss
streaming yeah Naga Onan time finally
you can meet your belov laa friend yeah
laat Tomo by the way enjoy the game Kyle
thank you Roby wolf glad to see you
having lots of fun new friends
adventures and goals may the good times
continue also appreciate all the help
you provide others to make the
experience enjoyable good luck have fun
thank you Kum in Dark Souls they call it
Holo here it's Halo D get some help I've
had 8 hours total sleep in the past two
days I'm
holl get some help I need I need no what
I need I need
no get some help I think I think you
really need to sleep yeah um I know that
I need a lot of uh pamalo luck but
please please please please make sure
that you have some
sleep don't don't be like Kyla because
you're totally not Kyla
so pamalo please if you really really
need to rest please go sleep like right
now even though the stream just
started please go to sleep if you need
to
bang yeah
a bro Soul send grind tonight good luck
heav take the luck even better so s
grind why why we need to grind we just
need we just need like half stack of
Soul Sand and then we just go back to
the Overworld right we don't need to do
like many many things about that right
we just we just take what we need and
then we go back isn't it right I know h
thank you hello hello for months thank
you let's let's go let's go yeah
congrats Emerald gang let's
go we need more than we need sleep get
some help don't do
and then hello you cannot express Beauty
with light from the sun and there are
many believers who believe in you what
I'm I'm not something that people should
believe don't trust me I don't even
trust
myself you'll have to dig many diamonds
in the future to meet their Expectations
by the way this is the fact no that's
not the fact thank
you
uh so
H oh they found my
place I don't know because because I you
know
um I was
like your house has lots of gas oh I
don't know because I lock out up uh
before I uh before I went to my dinner
and then after that I thought okay I
thing um I I I got the protection 4 for
pretty cheap price right so I thought um
before they go to the nether maybe they
going to need
it and maybe some of them also try to
find The Mending book so I put a
coordinates to the trading
Hall uh because I I put the coordinates
on the server like the Discord server I
say something
like if you need The Mending
book wait uh I I say something like if
you need to repair your tools or
something like that the manding book uh
it's it's inongo right so I don't know
if I type it correctly or not but I said
something like if you want to repair
your tools you can go
to yeah I I put the coordinates there
right so I don't know if any of them
like um read that actually actually I
don't
know
yeah get some help they say the book is
tiep at that place
oh of course the book is cheap because I
don't know I I grind I grind that for
like I don't know it's almost 20 hours
grind for all of the books and it's
actually not finished yet because I
couldn't I couldn't find um efficiency 5
with a very cheap one I got several
efficiency 5 but it's like 50 50 64 so I
still don't really have one yet and when
I when I found like the cheaper one I
just killed the the first
fager to switch it so
I guess I'm happy if they
feel
that
uh
useful by the
way you found the Unbreaking three so
what's left for what's next I think the
only thing I don't know what's where
where the power five go I lost the power
five and then I also need um the I got
the fortune tree already I got the
Unbreaking tree already uh I got
protection four
already I only need uh efficiency five
right now the the most PRI is efficiency
5 and if I could find any um Power five
that should be
good efficiency five yeah h
the one you kill is the power five doar
I don't know I think I mistakenly killed
a villager I don't know it was still
there in the afternoon the power five
but why it's gone when kiaha came to the
place I don't
know good evening K thank you just ky's
react when being how get some help
moment Mas yeah thank youo hello thank
you what's that
[Music]
halation get some help what do you mean
don't sleep go sleep full nether armor
let's go nah nether is very hard to okay
the ancient debris might be not that
hard to get but
upgrading your armors and tools to neite
is pretty hard in the Minecraft new
update so I don't even think if I can
get like NRA upgrade I don't
know no t t Tor is only for the week no
don't say that everyone need
Tor thank you finally Kyla can be back
to her habited nice I'm very afraid very
scared copy atalo let's go get some help
don't copy copy we only sleep in
Minecraft don't do that thank you to
much thank
[Music]
you please sleep guys please sleep or
else you're going to lose your mind and
lost your soul like
me uh it's been 3 days already and then
uh I'm starting to seeing things already
please uh and the
[Music]
demon the demon inside of me uh is very
visible to me right now dang
yeah please please please don't do
that bro you're the one need sleep I
don't think so thank you noris go for
you Kylie you have reignited my love for
finecraft hardcore modon let's go oh I'm
on day three my son have gotten some di
finally let's go
GK
you what is that sleep I don't
know but yeah please do sleep hold on
let me AR the sush bus like real quick
before I got into the game KY do as I
say not as I do exactly tasas tenasity
thank you don't worry it's morning for
me nice then wow how long time no so
happy to see you have so much fun this
part happy happy adventure thank
you good luck thank
you so the goal okay let's uh let's plan
what we going to do today today we're
going to see the mission
first uh because I actually saw the
mission from peora Senpai news already
but I want to say it again uh
[Music]
um hold on
uh wait where is my Google Translate no
what this
one yeah we going to check the daily
missions
first
hi uh
put it back and then this one we need to
put it
back and then we're going to che check
Che we're going to check this because
people say that uh there were like a lot
of guests
wait they leave this for
me someone literally forgot their
crafting table here
[Music]
LC okay uh
Fortune so I have Fortune three for 28 I
have mending for 10 and 18 for infinity
and then looting three for 16 I have
Unbreaking three for
11 right so good right Unbreaking three
for 11 and then feather falling 4 for 20
and then the sharpness five for 20
and then flame for five and then silk
touch for five it can go as slow as one
actually and then I have this protection
for for only
15 and then the torns tree 15 the torns
if you remember the torns should be on
the first Booth but why it's on the last
Booth
because yeah because I try to find the
cheaper
one everything is uh everything here are
very very uh cheap
price right it's very cheap and let's
see if they take uh take a
free
Hab uh the S touch oh
almost okay it was like two lines before
Oh the books also
gone
okay The Mending they really like The
Mending
actually actually I haven't put the I
haven't put um I haven't put a chest
like there should be another chest B uh
besides the Unbreaking actually but
maybe they didn't
know I I didn't expect anyone to come
that fast actually uh the Unbreaking is
actually
here yeah
because there was a raid even earlier so
they R
oh oh I see
in a seed but didn't take us inside the
house yeah because I that time I haven't
I haven't made uh I haven't made the
chest yet
and I'm not really sure where to put it
because this is like
um it's kind of like
symmetrical not really but well I don't
know um maybe I should put it somewhere
I don't know uh the Unbreaking the
breaking is here right maybe it should
be like here CH but
[Music]
later you can get rid of the crafting
table looks like Ina forgot and made
another one yeah free crafting table for
me thank you so
much and actually I still need to do
this you
know but I don't know uh hold on I need
to sleep I
[Music]
know that's our luck Ella [\h__\h] luck but
it's off stream lck
98 thank you don't worry I read that
already thank you dumb question anyone
here ever impulsively spread their arms
out and start limp walking almost
looking like you're a penguin W wedling
because of how cold it is during the
evening in Winter or just me oh I don't
know oh yeah it's winter in Aussie right
now right yeah but in the other places I
guess it's like uh Fair very hot right
now oh
well X bread do thank you and in ID we
don't have winter too
so it's always hot in ID
though it's a tropical
Country tropical
country why the iron is like dying who H
you
[Music]
okay that's a dip question right there
yeah who heard you
the is not
here do you consider it as a good thing
to not have winters at
all kind of yes it's actually like a
6040 but
actually if you want if if you ask me
whether if I going to pick like four
weather or just two weather I prefer the
two weather one even though it's always
hot
but I mean it's easier that way you
know for me that's just personal
[Music]
opinion yeah few more weeks before
winter but still freezing ah expr
talking you uh survive try to
survive don't
die oh Miki oh yeah Miki uh joined the
server
already so welcome to the
server hello
hello hello
hello thank
[Music]
you thank youe Fortune Fortune oh
Fortune Fortune here Fortune
here here thank you Fortune wait Fortune
wait
um Emerald
emal thank you
[Music]
I don't have
enough
iron thank you very much I saw your
stream for a long time yesterday after I
died
thank you thank you very
much don't die again please survive I
need you I will I will never die but if
I die again I cannot come back never oh
wait wait wait
wait we should we should give her the
water potion hold on just in case
take
this oh thank you very much what oh
po thank
you I will I will give something for you
wait please wait for it okay I will find
something okay okay yes I will thank you
very
much P happy happy happy yay happy happy
I'm so happy that you're
back yes I'm
back do you need something else do you
need anything no it's okay thank you ask
S I need
anything
anything wow done a fortune
Fortune
yay thank
you okay okay thank you thank you thank
you for
coming happy happy happy happy happy
happy happy happy Unbreaking okay
Unbreaking okay okay
Unbreaking
Unbreaking huh
thank
[Music]
you
what
okay yeah yeah okay here here here okay
here thank
you get up
happy happy happy happy happy happy
happy happy happy happy
Tashi happy happy
happy nice nice
thank you thank you thank you for
coming if you need anything please come
back you you yeah Rica please bring
everyone here if they need anything oh
okay thank you yes thank you I will I
will I
[Music]
will you want
dond diamond diamond we are going to
find diamond oh okay
have
fun bye-bye bye-bye good luck goodbye
don't
die anything you need to help please
tell me okay okay okay if you if you die
I will refice you again okay thank you
thank you byee thank you
[Music]
okay I probably
nen but Dong Dong Dong I understand
okay I think everyone need to start
talking with me with uh the with the
voice of this thing that they want to
say I understand voices
cuz I have voice like a lot of voices in
my head too so I used to be talking with
all of that
thing yeah Dong Dong Dong yes
[Music]
don't listen to the to the voes Kyle
it's a trap
nice wait I'm trying to do something
hold on
[Music]
I really need
the wait I should I should remove the
take free first because there's nothing
[Music]
inside but actually I'm very happy that
um that many people come to this place
and it's
being useful I'm
happy happy happy and just realized the
infinity is eight hold on
and
infinity huh it's okay it's The Mending
guy everybody loves Kyla Mart Kyla Mart
if only I got the money not the fager
though
protection
tree curse of
binding sweeping
H sweeping
h Ming
24 I really want to go to the city and
see the mission
but I'm still trapped here with this
trading
Hall enchanter what's
enchanter oh enchanting table someone
got the enchanting table
already we still have plenty of time we
just need to chill you
know one thing that I know the mission
about the nether uh we need to find the
nether fortress and then the first
person that found nether fortress going
to get like U many many
diamonds but it's okay we just going to
chill it's
okay I mean think it that think it this
way if I can get the efficiency
five the nether mining going to be
easier
too so
yeah that's
rer I need efficiency
five the cheap efficiency
5 and
actually I
was trying to check the percentage of uh
the perc the the rates percentage rates
of this gcha
fagers to get a left five books actually
it's a
0.64%
only so if you can get
like level five books with a very cheap
cheap
price it's actually
crazy it's very crazy
1 in 200ish easy gacha yeah but it's I
think it's going to be like double the
rates if you get it
cheap oh this one is fire protection
tree we have 5K fears you need we are
lock
section it's free gacha anyway it's free
gcha
but I don't know if I have the time to
do that I've been doing
this since day two and I'm still here in
day
four get some help walking into my S for
the short stream today hello welcome
good luck today KY thank you
Z so many ois and favorites to watch Hol
de time let's go mdal Rex thank
you uh wait I just realized I need food
where's my
food oh since they are all in nether I
can just sleep I think oh five people is
not in
nether I thought everyone is already in
the
nether oh yeah uh aski Senpai and Rea
are doing uh the diamond grind right uh
so that's three of us and then I don't
know who is the other two that is not in
the nether
yeah c get some I don't need this love
for tonight have fun corn beef thank
you Rea Luna oh Luna Senpai too I see
okay oh they're not sleeping
okay hi
by the way my all of my armor is
protection for already and then I have
this Thorn Tree on my chest
plate so basically basically I'm pretty
much
okay get some help I'm pretty much okay
why I have this jungle flying out of
nowhere just saw a clip of your scam
situation scam situation oh okay I
thought which one I already forgot about
it but yeah been in that situation
before I was out overse then and it was
agonizing back then to find out months
later lost almost a year of my salary
stay posited and no to scammers yeah I
hope you're feeling better now and I
hope uh all of the money that you lost
going to be like uh coming back like not
just coming just not you're going to get
it back what you lost but I hope you get
more than what you lost so yeah stay
strong Aiden thank you bring also going
to bring the creature wat aure S A and L
to watch along have you met with wat on
the serfer yet
what not
yet not yet not yet
hold on hold on I need
food food food food food food food food
food food food
okay
Ming Ming Ming
efficiency efficiency 5
you efficiency
5 chip expense chip expense chip
efficiency five please thank
you thank you you
please this oon is not nice to
me impaling impaling five for 26 that's
cheap how did many of the F you got
today like R your dirt check any
positive feedback I don't know Legion I
don't even know I don't even know um who
took the free book I don't know mending
16 mine is actually 10 I think
yeah who say that Ming book is hard
right now because Minecraft nerves that
why I keep getting
mending I need efficiency
five oranges
orang I need efficiency five La going to
go somewhere first have some of my luck
by Boron thank you
uh what a
deal take care
Bon this is lack of this
20 when is
actually it's
fine I think paa needs someone to revive
her want to help IM thank you I mean if
she ask why
not if she ask why not I
mean she basically have the farm that
everyone
uh needs it's a very crucial Farm r
but people need to understand it's not
that easy just like
um it's not about we want to help or
not the system
is the one who died need
to try to find the
diamond like as in if they don't ask for
it
then what
together what could we
do uh rip
tight get some
help giving people borrow time defeats
the purpose of Hardcore run anyway chat
yeah CL car he efficiency 4 okay you
can do
it yeah I just want
to let you know that it's actually
um it's just not that
simple it's
not just that
easy to revive
someone that seven
[Music]
chally my efficiency 4 I'm aiming
five if you if you take the efficiency 4
it's pretty it's so expensive and it
going to waste a lot
of level guys if the efficiency 4 is 40
you need like 80 emeralds
and many many
exp like I mean yesterday we got
efficiency 5 for
50 and we skipped that why we should
take the 80
bless
protection
NE
efficiency oh Gan
efficiency I can do this all day I have
I've done this two
days
Ming piercing
for knock
back power
four I'll take power five or
power five the cheap power five
and efficiency five
please if you want to give me 50 60
efficiency 5 I'll take it OG
son
please if you want to scam me I don't
care anymore just give me
just give me that efficiency five I need
it change the
filager change the
fager you guys lost hope of this vager
already bless protection
lock of this
thing
h h hold
on
[Music]
get have some for Kaki hi bargaining
haggling tactics oh so Kaki hicky I'm
doing Kaki hi
it with the OG
son hi uh this OG son not
[Music]
nice uh excuse
me get some help
uh
wait I need to add one more
let's try a new
one
oh
Oak
uh I forgot what I should do
not like that
[Music]
obviously one two
three get some
[Music]
okay uh
we need to go
deeper it's another achievement
right oh enter nether
portal I just going to chill chill chill
chill forever I'll be
chill chill chill chill chill chill
[Music]
chill just
chilling just chilling
this one I don't need get some
help
paper you'll strip nether clean once
they all
log no
it's it's not like that we need to
control
ourself thank you so much understandable
don't do
that I need
this uh and then I need red
stone and then I need
trapo trap
door sleep
PR
progress It's better to prepare three
more hours instead of being greedy and
impatient and losing all of the 40 hours
progress
B night Goldman
Mina
okay it's okay who needs sleps anyway
in I need the
l
laugh laugher
[Music]
laugh laugh oh laugh oh I have the
laugher why should I make one
wrong one obviously not like
that brain is not
braining okay next one
is Barrel
here and then prepare the trap door here
okay while we wait until morning we
should gacha this o sun
again come
on efficiency one very funny
oh
J you know you can
find the efficiency five
somewhere feather
[Music]
falling Fortune tree if after this you
got that efficiency five books I might
deliberately stop my toes to prove a
point and showing super underl on no
don't don't do that don't do that don't
do dangerous thing don't do that is
there where we donate for the efficiency
five oh thank you zamb booy thank you
but yeah thank
you for efficiency 5 thank you oim
mandas thank you this looks like a
filming a horror movie or really are you
sure about that because it seems like
it's it's just
fine it's like like if they want to stay
alive all of this OG Sun they need to
give me a cheaper one because if it's
like expensive and then suddenly I got
to find the cheaper one and then they
just got
eliminated
so yeah
that's kind of
scary
well that's why they need to give me the
keep
one maybe other member just see that oh
yeah it's a very cheap uh
books but no one needs to
know the behind the scen story right
right and there is actually no evidence
on that one they don't know yeah they
don't know and they don't need to
know sweeping
H3 sweeping
H3 sweeping H is three right the
max get some help
yeah
right get some
help
help okay hold on
it level up
okay curse of finishing wow so
good oh in set five insect for one
Emerald
[Applause]
h n
n wait y a b
pain
pain pain all of this is
pain I don't I don't want to go to the
nether I'm
afraid my heart is not ready for that
I'm baby gooo
Gaga Babu Babu
what does that
mean goo gaga Babble Babble wait where
is sing
please handle my
luggage oh or the the the
[Music]
items actually I'm happy
that the Traer come to visit here I'm
happy I'm not alone thank you so much
for coming thank you thank thank you
thank you thank you thank
you
rude this girl is kind of weak
get some help
cover me with
Diamonds cover me with diamonds
oh no it changed already the sweeping
age
whatever wait I I actually need to stop
playing with my cats if you want to
ignore me this is my
property
what what what are you looking at
arato go must oo you good nervous
anxiety too much people y it's okay take
your time you can
join there when you're ready
what
what what I'm just
okay and then this one
what I think Kyla has lost it sassy
thank you the irony of blackb with
pyrophobia or SN cave M phobia I guess
get your bearings like you're no
ordinary and PC I'm not even an
PC looks like K is on the menu for
tonight boys no don't do that car thank
you even the sky cry for oisa after
hearing that I apologize I gave the N ah
the fur for haggle is k k simar reading
luckily but different kaj
oh hope I don't overload you it's fine
it's always nice to know new vocabul
thank you just following up for the
efficiency five maybe I need to to get
some thank you andrean thank you thank
you hold on I going to check my Discord
first oh okay m
it's
okay what I
say is it ref five
already not sure oh okay
get some help hi hity get off my
property and get s k probably what is
Hipp
hopp that should be reference of
something
right it's not just a random word
right oh it's
meme get some
oh nothing basically just to rhyme oh
Kay beam Sala beam oh I got it I got it
I got it
[Music]
atic
this not you yeah whatever it's
okay bro bro bro bro bro why you don't
go to the
barrel go to the barrel
where's the O son get some help Haya why
they always want to go this
one what barrel
barrel you see this
one
okay go this way
one yeah and then go this way hello
hello hello hello this way this way and
then this
way
okay that way that
way and then just a little bit more this
way and then
this
way
huh wait hold
on what day is to
tomorrow Friday oh okay
I
see Saturday I got a message
from my teacher I have class tomorrow
and then I was like huh
class do I even have
class
class what
class I was like
I think by tomorrow I already forgot
what is my
name all of us here are witnessing the
ascent of Ella into Kyla sh of Minecraft
again we are truly blessed I'm not Shin
Shin no no no thank
you yeah thank you kazami re ask him a
question yeah ask him a question right
he might answer oh by the way maybe he
won't give the efficiency five because
you keep calling him OG
o what's
OO tell your teacher Minecraft is more
important I know
right I know but
yeah ha give me a iy 5 and I'll end your
suffering
please the Golem not
yeah oigo oh
o5 oiro
[Music]
what wait I got free
carrot
respiration by tomorrow you'll dream of
real and wake up in Minecraft yeah IND
the ex an
mhm l
two power four efficiency five you can
do it you can do it those were the days
what's that enter a Bastion oh no a
s oh no they are all entering the buson
nice they're raiding the bus
still
they're they're all they're all having
so much fun in the Bastion
yeah Kori [\h__\h] left the
game K life
reaction bless
protect get some help
the thing is you know
um the thing
about playing together adventuring
together with the other people in the
bason I'm really afraid
of
accidentally swinging my S into someone
so
yeah because bason is like
pretty like uh there's not so much space
to move it's pretty cramped
up not you actually not you but it's
okay
up
up uh go back to your
station go
back go back to your
[Music]
station go back go back go back go
back not there
bro you want
this yeah you want this you don't want
that
okay understandable
go
back go
back yeah
yeah gotcha hold on hold on hold on hold
on go back go back
gotcha adios
stay there
forever
okay M join the
game okay new OG Sun let's go first try
efficiency
bro oh I'm
broken
H hold on
rip
tight
loyalty gas oh yeah there is also a
mission about killing a guest
cross
wall
channeling get some help Ohan literally
say no de de
[Music]
multishot foress some uh
but
guest sharpness three no sharpness needs
five Frost
Walker can we kill guest with
[Music]
Tor I don't think
so I don't know
Unbreaking
one low HP maybe yeah
maybe this oon is actually worse than
the first one
SM
tree mending
34 this is like really wor really really
worse loyalty one
mending
sure it's a bad one and it's very
expensive oh silk p seven okay okay okay
okay maybe you can give me like
efficiency
five I will give you free time if you
give me efficiency five I promise I'll
leave but if you really want to suffer
here then okay
flame
S protection 4 38 no my protection 4 is
cheaper right
15 looting tree 12 hold
on hold
on hold on
h
h lumayan
aqua affinity
16 okay
[Music]
at least say thanks
thanks thanks
than thanks
is there really really like no hope for
efficiency
5 now I
regret I know that I shouldn't I
should take the efficiency 550
yesterday KY be like you have outlived
your
usefulness sorry guys
thany no
back
nah
wait wait they want to sleep
they want to sleep but I need to lock
that wait
sharpness wait oh no they're sleeping
sharpness
19 wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait oh goodbye I can
sleep
the OG Sun lives another
day five sorry no bed if you don't want
to sleep but that's a lie we do have bad
[Music]
[\h__\h] you're not allowed here
wait
[Music]
sharp if you can give me sharpness five
I know that you can give me efficiency
five for real for real
by the
way how to find uh anent debris
again 15 level
15 15 or my - 15 I
forgot oh positive nether got
no me got no minus right no negative
right oh yeah
okay I think later I just going to like
straight straight mine
until the other world
because we don't really have TNT right I
mean I do have some
but I don't think that's going to
help plus
sharpness
4 just don't do another n we again and
we good This Server going to ends like
in 4 days no 3
days so it will not be possible
[Music]
Thorns
one ah piglin ah ah piglin BR Dal Dal
Dal guys
Dal Dal do doar doar doar
[Music]
doar dollar
dollar oh
no oh
no
l see
I kind of love my peaceful life
here sh not 538 my sharpness
is 20
it's actually
really it's actually really
funny
59 okay you know
what I know that it's expensive
but I'll just lock this first just in
case before I regret it
again yeah but I still have uh this one
space right later in the meantime if I
have like free time I
can
yeah yesterday is like 54 for that one
right
yeah Lou tumbal not like that it's not
Lou name luck no don't say
that this sacrifice work
for okay we just need to
find some
uh do I have enough 50 what 59 isn't
it
uh wait wait wait
okay try to get seven more
emeralds and then we are
good m
[Music]
oh by the way I don't even know where is
the portal though do you know where is
the
portal is it like in the middle of the
city I haven't gone back to
the city yet
okay thank
you your ocean needs help what
why what
happened what happened
[Music]
o what are you doing
here don't get into my
house
uh uh
uh
efficiency GG this is going to be very
expensive uh
efficiency five
[Music]
wait
this this one is
if this one is 12 oh it's the same one
so
okay oh yeah but I don't have enough for
the
Unbreaking this one got Unbreaking
already so
maybe just efficien C5 this one
wait
but the thing is anine the Brie can not
oh wait I don't know okay
fine the Unbreaking going to be
fa need a lot ofp I
think Haya 18 where to get 18
[Music]
TT oh the TTT is working already
but I don't really know about the
place wait let me reply to B first
get some
help wait
uh T I got no Koreans
about Bo
Mama what's that warix loot a chest in
Bastion Remnant very nice
okay no trims I really want to go to the
basan remnant not for
anything I just really really want to
get the nadra upgrade if I can but maybe
I can't so adios
[Music]
we just need like one right just one and
a dream but it's not that
[Music]
easy fire potion
yeah Fire Resistance potion Minecraft I
forgot what's the
material thank you so much for the
membership gifts thank thank
[Music]
you oh mm
cream I see
okay so I'm going to put all of my stuff
first hold on let me put my stuff
and then the
roten flash we don't need a
bed just bring the bed for now later I
can put it
uh and the in the other chest and then
we don't need
torch we don't need the Mine card we
going to wait we don't need
this we don't need the B
who is cutting
onions who is cutting
onions crying obsidian
[Music]
s pie oh
no that's so
sad that's very very
sad what should we do about that what
should what should we do about that
information subar
what a
deal awkward
it should have been me oh no what what
what is happening what is happening
there what is happening I don't know I
don't know
an hold on before I
go and have fun
thank
you good luck good
luck this
one I'm trying to put all of the
stuff here
what's
that how many depths do you have please
return it in real
time thank you for your hard
work one five
hi the dep though
Haya
hiya how to repay your
Deb what's
that please use other than cash
let's talk
[Music]
later oh no oh
no and Unbreaking I'll take the
Unbreaking and then I'll take um I I
need
a I need one crafting table for sure and
then I need
um uh anill anill I need one
anill I need
one
enill and then after that I don't need
the emerald just put the emerald
here food one stack uh Shield uh maybe I
should make like a new
Shield just in case oh yeah by the way
why I
do why I bring this lecture to NE we
don't need that
and
then oh yeah gold
uh m this
one we need the
Unbreaking
Ming I don't have The Mending
now uh we we we we need The Mending
though
wait wait wait wait wait mending
Unbreaking protection for
do I really need it
actually do I really need it do I really
need that golden
helmet wish you the best oh very very
good motivation let's go you going to
you going to uh finish your thesis in
one week let's
goang a little TP combining books first
is way cheaper fire resist po better
from pigling gold trade ah yeah yeah
yeah yeah true true true Sur M thank you
more food I don't
have more
food just bring all of the
food y thank you
M this is thank
you what do you
need what do you need
yeah
I I I need
[Music]
this book okay
okay yes streaming
now you no streaming now no stream oh no
streaming okay
okay cat cat uh-huh what what your name
what your oh no name no name no name no
name yeah
[Music]
Pune
Pune oh hello hello hello h Hello thank
you thank you thank
you thank
[Music]
you cool yeah cool cool yeah cool cool K
is cool yeah yeah yeah
yeah
cool oh you want to
[Music]
go okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
to wait wait wait wait
here here
here come here come
here yeah your your voice is like so
small okay okay wait wait wait sleep
sleep no sleep sleep sleep
sleep
okay
together me to me yeah
yeah
yeah okay
okay okay
oh regos going NE reglo go
NE uh scary oh NE scary no no no
scary not scary no
scary wow wow really
yeah NE no scary H
scary yeah Haim
scarier no no no I I not scarier
oh okay
okay Kawai not
scary okay okay
okay no no no no cute no cute no no no
cute cool cool cool
only no no no no C no
C no
if you say that I'm cute I'm going to
fish you again
fish no no fish I am a
human
no wi no wi cool
cool wi cool Kyla is cool
[Music]
I am a human yeah I okay wait try again
KY
cool KY
cool yeah yeah yeah is cool
go home go home okay go home thank you
thank you thank
you see you again see you again thank
you for coming
[Laughter]
byebye okay okay Kyla is cool no fish
Kyla cute
fish
[Applause]
yeah say k cute I
[Music]
fisho
okay
wait Bon
yeah what's that
Bono
B Oho
ohoo NE together okay NE together yeah
thank you thank you okay okay thank you
thank you thank you Happ happy happy
thank you than thank
[Music]
you thank thank you thank thank
you please come
again
much I'll will be back I'll be back too
I'll be back yeah adios say [\h__\h] see you
next time oh yeah see you next time bye
bye-bye bye-bye don't
die it's actually so funny you know
what oh yeah by the way she never
realized that she actually took my bed
but it's
okay
B
Bono I think I think every single time I
interact with
Haim I'm going to be
like making a new
language get some
help
help but actually I'm I'm getting better
I'm getting better at uh catching her
English word you
know yeah it's actually I'm getting
better with that one
okay
now wait I need to put the fishing
rod okay I think that should be
enough get some help I need to farm
this and
then I need to make an new
Shield
okay and
then next time invite hajim for
adventure yeah that's actually what C
say right let's go nether together right
yeah now I have to take classes in Kai G
language
yeah you
should you seem to get along with regos
really
well yeah I'm happy happy right yeah M
St thank you so it was all really just
for them to say you're C
yeah I'm
cool hajim Haim said that I'm cool let's
go guys now I'm having a heart attack l
so cool cool thank you cool cool KY
K KY is is what
cool right kak thank
you and
then hold
on okay I think think I'll just bring
this wait I need to make a new
Shield just in
case if something happen we never
know iron in
[Music]
and
then and
then wait I need the
sharpness
[Music]
five I need the sharpness
five 20 20 is not that much
right I believe I can do
it
hi
hi hi
uh no exp no I'm I'm taking all of the
stuff to
Nether I bring the anvill
already so yeah get some help
nice we got 10
exp
uh sharpness sharpness
sharpness where is the bat
nice
now 12 why is everything
12 it's okay diob
buis diob buis you know D
buis okay now the mission is don't
[Music]
die
uh can I actually using
um boat Strat
in boat Strat in
nether like in Bastion no right it's not
that easy right
yes but possibly fall in laa no I mean
to stop the mops
The Brood yeah The
Brood need a lot of boats need a lot of
boats why we do need a lot of boats just
bring one stack of wood
then just bring the
iron for what I don't
know wait wait wait
wait okay nice we got 12 we can
Unbreaking we can Unbreaking
the pck
first why is 90
why it's 18 now
it it was 12
[Music]
before
scam it's the
sharpness oh really did I put the
sharpness
[Music]
no no I mean the previous one when I
said okay how about we
Unbreaking wait what hold on hold on my
brain is not braining
[Music]
oh previously I want to put the
efficiency five
right the previous one is efficiency
five the 12
one yeah I'm not talking about the sword
I'm talking about something like an hour
ago
do
[Music]
KY
oh
coming
[Music]
coming need to drink
Ella just mistaken hajim with
h what's
that hence the fishing what what's wrong
with the
fishing thank
you get some
help random game recommendation f store
it looks like Minecraft but has much
more realistic survival very Grand
friendly sming is very fun oh thank you
full
moon and C
Flo thank
you thank you thank you where is the
building where is the
building where is oh that one
[Music]
drinki drink
drinki Dr
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's
go let's go let's let's go let's go
let's go let's
go all right
just so you know we're going to TT first
okay but then we can go do all the
missions if you want let's go okay let's
[Music]
go
diamond yeah
[Music]
y
thank thank
you thank you nice to meet you thank
you nice to meet you nice to meet you
the my
soul my soul
my
[Music]
soul close the door close the door oh
close the door okay close door okay okay
[Music]
already okay
okay let's go let's go come on come on
[Music]
going I don't know
I don't know why I don't know I don't
know I don't know I don't know I don't
know you don't know I don't know I don't
know netherite very
heart very hard I'm afraid
kaai okay okay
okay okaye
[Music]
yeah you still have
uh uh the the what's it called Infinity
enchantment yeah but I don't bring
it oh no
problem but they're saying they want it
to have it okay they can just come to my
[Music]
where where is coordinate house
coordinate
Discord this Discord
[Music]
coordinate thank
you yeah I I look this wow
[Music]
let's okay okay okay
okay then I guess I did that too
[Music]
commemoration
pictur at the
death
y
[Music]
for
speech
[Music]
fore
nice fore
[Music]
I'm afraid to
SL what if I
accidentally what if I accidentally
slash
them welcome back
disconnected
disconnected are you okay yeah the
Minecraft is not okay I'm okay Minecraft
is not
[Music]
okay yeah come thing of it I see a lot
what are you doing here I don't
know we want to make a
bowl yeah cuz me
and we don't have one I don't
have understand
[Music]
I 18
what did you have for dinner oh uh wait
what
is I think I forgot
already oh I have thought it was an
important time for
you yeah but it's it's the topic of the
conversation not the food
right but the food is connected to it
yeah well yeah
well what was it I think I think wait
wait wait let me try to remember because
I think my brain and my soul already
left my body uh I think wait n Padang I
think I don't know if you know Nas
Padang or not but yeah I had that one it
Nas Padang is like spicy
food that's it yeah
okay what did you talk about
wow a lot of
stuff nice a lot of stuff yeah I don't
know my my Minecraft is like
that Minecraft very weird oh yeah yeah
yeah
Miki
yeah she wants the Infinity the infinity
infinity my
house yeah my house at home at
home yeah
[Music]
KY house go
now want to go
okay okay let's
go Emerald we have you
Emerald they have emeralds
[Music]
K this intrusive sorry
all good all so
good all so good all good all
[Music]
good a
[Laughter]
bye-bye byebye
byebye oh byebye okay byebye
let's
go let's
go
Ki hi I'm making a small smaller t house
oh okay okay okay t house okay okay
[Music]
let's
go let's
go go let's
go go
H
yummy quartz yummy
this is
uh Crimson
[Music]
Forest
okay this way this way
Emerald
okay are they all have
emeralds we we need to We need oh I
don't really have the stock we need to
buy
it
[Music]
I okay okay she's going to go get
oh how much do you need how much do you
need around 20
maybe you you can you can have like iron
ingot uh for for four iron ingot you get
one emerald in my
place so if you have like fire Ingot you
can trade it there at my in my you're
good I I don't think I wait maybe we can
check the iron farm first hold on I
don't know if they have it um I um I
left some at the start Point here here
let's come here wait the iron farm oh
we're going to iron farm yeah just check
that works yeah that works too just just
check okay
okay okay
wow
oh I don't know if that's
enough um we we and you can take sugar
cane too sugar cane sugar sugar cane
yeah sugar cane can
also convert into emeralds
now I
don't let's take this one
maybe
this
come can we go back to
the I left
some I think should be enough I don't
know can we go back to the starting
point this is the starting
point this is actually the starting
point the iron farm is the starting
point where where do
you yeah sugar cane okay too if you
sugar cane
oh not
here you're not here right because of
your B the you you want the the the the
first point no the individual the
individual yeah the individual here here
here it's here okay okay
okay okay I don't know where did they go
everyone is
like every
[Music]
how much do you need around 20 right
so I have
five I have five five what five Emerald
or five iron yeah five
amerald we we're going to I think it
should be cheaper than that I don't
really
remember how much
IR uh four iron ingot is for one
Emerald oh okay um then I should be good
okay okay and I don't know where they go
[Music]
maybe we should
like
nice this is like a playground
[Music]
G
okay let's go oh that one is R was
I
[Music]
guess oh Miki
hello okay let's go let's go this way
[Music]
jumping jumping jumping jumping
I think she cannot hear us too
[Music]
far is a cool yay
cool no no no no no
[Music]
cool we put that way say she wants to
zombies tonight let
[Music]
okay this way this way
yeah it's okay k k know the place so
it's fine oh
[Music]
okay not not not this one this is this
is like to beautiful right
[Music]
no not this is too good to be true right
that one is
mine not
this they thought that the village was
her home yeah I know
right
n the stream died what
here uh Senai here uh the the what the
emerald
uh you right click you right click and
then you click the iron ingot one the
four iron ingot yes mhm and
then this you don't need to have it on
your in your hands you just you need you
need to have a an iron exchange wait do
I Doon exch is this one to dis guys oh
oh yeah right they do have it too oh do
I do I give do I give it no no uh click
uh right click right click the this
person out yeah yeah yeah I'm I'm trying
to yeah it's okay it's okay it's okay
it's
okay I'm I'm trying I'm I'm right
clicking oh okay okay okay there we go
there we
go what a
deal what a deal
nice
17 no no
yeah thank I love you okay after I have
the emerald and then yeah just uh find
the infinity
Booth
Infinity yeah this one this one yeah
right click it right click and then buy
wait you need the book the book is here
uh oh yeah I have
oh you have the book
okay what do I buy the
Infinity the infinity
book you offer you offer your cursor to
the purple color books and then infinity
and then you click on
it Infinity you click on it infinity
infinity yeah
infinity infinity this this the
enchanted book yeah yeah yeah that one
this one
mhm from the trade menu coming on wait
you you got that one right you got the
book already oh yeah I have the book and
then I exchange
it
yeah you need 18
[Music]
villager I think she wants one of your
villagers oh yeah yeah yeah you you can
do
it okay okay
uh it's
okay yeah she wants one of your
villagers
[Music]
uh that one right hold
on I think she wants to trade the
[Music]
stick wants the
wait
uh where's the
[Music]
vag
see oh I think I think they go
somewhere here
yeah as always they going to go to the
composter and then they're going to go
to this
one and
then
okay
Senai C here here
thank
you this one this one this
[Music]
o thank
you uhhuh ha I don't have the bow what
do you need to make wait I think I can
make it for you hold on hold on
uh but you have the infinity book
already yeah I
do come here come here okay okay
okay hold on let me
eat
okay h b
bow bow is strings and stick right so
one two three oh they're
sleeping oh they're sleeping
okay I think St wanted to like defeat
the zombies right so I think we we don't
need to see oh okay okay yeah I don't
need this oh yeah yeah she okay uh this
one take this and then take that and
then go here to the crafting table here
all right and then bow craft the bow
B the normal bow right yeah mhm okay
okay okay okay and then you click the
anvill the right click the anvill
uhhuh and then and then put your bow on
the left box and then the enchanting in
the Enchanted Infinity book on the
right okay okay okay I got it
yay and then do you still have any
Emerald
no um no I used up all my
you just need one arrow for the infinite
or maybe I can give you like three just
in case oh thank you thank you okay okay
okay thank you now what wait are they
finished with that I don't
know mm
we are running out of emerald
[Music]
guys doesn't have
the bow oh okay hold on you don't have
any
more actually I have this one bow you
know
but I don't know
how okay okay
I don't know if my exp going to be
[Music]
enough
it's yeah um
wants to gu and here is it okay oh yeah
yeah yes bring everyone here let's
go she's going to be right back yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
okay let's go
sleep oh
sleep wait uh actually don't you have
any more like am ingots no
I think you need to put like Unbreaking
hold on hold on again Unbreaking
Unbreaking
Unbreaking where is the Unbreaking
Unbreaking oh okay nice thank you no
it's 11 you don't have
11 no no more engl uh wait let me
see 11
wait Unbreaking I have the
free oh this one this one you still
have uh this one this one wait where is
it this
one oh this one oh you got it hold on
hold on hold on hold on I have
to it's
okay I can take that for you thank you
do I go back to the Anvil yeah anvil
okay um so the ball and then the this do
you have enough level for that you need
the
level oh yeah I I think so I take
it okay thank
you thank you done nice
[Music]
is I
bow she needs a bow I think yeah she
need a
bow she needs a bow too yeah she needs a
[Music]
b
oh thank
you thank you
[Music]
you good no no no no God no c not
coming thank you very much you me
[Music]
yay thank you for coming
follow the Villager followed inside yeah
it's okay it's fine
[Music]
again I wonder if she'll ever noticed it
wait
[Music]
what read it all
out oh you're not seeing it K look
here I'm
not aara I'm Kyla I'm not a ky I'm
K yeah that would be my part oh you know
what that is referencing yeah I know b b
right okay try again try again first
first take first take you start okay I'm
not K I'm
Kyla and I'm not a KLA I'm kiar
[Music]
y k k k
k oh the Villager wants to join you we
did it we did it it's okay
yay Anda but you know why I wrote this
because subu Senpai called me Kyla
several times today oh
really she did she know who I am she
did I see
I think she was confused because I was
leading her to Kyla's house so she was
also calling me Kyla oh
no she also went to your
house wait
uh murder Kori where is I didn't do it
where
[Music]
isori Ki Arrow okay
oh
arrows arrows Arrow arrows okay
Arrow I I I gave the arrows already yeah
what's what's the what's arrows inongo
yes yes thank you
[Music]
very thank you
okay thank you very
[Music]
hello hello hello name is
can nice to meet
you my name is not Canada I'm Kyla nice
to meet
you oh come in
come no no
no
[Music]
J this is my
mama
m m
baby I'm I'm at the Mama's
[Music]
baby Miki no no no Miki this this Miki
here
[Music]
for
wow okay
[Music]
okay
okay let's go let's go
[Music]
no okay okay
come no
[Music]
going to
be I'ma my memes
[Music]
no first
speech
speech forign
I don't think I don't think it's this
way are are they sure it's that way it's
not this
way it's they're getting further and
further
[Music]
we need to go that
way we need to go that
way guys
guys I I don't think they know the way
we we we want to go to the portal right
yeah I yeah they they just go further
and
further oh uh I don't even see them
anymore
[Music]
yeah I think they just got into the
mountain m
I don't
[Music]
know
noticed should we should we should we
wait them or should we just go I don't
know I we should wait for them okay they
went that way right yeah they they went
to that a mountain thingy they went to
the Village I think Village they think
that's the other Village that we went
through yeah I think yeah I think I
think I think they go to this Village oh
yeah yeah there there
hello hello hello
[Music]
ohiki is at spawn already they
sayik they say Miki is already at the
spawn
point oh okay okay let's go then I don't
know sleep
sleep fore
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's
go let's
go she's at spawn okay okay have to
start leaving people behind
because we can't keep on stopping no I
think I think mik mikoi led the way and
then uh Kori Senpai got to meet Luna
Senpai so she stops a bit there I think
yeah yeah
yeah okay okay
[Music]
yeah she's going for you think there'll
be many
Clips definitely becoming a c
you
go
hello the flower ah thank
you thank you thank you thank
you
y foree
[Music]
okay okay I don't know if I don't know
if they're
like
going at this point I don't even know
where where where where will be like
going where who who going to stay I
don't
know who going to stay who going
to
go let's
[Music]
go
for
[Music]
spe
fore
spee let's
go let's go
[Music]
okay we go back to T
for
[Music]
spee yes
good you want we probably already have a
lot of things that you don't have yet so
just feel free to you know okay thank
you
yeah it's okay you don't need to hear
yeah I can always life and hear you
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is
maybe it was on
purpose what do you mean on purpose
because she's only uh participating for
one day and maybe she's just like all
right I'mma end it in a dramatic
way very nice
plot St
[Music]
St foree
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait wait she
okay fixing it's okay it's okay is it
really though yeah it's okay it's
okay I I think K would would be chill in
every
situation I think I would have just
ran oh wait I forgot the
Tes foree
[Music]
are
you a flag for magma
[Music]
oh it'll be faster this maybe too fast
doie
doie doie doie
[Music]
K thank you KY thank you
K thank
you God I could not
react it's so
okay it's
[Music]
okay what's that be
careful m
[Music]
wow he's
dancing oh God
[Music]
where are we going to go we just going
to go straight can I can I have some
blocks
please throw you a whole block again
here I'll you another one if you
want let's go oh
oh
nice don't fall okay don't fall stay
down stay
down I could make the sides
[Music]
but we go that way
oh gas
gas
[Music]
gas just kills it casually
you got a kill for the gas yeah for the
mission right mission complete yeah
complete
ni
mhm nice nice nice thank you thank
you
okay okay
well the other side is dangerous I leave
I leave
torches
[Music]
okay I didn't read if you guys answered
but a
[Music]
that's ath to for but not but it's like
not naturally generated
right yeah I think that's someone
[Music]
else
for
where where' you go
so gu guess
[Music]
[Applause]
how many guests that we need again
um one person one
okay let just do it together just do it
together as
[Music]
aam know you know
fore spee
[Music]
nice
yay a few more
[Music]
please
fall
[Laughter]
for
speee
speee Fore
guess
you yay nice
one above
oh it sounds so close it sounds so close
yeah the gas right I think it's below
[Music]
okay so cool though
what if this was just the way back this
is just the way back I think this is
like the TT way
right oh this is the T
way this the way
back yeah this is this is totally the
way
back uh don't know what this
is where are
doesn't
continue this is not
the if we go this
[Music]
way that one see this
one this one be careful be
[Music]
careful are you okay yeah oh my God
yeah oh no who's
that saw that
[Music]
[Laughter]
was too
curious she
fell yeah really was about to close it
off saw me put
[Laughter]
[Music]
go
back let's go back wait uh all of you
want to go
back um I think she's going to be making
A New Path Oh I thought I thought want
to go to the the the the world like the
portal no the portal back as in on our
path over
here
[Music]
he what what is that
again
[Music]
for fore
hello yeah just go just go
[Music]
[Laughter]
K everyone is Kyla
now everyone is ky now
[Music]
I'm glad I went with this group
spe
[Music]
[Laughter]
this where is
pule
dangerous dangerous
okay
dangerous be careful
[Music]
abai has to go to solo server and uh get
seven diamonds on her own in 30 minutes
[Music]
thank youe
this very dangerous right guys imagine
like
if from
[Music]
racing FL
hold on hold on you fixed it you fix it
KY you're the
[Music]
fix it's okay it's okay
is burning it's
fine it's
[Music]
fine you do some of the pleas yeah
actually what are we doing right
now 100
she's so
chill she's so
good I can't stay so calm
[Music]
work calling for you wait what oh yeah
number
one oh my God you still go straight I
think maybe yes
[Music]
is it okay to use Cobblestone yeah it's
fine yeah anything except don't place a
bed in the nether never place a bed in
the nether yeah I I know that much
okay oh thanks for the raid thank you
for the ra
she's so good she's so good
okay
[Music]
oh it's better if I don't build here uh
if I'm not digging there's so much MMA
Eternal oisan have ET
[Music]
two in the nether
yeah it's like on your
left you want to go
left I don't know proba sounds so close
I want to take a look close I don't
think I think it's on the left yeah it's
kind of on the left but I don't know
[Music]
yeah you want to oh oh this one it's
right there it's
right is it can you see it there there
there there it's so close it's so close
uh dangerous dangerous be safe be safeer
be safe be
safe be safe take care take
care let me kill him
[Music]
no no
no nice
[Music]
nice
no no
it's they hit me oh my God they probably
because the I'm afraid
I afraid if they
[Music]
died
nice
achievement we both did it yeah we both
did
[Music]
it yeah we did it together
nice okay we can continue
KY where what what what should what
should we do now I don't know uh we we
have to more gu we continue we continue
okay okay foress
[Music]
this is not Sol this is what is this
I think we're looking foress and these
people yeah we're looking for
[Music]
foress I have enough you still need like
everything right like the or are you
trying to do the
missions or do you want to the missions
the missions are just uh glow stone and
then gas a green mushroom mushroom green
mushroom and Soul Sand you got to get
Soul Sand oh Soul Sand it's done it's a
war fungus oh the oh oh the war fungus
oh okay okay
[Music]
okay it's apparently down
here
what really she foress
[Music]
we want to fall down is it
yeah we want to go to the
Fortress I think if you want to go
down we can do something hold on you
make Bridge
[Music]
[Applause]
where is
[Music]
it where is
it where is the guest
[Music]
yeah I don't know kind of say it
though it's okay
[Music]
it's
okay nice one nice
[Music]
one what is going on
the
food does she have the
now are are we all
fine where is
it how far is it actually it's really
far huh oh
okay it's done it's done it's done
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait okay oh she so
good yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
oh can wants to do the mission okay okay
we're going to find another one it's
okay that doesn't have the
B doesn't have the
B maybe maybe we can like land it first
yeah I was thinking about that but that
one is very
aggressive that one was yeah that one
very is very aggressive
[Music]
where's the
Fortress Fortress Fortress I saw it
earlier
[Music]
oh that
one
[Music]
skeleton that one that one guess guess
guess that one
[Music]
on I Senpai uh wait I I I going to I
going to land uh Canada my bow first oh
oh oh she she got oh she
[Music]
got
fore
[Music]
spee spee foree
here here this way this way that
way down here oh but this one is down
down here
too we are like pretty close already
this one I
think don't fall okay don't fall don't
fall okay your's kind of dangerous
hello let's
go I think it's fine
though yeah you
can which way this way hold
on this way this way can you go back
here okay yeah just follow down down
right yeah yeah it's safe but just make
sure make make it slow yep okay wait
Kara goes that
way yeah I think so okay hold on just
wait there just wait there don't don't
move okay okay okay we're like pretty
close
light up the
way
okay we can just make it safe here hold
on
okay
okay okay okay thank here here here
okay this is so scary yep okay we are
here
already
okay
yep and then
okay I just going to
check
okay what if what if I just dropped down
yeah
um yeah if I drop down it's okay it's
okay and then I going to
make the
pathway oh there's a path over there I
see I don't want
okay can I fall down can I just no no no
no no no don't don't don't don't
don't
okay oh they're there we we can see it
yeah they're there already okay yeah I I
can see the name we just need to go now
uhhuh we just need to go now
wait
okay thank
you
you okay oh my God oh my God oh my
goodness oh my goodness what happened
okay let's go almost got pushed down a
it's okay it's okay it's okay it's fine
it's
fine let's go it's fine it's fine
thank God OBS
magic OBS is
Magic yeah OBS put some magic people are
saying my game is too dark
oh yeah increase your increase increase
the brightness
guys yeah that's why I did some magic on
the op
[Music]
nice is it their head or what are they
dropping they drop their head sometimes
if you're
lucky okay
[Music]
okay
okay what's this
[Music]
oh the
blaze I hear them yeah
yeah the blaze oh that one be careful be
careful it's coming it's coming oh my
goodness run run I don't want to shoot
the run just run
[Music]
we
do no we kill it like a Pokemon kill it
if you if if but it
burns nice and then take the
drop take the
drop nothing drop nothing okay sad it's
okay
[Music]
for nothing oh
guest hi
oh where where the
guest voice come
from oh they're there
already they explore everything here
already pretty much I think I really
wonder hey wait we really need the weer
skeleton head
right they are going that side but I
just want to go this side
first for what for the
winther but I don't know if maybe uh if
maybe pakora can like just spawn
it or whatever I don't
know
wait can just go this
way
what not anybody
ouch
wait go
away go
away
adios okay it's
safe I think they go this way because I
saw their name
here yeah they're
there can just break this wait wait no
piz yeah they they they they go separate
wait look at
that uh Tre
deer and then coori Senpai and mikoi I
don't know where are
they wait it's not this way wait where
are you going
to the other
way yeah
Kor and mik ran back oh they are
together at least they are
together like I mean at least they're
not uh alone you
know oh no drop oh wait I need this yeah
uh I already killed like two blazes and
I got one Blaze Rod nice
I need go that way I don't
think
okay into
fire into fire
[Music]
F no one wants to think is that a
skeleton
where the mission open you still have
you don't have yeah I need to kill two
more skeletons oh okay well they're
everywhere they're also at the TT so
yeah yeah
yeah I wonder if the skeletons at TTP
count when I kill a bunch of them at I
don't I don't know if that counts or
not oh they're
downstairs are
they I don't this is like a pretty huge
area so I don't know
oh there's no
more yeah I think I see
[Music]
who please r
who's is this sakur do
you is that Sakura
there yeah really my eyes my eyes are
blind cannot read it okay then maybe we
need to go that way right
right let's
go let's go let's
go
m
Miki I think the name the name is up
there hello
this way this way this
way it's up there can I
just hello
hello what
happened is
upstairs so close to dying what is going
what what are you doing what did you do
three more Hearts left I what did you do
I underestimated the
curse the the curse that you get from
the Wither
Skeleton yeah yeah
yeah I thought it was over for
me I like this
feeling you're living on the edge I
still see her should we just it's about
the edge it's me
mik is still there
though I heard still there yeah I heard
the voice
like once but I don't know
[Music]
Miki
nothing
nothing I don't know I
think I think I think she'll be
[Music]
fine let's go
and
[Music]
rest my shield my shield doesn't exist
you know I like to ignore my shield
boom boom
[Music]
spw why am I burning
again
[Music]
foree thank you
Fair Pro
GG fairy
pro pro
player
[Music]
yeah hot hot hot hot
don't die don't die nah it's
fine okay
shoo
wait actually why are we
[Music]
here I don't know why are we
here
we thank you thank you it's to spw I
think
[Music]
it's
for torch no we cannot torch the Spawner
in the Fortress
[Music]
fore wow
what is
[Music]
until we have a good solution
speech
spe foreign
oh they're like spawning outside of the
range don't come
[Music]
out
for
[Music]
thank come on come
on so long you know what are we trying
to do
what are we try we try to farm
it a okay
[Music]
guess
wow that's very nice
try do you know how to build it so that
you can get the drops
oh it's it's uh they're like specific
build you know how to build it I can how
to do it but maybe
[Music]
not yeah later I I can do it off stream
though yeah want to build it now oh you
want to she she wants to build it
now we don't really have good Stu right
here but saying we might go back yeah oh
okay
[Music]
maybe it's okay it's okay it's
okay it's okay
[Music]
okay
okay it's not recommended to build in
hardcore wow we have no choice
[Music]
[Laughter]
you want you want
[Music]
to
okay oh oh nice
be fine right but she'll need
[Music]
a
sorry sorry
sorry got it got it got it okay nice one
nice
one yeah the the rods the rods is gone
it's fine it's
okay it's on the ground
if only Al was here go there
[Music]
wowow go away
[\h__\h] done
[Music]
what's
let's let's go let's go let's go let's
go let's
go if we really wants to go back we
need I think we can just like U make
a we can just go that way
actually the portal is at
0 portal is
0 uh I don't really remember the way
back like the one that we came from but
I got the
I I maybe I can go by the other
way it's that
way that way yeah but we need to make
like the make a new way not the one we
come here
yeah oh wait so can we can we go home
this way
I'm so confused which one's the
achievement because we acted like the
Bastion was the
achievement left or
right got check the miss
[Music]
iiki is
somewhere all get I don't
know we go that way if we want to go
back cuz we also took a
picture the Bastion
[Music]
together foree
oh genius genius
[Music]
genius we're making two
okay we can
just hold
oner dangerous
dangerous
[Music]
danger
wait wait wait
wait don't get close don't get
close is that love don't get
close don't get
[Music]
close isn't that what you say when
you're in love or when someone's really
magnificent oh yeah don't get close
don't sweep the
Flor was it
you went up a level yep it's
okay no
blocks
wait block okay I think they still have
blocks this
one we should go to that
I'm so scared you
now don't be scared everything will be
just
fine this place is very
peaceful sometimes
laying out the red or dark brown
caret as for Block yeah I need
blocks ah I got
you
uhhuh
disconnected as always I have wait I
have uh let me give you thank you
just disappeared I thought you fell down
yeah
disconnected okay we are that
close
P oh yeah B oh portal we have portal
here really portal
[Music]
that's the destroy
portal not not not not not our portal
but it's the other portal
it's the the destroy one
yeah theyy no I don't think so because
it's so close I think it's too close
it's too close to the city one it going
to break the city
one
wait go up I'll be I I'll go up
later I just need to go this way
ky's chat be like can you get much
higher can you get much much
Tire okay and then we going this
way okay another one another one don't
fall don't
fall okay don't fall don't
fall don't fall
down fall
down we got
our what do you call it
the okay
actually actually instead
of the
maybe we should
just wait
[Music]
wait
one I wonder if she made because the are
[Music]
wait wait wait wait okay I need blocks
have
to seven diamonds in a Solo world
always so
thankful I used up like my 1,000 brain
capacity for this trip
you know the feeling of
like okay not like
this
uh let me ask
okay danger dangerous dangerous danger
danger
NE never stress me like
this but this
is different
thing I love you I love you
[Music]
mik let's go I love
youai I love you I love you
be careful be
careful be careful be
[Music]
careful be be careful is hotti
Hottie hotti
[Music]
hoty hoty hoty
be careful be careful be
careful be careful be
[Music]
careful thank
[Laughter]
it's okay
[Music]
thank
you I don't think we have
enough
foree
spee spee
we can go that
way
wait I don't know
[Music]
400 more blocks
okay we just go positive X oh
no yeah dangerous there is like no way
dangerous dangerous and we are actually
running out of blocks right I still have
of blocks
[Music]
thank
you just go up or just go up
okay the coordinates is like y7
right8 hours went by it so fast thank
thank you oh you stream for eight hours
already yeah nice you can go
12 so close to
12 you want me to go to 12 I don't know
[Music]
lava
okay should be
fine wait why why they stop get some
help
why do they
stop am I lagging or
what am I lagging am I disconnecting am
I fine
relo there go
n were you lagging yeah I I was like
where everyone stops
talking is this the Indonesian internet
no I think it's the m
I think it's my Minecraft my Minecraft
just had enough I
guess I don't know my Minecraft asked me
to stop
probably oh my
[Music]
goodness oh my goodness oh my God what's
that
[Music]
could that lava but could I have gotten
out yeah not like immediate
death how
deep hot tourist
destination what hot
tourist
destination nice
[Music]
wo this is officially the best tour ever
successful very successful tour I
see
nice I think in Japanese they
say very nice
tour no I didn't pronounce it correctly
I pronounced
inat oh this is the mushroom biome well
maybe we can a mushroom for you and you
one oh yeah or does not grow you
[Music]
you need the green mushroom
right take it take it
[Music]
we that close
right do we go here or do we go that way
I think I need the I need I need one uh
yeah I need I need that
yeah on
we just need one right we just need one
right over down here there you just need
one right yeah just one yay
nice I think everybody got it
yay let's
go okay
oh I can do it Kyla okay you just build
the
ground we are that close
already okay okay
I do have some experience with this in
the end yeah so it's been a while though
building pops like this very nice come
on
okay yeah okay hold
on we just go lower a bit it's
fine go down yep lower a bit it's fine
oo still thinking about Subaru Sire oh
yeah oh no ran out a
foress what happened
actually yeah she want with us in the
group on our first never trip and and
yeah she fell I think she fell into the
lava but because uh yeah but because of
a p the because of the what the pig
attack Oh I thought it's because of the
Ping oh that's very unfortunate yeah
wait what is going on Minecraft please
let me play the
game you're being bullied I don't know
Minecraft bully me so
hard Minecraft asked me to stop yeah
they're trying to Nerf you not
nice I think in Japanese they also say
na na na yeah they they say that
I have a few
more someone behind me literally putting
torch
te and every single time the torch is
put down it give me
weird feeling yeah does it scare you
yeah because does it give you a nervous
feeling yeah because I never
torch uh the way in Nether and every
single time the nether got a little bit
brighter it means lava so
yeah yeah so it it's like bangle me
every time
you put the torch it's like my
auto yeah it's my AO
[Music]
reaction I get it makes
sense it's
okay I can I can say before I place it I
can say it's fine it's
fine wait we need to go up
again okay
[Music]
big that was indeed lava hold on that is
not my torch yeah right you know what I
mean right mhm if it's suddenly bright
then same way
yeah but don't worry if it's not in
front of your eyes then it's all good
okay hold
[Music]
on okay come on come on Pinky
that almost sound like I was saying that
to to build the bridge with me come on
Pinky Okay hold on now we need to
turn it's
okay this way and then we should arrive
right I don't want to do it we should be
arriv
[Music]
like two blocks
up right
carefully how does she know
where we even took a curve how does she
Mo do you have the coordinates yeah oh
damn so
reliable no it's not about that it's
just it's just how I
survive seems like we traveled far
yeah now we're making
a path specifically for the Fortress to
reach it easier that's also
good it's there we
[Music]
arve or so it seems
she'll do anything for you
say how did they get where did they
go oh I didn't see oh
okay don't have one com
to we should put it there yeah so people
know where it
leads
yay thank you thank you I'm so happy
happy happy happy
happy okay okay
okay okay
[Music]
okay M skills right
that's right feel I don't think even
when
M okay
[Music]
okay for
n it feels like we have been in the ne
like forever right and then we go out
and then it's like boom years oh my God
we've been in the nether for 100 years
people age in the real life and we is
this a spoiler young and people and then
we're like watching
it what happened here what happened
maybe tomorrow we have to fight to death
in here wow let's
go well if I die I
die nice
for
[Music]
y thank you very
much thank you thank you
[Music]
it for
us who going to write
it um okay okay okay thank you
[Music]
no diamonds for Fortress
Diamond I you
like I think I think it's going to be
divided if I remember
correctly just said there's no reward
for the Fortress only for
the
wait oh yeah um yeah the Bastion
yes oh
Bastion one person use it
[Music]
first oh I think she's showing she's
showing her the she's showing her the
island
okay free Iron armors are playing what's
this what is this way another another
Farm the second one in this one's empty
oh
really okay wow wait hold
on
Wow we really need two iron
Farms very hardcore I
see very very
hardcore can I shoot it I
wait
b b
doco
b
bad
[Applause]
bad bad
b
[Applause]
b you sound like
a hello hello
nice one nice
[Music]
one hello hello yep mhm
I'm going to write something in it right
now oh okay really
quickly how do you make a
potion no idea you need the you need the
materials what what what kind of potion
is
different every potion is different
material any potion it only says potion
in the mission a uh you need to have the
[Music]
the what's that the potion maker kind of
thing and
then pretty sure I don't have any yeah
the Brewing sand yeah that's the word I
I have it uh bre sand I have it in my
house but
yeah um I got Nether
wart um yeah nether W yeah mhm oh nether
W this
oh uh wait let me check again fire
resistance fire resistance anything
extra it the skeletons and the g go it's
the blaze powder I can still do the the
powder the what powder and then oh we
need the bottle of water oh we we if you
want to do that one we can go to my
house
actually okay okay okay potion maker KY
yeah I have the potion maker
can I go and make yeah we we can go
together and
make okay let's
[Music]
go I'm not
sure but I saw
both for all of us
[Music]
automatic potion machine oh where uh you
oh okay okay okay let's go
then mhm
[Music]
oh you you just need to put the the the
the the what the the the materials the
ingredients the
ingredients oh really oh this one
oh oh I I I can I can I can take it for
her thank you okay okay wait wait okay
wait thank you thank you
automatic
automatic that's okay guys it's just me
trying to balance my life
[Music]
after after many things
happened auta
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah very nice T you know tour very nice
do you want to go to another
tour you know NE T
together with me
you don't
want even if you want I don't want it
anymore it's okay once it's enough right
maybe
uhhuh highlight opening soon no it's not
opening soon it's open and closed
already
thank you so for the membership GI thank
you thank
you oh
wait that's the flower from
hatot
hot guys should go back
oh
my almost
broken I I need to take get some
help okay Ella and H versus Ella
increase the
contrast opacity
100%
ha
cont the mouse is broken what
broken ah
you good I'm very
good never ever been this good
before so
good very
good okay okay we come back
okay okay automatic
[Music]
potion's go
thank
[Music]
you she's throwing nice
NE thank fore
[Music]
bone meal we going to take the bone
meal bone me bone bone me a bone a bone
of
a be like
that KY
get get get some
help 19 is 19 enough I don't know
the glass is
missing I don't have a
class yo what's up
hello we are uh canot bone me this
trying to make something yeah good luck
I cannot
B cannot mil
okay it's just that the the CL was Miss
thing I guess or what happened it's not
working I don't I don't know how it's
supposed to work oh cuz I didn't build
it but I put in the never
wordss I think it's not supposed to be
like it needs to be the blaze powder
you need
to to you okay I got it I got it
yeah blaze powder yeah blaze powder yeah
M the
powder
powder yay it's
working nice
[Music]
nice not again okay okay it's mundane
already and
then you
need everyone's sleeping okay okay sleep
sleep s
sleep I forgot
already maguma cream oh yeah maguma
cream
[Music]
it's useless but it is a
potion better than nothing
this one is wrong
[Music]
one we need
to oh the the nether word in the red
stone right and then after that we
go red stone after that to make it 8
minutes oh
[Music]
the mag cream first okay this is this is
like this is like wrong
order we shouldn't get the mundane
potion it's a wrong one so instead of
here it's a how do I make how do I make
potion hold on you need to take the you
already made a mundane potion at Le
mundane potion
is mundane potion is the wrong
one you need to no no no it's it's
different uh you need to take the
bottles
one taking out the red filled it with
the never yeah and then you need to take
the mundane potion first and you need to
re fill it with the water bottle you
take
it
m okay it should be correct right now
yeah and
then this is not
savable I guess I can drink it and it's
empty yeah it will give you no effects n
okay and then after the
yeah this one is correct this one is
correct okay and then after this you put
a red stone to increase the
time okay the duration I mean you need
redone okay this one is 3 minutes one
right and then nah the rest I put it
in um do you need the red stone dust
yeah you need the red stone dust yes you
make a red stone
uh no you you mine it but I can just
give
you um there's
there's Redstone Dust both
oh okay nice you can take it yay GG take
it I take
it dude do I make do I make red stone
with this red stone with
what do I do I make red stone with the
dust or what no no you just need the
dust oh I just need the dust and then
what do I do with the dust you later you
put it
there but
here yeah uh you put it wait you you you
click the this one this
thing this
one thank you the Brewing
St the brewing stand what do I do with
the brewing stand brewing stand and then
hold on why there's no
what okay okay and
then you need to put
the it what what the nether no no no not
that one I I I oh no no no no hold on
hold on no that one that one oh the W
yeah the W first is this is this
automatic already okay okay I put it in
there oh okay okay wait
this is this is this Magma Cream
yours I I I took the magma I took the
Magma Cream did we already wait it's a
water bottle
now I took the Magma Cream Ward First
Ward first and then the magma cream and
then redstone
[Music]
first okay take that okay MMA and
then red stone red stone red stone and
then red stone dust yeah the last one is
red stone dust I'm out of red stone you
got to
put okay take the MMA okay done done
take the MMA okay
and the Redstone Dust yeah and then
after this it's the final product you
can just take
it thank
you okay
[Music]
done on your own or you have a
potion okay
oh does anyone need the r
dust this one is really correct the
first one is neither War
[Music]
that's my bad
what what we're we're good let's go
let's go home
okay
y yeah what is happening mine
now I need to figure
out the way she
appears disappear yes you did you write
your diary
yesterday um yes I did uh what exactly
am I supposed to write what I
did yeah just write whatever like
anything just make it as kiaha Journal
like kiaha diary anything but it's
unlike
this it's not like I need to write
exactly all the missions I did no the
the the mission you just need to put to
write on this this book not in on your
diary Diary is the personal
thing no no it's not it's not it's here
[Music]
find your
name and then after you write later you
put it
here and then
tomorrow tomorrow uh after the peora
news you P going to uh put it
[Music]
here into the locker yeah your
locker okay I'mma write something then
[Music]
okay the maguma cream
gone but this five maguma cream is mine
onion Senpai I think onion Senpai just
dropped like one
[Music]
speeech
fore you are back
[Music]
what are you want to do
now I want do right the diary oh okay
okay di di okay maybe after
after wait everyone finish finish the
right
mhm what are you doing I don't know I'm
I have nothing to do
[Music]
I think I think yeah I have a dirt house
dirt house
yeah dirt
house yeah it's all right it's all
right let's go let's go so you want to
write it where where do you want to
write
it right right right diary yeah diary
about about today
today today this oh
okay okay
okay okay okay I want to go your house I
want to go your okay
okay po Ana Senpai I'll go with hatama
first to my house oh
okay you thank you bye-bye
this way this
way this way this
[Music]
way sorry wrong
way brain my brain is not braining
anymore
where are all of your armors it's gone
it's gone oh oh yeah because of yeah
because of the lava right
maguma oh yeah oh yeah yeah oh
no oh
no oh no
squishy so beautiful actually that
Village is empty so if you want to live
there you
can yay yeah this this Village is
empty yes yes
yes please don't die wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait no no
no no more
it's okay you you you have no
bed run run to the house run to the
house yeah let's go let's sleep let's
sleep my
baby sleep sleep sleep yeah I'm going to
sleep oh no bats
here no bats no bats BS no
bats no
BS I was the B no bed no
bed where's the bed no bed no bed no
bed I have the bed but I only have
[Music]
one e
yes
ouch I'm
fine
okay oh
finally thank you okay let's go let's go
let's oh
you don't want to take that
bed I think yeah you you you need yeah
just take that
[Music]
bad take bath take bat nice let's
go let's go let's go let's
go wow
oh no okay okay ni I'm hiding it's okay
W okay hey
wow okay
ouch okay
okay very
y let's go let's go let's go let's
go are you streaming right now yes yes
okay I'm streaming okay okay
okay okay okay I'm streaming too I'll
okay you streaming too tonight
why build so far by the way no it's
actually not that far but it's just
wrong
way it's behind that
mountain from the
magma
what your house near from the magma no
no no no actually actually it's not that
far but but I just I just I just bring
you the wrong way
I just I just take you the wrong
way yeah I don't have the boat but it's
okay I can make hold on hold
on I can throw this one and then this
one hold on okay wait
okay let's go got
okay let's
go she's my baby
yeah get finally finally we leave
together yeah live together
nice nice nice KY
kyos yeah kyos lost the way kyos lost
the
way okay
okay this Village is no one is leaving
here
so so
yeah negative x negative z Oh that way
that way that way that way that way that
way that way wait what this this house
is
broken
wait I'm wait
what maybe I eat
flow not that way that way no that way
kyos
[Music]
kyos okay
that one that one you see you see the
dirt
house with with the tree the tree house
tree house that's that's my house can
can I can I have the
food that's my
house can I get the food
food
wait yes thank you
[Music]
okay did I make
that yeah for the books yeah
oo a it say your house yeah I live like
this
yes what's so nice about this but okay
lighting food lighting
food
yay oh sorry Kyle is
na oh you don't need to read
that that that Kyla is very weird very
weird Kyla I don't
know very weird Kyla yeah
[Music]
I'm your
demonon
demonon what does it mean that thaton
demon is like the devil yeah devil yeah
ah devil yeah this this all of this all
of this right all of this board is
written by the devil not me yeah not me
not me it's it's it's the it's it's not
me yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it's not
your right
M I'm not a ky I'm K oh that one uh this
this one is uh Kiara's
writing yeah I I thought
that it's
funny I'm not I'm KY sounds sounds
similar
yeah can eat can can I eat this eat what
this one berries this one oh it's belly
Berry it's Berry you can eat it yeah oh
I can e that blow
belly ah I'm I'll put the bed y y
yay
yay I need to I need to remember how to
back oh this one this one it's actually
not that far but I this one this one
okay
here it's
okay you you go this way and then you
find that
village Village yeah the village that
Village
mhm and then we just go
left
[Music]
wait sorry disconnected sorry kyos sorry
actually kyos
sorry
okay this
way get some wait I think I think later
I'll I think later I'll make the I'll
make the
way okay to to go to go to the city yeah
I'll it's make way yeah I'm make
together oh okay
okay yes nice I like building yeah I
know you like
building just tell me what you
need ah okay
okay see it's actually not that
far that
one the this ala chy blossoms
yeah and then actually do
you uh you you go to the pulas and P
Farm
already
P Mama paa senp Farm she got a farm free
food farm oh really yeah you hav't I
don't go yet oh okay it's it's this way
yeah there's Farm
here this way this way this way hold on
not that way this
way
hello hello
[Music]
wait
armor the armor is somewhere it's okay
since she talking
with uhi Senpai the armor is there
we can have this
one this one
here we don't need
this we change this into phone
oh no we don't have
[Music]
the the what oh wait is there we can go
this
way wait it's actually faster
by
[Music]
walking and then
okay oh
hi okay wait
oh we just need to go straight from here
[Music]
my is my
daddy my
dad
Grandpa yeah be you
grandpa is my mama
mama
M I can't I can't
[Music]
baby b
T spit on oh really
wait did did did did you take uh the the
armor that I
Dro did I I think I think accidentally
this one no no no this this this one is
this one is for you this one is for you
thank you thank you yeah the iron one
yeah hold on hold on hold on uh and then
you also drop a chest plate cuz I can't
remember if this is my own chest plate
or this is I don't
know should also drop a chest plate and
I picked it up cuz I also have one oh I
see I see I don't know if this is mine
or
yours
[Music]
huh wait
sleep
sleep oh I forgot it I forgot it
[Music]
the pants I need crafting table
a thank
you
okay okay
okay we we want to go to
the uh paas Farm the farm the farm yeah
we want to grab some food what do you do
at the farm oh food yeah the free food
yeah let's go here oh yeah I think I
think I I need some food here
you speech speech
this
way that's
[Music]
a I want to take this oh yeah there's C
milk I need a
[Music]
I need to wait let me Mo there
come
on okay now what what are you trying to
do after
this I want to go look for diamonds oh I
see yeah good luck what what are you
what are you going to do after this I
don't know I think
I think I think after this I want to go
to the nether
again I think
[Music]
y let's let's do the mission um
so hasn't done any of the another
mission I thought she could take along
with you the another
missions yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
we I I if you want to go to the nether
yeah if you want to go to the nether
then you can go together with her
yeah mhm
yeah okay wait but oh the the mission is
just the mission is just gas right gas
gas and then the mus because I don't
know because she she she doesn't have uh
the weapon right ah yes I don't
have to the
[Music]
equipment blend her yours then for the
guest oh yeah yeah yeah I can I can I
can do that and
then the guest and then the
mushroom I
I she lives
yay yay yay anything else you
need and then what else I'm not going to
die anything else you need
wait what's the mission um gas mushroom
mushroom glowstone um see the see the um
Bastian see basan Bastian basan or
Fortress no um basan or Fortress I I
don't I don't know if B you just have to
see you just have to see them with your
eyes no need to go there because if the
B the one that we saw the last one the
red color one is actually B for it's
Fortress B another one so I don't know I
oh Soul
Sand okay and then Soul Sand and then
glowstone glow
stone glow
stone okay okay okay okay glow stone and
um if she wants to do the others um
there's also the the V three skeletons
Mission and I think that's it okay
yeah yeah yeah I don't know
like is it really okay because nether is
Nether Nether is like you
know my T is like because because you
know right that hatam is actually
together was actually together with us
in that group uhhuh earlier but but but
this is yeah this is her this is her
first day right so yeah what happened
was that I think she got pushed down and
cuz there was a lot of people but I
think if there's only two of you guys it
should be
easier is what I think yeah and if she
dies she canot revive Again by the way
yeah pretty much like
[Music]
that going to do it
the missions I the thing about the
mission is um it's only daily so the
missions I know right will disappear
tomorrow
yeah you
try she wants to
try I don't know or or like um we can we
can drink uh we can check another
mission tomorrow yeah it's okay I think
mhm I think I think it's I think it's
not only today yeah the I think I think
because the first day and jump to the
mission is not really
[Music]
yeah too risky for the first
day it's okay it's
[Music]
okay she doesn't want to trouble you I
mean she she wants to go but she doesn't
want to trouble you oh I'm I'm okay
I'm okay though it's okay okay H if I if
I die twice
um never mind yeah you you cannot you
cannot you can you uh you like you
cannot be alive again right if you die
twice
right I don't know I I don't know can
you be tce I'm I'm
[Music]
honest yeah I don't know because
um I don't know maybe isn't it maybe
like bet it's better for her like to
just get the diamonds
first Diamonds oh as right diamonds
armor yeah any any any diamonds like or
maybe I actually I can make her I can
create her what's that bow
right yeah better equipment first right
yeah because
[Music]
NE um until what time are you going to
be online I don't know I think after
this I'll just go idle meeting first and
then I going to be like taking like 15
minutes break I think I want to eat
first I need some energy and then after
that I'll go back
again ah
[Music]
wait wait whoa whoa whoa what
what
[Music]
for
speech for
[Music]
Let's Go na
byebye bye thank you goodbye thank
you I'm scared bow do you have
bow oh I don't have bow I need three uh
wait wait um
B oh I have a boat I have a a boat no
bat b b this one
bow I think it's it's okay uh I I I can
I I can just uh borrow it first I can
lend you the bow later
[Music]
I my
okay that's okay I need to I I need to
Alive no alive Al
I okay hold on wait
uh oh you need to go
eat yeah but I okay it's okay it's okay
okay I I I I I just want to go idle
meeting first like real
quick I'll be right
[Music]
back
okay wait I'll just go idle meeting
first wait
[Music]
get get get some help
got get some help
[Music]
get some
help okay hold
on okay m
hello hell hello hello hello um I gave
her a gave and then blocks a bunch of
blocks and stuff uh okay I think um I
think we need to go back to my house
first and then I'll make her a bow and
then
and then I can leave to the
nether okay so you're going to I'll
leave for you yeah okay thank you I'm
not I'm not going to go to the nether
yeah it's fine yeah but um she speaks
English and yeah it's fine I think she
plays a lot of Minecraft knows yeah it's
okay she'll be fine have any
problem yeah I Tred he plays Minecraft a
lot like yeah
okay unlike me I'm a newbie I'm so sorry
for all the problem today please please
survive okay yeah yeah unlike me I'm a
total newbie you'll be fine TR today
thank you good luck for mining thank you
for everything [\h__\h] thank you thank you
for
everything thank thank you let's
go go good luck thank
you okay um we need
to we need to go that way
first rip
n
n negative I got St I I
yeah let's go we'll not
die yeah I'm I'm scared because I that
twice we we got
it everything will be
fine yes yes I can do it I can do
it I'm not going to I'm not going to
bring the bed yeah we don't need the bed
yeah we don't
need we need to go that way everything
is
fine okay
okay go that way
don't lost
again don't lost
again it's okay we have been finding
elra
together El is more
scary really yeah nether is
fine wow
yeah so many
end
Ender yeah
end mhm is not not so scary yeah nether
is not so
scary okay I'll
just go around
okay oh there's another gate oh yeah
that's the
gate gate what
gate a
gate okay we
arrive oh that
the ne no uh I I need to go back to the
house first I need to put some stuff
yeah you don't have bow yet
right no bow right okay no
[Music]
bow I need to get this and
and
then we don't need we don't need the
[Music]
bed this
one this
[Music]
proen the ne wart is one and
then cream
Deer
uh
SK and then the Phantom membrane the
boat the boat yeah it's yeah I mean just
bring it it's
fine this one this one the right
mushroom everything is fine everything
is grite we don't need
granite and
then I just realize I don't ah it's fine
my S touch is
fine my milk touch is fine I just need
to
get the efficiency 5 is expensive I
don't
have any money I think we need to sleep
first it's like dark oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah after we finish I
want to I want to ride di yeah let's go
yay
actually maybe we can just fix my
diamond pck with the
diamond
16 okay wait
H
[Music]
Infinity o his sounds really o oh it's o
o yeah oan
[Music]
H okay this one the
bow W bow oh this is and then
yes and then this
one
okay nice okay okay hold on I put wait
shield shield hold on
sh
a extra block okay
um
shill SHO
[Music]
okay
then extra
block okay
okay okay okay let's go you good with
this I'm good okay okay
I drink water
and I how to say mama need to
rest oh
no I just drink water oh okay okay
okay oh Helm hel gold Helm um okay wait
wait wait wait I need the gold
helmet gold
okay let's
go
same helmet why I
have oh it's a unic
W you already have I have your uh the
design
design uh the UN no not the form uniform
unifor your hand oh no no it
wasn't oh that's that's that's the
that's my that's your clothes yeah
that's my
clothes that's my clothes it looks like
same yeah
I just
misunder
okay okay
okay okay okay so this is your first day
right yeah it's my first day
yeah there's so many p in my day mhm
are you going to play again
tomorrow I'm not sure I think it's not a
stream or not okay okay yeah but if I uh
when I go back home I want do it because
we oh there's a hole
we Rec create the out the way oh okay
the home right
yeah okay
okay this way this
way this way this
way what do you think what do you do
tomorrow um Minecraft again
oh no I mean uh in hard uh hardcore oh
tomorrow H I think I going to
see the Mi about the missions first
yeah okay okay oh I hope there is
some
there's I this
[Laughter]
[Music]
hi
byebye I I tell the she give then she
borrow the armor for me yeah yeah and I
I don't I'm not going to die okay let's
go oh no yeah oh no oh
no oh no oh there's a design there's a
nice really nice
design cool it's cute and cool okay okay
okay
be careful be careful
hey
okay
so which way we going to go this
way no not this
way no no no don't don't don't go back
go back no not this way scary scary
scary scary scary scary too much too
much okay
and this one
no this one I can't believe this
okay nice cute door maybe not scary this
one this one
okay nice oh nice oh no okay we go
yeah I don't know my Minecraft my
Minecraft sorry this
connected okay hold on don't fall don't
fall I'm not going oh we need to get a
glow glow stone yeah glow stone uh wait
and the mushroom mushroom and the
mushroom yeah oh the mushroom hold on
the mushroom needs to be
green green yeah the green one I tried
it try to find is it a gr no it's not oh
that one that one you can you can get
that one but hold on hold on hold don't
don't don't don't don't jump don't jump
don't jump don't jump I will jump you
don't jump okay don't jump I have a oh
you jump yeah I jump you don't jump hold
on okay okay hold on hold on baby jump
but Mom jump yeah baby baby can jump
yes hold on okay wow strong baby
yeah
okay okay now you can go down there's
someone over there
oh okay go down
here take that one
green yay Green Let's Go
nice one Mission done one Mission done
and then this one this one glow stone
you can use that silk touch I have a
silk touch oh you have a silk touch oh
okay okay thank you okay thank you you
so I make
some make some the
yeah okay
okay is this silk then silk nice I got
it nice one nice
one
nice nice nice yeah take all
yeah okay okay yes ooh okay uh can I
have my pickax back oh yeah yeah yeah of
course
yeah ah thank
you okay and the next one is oh next one
is the guas the B one ah okay uh that
one hold on let's go back here go back
first yeah go back first
the build be gas yeah the gas
gas this way this way go this
way I don't
jump yeah don't jump yeah I don't jump
okay okay we go this way this way
go go go go go go go go go go
okay wow this is very
long long long
way long long
way sorry it's okay
oh that way I came here before okay yeah
um sometimes there is gas here but no
guest H
okay no
guest
wow sometimes there is guas
but no guas
H
maybe I think we just need to wait
okay maybe this way I don't
know oh I heard
it I heard it the
cry yeah
somewhere it's somewhere
[Music]
uh is it like
upstairs upair I think it's up uh hold
on
o I think it's
upstairs I don't
know
h h
gas no
guest no guess okay fine okay we try to
find another way then okay TR let's
go there isn't gas that way then we can
come back here again yeah
okay let's
go the gas is
weird
Okay it's guest
guine okay
it's okay I just put a voice on um the
enemy voice on oh I
didn't yeah it's
okay okay
okay I think I Hur the the the guest
okay hold
on we
go this one is the T we go this way
nether castle
Road
Castle
yeah do come
here uh yeah but after you died
after yeah after you di
yeah I thought I remember this way yeah
after you
died
[Music]
okay don't touch the P yeah don't touch
the pig correct
yes no jump yeah no
jump dumb
scary okay we're going to find um souls
and souls and wait maybe we can try this
one one hold on wait wait wait wait wait
don't get close don't get
close
don't don't move wait don't move I don't
move yeah hold
on don't okay
okay I don't okay
okay okay wa wa try
to find
okay come
on Minecraft
Adventures second
time
Minecraft H No
guest still no
guest still no guest okay still no guess
we continue that okay okay we continue
we
continue wait uh positive that way we go
that way we go this
way way
yeah let's
gost there was there's the end yeah
don't jump okay don't jum
don't
jump oh I
think but I
don't I don't think fighting it here is
nice because the guest going to break
this okay okay yeah so no not not nice
not nice continue
yeah dangerous dangerous
cannot yeah yeah yeah
yeah we continue first safe place okay
we going to find safe place
yes
okay me go this way
okay don't don't don't don't jump okay
don't
jump okay
[Music]
okay looks like a gas no
don't don't don't don't no gas no gas
here
No
guest
okay and
then we need to go to the nether foress
too to see to for the
mission for the
mission
okay oh I can hear yeah I can hear the
guest too but hold on hold
on okay uh I think oh
nice hot tourist destination let's
[Music]
go this one is so sad okay uh keep
running keep running keep running first
keep running keep running keep running
here here here go go go go go go go go
go go go go this way go this way go this
way go this way and then hold
on okay wait wait don't jump uh stand
there okay don't jump yeah okay okay
don't
jump
yeah m
what biome what the
biome
wow B oh you enter all biome with NE
oh this
is
okay it's
coming oh run run back run back it's
okay I still try to okay there is
I'm
waiting okay it's coming it's coming
let's
go is it is it too far
okay oh no
[Music]
okay where where's the
guys
um it's in
front it's in
front wow
I can see it I too far okay
okay I think it's below
now okay wait
um
okay oh I need do I need to change the
setting
um maybe I don't know okay I
oh it's there okay it's coming closer
wait I think I think use my bow instead
of that
because
okay
okay if it's coming
out where oh
it's on the
[Music]
right I'll stay in front
gas
doco wait wait wait wait wait the
voice oh it's it's down it's down here
it's it yeah it's there hold on hold on
don't jump don't jump it's okay just
wait I going to okay can see it
now it's
okay don't don't run
back okay
okay I'm scared okay where's
it it's okay just
wait okay
I'm it's it's there
wait wait
wait hold
on it's coming up
[Music]
again hold on
oh there is
two there's two yeah oh I can see I saw
that a bit yeah there are two uh hold on
oh there's
two it's pretty close
now
can nice nice a little bit more it's
okay it's okay just wait just wait
okay it's okay it's okay you hit it once
great one okay yes
yeah it's
[Applause]
okay try again it's okay you're doing
great I try again
yeah oh
no left
side okay
I going
to pull it back
again
okay where is the other
one they're running
away
really h
where are
they okay
um uh maybe we can check the other way
first there maybe yeah just just uh no
that way just keep running okay don't
stop don't stop in the middle keep
running oh this way this
way this way that way this way yeah okay
okay keep running keep running keep
running keep running no stop keep
running okay no
stop I need to stand on the stor yeah
because they bre okay hold on now we
just going to make a new
way
okay hold
on wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
Rock don't
the one we need to
go
nice that was so close
oh but actually this one is
okay it's okay
D it's
okay okay okay just not there
right yeah looks
similar yeah it's okay it's
okay this one it was the same situation
when I fall into the Maga yeah but I
think I think I'm just
lucky just lucky yeah I'm just
lucky you sure I'm just lucky that I
didn't die
[Music]
wow
oh so it's not on purpose no it's not no
it's not really no it's not it's an
accident
I accident no that's that's that's not
straight straight fall into
the the
hole oh because maybe because I because
I didn't scream I should scream maybe
next
time maybe because I didn't scream so
you think it's um oh she do it in
purpose yes
[Music]
look like a good good Ella no no God no
God no God baby I'm just baby baby baby
baby how many how many times baby are
you baby every time baby every time
yeah how how many
lives 100
lives yeah get some help okay hold on we
are up here already but hold
on infinitive baby that's
cool this way
okay okay we need to go that way right
now I'm running out of
blocks
[Music]
okay
okay huh
[Music]
W but I don't hear any
guess
okay go back I don't hear any
guess no okay just go back
then okay
I just going to close this way again I
think oh that's the guas the gas sound
but no no no no no
no no no no that's gas yeah that's guas
but no we we we cannot we
cannot cannot cannot we need to we need
to be
safe okay what about here is it a
okay maybe you can
try
nice
mhm mhm maybe is there
no it's okay it's coming it's
coming jump jump jump I'm jumping I'm
jumping I'm jumping
I
know I should
have I should have closed the magma
there I
know I
know yeah
I'm saving all of the hold
on are
we this
way did I save everything
can use the bucket of water yeah we
can
okay behind you there is something this
one
any items left I don't think so
uh she got the gold right she got the
golden
[Music]
helmet the
oh get get some help and
[Music]
then hold on this way
nope okay let me just kill that
one and
then yeah I I I have all of the NES item
and I think I can like
um I don't know
wait n is still there right
g g get some
help oh
wait let me reply first
okay
okay uh
wait wait I cannot pause there
what
get get get some help
what is going on with this world
I should have blocked the way right
wait get some
help yes
[Music]
get get get some
help okay let's go back first and I
don't know um see
say I see said at least bring back the
uh n item but n just died too
so I had know what to do
now okay
hold on
okay done
wa get some help
pry thank
you s this is too s I'm going to die
to well don't
die get get get some help
get some
[Music]
help thank you
it's okay about about that we can still
uh see like what's the what's the court
going to say about
that so it's
fine about
that I mean if if we go to the court
right if we go to the
court I think I think since
hatama hasn't really
like uh this is just the first day right
so I think everyone will be
like uh agreeing with the another
Revival
yeah and then
yeah
because uh I don't know tomorrow going
to be like a
very uh like multiple cases for tomorrow
right we got like so
many
names has anyone been denied Revival so
far not really but um we did have the
what's that
uh we did have the
very hard case like a difficult
case I think the only rules is the last
day no one will be reive anymore
like uh the the the last the last day I
think it's the last day I
think what do you mean difficult uh the
the difficult
case like uh some agree some not not
really
don't it's not like not agreeing to
revive but it's something like no she
she ever tried to kill me once something
like that you know
yeah trial the
trials oh so there's like a voting kind
of thing yeah yeah yeah yeah there is
like the
[Music]
attorneys and then there's like the
defendants get get some
there will be the
judge okay
my car was Trail two for killing a duck
and a cat the other day oh really
okay I going
to
wait I going to save
the chest hold
them the chest
[Music]
I need to make a
chest put n item in front of her grave
me no I will I will I will save it first
um I'll save it here this one this
one this one
Unbreaking oh the boots got the boots
got feather
falling
okay and then the glowstone the
milk and then the
food this is her
[Music]
bow okay oh this is her
torch this is her
Shield I think that's
everything yep that should be everything
[Music]
nny tweeted that she fell asleep while
hunting for iron
[Music]
oh this one
okay yeah I think I should go to the TT
first wait let me sleep
first
and
then
oh I need to go to the TT first
J
it's okay guys it's okay
um I'll just going to fix all of my
items first and then maybe just call it
a day like this is
like too much
happening so I I I just I I cancel the
break
just end it but I think I'll just uh
keep laying like off stream because I
know that I cannot
um I cannot like um I'm not planning to
sleep like at this hour or
to yeah
uh this
one Court the court the court the court
wait the cour cour
doco that's fine yeah it was a very
chaotic day yeah
help today episode too much tragic
happened
di this one wait wait wait the cord cord
Doo uh oh cord that way
TTT
I don't know if Miki going to work on
the farm like the
place Farm
because I don't think it's actually a
nice idea to do that
actually I hope it will not uh take a l
f them again you know
seeing this makes me want to try
hardcore plus Lev full mobs I'm going to
die within 10 minutes it will be great
nice gra thank you
you're 97 set turn off event but that's
just how it is this is a hardcore
minecra anyway Ella assisted a lot of
Hello M today let's not forget that
thanks Ella
here thanks I want to say you're welcome
but why thanks thank you for the SC your
97 thank you thank you
[Music]
okay we're
here I'm going to fix this
first then we're going to chill a bit
[Music]
man what a day to rain
I can feel you
Kyla I don't know it's it's just a weird
weird
feeling yeah
sa s Mak
no you do great job don't be sad
um it's just like um mix feelings of
everything yeah
it should
just actually I don't know you know what
if because um before that things
happened right before that things
happened I I fell down
right if if that time I died like let's
say if I fell to the lava that
time she should just she will just go
back right and that will not be
happening
[Music]
I don't know it's just weird
like a combination of weird feelings
right
now weird
fings oh everything drops there
okay
okay yeah honestly
speaking I could just like land here my
armor
too yeah but things happen right things
happened blaming on the End Dragon and
Unleash Your reach to it
why it keeps
raining Minecraft stop
crying I forgive
you but I will not REM I will not I will
not remember I will never forget
I'll forgive you but I'll never
forget I can just do a flip
here but do you forgive
yourself that's actually a good
question that's a very unexpected
question about that I don't
know get some
help slow maybe solve by updating the
Java yeah but that's actually pretty
weird because if it's about update
dating the Java it was like it was like
very random some days it's just fine
some days it's
like the first one is fine like I mean
the first episode of this Minecraft
hardcore is
fine
then the third one is like very very
bad I don't
know yeah sometimes it's like
working fine sometimes it's not working
fine today is the worst like the
Minecraft uh disconnection get some
help you're one of the best people I
know there are always things that we
can't prevent but you did your best
nonetheless thank you cor Del
it's something that I just need to
like uh think about it again after this
with a very very clear
M yeah
[Music]
get some
help if are never ending only what is ha
had a good time with her baby she can
laugh about it so don't beat yourself up
about it thank you shiny Rocky yay it's
it's
fine why your XP stop moving oh because
it because I'm doing The Mending Buton
uh for
the
yeah now I don't know
like
uh what's that again
um it's always hard for me to like uh
what's that again
it's like I don't care how many
times I died you know like even though
uh like if like let's say
um I don't care how many times I di like
as in Zen L how many many times it's
fine
but if it's like about someone
else it's just so hard to digest all of
this
yeah and that's
also the reason why I was like very very
quiet earlier like as in with the group
one with the group
one despite all of the language
barrier I just want to make sure
that
everyone came
back
safe
yeah okay
get some
help okay it's
done let's go sleep and go back
okay
okay this
one oh we can just go
that you're looking for gunpowder or
something nah I just want to M the p and
it's
done yeah like I mean you know
um 100 Zen loss of mine means
nothing uh get some compared to just one
di like
[Music]
that we go that
way are you okay Kyla I'll be okay
B
[Music]
okay
coordinates negative
the building in front of the portal I
don't know what's
that we'll find out tomorrow I
guess we'll find it out tomorrow
H I cannot go that way now because
there's
a fench
now I'll take this sugar cane
[Music]
okay this
one oh yeah I I
haven't done my
RDA I still miss some SC and SB I think
get get get some
help
o and then we go that
way don't forget to put sharpness five
and Unbreaking to your equipment yeah
now we have TT so um we don't need to
worry much about the
EXP let's this very weird
hole H
wait oh yeah I need efficiency five for
my shuffles too
maning
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah since we have the TT I don't
know if I still need
to finish my spider and Zombie
Farm I mean I have the Soul Sand right
now
sugar cane Farm oh yeah sugar cane Farm
spider
spider spider I I know it's for potion
but what potion is spider
eye
weakness oh we don't really need that
go oh I have the bed
here bed bed
the weakness not necessary in hardcore
yeah we don't need
that
okay it's
done we can wrap it up hold on um
[Music]
I still have this so I still have a
homework for finding this
guy
pleas
hi
hi hi
[Music]
and strings you can craft scaffold huh
we can craft scaffolding from
strings strings
bamboo plus
spring I think scaffolding is
just
bamboo cannot hold
on
oh
H very funny actually
yeah I
see
understandable
okay yeah I think I'll just um make the
spider farm
yes spider farm
yeah spider farm spider f
[Music]
K have any interest on F of Exile just
have a dream Kai play F of Exile I don't
know not really sure maybe not
because I know that game got a lot of
things to grind and
then that's
a like how many years
already of that game
[Music]
it's going to be hard to catch
up trap door
oh the trapdor is still here I thought
there is no trapdor okay where is the
Villager
villager stop being
farmer oh Path of Exile
too oh
we can talk about that later
like uh bat of Exile two
right bad of Exile two wait where is the
new fil
ah
farmer I removed that already why you
still a farmer
I removed the composter
already
Barrel I don't think it's the barrel
vager no it's not this is a
farmer no not that one
huh okay that one is actually very weird
[Music]
that one is very very
weird and it's gone
now it's gone gone
I think this Minecraft is broken
totally it's broken
broken okay excuse me excuse me this one
okay
okay I'll
just lock
myself here forever
okay
okay I'll lock myself forever
de good night early Kyle I'm a bit sick
today can I get a get some help before I
go no if you got sick you need to get
well soon not get some heal get well
soon fast recovery thank you Zera yeah
enjoy your rest thank you thank you that
space grief and love are conjoin you
don't get one without the other all you
can do is love her and love the world IM
U emulate her by living with daring and
spirit and joy Jandy Nelson thank you so
much for
the pajang
thank
you and
[Music]
then
nice and then Z she mentioned that she
had fun still you both did your best
yeah yeah yeah actually actually she's
uh really really okay with that and then
like uh like yeah uh I say it like uh I
going to fight for her
and then I G to see what can I do to
like uh refi her and such thing like
that and then um they say she had
fun but
yeah it's it's it's totally just
it's going to
be the battle with me and myself it's
okay yeah she fine with it it's
okay and
then
zough wasn't your fault kind it just
happened I'm sure doesn't believe and
she hope for you to have lots of fun
regardless yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
true and
then let me scroll up a
bit keep your head high keep your chin
up and most importantly keep smiling as
life say what as Liv as the beautiful
thing and there's so much to smile about
thank
you help scares or she left and got
creeper can Noella what n or which
one oh you you say about the the other
possibilities
well yeah who knows
right what is going on with that drown
that drone is very
weird the Drone wants to be nice to
me I am
SL nice thank you for the first super
thank you thank you curn of Saturn of
events but that's just how it is
oh I read that already thank you GG
thank
you
uh
and the chat sends you a little more
luck and drink more thank you don't take
my thank
you oh yeah welcome back glad to have
you
back and then
Rich you did great light it's not your
fault thank
you thank you your man K funeral fun
thank you rip Travers please don't curse
Watami nah it's fine it's okay mdal is
next I'll be I'll be staying
here
um for quite some time
and
reflect and do meditation down here with
the
drown it's
okay
thenal gone until 2026 after the fall
year 97 thank
youus one L our Lu being my heart F nice
I think I just suffer a heart attack s
thank you what up I love you and chavers
now remain on H de thank you m k today
is amazing thank you T and ha protection
fun thank you girl funny here's my luck
and potion fun thank you music silence
thank you giving my luck Brew aama
protection fanai thank you darwis I
heard you need more luck thank you your
man protection fan thank you take my
luck please I con stand seeing her died
again I know know
right yeah mhm cookie fuin thank you
pancake got thank
you cor L Kal showing her home reminds
me of true crime documentaries when the
psycho killer shows his house to sub
guest but you're all
unaware wow you're you're you're
watching a true crime documentaries too
much and then share cing you rain alun
these are symptoms of a low social B I
survive though thank you and
then
of Z thank
you g funny congrat for safely getting
back home don't forget to ask them to ra
five star for the tour gu service thank
you k you short of 12 hours again
yesterday why do you keep teasing yeah I
should I know that I should try better
on that one right sherov thank you hello
KY good luck with your Minecraft JY it's
been two years since the day you have
saved me thanks a lot God bless you KY
take care ARA thank you uh Kyle
Gathering followers so fast no I'm I'm
not KY sh sherov thank
you and then we born to too late to
explore the Earth and too early to
explore space but just in time to see my
oi playing hardcore MC with Hol members
Jon bless bless thank you J Ryan thank
you Ben KY C proving that she is
minecraft g no I'm not thank you thank
you so much for the membership gifts CR
today is such just a wonderful day Ella
having a conversation with other H I'm
proud of you thank you we have The
Bravery to bring back slavery get some
help Flo thank you random E I read that
word ready than you and then I guess
that's
all yeah that's all that I missed and
then wiie iol luck incoming maybe T drw
more Cod yeah I I I going to have
a comfy talk with a drown after I end
the stream yeah
mhm D be yeah we got a house to build
for you and hatama
yeah thank you AR you done got C don't
be guilty for it thank you when milk why
that milk thank
you are we done for today yeah yeah yeah
yeah I I'm I'm going to end the stream
and then I'm going to eat and
then uh I'm going to write
the
journal
right
um all that's all other class yeah uh to
tomorrow no today today I'll have a
class too
so yeah it's actually not too bad this
is already like uh 7 and
almost almost 7 and half
hours
so it's okay I'll be back again
um hey wait hold on
I don't know about
the
wait usually
usually the court happen at 5
right my class is at five
though okay um it's okay I just going
to I just going to write a very long
long long long long long long long long
text to P
Senpai and
then yeah I just going to write
a lot of
like one page of A4 no maybe maybe
that's too
much PE is going to wake up and go y on
sister y
[Music]
yeah mention a lot of diamonds for bribe
purpose we're not going to bribe anyone
get some help get some help
Discord I going to Che P Senpai to
explain
everything
yeah she's going to think you died
oh no I going to I literally going
to write the the whole
story yeah like I don't want to say
about who died first so it's going to be
like hatama and
I we have a great time and then we we
went to the
Nether and then we finish some missions
and
[Music]
then and then after that yeah guess this
that this that guess mhm and then boom
boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom boom blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah and
then
yeah and then I'll end it
with I
back
for hatama life
you can just take my life it's
okay yeah very easy to understand thanks
you're
welcome I I I will I will pay for
anything
yeah trade
lives yeah trade lives
sound like set ending what do you mean
set
ending she going to say no no no I can't
take God's life I'm not
God if I'm if
I'm the
gut I could be able to prevent that but
I'm not
sound too long story short no no no no
no no no no long long story short no
it's going to be a long long
one start your diary Noel with a poem
about the ba banality what is banality
of existence said the mood I always
appreciate the huge heart you have rest
well KY no I don't don't have huge
heart my little poor
heart rain thank
you I have this fairy tiny tiny soft
heart customer johnon good day mate hope
you have a good meal today thank you for
the stream Johnson the 5ifth oh oh
Johnson the 5th oh
hello it's been a long time tomorrow
going to be Johnson the
6th
yeah fire
fire
potion
gin get some help
[Music]
PR
yeah um fire
resistance yeah
[Music]
rain
aler if your heart is small mine is the
size of
a don't say
that okay then I think that's all for
today it's been
an amazing
day thank you so
much
bye-bye thank you for the stream thank
you
adios byebye thank you thank you
by by bye I'll see you again tonight
yeah I'll see you again tonight bye-bye
[Music]
a