[Music]
he
happy Mother's Day
you hey thank you
welcome you get off the cat hair off of
my
microphone ooh so much cat
hair so much cat hair on my
microphone happy Mother's Day at least
in my
country are you guys streaming hard
Challenger oh wait oh my tail is there
okay yo yo y y y y very close to 1
million yeah yeah yeah very close I'm
I'm I I'm streaming it silently on the
side too
now and with the hack playlist y'all can
help me out with that you you guys know
the hack playlist let me give you a
link
oh here during the Stream how about we
all play this on the side it's 5,000
views left 5,000 if we all put our uh
energy and uh together our strength it
is it how many people are here right now
1,800 probably a bit more CU YouTube
being weird if everyone listens to it
like four
times shouldn't that do the trick
or why am I being like really
stupid what wait that makes sense
right like three to four times okay okay
okay okay okay okay and
please listen to it on the side so we
can get finally get our Challa to 1
million the it deserves even more let's
be freaking real it deserves so much
more but
yeah uh where's my
gun
it oh
JF who the hell needs gif
Twitter tell me tell
me
ju convert to
jbag Let's Go download jbag thank you
this is so stupid what the hell there we
go I got the gun I got the
gun uh oh did I say
Jif Jif is that how you would pronounce
it J
F let me fill that real
quick
uh col
key immersion
destroyed okay
uh custom color select color or can you
not sure
color that one yes okay and now yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah I mean it's a bit green
behind my
[Music]
o you see what I see
H yeah I mean also that's that's that's
my they should be on that side huh uh
that's okay I can I can um turn it
around actually okay wait if I
what if if only if only it was a
PNG then it would have been
easier that's okay W I'll work with this
for now and I'll
Transform um
although I am left-handed if I would if
I were to use a done I would probably
have it on my left hand oh well we don't
we don't need to be so realistic what
the hell obious why is it poging out
like this again this so weird here we
need to need to open task manager in
order to make it become normal again
um
well why can I not flip it
horizontally oh it's henter no no no no
no no
no flip there we go okay
[Laughter]
what do you think about
this is it too big I'mma shoot you I'mma
shoot
you you better be careful what you
say let me pour some
water say I'm cute give me kibble or I
shoot you this is
theak clean my freaking l or I'll kill
you I
shoot you want me to shoot huh
huh huh what what do you mean you got to
know what why didn't you buy more oh
yeah what about the sneak snacks what
about what about the the the SOP Sloop
liquid ones huh you don't have those
either you want me to shoot you
it's over I can live on my on my own I'm
an independent kitty cat I'm an
independent kitty cat I don't need you
stupid humans I was just using you
anyway I can do this on my own this
house belongs to me anyway it's not your
house it's my house the moment you
adopted me it was always my house it's
over
you need to understand the import
important fact that cats are smarter
than
humans
okay and I have outsmarted you or
however that's normally
said wow wow wow wow
wow okay I I'll let you go this one time
if you continue to work for me as as is
my
uh
uh wait I'm trying to think of a word
that doesn't
sound
scandalous as my butler
Butler okay okay okay now we're ready to
play now that we got into the
mood okay
okay I I I by the way I ate pancakes
before the stream that was nice I made
pancakes
pancakes oh you don't hear that do you
uh which one is it
all
game wait even when I'm looking away I
still my hand will not move I am always
aimed at you guys better be
[Music]
careful okay well let's do Desktop sound
then oh but it's a bit
noisy I didn't prepare well I started
the PC 5 minutes before stream
start Trigger Discipline H excuse me do
you you want to be shot or do you want
to go to the user room which one do you
want it to be
huh
huh better be careful what you
saying okay let's
continue uh controller are you working
yes dead beat wait did just said dead
beat somewhere there
interesting it's to me like dead beat
was a word um that I didn't know until I
met
Kelly so it's it's weird for me to see
it used in like like actual like actual
something like
something means useless burn bum useless
bum dead beat means useless
bum
oh w w wow wow welcome back everyone to
nyakuza or I like how this sign moves
when I run against it
wow
oh I'm
[Music]
sorry that that was
a what okay okay I'm sorry can I destroy
for your plans too
no okay what about the
bucket sorry I'm just testing out what
what works in this oh my oh sorry you
probably were really trying hard to
raise your window oh God it oh I'm so
sorry I'm so
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry j Festival ooh the bucket will not
be destroyed though huh cuz it's plastic
nice bucket good
bucket what are you
doing oh look at y over there
[Music]
oh okay what were we doing we were about
to being shot I think right on this
bridge we were standing here and and
each one was like well shoot me bit
shoot me if you want to and then they
didn't shoot me
cowards okay oh what is that what is
that raged Club can I use that for
something for like for like uh choking
someone
perhaps uh I feel like that's the only
use I can think
of threatening man I forgot how to fight
how do we fight again ah bunk bnk bnk
nice that was easy and B B oh come on
one more one
more oh oh
you're lucky I'm not using my gun
yet okay where are we
going following the pink thing I guess I
got to go over the
bridge W so cool it's so
pretty wow wow
[Music]
wow tyan thank you for the red super
chat kind of okay let me in let me in
let me in let me in let me
in I want to sing okay I already sang
Yesterday a lot got to got to chill
what got to go over
here oh are you selling some onini or
something they want to fight
SAU sauce they got umbrellas cute it's
like they can do a little dance
Dan Dan
[Music]
oh wait she actually really gives me a
bowl of pork soup
oh so thank you thank you wait did I I
didn't even pay for that thank you did
is can I eat that like
anytime audio low wow surprising
okay
okay no I didn't really go up much
higher did
it okay well
no what is that
oh we're back here oh that's where it
led us let me let me heal
us
recover oh
okay I hear
R this dude not me itan runs like a cool
dude is this your home now kiar
nuh-uh well we've got a job to do
tomorrow better make sure we don't over
sleep yeah good night
all right sleepy
sleepy below what the okay
[Music]
wait is it weird that that umbrella make
me think of that song does it have
anything to do with
umbrellas is it like being danced with
umbrellas
it was fine oh damn
it okay well now you bum Boozled me I'm
confused uh what are you doing with a
gun I'm
theak why should I not have a
gun wait wait wait wait wait
wait Cor is
line maybe here after all like here here
yeah okay okay okay well if you tell me
the audio was fine then let me turn it
back down
[Music]
again okay streaming H Challenger as
well a it no wait that's damn it you got
to repeat
it okay everyone stream hi
[Music]
CH please put the gun down hell no hell
no okay
hi good morning oh all right let's head
over to hakan's
restaurant at the actual proper
restaurant M mhm she said it was just
down the river as I
recall okay just follow follow the river
I guess what do you
want
party the are you talking about
what are you talking wait I want to do
cans cans cans can o tax can I ride
it can I do the Cs again is it early
enough you new me what are you feeling
today collect count do
it uh
easy I never did a drunkard voice before
on stream how do I this again
okay how do I activate the oh oh I
should have got down how do I activate
Anem the drink again oh my God
I probably
xray no no no no no
[Music]
[Applause]
no wait do I have enough for the goal
already I do don't
[Music]
I no you just say hell
no it
oh ah wait
y y byebye
bites all M all the CER M now hopefully
nobody bumps into me now cuz I'm going
home that's enough for me oh wait let's
take those with me as well all right all
right all right all right all right all
right oh the lucky oh whatever we don't
need it we don't need it this game looks
sick I got to try it yeah it is
sick hello
hello oh
can good that's what talking
[Music]
about why is yako are doing public he
we're not doing this for the public
we're doing this this for us cuz we
struggling okay those people with
money
them doing this just for myself and no
one
else you did pretty good come
again bye-bye okay now to the on to the
restaurant it said end of the end of the
river s a
spe I that but on the map it kind of
shows me like to go over there let me
let me go to the other side wait we're
having a conversation again no
okay no you want trouble
huh I heard you talking to me from the
side I was just minding my own business
and then you're
like shut the up I throw you down
that River
where you belong into the freaking
trash drown there you
fishy okay that's that was that way too
easy
byebye with
you Mr
Obvious oh haven't seen anyone with de
kind of hair before I'm sure you already
know this but you're in yokoh so
what what is your problem
wow wow I guess he just States the
obvious oh cuz I am in
y oh the lady with the with the ugly ass
[Music]
leggings yes I am
here very polite
[Music]
huh she
drunk this is not a restaurant is
[Music]
it ah that is not a
restaurant we're
cleaners that is not a restaurant
oh oh thank you for the red super chat
M wow
five oh wow yeah wow
no you do the
tissues aren't you used to these kind of
tissues
huh
yeah
well Bach
Japan you want to fight
fa for 15 years and what did they
nothing it
seems It's
traditional what a weird
reason that makes sense okay I
understand the
name Japan cleaned up oh really oh
who the hell is
[Music]
that
for the acting like the animation plus
the voice
acting is
better like the Japanese dramas I've
seen on Japanese TV
I don't know it's a really weird thing
to point out I guess but what that's one
thing I've always uh noticed about
Japanese dramas Japan Tov is like the
acting I really don't like it
Japanese protests always so peaceful
[Music]
they're trying to
survive I I understand both
sides oh she actually does that
I hate him I hate his attitude he's
idiot punch him punch him in
them or between his legs
title don't like his
attitude the way he speaks it's like
so like looking down
upon but like still in a kissing me off
[Music]
Polly yeah right's mother was a
prostitute oh
[Applause]
no thr him come on thr him why did you
not do it why did you not do
it
Yi why AR they scared of freaking
tissues come
on that's what makes you run away
freaking tissues they're soft as
feathers ridiculous see this is how how
peaceful and how lame protests
are there at
least it's it's been two over years
since blade Japan started protesting in
it now they're marching around almost
every every week a lot of places have
shut down thanks to
them but you holding out for all the
girls you've got here right most of them
don't have Japanese citizenship they're
children or grandchildren of illegal
immigrants if I shut down where would
they
go if we're being honest they'd probably
fall in with some leeches who'd skim off
most of their
earnings so I do what I can to protect
them myself you know
n okay okay yeah yeah yeah I show the
tissues might be yeah not so clean I get
it I get it I get it but still like if
that's what stops
you it's not like he's going to like
from up there throw it down and and it
like instantly falls into your mouth or
something it may drops on on your uh arm
when you're wearing cloes so like I I
mean I would run as well
what oh oh you came back for more trash
fellas did a on us this
afternoon you're still out protesting at
this hour do you even have a permit no
this isn't a protest B Japan helps down
TR the end the week
too sometimes that means giving people
like these guys are support
they were just hanging around a
hamburger joint in front of the
station they lived on cheap processed
food their whole lives they don't even
know what a good de good meal tastes
like and they can start to
grow so we're trying to give an
opportunity here tonight will cover the
build what are you getting at oh I just
thought I'd take these boys to Fe on
some Hiers cooking from this fun
establishment so that's your ankle you
really fought this through what hold up
what's the point of taking him somewhere
with no
food that's exactly what he wants to
hear my permit says I run a restaurant
so I can't
refuse are we going to cook are we going
to cook what are you going to do then I
guess I'll feed them until my the money
runs
out then I suppose my party ENT I you to
enjoy your
meal if they have any food to say look
for to he
[Music]
so men tonight old lady I'm afraid all
I've got left are some stale
crackers 10,000 Yenni that's like $100
eat
up you with
Granny I'm not a fan of crackers I have
some cookies I think they're a little
moldy
though you got that food
uh I wouldn't eat it but I think it's
appropriate for the
occasion you take Us For
Fools calm down
fellis we're perly allowed to be
dissatisfied customers you're not even
in the restaurant yet you didn't order
anything you not going to you go
somewhere else what the yeah get us
some real
food H shut up stop complaining and get
out of here so oh I see you were saying
this place doesn't have anything to eat
guess we'll go tell bleach the B guy who
gave us the money
then you're going to pretend that was
your go from the
start that sub story was finished paper
you guys got hired to mess with her
business so get out of
here oh the guys get with us you first
you consider yourself
defense beat the out of them
let's
go sorry I had to drink some
water one down um pigeon raid on you
maybe is that AOE by the way it's not is
it yeah it's not oh oh oh now the
start bleeding oh no oh perfect guard at
least
one oh can I not do perfect guard twice
seems really
difficult t
Team I get one soon ow nice sounds good
n has a hdden skill use it oh wait how
low on HP are
we
Face nice yeah
that was kind of
unnecessary oh wait
uh what he's going to sleep
here oh cute
oh mad dogging me huh I don't even know
what that means so it does have no
effect on me
oh oh
M Rock swing how about
that yes
[Music]
bye-bye power nap I can't do that when I
take a nap I sleep for like a million
years I was
trying okay okay okay now go go go kill
him
nice don't even need skills these dudes
are
lame okay byebye it's over guys
all oh level rank up
ooh I actually never looked at this
closely oh I learned a new skill
headbutt barrage bar job dead beats
there we
[Music]
go I I don't know what I'm
seeing homeless guy pyro belch what's
that are you done guys huh still hungry
[Music]
shoot me please
Kor oh no I will not I will shoot people
who deserve
it no
problem oh he wants to do it again
huh oh what is that
will you let me sleep in your
place don't you need
it do I have to live with one of those
sexy
women what does she what does she mean
but yeah I guess that's good we got a
prop proper room we're getting up
[Music]
there but once he has an address he can
get a job
right I don't quite understand but okay
[Music]
I don't get the logic but okay I agree
but I also don't understand
[Music]
y she said the thing yeah my own thing
yeah that sounds good job and it's a job
and and a
[Music]
home all right
so happy for n like how long has he been
homeless probably a long time
right yeah
drob the
history the history of what happened in
that room yeah think of
it a oh come
on it's like they act like these Yakuza
people act so
badass oh no that's really bad suck from
what I know they act so badass but
then they have this big big height at
least in the game I don't think they
really do in real life
like he was a doctor and I mean I know
that but but he was selling the drugs
from the
hospital are you
[Music]
stupid
for
Fore
fore fore
he really does look like 40 no
no what kind of skin cream have you been
using what's your skin care routine tell
me
Jon uh
Yak n
for
Fore
spee
fore
fore fore
[Music]
cutee
speech foreign
speech
spee
[Music]
for I'm getting emotionals kind of cute
man
for yes do some hero punch some
yaka idiots kill them all and
beat the hero at the end of the day
cheers go
[Music]
that fore
spee
fore
fore fore
fore foree
[Music]
the dragon of Yokohama Yokohama no let's
go got to move on guys got to move on
The World Keeps
spinning can't be sad
about dead maggot
[Music]
dying
cue cute
H
H did someone go
in they sleep early huh wa I don't know
what time it is
but oh
buddy not everyone sleeps at 4:00 a.m.
K I don't know what you're talking
about oh
yummy fried chicken and hot dogs on a
stick wait is this
sausages
[Music]
for oh they you over
is there GP oh
my is there
GPS huh GPS oh oh okay yeah
you were tracking
him that really reminds me of a story of
a friend of
mine that that really really fascinated
and upset me I don't know if my friend
is watching
this no it's really about a it's not
about me I would have been so mad oh my
God my friend has a friend and they're
working
together and my friend got a new
phone and was like she doesn't know
about much about technical stuff so at
work I guess she kind of showed her
phone off and then her working
colleague um took her phone and like was
doing stuff of it and she didn't know
what what what he was doing but no no no
it's really not me it's really not me
but then he in I guess like installed
some kind of weird
tracking like but the thing is like that
friend
um they're they're not like dating or
anything they're not by far not in that
kind of relationship they're just normal
friends uh but for some reason two
of uh her working colleagues superiors
actually kept on like for fun tracking
where she is but like one reason I guess
was because she would sometimes come
late to work and all that but doing that
without letting her know like she didn't
know that that was going on and then
like a year later or so she found out
and they were like ha ha
funny but but when I heard that story I
was like what the actual what the
actual what the actually but
they're all friends and and work work
colleagues but I I just don't understand
like right it's
like oh my God I'm still not over that
I oh my God yeah she I guess forgave
them I guess but yeah this
ridiculous ridiculous
[Music]
GPS yeah well makes no
sense that's illegal but nice that's not
nice teach me not going to teach I don't
know how to do that even
how to send your how to install
something that sends a location to your
phone from another phone I don't I have
no idea how to do
that yeah it's a huge violation of
privacy
exactly
foree fore
story is complicated got a
[Music]
focus
for oh was he able to ra his
mind
for
fore
[Music]
for questioning someone so long until
they question himself
foree
fore
for
Fore happens a lot doesn't
[Music]
it
fore foree
that's nothing I wake up at 1 P.M
all right free party let's
go oh man come
on that's
stupid that's quite
stupid yeah sounds like expensive HS
indeed drinking and women
[Music]
yay n change from dead beat to
freelancer no more dead beat bye-bye dad
beats getting promotions now dad beats
promote it
now all right I'm sorry sorry
guys uh yeah okay is it morning can we
do the
cans we get a bit of money from that
don't
we dead it's working now
oh a bat take it take it it's like wait
that's like um what do you call that uh
um
AF um the one who pulled yeah Excalibur
Excalibur pulling out the sword yeah
yeah yeah that's the same
thing s stck in the ground I think it's
a bat why the hell would there be a bat
stuck in the ground
who knows it's probably some kind of
lean
prank I'll
just they're really doing it they're
really doing
it hey what are you doing isn't it
obvious I'm trying to pull his damn bed
out I bet if
we
did we could get a few
y p he did a pun he did a
pun you're stuck in
there no way no
way that's is son you're strong give it
a
shot so let me
edit jam it man one budge must be pretty
wedged in there you're too a prophetic
I'll show you how it's
done come
on come on
cry I guess oh come on but what would to
do any differently than I did I bet only
chose hero well okay okay yeah he's the
hero yeah yeah yeah yeah he is a hero he
wants to be a hero that's
right hero
him you know how in RPGs there's always
some holy sword only the hero can pick
up C her has been on the quest to be
become a hero since he was a kid S I
mean kind of uh oh well that dirty old
bad isn't exactly a holy
sword leave it to the to reality to
crush the
fantasy the holy sword of the
hero I'll be the savior of this
world that's theity you look actually
the part H if you Knuckleheads are done
Ro playing shall we go find some damn
jobs what is it this
time hey you guys you having a good time
well sorry but we're dead hunters you're
looking for
Callie so make this simple for for of
all you
cash we don't actually have any what
does that mean d is that a way of saying
something free m dudes and no G you're
right you need to life better than that
old
bastards damn the TRU really hurts when
punks call you out on
it hey Mero feel like using the holy
sword to Smite some
monsters good let's
go why is he suddenly so big
did you see those guys transform oh my
God yeah they really all of them did oh
my God the left one is really
[Music]
B no I see it too I see it too each
one oh god oh
no let's try that out let's see what it
does
oh we call that a fire spooker oh man
that didn't even do that much damage so
what we have mega
swing where is my new
skill W that's my AOE skill
[Music]
nice sh
oh perfect guard oh oh that
[Music]
hurt hey come help
me nice okay one
down don't oh come on
I sh
let a power
now so
cute buk BKK come on
nice
[Applause]
good level up rank up what's the
difference between rank up and level up
fore
[Music]
rank increases the skill okay okay let
us update the B thank
you fore foree
cute what what what you just changed
your job from dead beat to freelancer
now you're already a
hero enemies throughout the city will
change their appearance according to
kasa's Wild
imagination okay
he's a
okay
okay maybe you should go home and become
a
streamer play on your little
PlayStation all right I want to pick up
some cans but I got to you up first
huh be
burn
you know would like this
game cuz of the
puns give him the last strike oh wait
strike that that wasn't even the pond
wasn't even on on purpose but it's funny
because he has a baseball
[Applause]
bat yo can I get some
cans yes please ooh medium let's
go we got the
next uh thingy what what changes though
more more
enemies I'm going to I'm going to ooh
going to go that one
[Music]
uhoh can I have
that thank
you no oh
where do I
go no no no no no no no I want to use it
a little bit
later we we have 2 minutes left where oh
oh where am I oh there we go oh behind
me
[Applause]
ah H wa there's barely any
can oh wait I didn't see that
I want to turn
around give
it I don't how can I miss it again okay
whatever oh
it's not going so
well oh oh here's the lucky go wait wait
wait wait ah
yes yes yes yes thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank you oh ah
thank you thank you thank you thank you
oh okay let's go let's
go you idiot bastard
[Music]
right at the end but okay we got the
minimum anyway we passed
anyway 2006 or so yeah yeah see
rank next time next time next time we'll
do
better okay
bye-bye so where do we go now
where do we go now follow the pink
thingy I don't have money for taxi
probably so going to ignore that a nice
weather
today
tanky ooh we're going here oh yeah hello
work hello I want
work what I should have bought some heal
items damn it that's right yeah maybe
after hell
work I'm another day of no work
same here damn
it chill dude that's someone's
bicycle mat might have taken the cake
but a lot of these people are pretty
rough around the
edges what do you expect finding work
isn't easy these
days well don't let it get to you just
got to be
patient hey isn't it a
Dy you're right it's a
dy I literally can't remember what kind
of voice I do for most of these guys so
I keep on changing hope it doesn't uh
bother you
guys can't say I remember them I you do
you R your lives did I I take it I
arrested you at one point or
another you aren't allowed to forget the
yaha p pink B
it's in J's top burglar what a cute name
oh yeah that takes me back man how long
has it been since I busted you guys 20
years we got criminal records now you
and now we can't even work
you're going to take some responsibility
for that that was your own
responsibility you
idiot hey so that that just follow you
guys got
busted you cop bro n just here to fun
some work come on let's leave these guys
and Ste and get out of
here
huh what hold on Adai why are you
looking for work because I lost my job
at the station you
prick you quit that means you can't
arrest us anymore right no matter how
many times we hit
you you're sure want to fight us I have
a hero here in my
team you that bent on Revenge why not
put that kind of effort into your job
hunt shut the hell up we beat the
out
you let's goass
men what are they wearing Auto Battle
mod can I'll be selected El to turn on a
ble mode
on use up down left right to make a
selection okay do should I ever use
[Music]
that let's see what
happens oh but I still have to press
that I guess it chooses the attack for
me but I still have to press the buttons
oh
um
P for Grants Auto balance F yeah I think
so
nice he stole my
lunch give it back seaweed on nice we
got some lumo from them
why why why did he give me my ony
back damn you we'll cat you back for
this don't you forget us this time yeah
you can come back anytime let's hang out
again talk about taking it
personally you arrested so many people
you don't even remember remember what
they'll look like you son it's a ancient
history now but I didn't have to deal
with like that while I wor badge I
wonder if that's going to be the new
Norm for real I don't want to be
anywhere near you
then let him come I'll take as many as
they can through with me well hell work
Waits that's
all it's tough making all these voices I
wish there were more female characters I
want to look for before I go inside I
want to look for a there I go for a
vending machine oh which one should I go
which one has better food is there a
difference o 10 MP 15 MP 10 MP oh this
is all MP green oh these are actually by
the way old drinks that really exist in
Japan
M wait this is 10 MP this is 10 but this
one is
cheaper this is
155 okay let's get uh
two of those I don't really think I'll
use the MP recovery much
though and this one attack
evasion can you gain more money oh wait
I want what about
HP I forgot about treasure hunts
10 on it is there on it
HP h
uh what about that lady over there
though I oh wait I imagine something but
can I not buy food
here poof no there was no lady here HPS
from restaurants oh is there nothing I
can like bring with
me I do have something though I think
let me see I have onini on kitty I have
two one another another two and that
soup okay I mean we're fine for a little
while until I find something
again I didn't see them
here what was
that what was that you're fighting
against some
bugget that was too
easy oh oh my God hiso his outfit is
like like a t like a I don't know like
M like a standard the basic outfit in
Japan that you like like
yeah like in Japan if if when people
like dress up or cosplay as otaku for
for like I don't know for a joke or so
they they dress up like that I don't
know it's kind of weird to
explain that's like the
typical dress up
for
this yo I'm back and I got an
address oh we're so close to no no wait
yeah no we are closer to K you could
have been the nice number why were you
lame so close
wait sorry I was pouring in
water all right to it down no need for
Fe
Trix oh huh weren't you the J
oh oh AR you that homeless guy I sent
over to the bar for a
sidekick so you've got a roof over your
head now huh oh thanks for the job you
helped us get
glad to hear it so why are you you on
that side now what do you mean this is
my
job oh he's the
boss the
director you're the director of this
place director think you can find do
some
work oh you made some
friends yeah my party's got free people
in it
now
party you play games kasuna in his head
the whole
time yeah I'm a big Dragon Quest
fan Dragon Quest that's a good one I
play it myself
what anyway let's see what jobs we have
for the hero and his rtin
R in you
here we are in your depth
good that said I just want to warn you I
made an exception last time I was trying
to see if a couple of homeless guys
could stand on their own
feet oh but now that we're doing this
legitimately I have to follow the rules
what rules the Golden Rule I can only
aside jobs that you qualified for
even a Dragon Quest some jobs are locked
until the character reaches a certain
level or skill right think of it like
that life is just a big rpt when you get
down to
it sure so what would our current
experience level let us change
into an xcon a bum and a fired cup
here's the best I can do for you right
now
what will it be what will it
[Music]
be ah cleaning cleaning and wait wait
wait
waitressing a special bath
house so a soap land yo again back to
our home place thingy hold on maybe
that's the best you can get these two
but I've got years of service lean on
according to your documentation you've
never been married what's that got to do
with
anything I can see in the future
guys you're telling you're telling
you're telling me you've gone this long
as a lonely single M about resorting to
paying for it this seems right up your
alley excuse me what the what the
how dare you I mean it's not even
that illegal
anyway what you boys need is to build up
some work
history and don't think this Bath House
gig is going to be a walk in the park
the owner there is a little eccentric
and it's totally up to him if he takes
you on board good
luck okay let's go nail this into you
all right we're going to an interview
guys everyone suit up you're not going
to
change okay I guess I mean it's maybe
not necessary to wear a suit
okay
taxi again not going to take it I don't
have the money for it oh I rest
so Tako Yaki
here oh my
God want to go back to Japan now dude oh
man I want to try
this p and call match up symbols
on the free spinning re to win tokens
each one ination oh no guys I've started
this I'll probably get
addicted oh no oh
no uh-oh
gambling
oh I choose a place to oh is there a
specifically good one oh my God what is
this God Hest toys de FR Return of the
Gods oh my God I don't like the look of
Pachinko it's kind of creeping me
out he out the money yeah how much money
do I have anyway
There Goes My okay
okay let's resist let's do it when we
are rich
okay um but by the way the Tako Yaki in
restaurants like that can I like do a
takeaway and eat it anytime or do I have
to eat it
now oh
like right now
huh okay then I don't need
it
[Music]
more okay where do we
go
[Music]
um
for what a CR what
what he's got too much defense now what
the is your
problem I'll kill you I'll kill
[Music]
you
ridiculous where some prop out cloak you
cream don't even try to touch
me ew ew ew why he got so much HP
go go go go go go go
go he's resisting everything Caleb oh my
God what the e
e that shouldn't even have any effect on
us thank you for the red
Caleb what is this I
now one more time this
one but skip this s guys takes too long
dance of GLE you
huh
[Music]
nice nice what a weird
do oh my God
[Music]
uhhuh uhhuh the city
inde gets ugli and
ug what's with that scar
what is going
on I'm just like I'm just like so
confused no
I was you know I thought this was a
serious game and it becomes less and
less serious every
minute
okay welcome to Yak that's Yak nice
this my first time playing yza game I
thought it was really like sad serious
dark I don't know
scary
what wait in some way
like in some way you're the creepy guy
s
[Music]
fore for
Fore foreign
I'm just mad because of the stupid
puns and because of that was creeps
[Music]
for
for who could that possibly be
not me no no no let me out of
[Music]
this we on the same
wayel give me money
thanks for the membership
[Music]
welcome puns are good others
suck the puns in my title of today's
stream are
A+
for
for okay okay okay
[Music]
de is this
okay
okay not loud
oh the
Colors oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my
God red for
fire
foree fore
they don't look like creeps
though chills
me oh my God my serious man
oh well fire against fire I don't know
if this really works resist is he really
resistant because of
fire wow w wow maybe we should say is
outside cat me outside how about
[Music]
that maybe this can't this is AOE
right oh no
okay bottle switch oh no oh no oh no we
need to take him
down
Qui oh that's AOE I didn't know
[Music]
nice
oh oh on the ground stop
it take this
H I don't know don't
really oh yeah give me an item by the
way
H please come on give me some
fool I got no more MP that's sad I I'll
end it with without MP I'm
[Music]
fine oh wait
no just just doing normal
attack huh you're fighting against air
huh the white
[Music]
board oh yeah let me repair your spine
I'm I'm a hero
practor oo sui red sui
monster
okay we we register some sui in our sui
deck hero
pror my back is fine thank you for
asking
got to catch them all guys want to be
the the suji Monon
Master oh my
God this is
unbelievable okay okay okay enough of
this now okay
dispatch them
all that's literally what I said okay
I'll forgive
you my is suim Master you kidding
me kidding me this game what's the
real if only I could be reor as a sexy
lady you know what I do i' could a job
gar this club right here oh my God it's
an an
girl wow UH 60 Minutes is uh 100 bucks I
don't know what they do in there though
oh wait no that's this one I guess what
he's looking at is the other one Chey
man
Jackal petty
coat I like the detail here everywhere
oh here is so
Bland
okay here right I don't know if I really
want to get in
here okay let's
go cute girl oh my those are like oh my
God I know the girl the the um
they actually use real girls here and
adverti
them heard of her okay what the
I've seen her like on Twitter I've
[Music]
this game makes so much advertisements
for like Brands and
people oh my God
should I shoot this
dude rip out one eye
huh let's rip out an
eye I feel like ripping out some
eyes women these days I'm going to
you
up
yeah yeah yeah
you are such a
piz girl is cute on the in the
background cute Kai
Ura if you guys want to look her up Yuka
Yura
[Music]
what you GNA
do rip his eye out or or something else
in in the form of a of a round
something not going to say
what I have no
mercy
fore spee
[Music]
all these
girls I'm not sure if I like this
decision from mean but
okay a group of P called uh a group of P
called bleach Japan believe they already
back the same guys as the other
day oh
yeah I've been demonstrating in front of
my shop for a few days in a row now Like
A Clockwork it's a pain in the ass you a
pain in the
ass they're specifically targeting you
with these
protests we're the last place in the
area that's open about being a bath
house the others have already branded as
men's salons or bubble massages
that makes it hard of a Bach Japan to
build a case against
them so they come after us since we
still open about being a
suland they think if they can close me
down I'll start it will start a shock
wave and clean out the rest of the
area am I lucky you would no and the
yaka would protect you theyve tried
complaining to the S Clan once thank you
for the membership welcome
they had some lame excuse and then they
showed up after everything had quieted
down besides please Chan rank ranks are
failed with the types who read up on
anti anti Yakuza laws for the fun of it
those kind of people are tough for even
the Yakuza to deal
with that's the Yakuza for
you so if I can't go to the Yakuza and I
can't go to to the police who do I turn
to even my employees according to avoid
being harassed I might end of my rope
over
here so that's why you're under
staffed but basically you're saying as
long as the girls stick around you can
still run your business that said
between bleach Japan and the way you
treat them I wouldn't count on them
sticking around
either you don't get it at all girls who
come here to work already have their
backs against the
W the guys who work here all Japanese
but they're in the same situations as an
immigrant who came here to get away from
whatever it may be using a job using a
job like this may as well be
deportation they've got no one to go
back to to or rely on I always figured
it was the money that brought girls to
this kind of
[Music]
work of course a lot of people who come
get tempted to the side of things
because it sounds lucrative but those
are the types who think they'll strike
it get rich without doing any real work
thank thank you for the
membership uh soon as things take a turn
for the worst day Run for the hills
that's why I only rely well only hire
women so far out on the ledge they can't
afford oh my
God women like that work their lives
depend on it that's why that keep
business
stable stable my ass you're just taking
advantage of women at their lowest
you're the scum of the Earth
say what you will but lust weighs on the
soul just as heavy as hunger if not more
so except with lust you can't to satiate
it at your local Deli you have to hold
it until you find an
outlet so as long as women are willing
to be on the menu men are going to be
placing orders that's the world we live
in I mean
it's
yeah
true n whatever if we drive the guy off
will you hire us or
not kasuga after everything the Slime
Bel just said you still want to work
here I certainly
don't this guy is nothing like hu the
world be better off if we let bleach
Japan take him
down shut up it's work and I can't
afford to turn that
down you shouldn't just
I'll take a job and I'll get it done
right you going to hire us or
not I don't know man I don't
know
fine thank you for the Super
Chat thank
you thank you T Pack I don't really know
any T Pack uh songs rap
songs uh prostitution is illegal in
Japan yet this establishment is flun
sorry I was too
slow working hard as ever
huh you guys from the other day I know
I'm not using my megaphone anymore but I
still want to use why are you
here oh as up today we're
employees employees
her my friends the accomplishes of
criminals the purveyors of pers ution
have made themselves
known I'm sorry criminals if that was
the case why aren't we getting
arrested because soins are dodging The
Lawns By registering themselves as
public bath
houses my friends this is what we call a
great Zone the dark stains of
Japan let us turn this gray to White we
must bleach it
out and what about you you think you're
some kind of pure clean soul yourself
never committed a single CRI
crime of course I obey the law that's
the obligation of every righteous
citizen so you never ever like taking
the wids outside that's technically a
crime you know yeah never once not in my
life
seriously what about speeding everyone's
gone over to speed limit because they
were running late nope not a single
time you liar it's illegal to go even 1
K pH over the limit you have to have
done that afraid not if you doubt me
then prove it prove I've committed these
crimes okay how about what you're doing
right now all these people blocking the
road has got to be some kind of crime
doesn't
it you're so ignorant it's
funny permit we have permits from the
canaga police for this demonst
rtion damn
it well prepared this guy do you get it
now the police has been
magn enough to let us use this road for
alur but where you standing Now isn't
technically the road it's the soap oh
that's the soap PL mhm mhm true
it's just I just got a
little also it says here that there's
only supposed to be 10 of
you I'm no mathematician but this looks
like more than
that we just got more support than usual
today that's the nature of a proest the
number of people can once it up until
the day off if you don't like it file a
police report but I wouldn't get your
hopes up about the I'm coming up to do a
head
count the difference between 10 or 15
people is wor their time and it's
certainly not causing any
trouble you're on the right track
kasuka in that case I've got a warning
for you the legal definition of a March
means you're not allowed to stop
moving if you stop and start giving
speeches that's abstracting traffic your
right to use this road as pred pred
predic prediced
and you performing a
March so the fact that you stopped here
is a pretty clear violation got
him even that's technically a rule
everybody steps to give
speeches and the police are fine with
that you know what you call that a great
oh bleed yourselves
my own arguments used against
me lying on the gray area to criticize a
great Zone man that's
irony my friends let's keep going for
Maring go let's go let's go let's go
quick quick I'm scared
momy to go no
more watch where you going o your
trip oh
h42 address is oh isn't this the one hak
run yeah we're living on the second
floor you know hak son a b from 10 years
uh years ago anyways next is you number
h41 you number you mean you're number
you're
number you mean number was your real
name this
time after that whole speech you gave me
about homeless people using fake
names shut up you believed it was fake
that's what's important you just
Goble I love that name
you okay okay and the last guy is K
who's wait AG
59 about's your problem you have a
problem with that only had two months to
go until I hit retirement but the kaga
police Let Me Go a few days ago that's
rough H that's
all what's up yeah I mean we're walking
triy triy of red flags aren't we a bum
an EXA and a cup with a dishonorable
discharge what up it if I was worried
about stuff like that I'd never find
anyone to work for me and besides I just
happen to have the perfect job for you
PR no no and that is I hope you're not
going to make us clean the baths to kick
things
off no I only get that done every 6
months oh my God what I'm really after
is I name's n her she's my top earner
for 5 years straight o that's the girl
who called to take a day off and you
blew her up at her right yeah that's
right she's your parner huh yeah you
weren't kidding about these girls being
on the uh never mind I told you if all
you've got going for you is being cute
and young You'll Never
Last the core of a so pled appeal is
service and love the emotional dep that
makes her repeat
customer emotions H I guess I could see
that men are lonely creatures when it
comes down to it every guys who put up
to toughest friends need a place to be
who they really really are at the depth
of of women's ability to give him that
is usually proportional to her own
baggage what I don't understand
sentence nanoha's father is of an age
where he can't even move on his own
anymore so she quit her job at a big
firm and fell into this world to afford
him the best of
care skipping all the stuff between a
white collar job and prostitution is a
pretty brave
leap that's why she's so good at it she
gives it everything she has no matter
who the customer is all for the sake of
her father but that being said she's
recently started finding reasons to J
take days off how can she how dare she
this never used to be this case though
thank you for the membership welcome
between bleach Japan and N are taking
days off sales are really slumping so
that's why I need a
hand a hand like on the customers oh
listen M no
you IDI I want you to look into why
she's taking time
off didn't she say herself it was
because of an
irregular irregular
period I can't take that at face Val
knowing here so you last check into a
panties no wait dude promising promising
there aren't a lot of reasons why
someone needs who needs money starts
taking a lot of time
off than she's got a side piece thanks
for the membership welcome you do know
this industry don't
you care to fill in the class oh it
means she could be meeting someone
without going for the store
ah normally a customer pays for the
service that Mone and that money gets
divided up between the girl and the shop
but if they mean in private the girl can
offer a discount but still come out on
top by cutting the shop out mhm smart
girl once they start doing that the
girls start to wonder why they need uh
the shop in the first place mhm of
course all the shops have strict rules
against that kind of
thing even if it's just an innocent
thing on first once they get a taste for
the extra cash it doesn't
stop they'll even start using the shop
to learn more customers out on their own
business it's a death nail for some
shops so I want you to find out if she's
seeing someone on the side
n why are we working working against her
I don't want to work against her I don't
want to help this
scumbag what do we do if we find the guy
make sure uh he never wants to go near
nanoha again and I don't care what
methods you use you're a Yakuza a nurse
and the cop I'm sure you free can come
up with something
creative hey hold up shouldn't you be
using the sa clan for this kind of thing
think of them like a car insurance if
you use them the wrong way they increase
your premiums thank you for the
[Music]
membership so it's cheap for if I can
solve problems
myself that's a boss for you always has
a trick or two okay can you tell us
where nanan lives for
SS actually it seems she's been C
surfing for a while and hasn't gone home
in quite some time wa how the heck do we
find her then if you keep an eye on the
pocket Cafe she'll show
up she hangs out there a for the price
of a cup of coffee she can stay for
hours to use the free Wi-Fi and charge
your phone yeah so I'll hope for the
best get her to start coming back in
regular and I'll have suitable payment
for
[Music]
you sounds to me like he hired us as
cheap cheap detectives exactly should
have hired amen
no know me as Qui as schema he seems
sloppy but he knows his employees both
on and off the clock if he's doing it on
purpose he's good doesn't mean he's not
a scum back his bottom bottom line's all
he cares about yeah I don't think so
actually uh maybe it's not true all the
time but yeah most SS Prof it up that
work as
misfortunes you mean like they're deept
or their family issues they pray on
people like like that right basically
but women work hard to get out of that
situation and the shop supports them I'm
not cool with the way nomia talks about
people but he's not sugar coating
anything either he understands the
reality of the
business well that's one way of putting
it I grew up surrounded by every kind of
SLE back Kam could throw in those doors
and I bet this guy's actually got a lot
of love for his girls I I I wouldn't
want that scumback love though
I take him any day over some
who doesn't care why the girls get jobs
during the first
place I don't I I I don't think he
really cares though but
okay well just because I hate shits
doesn't mean I have to like SLE back so
let's find this proof and get
paid all right we still I know for sure
if she's actually seeing a guy on the
side let's start with this C she
supposedly goes to
all right
okay all right all right all right all
right all right let's get the job done
guys shall we that was a lot of
story o let's fight let's fight there's
a lot of people to fight yo want to
fight let's have some
fun fashion
police wo it's the fashion
police Bob cutter oh that
hairstyle I mean it looks good on some
people oh no oh
no
oh nice one
in oh
I used the wrong skill but okay let's
look at
it oh oh car is in the way move oh come
on we had that before like a similar
[Music]
situation oh I like this
place oh there's some yummy food here
Italian
[Music]
pizza wait we can go
shopping wait wait wait wait wait wait
we can go shopping
here chicken D Soul chicken of wait sa
is sun or
salt
chicken son chicken the
sun
um yeah I don't know what would no I
wouldn't
know but I can take this uh with me
right oh my God yum oh
yummy I I Lov eating K in Japan for some
reason so
yummy how many fluffy K with
purchase wait I actually got quite a lot
of
money super spicy frankfur oh you make
me really hungry oh
man
oh 1500
po fries oh yummy yummy yummy yummy
yummy you're welcome that sounds really
yummy okay I could use some healing
right now actually but oh well well
we're going in here for what oh we can
buy something here too oh wait there's
an actual can we like buy medicine
here oh wait you can buy so much stuff
here Burns cold
symptoms paralyzed muscles cleanses your
body of
poison we can like do gardening later on
what could improve your
style for
real C attack
zero why there's so much stuff here well
we can have a guard
[Music]
what what
what there's a lot to come for
[Music]
real I'm not sure if I'm like into that
though like I I don't want to bother
with a garden God damn it please
no anyway I need to follow the pink
signs over there over
there Revenge
books will teach me how to take revenge
on
people oh my God it's all with light
sticks are you cheering for H life thank
you
w I can see how they're Restless I mean
it must be really tough watching all
those H live
streams oh my God look at the the
bades thank
you I didn't want to fight those people
they seem like good
people
man wait oh that's where I need to
go wait pocket no wait that logo looks
like not looking know
there's a cafe chain in Japan that's
called that has a like that logo but
they changed the name I guess they
didn't get a proper contract to
advertise them huh oh oh oh oh
your guitar cannot hurt
me next
[Music]
up
fire we're doing so many fights this is
fun
[Music]
what out that did a lot of damage on him
huh okay one left guys
[Music]
wa wao wo wow wow that was good
damage oh we got some more
sujon
okay is she in
here oh or is that who
are we going to act like we're wanting
her
service oh is that the dude
[Music]
fore fore spee
got this
smooth
oh very good audio
surprisingly oh she's not feeling
well might be completely different
[Music]
million well she's paying
him yeah she's getting
blackmailed
for are they like making it sound
confusing to like recr
the fact that the audio should be bad
and I don't hear
[Music]
everything okay so she's getting
blackmailed and something about her
father
and she
pays that D money for whatever
[Music]
reason they're holding him hostage you
think oh did I hurt you little baby oh
you you so
[Music]
bad I've seen them before
after oh his b are broken oh I'm so so
sorry
oh show me the bill first of all
mhm for
real do you know who you're dealing
with I'm a freaking
hero die to Dash look at
him look at
him I got no MP man help
[Music]
okay suon for him well that wait that's
like barely
anything
[Music]
n let's go with that
one oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah get into the
ground perfect guard I
sh I think you need a bigger size
t-shirt I love rice it says that's so
cute wait no no no no no
wait I want to he myself damn it oh my
God what happens if I die what happens
if I
die can I use an item on someone
else only on myself
right
right I can on someone else
ah okay nice I have this pork soup
sounds so
[Music]
yummy oh wait I got the wrong
butt oh nice
guide take those beans and
pigs don't mind I'm just feeding the
pigeons take this 66
criticality we got some more suji deex
monsters oh my God I love
that we're collecting
data
nice where is nanoha oh no we lost
her I should probably come back
now what should we do head back to the
soap plant even if we did we wouldn't
have anything to report hey oh yeah the
dude well he looks scary look at his
eyebrows oh let's follow
him yeah we got to pick the phone up
again oh they didn't do it they forgot
about
it wow the way he walks up the stairs I
don't know it looks kind of like
exhausting
oh oh he doesn't look very
nice looks kind of
scary not Qui now he looks Rich evil
yeah lives uh nicely wait it actually
says something uh something something uh
a
castle oh should I save wasn't there
automatic safe in the game
[Music]
nuring oh see is your dad in here
then can you put the scary gun away
no get used to it
only had chap
okay I'll save after this
going to ring the
bell let's see if they let us
in she sounds
nice n is probably a fake name
though
oh what is she using her real name
I didn't
know
oh well that sounds kind of shady
[Music]
I mean it looks great from the outside
but who knows what's happening
inside
oh okay uh
should I is there any anywhere where I
can heal myself close by I wonder cuz I
don't want to use up my
[Music]
items probably not and let me drink some
drinks we got to buy more of the MP ones
after all it seems like I do need them
huh kind of underestimated the M oh by
the way do we have new gear
no for him
maybe no it's all the same right okay
and for him no
okay uh and I want to save there we
go complete uh don't use our items find
the
restaurant okay yeah we got to go
somewhere else anyway right now I just
hope I won't get into fights right now I
mean my HP looks fine and the other
two have decent MP as
well Restaurant
please is this what you would call open
world
somehow cuz somehow it feels like that I
I feel like that's really
cool there must be food over
there right right right
I'm not looking at you shut
up oh wait there's the shop again is
that something soft ice
cream do I have to eat that now no MP
and HP
oh mango
pudding 50 30 30 20
pudding I mean I'm personally not a huge
fan of
pudding but I'll take
[Music]
it
okay oh there's another place here
CH Chinese food yum yum yum how do I get
it what is it here hold
it hold it was it here hold it is it not
open elephant hello
elephant I'm elephant Oh wrong but wait
what's there wait I can buy armor over
there a boie c there wait it's say toys
isn't
it cute outfits cute Chinese dresses
is all right take care out there don't
get us in trouble yummy
yummy oh wait that's hella
expensive are we ever going to have that
much
money
W everything so expensive
okay
hopefully way too expensive now so what
was uh here oh
nikan I love
nikan oh that gives oh that Shin bun 300
HP I would I would normally go for a
pizza man or a normal nikan but okay for
the sake of the HP we'll take it wait
now we're running out of money H maybe
just two of
those
okay okay
now now we're stocked
up not going to buy anymore for now also
don't really want to buy uh fight them
right
now
my okay you challenge me you challenge
me you challenge me
maybe I can get some more enemies in the
area yeah free free at
once oh perfect
guide and uh
here yes yes yes big area
hit what the
[Music]
let me try on
you what what what what what what what
no y Manion reduced to
health
mon
[Music]
there holy
holy
it wasn't that much money say it's
okay I didn't notice they were making
that much damage what the
hell
what my level is too low and why I've
been I've been I've I've been the
grinding get out of Chinatown oh am I
like in a dangerous area that I should
go to later
on not again not
again it's a high level area oh makes
[Music]
sense okay okay where do I go where do I
go isn't that chinat town too
oh wait now we're
there
here what okay from the other side I
guess oops I was just looking for
food excuse me
oh can you tell me how to get to the
station oh it's
okay can you tell me how to get to the
station no
[Music]
guy C
je come on show me your
English show me what you
got don't
worry no I mean that was
fun nice
suit can you tell me how to get to the
station you your freaking phone Google
Maps
[Music]
hello definitely paid off yeah yeah sure
sure
yeah well that's true you should be at
least able to tell someone the
way so
oh are we going to go there to learn
some
English
wow okay chill guy chill
D really excited this guy
oh cute
[Music]
girl sounds
expensive C
cutie
pie great weapon
outside good job good job
buddy yeah she doesn't seem very
interested though
uh stop laughing like that
please yeah just talk to me ignore the
other
dude let's make her full love with
each
for okay chill chill chill
chill okay
number one just like
[Music]
me
foree foreign
I like her voice it's kind of
cute why there we
go yeah let's
go this facility is all about developing
one's personality passing will improve
different sports no problem let let me
put on my sports shoes this will certify
that you have sufficient knowledge of
sports it's and its history throughout
human civilization passion plus 30
Charisma plus 30 what what does that
help me in in finding as
[Music]
well
oh this this this this this graph is
calling me a
dumbass and a pushover and lifeless
repulsive I don't know what that that
word at the bottom means but I'm tast oh
my
God have increase effectiveness of some
scales interesting let's do
it wait do I have to answer actual
questions in bing what the 10 ah pins oh
my God oh my God oh my God oh no what is
the name of the track and field event in
which athletes push a metal bar as far
into the
um what
shot put never heard of that thanks guys
basketball is a team sport where oh my
God that's a long question what
is the maximum amount of points of
player can score from one shot exploring
addition Point what what the
what what what
what go
is are you doing it on
purpose what is the turn for when the
hole is is reach Strokes below part I
don't know it's all birds why is
it not Phoenix
Eagle I don't know I don't
know I don't know guys help me help me I
shoot you Vol
okay pencils
down it better be right guys
better be
[Music]
[Applause]
right thank you everyone I am now dull
and tactless
yay wow but it's not fair that like the
questions are so long and barely give me
time to read the questions it takes up
oh we got one wrong what the
chat do you want me to shoot
you you guys have no idea what you're
talking
about that's the point they just
triggering
me oh my
God is there something test that has
nothing to do with sports please
easy easy
easy is it always the same like if I
fail and I take it again is it the same
questions are the test even worse oh
no yes okay no a pool of questions oh my
God that's really difficult
it takes money each time oh my
God I'm now enrolled at na Vocational
School
exam for
[Music]
free oh my
God someone make shut
up fun for study session need for
schooling thank you
[Music]
son but more than that money I would
prefer correct answers give me the test
ansers or I shoot
you uh is he okay in his head
okay finally he shut up oh sub story
completed I kind of want to one
more how much is oh wait but we don't
have much money right now how much does
it
cost wait I did two before
one why why did they not make me do one
before s of
proficiency wait these are all grayed
out the the tier ones a tier one T2 is
below two ah I'm the world studies maybe
Cy can help me with that Dr part decided
that are unnecessary to know about but
are nonetheless beneficial interesting
what is that
about if you have sufficient knowledge
on recent crime activity and the
antisocial forces of
Japan animal
science mammal insect
fashionist well Ena Ena could help with
that maybe we can try or or music
require listening to music in order to
correctly answer your question I want to
I want to try wait that's so expensive I
don't have the money for
that wait are they all the same what are
they all the
same oh no but they're all freaking
[Music]
expensive okay I guess that's not
happening
now that's not happening
okay uh anyway we were going to go
here no wait oh I got I don't know I got
confused we're not going
there I know Namba has a healing skill
and know he can sleep right and I guess
he has another healing skill but can I
use it outside of a battle as
well realistic studying is expensive I
guess
so hello chubby boy
in the skill oh yes you can oh
interesting wa nice
guy w w he counter
attacked wow he really has a lot of uh
defense
go
[Music]
pig my my guard was good
yay level up oh we got uh itan got
healed thanks to to level up
nice oh wait is in this are are we in
the are we in the Chinese District again
there's some some guys coming at me I'm
kind of
scared wait got 2,100 y from that
no yes leave oh God no no no no no
no no no no no can I leave level oh
no can I can I leave the fight oh
wait what what what uh no no
L1 run run run run
run me better run run run run
oh no there's e why do I have to I want
to see the big map how do I see the big
map is that like a way to see the big
map cuz I feel like I'm totally getting
lost why do I have to go
through these high level
areas select
button ah I'm here if I go here and I go
here he but then then I have to go
through that
area take a
taxi
[Music]
taxi taxi
isn't
it it's your freaking imagination don't
don't always think it's all about
you Uber
please wait is that a yeah that's a
taxi or we could just take the freaking
suine
know get
in uh
I cannot
go
okay I can't go there
anyway but that District at least is
safer how how much does it
cost I'll find more taxi spots
later okay just
walk okay
byebye but it's dangerous
okay we'll go we'll try to go down here
that way there's one enemy there maybe
we can fight
him
wait so that's sorry sorry don't mind
me be quiet
don't make
trouble uh trouble
maker down oh wait there's more enemies
there
no I can get hit by cars oh
really okay Dodge Dodge don't don't no
don't get in trouble but maybe if we can
run if we run in the right
direction o there's a lot of dudes there
maybe take this side
I that's where it came
[Music]
from why did I get so
lost
okay yum sorry yum okay
sorry
[Music]
sorry oh I took the wrong road again
H should be over
there and there we
go what o heading out flyers
[Music]
for oh
delivery something
count count I didn't even see that I
look at I only looked at the Japanese
letters
I want to eat a
[Music]
snack he's so
stupid okay
the music is nice
are you going to do it on the
street
[Music]
for oh
huh
[Music]
huh he looks like he could pound me
deliver help just going to help me
deliver some
right oh I like the accent he speaks in
Japanese why are these people always
looking for
[Applause]
[Music]
P pal are powerful allies with a wide
range of abilities but calling them cost
money the price depends on the pal meate
although your first call to each pal
meate is free oh well well well P mates
oh on duty for sure okay
let's see what I
do W the finger the finger calll
yes special
delivery I'm a ground
P
hell Serv
oh oh
yeah okay
wow
wow great service 10 out of
to open
[Laughter]
goodbye
goodbye thank you really nice getting to
know you hoping we can't be
friends it's good to have strong
friends to help me move
Apartments why weren't you here a few
days
ago the flyer is a pretty
misleading oh the
backside oh my
God you not have access to
pmates
thanks there was a cat and a chicken on
it too yeah what the hell what are they
trying to tell me
thank
you oh wait wait um uh little break uh
to get a snack and to go on a idle
meeting I'll be back for you guys
in uh two 3 minutes 1 minute
BRB ah my leg fell asleep though I can't
get up I need a p mates to carry
me oh oh it's waking up now it's waking
up yes wake up wake
up I
think I'm still ready to shoot you guys
anytime okay be
careful
e
e e
stream how Challenger yes thank you I've
been streaming it on the side but I it
feels like almost it's not counting
views or something weird so let's see if
the potato chips from the other day are
still
[Music]
good oh God cat hair everywhere again
it just went up a uh a little bit maybe
no
yeah maybe it's not not really updating
one by one but like in
chunks I
sure okay I have I think no cat hair on
no uh no cat hair on my right hand but
on my left hand I definitely
do YouTube has been weird with heart
Challenger
yep my back is fine thank you snack
time kind of want to put it in a bowl be
right
back e
hello hello Chun is you there yeah I
just saw her she woke up from a nap very
confused smoothie as
[Music]
well
okay
oh thank thank you thank you
m i i i it went by fast but I think I
got the gist of it already I'm going to
read it
properly soon but thank you I'm glad you
like the new outfit
now I see how the old one was yeah
iconic cuz everyone got used to it right
so
M weing on those um fluffy potato chips
again cuz I did not finish the bag the
other day
yes back to the
game
M playing with one hand for a
moment just came back from high chall
noce
wow holy
how much is that in USD 20 million
yen
200,000k holy wow
macaroni
fore spee
[Music]
I don't buy his
she look normal but she did say that she
her health wasn't well
the excellent
course how excellent is it
really wait sorry what does benevolence
mean thank you for the Super
Chat are you comparing me with that
dude you could me with
[Music]
him foree
fore
[Music]
spee
for eating potato
chips
for sour cream although I would normally
go for normal salt but this one is sour
cream and it's in the shape of a bear um
head
[Music]
in Japan you only do that
pose if you really really really
desperate or really really really sorry
and you really really really up
oh you think you can get a job
there you don't have such a good record
yet
[Music]
okay sounds
good
come which girl looks cute all of them
look cute
damn move I want to look at
them now
know no Tak here though
so she's cute me me is cute she got the
ice
cream cute she's cute
too they're all
cute let's
go okay where do we go where do we go
where do we go let's look at the map so
I don't get lost again um here go around
the corner and then there oh oh I can oh
I didn't know I could do
that well that makes things a bit
easier wait for a moment I thought that
was the C place but that's not possible
but let's go to the vending machine
that's not a vending machine is there no
vending
machine I want more mp uh thingy pleas
cuz I don't think I have any MP drinks
anymore I wonder if I can get bigger
ones though like
uh ones that recover a bit more than the
ones I had
before treasure
[Music]
hand okay give me something give me
something give me give me give me there
we
go these are not MP drinks
freak okay whatever we're back at Hell
work ah what about
those damn it treasure hunt go to comy I
don't know where one
is once we see one we'll
go oh come
on the blue ones
maybe is that how you differentiate five
again wooo
okay 15 10 that's like
nothing but I'll buy for
emergencies
okay so let's see if we can get a job
over there hey I'm back
doesn't matter if you want to work I
just can't invent jobs especially not
some like castle that's a friend a
retirement home with best incl
stuff they wouldn't even post openings
for hella
work so you're saying you can't get us
job
there sorry but no
Dam well I can't get you directly
employed by the S like Castle but there
might be a way as contract contractors H
ho ho
the full-time staff doesn't do a lot of
demial jobs the caretakers are employees
but they go for attempt Agency for the
rest it's an agency exclusively for
caretakers W so if I can get on that
list I'll be able to get into sun
Castle not even contractors are going to
get in if they have all of zero
experience
mhm that r that castle of course and she
s to unless you're hiding care take a
work oh but we still have our
number what do you mean why of course
it's him no next newse that's the kind
of experience they look for you could
get into stake Castle pretty easily
noise I used to be with the police then
how about
this you got an idea
M
mhm security
guard easy what about
him
oh wa what did ichan get
what what are we
doing is so
[Music]
cute he has this death going on
though here we
got as a security guy
is looking out of the
window how many times are you guys going
to ask me what I'm eating potato chips
potato chips potato
chips he's a cleaner
you look good in the
uniform stop stop asking what I'm e
you're
[Music]
welcome what flavor I already said that
to
thank you for your red super are you
impersonating that that weirdo in the in
the in that uh School
guys pay attention to what's going on in
the game while I shoot
you I'm not sharing any tips with you
no no way he
walks mm
can we go to the excellent
room huh
she so she's so
purple nice Style
I want her to be angry at
me I kind of like
it but I mean like because it's kind of
cute oh she made it
in I'm sorry I don't have a grandma okay
I want a grandma to be angry at me
oh the Purple
Lady fancy
grandma oh now you guys are finally
being nice to me excellent area she
doesn't want to go
in she's
why is she
scared what the are they doing with
them in
[Music]
there what what
what the
hey
guys you you late put some extra polish
on the bathrooms yeah whatever sorry I'm
doing not doing the voices right now
just too much wait where's n still
working I guess wasn't expecting you
guys to take the job seriously that said
we're going to finish find some info or
some proof pretty soon yeah I saw
something weird in the excellent room
though you got up there what was
weird hey guys I'm so tired I could just
die right here well KAS was just saying
he CAU onto something suspicious
what can you put off dying for a few
momentes I can't I know him being a baby
but can we stay until tomorrow n
cute I'm tired as and they want me
to come in early tomor real that's like
a real this is too real this old woman
just passed away so I have to do all
this crazy stuff
what oh wait oh
that that that
it's crazy to even think this but it has
to be that woman was killed in the
excellent
room the the accident room you
sure I didn't see but it has to be it
why would they kill their own
customers what def just means no more
income doesn't it yeah not
necessarily they could scam their
pension payments for
instance menion someone all dies but you
don't report the death and just keep on
going with your life yeah I guess so act
as if they're still alive oh my God hide
the body somewhere and the dead person's
pension and medical insurance payments
keep rolling are there actually people
who do
this please tell me
no you're saying that institution could
be stealing money can they do
that what
yes but they kill them on
purpose to save the back of security
the
natural diffs okay and they yeah
okay I would think so if anything they
would just wait and then not report it
but that's still oh my God that's
horrible thank you for the red super
chat do attack thank you if they have
that stuff on hand it's super easy to
get that money and if Swan dies it frees
up the room for the next
sucker every time a patient dies they
increase profits
so that's why she can't see her uh dad
Grandpa dad because he's already dead
that's why they won't let him see let
her see
him oh my
God so she pays a lot of money for him
to have a nice like place to stay in and
then they kill him and she keeps on
continuing paying because they lied to
her my head hurts it's really
dark should
I should I
know I remember them because they used
to combine haris my girls all the time
but about 4 years ago they got their
hands into another business and another
family took over my place
I've heard of Yakuza running a security
company as a front before but I've never
heard of them actually being on site
themselves wait what if son like ccel
itself is the Sero Clan's
business
o in that case it would make perfect
sense for them to be scamming
pensions okay say there doing this whole
pension scheme wouldn't that mean
nanoha's Dad is long dead yeah yeah n's
dad is alive o how do you know remember
what n son said when she gave the guy 2
million Ken you mean when we were e
dropping on with the phone you the guy
who took the money said something along
the lines
of ah they're still waiting for the rest
of the money so but they could still
like say he's alive and just wait for
the money and but in reality he's dead
they could still do that just wait for
the
[Music]
money well if she does if she doesn't
pay it they'll execute
him they're probably saying if she
doesn't want him to die then she needs
to pay up what the they even tell
her that that's going to happen happen
they're quite open about it huh why
doesn't she go to the police oops ah
because she's a prostitute I dropped the
Pato
ship like they wouldn't she didn't she
wouldn't need to tell the police that
[Music]
right rip potato pre second rule no was
too lazy too lazy pay up or he dies and
even if he dies the police they just
going to look the other
way police what the
and then they'll bleed his P
pension payments dry it's
Unthinkable hold on how many days ago
did you hear that conversation oh
10 it's already been 10 days
how if I just is going to be killed
tomorrow oh my God
fre million no way nanoha could scrape
that together in the state she's
in I would lend it to her if I could but
that's not the kind of money I have just
lying around oh really you
don't even if you did pay these arakas
out they could double cross you in a
heartbeat yeah it's down to the wire
then we have to save him no matter what
Jakes yeah hero
time my dad's probably in the excellent
room let's do
it don't worry ichang gets turned on by
this kind of stuff when he gets to be
the hero he loves
that
uhhuh if they fill the house everybody
gets a bonus fill the house with what
men oh
God if everyone gets a bonus everyone
from the latest to the staff goes home
happy
[Music]
yay how big is it
usually oh so your plan is to make to
get customers in here to get the money
and then pay
them I'll have it stuffed and ready for
when you get back so you better come
back alive what what what what
what I thought we were just going to
force our way into the thingy in the
retirement
home let's get some rest
okay side trip on the way where
too a place I used to freak in bar
District you can drink and
S yes
did I
hear oh-huh
uhhuh MH
mhm can I sing
too I hope the songs that
know okay
no from rips to Canes we got it all come
to love magic for all your adult weapon
needs
okay
um might be wor swinging bye
ha
okay um I guess we're going to use those
things for a different purpose then it
is intended to be used for anyway oops
uh
where are we
going here that's so far
away all right I mean I guess we could
maybe let's see where where the taxi
takes
us seems expensive
though ah let's walk probably too
expensive let's go
but after I use a taxi once can I use
fast
travel
what running is
cheaper I
can oh but then I wouldn't want to use
it for such a long distance but like
rather a short
distance okay let's see
we oh it makes no sense now okay next
time next time next
time
uh yeah that's
safe why can't we take a freaking
bike run run run run run run run
run oh oh you have to pay money for
using the taxi uh like for using the
Fast Travel as
well I was about to say
um
sorry we might get healed at the K
though
no
wh bam thank you ma'am
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no I'm
busy and I'm a bit Hurt
No okay they're on low level somewhat
so let's do this
K come to my
rescue oh wow
[Music]
65 okay uh what
here can I talk to the driver to add a
new taxes ah oh okay I just talk to them
but I don't have to use that them right
I Sor I got a hiccup
okay I see I see I
see oh we've reached this spot surv Jazz
andn oh nice I like how to built the bar
around them
piano oh actually it's really
chill yeah play it SE
phone W I love the atmosphere I don't go
to bars but this is
nice
hello nice atmosphere
[Music]
uh don't make it sound like he has no
friends that's
sad
fore foree
[Music]
thank
you
son it's Rob
son seems always tired
oh this is so sweet come on what a bro
[Music]
man if loading
oh okay but kind
okay they get alcohol coino disco Queen
C I could use some tunes which city
should I
play oh
[Music]
oh it's a banger
holy this is
[Music]
good I wonder about the DMC is this a
song originally made for the game
[Music]
oh my God yes okay then it should be
fun oh my God that's a great song where
how do I sing kok
though oh why you why you stop the music
please don't stop the music music
music kasuka you're drunk already I can
keep what says you your tab doesn't
exactly look like it can keep going come
on don't be a n should I throw some back
with I what drink links Ding and
fighting your companion will feel your
bond
go you just saying yeah well
that that's something else I always like
a full
moment fine
sh he's just enjoyed the atmosphere and
the
lady
uh well I don't know they all sound like
I don't
know whatever
each can
make on his
[Music]
own why is
that wait why why can I make a smoothie
but not an not alcohol for
myself need a permit but what if I'm
only making it for myself what the
dangerous I guess
so okay I guess if I don't really have a
like a permit like a license then I
could make something that's like too
dangerous and like poisonous right I
guess they for that they don't want that
and also I guess like if you illegally
make too much and sell
it and you could like kill people with
that as well okay okay okay okay okay
okay
okay I see okay
by the way the pancakes I made today
were not like like the The Fluffy
American style pancakes but I made um
Australian style pancakes the thn ones
that we roll up almost like a crab but a
bit thicker than a crab and I put in
Nutella which is a chocolate spread and
strawberries and not strawberries and
raspberries and
blueberries it was yummy yummy
yummy but it was weird when I opened the
the egg box
thingy the moment I opened it kind of
like one egg ripped itself
apart cuz it was stuck on both the
bottom and the top part of the box and
when I opened it that one egg opened
itself was weird I never saw
something like that I tried to I tried
to get out the eggshell but it was so
stuck to the to the cardboard
thing I couldn't
not taking eggs no not taking
eggs dragon
eggs a phoenix eats dragon eggs for
breakfast no no no the
EG the ner from Game of
Thrones don't write that lore down don't
write it down that let's not make that
lore let's sayeg
spee
fore spee
one more
round namb is just sleeping huh can I
not like talk with
him KAS feels is born and with alachi
grow stronger alachi will now gain more
experience when he is not in the active
party
[Music]
now I unlocked in revisit okay
I feel like I have a cat hair in my
fro
Apple just fulfilling my role as a cat
now yeah
let's
R sound like Castle let's go but no can
I go back now is it
[Music]
closed wait okay
so uh where are we going where are we
going I'm blind I don't see it oh it's
all the way up here dear Lord okay we're
going through some unknown District
[Music]
okay okay getting some some text
messages that I don't care about wait we
can do cans we can do cans we can go k
can I it's open okay let's do the cans
first I just feel like doing that now oh
we can do hard now but I don't feel I'm
ready for it let's do one of
medium 3 two one go okay let's go
right that was
early oh it's no one no no no no you
suck okay oh there a big one
give me that give me that give me
that cat hair on my
nose cat hair
everywhere oh
[Music]
it
speech I got another one how much time
okay get him
get off of my
nose
nose wait wait wait where am I oh
here we still got enough
time oh give me that give me that give
me that give me that give me that give
me that give me that
yes
okay let's go slowly back to the go
we're doing way better than
before it
I could I can only have one at once okay
go going back going back someone who
wants to bump into
me
[Music]
no not that was my fault wait there but
we still have time we still have
time okay turn around turn around turn
around
hi run run run run run run run
run oh I almost got
400 oh well
okay
nice that was so close to
400 I wonder if we could have had like
an even better rank starting from
400 b yeah it was probably a after 400
check the shop of the candle okay okay
okay
woo I'm getting really good at this oh
yeah yeah what I was
saying take this this to celebrate
leveling up thank
you e point oh yeah I got so many eag
points W in bonus the game I played back
when I had place of my own PL
okay
so my people tell me I need to talk to
you oh I could do it again oh I thought
I could only do it once per day for some
reason are you kidding me 500 yen for
7,500
points I am going
to oh wait they got close to
look at this we got a
TV can I like decorate my apartment at
some
point I can buy
CDs I can buy o why would I buy
those oh o but I'm a hero I don't need
those
[Music]
books oh but that's look quite expensive
Persona 5
soundtrack High pay
token slot machine to the high P
here 50
MP not hold I don't I'm not sure what to
get oh I'll save up some
more
actually okay wait you guys told me I
can go to the C wait what was it again
here
survive okay it's quite far away but
let's go wait did I ever talk to the
taxi I think I
did happy birthday little
boy if it's on a map you did ah
okay what is this sub
Quest
[Music]
for his name
is
you oh I
run oh he dropped his little tissue
thingy sh
okay well no but but I got to go k to be
honest I Wrong
Way
K
yummy you want to
fight you look weak as
hell I'm hry hungry homeless well why
are they so far
away run bunk
BK oh that was weak
damn all right all right all
right
a can I get him
too no the one on the right side
unfortunately
not oh
[Music]
okay now moving on
anyway I need better weapons adult shop
has some good stuff the the adult shop
has some good stuff huh how do you know
is that a comy oh wait it's a
comany comy
[Music]
please uh we want something for
MP
o stuff is cheap here isn't
it not
e oh s how much thousand yen dear
Lord 3,000 and 400 F and 400 are you
kidding
me
[Music]
okay let's go for the cup
socket I guess 300 50 yeah yeah yeah
yeah that would be the cheapest
[Music]
option
and so we can get one of uh
those
byebye I don't really like Nat but okay
got to deal with what you get uh that
way okay seriously adoring the outfit
and ears thank you me too thank
you so happy to hear that you guys like
it shut up guys by the way about
tomorrow the read broadcast um I'm not
100% sure yet if it's really happening
tomorrow uh because I wanted to go with
my friend to
uh to do like uh some shopping for my
apartment and I chose a time that would
be like in the middle of the day for
me I'll try to figure something out cuz
I kind of have to be home to click the
start button you know I I'll I'll f
think about it maybe an hour
later okay so how do I do K again
here
o 500 yen
guys
what oh I have to use a controller to to
okay okay
what oh what I have to remember which
one is
where no
what how do
I how do I get out of
this this a r game where you press input
[Music]
okay
okay what how do I
exit
oh oh s it looks exactly like the the
the actual interface in Japan for joy
sound
K oh
sing it's bakam but wait will not get
like DNC from this I don't know bakam
might be fine
huh okay we'll risk it
[Music]
guys I've heard this many
times
okay I don't know where the things are
by
heart I always have to look at my
controller
[Music]
my second ribbon
game oh
[Music]
oh wait I got it
oh missed
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't even know the the
song oh wait where oh
oh a
yeah are you going for the second round
[Music]
oh no we're not going for it
okay
oh what a beautiful
singing who are these
people who are these people in the
ranking oh now I feel like learning the
song and singing it in in kok
stream all right now that we did that
we're
leaving we did it guys we have done it
uh
oopsie wait actually you know what let
me let me
save hope you enjoyed that guys
so actually getting we're closer uh we
actually didn't even go that like far
off our actual path I hope this area is
not too dangerous though cuz we haven't
really walked through here before so I
have a my feeling ah level 10 okay
that's still fine
excuse me please
no nice swing the bat swing
it let's try this
one wa aen
face uh
no just attack normally you can do it
[Music]
it's you should try hitting those extra
triangle and square buttons and
skills I've hit it a a lot of
times what are you talking about
yeah I've been hitting them a lot of
times I've been hitting it all the
time of course it's
working yeah maybe not always at the
first time cuz I don't know it by heart
but I do HTE it at least at the second
time when it Grumps
me what's your
problem in any case I'm very much aware
of
it oh we burnt him
alive let's go at
him or does it have to be a certain
timing
I mean like like a ribon game like
really the perfect diamond I mean I'm
trying really I'm
trying
f i no
[Music]
no
Run come
on she hitting it again what do you mean
[Music]
yeah that one was Button
smash you
what do you want what do you want huh oh
my God
wait yeah B I know I can hear myself too
but I don't know
[Music]
Dam
uhoh ah good that I healed him before
otherwise he would be dead by
now we're right at the station where is
the freaking security
oh my
God theyy got that's real good
okay
uh okay now we're doing fine again let's
go oh where's my path a I lost
it there we go
got to grind the Dragon Quest yeah
what's with her side quest I don't
really want to do that one
now let's see if we can
save the
Dead Oh treasure H bronze blade what is
what can I do with that 500 e
let's drink some water everyone
hydration
time okay okay okay okay
okay and that
way almost
there almost there
that way ah there it is that's it
right wait what isn't it oh taxi it's a
taxi taxi taxi
[Music]
leave me
alone I'm
busy who hurt you
tel the Yakuza the Yakuza hurt
[Music]
me does she know what's going on in this
place I'm guessing no
uhoh is
that hi
hi oopsy that was totally not on purpose
right he going to get mad
take it take it take
it surprised that that dude isn't more
like like the moment when he drops his
stuff like more like oh my God yeah bu
and like instantly tries to put it back
together because he knows he is carrying
some Yi stuff with
him
oh is that
him we got to save
him
oop for
so did she pay or
not so you think you're doing something
good or what
[Music]
oh give it to him kill him rip his hide
out and his lungs and his stomach and
his vowels
everything I'm
the even
are you guys surprised
H we're here for justice
[Music]
now he's got a te Tas te Tas
fore we'll see about that
okay let's
go
[Music]
mhm this is I love this
whole I don't know I I love
this I love how exaggerate they
how how much I exaggerate
everything
[Music]
okay B
beaches now they're like not so close
together anymore
so ah
come at me
bro where my perfect God
uh let's make him gone
ni now we recover
be don't underestimate pigeons
[Music]
thank you death
bites they're from the streets okay the
pigeons here from the streets they know
what's
[Music]
up
for
potassium
fore foree
oh petrick don't worry I just snapped
those idiot yakuza's neck
we look like a funny gangor
[Music]
eyebrows yeah that's just weak as hell
foree
[Music]
for S CL oh that was way too fast
Justice it's time for Justice
holy
what do you call that roundhouse I
don't know not familiar with these
things oh I should have gotten
MP damn
[Music]
it I see that one
IND
pigeons see I tried to I understand not
what you guys mean but I've been always
pushing it I just didn't realize that it
had to be dad
exct on him
you're
welcome still drunk oh wait oh that's
why that was cheaper wait does it
actually have an effect on on me
attacking them
oh oh
oh wow wait oh he just does whatever oh
I can't control him okay well it
actually might maybe it makes him
stronger actually maybe this actually
the other way
around I wait no I wanted to n I I
wanted to heal
uh uh
namb I got confused
maybe we should focus on one
[Music]
enemy who who
w Wait
um yeah use it on myself
pleas okay
uh we might want to use an item
though
[Music]
50 all right I'll lose
that oh wait thought he's also
drunk five perfect gued once at least
[Music]
okay difficult very difficult
let's try to get TOA
[Music]
down the N heal him more
okay burn his eyebrows off
oh top guy down okay
nice okay
um do you think we should take a um heal
again yeah
maybe okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay okay ah now we got damage plus I've
been matching it all along but I guess
it wasn't
enough wa BV
guide okay there we go wait is there
another one ah yeah there's still one
more got like quite a lot of
HP let's do this
a bit more a bit more Jus come
on has no
[Music]
mercy
nice level up rank
we need the card
dude blow it up blow it
up oh yeah go ahead and call the police
okay sure do
it
foree
spe foree
oh why why would why would the chairman
do that
though isn't the chairman on on his
side on that dude side
totka
fore scared
I but I I can't imagine like Yakuza like
his his boss actually being against what
he's doing even even if he doesn't know
about it like they do bad stuff and all
that so isn't that like kind of like
what what he likes to do the chairman as
well wouldn't he be like hey good job
you've been doing all of
this they have on
do
they okay that would be
nice W that's a hell of a
gate this place has that Yakuza HQ
feeling down can't hurt to be cautious
let's make sure we're really good to go
then okay hey you wait right here a
little little yeah I'm probably not
ready I would need some items
maybe maybe
maybe weapons lying
around wait why is there something
marked on the map is that still the mark
from
before yeah it is
right uh where is that you think we can
buy something at that adult shop where
is
that uh what's that purple a here J no
not that one not that one maybe that one
hustle Boutique hustle
Boutique
uh next to
me
oh
nice good good
placement is it expensive okay L's
really can't run straight it
seems can I have a made outfit too it's
cute oh rugged cane is that stronger
than what I have can equip ah
number shoor
for that would be for
me h plus
33 oh plus 6 plus
22 so it might be worth it to buy the
pipe and the
shoehorn oh wait but there's other stuff
too sexy microphone
let's buy one of
those equip okay
oh and
then oh uh uh yeah I can still afford
this
one up the defense of your healer with
like actual
[Music]
clothes we could get that for him 11
yeah
probably or wait we have uh 5,000 y left
that one cost 3,900
h a bit broke can I sell
things where we
go do some more cans or whatever I don't
know uh
so that's for you uh that that's for
you sell stuff at the pawn shop unlock
pawn
shop where's the pwn
sh
pinky side quest M you think we really
need to get that prepared that prepped
up for
this you have to do the quest and look
at uhhuh
uhhuh
well can let's let's go to the can Quest
even though it really doesn't give me
that much money at
all but you got to do what
again no no no no you want to fight you
know what let's
[Music]
fight also it would be good if we could
sleep once somewhere you guys want to
come over here maybe
yeah I got no what are you
wearing I got no MP
[Music]
I got a new
skill oh that does a lot of damage and
stuns
nice are you for
real how
pathetic
sck may leave them
enraged don't know if that's good
[Music]
kill
him but he's so
creepy so
[Music]
creepy so wet
okay one more to go level 9 that's like
[Music]
nothing hi CH out yeah it's really
close really really close
now if if we're realistic everyone who's
watching the stream right now should
just watch our challenge of once and
then actually it should go to 1
million please guys please
guys here URL go everyone who's not been
streaming it the whole time do it
now
know it's a bit more
way
overdue Y what you
got oh way too
expensive bye I want to go to the
Cs 1.5
1.5
oh and looping it from the start
thank you so
much for all the support
guys threatening man you're not
threatening to me at all
[Music]
one hit guys did you see
that oh wait by the way what happened
with these guys I didn't find him
yet the
boy
no you D's handkerchief I'm G you I'll
give it to him when I see
him shakun is a good kid I saw him the
river fairly often so I tried to talk to
him and to my surprise he was willing to
stick around oh boy here we oh boy here
we go before long shun would start
telling me what happened at school and
I'd tell him stories about the good old
days that right so why you wanted to get
him a present the long and short of it
anyway to tell the truth I have a son
about shun's age whenever I look at him
I can't help but see my son I wasn't
able to do anything remotely parent
likee at the time before my boy and it's
not exactly atonement but I figured I
could try and do something for
short right that's not a bad thing
wanted to do something like that just
don't go overboard if you do
[Music]
yeah okay
hey still not over with that Quest I
guess
okay back with the
cans I'm
feeling
canting Rebel chicken what the if
you if you don't what high Challenger
now I'm going to shoot you Rebel chicken
I am going to shoot you in your forehead
head
shot understand
understand I think we understand each
other let's go hard
mode
yes it
oh okay right and left and
right that was
close 300 is
minimum ah wait back
yum okay
go go go go
go two and a half minutes left no
problem no problem absolutely no problem
mountain of
KS oh he bned himself
to just chilling you're just
vibing you want to fight
yeah yeah
uh-oh
[Music]
y we still have time we still have time
we'll get back at him oh there's one
nice that's what I
need okay okay okay
[Music]
okay now we might want to go
back oh yeah
oh no no no no no are they following me
no I still have 1
[Music]
minute good lucky
go
[Music]
come I
can okay okay okay okay a the the me all
time I ready to the
go wait wait
[Music]
wait wait wait go back go back go
back no I want give me
that I want 500
go
[Music]
go going back was really
difficult
okay I want to I want to get I want to
do it
again again
we can get a rank we can do
it
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
okay I was
doing going to you he up next time
I see
you
[Applause]
uh-oh I'll kill you
[Music]
can I restart please this didn't go as
planned where am
I okay okay
two you
f okay I'm getting a lot a lot of hits
oh my God that was so close the moment I
got it I activated it that was so
close oh
uhoh someone's coming at
me you
go they're going to get
[Music]
me this is so
bad no no no no no oh nice
Dodge okay
okay let's go to the
goal I want to do it
again I want to do it
[Music]
again I want
500 I want
500 I want 500
I cannot accept this
outcome I did the wrong
wck
[Music]
ah okay okay come on this time this
time okay I cannot exactly I canot
accept
[Music]
[Applause]
it mhm I I question my choices is
low where am I I need
to oh thank
[Music]
[Applause]
God and straight to the next
[Music]
one okay
I would need an energy drink for me
again
please there's one there there's one
there there's one
[Applause]
there that was a weird
lag oh someone's following
me following me
there's one there there's one there no
one's following me
now
okay here Here Comes one and another one
yeah we got
500 and we still got minute
though oh M where is she I see her
uhoh the other dude's
[Music]
[Applause]
coming okay we should probably try to
get home now I got 50 seconds left
that's
[Music]
[Applause]
okay let
go it's got to make it home
safely
675 I could have even gone for 700
look at this
[Music]
mountain
yes recycling at its
best
a
wo yes yes that's what I'm talking
about so
you rank up mhm
[Music]
H
mhm who what you going to give me W oh
nice we have 34,000
points okay maybe now we can buy
something
nice oh no no no no no no no no no
no no no
no sorry I pushed the wrong
thing I I P the wrong thing again
I'm pushing all the wrong
buttons okay uh let's see 34 that's a
lot holy do we have
like something we could use as a weapon
or here shoes should I buy those shoes
it's only plus one plus two
ear like
gear m
it's it's it really barely it's not
really worth it in my
[Music]
opinion plus three maybe that
one yeah you know I'm going to yeah
going to get that can I buy another
one a hat for everyone a straw hat just
like
mine
okay and we still got a lot of okay yeah
we got so many points we can afford it
huh
okay okay
and I would have done that oh that would
have been better
okay shoes oh wait plus two oh but
this these ones have magic and
Agility those ones for number
maybe the short gave deck too oh yeah
true who else should we give those to
the SCU
chanels maybe everyone but but I mean
magic is only really used by number
right but
agility
agility lever is better for the others
okay you get those shoes what are
those what are
those okay oh wait that's
a for
who I don't think anyone was able to use
that oh wait uh still want to use some
points on some foood
14,000 points left let's get
uh
these and
these thank
you now uh I think we're ready what do
you guys
think what do you guys think h
but I would also like to sleep here I
guess wait where is
that yeah heal at the camp
yeah healing and
saving nice that they still let me sleep
here recovering while
tripping
okay
maybe one more stop at the company see
what they have
again what we need
cuz we have
something we have a lot for HP but we we
barely have stuff for the for
MP I would like to have something for MP
maybe something that doesn't make me Dr
drunk but these are just
15 and this one makes me really it's is
is getting drunk like a really bad thing
for the
[Music]
fight oh I can deposit money Ah that's
smart for the case when I die
huh depends you can't control them
me give Sal this
Ste okay generally no
but okay
H let's buy one huh and
[Music]
uh
okay thank you
[Music]
byebye
saving well we're already at chapter 4
huh when we're probably closing that
chapter we started out in like chapter 2
today I think
so what where is it why wasn't it down
here
yeah
okay let's go don't run into the car I
it it I
it was in the middle of traffic oh don't
really want to fight these guys now I
want to keep my HP and my mp let me go
over that
bridge oh wait no that makes no
sense a come on
oh by the way can I have
some that's free I love it wait where
where I need to go to sleep
again one more D want to I want to keep
my
himp m
oh
okay don't forget to treasure hunt every
once in a while who knows maybe maybe
suddenly I find a lottery
ticket I used one
probably
no nice
Dodge oh it's that place
like I said before this is my
merchandise not for this trash but it's
spilling out from your property sure you
can't mean I Che you never heard of a
little thing called roadside business
loads of places have flags and signs
outside you got a problem with those
H I just wish that people from the
welfare office would treat me like they
do everyone else thank you Lonnie thank
you soon for believe me you will be
beautiful when you grow
up you're already beautiful now hey wait
we're still not done
talking that's the owner of that pawn
shop ah the one I wanted to unlock huh M
[Music]
mhm oh so he owns a dump
huh excuse me but who are you I'm Kasa
and I'm kind of new in town sounds like
the neighbors are pretty up in arms
about this place KAS so you Kasa son
you've heard of me indeed I've heard
rumors about you from many of the city's
homeless ohoo I'm famous talk of a huge
new guy on the scene named kasuga with
even bigger hair I'm actually with
welfare services so I have a lot of
connections with the homeless mhm oh wow
I never thought I'd get to meet you
oh that is a reaction that I like to
hear I guess I'm making an name for
myself here too bad it's for all the
wrong reasons I'm condo I work for the
public Division of Welfare Division of
Welfare sounds like you have a lot on
your hands well that's the nature of a
job still this place has been a real for
on my side you're saying it's a pawn
shop right correct do you want to G
son his his name is gie that's trash in
Japanese keep saying the trash is all
his merchandise which well sorry that's
said it was indeed a pawn shop at one
point but after his wife passed away he
became somewhat of a recluse and the
shop turned into the trash he you see
today I don't know the names in in
Yakuza though it's also
obvious I like how all of the a lot of
these things are up it's just like sh
shun he refuses to listen to the word I
say so now I'm clouded between angry
hoarder and an angry
neighborhood man I mean even I'm
starting to feel bad
thank you for the Super Chat
than say maybe you could try reaching
out to him
KAS I'm sure by now guman has has had
enough of me or the neighborhood folks
pastoring him I'm thinking maybe if a
new more intimidating face gives it to
him straight he might finally get the
picture you sure about that at this
point I think throwing him a curve balls
best bet I even rev you for it so could
you please help for the sake of the
city of
course okay I'll help sooning as you've
got your hands
full uh I get G right away okay is he in
there
what is it
now it's got of cute
hat cute
scarf who are you you look like a
Yakuza oh I see so even the welfare
offic is in their pocket is that it well
I'm not sure what you're getting at this
is kasan he just recently moved in he
want to express his feelings about the
state of your
shop I'll bit come on that guy's yaku
are through and
fr I'm no Yakuza I'm just never a
citizen like you so oh tell me you ever
think about cleaning all this crap up
it's not crap it's a pwn shop and that
is all respectable merchandise I'm not
getting rid of it
mhm doesn't look like he's too big on
changing his
[Music]
tune wait
I'll have clean
too come on don't be like that I'll even
help you clean up they say newspaper is
good for cleaning
windows like I give a damn this shop is
perfectly fine as it is now leave me
alone hey I got kind this
up I thought that would work he's
that set on leaving it the way it is I'm
afraid we're done talking you
can't see say I didn't see this coming
this is usually the part where I get
chased off yeah nah I don't think he's
looking to chase
us you want us to
fight
okay Maj he wants to fight
aaka thank you guys for the Super Chat
thank you thank you thank
you okay it's free versus W wonder I
feel a bit uh sorry wait we're not going
to use any mp on this
idiot there we
go level up
noise go go go go go go
go damn it hey so how about you think
about
dumping all this trash oh wait they
talking
[Music]
oh for
for
[Music]
fore
for
[Music]
e
for wa
scaring him with my
gun he's used to it he knows the
Yakuza
for nice we unlocked the pawn shop
guys we did
it also by the way I have my chunkies on
my in my arms right
now pting her so I can't touch the
controller keep on talking
guys
for flame amulet ooh
that amulet is perfect for me
yeah he knows
me our Challenger needs 1K to go
noise thank you
guys who can get the last view the 1
million
reveal who can get it let's make it a
challenge
wa I want to pet my baby's belly a bit
longer St my
ni I
know my
[Music]
baby my baby
baby oh there's dudes
coming my
baby my
[Music]
baby now my cat is shy she doesn't want
to speak to the to you
guys
a
baby if you're going to try to touch her
I'm going to shoot you guys that's why I
have my gun
out don't touch my cat actually to be
honest they really normally normally now
because of the new apartment they hide
whenever people come but normally um
they both both are very friendly to
strangers coming into the apartment like
with the old apartment at least now they
just have to get used to like the the
sound of the bell and people coming in
they're still very
careful but normally they really don't
mind and they let themselves be pet by
uh
guests yeah they don't mind at all
especially chunkers very friendly but as
I mentioned before like whenever you
like try to touch her she runs
away but then she wants you to follow
her and then try again to touch her she
does that all the time and then smoovie
is
uh just normal I guess towards
strangers okay baby left chat
let's go uh follow oh can we not
find uh wait let's run now not that
direction can I run the other direction
please oh yeah okay that's right okay
okay okay okay okay I want to get there
with full HP if possible but we probably
have to fight some smaller dudes anyway
right we're not going to get straight to
the
boss I
suppose we're probably not going to be
full HP at that point
anyway there we
are safe one more time thank you for the
membership welcome I hope you're going
to enjoy your membership you you just
joined in time cuz I'm the the one that
I the the membership only unarchived kok
stream that I did yesterday I will
rebroadcast it I'm gonna inform you guys
as soon as I know more
details I don't understand why tosuka is
like cooperating
now what do you think will happen to my
reputation work with me here looks like
this isn't someone's bugging behind me
oh he's doing a work
out H it's going isn't going anywhere
until I at least put on some
armor oh I didn't put it on okay well
the game actually wants me to put it on
wait oh wait I need I need
accessories oh I do have some ah
okay I have the flame amulet does
everyone need
one
H I'm going to give him this
one I need one more
[Music]
maybe oh yeah now we can go
in
okay even though number has nothing
on oh what a
beautiful house the
pretty I like the
Colors
oh okay nice welcoming party
[Music]
eliminated thank you for renewing your
membership than
[Music]
fight round one ding ding ding ding d
d t guys underlings okay okay okay why
are we in the middle I don't like
this okay here let's just get all three
of them no why did only got one come
on God damn it
[Music]
maybe woo wait did I
hit did I hit him no he just fell down I
guess because someone bonked against
[Music]
him
oh I was about to try to dodge but he
just falls behind
[Music]
I wait no
no good
[Music]
night oh I like the the
music what do we have here
[Music]
H let's try him
yo
okay okay okay okay I don't even need
the
skills for those
daos thank you for the membership
welcome perfect
[Music]
guard
uh on him
take this I heal you oh you were healing
his crotch but
okay with the chance
woo he was yielding it as if it was
really really oh oh oh oh oh really
really uh uh
lightweighted you dude
one
more someone dead huh oh W oh oh
oh taking another nap n's just sleeping
all the time
it's you and me
dude too ear but he's dead
okay
[Music]
nice
R and here they open the
gates oh you say you want to finish me
off yourself but you're just closing the
Gates Again what are you doing thank you
for the membership
welcome how about we like climb up
there oh there's some items here
though hot stone
I would say we just climb
up oh this one's
open oh should have healed before
yum yby that's a lot of
dudes he you going to
run wait I oh I see what you're
doing oh oh I that was not it
oh oh is that going to stop them
really I always wonder if that really
was happy Mother's Day thank
you you
too
oh that it might have not been the best
idea to go in here like with Free
People think you
can take up all of these dudes they're
in the box they're in the box they're
probably in the box at least one of
them oh whybe
not
smart oh n was in the Box
okay
n h now what should we try the cor that
connects above us maybe we can get to
the Chairman's room by going up to the
left
side yeah we can give it a try that
looks like a
face I know round about but it will work
seems like the stadio clan members
unlock the doors for us
too hold up security might be tidy that
way let's see if we can enter from that
door over there
first
okay uh I I see what you mean yeah he
does look a little bit like hide Kojima
yeah
fascinating my name
uh yeah
okay
oh hello thanks for waiting for
me thanks what not the eyebrows from of
the dude of the on the on the right
side look at him right side
dude looking ridiculous my
friend W
23 go go fire fire
fire wow that doesn't do much damage
[Music]
give it to him give it to him you're
calling for back up oh come on that's
lame oh sh H that was way fast oh my God
okay two times perfect guard this is a
good
good good
ratio damn it
[Music]
damn it
for oh I I stun nice
oh
oh oh thought that was me
[Music]
attacking take him down so he doesn't
bother us
[Music]
anymore
okay 69
that made him snap his oh what the
wow that is a very very bad thing
to
do OHA is in Rage
oh come
on okay okay
okay he's the only one still think
[Music]
normally I don't really want to use up
so many MP
[Music]
for uh
you but also needs
it
h take this
[Music]
almost H oh he almost de
okay last last hit for
[Music]
him
KO it's okay it's okay we can do it
y he's still alive still
alive we can do it with the next hit
right we can do
it going in 99
that was
tough yeah oh I should have listened to
that
huh there's a little Shrine looking
thing over there
money yes money
helmet okay we can use that
though oh listen to that
again no
okay sharpness light oh thanks thanks
thanks thanks I probably need that so uh
skills uh number please help healing
powder on you and you and you and
you one more yeah uh then use
uh if I use sake outside of a battle
does it affect him in his NE in the next
[Music]
battle yeah only a little okay
and gear I guess we have a helmet now
why not use
it probably
better oh yeah okay I mean his
electricity defense goes down but the
rest goes up let's go with
it
okay wait which is that the right door
oh no that's where we came from but I
wanted to pick up those items anyway
mysterious mushroom imp pure lead what
is
that okay going back in oops
sorry
sorry oh this is like a real
Dungeon
[Music]
RPG crafting meds okay TR this isn't too
bad of a status in this game can be
easily killed with other items
H where do I go do I have a map oh I do
I need to go here huh should I check out
the other
rooms what's in
here no one no one okay
nice first a kit
yo okay that was worth
it might not be so
uh
safe in other rooms but for now also
what we have up there we can't go
there what's it that door doesn't
work
okay then I'm going up I'm going
up are
you oh we can just continue walking up
nothing
here
okay y the
music
rtic
hello I'm the new
member let's see about
that go go go on all of them please on
all of them only on come
on oh no I think it got two one one more
at around the end it got bit more
damage
okay yes oh yeah and extra damage that
was nice
sweep cleaning up
here y
go
oh that
damage
nice what's in here Ty oh nice we're
getting a small items for MP and HP I
think tyina was MP maybe not I'm not
sure
[Music]
ah let's go to the other room
first anyone here no no it's
items oh yes a string and Gau is that
also something I can heal myself
with now we got here
okay nothing
here
oh I'll be the B
H can I save
no ah to stop ah yeah we had that
before
oh
oh he looks strong can I call
like how do I call the the
dude The Ground Pounder
is that like a middle bus I
wonder yeah cuz it's only one and he
looks strong let's use my
skill it cost 10,000 Yen oh it does it
only give me the option when I actually
have the
[Music]
money oh
wow he's really strong so
join I use G
[Music]
bre how you like
that Tong
provoke as stes Fe
[Music]
what does that do though if he's if he's
scared can he not attack anymore
[Music]
maybe I we so fine was so fine
while he's on the ground it makes more
damage interesting thank you for the
info oh no oh no herculan
effort let's skip making the first move
see how go okay should I guard
[Music]
that's what you want me to
do he brought a SAA can I attck
now I'm going to do a Power na on
[Music]
him blocking is for noobs I I normally
wouldn't do it but the game told me to
kind of chill
[Music]
I always click it too early I
think the button
[Music]
for stay on your
knees stay in bed for Mercy oh
[Music]
on
him okay
T Jer have some healing powder for your
[Music]
crotch he's really strong man how
do I keep on missing
it let me see
[Music]
rest me too
much I use that than
D oh he comes again pleas charge y oh
that didn't really do much or anything
at
all let's attack
normally oh he's guarding
[Music]
he missed 600 views left nice oh I got
defeated
[Music]
nice okay we did it guys uh the half BS
is down so we should be fairly close to
the why do I not have a key oh I do
to the final balls work over
[Music]
rolls maybe for
him wait I have those
too six six ah healing wait I should
give those to
[Music]
Namba because of the
healing and then for
[Music]
this one work close and for
other this one's better too okay okay
okay we're getting some nice equipment
hello okay uh where did we come from
from here okay we go
up up we go oh it's locked
o but I came from
here almost missed that
still
there what what what is he like a
rester
wow wow
okay by the way guys my eyes are getting
pretty tired so I don't think I'll be
reading
many superch maybe only for an hour or
so
today we'll hopefully um kill the boss I
guys like get this chapter done and then
I'll read a few super
chats yeah it's been 5 and a half hours
now maybe around 6 hours we should be
done with
this come back you my
myself this is such a romance I love
this
[Music]
free but I was
G you said it does this mean we have to
climb back
up seems like it let's look for another
way okay what do we have here Rec oh
nice oh thank you thank you can I save
too
no okay
uh so but
that's I'm not looking I'm not
[Music]
looking okay okay do I have a
choice oops doesn't look like it
y I feel so strong thank you for the
Super Chat yeah I'm glad my neck is
feeling better like it's been it's what
it was my spine my neck still feels like
has some kind of blockage a little bit
but it's not that
bad but I should like tomorrow is Monday
so
[Music]
hopefully hopefully
tomorrow or the day after tomorrow I
I'll get um contacted the confirmation
for my insurance and then I'll start
like making appointments for
doctors got to take care of myself a
little bit
better what did you do to help respa I
just waited and did like you know I told
you I did the the I took a hot bath and
and oh nice and massaged with that
machine that I have but that didn't
really do it but I waited like two more
days and now it's okay it just it took
it took three four
days kind of
tough yeah thanks guys yeah I have like
a a thing for the like a massage thingy
for the shoulders I have had that since
like a long time time since I always
have issues with my
shoulders I use it when I'm like really
like desperate for
some
massages but in Jaan I would normally
just go get an actual massage instead
because it's much cheaper which one
should I go first you it's much cheaper
in
Japan then oh okay then here it's easier
to get cuz there's so many massage
places in Japan desperation massage
yep another one he also looks kind of
serious I like these Japanese star rooms
here
[Music]
stop crying you little
babies okay with that attack I should
always try to like get the front man if
someone's behind him then it's
nice yeah that would work well when
they're so spread
out s
let's use that let's have some
fun oh that actually didn't do that much
[Music]
damage let's use my magic skills a bit
more by the way next week is it next
week or the week after I think next
attack Rose oh next week is uh the
Diggy comei digy
comei it's a German one so we normally
would pronounce it Diggy Comey i'
say yeah we have a healing station
pretty close
true we should just let it all
[Music]
out I still don't really know what
exactly will
happen but I hope you guys will put me
and then take a look at
[Music]
it give me an
item let's see if he gives me something
please come on
oh he missed he's scaring up for
something Big
[Music]
Y BL you speak
[Applause]
German as
bom okay there we
go let's go back to heal
again did everyone just level up then we
don't need to heal do
[Music]
we thisy go to maybe the iron is along
the
corridor wait which which one the one I
could open I
guess I think I know which
one yeah see we're healed fully okay you
guys are posing with the samurai
clothing let's do
a there was no door here ah no there was
let's check that that small room out
before we go they mes on items I smell
it and of course it's safe as well
mysterious
Stone what do we got in
[Music]
here is just I don't like that that
that's so
annoying oh R chain
mail in this day and
age okay what did I buy all this see
they make me buy all this gear make me
spend all my money to actually get
inside and now they give me all this
gear for
free what wait
is oh oh it's an
accessory nice
noce I keep on getting stronger and
stronger what do I do with all this
power that
cosplayers yeah I would say
so let's see if this key
works of course use what the hell why
would I not use
it h it worked what do we got here oh
some
plans hey
yeah there's a small key there too it's
some sort of blueprint for this facility
that's interesting there's a ladder icon
at the edge
here
oh looks like it connects with the room
where we found the key but I don't
remember seeing a door H maybe it's like
under the
tatami this building is a glad and
Fortress so hitting bage wouldn't even
surprise
me okay nice information h grenade
y savey shoes holy there so many
items um maybe
him oh wait it's actual
shoes oh Magic and the
guilty ooh wait what shoeses number
wearing scuff
sandals okay
okay oh I said pachan you guys make fun
of me when I say that don't
you
um of course we do oh here is like
hidden there okay smart
kasuga you got to look behind the
obvious a
button oh come on
that's that's actually quite
noticeable press it press it press it
make it go
boom we should use the armor too ooh
hidden
room okay thanks old
Samurai
items yes diry
Lumber I can't believe we'll actually be
crafting in this game later this is
quite the
RPG okay nothing
else not hold oh wait we can go up and
down uh for now well I guess down
first oh cuz I reckon there's going to
be some some items
here up we have more
enemies that's my RPG logic yep and I
was
right I am right
jacket smart
[Music]
Ki jacket for
who a actually I don't like Dragon I
don't think anyone needs it you got now
nothing else here
right stream challer 200 more
views post it on
Twitter post it on Twitter guys make it
go faster why did you just go down
there come up with me no ridning
away Y open that how oh so many items
nice nice nice
luxury and enough safe what the hell I'm
surprised I have even so many
keys Health
ring we're getting really buff
here silver save are free silver saves
oh golden saves
need uh-huh uhuh I one key fit so
oh looks familiar to me though that's
where we fight fought that one big
guy but maybe it just looks the same
to confuse us oh they got Bond
extra what
it is it or is it not the same room
anyway I'm going to yeah it
is I'm going for that
door I can drink of n now
oh were we not here
before wait
what oh
what I didn't know I had stuff in
here okay probably don't need it though
and also don't really need need a heal
either oh okay for bleeding something
here oh
yes is it boss time oh oh that makes
sense I
guess that makes sense which door which
door which door here this one okay let's
go let's go let's go let's go I'm
ready which
way up there but is there an item
here
yes always think that you're in an RPG
in this game mysterious carrot sorry
about the plans
dude funny
let's go this looks
beautiful oh
tosuka you freaking
rat you're such a pain in the ass we
just want to see the chairman out of the
way you made it this far
wait you made it this far and that's far
enough oh oh those boys
again they still standing up to all
that ah long no see this time will'll be
different they're free of us to give our
un
stoppable yeah they all three of them
that is Unstoppable TR against un Trail
come on
N oh y are they at least already
weakened or something I mean we got
better
armor than before at least at least a
little
bit you okay okay okay
y ah use it is it at him now now he
moved should move
[Music]
what do we do what do we do
uh let's do
[Music]
that we should throw the hand I haven't
been using uh like weapon items for a
while oh you healed him how many time
please tell me they only do that like
once per
[Music]
fight yeah oh that didn't even do that
much damage but okay
got to get rid of the Healer oh
okay I guess
so wait which one was the Healer the Ida
guy
right he's doing it
again okay okay full
power full power towards this
I'm going to stick this in your
let press that exam time
oh Namba Namba
no get him get him get
him
okay let out of Battle Cry
Oh come on come on come come on come on
come on come on come
on we need to get him
down he gets up too fast can he heal
himself at least no it doesn't seem
so
oh oh maybe she does something like that
too
yo everyone's
[Music]
attacka do not underestimate the Buffs
right thank you for the membership
welcome have
[Music]
com die
yes okay that zako is
de oh where
[Music]
oh you know what I want to heal
um Ian on his own so I'm going to heal
I'm going to heal ich with an item that
also heals MP here for your CR you're
welcome cuz I want to use that um mango
ping that we have
yeah there we
go I I'm
bleeding
o oh we have
this why not use it I
guess
not I was just thinking
let go help
[Music]
me oh did we reach 1 million finally
thank
you thank you we finally made
it a finally thank you
thank you for all the help
guys I know I've been annoying everyone
with streaming High Challenger for a
long
time thank
[Music]
you we did it you guys did
it thank you for the support d k
I'm bleeding
again
y should let myself get healed by uh
Namba to guy standing there just
watching I just
realized thank you thank you thank you
thank
you where is he
[Applause]
[Music]
a this this uh this this this this fight
is really long
go why are you so
strong thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank
you thank you very
much ran ass fumes
yo yo beat him beat him beat him
knock out his
teeth
[Music]
Miss I'll take
that thank you thank you thank you thank
you
everyone and another heal
there you
go yeah has no
MP but he's back to normal pound M
wasn't it super expensive though I don't
I don't have the money for it do
I
[Music]
MP okay we need it we need
it yeah I don't say the one milon Eva
but I trust you guys you wouldn't say
that for no
reason
ouch yeah you keep on crying I don't
[Music]
care we're over 1
million hi fortunately has been really
infected by the you know the shadow
bamboo Bambino bamboo so which is not
fair because a lot of lot of effort was
put into that and a lot of
love it's really not fair but what can
you
do oh he's dead nice all right perfect
guard now let's get him three verus one
now do I have my cat me
what was that in the
game I heard some
meows thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you
go P it's only a little bit more and I
probably get level up after this so
let's throw it all out
there he I hear a meow
again I think it's the
bgm do you guys hear
[Music]
thato you're not going to help you're
just going to watch
thank you thank you thank you
guys I pressed it at the perfect timing
why does it not count oh well we got new
boots too what's tungsten what's
that what we didn't get level up from
that come
on
3,000 from the Noe
[Music]
don't with
right thank you for the super chats
[Music]
everyone was that the
boss finally reached
him chairman of the clan
he looks like a decent
[Music]
dude
for I mean we have some like baseball
bats and
stuff
oh are we going to learn more about the
mystery behind
it seems like he
knows
[Music]
for oh are we going to talk about the
um the room
though
oh oh y
y
it's oh does he have like no fingers
left cuz he's wearing those gloves to
okay what did you
do he's going to cut it off
[Music]
himself oh
I love his
office he got some good
taste fore
[Music]
that's very sweet of him cuz in the
beginning it was just an innocent
thought
huh
for even if he would have told him not
sure of that boss would have been happy
[Music]
oh oh he does support it
he does
approve I mean yeah that's what I would
have thought beginning about the Yakuza
but you guys said they have honor too
apparently they
[Music]
don't yeah but they you're doing it
against their
will you not asking them for permission
or
anything
fore
foree
spee
[Music]
fore
fore okay
but oh he got kicked
out this is nice he keeps his finger at
least
I mean if I would have to choose I would
choose getting kicked
out
[Music]
fore oh
could
[Music]
viated is that your new Idol
it's
fore
[Music]
for about the
money okay I would like to know more
info about that though
[Music]
oh
man oh
man hurts it hurts broke
[Music]
very
interesting we did it guys that was a
tough
fight a long fight
put the gun
no got to be ready at any time until
it's
[Music]
okay doesn't see MOA so I guess we're
joining that's new arm
hurt yeah it feels a bit exhausted yeah
they're actually closing the whole thing
now well what about the money that that
she paid for the service
[Music]
for
Fore
fore
huh I don't
for
Fore
speech speee
[Music]
speee
[Laughter]
foree fore
give her back the money
so he go he went telling them they
their relatives need an operation
otherwise they'll die but they end up
dying anyway FR operation
wink
wow y she got the money back
oh how sweet are you
she's staring at the money like what
what can I believe
it what cling
on MM it's a lot of money
[Music]
spee
Carl Williams are you going
around uh all the members sending them
Super Chat telling them how low or how
high their new outfit is in your
opinion I don't think we give a
about that
so we did it the chapter is over I think
no wait we still have to report about
Nano okay okay we have to go to the
creepy dude
again go to
him don't get don't get run over by a
car oh
yes oh YZ on the other side good that we
took this
path going to run over here oh oh lot of
bad boys
coming Wait I messed something
up over here
over
here content warning everyone
watch what's
coming what's coming content War what do
you mean safe
okay naked maybe should
I should I sensor
something St being dumbed okay oh
sh oh you again you alive again H you oh
perfect God I'm not
healed I'm not
healed oh yeah with the sign
yeah
resisto no no
okay kill him already
[Music]
okay
um
yum I'm going that
way thank you oh thank you guys for the
pinkies pink you pink
[Music]
I don't really want to find you guys now
I ran just into the door there was no
Escape well I mean if you're running
into the door yes there is no Escape
then oh wow
guess I got to burn them threee at
once
[Music]
yes what that
P
nice you's got those moves
is the like the like some kind of
like
dance that Idol otakus do to
certain no no no
no yeah maybe we shouldn't fight
you we got the hell out of there nice
okay
oh well I'm going to sue this driver she
drove
me
you all right we have we have arrived
everyone I hope we don't have to fight
[Music]
is someone hanging there no
no did he kill
himself because Nano had
left can I really show this
I just realized the screen is really off
the whole time
too what I didn't
notice my God the the screen was off
like this the whole
time did you guys not tell
me um but well you I think I'm going to
hide it
well now it's too late damn it the scene
is
over all is this okay did someone stream
this game before and was it
okay C rang it was fine okay
uh we finished the
chapter
okay yeah
man chapter
five I'm wrapping it up though can I
like if I stop here it will show me the
same thing again right when I restart it
next time
okay but I don't understand he seemed
very crazy about it was it but did he
kill himself in the end because of money
or because of the girl that because she
left
I M that that's not murder he got hung
that's a way of doing it yourself if
someone would have murdered him
would have been different I'm sure of it
next chap next chapter will tell me oh
okay okay
[Music]
okay I'm glad that there's like I said
it today that I thought this game was
really serious but I was surprised
because like there were so many like
ridiculous Parts like funny parts in the
game as well but we got we we went full
circle and when back into the serious
Parts again at the end
um and uh yeah I like it I like it I'm
enjoying it very
much I think it's already uh been six
and 6 and 1 half
hours I don't know when I should read
super
chats I don't know when maybe tomorrow
in the evening maybe I can do like a 3
Hour 4 Hour Super Chat reading
separately
you said no string yeah but but but in
the evening I can take some
[Music]
time I don't
know I'll I'll try to read at least some
now though I
guess uh
[Music]
it's been six and a half hours I'll do a
little bit
um
but um I'll take like a a little break
the Super Chat intermission and then
I'll see you guys to read some super
chats maybe for 1 hour at the most maybe
let's see let's let's try to um Zoom
through it today a little bit
more okay A little bit can't last for a
while B I know my my little bit so is uh
quite the
bit but I got to get through it it's
just going to pile up more and more and
more and more but I've been trying
really hard
to get through
it damn it's a
lot now I know a little bit how how it
was for like Ci for her birthday and am
for her
birthday not quite as much but
still oh my
god oh man all right all right all right
I'll see you guys in a moment uh thank
you guys for watching yaka today today
and as n tomorrow no stream I'll also be
um making the
schedule even today after the stream or
tomorrow it might end up being tomorrow
because I just want to chill after the
stream probably take a shower and all
that put down the
gun
okay don't let you guard
[Music]
down bang bang
bang
bang bang okay okay okay no moreza no
moreu
I'm D thank
you
okay please wait a moment please hold
please hold on please hold the line hold
the line hold the line please thank
[Music]
you e
oh
think I'm going to make some
tea one moment we'll take a few more
minutes
[Music]
yo who is still awake
yo y y yo
yo back back back back back back thank
you for
waiting thank you very
much
Y what a fun fun Journey we're having
here with yakan yakan I've been like not
inspiring enough to make like a new
thumbnail so I just slapped on part
three on it I hope I hope that's okay by
the
way cuz this is going to be another long
Series so making like completely
original Super Special thumbnails each
time I don't
know I hope I hope it won't impact the
serious of the thumnail doesn't look
super special each
time m
it's been one hell of a ride so far yeah
literally
unwatchable oh yeah Mama L's art of me
with the gun trol yeah I should be I
should use that yeah I forgot about it
or yeah just adding uh the the the PNG
gun what was I just going to say what
was I about to say I forgot
ah the the people who've been watching
this stream so far I wonder if there's a
lot of people who just never saw the
game before or if there's again mostly
people who already played the game or if
it's like half half or
so never played it before never saw
it never played never heard of it or a
lot of them never saw never first time
oh well surpr well that's great because
then it's for you guys it's like
watching a movie
again I
generally think it's more fun to watch
someone play a game when you haven't
played it yourself yet and of course if
when you're not really planning to play
it yourself if you plan to play yourself
I understand the hesitation of uh
wanting not wanting to watch that
streamer play it I totally get that I
know that's like a big
problem you guys hear the bgm don't
don't
you
okay it's got bit exhausted to be honest
U my
my my my my
voice of all the male voices
it's fun to do them and I like that you
guys enjoy them as
well but with all those male voices h
oh it's really tough for my
FR
yeah yeah I'll do it I'll do it every
now and then but not not maybe not like
forever h no I can I can read at least
some of the super chats it's okay and
where was it though uh in my drive I
saved
it yeah super jats uh what was the
number this time now I forgot now I I
don't
remember something was 200 I think
242 thank
you I made a lot of tea so once I'm
drinking the tea it will be
[Music]
better I'll be reading it a bit quicker
at least I want to but if there's always
so many red super chats in there I
can't haha uh the struggle the struggle
of being
uh so blessed by your
support I don't want to complain so
let's
go did I did I read
242 desable did I read that Super
Chat wonder if you're
here send a r to
jet yes I
did okay okay use
Soda random spy thank
you uh was that was that a red one I
keep on forgetting I think that was a
red one Tel you're too cute congrats on
the new outfit love it thank you random
by d d d thank you very much
I'm glad you like
it you uh are going to see a lot of it
in in the following weeks
so get used to it thank you looking for
the top D and thank you for red Super
Chat as well oh wait I forgot to give
random spy kissy random spy M looking
for the top m going shopping was fun and
you even got a new haircut we should do
it more often more dresses more
hairstyles more fun you're looking super
cute and fresh k lovely also perfect no
SCU stream well done in U yeah um thank
you thank you for pointing it out uh I'm
actually myself quite surprised that
that went so well as it
did thank you guys for the Super Chat
thank you because yeah you guys were
following uh what was what was what
happened up until then right first the
move and then the internet not coming
uh yeah that was quite nerve wrecking
um and I started I was able to prepare
it uh pretty yeah late but I had like an
idea of what I wanted to do uh
quite quite a while before that
so I'm surprised it all went well I I
did actually rehearse before the stream
um because of the all of the curtain
moving I didn't want to like you know me
mess that up that's actually really easy
to mess up like cuz there were like two
two curtain animations that I had in
there and every time like I I was using
Studio mode and I had to always check
that um I'm opening the right curtains
and then they they don't open uh they
only open until you like transition the
scene and uh so I was always
preparing uh me the behind the
curtain I don't know it was kind of
complicated I was it was I was very
close to messing it up but it went so
perfectly I'm so proud thank God thank
God it went so smoothly thank you thanin
[Music]
snow hat em Sky j k
good Apostle
the d r
DC
CHR lunch
thank you for the pinky TIY ooh with
your camera did you take lots of
screenshots tyy thank
you yes I am very photo
photogenic shopping for the new outfit
went super well I thought it was cute
and more unique than just throwing the
new outfit out there yeah but I feel
like once again Holo Ian kind of like
revolutionized the way of re revealing
an outfit
again like I feel like we once again
raised a
bar especially with
am am and youa youa as
well yeah K was pretty standard but she
was the first one to go she didn't she
didn't know what we were going to do I
feel like maybe she if she knew what we
were going to do she would have maybe
done a bit more but uh I think it's
totally fine to reveal it normally but
being the first is a bit difficult cuz
you don't know what the others are going
to do you you can't top it if you don't
know what they're
doing but there's no need to top anyone
we're hold and we hold strong together
actually yesterday um after the stream
we we were just chilling and uh talking
for like I don't know 50 more minutes
and uh updating each other on everyone's
lives and stuff like how everyone has
been doing doing a little bit of a
advice s and hearing everyone's worries
and all that so that was nice yeah um
I've been seeing
some
angst angst people
again trying to
like uh
claim that I did something during the
[Music]
stream against Kelly which is again just
ridiculous
H but yeah I'm not even going to mention
that cuz it's not worth mentioning it
it's just stupid it's just so
stupid but yeah just keep in mind that
we all have a great relationship with
one another and
uh yeah yesterday was once again really
great to like have fun together on
stream with a game and then later on we
just
privately um had uh some deep Heart to
Heart
talks yeah yeah yeah no I even noticed
it in the in the chat in the live stream
cuz I was paying quite a lot of
attention at the chat during the stream
cuz I wasn't the one streaming so I had
more uh
abilities to spread my eyes and
[Music]
wings I was even interacting with the
chat I was even like I once I even type
the heart into the
chat does G's chat act differently than
us a it's hard to say yesterday during
the collab I didn't really feel that
way I don't know I don't know I
mean it depends maybe I don't
know h
thank you for the red super
chat this is too cute big props to hooka
Papa quality as expected I actually use
you as my reference when paping my
friend's model because you're just so
well made Oh you mean for live
today and my favorite too of course PS
expect to see me with a kitada profic
from now on
thank you you know I've been uh seeing
people using um me um as their Twitter
icon it's pretty cute I like it as long
as you don't like use the same as mine
and then confuse people with it try to
you know make them think you're me or
something as long as you're not doing
that it's totally fine I I like when you
guys uh use my icon or something related
to kfp as your icon and also have
something in your name or in your
Twitter the description and all that
H that's I I I I feel the support I like
that you guys are spreading it and not
not afraid and not embarrassed to do
so are you a fox or a cat well first and
foremost I'm a
phoenix and this is just you know a
little bit of a transformation you know
I'm good with shape shifting and stuff
you could say I'm both Fox cat
[Music]
my tea is too
hot yeah yeah let's keep let's keep
telling the tea it's too hot for me to
drink I'm I can totally drink it if I
wanted to Lama Phoenix but I just want
to give the the tea some confidence have
confidence
[Music]
H sorry I've been I've been um blowing
at my tea a lot
quicker faster
[Applause]
[Music]
faster it's so
hot kfb
helps oh my God there is a blowing emo I
don't
know D thank you for the red super
chat no I can't believe I missed the new
outfit R I love you kid oh you were late
huh no problem you came at the very very
end still that's still something I hope
you watch the archive though and I hope
you like the new outfit thank you I love
you
too thanks for the support same d
D isak Animan gamer Alfredo P Chase for
Chase FW D Luna AEL D John Bob 008 D
thank you for the
pinky love the outfit and all of the
accessories I look forward to seeing
more of it I'll admit I was getting
impatient waiting for the new outfits
but I'm glad yours was worth the waight
M thank you thank you thank you that was
only the second one it was really hard I
think for you guys to wait for the
others huh cuz it was a long week a long
exciting week and because of all the
hype and excitement I do personally feel
a little bit exhausted I can't imagine
how it must be for you
guys I don't know do you guys feel a bit
exhausted I feel quite
[Music]
exhausted yeah that was a long long week
but but better way better than just
having it all on one day in a marathon
that's that's horrible no I never want
to do that again
never want to do that
again I think it's it's it's very good
that everyone had like their own
day should do it like that every time in
the future I mean back then it wasn't
our decision so you got
s ala pet soup vampire thank you for the
pinky such a cute and precious outfit F
oh my God right the pacify is adorable
and the cat style is just so
cute wait does the that M mean laser
poter is work on you cat toy so many
questions I
am I am way too mature to be playing
with laser pointers
okay I play you know PlayStation and and
switch games that's what I play with
those are my kind of cat
toys and and with my cats
H why are you ding that try try using a
laser pointer on me try pull out your
lasers you want to try
[Laughter]
me meow meow meow me meow me meow me
me me
[Music]
I was just messing with
you I don't give a about you lasers
[Music]
Super
Chat thank
you H where was I damn it there there
a m thank you for the red super
chat T you are giving me a heart attack
I like your new outfit so much and it's
so cute the cat is drive me crazy too
love these new things and your outfit
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you I don't want to use like the
cat stuff too often because I still
after all I'm a phoenix and I I want
people to know that I don't want I don't
want to rely too much on these G ears
they're really cute but I'm a phoenix I
got to I got to stay loyal to my own got
to stay real to myself be
myself
but every now and then I want to use it
cuz it's hella cute thank you thank you
I'm glad you like it thank you for
coming to the reveal m
and
wind
[Music]
5or
Captain
Uncle T logical Paradox thank you for
the pinky thank you for the beautiful
out showcase it fits you very well both
literally literally and figura fig
figuratively
thank
you thank you thank you thank you I'm
glad you enjoyed it thank you soon thank
you for the support K KFC thank you for
the red super
chatow hey girl I love the new outfit
with the cat it's extremely cute your
love is so beautiful it always makes my
day I love you and all your weirdness
keep up the good work I like I I the
true K proove of the new outfit have a
nice day fake k
I haven't heard from you in a while but
here you go again telling me I'm the F K
I'm the one and only true
kada you are weird you weird but thank
you for your support thank very much
glad you enjoyed it glad to see you
still around thanks for giving me a life
sign
than S Place D thank you for the
pinky I love the new look also what did
you think about Kell's new outfit oh I
think it fits her really
well very casual very comfy it kind of
gives
me uh it gave me some kind of vibe that
I'm not sure how to
describe it's it reminds me
of maybe maybe of KDA a little bit and
of maybe not so much upto-date
fashion but it's is really
cute um like without the jacket it's
really cute but with the jacket it's
just comfy and cool and I like that she
went with that um comfy look rather than
uh you guys fought the same thing that's
cool rather than like going for like a
sexy killer look uh cuz it's good to
have some contrast from your main outfit
I would say
personally oh I'm obviously a sexy
killer in bu of my outfits but it's
still very much different Still
Still H Trava G also thank you for the
pinky I need time to possess P all all
of that cuteness I love your new outfit
it's absolutely gorgeous hook did
amazing thank you I'm cat Kata is so
damn cute and sexy it's confusing me I'm
an ow Dam it
yeah uh isn't
like an isn't is a is an owl kind of
like one of the praise of
like straight cats or like at least
smaller owls I can say
that we can see
how cats might try to go after smaller
ows maybe they both eat the same yeah
they both want to go for the mice maybe
the cats would like I kill cats what the
what really I think it would depend on
the size yeah there are some pretty damn
huge owls but how would an owl kill a
cat ow a
deadly really I want to see
that well actually no I don't want to
see that don't send me videos of Al
killing and eating cats please I
actually don't want to say that it's it
sounds fascinating but I don't want to
see
it and J
Reinhard friendly Chung
[Music]
tile title
okay I can't read
that oh my God I cannot really read it I
mean I've seen it before I'm not 100%
sure how to read
them Cattail is very long yeah it's
pretty long isn't it
[Music]
silver tongue
slacker relates to you more than ever oh
oh cuz of the cuz of the
pacifier oh that's cute Eric Wang D
thank you is that a pinky I think no
we'll pay for it what was I talking
about I wonder thank you
[Music]
ericf Ty P Brown 121
vangard SK thank you for the red super
chat M your new outfit is too cute and
make me speechless especially those cat
ears just make me P pass out but you
sing Heart singing heart challenge will
let me wake up
again thank you thank you thank you
thank you for watching the whole stream
even if you passed out hope you're okay
sorry for um making you lose your
Consciousness but I appreciate the
support thank you for being there for
the reveal life even though it was
probably quite early for you in your
country but thank you very
much
iron K alred
Tak life is so much better with you
[Music]
Melman 9812 D soon just
Osborne Tom Hamilton thank you for the
red super
[Music]
chat was expecting Farm but this is
Extremely Blessed Tom Hamilton thank you
sorry for not being the farmer your
dreams but I'm
still still cute aren't
I I'm I'm the girl from next door the
weird really weird vtuber girl from next
door thank you thank you tomon I'm glad
you like it anyway thank you for your
support thank you soon
ericom
Captain thank you for the pinky the
cover was great you and G sounded
amazing and youa really update herself
with the video there are so many
pictures and she even worked uh kfp into
it yes of course she did she just knows
me too well uh and everyone showed up
eventually and now the Dancing Yeah the
the dancing at the end blew away a lot
of people that was really cute that she
included the
choreography she's a genius the video is
perfect we talked about it a lot of
times but I'm still amazed with
it yeah can't wait to commission her
again and see see what she comes up next
time what she comes up with next
time cuz I'm for sure going to
commission
hurricane it's just so much easier with
someone who um can like do both of the
things video and video and art at the
same time yeah makes it much
easier it's worth worth it worth every
penny large black
red wol Chris
Harvey Russian
[Music]
name de
Lucio
cyer TI thank you for the pinky I fre
sound was so good right thank you I'm
glad you enjoyed the tyy I hope you're
listening to it a lot of times it's such
a fun song it was great to sing it
togethera I think it was a great choice
even though normally it doesn't seem
like the song that people would choose
as a duet but I felt it would be quite
good as a duet
too so that's why I went with it and
just because I felt like it would suit
our
voices gentle
cor
5 thank you for the red super
chat that song cover is amazing both you
and good are knocked it out of the K has
both of you go son and especially thanks
to Yuna that was a really beautiful MV
Sami let's go hoping for future duets
with Ena and El too actually now that I
did a collab with Cali and GAA I was
thinking maybe I should just uh make it
my mission to do a utat song cover with
every girl at least once so next up I'll
do like Ena and am one by
one it wasn't blad originally but but
could be fun could be fun to have one
with each
girl having something special with each
of
[Music]
them by the way guys I'm going to
personally warn
you I'm not happy with how I sound in
Country
Roads not really happy with it
maybe that's why um I wasn't 100%
excited about it no wa not about the old
microphone no no no no no no no well but
I'll let you guys judge
it I'm just not very happy with it
therefore like if I if I'm not happy
with my voice in a song then I I I just
don't feel comfortable with promoting it
that much but uh yeah you guys listen to
it and and make your own
judgment Luka um
danini Epic
[Music]
Z yeah yeah it was mixed by a different
guy I don't even know who mixed
it and yeah it made me realize it's I
guess really a huge difference depending
on who mixes your voice makx your voice
sound very different GD thank you for
the pinky woohoo it was a bloody Ripple
cover song made yellow I like how you
letting out your Australian you fake
fake Australian out
there than thank you thank you didy for
all the lovely support you're giving me
thank
you
mate the cute Master random
spy all this is right when when the
cover uh when I was showing watching the
cover with everyone everyone's like the
cover was so cute I'm crying so cute so
cute where can I want listen to the
Country Road cover it's not out yet it's
going to be released uh I don't know the
date by heart but next week Sun Saturday
Sunday depending on your time zone
maybe mens thank you for the pinky D
congrats on the new outfit K you deserve
it you look absolutely stunning thank
you for always being so determined and
hardworking it doesn't matter how many
issues there are I'm always going to be
there to support you much love from
Britain oh one of the few UK fans huh
thank you very much for being here very
happy to have you here I'm glad you
enjoyed the outfit so much thank you
very much for being there for the live
reveal thank you
[Music]
T yeah we hit 1 million views in the
heart Challenger thank you for your
support thank
you
uh I I saw yeah I saw the clip I mean
there were several clips of the members
only stream just uploading songs and
then the one clip of that one
incident uh I think the the one of the
songs we already got down perhaps I
don't know working on it working on it
always working on
it
yeah yeah I just hope people don't like
uh make a drama out of it cuz it really
was an accident
yeah oh well anyway yeah I'll take care
of it just because it's memb only
content
TM Dan Ty Dan thank you for the pinky
just wow I can never get over how
beautiful you sound you and gooda fit
together singing perfectly and that was
absolutely amazing the video was amazing
too just wow you really hit everything
out of the part today yeah that was a
crazy day crazy crazy day thank you very
much tyen I'm glad you like it
M GAA has such a beautiful beautiful
singing voice so yeah I think our voices
together sound very very refreshing very
young and and
energetic very
sweet yeah it's a good sound good
sound good Jing D
Co thank you for the red super oh my God
I'm genuinely speechless that gave me
the chills just oh my God I'm
speechless B are you
okay thank you thank
you thank you I hope you can speak
again thank you I'm glad you liked it so
much
s d Brun d g shell thank you for the
pinky that was just beautiful I could
actually feel the heart
put into the cover the art to go with it
was great too pretty much encompassing
your journey so far mhm love it girls
here's the many more more memories to
come yeah yeah yeah yeah it showed a lot
of uh it showed all of our collabs that
me and GAA had together and then also
like separate things like um me watching
you hatch that was very adorable I'm
glad she included this memories made me
really emotional too when I watched
it D thank you for noticing that
stand
stand I missed my son's birthday but
this was so worth it oh my
God that's not
goodal memory D 17 for
the Casual
Commander
24 TV Island
Vamp s for thank you for the pinky love
the song and your new outfits the cat
ear
are the cat ear are so cute thank you
hook for blessing us with K's new sexy
look yes thank you hook Papa thank you
thank you I'm really really um glad that
it turned out the way it did really
thankful for my
papa and I saw this comment on Reddit
somewhere under a post um that was
talking about the new outfit or
something like that something someone
wrote that like me and hooka Papa are
really on the same W
wavelength like like you know stuff like
the swimsuit underneath showing it to me
he just understands me
and that is so true I was like yeah yeah
that is really true actually I I took a
screenshot of that
comment where was
it oh my God what stop bugging
around from this and the pacifier you
got to love how synchronized he is with
kada in the in their personalities like
couldn't imagine any other person being
K's Papa or vice versa they are truly
botom
dwellers yeah
yeah yep that's how it
[Music]
is oh my
God oh my
God
and where was I ah there it is
lunchbox 423
be
Fox thank
you prime
Don looking for the top thank you for
the pinky samon song is one of the
things I've been waiting for since the
first time I listen to you both sing
this is a dream come true thanks K to
think some people thought you two didn't
get along people on the internet am
right yeah that was some kind of
narrative in the beginning huh
yeah it's
um weird people just like narratives but
it's okay it's I think people have been
proven wrong back then when we did our
first
collaboration uh yeah that's quite a
while
ago I've been I've been on very good
terms of G and
uh yeah I've been supporting her in my
own ways
trying to help her in my own ways high
fructose corn
syrup J
[Music]
dragon for
got
you didn't tell me what what what color
that Super Chat is Naga are you
here are you in the
[Music]
chat I'm drinking it's red okay thank
you good that you're
here the people who I need are always
here in the moment when I need them
dve
me oh she's doing the speed thing
right
cute
cute cute cute cute
come
on think she's going to draw everyone
yeah yeah yeah cute oh she's so talented
ah
amazing okay okay we got to finish this
we we have like uh 70 super chats left
to go for the new outfit real reveal
super chats and that's all I'm going to
read and then we're finally done with
that
mhm so I knew the cover was beautiful
you beautiful this whole thing is is
beautiful thank you thank you n for the
red super chat and for the support and
your kind kind kind sweet words thank
you soon thank you I'm glad you like
it the color and the outfit I guess
thank you it was a big
success I I am happy you like it I
appreciate your support D please keep on
supporting K said
for for
[Music]
super thank you for the pinky cover song
with my two favorite girls Yura hit me
right in the COO with all the knots to
your past collabs yeah loved how at the
end all the Ang girl showed up and that
animation was so cute going to be
playing this arm thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you very
much lots of references they really
really cute I didn't even have to ask
for that youa did all of that on her
own absolutely perfect she's she can
read my mind thank you Pon thank
[Music]
thank you for the red super
chat my first red Super Chat originally
I was planned to send my first red Super
Chat When You Reach 1 million didn't
expect a new outfit to come this fast
the new outfit is so cute and n k I am
dead got the song cover was so beautiful
I cried all those memories
M thank you
yeah I mean it has been over 6 months I
think uh us getting new outfits is uh
quite normal I mean if you look at how
fast other members in h life Japan get
new outfits it seems reasonable
especially with Holo Ian's success it is
what it is it is what it is
yeah so next goal 3D let's go
thank you alien please keep on
supporting puding D the Admiral d n
Jessie
d Edgar iano 117 D
Alexandra magic a
random jly it probably is Larry
D
honey seven evil br
[Music]
un
thank you for the
[Music]
pinky pudding was a pinky where was
pudding there oh my god oh
sorry missed it somehow wait wait wait
wait wait amazing song an outfit sh I
loved every bit of the new outfit
especially the cat years that was a very
welcome surprise and I especially love
the blush oh love you deep deep K here's
a toast to all that has happened thank
you the blush uh yeah is a nice addition
it's a small detail but I appreciate it
now I'm using that expression way more
often thank you for your support and
also thank you for all your Clips thank
you very much thank you for doing your
part people don't always have to you
know send super chats you can just do
your own way of support and pudding is a
good example of that thank you very much
thank you
soon where was I oh yeah h d thank you
for the pinky congrats on the new outfit
and C potential this new outfit is cute
so cute especially in this cat form it
made me fall in love with you all over
again and killed me countless times
during the stream thank God revive is
quite fast oh you're also a phoenix is
what
that is impossible that is impossible I
don't know what you're talking about
hokan you're a chicken are you aware of
that
H thank you for the support this Laria
too dear Lord $400 red Super Chat thank
you so much oh my
God M Mah Mah m m Mah Mah mAh
now that smovie and Jers have a fox Mama
the first is going to be everywhere more
than ever before you'll need this top
tier room of Robo vacuum and industrial
air purifier forget the little robot
it's not going to be big
enough what what do you mean it's not
going to be big enough for my cats are
you saying they're so
fat um the the Roomba I already have but
I was I didn't really have the time or
uh
uh brain space to set it up yet uh
sometime next week I'm going to try to
set it up and see how it
works oh come on stop making fun of
chunkers like that don't do her like
that it's mostly just fluff okay she can
fit
through toilet like that should be fine
should be
fine come on poor Don girl she such a
sweet girl she doesn't deserve this
bully don't name her chunkers then her
real name isn't chunkers anyway she has
a much cuter
name
ni
[Music]
baby nah she's not going to ride the
rooma no no Pro no I don't think so
she's going to be scared of it probably
got to get her used to it it's going to
be a little bit of an issue
probably cuz those kind of noise to
scare her but I hope she'll be fun when
I get her used to it I don't want to
scare her I feel bad when she's
scared hold talk next week yep hold talk
next week yes yes yes yes yes yes k
australi card D plus good thank you for
the red super chat
500 amazing thank you
absolutely insane support thanin from
the bottom of my heart for this huge
donation amazing outfit amazing song
amazing Phoenix thank you for bringing
so much happiness and positivity to this
world K you amazing multi-talented fire
bird I see this person calls me Phoenix
this person has quite the respect for me
thank you plus good do you understand
what's up I like you I like you finally
someone who knows what I
am thank you very much BL good thank you
for being part of kfp and supporting me
this this great way thank you very
much
sh 47 thank you for the pinky great
outfit great song great stream is all so
good mhm I agree thank you thank you for
your support thank you for coming to the
stream2 thank
you
for slim
than oh my God we're done almost looking
for the D Mr Ken Big D and razid daies
is the last one with a
pinky thank you razid daies here a pinky
to let you know I didn't miss the song
Premier this time boss aha it's on my
playlist as well now you and K sound
amazing and you not did an excellent job
of the visuals lots of love to everyone
involved thank you for your support
thank you
resies thank
you now we're done okay I'm going to I
need a break it's 11:00 p.m. what the
oh my God it's been 8
hours 7 and a half uh it feels like a
million
[Music]
hours you did this to yourself no it it
was you guys you guys you guys are sing
the Super
Chat oh but I I I appreciate the support
so so so insanely much but going for
these super jets is really painful
sometimes don't blame
us I'm sorry I'm sorry no one's to
blame no one to blame my head my face
hurts and my head hurts I'm I'm going to
take a break
guys I'll be uploading the schedule for
the coming week tomorrow I think yeah
it's not happening today I think I have
it like roughly on my on my calendar but
I'm going to do it tomorrow tomorrow is
no stream anyway so
so please wait a little bit more for the
announcement of the H talk a little bit
more and the
rebroadcast I might I might move that as
well I might do that maybe like actually
it would probably be even easier to
catch for more people if it was on the
weekend
right I'll think about it I'll let you
guys know as early as possible thank you
guys for being here especially the ones
who have been here since the beginning
of the stream thank you for following it
all thank you for watching everything
also the people who came M way through
at the end thank you thank you very much
I appreciate
it now one
second let me try something
thing
[Music]
CH k
okay yes okay I wish everyone a Happy
Mother's Day if uh if in your country it
is a Happy Mother's Day don't forget to
tell your mama about uh about it I mean
your mom probably knows if it is Happy
Mother's day but tell her happy Mother's
Day I already did with mine mama not
meeting her though cuz we fall apart and
but yeah and
thank you for the support as always I
love you guys I see you on
Tuesday unless I do any something
gorilla tomorrow but I don't know I
don't think
so thank you and enj when we say
[Music]
oh I I was going to do this I came
during the stream now I didn't know I
had to Loop it
let me Loop that
here okay
yes I want to add uh this is from AKA I
retweeted it they animated it as well I
want to add like like a like some fonts
there though like but I want the font to
be animated as well and I don't know how
to do that kind of stuff but I want it
to be
like you know like like the other one
like this one thanks for
watching please
subscribe you know I want that in there
too if anyone wants to do that like only
the
font that would be dope like only
something like thanks for
watching cuz I can't animate I don't
know how to do that kind of
stuff thanks for watching please
subscribe uh leave a comment leave a
like something like
that some cute animation that I can just
place on top of this
the stream heart challenge no we don't
need that
anymore we don't need that anymore but
this is so cute I love
it oh my God so cute I always wanted
something like that too like a life
today animation of an illust fanmade
illustration looks so good I love this
illustration I love
it want to change your BM I would love
if if I had some kind of like tropical
house bgm for the ending maybe like a
remix of one of my songs
but yeah that's probably not going to
happen so maybe I'm just going to look
for copyright free
uh copyright free um uh house tropical
something like
that I feel like that would fit this
H stream
IA no no no we're not that desperate
about Iota Iota is doing well enough on
its
own tropical
tent all right guys byebye
[Music]
this is so
cute I can't stop looking as it
[Music]
yeah even with a pacifier there's a
version a different version too with no
glasses and no pacifier though yeah it's
so cute but this also the thing is this
has the the I said bye already but this
has the cat ears and the straw hat which
is a combination that I cannot do but I
love that they did that cuz it's like
Aida is reading my mind like this I I I
I that's like the perfect combination
straw head and cat ears
[Music]
hello I don't know is watching thank you
and the person who animated it too thank
you thank you
[Music]
you this one is cute too though I love
them both a
struggle I don't
know such a
struggle anyway byebye
[Music]