foreign
[Music]
okay
takeoff is now kicking key come on hey
new background
this is a special
like I don't know I didn't even request
this but uh I'm at the up oh oh oh there
it goes here it goes it's moving kfb
2400 is ready for takeoff
we don't even have the sounds the laptop
sounds right now but it was supposed to
be a joke
we know
about the laptop noise
well there it goes it's gone
it's gonna take off
I mean no I didn't really say he should
make like I didn't directly I just it's
more like a the same kind of like oh
wouldn't it be funny if as uh uh we're
done
with the flag compilation that I I was
less serious about the vlogm compilation
then I was about this airport uh or I
was less less hopeful
anyway what's up that dead or or
hopefully just sleeping chicken down
there huh
well I think it's about time for the
plan to come back foreign
[Music]
he probably fell asleep accidentally in
there and then the other guy Frank
you know he just went to work and he
didn't realize that Thomas was still in
there
yeah I mean honestly not Frank's fault
say blood no way
well
made up yeah there it is mate please
come back that was a short flight or is
that a different plane
that's probably a different no it's the
same
I don't think that
I think it changed its mind I don't
think it's
I don't think it went anywhere I think
it just went like checked out you know
had a little walk a little walk and then
it was like you know what I'm not doing
this like I'm being underpaid
unless you change my salary oh no what
the [\h__\h] like don't Pilots get paid so
[\h__\h] much
but maybe it wasn't the pilots you know
because you need a lot more to take off
than just a pilot
yeah maybe maybe maybe the
maybe the birds were like [\h__\h] you
airport for constantly shooting us
so they actually came here to sabotage
and now the kfp 2400 cannot fly
yeah and it could be many many reasons
yeah just taxing around the wrong way I
came back
huh
uh
that that mountain that marvelous
gorgeous mountain in the back is most
likely fujisan
yeah
um we have very good weather today
perfect weather conditions
uh I have yet to see fujisan during my
trip at the moment
the occasions where I could have seen
him he wasn't available for my call
registration follow Fest tickets hasn't
opened yet but I already have my trip to
Japan but oh let's go well even if you
don't make it for the concert I'm I
think you'll have a great time
especially if it's your first trip then
you know it's always worth going to
Japan for the first time it doesn't need
to be for a concert I don't have much to
say about playing so I'm just gonna wing
it
but you didn't do anything there's no
you need to follow
where's the follow-up
you ended it there I mean I get the joke
oh wait is it changing songs oh it's not
looping uh here there you go the thing
is I can't hear the music you know I'm
in the studio right now
uh streaming a little bit I was told I
don't have to end that three hours as
long as I end uh
uh you know at a reasonable time
because there's no one using it
afterwards
um
yeah
yeah yeah huh
how difficult is it to travel to Japan
without knowing much Japanese well
well Tokyo I think it's very
navigatable especially if you use Google
Maps like me all the time
um it tells you which train which
platform to take and all that and
usually there's English writing on quite
a few
places at least in terms of like
transportation
um there there will always be an English
translation voice uh and text so yeah
it's not that harsh but you know I mean
I can't really really give you the
impression of someone who doesn't speak
Japanese because even the first time
when I went to Japan when I was young I
already was able to read and speak
Japanese so I never experienced the
feeling of being suddenly in Japan
without being able to speak Japanese so
you might have to ask someone like I
don't know amen or or
um or so but
um
Emma has been getting lost in stations a
lot
um just for not forever you know she
always finds her way back
um and she's she's a bit fascinating to
me though because
like the other day oh here we go here we
go guys do you hear the museum by the
way I should have made it louder the
other day when I said goodbye to her uh
after that uh Yakiniku
and here he goes
you know first you know the other girls
you may have heard it in a clip or so
but
um Bales and some of the remaining
Japanese members they went uh partying I
was first gonna like join them
but I know I ended up not feeling like
it so I I said bye bye and then I also
said bye bye like we left together
and then
you know Emma said oh she'll she'll
follow me
um to until I I go into my taxi
introvert moment yeah that may have been
a little bit of an introvert moment for
me
I fell a little bit out of place so I
was like okay okay have fun guys bye
um but
yeah where was I so I jumped into the
taxi and Ahmed was supposed to find her
way to the train and then go home but
she told me later on the next day or so
when we went to enoshima she told me she
she ended up going to like every single
arcade in the area
every single one and then eventually
ended up bumping into the girls again
so I guess
am I really
really admitting to me like oh man
I I applaud her for her courage
to
[Music]
like you know just
[\h__\h] go into it
she's not scared she's not scared came a
moment hmm
well I didn't get sick what do you mean
[Music]
um I I my plan is to read super chats
but here's the thing I kind of want to
do a thing
I want to do a thing can I do like um
how do you make yourself a roulette
I want to do a tangent roulette and you
decide like what would I
what I'm going to talk about there's
just one thing that I will 100 talk
about which is the enoshima trip because
I have I downloaded all the pictures I
sent them to jenma on this card and
download all them yeah I I want to do it
like a wheel okay I think I found one
um
choices okay okay okay okay
and then whatever is left over today you
know those tangents I will use for my
um 10 hour Fire Emblem streams that are
coming up that I'm so excited for
oh what should I talk about yes oh
bye-bye Carefree 200400 bye-bye
cookies
um so let me open my notes
um I think I think uh sometimes I've
been slacking a little bit of notes but
I think I can remember most things more
or less okay so oh man these are some
really [\h__\h] long notes and I don't
think I've told you about any of this so
I have Game Center Trio
uh and then I have
[Music]
um
this one
this one who I told you guys about
much to talk about to be honest
um you know what I'll leave that one out
I feel like I already more or less
talked about this one
and ah oh and also the movie former
Bells Elena Kelly karaoke
did I not already like mostly talk about
this
I feel like I talked about this at least
for the most part there wasn't really
much more interesting yeah I did okay
okay
but here here it goes Marine I did not
talk about my Madden off guy did I
Mari
uh
I don't forget that okay
and good yeah all of whatever comes
after that I did not talk about it
[Music]
um I I
love her foreign
[Music]
but let's put it on there anyway
um
did I forget something
did I did I write something down
no I don't think I wrote anything down
but I think I can go with my brain
okay okay okay
I I don't talk
um there's not much to talk about there
I think
okay
I mean I met her and we went for a poof
and I paid for it she wanted to pay for
it and I took away her purse and I I
placed it somewhere else and then she
tried to take it back and I was like
and I pushed her like I mean I didn't
push her but like I kind of guarded her
purse
and the the restaurant
cashier was like hmm
anyway yeah besides that I mean just the
stream and I don't know
[Music]
I don't think it's worth a whole wheel
section anyway
apply wheel changes a wheel title
tangents okay
I don't know if I can show the way I
want to show it though
let me try to show it
um
in order to show it
let me just check okay
and
see I got so I got tangents for like
whoa
but I am going to tell all of them today
because like honestly in the recent
months whenever I did like long streams
you know I always need something to talk
about and I feel like I've been running
out of stories because
in my two years more than two years of
whole life I definitely
um
told you everything of my past that I
can tell you like exciting stories like
like you know my my uh Airline audition
story my flight bomb story my all kinds
of stories yeah and I feel like I ran
out and I'm like oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
am I supposed to tell you now yeah so I
need these tangents to survive and yeah
yeah you know what
flight button yeah I told you that one
that is now
[Music]
um
when this OBS is Japanese it's so oh
yeah
okay
so the wheel is here
and okay
I just should this should go well
click to spin okay okay
so okay
now we have to do my dad
should be good hi
there it is
my tangent whale
I have to come back to Japan soon again
oh yeah yeah I will anyway I will I will
I will why is this a dark I don't know
it's dark mode I guess
um well I Love Changes SpongeBob look
what
do you mean my lap
well [\h__\h] you
um
also I'm opening some hot tea which
isn't so hot anymore
bless Japan for having
vending machines and convenience stores
and supermarket and Zone that sell hot
drinks in the bottle
it's amazing it's amazing
[Music]
how are you feeling are you not sick
anymore oh I mean
uh
there's hmm I think Hmm
still a little bit every now and then
um but it doesn't disrupt my day anymore
and also I haven't been like
coughing for a couple days
um
the flag them that's still around
um yeah
I sound better yeah you know I streamed
here uh for the wildcare connect stream
with the same microphone and so on but I
feel like I sound much better
like I'm you maybe don't notice the
difference I don't know but I felt uh
like hearing my own voice
it still sounds very hoarse on that day
um you don't sound like you're dying
anymore yeah yeah I mean like I don't
think I'm think I've been sounding like
I've been dying for a while what kind of
times
[Music]
I don't need you
don't know
[Music]
um
ah I don't hear it read back your usual
stuff
good I sound isolation story yeah hell
yeah like there's like wow cool sound
isolation which brings me to a tangent
that's not on the Wheel
um
of what just a random thing because like
I'm talking about this now sound
isolation
it's so cool like I've been to a lot of
the members homes now and let me put
this a little bit down and
[Music]
a lot of them
really a lot of them have sound
isolation like rooms separate rooms in a
room like they they hired like or they
bought or they hired people to build a
sound isolation room inside of room
it's yeah it's crazy like you know I
think I've heard maybe maybe
Senpai or so talk about it before or
someone some member talking about that
they like kind of like stream inside the
sound isolation Booth tiny one and and
in my imagination or maybe it was really
how it was described back then
for at least for this case my
imagination it really sounded like they
are within like one
one square meter space like a a freaking
tinier than a shower boot or pretty much
a shower Booth is what I had in mind
when I heard that
hmm
oh I don't know who wants who that was
but but so I've been seeing a lot of
those now maybe they have like invested
more since then but
it's crazy it's crazy
it's not just foam on the walls no
[Music]
it's it's fascinating like
okay one one member I'm not gonna say
like who who but for one member I I saw
that the booth was like not really
sticking to the walls but like it you
could really see it was a room inside a
room
but it was weird because it looked like
you were entering a different world it's
kind of cool but it really looks like a
recording booth kind of thing
um
yeah yeah it's a free yeah freestanding
room yeah yeah you can see the walls and
there would be like one uh meter space
to the actual wall for example
oh and I don't know it's so cool it's so
cool how does the door work like a kind
of like a recording both door
like a strong door you close the door
and yeah no sound comes out and uh um
yeah it's like really properly made it
looks so so professional fancy and then
for others I saw that it was actually
sticking to the walls so when you enter
the room it doesn't look like a room in
the room no it just looks like a room
and
it's so cool because you see
whoa on the walls they like put the
isolation like stuck it on there it's
not just those wavy panels you know no
it's like like the proper stuff is so
cool
and I asked about the price
if you
if you buy this a lot it's a lot but I
think in Japan you know
mostly places are very thin walled so
it's worth the investment if you have a
job like that and if you also want to
really focus on like recording and
streaming and singing and so on
um
yeah but I I would say no it's not
really necessary in my place because
uh there's no sound leaking
and the place where I stream the room
where I stream is really far from the
actual like entrance door for example
and just generally our buildings are
built with thicker walls yeah
yeah yeah
so is that attention yeah
foreign
[Music]
but even considering that
I don't think I I feel like it's worth
it for Me Maybe if I
did much more sound recording like
singing recording at my own place like
much more than I currently do
um and maybe if I I don't know that ASMR
so I don't know
but some members have different rooms
for ASMR too like what the [\h__\h]
yeah
pretensions attention to religions for
the appetite yeah yeah it's the starter
it's the starter
um
yeah oh my God it's fascinating hmm
sounds like Overkill
really he had a cool like if I first
thought it was a safe
I was like Louie do I have a save for
like important valuable things and no
looking closer it's like a humidifi oh
no anti-humidifier for your microphones
for your special microphones
foreign
and you you can set
it's a relatively small box it looks
like a safe box you can set how much
moisture you want Inside the Box
yeah yeah because for some like good
microphones you want them to be kept in
a good like humidification
yeah
[Music]
I I don't even really realize that
something like that exists
hmm
it's fascinating
yeah it looks like so professional like
seeing everyone's setups too like every
I think it you know if if I lived in a
place where off collapse where a
like common thing you know if I had lots
of visitors I would probably set it up
like this too but it's not so not
necessary but visiting all those members
they all have like everything set up for
off collabs like they all have those
like like headphone Splitters so that
everyone has feedback in their ears
which is very important for me we didn't
have that in the en uh of course A lot
of the time
yeah it's like a like a Mac a headphone
splitter that goes like six different
ways
and I know some members are caught on it
for example not everyone does this but
Coronet for example has like several
microphones she has like I know up to
like five microphones or so in case of
five that she has a five people off
collab
like ready to go yeah and everyone has
several phone stands and several
charging cables and everything
everything like multiples
yeah like so prepared and I was like yo
this is so chill like I don't have to do
I don't have to bring anything I feel
like everything's prepared I feel
relieved
um
[Music]
foreign
let's spin the wheel and maybe you know
what we can do after each fulfilled
tangent I'm gonna read some super chats
how about that okay here we go
which one's gonna be oh
start with the best one because I got
all the photos
all right all right I appreciate that
okay okay
we're gonna talk about
enoshima with hachama and amenities
um
so
oh where do I even start
um so you know I mean it's your first
time in Japan right
and now a few things overlapped for this
to happen I was trying to figure out uh
I was trying to plan a collab of hachama
and now let me warn you it ain't
happening this time but it's gonna
happen next time I'm in Japan just you
know things didn't work out
um but that's okay
um so uh wait wait wait
okay
yeah it's okay but we got to hang out
you know but anyway so I was I was first
hoping to collab on uh Saturday with her
and
um I was like uh well if we can collab
then let's do something small beforehand
and if we can't collab then let's uh
just spent the whole day uh sightseeing
with Amit how about that because I at
the same time I asked ammo if she's free
if she wants to do something because I
want I I know that she hasn't been
um
uh like I don't know I feel like she
hasn't been seeing that much like
special stuff yet besides like and oh
wow arcades and more arcades and even
more arcades
so I felt like
I wanna I want I want to be in charge of
showing her something and there's one
place in Japan called enoshima that I've
been to many times I'm very very
um I have have confidence to show you
around
[Music]
so enoshima is outside of Tokyo actually
it's in a prefecture called Kanagawa and
you know that's where Yokohama is maybe
you heard of Yokohama and lots of cool
places in Kanagawa actually and it's
from Tokyo depending on from where in
Tokyo you depart it can take you
one hour to one hour 50 or so depending
on from where you leave off
uh-huh
oh yeah apparently recently there's an
anime
shows up
[Music]
that's interesting they made a trip to
enoshima that's so funny because it fits
perfectly with you know now now a lot of
you guys know about it if it wasn't for
an anime a lot of you guys wouldn't know
about it right yeah maybe I should watch
it I didn't watch it no
is it an early episode or one of the
later ones
just like me for real for real best
anime 2022
[Music]
foreign foreign
it's an island as you can hear in the
name but there's apparently also a big
aquarium that I've never went to before
I just always go to uh the island I've
been there so many times I've been there
in summer or like more like a spring
summer or so I've been there in Winter
or like fall I've been there in like
pretty much every season
example
[Music]
and I personally just think it's perfect
for a one day trip to see a cool place
that's kind of compact
uh outside of Tokyo uh very
instagramable
and uh yummy food special food special
they have some Specialties there and
they got a lot of stray cats too and
yeah it's a cool place so yeah so
[Music]
um
when it turned out that we can't stream
I was like all right let's do this
actually
it was a bit more complicated than that
first I was kind of losing my mind
uh because like
somehow I mean like I mean I'm gonna get
confused with the schedule so so she was
like sorry can't come with you guys
after all and then I told hatama sorry
so I know we can't stream but also
enoshima I kind of only chose because of
Ahmed if it wasn't for Amy I wouldn't go
there because I've been there a million
times
so uh let's just do something small
something else all right so then me and
hatima were talking about what else to
do and how about reserved uh uh a shadow
place for us we were just gonna you know
hang normally and then
the next morning
on Friday the day before am I was like
sorry I made a mistake actually
um I can't go so are we going and I'm
like I I yeah with this point we already
kind of canceled the enoshima but then
yeah she was saying and let's go and
then I'm like all right I'm sorry please
cancel that reservation because I think
we're gonna go to enoshima after all we
blah blah blah blah it was a such a long
back and forth and the thing is we
weren't even talking in a group I was
talking around corners so many corners
and edges trying to organize this
it was really chaotic and but finally
eventually when we set it in stone we
were going to enoshima yeah
voice can always be organized because
there always has to be an organizer it's
it's and it's and if I'm part of the
group then it always is me it's always
me
let me let me move to my uh did I write
down
sorry am I just relying on the photos
did I write something down
oh
I don't think I did
oh here here's my uh Yakiniku attention
okay okay yeah no I don't I don't need I
don't need tangent uh notes for this no
no no no okay ah but they saw this
tangent engine taking off
um
no no she she made a mistake she thought
like it was on the day where she was
collabing with bales
um but then she realized no and then she
came back to me and was like okay yeah
I'm free after all
um
we don't have to read super chats yeah I
mean
I'm like you know
far behind because me being sick and
then me traveling and all that but we
can always read them at something
they're not gonna disappear they're on
colonizer they're not gonna disappear
right
hi uh okay um
where do I even
so uh I said okay I made a group after
that after it was set in stone I finally
made a group called enoshima and then I
said hey let's meet helban 12 p.m is
that okay
and yes so
I started uh in the morning I went I
woke up and did my makeup and then I
jumped into a bus and then the bus I
jumped into the wrong bus actually so I
thought I would be late but turns out in
the end
I was
five minutes early
and it was actually cold and it was kind
of raining on the day so I was like
standing there uh
station if you ever guys if you guys
ever go to enoshima there's two stations
there's one called katase and Oshima and
then there's one called enoshima for
some reason I always end up using katase
um it's not like one is better than the
other but it's just depending on where
you're going from different lines will
travel from there and yeah
me nothing is
random facts yeah yeah if you want to go
to energy I really recommend it if you
guys go to to Japan especially maybe for
the four fans and you need like you need
to do something take inspiration from
your Oshi kiwawa and go to enoshima okay
um you could just type in type into
Google Maps and then go route route and
then it will tell you how to get there
from your
um Hotel no no no no no no okay
okay and I'm kind of um excited right
now right after Kirby Cafe well I think
you guys should reserve a whole day for
it though I mean you can spend less than
a day there but honestly the train ride
will already take you quite a while so
usually invest some time or maybe a
whole day and even if you have more than
like if you're done earlier with the
island you should do that during the
daytime and then after that maybe you
can go to the aquarium who knows or you
can go surfing because there's a for
some reason there were a lot of surfers
I was waiting you know and I saw like
tiny children that were like as Tiny as
where my waist ends oh no where my hip
ends I don't know how old you are when
you were that tiny
um and they were those tiny children
they were wearing like those surfing
wetsuits
and carrying the tiniest surfing board
that I have ever seen
ah thank you for membership
yeah very tiny and yeah they just came
from even though it was shitty as [\h__\h]
weather and cold they just came from
surfing yeah I guess if you live there
you go surfing even when it's shitty hmm
um
[Music]
surface it's so cool
um yeah
um so anyway eventually until I arrived
and the good thing is already so
handsome on the day before
[Music]
I think it was the day before was it a
Friday I think so well or the day before
before I'm not sure anymore but I
already saw her so there she was and I
was like
wait wait I didn't even say her name I
was like and then she's like haha and
you know recently when I've been
greeting members in the public I'm just
like bouncing bouncing bouncing
yeah I can't really say anything so
yeah yeah yeah and then you know on we
waited for Army am I kind of got lost
again so into no surprise
um
and then she oh
yeah me and hatama we're like chatting
until AMA came and Emma came and uh and
then we started speaking English yeah
and now I got herself a little umbrella
and then yeah
we walked over to the island there's
like a like a big bridge connecting the
main land to the island yeah and
[Music]
um walk
and talking English and I feel like
if
it was like almost like a a whole live
English collab
which is a funny statement but you know
why it felt like that to me because I
was the one constantly like asking
questions and throwing out topics
yeah yeah I think yeah
and that's I guess also recently but
yeah I was like constantly making the
communication at least in the beginning
I think like the other two maybe needed
some time to warm up
um but we were all kind of Chill on the
day
kind of just chilling
I'm it was a bit shy I think or just
chilling in her mind
no I really I really wanted
um to impress Amit and have her see
something nice
so
I will I I felt like if we just like are
quiet the whole time it will not be as
fun as it could be so yeah yeah
[Music]
um
so uh basically when you walk over the
bridge first you are greeted by like
a busy little Narrow Street I mean you
could go sideways but there's just one
main Narrow Street that kind of goes
upwards and will lead you to a big like
um today gate and lots of stairs and so
on and then that's straight there's like
a lot of tiny shops already like for
buying souvenirs and for buying like
already some food some restaurants
there's a big Spa that looks so good I
never went into the spa before but this
time it looked even better to me like
they have a pool and stuff in there so
cool like a nice nice Spa with Ocean
View but I would say on that day that
Ocean View didn't really help
yeah
[Music]
um
yeah so uh we first looked at like the
little shops and some food and so on but
uh we decided to not go like eat
anything there just yet we decided to go
eat in the restaurants that are like up
higher on like deeper into the island
um
so we went just like window shopping
and uh there was
ah there was one thing uh let me see if
I can find a picture
uh
that one thing that I bought before a
long time ago like actually several
times
um here let me use this
at enoshima yeah
and there's this thing
this thing here it's called marimo
um
yeah it's I guess it's a little like
moss ball inside some water it's like a
tiny cup yeah
and
you know I'm in love's moth right so I
felt like does it get any more perfect
than this it even says it's alive on the
on the that always fascinated me it says
on the packaging that this thing inside
there is a life and I'm like 20 minutes
alive will it get bigger it never did
get bigger but yeah
um
so we saw it in a souvenir shop and I
was like look look look look look look
this coke manual it's super cute it's
like a blue moss ball it's alive and
it's cute and I I bought one before and
brought it to Austria and so on and you
should count one don't you like this and
then she's like
hmm
she's like yeah no no no I can't I I'm
sure I can't bring that back it's
illegal you can't bring live things into
the to the into the airplane and so on
I'm like
I have traveled a million times more
than you for like long distance flights
whatsoever and I've brought this before
but it is they're not gonna take away or
like
like you shut you into jail or [\h__\h] for
bringing a little Moss ball
I mean
hey she brought illegal cashew nuts
before well there you go
um
us rules hey
whatever yeah I thought it would be
perfect but okay so she didn't get it
yeah
um and liquids yeah but
um no no liquids are only NG not okay if
you put it in your hand luggage but if
you put it in your Main Luggage it's
okay
hmm
anyway
s
[Music]
i I brought I brought it to Austria
before oh well oh well I mean in the end
you know she has probably Moss somewhere
else so
it's not even that alive it's not like
you're bringing a freaking Chicken in
your suitcase I don't know eh my
relatives had to smash a snow glove
because it contained liquids in the
American airports rejected it but did
they have it in their hand luggage on
their um check luggage because check
luggage should be okay
I'd be okay
plants RNG well the the one that one is
plastic the middle one it's just plastic
okay whatever I just you know if you
guys come here
get this little Mighty Mall okay it's
cute
get it I'm telling you to get it
all right all right all right okay
all right all right it's illegal
s
and so then then there's one weird thing
like I saw
this thing normally they sell normal ice
cream and [\h__\h] but on this day
or this season everything was
denim themed
yes I'm saying denim themed
and they had denim themed drinks and ice
cream and denim themed
uh
nikuman
uh what's it called an English
meatball yeah
so I didn't get that one but the photo
looked cool like this thing the setup
looked cool denim on denim those are not
real by the way but they were selling
real ones like denim colored meat buns
yeah yeah
because at the moment they had
everything done in frame they have like
you know here
I saw this like right next door was a
store that was selling everything denim
themed like clothes apparently
surfboards hats uh aprons everything in
denim shoes hmm
everything in denim
um
um I think they called it
uh denim
denim
denim Road or something like that
um I think it's a like just a Time
limited thing though
and they kind of collaborate with each
other making everything dead and famed
um also denim surfboard work well
obviously it probably doesn't work
it's just a joke
a jerk
yeah oh this dance is going to take a
long time guys the other tensions I
think will be shorter but trust me bro
don't don't don't leave me yet so they
had a hot chocolate with a denim colored
mint
no no the the whipped cream I think on
the hot chocolate
was probably mint flavored but denim
colored also so that's what am I ordered
and then after am I ordered it hachiman
was like oh I wanted to and they both
got it yeah but then Ahmed was like no
hatima was like walking around with her
hot chocolate a little bit and then
eventually you know because it was
raining but it was really only slightly
raining but when she walked under like
um like a
like like ceiling thing whatever
the rain dripped into her drink and it
kind of destroyed all like it was a lot
of like
and it destroyed all of her whipped
cream
yeah oh wow yeah I didn't mind I think
foreign
naturally flavored rain
like problem it's just a little bit of
water from the sky like whatever
[Music]
and yeah we consumed that and then uh we
walked up to there's like an you can
walk up the stairs like the the whole
island is kind of hilly kind of
mountainy and you can walk I've done it
many times but you can also be smart
like us this time because it was cold
anyway maybe if it was warmer I would
have said we should walk because that's
the end of Shima experience if you go
there for the first time if you don't
walk then you're lame
um but
and this time you can buy a ticket to
use an escalator yeah and there's like
three escalators with different like
stops and then you can write up but it
only goes up it doesn't go down and this
doesn't necessarily mean that you will
never have to walk up because after
going up to the very top and walking
around a little bit you will eventually
be going down to go to the cave and then
you have to walk back up again in order
to go down again
because you can't just walk around the
island after going down the cave you
have to walk all the way back up and
that was [\h__\h] exhausting later on
um but yeah it does it does help a lot
it takes away a lot of the painful uh
walking upstairs so
we bought a ticket and at the ticket
counter
for the escalator there was a cat
it was a funny cat he looks old and yeah
he was just standing right there in
front of the staff and in front of the
escalator
has a lot of stray cats but on this day
I only met two but don't worry I took
photos of both of them yeah he's an old
looking cat grumpy cat and I went up to
him and tried to take pictures and then
amen and hatima followed but Ahmed Ahmed
was especially like motivated to
interact with the old grumpy cat
um
I think
I think Japanese people are generally
kind of like overly cautious when it
comes to stray cats in terms of touching
them they normally don't touch them I
think
um now if I when I until I experienced
that caution I never gave a [\h__\h] and
would always touch stray cats in Austria
uh and I think Amazon is the same
because she wanted to touch the cat but
the cat wasn't so
impressed by us and and when Ahmed would
reach out her hand the cat went like
like
so we took the sign and we're like okay
okay before the cat decides to run away
let's give the cat its space yeah
spot on
it was kind of cute because it was just
like
in the middle of like this
place in front of the escalator and
everyone was like I can't
[Music]
um
he owns that place
I wish I don't know it would be kind of
cool to work at enoshima because I could
kind of like Get To Know older all the
all the cats that are frequently
visiting the area and live there and but
the cats that I've met
maybe it's not so visible in this
picture but this was a chunky wonky I'm
telling you it was a trunker
which he definitely looked like he eats
a lot gets fed well
the other one I met as well so I think
and enoshima they have a good time
they're happy Stray Cats
um
it's definitely not hungering
it was very healthy yeah yeah
so ah oh wait ah we checked out the cat
but then we didn't go straight into the
escalator actually I was like wait
before we take this escalator let me
tell let me show you
kind of a secret but not so secret spot
and then I always check out
um when I go to enoshima and so we walk
to the other side and I took them
through a secret she could path that no
one ever takes
um it's kind of a weird path because it
goes through like kind of a graveyard
there's a somehow there's a little
graveyard but it's kind of like
like not like so out in the open
obviously but through the graveyard
there's like tiny stairs Tiny Steps
and and it leads down to there's a
different path too actually but
um I I somehow take that pop and I was
like trust me trust me girls follow me
don't worry this will be a cool
um view okay and then
ah
we got to here I I know
it doesn't look so cool here but that's
mostly because of the shitty weather
in the summer it looks better but after
arriving here I felt like you know what
maybe maybe maybe this wasn't as special
as I thought it was to me it's really
special because this little place it has
like Memories to me there's memories
here you know
[Music]
okay this is awkward it doesn't look as
cool as it did in my mind but I mean Amy
found something to do
Anna started vlogging down the shore
with
um a constantly like she was like bowing
down to find some stuff in the sand she
was looking for crabs especially the
whole day she was looking for crabs yeah
did not really find a single alive crap
maybe some I think we found one tiny
hermit crab that was alive
um
so but she was looking for crabs and
other interesting things and so me and
had to adjourn and looked like for some
like cute pretty uh shells and so on
yeah yeah imma does is I'm gonna do
exactly I feel like oh thank God you
know Amy likes nature so even this
shitty place not looking as as pretty as
I thought in a winter shitty weather
even this gives her something to do and
she would like several times
the waves would get her and
thank God her boots were apparently uh
waterproof yeah but they got very very
very wet many times
um
I was like are you sure it's waterproof
she's like oh I don't know I think so
maybe
she seemed okay throughout the day yeah
yeah
yeah and so she found some some some
stuff and referred him back into the
water and then this and that and we just
spent some time there and then we went
back to the escalator
and yeah then we went up the first
escalator and the first escalator
I feel like
um
foreign
I feel like in the past I might be wrong
so I was asking Japanese Bros if they
know but I feel like in the past the
escalator was just out in the open
outside
sure
oh
my theory has been approved
back in the day those escalators were
out in the open
and we went there this time and I'm like
this
what is like
enclosed now in in walls and ceiling and
on the walls there's uh projectors
several big ass projectors that project
onto the left wall some like aquarium
footage really cool aquarium like
jellyfish footage no I think it was the
right one no I'm not sure it doesn't
matter but there's a bunch of big ass
projectors and everyone was like holy
[\h__\h] this must be really expensive and
I'm like you know I'm just fascinated
that there's walls what
foreign
[Music]
big big Improvement
so after you go up the first I think
this is what we saw let me check yeah
yeah yeah
after you go up the first one
you come out and see this this is
exactly what you see once you come out
of the escalator there's a like a shrine
over there right there's several shrines
on the island though and on the right
side you know where the people with the
umbrellas are standing I'll show you
what's there in a second on the left
side you
um tie your fortune if you got a bad
fortune that you didn't like
and yeah so um
and on the right side
let me show you the picture
now
there is this
uh
a donate magical donation box in front
of a dragon statue
in the water
so the challenge here is to throw your
coins your donation into the donation
box without
missing it
foreign
first throws a coin Mrs yeah
where where is your aim of it huh aim
doko
yeah
and then next goes hatama throws a coin
the donation box flawlessly
and I was like [\h__\h] why didn't I film it
then Amazon froze again misses and I'm
like
and I'm like wait I want to film this
now I don't have the video right now but
I might upload it like later on Twitter
so I'm like okay I'm fine with now throw
it one more time I'mma froze again ow on
video and she misses the first time
he's got a first try and she nailed it
I'ma just misses Mrs Mrs
foreign
[Music]
it was funny then we gave up I didn't
throw because
um
I don't know I was busy taking pictures
so then we went up to the uh the shrine
that you saw we lined up and I was like
um
you know here for what like a week or so
I don't know and I asked her so amen you
must have been to a shrine by now right
this is not your first try this right
and she said she only went to like one
tiny random ass one like there's big
shrines right and but there's also a lot
of like smaller ones smaller shrines
scattered throughout the whole like
every city in Japan like tiny ones like
really tiny in between like buildings
any ones just for people who like just
want to quickly go to Shrine before
going to work or in the break or
whatever it's really
so she went to like a tiny tiny tiny
tight and didn't really know what to do
either right
um yeah but I felt like what the hell
how how how
gonna go to big one now here she had
like a relatively big one a special one
that's for sure
[Music]
so uh we lined up and I worked in the
shrine before as you know as a Mikko
um
foreign
[Music]
but I kind of forgot a little bit uh
what the right order and so on is and I
don't I don't think there I've talked to
Japanese people before and there is no
right older people even Japanese people
do it a little bit differently
[Music]
ah
Naruto Domino
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
tonight
okay okay I'm trying to figure out you
know if there's like rules for real
because like when I with my previous
experiences
there is no like right way no no like
100 like the right way to do it but
there is one most
um seemingly right way to do it but you
don't have to do it that way so if you
want to know remember this and next time
you'll be safe you look like you know
what you're doing you go up to the
shrine
possibly you should already have your
coin prepared there's no set amount of
money that you have to throw in you can
just even throw in like five cents
um I think most people throw in like
something like maybe two or three
hundred Yen coins Maybe
midnight
yeah
going oh go ahead okay there's actually
a good excuse for you to throw in five
uh Yen which is like
scent is because Golian
five five Yen sounds like like go in
it's like like like a nice nice word in
Japanese
hmm
Julian
is not good
yeah it's like a luck luck Strat
okay okay so you have the coins ready
okay and you go up to the shrine and
um
[Music]
so first you throw in the money and then
you
about two times and then touch patch and
then keep the hands together
and think of something nice maybe pray a
little bit
wait a little bit
if there's someone next to you then
don't go walk away immediately okay
even if you have had empty moment
just wait a little bit maybe like 30
seconds
give the impression that you're
thinking of something meaningful
foreign
[Music]
so
foreign
this time there was no Bell I think
it was this place by the way this was
where we were doing it
um
[Music]
oh
okay oh
oh no hold up okay in case there is a
bell
following pattern throwing money cutting
cutting
ring the bell
head empty
[Music]
and then hmm
yeah
but you can't really do it wrong people
do it different sometimes sometimes they
only bow once sometimes they even clap
after they had their praying moment so
they clap like four times in the end and
so on
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes did you notice the Triforce I knew
you guys would be like oh because you
know also
[Music]
was very noticeable to me and I was like
try Voice Triforce and she was like
understanding I was like what the [\h__\h]
did you never play Zello what the [\h__\h]
she said no but even if you never played
Zelda don't you know the Triforce
especially because aren't you like a
gamer what the [\h__\h] foreign
[Music]
and I'm curious because this is not the
only place where I've seen triforces in
Japan before
um but generally on nanoshima I saw it a
lot
oh my god I've been talking for over an
hour
[Music]
without one tangent today this is the
longest story I have though okay it's a
whole day so stay with me
[Music]
ah
um
going back to bed what the [\h__\h]
is getting into it
foreign
okay so we did that and then
um I made us get fortunes and we got
fortunes and well we all just had like
decent normal luck uh yeah I tried
translating it a bit for Ahmed what her
Fortune had
um but I was like wait this is not it
this is not it last time I went to
energy I saw something really special
somewhere they have a more special
fortune that I want us to get so I was
on the lookout okay but
at The Shrine hatama went to get a
Goshen uh like a stamp you know what I
talked about with I am a senpai at these
shrines every Shrine has like their own
stamp and you can get it for a little
book atama didn't bring her book but she
got a really special stamp thingy
um like time limited edition and while
she was getting that um
it was like standing in front of this
thing and it caught her attention
foreign
guys
okay to just to talk about this
what do you think you're calling your
attention
yes Moss
like she would look at plants and all
that a lot she was also really
fascinated by some trees that she saw on
the Island the island has cool trees
I'll give you that yeah yeah trees that
don't really exist outside of
um like I guess so like maybe maybe
outside of Japan but not outside of
maybe Asian countries I don't know
um
so this little statue
um there was kind of like standing at a
shrine right next to the other Shriner
showed you like literally back to back
and I don't know how that works like is
there like don't they like you know what
about the God competition like
is there like a rivalry going on or
anything like is it okay to have your
it's like having like two different
convenience stores right next to one
another like aren't you like like you
know intervening in each other's
businesses I don't know how that works
like yeah
but uh here this one was covered this is
not the shrine though this was next to
the shrine kind of protecting the shrine
I guess but it had it was covered in
Moss so first she's like it takes a
little piece of moss and then she puts
back
she was just showing me the Moss I'm
like oh cute
and then she goes closer closer and
she's like look Kiara look
she's like look at this
and she tells me what it is and I forgot
what it is but she says it also is
called like the Shrek's ears and I'm
like you're right
look at that it's hard to see in my
picture but
um look at
do you see the ones that are like
standing out sticking out she's right it
looks exactly like Shrek's ears
yes yes
[Music]
somebody once told me
call Cali
uh yeah that was cool it really looked
like Shrek's ears but that's such a
detail you see it's it's um this photo
is on like below the pause of this thing
so you know how she pays attention to
these tiny things
man
see I wouldn't have looked at that and I
wouldn't have noticed that
yeah
something you wouldn't notice without um
exactly I like how we take Hamilton's
special place and I'ma gets distracted
by Chris no no no no the thing though
the thing though is that if she were in
the middle of talking on the day I don't
think she would have seen much Moss so
this was like a moss Paradise for her
okay I think she appreciated everything
about it
yeah yeah nature
so and then I found
I found it
I think we took one more escalator
um we didn't stay in that area for long
it's like really just those couple
shrines next to each other and then you
take another escalator and then there's
another Shrine and more like places to
get fortunes Etc and and and uh so I
found it there was one special
special Fortune
we gotta get this one we gotta get this
one girls we have together I know we
just got one boy we need another one
it's a fortune that is
invisible
vegetables
um
invisible Fortune I'm like don't worry
I know how we will see what's up with it
you know I was raining a little bit so
they already noticed
that something's happening with the
water yeah yeah
but then I was like don't don't look at
it yet no don't try to say we're holding
it up into the sky trying to get catch
the raindrops and read it through there
but no I was like No just come here and
then there was a little like um
like a water fountain thingy um in the
back where usually there was like like a
kind of a Scoopy thingy but for some
reason it was missing on that day so the
only thing we were able to do is uh
lay it on top of the water
yeah
so once it comes in contact with water
you can read what it says
um
I think the left one the big luck one
laughs
may have been hachama I think
and I think I was too kichi the middle
one
no
may have been I'm not sure I don't know
but we had like a middle luck and then
another minute
a bit confused in the order of these
though because there's like middle luck
and just normal luck I don't know which
one is more like better
kitchen
over there
[Music]
but no none of us had like really bad
luck
or not all of us were above decent luck
so uh pretty pretty good gotcha I would
say yeah write up is not a lie I would
say Okay
um
foreign
[Music]
s they're kind of written in like
fancy speech
so let me see
it's hard to read from here
[Music]
can you guys read it
you don't know
you man oh
no no no no no no
lost
wait what does it say for love
Yoku
something something
you know
oh for for
um studies that says you'll be fine if
you study well done
[Music]
for love it says look at your partner
and then go on
um
I think I still have mine in my in my
jacket pocket one second which one was
me yeah I still have it oh but I can't
read it it disappeared again
I have some water here since I'm gonna
make a mess if I
wait maybe if I spray the
um I have some disinfection
spray so if I spray this on it oh
does that work uh
or or does disinfection not work does it
have to be what
I didn't see whatever it is
oh no wait
at least let me read like which one the
top just the top thing so I know which
one's mine okay kitty okay mine was
Cutie mine was the um normal just just
luck just luck
foreign
the big luck one says give love to
people
and and the left one says for study she
says don't worry and use the practice
and says
[Music]
um
wait wait I think the middle one might
have been amen
oh
for traveling it says
don't go too far what
is
um
well that's a problem
if that was Ave then that might be a
problem
oh I think yeah I think that might have
been on there what about it
[Music]
foreign
for the left one let's say that one was
Ahmed because I'm not sure anymore it
says just um to plan everything properly
and yeah
then yeah ahead of time yeah
if that one's I'm in then uh we're also
having a problem because she did not
really plan much
[Laughter]
oh yeah well I mean that's okay though I
think we're okay
what else what else
hmm
oh birth birth okay we have some birth
information
the the big luck one left one which I
think was awesome but I'm not sure and
says she'll have a she'll have a uh a
comfortable birth but be careful of what
comes after
foreign and the middle one says
oh okay middle one also has a
um a comfortable easy going burp and it
should uh be careful
of
the parents your own parents or yourself
I'm not sure
hmm yeah yeah and and me
mine is kind of like disappearing but it
does kind of say I think that I would
have an easy birth
Young
what does mine say about traveling uh it
Suited
I think my travel lock says
I'll be okay
it says if I'm if I don't go alone I'll
be fine but I always travel alone but I
didn't meet a lot of people here I just
I just go there alone
um
[Music]
it might not be about you know the
flight it might just be about what comes
after the flight I'm not sure it just
depends on how you see it I guess
um
I like reading fortunes
I like them
I mean I'm not like
what's the word superstitious
um well I think reading these are these
things is funny to me open to
interpretation exactly
foreign
[Music]
no like I don't necessarily believe
what's written here but I like reading
it you know I don't I don't believe it
[Music]
yeah but it's funny when it's like
accurate
yeah
fortunes are fun yeah
um
[Music]
don't worry my fortune is already
um uh dry at least the part where I put
alcohol on it
wait let me see if on the same spot if I
put water now it's gone forever
careful careful
oh yes it still works wait no
[Music]
oh yeah I think
I think
where I put the alcohol
the pot is gone
um
it's okay I got a photo of it I have a
photo of it I don't have a photo of it I
killed the fortune oh [\h__\h] yep
[Music]
[Laughter]
play invisibly yeah it's just like uh
this is the Big Blob like let me show
you
I'll take a photo I'll take a photo it's
[Music]
ah
wait
downloading from Discord oh [\h__\h] what
did I open what's that
[Music]
this is what it looks like now I can
read the kitty but
foreign
disinfectant
you read it I have a picture for
eternity
[Music]
it's okay it's funny
okay okay continue the tangent
an attempt was made
so okay let me go back to my picture
folder
okay yeah all right so then after uh we
did that thing with the fortune we just
walked around and went on another
escalator then when I reached the top
and you know with the escalator ticket
you can get a escalator ticket that
comes with a thank you logical pair of
dogs
two
uh what was I saying
uh oh yeah it comes with a ticket for
the sea candle which is like a like a
lighthouse thingy on top of the island
that I've never been up to before so
actually even though I went to ignition
moment many times there was something I
haven't seen there before too so I took
the chance but on the way to the sea
kennel there was like a little Park
um that had so many like cute
decorations and flowers and all kinds of
cute gardening and terrariums which I
was like this is good for I mean just
I'm gonna like this I'm able like this
yeah she did like it
there were a lot of terrariums yeah we
inspected them and then it was like this
cool thing was kind of cute like small
little thing it was really small
um
good and instagramable this picture is
huh Mr Instagram
it looks like it was taken with a uh
uh like a proper camera what do you call
the one with the
reflector [\h__\h] inside
no filter though but look at the
bulkhead
DSLR I guess so yeah put a bouquet at
the back okay
wow I love this level I'm like
Arrow Arrangement is so cute with the
enoshima found in the front it's so cute
there are so many of those like all over
and I think this picture
oh I'm not sure what I was trying to
capture with it but I guess just a
general like overall Vibe it was really
empty on this day probably because of
the rain and just this big uh Garden
Park thingy was just generally empty I
would say but
um Japanese people love like lighting up
uh like trees and so on in the winter
time so it was the sun was like starting
to set like slowly because it was just
really cloudy so we could already see
everything glowing and yeah they went
like there was like soft cream and like
a little cafe things pop-up cafes and so
on everywhere and you see how things are
glowing and the decorations on the trees
have every winter themed and so on yeah
and one more one more this
Hmm this they got like what
oh so so much like in the summer this
doesn't look like this in summer I guess
it's just lots of flowers blooming and
so on but yeah
apparently there's a Miami Beach square
that you can go to yeah yeah Miami
pretty sorry and without filters they
don't look that good but it looked
pretty cool in in reality and then it
was like this
wow
perfect to walk through as a couple and
take some cute pages together I was just
taking pictures of the thing without a
couple I mean there is a couple in there
though
yeah this was it was so pretty like even
though it wasn't dark it was already
glowing so blue imagine this when it's
dark
we walked through this together yeah we
weren't a couple we were tripled
animated no doesn't animate it was just
constantly glowing
it reflects on the ground though yo it's
also blue hmm
with a couple of the toilets
[Music]
for you to fall
would probably look amazing during the
evening yeah the whole park though like
everywhere everywhere on the trees on
the ground there was like everything
yeah yeah like a Christmas tree all the
time all the time but if you go in
summer it won't be like this I'm pretty
sure it will be more like flower focused
I would say yeah and yeah and then we
went up to the Sea candle oh
[Music]
um
which I posted on Twitter this picture
now this one's actually with a filter so
it's prettier but yeah lots of flowers I
was surprised to see some flowers that
were glooming yeah
lots of tulips and then up there you see
the sea Cannon we went up there with an
elevator and normally with good weather
you can go outside on an observation
deck but it was closed
the observation deck was trimmed
um so we couldn't go there but we still
got a really cool View
and one photo I took up the view I also
uploaded on Twitter this is the bridge
that I talked about that you have to
walk over to get to the island and
yeah over there that's still kind of
enoshima if you walk of the bridge to
the left side over another Bridge that's
where katase enoshima station is but if
you walk over the bridge and then just
go straight that's where the enoshima
station is
but as you can see the weather was kind
of shitty yeah
but it was so cool I honestly feel like
you know
um with
if the weather was perfectly clear with
not a single cloud in the sky it would
be kind of boring I mean the view would
be clear and we could have seen fujisan
but I like like layers of lots of
dramatic looking different shaped uh
clouds I thought it was really cool
yeah tour guide Wawa yeah
oh about those layers yeah I love those
layers
foreign
[Music]
don't think Emma could have gotten a
better tour guide then yeah yeah I hope
she liked it
um yeah uh she actually also put in some
money in like uh on on top of here they
had like binoculars yeah she put in some
money and we all took a look but it was
so difficult to look through it like uh
haven't used one of those in a long long
time but why are they so difficult to
look through like my eyes were so
confused I was like
it felt so weird
I don't know why
hmm
[Music]
good boy
I really zoomed in yeah yeah but like
it's more I mean like I don't know my
eyes were so confused
because a headache when looking at it
yeah but we we were looking for it was
kind of cool yeah yeah
[Music]
after that we're like okay now we have
to find a restaurant and so we walked a
little bit more towards the cave there
were signs that led us through cave and
on the way to the cave there's like a
lot of uh cool restaurants that all kind
of sell the same stuff
um one specialty
uh in enoshima that I think
none of us
ended up getting
it's
like tiny white bait I looked it up it's
called White bait tiny white fish
um
they have them like in on rice balls or
they also fry them like tempura
and so on uh yeah
um
[Music]
I'm sorry yeah
um
I think I'm I'm actually I have to say
both on this occasion and on the when we
went Yakiniku grilling meat
um I felt a little bit more
how to say
validated
because I wasn't the only one
who didn't enjoy
everything
I would I wouldn't say that white bait
is such a like weird uh obscure thing to
eat at all to me that seems way less
obscure than eating octopus for example
I would be less scared to eat the white
bait than because it's just tiny ass
fish but yeah you know but yeah we just
both didn't feel like ordering something
like that I don't know actually I'm at
the whole time said she wanted to eat
crab so at every restaurant I was
checking the menu if they had crab but
surprisingly they all had a lot of
seafood but no one had crap I'm
surprised I was surprised I mean I know
it's not their leg specialty here but I
thought at least like one or two
restaurants would have some crab but no
no one had crab nuggets
but no crab no crap for I mean
unfortunately so in the end and she
ordered let me check the picture one
more time
yes I censored the soup
and she ordered tempura
and look at that bottom left that fancy
like
shell thing snail
thing
clam whatever and in the temple I was
like live
um like some vegetables and uh uh
what's it shrimp shrimp big shrimp yeah
and I actually so Emma was like don't
you like temper I'm like um if it were
yeah it depends on what's inside but you
know I'm always like you know I want to
try more things
um especially recently I feel like I
want to try more things that I haven't
tried before and I feel scared of eating
but then if I especially if I eat Alone
um if I order something and I'm like I
can't eat it then I feel sorry to the
restaurant and the people around me that
I'm just gonna leave everything
so I can only really end it if someone
like lets me try theirs I guess maybe
let me uh take a bite from her big
shrimp tempura
and she said it tastes like a chicken so
I was like actually a bit relieved
beforehand and
yes surprisingly I never tried it before
this is one of the things you would
think like at least that you can try
right at some point no I didn't and then
I did and uh it was fine oh I mean
it was fine
it was edible
Italian
[Music]
did you
know
now the thing is Ahmed didn't only order
this she also ordered
a way bigger portion than we expected of
jarusoba
I'm in town
so imagine all this
so in order to support Ahmed all three
of us shared the soba
and I still cannot slurp the doodles
oh [\h__\h] it's two hours
[Music]
that's okay it's okay it's okay it's
okay
this is the biggest main story that I
wanted to tell today anyway the most
important one
man
um
foreign
[Music]
this and I I think it was
I forgot I think it was
hmm maybe it was actually
no I forgot what it was there's some
tempura in there I guess it's maybe like
tempura udon something like that but I
think it was a bit more special than
that
kakiyage
it might have been yeah
which is
no no no no
um
was eating this
uh
[Music]
oh Denton foreign
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
the reason I'm so sorry is because
enoshima all the restaurants focus on
seafood and I was just too scared to
order something that I wouldn't be able
to eat so I went for something that I
could eat
[Music]
foreign foreign
I did this before I did this before like
many a couple not so many couple years
ago when I went with an Austrian friend
to anusima I showed her around yeah and
she loves ikura those little fish balls
the orange dragon balls right
um so she ordered like a
ordered something proper on the menu
yeah like an ikura Don something like
that and I ordered katsudon packet then
as well
salmon eggs was it salmon is that salmon
eggs yeah okay then that's that yeah
feels more proper to order that than to
order katsudon but it was really good
oh and I wanted to show you just so you
get a feeling of you know the Vibes
um
[Music]
we had a nice Corner seat on tatami mats
on pillows Japanese style on the floor
with a view of enoshima Cloudy view but
still a view
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
to like have the Japanese experience
yeah it was comfy and on for drinks
for drinks you know everything I want to
drink and Ahmed was gonna go for water
and I said Emma don't worry here they
will not scold you for ordering only
water and they will not force you to
order anything else don't worry this is
like a different kind of place you don't
have to order a drink
um but then I ordered
uh float floating float ice cream float
metal soda and then I saw it and she was
like oh
okay I want that and then hatima also
ordered it now it's
[Music]
um
so we all got we got matchings matching
can you even call it matching but we got
here
they're so good I love I love that
that's a thing like putting vanilla ice
cream on like a drink like this
because it's so good it's like you have
a drink at a dessert at the same time
it's so green yeah it's melon soda it's
really good you guys should get the
Minnesota ice cream float when you're in
Japan they have done a lot of Cafe menus
for drinks lots of places have it it was
quite a quite a tablet quite a normal
drink yeah
it's really good
why does Japan only have these ideas
yeah I have never seen this before in
Austria I don't know about America
or other countries
but I feel like maybe it's like an Asian
thing I don't know
is it bubbly yeah yeah you can see the
bubbles on the photo
root beer float ah you you
not even ice cream can save that drink
[Music]
foreign
like chooses the same thing that I do
because she like it seems like she
trusts me and also it seems like she got
excited um so she liked what I ordered
and then you know I know it makes me
happy I feel I feel like you know I feel
like a success because of that yeah
[Music]
so okay here let me get rid of all these
pictures
um
okay
oh and while we were chilling and eating
Amy's like what is that what is that
building over there I'm like what what
how do I how am I supposed to see the
same thing that you're seeing so she was
really curious about this one building
though so I tried I tried to find it and
she Zooms in with her shitty phone and
takes a picture and I look at it and I'm
like uh okay I know now what bill you
mean but in your camera quality is so
[\h__\h] let me zoom in with my phone and
then everyone was like so fascinated by
what how good my phone Zoom is but
actually I have two phones and I feel
like my older phone has a better Zoom
than my current phone my Samsung
um but look at this
conscription
[Music]
anyway it stood out to her
so maybe Japanese people know what it is
so I can tell I'm and she was like
really curious
foreign
well if you look at the edges
[Music]
boat shaped building no it's all shaped
like a boat we were thinking that maybe
they're in the middle of building it and
that's why it looks like I don't know or
order in the middle of tearing it apart
who knows
[Music]
welcome to geographer
um
yeah yeah
oh it's like super far from enoshima
hmm
well
Lonnie
what's going on
walk around
yeah oh well anyway
that's their food
we started our descent to the cave and
Ahmed didn't know yet what was about to
hit her
but
um yeah we walked down and we walked
past some more this and that oh wait I
forgot
the shuttle
somewhere I saw this kitokato
it was so cute because like you know it
was raining and the whole floor was wet
but there was just like close to this
like entrance to the park there was a
one area a little area where it wasn't
wet so of course the cat is like
chilling there and it was also pretty
chunky cat and Cat and fluffy yeah it
was slowly and this one actually we
tried to get closer to it and I'mma try
to touch it and I think yeah she let it
let the cat sniff
and then she actually did touch the cat
a little bit yeah only a little bit
though just a little quick Swatch and
then yeah
so Tabby yeah I think so
cat is scarfing no a little less fat
than Garfield
yeah
oh by the way since like
um we noticed that there were so many
cats and Amma was talking about going to
a Monkey Island or whatever no no no no
no not an island but a monkey place
um we like talked about the fact that
Japan has like so many like places with
just like where for some reason a lot of
like specific animals gather like
there's I think an island or place for
like a lot of cats and an island or a
place for a lot of uh foxes I think and
one for bunnies
and then apparently one for monkeys so
yeah yeah rabbits um
[Music]
foreign
or so why do they all come to one place
[Music]
time I want to go to the bunny one and I
want to go to the cat one I want to go
to these places
and the fox one oh
oh yeah
yeah and then Amma told me about this um
Island
story and it was kind of sad told me
about an island where dogs
thousands of dogs
tens of thousands of dogs are
because I don't know they left some some
big dogs there and then they made more
dogs and then you know there's um
apparently just a few humans there but
there's mostly dogs the story of it is
kind of sad
you know it's real anyway
So eventually we reached this place
and I got really excited
because before you reach this place
there was like another place like this
right before before you go for another
like kind of like tiny not really I
can't even call it a cave but it looks
similar to that and I was like where
where
before Oh it might have been after this
I'm not sure anymore oh actually never
mind this might have been before
maybe I'm not sure anymore that looks so
similar there was like two places right
one after another you don't even know
what I'm talking about but you see here
the the stairs that go down yeah so we
went down there because when you walk
down there
I just I just
I cannot get enough of this scenery
and yeah we chilled there for quite some
time
the reflection was so cool and this is
what I mean like look at that that would
have been boring if the sky was clear
the clouds is what makes it so cool and
the summer setting or isn't that pretty
and it reflects on a really really like
sheer
what's the word like when the water is
so
like so not narrow uh what's the word
what does it say no
you help me shallow yeah it's not even
shallow it's like it's just like one so
oh a little layer of water
but I guess it's shallow and still and
calm yeah
yeah on on the on the
stones and sometimes some big waves
would come and go like swoosh but mostly
this area was like shallow and you could
walk around and like bounce but it's
kind of slippery so you got to be
careful and I actually eventually like
kind of like not really fell but I
stumbled and then I like I kind of sat
down in style but
um
I sat down on something on some like
surface that was kind of dirty so my
pants got really dirty no oopsie I was
like oh no it doesn't look like I pooped
my pants and then Emma was like no no
don't worry everyone looks fine when you
when it um dries
um and I had someone to give me a tissue
to like wipe wrap the dirt on my ass
didn't really help much but don't worry
I I was able to finally wash my clothes
today in the hotel hmm
and when you're not being shallow could
be so pretty oh interesting because like
oh oh word play some some people who are
too pretty can't be very shallow right
but this shallowness
is just so pretty oh
oh
oh the word play yeah anyway where's the
chat oh oh here you are hi
it's kind of Blended in with my
background yeah and
let me get rid of that
um so anyway we were spending quite some
time here and I'm I'm it was like I
think I really like this place which I'm
glad like I just liked it because of the
reflections and just this I don't know
it was a beautiful scenery that just
makes me feel like I'm free and makes me
feel at peace and Serene and I don't
know man but amen
Amy started harassing
and the monies but she said anemone or
whatever
it was harassing them
yeah she was like oh look here's an
anemone and here's an enemy and he's an
anemone do we have a stick there is
there a stick then she I got her stick
and then she like poked the enemies and
she's just like look look they move and
then they like kind of close them so
like [\h__\h] off yeah but she kept on doing
that
yeah I know her pronunciations but I
think anemone would be better
foreign
[Music]
maybe she's gonna say like two sentences
about it and that's where the story ends
so you're welcome you're welcome yeah
she'll tell it now we'll see about that
and I'm I I'm curious how much she's
gonna tell about it she would definitely
not tell you the littlest things of
herself do you see those you're just
getting from me but she would not she
would probably not tell you that she
found Shrek ears on the Statue and and
you know the little tiny cool things
they're telling you about her that she
was looking for crabs and then she was
doing this and then
why do I do this because I know you the
teammates will enjoy it so yeah
she barely even mentioned she was there
exactly
ah
the teammates deserve to know that I'm
enjoyed herself
I'm telling you
so yeah that was that was so kind of
cute though because honestly I would
just look at this bigger picture though
right again like with the shrine where
the the Shrek ears were I would look at
the bigger picture but I'mma notices
these small things I would have never
noticed the enema needs
in the water
but yeah she she saw those and then she
was also looking uh and I think she
found some hermit crabs and so on
finally
ABS she found the crabs
yeah yeah yeah
and I actually I took some I was talking
taking some nice pictures of the scenery
and then I uh somehow at some point you
know I asked how to take some pictures
of me and then the other way around like
she said oh oh your camera takes nice
pictures can you take some of me so I
took some cute nice pictures of hatama
and I I think I took some nice pictures
of her because she actually told asked
me okay mama can you send me those
pictures later they look so good I'm
like a pro photographer
yeah and then and then I I became like
the perfect like I would say like
Instagram boyfriend because
like even after she stopped posing for
me like later she would like stand in
the just imagine her on this picture
standing in the distance like looking
standing like really on the edge there
and like looking in the far distance
like you know and I took pictures of
that like really cool pictures yeah
candid like really wow emotional
beautiful scene scenery shots yeah with
her just standing there
poetic pictures yeah
thank you
no look pose yes yes yeah yeah those are
those are just better yeah
um
[Music]
hmm
oh 27 months thank you
Okay so okay
yeah
um I honestly didn't even want to leave
this place because I was just so
beautiful every corner every like
surface looks so beautiful to me and
then I took I found some Burbs
to this
is not genius am I I might be a genius
look at that you see those birds well I
love the contrast at this point
the shadow contrast was like
off the roof huh limitations
I just oh my God
wow
tiny rooms and they were tiny tiny we
actually saw like a lot of big burps oh
okay we saw a lot of big birds and
um I saw later on
there was like a sign that said what
kind of birds you seen in Oshima
and it was like like some Hawk
and I think like we saw a lot of those
Hawks like kind of small
Hawks and
throughout the day oh tomorrow
sometimes would say oh there's a
dragonfly
isn't it too cool for dragonflies maybe
I guess maybe she did see a dragonfly of
course
you know and then later she would say it
again and when we were sitting in the
restaurant she was sitting across me so
she said outside the window oh see a
dragonfly there's a dragonfly I'm like I
guess I can't see it from my point of
view
yeah but uh then
I was so confused because then she said
in Japanese
[Music]
she said
oh yeah yeah yeah
she said I think she said that because
maybe first she translated
and she mistyped because tombi is a
black card or so
but Tomball is dragonfly
yeah yeah yeah yeah so after seeing a
dragonfly a million times and even
showing me the translation like kind of
confirming that she's looking for a
dragonfly
eventually she finally realized because
I'm like what do you mean I don't see
them
I finally realized she meant tombi not
tombow
um
yeah I thought something was weird
something was off there but I mean
finally really that I realized she's
talking about the kites the Hawks um
anyway after finally leaving this place
we walked by a stone turtle
that I only took a video of that I might
upload later but there was like a
special view
um from the bridge if you look down
there's
um a stone turtle in the water
and I was like look look guys there's a
stump turtle and they're like
yeah
and then you finally reached a cave and
I showed you guys a video on Twitter in
case you didn't see it
uh there was like a cape video right it
looked kind of like this
inside and it would switch to like blue
uh and there were two caves actually you
have to pay to get in by the way but I
think it was like four bucks or
something like that and I'm gonna be
honest here
it might not be worth looking inside
it's not that big I mean for four bucks
and if you're already there then okay
why not but don't expect too much I've
been here a few times and
I feel like it's less cool now they have
they added these cool lights so that
that's kind of cool and you get like a
little like a little Lantern for only a
small section see where I was holding
this land our lanterns together to take
this picture
um
[Music]
good night foreign
not that big and there was like
something that I feel like was different
a couple years ago
that was like in the second cave some
kind of like Dragon Tiny Dragon Shrine
or something at the end of the path of
the cave and I think a couple years ago
there was some kind of mechanism that I
remember trying out where you ask a
question or something and then it
answers you with lighting up I think
once or twice and depending on how many
times it lit up and made noises you
would get the answer but I was looking
forward to that and now somehow that
whole mechanism was gone and I'm like
wait did I imagine that but no it's
actually gone so it's even less
interesting now is
foreign
[Music]
foreign yeah so uh the dragon was still
there and I was like you know Anna was
like we were walking in the cave and
Emma was like how long is this I didn't
like this she was scared of like maybe
earthquakes or volcano breakout or
whatever and I have to say the ceiling
is incredibly low like we had to duck
walking through it in some spaces
and she was kind of like
not feeling so comfortable and I was
like don't lie it's not so long and at
the end there's a there's a dragon that
will tell you that you can talk to so uh
we arrived but the dragon didn't talk to
us anymore I don't know why they changed
it but then we went back I asked her if
she's claustrophobic and she said no not
really
um but you know just like caves like
this are scary to her
because I mean I understand in theory
she made a valid argument because Japan
has a lot of earthquakes so she was like
what is an African earthquake happened
and I said well okay that makes a lot of
sense but but I know Japan gets
earthquakes all the time if it was
dangerous I don't think they would let
people in there in the first place
because they know they have a lot of
earthquakes
um
[Music]
foreign
come on
um
well okay Japanese people are saying
that well I mean if there was such a big
earthquake that would make the cave uh
like kind of start falling apart then
that means it would also be dangerous to
be outside anyway
but it seems like well in this area
Canto area doesn't have so many like
like really big earthquakes that really
affect something like this
maybe once in you know
a long time
but as I said if that were really an
issue then they would not let people in
here I would say you know Japanese
people are very aware of their
earthquake so they built their buildings
to you know withstand such things and I
don't think they would like
risk something like that
for an attraction
but I understand the Vlog like obviously
especially you know
um it's a scary place and it's kind of
like
um you have to duck it's small so I get
it I get it mine was a short very short
experience as I said I don't know if
it's worth going in here because it's
really short
it's not that like super special
ah
um
[Music]
and yeah after we left the cave it was
getting pretty dark and when we went
back up the stairs and I was dying
because feet very spaghetti weak and
breath very very asthma
um I at least took a break for a moment
to take a picture of this beautiful
beautiful scenery oh
because on the way back we noticed even
more dad things were lit up yeah
um
yeah it's a really Narrow Path which
there's going up and down and up and
down and restaurants on the sides here
and
[Music]
restaurants actually were closed and
some buildings were even kind of like
um falling apart I guess they were just
abandoned and I was like that feels like
a waste having an abandoned building in
such a touristy place like this hmm hmm
interesting
um
narrow Pathways with lights like that
seems so pretty yeah it was really big
Lana was taking that picture I was like
my legs foreign
[Music]
I think you'll like this one I was like
you know Ahmed was like looking at any
monies and all that and then me and
hatima noticed our shadows and I was
like
like telling them to do this
[Music]
Isn't that cool
I wish Shadows make the water so clear
and the rest is like wow it's a cool
picture right
oh I don't I don't even know anymore
which hand is which ones and
but yeah I I just
um
I think I know which ones have
because
[Music]
an anemone it doesn't matter yeah
that's my little secret yeah but we all
did like
um hand cam streams before so I mean
there's no big surprise here I asked
them if it's okay to show the picture
don't worry they said it's okay
foreign
[Music]
was wondering about something because
someone said that if you go in early in
the morning and you see people fishing
around here and
[Music]
um because on the way back I'm two hours
I'm not surprised it's a very very
interesting long story okay the other
stories are shorter I promise
um
little cover album oh yeah it's cute I
think it works
I was I was curious because uh on the
way back you know it was really dark and
then when we were walking over that
um Bridge right in the beginning of the
bridge on the way back I saw some we saw
some people
um like putting some like big like light
stick like a LED light into the water
and it was hard to see what they were
doing besides you know the one area
where it was lit up inside the water but
I thought maybe they were trying to see
something to fish something specific but
I was like what do you need to see it in
order to fish it the Japanese people are
saying was probably
um
not octopus
squid squid squid interesting
because
oh squid gathers around light
[Music]
it
is
because
there was one thing besides shirazulu
one thing besides you know so that is
very very
um like well known and enoshima and a
popular like street food snack is Taco
senbei octopus pressed
uh like rice cracker I guess and you can
buy them like packed up already in the
souvenir shops or you can get like a
fresh one and the the one store that was
making fresh ones was really popular
they had a long line and they basically
and they press
taco
cheese
yeah they press it into like a fairly
thin paper fin symbi a rice cracker yeah
it's pretty big and very flat
flatter than inner
yeah paper fin yeah yeah I don't know I
haven't looked um closely how they do it
um uh but yeah it's uh shots fired well
yeah we didn't eat it though
um both me and AME
you know again
I guess we're gonna similar taste we're
not we're not really interested
I showed her I showed her that it exists
I said do you want to try we didn't we
didn't get it though
um
[Music]
master
and I just got back and you're roasting
her ah don't worry
don't worry she
find she will never hear it
anyway
um yeah we were I guess where was I yeah
we were on the way back we were just
um I don't know taking some more nice
scenery Pages well walking walking
walking the wing Bop
remember anything like
particularly special happening oh oh we
went to bed
surprise though and uh I was like oh
yeah I mean that was the last chance to
buy souvenir because we were walking
through that street the one in the
beginning again and
um she got herself some chopsticks
some good looking Chopsticks and again I
would not have entered the store if it
wasn't for Ahmed but I found something
in the store
oh that absolutely needed they had that
stove is amazing I'll get I'll show you
guys some pictures another time
um but
they had like cups and glasses
that were shaped like the Paw of a cat
is
you gotta see it they look so good I got
um yeah I got two glasses and I got one
cup with a cute um cat illustration on
it and the the handle was of course like
a cat tail or so yeah
yeah and then we walked all the way back
and uh got something from the
convenience store I got some apples and
shared it with us and I had to get some
money from the ATM and then we walked to
the station we all took the same train
and we were tired and actually we
couldn't get seats next to each other
first time it was like sitting somewhere
across us and I was sitting next to
hachima and because it was going to be a
long train ride I was like okay this is
awkward if we don't talk so let me show
you everything every single photo I have
on my phone
so I showed her
um photos of my cats and of my apartment
and of my trip to the Maldives and so on
yeah I showed her everything she was
very interested
um
yeah yeah yeah and then eventually we
kind of parted ways and I said bye bye
to Ahmed but it wasn't that it was not a
difficult bye-bye because we said hey
we're gonna see internet again soon high
five hug bye bye yeah
I said take care of it don't get lost
again okay be careful
but that was
the energy my story
it's so cute this picture is so cute
yeah
[Music]
I might think of some more details
another time but this was I think pretty
much it
it's good it's good if I have some
leftover tangents for another time let's
actually good this way yeah
um now tangents are not over but let me
read super chats at least for half an
hour okay okay
let me just read like four just for a
little bit okay
where do I need to continue tell me tell
me
do you guys know please tell me please
tell me
[Music]
maybe I can just finish like one or two
streams
New Year's
um the hand picture yeah yeah I wanted
to post it but I was like I shouldn't
post it before the stream because I'll
show everything too early
um but I kind of need to go to
I kind of got an island meeting oh well
I don't wanna hey
New Year's okay New Years
okay I'm gonna go to our meeting and
maybe I'll find a cop drop or so okay
and
foreign
wait for me mute mute mute
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah maybe it was a real Island
meeting
you will never know
okay I have a fruit candy they have like
top-notch fruit candies here
[Music]
yeah are there fake idle memes no only
real ones of course how's your frog
doing oh my God I'm fine pretty well
doing okay
who did you meet at the aisle meeting
Jen Moss
not at the aisle meaning the moment I
left the door I was I was like really
spooked
it's Jenna was saying I was like
he was she was scared that I worried I
wouldn't find my way back apparently
Angel's jump scared you know okay and
you guys said New Year's New Year's
stream
[Music]
so we'll read some super chats from
the happy New Year stream it seems
can we go back to one or two more
tangents okay
okay
from there on here just
super chato
yeah yeah I skipped it before and I went
to a different stream but I know I I
need to go back to this one uh
click super chats and going back to 10
chance later
hi
can you even read this no
of course there
[Music]
okay wow this screen is looking kind of
messed up but whatever I'm gonna put
this here for now
cute I'm such a genius I'm such a genius
taking pictures like that am I not
cool fingers
yeah huh
huh
or one thing about
another thing that you know besides food
well another thing I felt connected uh
to AME about
was you know in the yakiniko day
like EV everyone
besides me and Amir oh here you go oh
dungeon not just a quick note okay no no
no it's just a quick note
everyone besides me and Anna had like
like cutesy
detailed made nails
yeah and me and Ahmed we were like plain
nail people yeah
[Music]
just wanted to say that okay that's it
that's it that's really it that's all
there is to it that's almost thing
yeah so Paula said bye
oh it really all I wanted to say
apparently not Thomas if I was not
um you know fascinated by my nails not
as some people may have thought when I
wrote that she was fascinated by my hand
no I literally meant she was fascinated
by my hand because suddenly
Cliffhanger
oh okay so here we go tangents
now that I got the attention of certain
TOA Senpai fans let me
um torture you by reading some super
chats
[Music]
um
Happy New Year I hope many of your
objectives happen during this next
exciting year also thank you for your
outstanding 2022 it was an amazing year
for kfp remember KP Loves You Forever
congratulations
um
yeah it happened it finally happened
uh I mean actually it happened a bit
earlier than I expected yeah they
implemented the buff already in the New
Year's program yeah it might not be the
final form
foreign
okay
it's purposefully more than that
yeah are you satisfied with the glove no
not 100 not because it's not big enough
but still because there's uh I I still
see some issues with the shape
um except especially when I like bend
over a little bit not just stand
straight
um
so I'm not 100 happy we'll see if we can
like get it to Perfection one day uh
yeah it's hard to convey
what I don't like about it but yeah
to go to the um plastic surgery again
apparently
No it should be natural yeah whatever
and thank you so much
yeah I I have some objectives for the
year of course
um now I don't know how possible they
are but I'll do my best and hope you
guys will support me
while I'll try to accomplish the
induction
skydunction Cruise Junction
jacket monkey thank you for the pinky
happy New Year Kiana here's to another
amazing year together with you on kfp I
hope you'll get a lot of chances to
unleash your full 3d Powers now that
your asset which somebody definitely did
not steal before has been returned to
you
right who stole my butt
um what reference is that who stole my
butt
hmm
who
huh youfi enough
if anyone I would say Ina because she
herself said it really only looks like
it
is back in the suspiciously large but
she didn't steal it
okay so there's no like particular thing
that you're trying to point out here is
there
I I'm assuming it's just a jerk okay
I thought there was a reference there
yeah
well Happy New Year to you too and yeah
I hope I can show off my assets a lot in
2023 yeah look forward to it take all
those screenshots that you always wanted
to take
um
chat thanks for an amazing year it's
been amazing watching you spread your
wings and so higher than ever watching
you make the most of this year has
certainly made a smile and trying to do
the same so my New Year's resolution is
simple be a verb Kiara will be proud of
oh
good luck with that I don't think it
will be difficult for you yeah
keep on doing what you do
and um oh might need some legal advice
from you sometime
yeah but yeah thank you for following me
for such a long time I hope that you
know I feel like it's kind of hard to
top
each year there's like pressure to like
do better than the year before and I'm
not sure if I can but um I'll try and
even if I can't I guess it's kind of an
individual thing if you feel like it's
better or not but I I wanna do my best
to keep you guys hooked and yeah have
you guys continue supporting me so you
lost
[Music]
oh
um
thank you guys thank you for looking
soon don't worry about always topping
yourself consistency is more important
yeah I think we'll have consistency
um
and don't worry the next trip to Japan
that I've been talking about
it
[Music]
definitely looks like uh I should have a
more stable like streaming environment
for that
um it should be fine
we should be able to do normal streams I
think at least
I should be able to stream from the
accommodation
and yeah
so
it's looking better than this time in
terms of that
uh no so for the next trip I don't wanna
like force myself to like go on an off
collab every other day every like every
day
um I also want to you know take the
opportunity for off collabs but
and yeah I it's like gonna be
close to this one and I also
kind of Miss like normal streams
so
um
there'll be more of that next time yeah
yeah
more normal streams I need to finish so
many RPGs after all I I need to play
Fire Emblem and then I need to play
Tales of Symphonia and then I need to
play this and that and this and that so
I'm busy you know
so soon
um
[Music]
Will's got a list oh yeah NFL player
rise up right away
I feel like we will be busy with Fire
Emblem and then I don't know
we'll see
um thank you
thank you for the pinky oh Gilmore Girls
episode 10 Christmas episode how
Timeless since I watched it Christmas
week oh Luke made Lorelei a Santa Burger
I don't remember that was a Santa book
best boy bestest boy because he drove
Lorelai to the hospital oh it wasn't for
her father yeah and it gave me the feels
glad Richard is okay happy New Year yeah
that was um I feel full episode yeah
quite a handful of emotions indeed
um
it was a good episode kind of showed you
like I think it was this there was this
moment where
uh Lorelei I was in the room when
Richard I think woke up
and then it's my chat's dead all right
you guys just did
oh you guys were just dead for a moment
okay wake up
um
yeah and then the moment when he wakes
up I think that's when the others come
into the room but for the really short
moment they were like looking at each
other
like Lorelei was very like moved and
and emotional and then the others come
in and it kind of ruins the moment but
still they had this like really small
short moment that was uh nice wasn't it
and it was a special moment
[Music]
yeah hope you're enjoying it
I like him
it's kind of a cool grandpa I mean not
really like in the like common sense of
a cool grandpa I mean he's still a
golfer and a rich dude
you know but he's like pretty cool and
like considering like how he
was raised and yeah
like considering his
situation
uncool but if you look at him generally
he's like a rich
like old businessman guy living in a
[\h__\h] Mansion so you know what do you
expect but then he's actually in like
really like a chill grandpa really nice
to be around
um
down Jim Tracy thank you for the pinky
happy New Year Kiana this past year was
so much fun with all kinds of memories
thank you for oh I have to try hard to
not break out in the song Thank you for
all you did to make it special I can't
wait to see what's in store for kfp in
the coming year yay me too I hope there
will be some fun things in store for kfp
um I'll definitely I mean I wanted it to
come out maybe like in December or so
already originally but a big delay
because
I I just couldn't like I I started like
creating a like a concept of ideas of
like which producers and so on what kind
of songs I want to set up for an album
but
um couldn't really get into the creation
process just yet but maybe around summer
I think
I'm aiming for summer now
um for the album
and even if we can't do a like in person
live concert in an actual venue
still want to do like maybe for
anniversary or birthday like a proper
like one hour YouTube 3d concert yeah
but that will mean
that I love to fly somewhere
to record that again
and but at least you know I already know
a lot of my own choreos so I'll just
have to maybe learn like six more or so
who knows depending on how big the album
will be
yeah but it'll be worth it I want to do
like one big big 3D thing
um so I won't have to get that done man
like for two years
myths
um
like anniversary streams and birthday
streams like always 2D man
I think it's about time that we get to
make use of the Japanese studio and all
that
to get like the same kind of high
quality
3D streams that we should have access to
so I will insist on that
hi jenma by the way surely I'm listening
to this
I am insisting and you know that
I want some cool pretty streams if I
don't fight all
right
I'll fight all
no
I won't I will not accept anything under
an hour
no
[Music]
the president asked I think Martin said
by yourself asked her because we saw it
together
apparently we can even have like a
members only portion for these kind of
streams
I mean it was something like like I
don't know if it's like 15 minutes or
something like that yeah
so I didn't know about that members
Encore
um I'll make use of that
I'll make use of that hell yeah
Senpai did it um
exactly
[Music]
Japan members have been doing it for a
while I don't even know that they were
doing that
I didn't even realize that that was also
like pretty and so on
yeah I just feel like myth because of
Japan closing its borders I feel like
missed out
um like a lot of opportunities and I
feel like especially I missed out on
them
um because no access to freaking really
mostly in Europe
um
and I'm not gonna lie it feels kind of
rough like looking at everyone around me
doing so much and breathing
and me really wanting to do it but not
being able to do it it's kind of rough
and now I really hope that in 2023
I'll get all the chances that I deserve
oh hello
[Music]
set me back yeah it really feels like it
was set me back
yeah
yeah it is frustrating mm-hmm
yeah thanks guys
I like what you've been doing up to this
point Thank You Gotta make it work
somehow all the handicaps
yeah yeah and thank you Jim Tracy
ultimate MK thank you for the red super
chat happy New Year first of congrats on
your parents on this fashion program and
your spectacular performance in the
countdown live because it's amazing also
I want to thank you for making the past
year so special and hope that this year
will be even more wonderful thank you
too for being part of a great year thank
you soon for all the support and yeah
I'm glad I'm glad you know those end of
the year appearances were possible
on such a short and tight notice and
schedule
anything planned for 1.5 million and no
no idea I don't even know like when
that's gonna like happen I I have no
idea like when the ref estimate is
probably going to take a long time
though maybe summer who knows maybe I
will kind of like overlap or something
anyway
soon nah it's very slow
happens when it happens
yeah
um unfortunately I don't get anything
special for 1.5 I think the next special
reward is 2 million and I'm like
you know I'm kind of like cool
regretting in hindsight I wish I would
have gotten a 3D outfit
um for my 1 million wish instead of a 2d
outfit because in hindsight you know
like uh recently a lot of members are
getting 4D outfits and I only have the
one and it's like maybe for a 1 million
or two million wish or if you do like a
concert right like Cali
but obviously I can't do a concert
anytime soon where I get such an outfit
and 2 million is really far so hmm
maybe I should have gone for free for
free but I yeah I guess I I thought back
then I thought you know I'll have more
ways like more it will be easier to use
the 2D outfit like it gets used more
often yeah yeah
um
yeah
damn it it
because it's I can't just get one it
seems like I can't just get one for a
YouTube live it has to be like an
in-person live concert you know
and
you've heard about the waiting list
two million is a lot
[Music]
um
today was still the right choice you
think so
um everyone Channel wouldn't be the same
without the outfit but maybe I could
have gotten the
um the the end of in 3D
could have still been a dandel I don't
know if I would have done that I might
have gone more for something like a
performer outfit like I'm not quite an
idol but like kind of like an artist
performer I don't know something like
that I don't know I don't know
um
[Music]
oh well anyway
thank you Ultimo and happy New Year to
you too hoping for your support and this
year as well Boosie
yes
guys it was German okay
[Music]
Dino Lord Jacob thank you for the rest
of the chat
uh Happy New Years Kiana and thank you
for an amazing year thank
you I'm glad you enjoyed it I'm glad you
think it was an amazing year I tried my
best
I tried to deliver content as much as I
could interesting content thank you for
being part of the Dyna Lord
hoping to have you around
for much longer
soon
happy 2023 came out our mips animal
performance on the countdown stream was
great I can't wait to see more this year
you're amazing wish you the best thank
you thank you thank you yeah
who's animal animal so much animal
animal was as I said before
I don't know I guess I was kind of
hoping for a different song
but at least with this one I knew
already
knew the song so yeah
and I guess I am an animal
glad you enjoyed it thank you so much I
was a drama action for the pinky happy
New Year buzz and chickens work has kept
me busy lately and but I'll continue to
watch your streams even if it's VOD only
I hope you'll have a wonderful time in
Japan also thank you I'm having
currently a wonderful time here yeah
yeah I mean it's been like kind of like
a little bit stressful but a lot of fun
like every day
has been very koi
Mary what's the word
full full with memories I can't find the
right word
thick thick
oh thick Every Day's thick how do I say
that
yeah I'm fulfilling I guess so I don't
know memorable memorable that's kind of
fitting
um
yeah
uh what was I oh yeah yeah thank you
it's what well I hope you'll be able to
catch lots of live streams as well thank
you Iris for staying with me Iris a
drama even if you can't catch your live
streams much I appreciate that thank you
um
[Music]
thank you for the recipe
what a superb one this has been looking
forward to all the exciting things in
2023. indeed
I think there will be many exciting
things for you guys and for me
um
gonna work hard though yeah you guys you
guys I'm gonna work hard and you guys
just um watch
okay just watch every stream that's all
I need from you and exchange in exchange
um uh work hard yeah
support Wawa yeah you watch me hard uh
oh I hate English
um thank you
it didn't look so weird in in in letters
when you wrote it in chat
anyway
[Music]
[Laughter]
s can't wait for more fun this new year
yeah yeah lots of great memories but I
feel like just in this like what two
weeks I already made like so many
memories that I made like I mean I made
as many member memories in two weeks
worth is worth what at work
how to English
of worth worth of uh like I don't know
four months of me being in Austria do
you get what I'm saying of course you
get what I'm saying you're used to my
shitty English
I'm so energetic today damn how do I do
it my face is kind of tired though you
know yesterday I got a massage here's
the tangent I got a massage
um the lady lady after massage said girl
what's wrong with you she was like holy
[\h__\h] like your head
your head and your shoulders and your
neck but also surprisingly especially in
your head is so hard
I'm sorry to say it again but she said
it's so hard and she thinks it comes the
pain that I have in my shoulders and so
on she thinks it comes from eye strain
and I don't know my eyes don't really
feel strained
but she just says that yeah everything's
so [\h__\h] hard and tense and yeah
I don't know what that means she said I
should massage my head more but I don't
know yeah I think a head is supposed to
be hard I don't know how much like wait
I want to lay on her words I'll I like
listening to her like advice and so on
you know I'll give it a chance but yeah
I don't really know if massaging my head
and like my the bones around my eyes
will really make my pain go away but she
said
my my body
my skull is like really hard
yeah
well says a lot of tension it's like
built up but I told her I have this for
like
10 years or so hmm
anyway anyway
[Music]
um
uh Apple
yeah I just read this one right thank
you Ethel
Thanks for the Memories
even though they were indeed very great
ah thank you for the membership
it was a Thai massage by the way I've
had time massage before though but this
one was kind of lame
to say my other Thai massages were
better even though this one was really
like well um reviewed not not a fine
massage I said Thai massage
yeah yeah I used to say taught did I
really I used to say ties right oh my
God I can't imagine that now that sounds
so wrong to me now hmm
anyway
s from Ireland cool thank you onto
YouTube downstairs and now I need a
translator
[Music]
here New Year's resolution for me I have
only one New Year's resolution and that
is learning Korean like to a decent
level because I disappointed myself this
year but hey I really wanted to but like
it was [\h__\h] busy
yeah I can't help it
um how do I switch this
can't switch it ah there we go
wait my my ear I can't hear
I get here I can't hear in my ear oh wow
that's okay I don't need my ear
just need one ear one ear is enough
[Music]
sir 956 thank you
even though you have four yeah I guess
that's even more why it doesn't matter
that I've lost one ear just now I have
four anyway
I can't believe I haven't watched a
Kiara's stream since last year oh wait
for a second I was gonna kind of be mad
like what the [\h__\h]
um but now I realize okay no problem no
problem
[Music]
um
no I didn't use cotton swap no I used my
finger
sorry
but the finger should be fine
oh
yeah oh well
it's half open now
half open yeah but you know have you
really been watching my stream still
like I mean I'm I'm not trying to like
you know make you feel like
guilty yourself
I haven't seen you around much have you
have you been around just just checking
like maybe you've just been watching
Vlogs or so
is that it
no pressure
have you been around
watching that because you used to be a
rama but maybe just right now yeah right
now I'm like close to a time zone right
so are you here now Buddha
welcome
[Music]
I'll see him someone said he's around
now
[Music]
busy with work well at least you're
still think of me at least you don't
didn't forget me like others did
that moved on
for once I'm gonna say that I am having
salty feelings about that
yeah it's sad and it's normal you know
you know you move on but you know of
course I'm also sad Shivers never leave
potential
foreign
yes
check the usual room
Maybe
impression
no no not me what does that even mean
if that means that I
have
a big
love for you
well then call me parasocial
if that means that
I if if me checking out your Twitter
accounts
means I'm parasocial
well yeah then call me parasocial
if me crying about you guys leaving me
and going to other people's streams is
per social and yeah okay call me price
social
if I feel salty about me introducing a
YouTuber to you and then you going there
and like putting your putting their Oshi
Mark into your Twitter name means I'm
being parasocial
yeah [\h__\h] do it
anyway so I'm not parasocial I think we
have established that I am not
parasocial
cool okay
that's a I think the first time I read
that name thank you I just got home
after free whiskey colas
don't really mind me but Happy New Year
can I love you best of holy and first
gen oh thank you maybe you should drink
those whiskey colas more often
no no please don't don't turn into an
alcoholic because of mate thank you for
um saying hi though and happy New Year
to you thank you for watching my streams
I'm glad you like me
I'm I'm really
um trying hard to make people like me a
little bit too hard I think but
yeah like recently with all the Japanese
memories that I've been meeting
but also with en members I've been
really
um I don't want them to dislike me
obviously so I've been trying hard to
make them like me for the Yaki Nico I
bought a present for every single person
you know I ran out of souvenirs from
Austria so what did I do I went to a
store that sells like German and oyster
and chocolate and so on and I bought
like a [\h__\h] ton of it and then I wrapped
it in like present rapping and all that
and got one for every single person that
I met at the yakiniko place even the
ones that I've met before
hmm
I just tried to in general leave a good
impression by
um really participating in the
conversation and trying to be like hope
and all that and I mean yakiniko the one
like I think it went well like I I I I I
had like fun and good conversations and
yeah
um
but I feel like I've been putting a lot
of pressure on myself
um to be likable because I'm like very
scared I
I want to leave a good impression there
I even
like in order to leave a good impression
I've also been like buying some cute
clothes and and and accessories like
yeah
I wanted them to think I'm cute so I
bought a new bag
s of bags
yeah
uh dressing cute for the girls exactly
no not Gucci I don't no no no not that
expensive no no
it's a Japanese back bread that's kind
of girly and I used to like it a lot
when I lived in Japan but I wasn't able
to really buy much there ever because I
had no money yeah but they're not as
expensive as like a Gucci bag or so no
no no no but I think their bags are
pretty good quality
um yeah and they have really cute
designs
hmm I like them cements
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
like ever since
this is part of the corner
tangent but ever since that meeting on
the 31st and then also as even more
after the golf collab we've been so labu
every day we're like messaging each
other like hey I want to see you do you
have time when do you have time like oh
I want to see you too I have the same
feeling I want to meet you I miss you I
miss you too she's been like one or two
days but I miss you
[Music]
hmm
um we're trying to make it look but our
schedules have are like really busy in
the coming days of the past days
we finally found one gap
for last meeting before I leave
yeah
and like isn't even yesterday even
yesterday like after the off collab with
Louie Louie told me that she's pretty
close of calling herself by two and that
the other day she like came over just to
hang
um not even stream just just to hang and
I'm like uh
well her stream just ended right like
before like half an hour she'll go right
like the pecora caught on the stream
they did actually ended earlier than we
fought so I was like can can we can we
ask if she wants to come over
and then you know it's because I really
want to be recorded soon bye and then it
was considered it was taken into
consideration but accordingly was too
busy with some work so she didn't come
but yeah after I heard that I left
I'm sorry I really got a long well with
Louie and we had some like fangirling
moments and all that
well that's starting to become another
tangent but you know
um like after I was gonna wait like
forever if caught on it would come but
she didn't come so then I left
uh thank you for the memberships thank
you thank you
anyway uh where was I miniature paint
shot
for the recipe oh in Japanese
[Music]
oh it should I answer in nihongo
um
[Music]
foreign
I want to my goal my ideal goal would be
to take time at least once a week to
take like one of those lessons Korean
lessons
yeah fight to fight
on
title fighter
thank you thank you
[Music]
do your best yes
yeah
[Music]
um
yeah okay okay okay okay don't tangent
kiwawa for [\h__\h] sake how long have I
been reading though probably more than
half an hour right how can I I haven't
read that many
[Music]
Happy New Year I hope all your wishes
come true hopefully my letter reached
you and wasn't too sad or cringe I blame
wikiHow if it was your lovely bird and
content creator keep being awesome love
from Chile wait are you here right now
when did you send it
cause
uh before I leave I could check with Jen
life she like saw some more letters for
me to bring home indeed
um
foreign
[Music]
yeah this would be a perfect time to
send a letter uh I think so like uh even
if if you send it now I might not
receive it like within this trip but the
next soon trip
yeah so I recommend it is
I know
[Music]
um
timing would be perfect
yeah should we really get started yeah
go should probably write the letter
really yeah you should I want to read
your lettuce give me your letters give
them to me
I cook it kind of see
try to go outside
write me your letters I want to see your
letters yeah you've been forgetting
about me you've been slacking
I need more family
yeah and more fan art too much
this background is amazing right
you know
um Eden sent me like the the draft and I
was like hmm can we make this airplane
leave like you know just like that like
move it out of the screen and then have
it just move back shouldn't be too
difficult right he said I'll try here it
is they did it
because I mean he has experience of
animating things and I feel like that
should have been
a busy airport yeah but it's only one
plane and that one plane keeps on going
back and forth
[Music]
surprise this one has no jump scare or
oh
don't give him ideas
um
no one gets off how would you know it's
connected on the other side you wouldn't
see it if they go in and out
they don't just like jump out of the
window
they go for that tunnel there no right
there yeah
okay
love back to Chile by the way myself
again thank you for the pinky voice yeah
I got to celebrate another birthday
review and care of me again and I'm
pretty happy back in school and already
got a side job doing what I love don't
think I would have without you pushing
kfb to be happy first take your
attention oh
did I really did I really do that yeah I
mean it's important but you know
somewhere deep inside I might be
thinking
but no
um no Tom we put um
um the more important things first
whatever is important to you and if that
happens to be real what can I do about
that just kidding um put your studies
and your job and all that first told
late yes
yes
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah no I I agree
with that totally
myself and good luck with school and
your side job I wish you all the best I
hope it will go back I hope it will go
well this year um
with coming to my streams too hope
you'll be here as much as you can Steven
Speck tangerson resoline thanks for the
pinky Happy New Year's attention
uh a Nerf and time on the program hope
you feel better soon and got to enjoy
the rest of your trip with the other
girls honestly
it's been a great time and that 3D
program appearance like was
life-changing was really big I feel like
it was like kind of an emote and really
important
like
yeah moment in my trip that kind of got
all the stones rolling I feel like yeah
everything going yeah
yeah thank you Happy New Years to you
too lorenzie yeah
spent some nice time together this
year's shall we
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yes have a great year
together Jeff Starr hope you stay in kfp
you must it's not not like you can leave
anyway right
for the pinky thanks for enhancing my
2022 boss meeting you and the rest of
care for your dogumi really was a
highlight of my year thanks to another a
history never uh year of fun canopy
dance
clean glasses glassing at each other
yeah I am thank you
we had a great time connecting with kfp
there's a lot of great people in like in
kfb so it was very heartwarming and
wholesome
seeing you guys get along so well
together it's very sweet oh yeah hope
we'll have more of that hmm happy new
year for the rest of the chat Happy New
Year hope you can reflect on the many
achievements and events that happened in
2022 it was amazing experience being
part of kfp and lots in you I'm excited
to see what you have in store for 2023
yeah me too I don't know everything but
I know some things and um yeah it's
looking looking exciting of course but
also like kind of I feel I don't know
stressed
pressured I don't know but I'll do my
best I hope you'll be by my side no
matter what happens you know School mwah
without a loyal thanks soon sir 956
thank question
[Music]
for the pinky and thank you for being my
beacon of light and my energy pill you
have my eternal love and support I wish
good help for you your kitty cat and
Mama doli love you always my Oshi let's
have a great year thank you but you know
who also needs some well wishes and good
luck my brother bro Tony
I hope I hope he has a successful 2023
actually yeah he's like starting from
scratch more or less again
and I hope it goes well yeah
taking care of my ketokatos yeah I've
been sending me some videos it's getting
along so well with them though they're
really used to him now
[Music]
um
yeah
how's your job and apartment search
going actually good question I should
ask him that right now
[Music]
because that's what he's supposed to be
doing right now no pressure but you know
I mean you can't
you know sometimes though
when I'm back he's supposed to like go
somewhere else he's not supposed to stay
over at my place by the way because I
cannot function when someone's at my
place no no no no no no I want my I want
my alone time with my ketocatos I want
to be able to run around in a T-shirt
and pet panties and I want to keep my
toilet doors and all that open and and
when I shower I'm Gonna Keep it all open
so that my cats can walk in and out and
look at me and make sure that I'm not
drowning and so on
[Music]
I am so anyway
Midnight Rider function flaming pants
thank you
another one
I feel you already sent one maybe I
imagined hope the three gifts I gave
brought you just a little bit of
happiness
pre-gift
which ones I felt awful as you struggled
helpless to do anything for you you're
so kind you've given me endless reasons
to smile touched my heart in ways I
can't explain
you're the most wonderful girl I've ever
met everything you surprised me makes me
so so happy oh yeah as new year begins I
hope I can continue to be here for you
in any way I can to watch you
conquer your Heights happy New Year much
love thank you
thank you oh you mean the Christmas
letters Vlog oh yes yes yes thank you
wait you organized us
did you
well thank you so much it's really sweet
thank you so much for for for trying to
organize those things as well and and
being part of the community you know
doing such special things I appreciate
it yeah but
[Music]
parasocial about my cooking
I think you care a little bit too much
about what I'm cooking
yeah you care too much about what I'm
cooking and eating
yes
but maybe it's okay it's okay I am I'm
actually glad that you know when I'm
cooking and uploading these photos that
I feel like most people wouldn't give a
[\h__\h] about uh but you guys you guys
you're like whoa that looks amazing that
looks like straight out of the menu or
cooking book or whatever you guys are
like actually way too nice to me make me
feel like I was cooking something like
life changing and my cooking reports so
yeah
so let's continue it shall we
I go back into cooking
feel free to like you know
uh copy my Superior recipes which are
totally my own recipes are not Hello
beep recipes
um
compared to what I eat it really is
though
I see that I'm learning about some food
I didn't know about before oh well is it
really thanks to me or is it thanks to
hello beep huh haha
help sheesh
the floors are really well oh I really
tried to make them look good
I really try
my best
like normally if I wouldn't take a
picture I would just like serve it like
whatever
but since I know I'm taking a picture
for Twitter I tried to serve it like
aesthetically please otherwise I
wouldn't give a [\h__\h]
the same
I mean yeah you say you eat with your
eye but
I don't think it makes a big difference
in the end in my mouth if it's good it's
good if it's bad it's bad
you you can't just make something shitty
taste good just by
adding a little flour on top yeah
anyway
yeah I'll try my best with my plating
skills yeah yeah yeah I'll I'll I'll
improve my cooking this year and more
hell yeah
and thank you for the two pinkies that
makes a kiss for you
foreign
[Music]
thank you for still being here you're
always so supportive
can I count on you in 2023
um
maybe 2023 you'll talk a little bit more
to me tell me your secrets die to tell
me everything I want to know it all
also go into January with the uniform no
naked chicken
so many things happened this year and
I'm glad I got to cheer you on and see
how you're dominating the stage like you
should can also get employee number
myself from your chickens
thank you of course you can get an
employee number and it's
two one
six
congratulations
yeah
and thank you for the support so far
yeah you have a uniform now it's looking
fabulous on you looking gorgeous
congratulations yeah Happy New Year to
you
and a kiss would you lock a kiss would
you like a kiss Here Comes one
[Music]
thank you for the support
um now
we should maybe take a break and go into
a tangent
all right remember
155 105 155 is where I stopped the super
chattel
and
um
I should have gone a tangent
how many this is 155 how how at the
scroll bar says I'm halfway through
oh I kind of am
kind of mom more or less sure
I don't know if we can finish them today
though I don't want to like I mean
they're sad they said I can go until 11
pm
but I don't want to like you know force
them to
[Music]
it's pretty empty here already I think
there's like just one staff member
besides General remaining for me who's
like in charge of
having this go well also I still have to
record a tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny
tiny thing that I messed up in the other
recording
which will take just five minutes but I
have to set up everything like the for
the recording blah blah blah blah anyway
it's taken
oh okay then it's two one eight
two one eight ten
[Music]
oh oh
Joseph no thank you I'm really worried
about you guys when you write something
like that on Twitter you know I know
everyone has their own problems but I
would be so sad if I knew that a kfb
member
was taken not by my hand you know
was not
taking it by my hand and turned into a
burger by my decision
so you know I want you guys to live your
little chicken life to the fullest
oh
yes so
live a long long
life and
and eat those corn on the ground
and yeah
I decide when you become a burger okay
yeah until then
until then I know it must be rough
for some of you guys life [\h__\h] socks
very often
but I hope 2023 can treat you all very
nicely
yes because everyone deserves it
everyone deserves a fulfilling happy
life
without struggling through every day
[Music]
I can't be deserve it because they've
been so nice to me and so supportive of
me but you also deserve support the
support you give to me you deserve to
yeah
okay so tangent
that time who wants to say attention
stop
spin the wheel
imagine it will fall and I know she
might have to hold tell this whole story
again oh
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi hi hi
so long time ago once upon a time
bye uh
thought uh I wanted to do of collabo in
Japan and the first one that I thought
of that I wanted to do was
because I thought it was a fun idea like
you know not just one-on-one collapse I
generally I prefer one-on-one collabs
um they're more fun
but uh you know this time I wanted to do
oh ninja she wrote to me next time oh
tomorrow then she cool out by the way of
collab um
anyway so
yeah I will I wrote hey you guys want to
play a lot like Mario party or something
over there and then off collab and they
were like hell yeah let's do it so the
time came closer and
um we decided to do it at Nolan's place
and on her Channel and so on but we also
decided to go for uh like some food
beforehand because
it just feels kind of weird to just go
to the place to do stream and leave and
bye bye it feels so unpersonal right so
yeah and I said I wanna go Yakiniku so
we went Yakiniku and they chose a place
that
um they knew was good so yeah it was
really really cool fancy place I've been
to a lot of yak and Eagle places before
but that one felt especially fancy
um now we had our own room which we've
been
um generally that's like a
uh criteria
for us like all of us when going to eat
together in general criteria usually
always is that we find
um something with a room like koshitsu
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
now we have private room
and first you know okay okay I'm kind of
jumping a little things here first
wait let me look my Emma notes I don't
have notes about this right
I think I did
[Music]
um
yeah
first first
I met I was the first to arrive and then
for that I came and
Brunel arrived with
some
merchandise
of hello did you mention this on the
stream but she had like a an a trophy
and uh Anya trophy not the whole life
Anya but the Spy family drove me she
told me she likes spy families I don't
remember that maybe I can next time I
see her maybe I'll find some spy family
merchandise that I can give to her but
yo I was like damn I can actually relate
Anya so [\h__\h] cute I love uh spy
family Anya so cute
yeah yeah she was like a kind of like
and while waiting for the others
she was getting the trophy it seems
yeah
um so she came first and then we waited
for the others but they took some time
so we went into the room first and we
then a little bit later uh soon after
nowhere to came and you know I met both
of them for the first time I was really
excited and I was also nervous
but yeah they were both very very sweet
to me and then Cali actually she had
like some work to do the whole day and
she knew that
she knew that she would be late
um
um but in a while until Cali came you
know I had this bonding time I guess
with uh two just the three of us hmm
[Music]
they ordered tongue tongue again homies
every time I go and foreign
here here it's like a normal thing right
so first time I experienced something
like this Yakiniku where someone orders
tongue I was also like
yo that's so weird so weird a tongue
I hope that but I eventually tried and
you know it's it's edible like it's
um definitely more chewy than like like
normal like parts of the body but it's
also not as chewy as other things like
insides
uh that are also a popular choice on the
yakiniko menu but yeah
uh it's it's edible it's edible yeah
yeah and
they had
not only
normal tongue
they had
God tongue
[Music]
coming yeah they ordered God tongue uh I
think I asked why it's called got tongue
um but there wasn't really a like really
special explanation
yeah it's just the
a good tongue oh oh but no like normally
the tongues that they serve they're
actually pretty thin slices but like
pretty big like you can like really the
marbling or something it does look a
little bit like a tongue yeah but if you
don't think too much about it then it's
okay but
um
[Music]
uh this God tongue was way thicker than
only other normal tongues that you
normally get served so that's why it's
so special yeah
don't think too much about it it works
it works I've tried it you know and I'm
the one who doesn't like eating weird
things you know I'm very picky you know
that but
um
tongue I got over okay I I still
wouldn't order it on my own
uh and Ahmed wouldn't have ordered it
either on the other day when we went
Yaki Nico she tried to but you know
we're not we're not the biggest fans
yeah
well so they ordered like Yuka and tan
and all that and I was like nope nope
nope nope I'm sitting this one out don't
worry you girls can have that you can
you can eat as much as you want from
that I'm waiting for my for my cuddle
bean and my harami and my dosu jodos and
all that
um those are like I would say
the more normal parts
like normal normal like more common
parts hmm
yeah uh on this day I didn't try the UK
I tried it on the other day with the big
reacting group and okay it was okay it
was edible okay still I wouldn't order
it on myself
but yeah yeah when then oh I think the
color beam was okay
hot hot on me was amazing
and the nose was really good too
and then eventually later when Cali was
already there because I waited I said
I'm I said I saw it in the menu I was
like I need to eat Chateau budion today
whatever it's like a really fancy meat
that they have in a lot of Yakiniku
places
um
yeah and I don't know what part of the
body is it but it's usually like one of
the like best things on the menu The
Chateau yeah so it's a bit more
expensive and when it arrived uh I
actually didn't save any pictures for
this by the way it's just food but
um just the usual Yakiniku stuff but
this meat
it had gold flakes on it
was really fancy
so but the food if you want to say it
[Music]
yeah just imagine like a really
beautiful marbled piece of meat we have
gold on it tiny gold flakes tiny yeah
it's like these things look really
expensive and really fancy but
gold flakes are also often on like not
that expensive like more normal Foods
too like even ice cream parfaits or
whatever just for making it look fancy
but it doesn't necessarily mean that
it's really like that expensive okay
yeah goldlinks are not expensive but it
makes you feel like you're eating
something really fancy yeah oh by the
way
um oh yeah what I wanted to say was
let's see
before Kelly came you know I was trying
to have conversation with no idea
but it was really hard you want to know
why
because even though it was a private
room normally at yakiniko places you
grill everything yourself
but I guess because it was kind of fancy
this time the staff
kept on coming in to grill everything
for us
it's out for a little bit there was only
like a one or two minute time window for
me to talk to them they kept on grilling
for us I was like yep yep I can't talk I
couldn't even like say their name and we
didn't establish what we would call each
other uh until a little bit later so I
was like
uh you I was just saying like yeah the
equivalent of you in Japanese because I
couldn't say their name well it was
weird yeah
and they wanted it that they grilled it
really well though you know they got the
skill
they have skill they know how to do it
perfectly but yeah
uh the name protocol yeah I mean when I
didn't really
um use it much though
[Music]
um
foreign
touching it for a second uh uh for some
reason kind of random but she didn't
make me touch it like money Senpai made
me yeah
I tried not to look at it you know be
respectful eyes are up here
but even when I look up here you know
and I still like notice
then oh
yeah
but
you know you know there's other things
on her to look at that are just as
beautiful okay
yeah
so anyway yeah while struggling to have
a conversation
eating some uh meat and waiting for
calories eventually she arrived and then
I feel like once Cali arrived we got
even more like
sign it and our conversation was like
even more lit up
and brightly we're having a good time
you know and
um
yeah after that oh by the way today I
got addicted to egg soup they were they
had some good egg soup and Korea got so
addicted she ordered like they had like
a big bowl right she ordered it twice
well into that egg soup
said it was magical
um
so then and we got into taxi and oh for
dance and I paid for the food
Arigato so sweet man thank you so much
and then we went to noida's place and we
kind of arrived late yeah so we arrived
and and immediately had to prepare
couldn't even see the uh like her place
properly first
um but
no I was like stressing she was like
setting up everything like a lot of it
was already set up beforehand
as expected but she had to like really
quickly do this and that and this and
that and this and that and even then you
know during the stream she was still
like fixing the things but yeah yeah
yeah yeah and then you know the stream
happened as you know and I won
I won I know you guys were like holy
[\h__\h] what's going on this is like
history in the making life changing
from the beginning until the end and I
think
I think maybe just maybe it's because I
went first
because I think before when we played
Mario party we established that it's or
was that Monopoly name was Monopoly but
I feel like it also applies for Mario
party it's kind of a little bit
important
to get the first turn it helps
it helps
I went first before
um
maybe there's more about Monopoly then
also helps them from Mario party though
and yo like from the get-go I was having
so much luck I went to the Stars one
after another and I also had so much
money and I also like almost never lost
at the mini games and you know I was
feeling kind of bad like what but I
shouldn't feel bad right what is this
what do you call that syndrome like
you're doing so well and then you're
actually feeling bad for doing well
because you feel like you don't deserve
it in plaster syndrome Maybe
foreign
[Music]
for once I never win
never in life knowing games
that's incredible I didn't know what was
going on I was always expecting it to
like be turned around but I didn't want
it but I think like
I think one reason maybe why it went so
well was also like my I guess you can
only really apply that to the minigames
it's because I
I I
didn't feel too like serious about it
for me like since this was an off collab
for me the number one priority was to
have fun with the girls
and winning wasn't really like in my
mind at all
um
but oh maybe the Ping oh for many games
but like if I play a Mario Party outside
of off collabs then you know it's like
um I'm more focused on waiting and then
it messes up everything Maybe
yeah maybe you just don't need to forget
about everything let it go let it go let
it go let it go whisper world of wisdom
let's go
yeah and
yeah sorry for the audio by the way
audio was kind of scarcity in there
um but yeah after after the stream you
know I finally got my tour I checked out
the place I checked out the hamsters
they were so cute oh let it be oh not
let it go
take out the hand says annoyed Stand by
Your hands.com
yeah she like put the hamster on my hand
and we show time
and she put like some food on my hand so
it was it was eating the food on my hand
the whole time
it actually had some leftovers didn't
even eat the whole thing but it spent
quite a long time on my hamster on my
hand and Cali
um had a different hamster on her hands
but not for so long
smell I didn't smell the hamster okay no
I did not I didn't even think about it
no
yeah it's so cute but it's kind of
difficult to really like get like a good
fluff out of it
because they're so small like especially
that hamster that I had like with I was
trying to pet it with one finger but
when you pet something with one
fingertip then
I don't know you don't really feel much
you know what I mean
so it was it was hard but it was a funny
tingling sensation a little bit to have
it on the palm of my hand and have been
eating it's got the cute little pizzas
yeah so cute why oh it's writing I don't
say that what the [\h__\h]
you're funny to hold in your hand yeah
it's so cute it kind of made me want
some hamsters for myself to be honest
I'm kind of fond about it
[Music]
that's cute so yeah
checked out her place and we talked
about some things talked about some work
related things and I got some
information
yeah showing each other some things
[Music]
and then eventually you know we were
talking about leaving and
[Music]
I was like all right and then we check
my route for going back home and then no
other Senpai it's like should I call you
a taxi and I'm like no no no it's too
expensive no I should go for train and
she's she's like
she still calls me a taxi so sweet now
let me tell you
and wow
I must say this
I'm gonna spread this this good
information here right now
95 percent
off the senpais that I've no 100 percent
the percent of the senpies that I have
been with that I've like visited and
collabed with have
called me a taxi can paid for it
every single one of them
wait who did I meet before Martin senpai
what did I make before
[Music]
right and I was like
oh
so nice
well this this is a
one-time occasion so let's enjoy it then
next day I meet with Martin standby
and you know I stayed over and so it
wasn't a problem of there not being any
taxes right not any uh trains or so
right but yeah my name said I called me
a taxi too I'm like oh
whoa so comfortable
the next day I meet with what was it the
next day but anyway the next collab I
met with Corner senpai
and you know according to call the
sapphire was
ah
she just wanted me to
feel comfortable and happy and safe and
she wanted to do everything for me I
think so she got me a taxi too yeah oh
Connie I love you and then
yeah uh wait what was after Konya
yeah that was right after I think
so annoying sample calls me a taxi yeah
yeah yeah yeah everyone called me a dad
I
[Laughter]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
they called me a taxi too
yeah minor standby called me a taxi
I know I'm a taxi no no I'm not a taxi
so yeah maybe I'm saying
next outfit taxi no no no no no Mr taxi
taxi taxi Matrix Matrix yeah
um
[Music]
foreign
taxi lifestyle you know
I think they can write it off though
good for them yeah
I hope they can ride off my taxi rides
normally they can I think so
yeah we got along well
and it was a fun collab you know we I I
think from the point of view of a viewer
it was less fun than from our point of
views
because I think the audio was not ideal
and
um it was kind of chaotic
but for me I had a blast that was the
most fun Mario Party game I ever had in
my whole life you know maybe because I
won but also
is that you know
no don't oh that's what you mean no
don't call me a taxi
no
yeah
was legit fun yeah
it was crazy fun it was
lovely boss thank you winning is fun it
really is oh my God I want to win more
and more
survive the
oh they Council res
okay I'm beating everyone's great hell
yeah
yeah that moment when when I don't know
who maybe was north of accident when the
game was like like minimized and then in
the middle of Cali doing some sick
tricks
and without that
oh
without that I think I wouldn't have had
the money to buy another star right
that was that was such an important
moment yo
oh and that was like Vatican because
even though it would be good for me like
I'm like oh [\h__\h] this is I feel sorry
for Cali man
[Music]
yeah cause I [\h__\h] up
with my snowboarding skills the screen
and we both screamed like someone ripped
up our heads
foreign
[Music]
oh one more thing like I noticed like
they were wearing matching wigs me and
Kelly know this like oh oh so I asked
him uh are you too
sorry for asking but are you guys like
are those Rings like matching and
they're like oh yeah and then tell me
the story yeah of having a couple weeks
I'm like wait that's so cute what the
hell like um
[Music]
like also whenever like
was like talking about something it was
so sweet hell no I do was like
I could always feel like she was so
supportive of who they are like every
time for that I was talking nobody was
like yeah yeah yeah and like really like
um like supportively supporting whatever
footage I was saying yeah
she was like so passionate about it so
cute yeah
[Music]
sweet watching that man like you know
they've been working together for a long
time but
um it just feels like they're really
they really have a connection and their
good friends
oh sweet
lagging where you took place all right
Lucio it's
half past more than half past 9 P.M
um
well
[Music]
sorry sorry
manager's son I'm sorry I'll read some
more stuff but just really quickly okay
because I feel like bad not
accomplishing anything
[Music]
okay we'll quickly wait someone but
that's okay but it's really difficult
when all of them almost all of them are
like Reds and pinks you know that's hard
to get anywhere
no no we're not gonna go until 11. no
definitely not I'm gonna end it at maybe
10 pounds uh
[Music]
uh ten ten plus ten okay so 40 minutes
okay Speed Run
um
chat Happy New Year from New York City
I'm so proud of you for finally getting
over to the Japanese studio and getting
to show up on the variety program in 3D
yeah I can't imagine what it was like uh
getting to meet everyone but the stream
was great and you were amazing congrats
thank you yeah I was really nervous
about it but as I said before that day
was like super special was like a
miracle that really got things rolling
and
was
it wasn't the destiny to mean of color
that you guys don't understand because I
have yet to tangent properly about it
but I think
I found something special in one another
yes I love her so much
I don't get it you wouldn't understand
you wouldn't understand
I love her ow I love her so much I'm a
dog person now I am
against so she's so cute like she's
different she's not like other dogs
like other dogs
no I'm not gonna dive into the dance
because I don't have time for it but I
love her so much
uh we were like okay I'll just say one
thing that after the after the stream
you know we were cuddling
on on her sofa watching Netflix and she
like she had her arm around me and I was
resting my head on the chest though and
and you know she was like
petting my arm and like you know it's
like oh man
oh my God
sweet
no okay
yeah
petting petting nothing nothing
it was so sweet
[Music]
and then I miss her
I miss her yeah anyway I love her so
anyway
there's too much to take in my mind I
need to stop I need to stop
thank you so much muffin and yeah so
happy about that day if that day didn't
happen you know I would have been a
terrible terrible terrible day
and it was it was a miracle Destiny yeah
thank you
Benjamin thank you for the pinky happy
New Year boss Happy New Year to you too
my sweet sweet chicken employee I hope
you work hard this year okay okay and
then let's see maybe I'll I'll spare you
from the
the hot hot oil another year well
depends on your performance like it
sounds thank you for the red super holy
[\h__\h] that's a big one oh my God thank
you
two years ago I never thought my first
Super Chat would get me a whole talk ah
it scared the [\h__\h] out of me I'm sorry
now you got a loyal chicken and got a
boomer like me to say you're my [\h__\h]
ever since then I've seen you spread
your wings glow and grow and have been a
huge inspiration to me I can't wait to
see what 23 brings for you and kfp happy
New Year Buzz oh yeah I'm sorry for
putting you on the spot back then I
thought it was um yeah funny
thank you so much man that's a huge
donation thank you for being so generous
oh my God
how do I even say thank you well I guess
in German thank you soon
uh I will try not to put you on this
Spotlight that anymore but
um
thank you for being part of kfp I wish
you a wonderful happy New Year too with
lots of success hopefully your dreams
will come true and I hope that you'll be
by my side while maybe my dreams will
also come true we'll see about that it
was an experience yeah
a fun one I remember yeah
thank you for everything
perfect donation but I appreciate it now
you get many cases
mmm
Happy New Year
School 2020 brain
iron Cafe
foreign
[Music]
Phoenix who knows what possibilities are
open this year hopefully you get to have
a ton of fun this year thank you I hope
so too well let's work on the album all
right I'll work hard on it I wanna throw
out a banger album even if it's a
smaller one but I'll do my best yeah
okay so let's work on that and I want to
play a lot of live RPGs this year kind
of didn't play many RPGs huh 2022
because there was just not that much
that I you know if I could have played
Final Fantasy I would have played Final
Fantasy 2022 you know
um but there's only so much choice that
I have
I'm really blessed that when you Fire
Emblem coming out let's go yeah ever
since the last one I was really excited
to like play again but I didn't think
that another like main big release would
come out so soon actually but you know
thank God Fire Emblem releases uh big
games quite frequently yeah
um
coming out 2023 I forgot about that
that's amazing let's go I'm so ready I'm
so ready I know I know it will destroy
my algorithm but I don't give a [\h__\h] I
wanna play fun games even if so few
people are watching you guys that watch
it with me are the winners because we
aren't playing the good stuff right
we're getting the good story lines we're
getting the good character developments
we're getting the dramatic character uh
interactions and fights and boss fights
and all that yeah
hell yeah hell yeah
exciting oh yeah Zelda at the end of the
year
oh I think I'll dive into that but I
feel like everyone will be playing that
but I don't care I'll probably one of
the few people who actually played until
the end I'll do my best
and of course I'll finish it I'll finish
everything I finish every game anyway I
think a dragon spider yes
on to a year filled with fun games all
right
foreign
[Music]
um
I wish his games would get better
treatment yeah on YouTube yeah I am um
they're not popular streaming games
I feel like they should be but yeah I
mean I guess 2023 I'll be playing a lot
of games that come out in 2023
so probably even more people will avoid
it than usually because they want to
play it on their own and have yet to
like have time to play it
um so I'm asking you guys to play it
alongside if you want to play it then
play it alongside please yeah don't
don't wait let's play Let's Play Let's
Play okay
hmm
that does happen yeah
my binge Rise Up Before You bled oh I
think you'll have time
don't I don't plan to play that on the
release
yeah this Friday it's releasing so you
guys go stop stop I'll be playing soon
after release
um
yeah
so bingeed because I like it
understandable
no I don't know if I'll skip it I don't
know but it doesn't have priority on my
list right now
okay okay
Rabbit Hole thank you for the pinky yeah
um
[Music]
foreign
thank you for everything always but it
doesn't actually translate to that of
course it doesn't it translates to
manager please raise your Sal ah my
salary I guess
trying to deceive me
no
no no no no no no well you can raise my
salary how about that
Papago is translating your sentence to
manager please raise your salary so
maybe that's what you mean I'll take it
I'll take it literally
through your super chat you are raising
my salary so thank you thank you foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
filled glass as half empty or half full
now I saw it as helpful you should do it
too
um Robert Carney thank you for the
recipe
I'm excited to start another year review
best girl thank you best chicken Robert
mwah happy New Year thank you so much
yeah starting another year we're already
like I don't know three weeks in or so
no two weeks isn't that crazy holy [\h__\h]
time passes so fast I hope we can let it
go a little bit slower this year I want
it to be slower
thank you that Leia thanks for the pinky
hey boss no happy New Year I love you on
kfp so proud of you thank you for
existing my birthday is on January 9th
oh we passed it I've been having a rough
time lately I lost my job but I'm not
losing Iris oh let's hope okay I believe
it will get better may I have a happy
birthday to an employee number
happy birthday to you happy birthday
with you happy birthday in your pants
too happy birthday too
[Music]
oh changed it up a little bit
yeah employee number will be
two
five one
bamboozle
[Music]
yeah happy belated birthday sorry it's
so late but I hope you spent on your
birthday
yeah well you know I don't know people
you like or maybe with yourself but then
if it was with yourself I hope you
enjoyed it and then gave yourself some
presents or so instead of always giving
me presents no you shouldn't give
yourself some presents all right treat
yourself
tweet yourself that was from
parks and Parks and Rec
I love that treat yourself hell yeah
don't forget about yourself all right
but thank you for your support I hope
you'll continue supporting me you're the
schools
baking soda for liters donation for the
red super chat have a happy and healthy
New York I can't wait to see what 20 25
has in store yeah me too me too but I'm
also scared I don't want time to go by
that fast what the [\h__\h] like this year
will be my third year anniversary holy
[\h__\h]
that sounds insane to me like what what
how what
but yeah let's enjoy our time we have
together okay baking soda thank you for
the support so far hopefully long long
long time with you ahead of us
[Music]
wow wow wow
agreed foreign
I know
you were late
how
no one was late one and a half hours
is it because I like I didn't give
enough of a notice ahead of time
oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay I I just saw
I I should probably end the stream like
like now I wish because
um I've been taking a lot of time I mean
they told me I can I can stay I know
it's not a problem but you know uh
for the sake of the sake of Staff
oh yeah okay and well sorry unknown for
not giving you enough notice ahead of
time happy New Year thank you thank you
so much for everything you do because of
you last year such an amazing year for
me you were the best looking forward to
making many more memories so if you went
kfree this year love you forever and
always love you too
well don't worry I I don't blame you for
being late to my stream it's okay you
know what happens but you were there you
still got that record that track record
yeah but don't fail too you know
pressured to keep the track record yeah
okay in 2023 don't pressure yourself
it's okay to take a break and all that
you know you need a break from Chihuahua
and even if you don't need a break from
me but just in general have something to
do okay like you know life offers so
much I don't want to like block like
three years four years five years of
your life
completely because you always gotta be
on standby or whatever you know there's
like so much you could do
um
that's a long time after all so
even if you don't need a break from me
maybe you need a break from life or so
don't don't let those years go to waste
you know go go on like a vacation on a
trip or something okay
because you know I don't know how old
you are but
um
it's just you know
life can be short and even if it's long
then you look back and then you still
wish you had a couple more years and
then
regret this spaghetti right so
enjoy life but thank you for the support
[Music]
and with that at number 224 okay
remember that I'll end it here
foreign
yeah well I mean just one and a half
hours more than I said I would stream
remember the number and we'll be back um
maybe another time to read more of those
super chats we'll get them one day
um
up too quickly
um record one tiny thing she got me
spending thank you thank you for the
super chats fun stream tomorrow on
entity on her Channel we're gonna
I offered her to play Geo guesser
together like we could go on a little
trip she hasn't played it yet and right
now all the Japanese members are playing
it so I'll I'll help her uh or orientate
herself
maybe not only Japan I think I'll make
us go to like America or whatever too
but I mean not like I'll be much of a
help in that situation anyway thank you
guys for watching and German we say uh
I'll figure it okay I was gonna say bye
bye what the [\h__\h] and in Germany yeah
[Music]
um
soon guys soon soon we'll be back to the
usual
way of kiwawa okay so a bit more
patience let's enjoy the time we have
for now with fun collabs okay
um
[Music]
foreign