[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hello
chicken
[Music]
hello
ah
it's been two two or three days I think
[Music]
let me lower this uh oh
okay perfect ah no not perfect
I am in Japan again look
Nikki master
hello good evening it is now half past 6
p.m in Japan
oh yeah I secretly flew back I even
I even tweeted from the airplane
I got so bored I
um bought some Wi-Fi
I mean also partially because I wanted
people to think I'm still home
for safety and so on
yeah bamboozled
how's your sleep schedule going well
um
I'm I'm kind of tired I'm gonna warn you
guys I'm kind of tired
but I have you know what I'm opening up
the energy drink right now because I
told you they have endless free Red Bull
here
oh hopefully it helps
you still feel jet-like well I don't
know I don't know if you can call it
feeling jet-like I'm just tired because
I didn't sleep and I just arrived like
a few hours ago
yeah I really don't like Red Bull well
maybe try again because I always thought
that I didn't like Red Bull
for so many years and then recently I
tried again and now I'm actually
fine with it um
was it a chunk or sweet no
uh
uh the chocolate Suite was scheduled the
stream seat train and the chances tweet
was scheduled but yes I guess I was in
the um I was already traveling
I needed something to tweet about so I
was like oh
oh okay let's tweet about junkers even
though I didn't go to the bed on that
day I went to the vet on the day before
oh I'm gonna throw you up no I threw all
of you no you didn't no you didn't know
anything you know nothing no no no no no
no and then I mean but when I was
tweeting from the airplane what was the
Tweet the other one about me not having
access to Discord was because this
shitty
um the shitty Wi-Fi on the plane it
worked for Twitter and it worked for
like
some other things but it didn't work for
Discord
I wanted to ride to the Denmark
but that one you must have fun you know
I'm how we would not know you would not
know anything no no no
it's obvious when you asked about the
ramp oh but that I was not in the plane
at that time that was something else the
ram I just asked about that when I was
packing
and considering if I take my own laptop
or not
um but right now because you know I just
arrived so I thought uh because I'm
basically straight from the airplane I
thought I wouldn't have time or even if
I did it maybe some things would go
wrong in setting up things at
um
at my place so now I'm in the studio
yeah the Stream time yeah the screen
time kind of gives it away
um
yeah looks like still in the leaderboard
oh
I don't know uh I turned the names on
leaderboard thing off maybe there is a
leaderboard and I I just um I didn't
activate it yet or so
um so I have the honor which is not
feeling anything special it's just
because I'm the only one who asked I'm
I'm not getting special treatment or
anything I mean it's a game where I am
also in so I think it would be fine to
receive special treatment right but it's
not like I can receive special treatment
I'm just the only one who has for access
to the new Hall like you have and then
the moment I saw there and doing an
update I was like
sorry
can I can I maybe get in early again
it's that simple at least only when you
maybe only when you're a whole Live
member I don't think you guys can just
be like excuse me can I can I please
hmm
no [\h__\h]
no no no I don't know why you guys
saying
poor Kaila poor Kaila if she wants to
get Early Access she can ask just like
me all I did was ask
yeah Kay also said
whoever wants Early Access can get Early
Access so
don't try to like put me in a bad light
huh I also need I know I need to I need
to sleep too I I'm tired but
um I want to do this I'm excited
um okay well honestly she does need to
sleep
um I think so it's important sleep is
important but
um
so all that aside and today is an update
for a gen 1 Gen 2
and yeah previously I did early access
for the gamers and gen zero right were
they released at the same time
and this time it's gen 1 Gen 2 and this
account we already have
uh all the previous ones but uh we also
already have some gacha money so I'm not
gonna waste your time with uh getting
the money together don't worry
yeah we're gonna do gacha first
and get some of these characters then
play a little bit then get some of these
characters and play a little bit ideally
I would love to try everyone at least
once uh one warning Joe if you've seen
me play holoca before
you should know that I
um I mean I think last time I played it
around the end I was getting good I
think
but please don't expect like yeah Elite
Gaming or so okay please
um
yeah there is mouse controls now though
when I tested them out and they're
actually very helpful it's been a while
though since I last played so generally
I need to get into the groove again
[Music]
um
yeah I remember that one run where it
was just going on and on and on and on
at the end with uh the last boss amen
small armor not because I wasn't doing
well but just because
I don't know for some reason
it was I what was that what was that
what was the problem I think I just kept
her too far away from me through the
items and all that uh the the the
attacks the skills and everything that I
had
kept small AMA far so far away from me
that even after like 15 minutes
I was still running around being
followed by millions and millions of
moms yeah but I couldn't stay still
either well anyway that was um something
what's up please please my mission today
is not to serve you with Pro gaming my
mission today is just have fun and show
you a little bit
of the characters okay and and the new
features because there's some new
features that I hopefully will show you
alright so let's try
and uh I'll get some noise characters
here we go so I'm not going to die jump
in the show
[Music]
oh I can't understand
cute I think this is for the first time
um that you guys see the the full body
is the bigger size full body is
yeah also not only do you see that for
the first time but isn't that like that
wasn't their last time
that's a new thing
[Music]
yeah okay so we got akina was a senpai
I'm gonna get I'm gonna try to get the
whole gen one first okay
what are the chances
oh man I mean okay the chance is
actually someone can tell me uh there's
four characters
one and four
oh yeah thank you I wasn't asking so
literally but okay
can we get a triple please no I don't
want a triple
here we go
[Music]
hey
cute
I'm very curious how everybody will be
attacking and what their things will be
called their specials and all that very
curious okay we got we got two out of
four we got the God God must be powerful
right I hope so
and all new costumes oh I wasn't made
aware of that so I don't think so
um because I asked like is there
anything I should be looking out for and
and I was told some things but not
costumes I think yeah
here we go here we go just one left with
the standby
ah cute the Earth is so cute look at
those curves
couple
[Music]
perfect now we're just misting
can we get hot tomorrow
that would be amazing if we could gather
it out no okay okay okay that's okay
that happens
[Music]
makes her stronger Russell yeah
come on come on come on
[Music]
okay now we got everyone double
except for hajama
all right yeah I think the problem is I
was asking for hachama but her name is
okay can I please get one Akai hot sauce
and five please please please please
please please
it's because she was like I'm not
hatchimal I'm Akai Hato right now
[Music]
cute
very very cute all right mission
accomplished we play a little bit and
then we get gen 2.
oh my God so many characters look how
it's filling up oh my God there's so
many already
oh and I'll also show you um the new
upgrades if you want you want to see new
upgrades
some things are already upgraded here
I'm I'm not sure I think I think from
here it it's new
because the the this one doesn't look
familiar to me
this one does not look familiar to me
am I yeah that's that one's new and then
from here on all of them I think so
eliminate
grants the use of eliminate on options
when leveling up
eliminate
eliminate oh wait
Oh you mean you can
if there's something you don't want to
have anyway because you're aiming for a
certain build
you can make the chances for the ones
that you actually want higher I guess
okay cool
enhancement rate up increases a chance
of success during enhancements by three
percent per level oh okay cool there's
already some one point in there
oh they have that in Vampire survivors
my brother was playing that um the other
day the day before yesterday he was like
oh there's an update for the vampire
surprise and I'm like what you play a
vampire survivors you should play Holo
cure we have like a better version of
vampire survivors did you know and he's
like nah I don't know and then he
started playing Vampire device for the
rest of the evening like addicted
and then we have marketing increase the
number of fans fans spawns by one per
level
yeah oh this will increase the
difficulty of the game oh okay okay okay
if you want even more of a challenge
then we have stamps oh yeah I want to
unlock this for sure unlock the stamp
system stamps may be dropped by targets
which can modify the main weapon so we
should do that right away
sold one
of the deal
this is new I don't know if this was
announced beforehand uh
was this did you guys know that this was
coming
[Music]
let's collect some stamps it was oh okay
um
okay okay now there you go
let's collect stamps I'll be like
collecting
um Post Office stamps yeah
enchantments unlock weapon enchantments
General weapons May gain enchantment
should I get this one too now
would be would it wouldn't it be a waste
to not get them General weapons making
and at what point can you enchant them
though
all right I got it
and unlock fandoms where characters gain
bonuses based on accomplishments
should I cut this down because look this
one costs 2 2010 and we still need to
get all of the other characters I guess
I'm still getting more money though when
I play afterwards
should I get this now I'm not fandom so
character's game balls I'm not sure what
exactly there's some tails
but okay and weapon limit limits the max
number of weapons that may be gained in
the game oh okay well I guess that's
also
kind of making it a little bit more
difficult like if you wanna yeah
limit yourself
G rank off turn off bonuses gained from
g-ranks on all characters
uh uh-huh and hardcore
was this not here before ultimate
Challenge HP is set to one can massive
bonus scored the longer you survive in
Endless mode oh
and refund all Ayah okay I guess that
was probably also there before okay
okay
[Music]
um I don't know if I I am oh fandoms
look at that oh
so in order to unlock something here for
example
kiwawa or anyone really
unlock requirements complete any of the
following conditions get five wins
okay reach g-rank six
clear all normal stages
okay I don't know how far we'll get with
this today
[Music]
okay yeah well then we gotta get started
all right let's start let's play a
little bit um I'll go with hachama first
and oh yeah there's time mode but we'll
try this one at the end
I thought maybe this one's good at the
end
or I was told this one would be good at
the end
first first we have to
get used to it oh wait
this is out of the Halloween or
oh hard stage I never played this I
never played these two
well is it is it more difficult though
than the grassy planes
[Music]
this one's from today okay today is
Halloween this is Halloween this is
Halloween I'll try but I'm scared what
does she have a red heart create big red
hearts
no surprise in how to form Hearts knocks
enemies back in hatchimal form damage is
increased by 15. okay
uh how do we change the form ah change
of heart there we go create a hard burst
that knocks back enemies or deals 300
percent damage change between half the
form and hatchimal form okay
I I think I put the special on Ctrl
uh let's go
so now I'm using the
oh I'm using the oh my God this already
looks difficult
I'm using the um Mouse thingy the new
mode oh dear oh dear oh dear oh dear
please don't come so close
I was waiting for a new PGM let's go
holy [\h__\h] oh already new enemies
I mean they're all new oh my God oh my
God no no no no no no not the not the
hot tones
don't hurt your idol okay oh coexistence
ah this sounds fun worldwide's strongest
Idol in hot toe form reduce all damage
taken by 20 in hatima from increased
attack by 30 spider related weapons
still 15 more damage so we should get
spider items gain one coexistence per
sec at 60 stacks change of heart becomes
Eldritch form where both had to unhatch
my effects are active for 10 seconds
oh my God
okay interesting
increase damage and oh plushie this
one's new too I think
delay taking damage on any hit by a
Target take only 30 of the damage
initially then take the remaining damage
greatly oh and you can re-roll oh don't
eat though
and this one's not me from last update
hey I never saw this one probably
because I didn't unlock something
specific or so
I don't remember seeing this one
oh no you mean re-roll is is old okay I
never noticed that one okay I'll go for
um
this one first ah if I even survive
yeah bye where's the food
holy [\h__\h] I mean this this is obviously
more difficult than grassy planes
already
oh my God
as a scale I forgot about the scale okay
um
um maybe I should increase movement
speed
uh because they're catching up on me
limiter
oh yeah pick up brains I want both
oh oh
okay okay I could have done that more
like in the middle of them
um Purity and insanity and had to form
heel free HP every three seconds in
hatchimal form Red Heart can poison with
healing okay poison targets around
dealing 40 damage per second but wait
right now I think we changed to hachama
form right because well I suppose she
starts off with how to form
so now we wouldn't get the region I
think
well we should get this one though
[Music]
oh hey that's a drink speaking off let
me take a sip
[Music]
um
increase haste by 10 speed by 30 percent
reduce Max HP by 20 no thanks
let's increase the damage
oh okay it's looking better now but I
would like some healing
signs of hearts and spring rate is by 10
percent
um
probably good
wow wow the range of the poison
well can I go up there ah [\h__\h] I got
stuck
okay it doesn't go up there this map is
pretty small I guess not endless like
the other one yeah I need to need to get
to know the room I'll give it another
try
but as I said we're not here to get like
super uh Pro gameplay today
we're here to explore the oh God why did
I go there
explore the game okay so forgive me if
I'm
knots
uh clearing everything first try
[Music]
come on come on
oh nice Okay
um
I think I'll I'll take Purity and
Insanity first because
why weren't you here last time oh wait
oh my God what's that okay
so I saw I saw a logo
[Music]
I have to go there
ah
should I
um increase damage I think I'll increase
damage
okay okay I'll go after the second what
the [\h__\h] is that light oh it says to
stamp
[Music]
good one good one get the stamp
um
oh attached
attach
apply on the weapon wait this is is this
the enchantment
if I can apply it does that mean it's
the enchant
no it's a stamp bomb stamp
wait bomb stem does that mean we
actually is it in chat with nstem what
confirm
attacks have a 10 chance to cause an
explosion that hits nearby Targets for
30 of the weapons damage oh it is it is
both
[Music]
whoa
ah
if we wanna you know have the whole
spider cooking thing then there would be
the lava bucket here but
this I'll upgrade the main weapon first
here they come here they come
uh oh
spider cooking
here it is like I asked for it and I get
what I asked for it's so nice today is
like really I say something and it
happens it's crazy
yeah bye oh wait I'll be there I'll be
right there
[Music]
okay so we stopped poisoning
I'm stuck
add an additional heart or maybe more
spider cooking let her cook let her cook
yeah
not cooking right now oh yeah bye yep
yep yeah bye okay I [\h__\h] up I [\h__\h]
up I [\h__\h] up
or did I oh
Apple Grado
we have two things that we can upgrade
right because there's two
of them
let's
do
um
[Music]
wait no ah
okay
Red Heart awakened at the end of the
operation Hearts shoot outwards
all right here we go we awakened it
okay now
[Music]
I want a banger oh my God
is that oh kubuki Senpai is
oh my God
why are they exploding on me no
okay now what do we want to focus on
next Purity Insanity Maybe
yeah
combo Explorer
jumping from above I need some food
am I which now now I should be the
healing form right yeah yeah okay I'm
healing up
what is that oh
it's a huge matches
okay is that the one that's
not Sonic
is nice because she's she's a Healer but
then she also is I don't know poisonous
are you excited for the update guys are
you already like getting your coins or
do you already have enough coins from
like last time you played the game
oh CEO stairs fires rapid tears at
random targets what that's Duke
very hyped farming coins all right good
luck
you have all the time in the world after
the update too so no worries
that's from last update
one
unbelievable
[Music]
downtown
okay okay okay hell yeah that's what I
need that's what I'm talking about
hey I'm in the groove now baby I thought
the stage was pretty difficult but I'm I
think I'm in the groove she says and
it's probably gonna die soon
oh okay um
I'm between spider cooking and limiter
haha
[Music]
all right spider cookie more spider
cooking
it's it fits oh God
uh well I should have done that earlier
but now I'm healing back we're good we
good
sour chance
[Music]
pictures but there was some food there
okay oh chicken's feather
five I'll revive instantly hail fifty
percentage be an all-known boss targets
are defeated
hmm
who's better could this possibly be I
needed I needed in order to go on longer
right
now
oh what's what's that range
do do
holy [\h__\h]
is that
A Healer A Healer what
you mean a Healer or a Healer for home
oh wait I forgot about the Yago stats
don't they get food no wait what
our young old piggy bank
um
[Music]
get him I'm trying to get off go after
him
they're healing bombs
to get rid of them
glow stick damage was 15. is that like
uh that Bob it's like oh my God I'm
gonna
wait
I think I got him oh my God
look he's up Sam the croony stamp
I love corny snack okay apply there's
another one though
uh uh what does that do delay between
attack reduce the delay between attacks
Oh by 15
and
we can stamp attacks have a 20 chance to
reduce attack and death of targets by 20
and five percent temporary flower flower
flower flower
it's an En meme
all right
now put that on there on it
okay okay
I don't think I was
ah I want to survive I want to survive
[Music]
it's not that bad except we calm down
again oh
okay is that like the like the mid boss
like uh fubotzera for example in the
other map
wait so when does this stage end
at
if if this one comes out at five minutes
hmm
oh it kind of came out at four minutes
so maybe maybe 20 minutes here too
um not that old
stage it
wait it's only been four minutes it
feels like way longer
die
I'm sorry I'm sorry
uh
Phoenix Center didn't help for too long
okay but I think we're gonna try a
different character now
oh
buy Targets in front
of Meek
and vampire Mal becomes banned for seven
seconds what all Targets are frozen in
any non-bossed Targets close to Mel are
banned from exist from Ben from
existence so they are deleted right
all types are from any non-bus Targets
close to Mill are banned from Susan
uh-huh
well the whole band thing is because of
her arms
exposure
around her chest I think
okay we're gonna try the Halloween
Castle again although
can I what if I do this now
is this a good idea
yeah bye
never mind I'm too weak to finish him
off now
hahaha
couple copy
cup of coffee
Mary used bite
and what do we have genius vampire on
live steel heels create one bat that
flies to the closest Target to deal 90
damage ooh what does that mean on
lifestyle heels
what does that mean
but that sounds good
that sounds good to me
[Music]
GA made the cooking ah I'm lucky because
I had uh I had made a minute cooking
before don't you need lifestyle for said
that's what I was thinking like doesn't
do we need something in order to make
that work
yeah she has a cooking one too every 15
seconds gather Two Men and many cooking
close by targets will slowly move
towards the cooking to eat it which
deals slow damage
oh
are you trying to imply that her cooking
is not good
wait can I eat the cooking too
looked like I picked it up that was
wasn't that metal cooking or is it
something else
I never liked steel thing when eating
food Mana drinks juice gaining 30 attack
and speed for 5 seconds
oh the next four weapon attacks will
have life seal oh oh
should I go for this
oh she feels super super fast right now
okay maybe now upgrade
oh the game really I mean I got used to
it at some point but now it's even
easier with the mouse
I remember you guys telling me to use
the controller back in the day and I
tried but
I
am I sorry I need to get through
oh no my chicken's better
mouth seems amazing yeah
it helps
map is bigger full of carpet all right
all right how do you know
[Music]
did you get early access to them huh
all right we're going down oh I'll try
to
maybe it's bigger it ends there I've
already seen it
huh
all the headphones are pretty slow
thankfully
I'm gonna need some some healing
I'll go I'll go up then okay
fine I already went up
but maybe I got stuck on the sides
like a like an old wedding chapel can I
can I have that
[Music]
yeah
okay but it ends here okay okay
I don't regret going here bye
ah
what was that golden golden bats oh my
God do they give me more
okay okay okay we have like a special
plug type as a Coco but
um
[Music]
yeah maybe I should use a chicken
sweater again
hmm
again
up
sorry I got
I think I I I
swallowed a uh something into my air air
hole
because apparently did you guys know
that you are when you liquid from
drinking something goes pretty much your
air hole is different did you know
I didn't know until recently or did I
know maybe I knew but I wasn't quite
aware of it
what
uh I'm never too confident when I'm not
taking it this time what
hide
how are you guys doing that
oh I see a light I see a Holy Light
is that what I think it is
wait no it's it's just that it's just a
shadow wow
why didn't I do this until now that's
the real question
okay
um I bent them it's a nice special
couple
the light effects are so cool
good job on those
oh the Healer
fantastic
[Music]
um
should we get genius vampire level 2 or
hmm
oh they're healing up
one or four
okay two bags of flies to the closest
Target yeah let's go for that one
can I get some hail too please sir I'm
an enemy I'm totally an enemy please no
no
ready to revive kills everyone
get those EXP
I didn't realize I didn't renounce that
last time
[Music]
okay what's going on here you guys
getting stuck huh those cheeks filled
with nuts
are
I'm sorry
I was talking about nuts and this is
what happens
what what a squirrel usually fills their
cheeks with nuts no
should we give manderson but never try
or change character
[Music]
try easier map
I think
it depends on what our goal is do I just
or what my goal is do I just want to
show you everything
uh like in terms of characters and
attacks or do I want to go until the end
with a character which I think oh
this breastplate looks familiar to me
because if I go for the easier one then
we'll go like 20 minutes with one
character and I don't know if I can show
you all characters then
anyway reduce damage taken by 10 and
speed by 20 percent
oh
when attacked there is a 50 chance that
attacker also takes 200 damage oh 200
my God
Yes actually it's good that we uh die
the whole time
so I can show you more
yeah you guys can probably try that out
yourself maybe I'll take one quick look
but around the end when I have a
character that I feel comfortable with
iron swings a large every food lion
following aims Direction and what sorry
Summons of Festival drums pressing the
special button attack at the right time
will create stronger sound waves oh no
it's like a rhythm game
it the right time
so I activate the special then I have to
press the button again at like a certain
timing
I am not a rhythm gamer let me tell you
that
whoa
let's while they're coming let's work on
yako Sample it is say
the curse of calling everyone senpai
has now gone so far and then I call
younger senpai
he's definitely not my Sapphire
[Laughter]
something felt very wrong when I said
that God and children oh my God oh my
God God cheerleader if a tiger attacks
man city there is 24 25 chance and a
massive beam from the heavens will
strike that Target dealing 300 percent
damage
that sounds amazing uh cheerleader
finally is when hitting a Target within
100 pixel gained two percent attack and
one percent speed for 4 seconds up to 30
attack and fifty percent I think we
start with God
okay
[Music]
all right
yeah it's quite a good range to maybe if
we die
on what's that oh my God
Holly Molly
I just saw like a line I thought
how are you playing Skippy rope or what
what the [\h__\h] who was that that name
hey where did that come from
what what enemy spot oh my God
no I don't
feel like some kind of like big enemies
enemy uh throwing at me where where
where where are you where are you hiding
okay here we go
huh
what is the timing
I don't know what I'm doing okay when is
the timing I I saw some Lions but I'm
gonna know what I was doing
[\h__\h]
[Music]
is it like
I don't know
I got like two hits maybe yeah okay we
will have to look at that again for that
maybe in a less stressful environment
ideally
oh
collateral damage
okay here we go thank you that's exactly
what I needed right now
[Music]
[Applause]
it's tough it's tough out here man
what the [\h__\h]
ah it's her yeah bye face say it's a
representative every 12 seconds games
say so negate the next hit and become
unseasonable for five seconds
while Ann says so close by targets take
200 damage and stand for
uh
0.5 seconds uh-huh
[Music]
all right I think we'll go for that one
then
in character your bike
[Music]
look at my speed
on it
okay I think my special's almost ready
and here we go
what where
I'm so confused
I don't think this is my kind of
character
probably also because I currently have
the special button on Ctrl it's kind of
um difficult to use it so often
in a row
yeah but I think
yeah I mean I know it goes like to the
middle and all that but
[Music]
I do understand like the system whoopsie
anyway I need healing
um anybody left some food out there for
me
oh my God that's cool
thank you
no why is there no food spotted
[Music]
oh
all the impact that every food eye has
damn oh cutting boards
um is 10 percent
um
what should we go from guys
foreign
defensive wall that damages targets
behind you hmm Effectiveness is
increased on certain characters
wait ah is that why it's cooled on minus
10 percent
on Oh I thought this was like at random
but
um
is that why
ah
[Music]
foreign
no no that's not it it was
random there's no reason whatsoever
right right right right yeah
oh my God
I don't know if the wall is helping me
though is it helping me
I'm not sure
but oh my God that's a
[Music]
fingers on the keyboard
let's try to hit those ctrls
ah
what I know I know I know
it's a rough special if we find the
special yeah maybe
um if it was above the
above the space key I might do better
maybe like b b for Benny Benny special
uh
yeah uh keybinds
but don't don't expect a huge uh change
or maybe maybe
the right one yet okay
I'm gonna try again
ah
you made yours cute I think I used to
have it on cue
and I think generally Ctrl or Q or
whatever is fine
but just very much change it
[Music]
okay we start maybe with ibifurion let's
get that every food I awakened
as soon as possible yummy yummy yummy I
had my first bite into an epifurai
recently thanks to uh oh oh I was gone
for a second oh no no no no
I don't know I was just talking about
how I had my first taste of an epiphurai
recently thanks to Ahmed because she
ordered
something that came with an epiphudai
in case you don't know what it is it's a
like uh it's a big shrimp
uh fried basically
yeah when we were in enoshima um
yeah a good chance eh YouTube dead again
not for everybody it seems
I guess yeah in tempura
that's actually different huh everywhere
and every tempura is different huh
I'm gonna go for cheerleader
oh I think that I found myself a cheer
mashup mashup
it's different but I think it's similar
YouTube please
seems to be a regional thing maybe
mom
okay
[Laughter]
I should have maybe gone for God I'm not
sure
oh my God
I hate like yeah maybe three times
what's up
I was looking for V
oh my god
[Music]
um
oh my oh my God
how fitting
uh what did I saying oh I actually
wanted to tell you
so
today you know sometimes I'm better at
playing games when I tangent so let me
tangent
we'll see if that's true or not yeah
today I I arrived in Japan
and you know
I saw a television crew
for for uh television program in Japan
that I really like actually
oh
Google
[Music]
I was not on the Telly because I was
joking I was joking with Gemma like ha I
should I should totally get interviewed
and then they would ask me like hey you
are nanishing in your phone what did you
come to Japan for and I would be like
well oh see now that now it doesn't have
the buff so it is random
well uh can't say
uh oh
[\h__\h]
I guess we're upgrading the awakened
every food ion
ization yeah
[Music]
I don't have to oh I guess ah okay if I
just walk away from this with Escape uh
then I can go back to this later oh okay
I never did that before because it was
never necessary
foreign
yeah it's a it's a program where uh they
go to the airport with a microphone and
they just speak to uh wait
what on Earth
sitting close to that show it's funny it
really is
it really is
um so yeah then they talk to the
foreigners they're like hey when did you
come to Japan but what's your purpose
and then sometimes when they find
someone who's like a little bit above
average interesting
and they
um
they asked them if they can follow them
[Music]
which one should I go for yeah there's a
Healer [\h__\h] him
mama
wax they're all good
let's go about a bucket then all right
um oh
yeah and then they would follow them
now we can upgrade it how about that
here we go
and yeah make like the program about
them for a while
um but I don't know it's a really fun
program it's been around for a long long
time and I always my whole life I was
like I want to be on that oh we just got
the breastplate now
um
should we should we
what
I'm not gonna say it
and I think during this the corona times
I think they probably didn't have the
program for a while because you know
foreigners wouldn't come into the
country
[Applause]
what's that scale
[Music]
I'm so useless and you just you guys are
just like yeah you're useless in general
haha thank you
what's going on
sorry about your ears
up
I don't remember saying that
but that's what you're thinking
um this this enemy yeah this Hawthorne
dark evil hot tone doesn't like attack
like downwards sideboards or everywhere
oh my God
sorry uh defeat the heel I can't get
this here
[Music]
um
and you don't need your ears anyway
okay
[Music]
so I want to stay alive
okay
oh my God
oh my God food food food food
[Music]
and ever
hold a knock back
knock back nice
[Music]
guys
no don't worry I'm in the studio
me
I try my best but there at the end I was
actually able to hit the drum several
times but
um it didn't really there were not many
enemies around me
foreign
today so I'm in the studio
for today but in the next coming days
I'll be um
hopefully streaming from my room as well
okay let's do akidoso senpai
I'm making it to five minutes constantly
at least
yeah yeah
okay so we have Ike sends to the closest
as well as random cards and fires a beam
and then we have shadies
and singing otherworldly folk songs Oh
summoning a storm of rose petals
stealing 50 damage and inflicts 20 slow
each while healing for 20 per second oh
healing
shall we do the grassy planes a little
bit hope hoping that maybe I'll get a
bit further only a little bit I mean
we'll die anyway we won't make it to 20
minutes probably but
okay
her hair her twin tails
[Music]
okay so here I can speak a bit more
calmly
I know
yes
crit damage was time
all right if this is all you got to
offer to me
then I guess I'll go over somebody oh
you guys want to see another one
Button had Crick damage plus ten percent
oh
okay oh
is that her butt
oh I wrote my favorite too I wrote my
favorite targets within 100 pics I have
a 15 chance to gain a debuff attack
speed or death every 1.5 seconds each
stack debuffs 10 of that stat up to 30
percent okay
while moving gain one stack of belly
dance per second if Aki stops moving
unleash a person deals 40 per damage
damage per second oh the it's like my my
dancer thingy having to continuously
move around
okay
anyway what I was saying is I didn't get
interviewed but I saw them and I I wish
I was interviewed by them because ah
[\h__\h] I tapped out
I survived
um because I used to watch that program
and I I was always like a big fan you
know and I saw them interviewing a lot
of people
just wanted to tell them what I came to
do but this time I wouldn't even be able
to tell them what I came to do
and
[Music]
foreign
level two
also tomorrow
or for some of you guys probably today
or a lot of you guys probably today
um I asked Ina
if she wants to do a Nintendo Direct oh
watch along
together
and she said yes so we'll probably do
that it's early in the morning though
um but I think I'll sleep early today so
we'll be fine
and we'll probably be on Ina's Channel
most likely because I'll just have her
set up everything
because I'm still like I just arrived I
still have to like unpack my things so
we're doing it on Ina's Channel I think
yeah
you'll be able to wake her up no she's
like waking up so early every day anyway
it seems anyway look at those and when
the target receives a stat debuff oh
there is a 50 chance that the target
takes 50 damage for each type of stat
debuff they currently have
damn
[Music]
yes she missed this
I saw her announcing that she missed it
did she oversleep
um
don't worry I I think it was both of us
being involved one of us should be able
to wake up
um so I have um dance planned for
tomorrow and then I need to go to a
dance lesson
uh
um
[Music]
yeah I arrived and I immediately have a
hard schedule
should I take the I'm warmer before the
debuff so that the mookie doesn't make
sense also I need to do my special skill
oh yeah the rose petals where exactly
does that again I guess it's doing
something that's for sure
and now I will go
they're cooking again wow it's beautiful
[Applause]
oh stop
hey we haven't gotten one in a while
okay what is that
weapon will sound like
there's someone perfect
there is no other effect
a trombone champ
do you hear it wait I'll be quiet in a
second oh
I have so many choices those you'll help
me decide I want all three of them
okay
and a drink definitely working
Hallelujah but I also need to
[Music]
ah thank you for that
psycho ax thank you
[Music]
I don't randomly
oh my God
that's so dorky and dirty I love it it's
cute
[Music]
don't
ah
level up aromatherapy
on this map I'm much better
because I have more time to also upgrade
everything before they all come at me
with everything they got
um
[Music]
I think we have to upgrade the aroma
therapy but oh you guys
[Music]
oh yeah
what about my salary
what about my celery
sorry Taco Daddy's get out of the way
yay
[Music]
oh so much better
so useless man
at least this one's endless so you can
go wherever
whatever
is my special ready no it's not
three dudes the more the more ice the
more dudes I can do
you do you dude
[Music]
foreign
I think out of those four
aquino's as far might be my favorite
in terms of like how how well
it works with my
uni style or who did we play first
katama I think hatsama right felt pretty
good too because she does healing so
thank you
yeah that helps a lot with surviving
Emma
[Music]
is
people who just come into the stream now
they'll be like why is her attack making
sounds what does that have to do
how much more can it stack wait oh yeah
it's at 221. I won't stop I won't stop
and
oh I have to stop moving
I finally does it on its own okay okay
okay and should I get another belly
dancing and then to stop moving now
you're scared to stop moving
what
at least you're special yeah okay okay
holy [\h__\h] can we do that again that's
amazing
[Music]
again
I'm gonna do it again
skip
those those Hips Don't Lie oh away again
let's go
that's amazing that was absolutely
amazing
y'all
use that at heart uh hard mode I I think
that is very recommendable
impact
[Music]
it's gonna get nerved
So speaking of nerved hips or so
I got the last and final
upgrade for my butt
uh for my 3D butt
all right feeling the boards oh no
uh and
[Music]
um
I I must say I'm a bit worried maybe I
maybe I overdid it
I hope you guys won't think I overdid it
but I I was like oh oh yeah let's just
go with this
I guess let's just go of it I don't know
I didn't see it in movement yet I only
saw like um screenshots and then
confirmed it's okay
um so I I'm I'm not sure literally
impossible never too much
no I I mean you say I would I could
still revert it but that's not for sure
uh I'll just upgrade the cycle X now
um
because they were like we want to make
it final so
preferably no more changes after that
for a long time ideally because they're
busy with other stuff you know
um
dogs
yeah but I'm
um looking forward to seeing my what
even that many animations on screen but
I was like whatever
[Music]
okay here we go
this might be a good run
foreign
[Music]
but maybe just in case
yeah okay thanks for the membership
thank you soon
also I don't wanna I'm wait I already
have a hundred
should I stand now wait until there's
some more enemies here
what the [\h__\h] is this sticker that's a
sticker
oh
I think so is the Sun a reference right
size up this looks like a planet a
planet stamped in a weapon here we go
increases attack size by 15.
okay
[Music]
thank you
yo the lasers are so cool though I
didn't know actually Senpai can shoot
lasers out of her hair they
that's why they're like this attached
like that
oh oh
what was it I just stand and then it uh
happens right I just have to stand
it's hard to stand
I just have it in me
should I do it now okay here
[Music]
I love that okay she's my current new
favorite character
Young
I think I didn't really want that I
chose it by accident but okay we can
combine it with the spider cooking
it's gonna be for a lot of people
[Music]
okay
here we go
we Max spider cocoon for now
yeah there's new collabs but
um
yeah I don't know if we'll see them
today because I have to unlock the the
weapons for the new collapse first I
guess
oh hi
oh
[Music]
go for the max or continue the lava
bucket don't Shield
I only to unlock them yeah I don't know
how far I'll get with that
finally
[Music]
okay oh CEOs tears
and the bucket and the cycle acts
beautiful
[Music]
I'll take them all give them to me wait
but the CEOs tears
wasn't that new
because then maybe there's a collab with
the CEO's tears
gosh I really need to go to the island
meeting but I will not go
[Music]
okay wait there are new costumes I was
just told oh we'll have to check that
out in a second
spider and tears
oh why do you know about it
what do you know about it did it already
exist
lava X
[Music]
and then tears and spider
it's old
ER
[Music]
I never saw it before I want to see it
and
I think it's time to stand
oh
okay okay
it will not be the end of me
I got into the dangerous situation there
but oh
switch that okay I guess we'll get rid
of the dooding because all it does is
duding which strengthen
spend the found stamp to level the
selected stamp up
wait would the trumpet be upgraded or
the sword no no
official
now we have to get rid of the Dawn no we
have to get okay we have to learn what
this one is
attack up okay I'm sorry we've heard
enough of the two thing if you want to
hear more dudes you have to play um
trombone trombone champ
uh okay that one just um is like left on
the ground
no more I can make the doodles
don't
don't don't
know
[Music]
I'm gonna put a bucket first
all right
you guys said what the CEO of tears and
the bucket
is that what you said
[Music]
cookie oh okay then I can combine the
bucket with the I ax okay
originally I wanted to combine the
bucket with the cooking but okay
[Music]
oh here we go I'm not gonna use it yes
but it's amazing akidosa basically has
two special attacks
so
we have pretty much
oh hey
now I will use it's good that I waited
I never did it that fast before
foreign
music I never heard this one before
[Music]
gorilla Spa attack damage is multiplied
by 1.5 times so
do you guys mine are actually I can't
hold him back anymore I need to go in an
idle meeting I'm so sorry I have to go
I'll be right back
[Music]
the energy drink man it's the energy
drink
I should mute I should mute oh my God
not that some other a whole life member
walks in and streams instead of me no no
okay BRB
I'm back uh
[Music]
hello oh where are the headphones I have
the headphones in my head
[Music]
did someone come in and stream instead
of me probably not right
okay
let's get back
what do you mean don't drop oh oh what's
my mouse on here don't worry I was just
I will not Drop it like it's hot don't
worry oh my God
I got a lucky day achievement
[Music]
um
I'll try I'll go for the bucket first
and then we'll do the tears
oh there's so much exp lying around
can't let that go the waste
trumpet though the trumpet must be less
to go go to waste yes
that's a short meeting you think so
can I not like I don't know which one I
would strengthen if I would pick it up
if I pick that one up and then click
strength and does it strengthen the one
I just picked up or let's pick
strengthen the one I already have
I want to strengthen the sword
oh my dad
ah
okay uh
we're doing
the ax with
the black kid right
yeah okay
I mean now
there's nothing to worry about
it
we're going for the win
hey
katana
cut I mean
the floor is on fire so no one
can get close to me and I also I'm
already about a close to 200 belly
dancing
[Music]
although we really don't need the
healing look at me
back
okay next time I go for something new
it's too easy
see this is a problem now it's going so
well but okay if we clear it then we're
we're happy to change character oh wait
but um if I
in fact the good thing is I'll I might
unlock something right
for like I don't know
a new item and a new collab item or so
so actually I guess we do want to clear
all right all right all right
okay now I feel the pressure
why did I just remind myself of that no
no I [\h__\h] it up
God damn it oh that red one just did
nothing right now because I already
picked up everything isn't the red one
so that you pick up everything
's not yet not yet
the hips my one shot
yeah I'll definitely not have that
problem again of endlessly
running away from her
let me do this first like
yeah yeah
did you guys see Callie's new outfit by
the way holy [\h__\h]
that was incredible
it's so cute I mean I think the
silhouette already pretty much gave away
everything
but once you see it for real it's just
it oh my God
which ones should I go they're both Max
Nails I think yeah and these two are
both Max so I can go for something new
um four
three
we don't really need more damage but we
also don't really need more healing so
whatever the pressure is
not there
oh okay
not a hold on maybe we'll end up
combining those I think that's a
combination right plug type ASA Coco and
the glow stick ghost neck no it wasn't
family that was fan beam that was the
beam the beam those two don't work huh
oh
new step
wait that snap looks like a koala
related stamp Maybe
I could be wrong
well this by the way again increased
haste by 10 speed by 30.
I'll I'll go with something that I
already have
no I fought because of the colors but
that's is that a bang
is that
her hair or
the hair or is that Mrs squeaks I don't
know I'm not sure
but the the turquoise reminded me of my
feathers
wait what weapon will fire backwards
there is no other
but no thank you
wait but can I now strengthen spend the
found stem to level the selected stamp
okay okay okay
um
no I wanna strengthen in this one for
example
okay okay okay 20 chance
well if I find the other one again the
dude
you know then we'll do that
[Music]
he powers
hello
Broken Dreams I never saw this one
before guys the dream is dead and
there's no hope bubble Shield is uh
Bubble Shoot also slows targets
okay oh my God
[Music]
it
which means it will slow amen so let me
go to that
I know it was last update but I still I
never saw it
I haven't seen it either
I'm not the only one
um
[Music]
sure whatever it doesn't matter
can we just
May the time go by faster Emma 300 belly
dancing
[Music]
speed it up speed it up
Megan 500 we're making a thousand
comment me deadbeat
anyway I kinda also want
s a pajama Style
uh outfit one day like counties but uh
this time we're going all for different
themes
so I will not be getting something like
that this time although I always thought
that you know
it could be very useful
[Music]
um
It just fits many stream Styles is that
by the way are the effects and
everything too loud
curious to see what you all get well as
I said before mine will probably take a
long time so because I'm getting a
different artist
and oh this seems okay okay a lot of
animals yeah
[Music]
yeah getting a different artist because
no time not available oh my God
I felt stressed out maybe it wasn't
necessary but whatever
[Music]
yeah we all have different themes
I don't even know what the other girls
are going for
but I'm also very
yeah that's the thing like you know
I think especially with en members
uh
there's like really really well-known
super famous artists
and that's cool but you know they're
also super freaking busy and that's
their face suck no I see my face moving
triple
all right oh
oh fight oh I don't need any more the
triple never
happened
I'm being spoiled
hi Max
oh my God
overpowered engine
it's like an unboxing stream yeah
uh
what should have dropped it did I what
did I did I drop something else
can I drop something
there's something down there
right there's nothing down there that's
how do you know is that like the stamp
s
yeah okay it's strengthen it strengthen
it ah
strengthen okay okay
now we got that
yeah
oh my God look at me
I'm bringing apocalypse upon this world
sorry to all you cutie patooties it's
all back
you may as well just kneel down in front
of me right now
and
tell me that you will vow to support me
safe defense
yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm saving the fans
they're from themselves
let's I guess
oh we're almost at 500 belly dancing
what the [\h__\h] is that is that a sticker
one second
there's so many effects that it might
affect the bit range is it going well so
far oh we can upgrade it now unless this
increase damage by 20 for each empty
weapon slot is this akurism of course
Empire is down
wait I don't have an empty weapon
on it
so we just strengthen yeah
[Music]
ironically this is useless when you find
it so late
okay then please
strengthen
let's go
foreign
[Music]
my flight thankfully very empty you know
what I'll go for Super chatur China
drop down coins
and I had empty seat next to me but I
realized you know my flight back uh last
time was also very empty
and I was premium economy and that's why
then also in this flight and I realized
when the flight is so empty I prefer to
I would prefer to be a normal economy
do you know why
I would like to be downgraded do you
know why oh oh wait I'll pick that up in
a second
because premium economy seats even if
the seat next to you is empty
you can't lie down sideways
yeah
so I think I would be actually more
comfortable in the in the normal economy
seat and Crowther weapon caused a small
snug snuck back knock knock back knock
knock
increase knockback strength five forty
percent
if effect already exists
um
Maybe
can I strengthen something again
oh I can
or should I use ah whatever we're
already so
so powerful
it doesn't even matter
[Music]
anyway
yeah yeah yeah yeah
interesting flight route because last
time we Flew Over the North Pole and
this time we flew uh below around
uh you know with what what did we even
fly over I'm not sure but we flew all
the way down south
so that was interesting
oh Decked Out level 50. achievement oh
fit I don't think I ever got to level 50
privately like privately what I mean in
my previous streams
yourself now we didn't go to the South
Pole
not quite
blah blah blah blah blah
the last time I got uh
I got a Oh wait [\h__\h] sell it sell it
yeah money
I got a little piece of paper that said
congratulations you have visited the
North Pole by flying over it
it's almost
time
I'm gonna wait to use my belly dancing
and all that
um until Amma is here but maybe the
special attack I will use soon I'm not
sure
so hungry by the way I haven't eaten for
a couple of hours
airplane food was okay though just okay
I wonder if it caps out at 900 oh wait
one probably we probably won't see that
because we're at 600 now
because the dreaded 90 minutes no
I guess I've sometimes I've died around
that time
but just to be extra safe everyone
I'll take the headphones
[Music]
belly dancing oh my God okay I'm using
this now
all right all right all right this is
the studio PC by the way
oh my God
[Music]
I want to stand I want to stand I'm
scared do it do it
I had to do it I got to nervous and you
know what this way we got rid of the lag
was it worth it
wasn't worth it
I think it was we'll be fine with Ahmed
um
look up 30 seconds we're fine we're fine
we're fine we're fine
[Music]
no it wasn't of course it was
I think I'll actually go for the
headphones because I'm scared I'm a
scared little baby
wait a second uh
I wanna uh settings uh how do I
damage numbers no damage numbers please
I'm so scared ah
oh is that Pokemon attacks have 20
chance to slow targets by 15 until 30
weapon damage from Five Seconds
[Music]
I like that one
potato pieces
what
oh that is well it fits because we were
just having a potato poteto PC moment
huh
swap should I swap it
and then can I strengthen this one
I'm so scared oh my God
please
go away please go the [\h__\h] away
cool
[Music]
chicken feather why is the stickers
feather
disrespectful the disrespect can you
believe it
oh
[Music]
okay
oh is she jumping again I don't see her
shadow
I got stuck for a moment
then
okay I did it I don't know you know it
was pretty low
just now so
there we go
[Music]
guys
ah I can do it
I can clear it after all yay
thank you for the win
um
oh did I tell you guys I met akisen bye
a while ago
[Music]
I met her she was so sweet I don't think
I told you
did I I'm not sure I don't I'm not sure
if I told you yeah let's go to the main
menu
from the last update or so as well Devil
head attacks deal 1.2 times damage if
the target is farther than 150 picks
that's Neo okay away from the player if
less than 150 pixels away damage is
reduced by 10 percent
our damage is reduced by temperature
no
okay so the one new one was the first
one right
and we wanted to check oh wait why do I
say that again
the outfits
was it
no no no no no where
do I see the outfits again in the gacha
foreign
this one I think we saw before and then
the Casual no wait maybe maybe this one
is new
maybe the the fancy ones are new
casual one we had before
yeah as far as I know uh only for the
myth members yeah
but we'll see we'll check
[Music]
um
the party dresses
[Music]
on her as a pixel art
Kelly in your fancy red dress pretty
lady
oh and then me
oh looks good
looks really good
still with the weapons though
even in the fancy dress
the other ones I think
um
let me see
yeah the Santa one oh she got the
redesign
oh you can still use the old one
but I think yeah by default
now
she should be this one I suppose
yeah 2.0
oh wait and the other one should be
did they always have the key
board
yeah oh okay well then just look at it
again because it's pretty
casual
Dead Steel come on that's new
nice work
in jeans and the coat I love her casual
outfit
it's so simple but our father yeah
father should have it too then right
oh there it is she looks like a school
girl and if it's just a pixel all right
it looks like a school girl outfit
[Music]
nice
peace
let me check here just in case
you guys tell me if that's new that
looks new to me
oh
yeah oh my God there's so many
music
too right they didn't happen uh separate
a different outfit right
[Music]
there we go
out
Corner cute gamer outfits gamer outfits
oh good oh do you cut tall okay
wonderful lovely maybe just the gamers
but who knows maybe gen zero let me see
uh
for everyone
[Music]
my God that's yeah it's a huge update
oh
oh my God her old outfit wait
God
wow it looks really cool in in pixel
Young
foreign
[Music]
but okay this one's nice too
ah you know it looks like
she's censored because of the pixel
stuff
and I mean
it looks like her leg area you know it's
mostly naked so the censoring makes a
lot of sense
oh
cute
cute yes I love her outfit
I want so pretty so cute
I love that one
oh and Miko said bye
[Music]
they're like also kind of school uniform
inspired one with the cat hats cat head
so cute
[Music]
y'all
yeah I didn't realize what was it was I
Colin
chicken
also I ask for example as I call it
changes too I guess it just yeah it
changed with the redesign
[Music]
she wears contact
the attention
to detail I mean I guess it's not like
the small detailed big detail
but they wouldn't have outfits for Gen 1
that they just added right
now
no okay okay okay
it's okay it's already way too much but
with that we will go and because I I
tried them all right okay so let's try
Jen
General
go get that gotcha
got more money now too
time I obviously the most I want super
to Senpai but I'm hoping that's the
Wonder Senpai will be easy to play with
too
here we go
oh
cute pretty
I love how that's wrapped around her leg
[Music]
okay one out of five
so far
so good I mean what else was gonna
happen
next
[Music]
cute oh my God she looks so cute
10 out of 10.
okay
oh my throat hurts it's probably the
energy drink
and I'm hungry but I'm gonna go by the
way for another
um one and a half hours then I have to
leave
no more Red Bull I have nothing but Red
Bull right now
[Music]
no dupe so far
wonderful
so cute oh my God
the big Pixar is so good
I love that Edition
they put so much effort and so much love
into it oh
why we're just missing aqua sapphire
and so they're so nice on my money
thank you
[Music]
this is hard to get and she don't say
bye oh
onion onion and garlic friends please
maybe there's an onion and garlic um
attack or something for them who knows
onion garlic onion garlic
the base for cooking everybody needs an
onion in their life you know
here
so cute
now we're just missing the garlic I love
garlic so please bless me with your
garlic powers
but before let me go grab some water
okay
it's getting empty and emptier
staff fusan
are leaving slowly
sorry I had to get some water because
energy drink is [\h__\h] up my throat
okay give me that give me
[Music]
give me oh super simple but that was a
nice neck correct just now
okay okay okay okay
oh yeah you need more coins look at how
many coins I'm spending and take that as
a reference
[Music]
just this one just this one is tough
pitching at seven
oh
here it comes
tonight
honey come on come on come on come on
come on it must be it must be
[Music]
foreign
how does it
oh I can just buy oh okay okay well
that's kind of anti-climactic
[Music]
anti-climactic or anticlimactic
anyway
love
oh beautiful
with all the full body ones too because
these are all new ah
look at
look at us
whoa
I love this it's so cute there's so many
it's gonna get filled up even more
okay here we go
I didn't want to search oh I was like
who am I missing with secret secret
member
Let's Dance
she's got the baseball pitch froze a
very fast baseball in front baseball I
guess okay yeah she originally she was
not so a duck she was sports related
yeah yeah yeah
she was a trainer right I say was
because now she's a duck
oh yeah oh they're all cute I love the
smug face on shilon and daksha creates a
very loud scream in front knocking back
and dealing five thousand five thousand
five hundred percent damage and stunning
all Targets for five seconds
okay okay
you know
I think I have a chance in uh to finish
everyone in normal stage mode in in the
first stage I mean
[Music]
um
but that the problem is that everyone
will take 20 minutes and I don't have
enough time for that realistically
speaking
uh so I would actually appreciate dying
early
because I only have one and a half hours
left yeah
less less than yeah now it's one hour
twenty dying makes more sense yeah
[Music]
and we haven't done the hard one either
but yeah let's let's do stage free then
they're gonna kill me after five minutes
per person
all right here we go
[Music]
hands on her hips when she stands all
right let's throw those
those baseballs
is what I imagine she screams at her
special or maybe just oh my
God
[Music]
cute bunny optimism she does have a
sunny optimism
hey supposed five percent when taking
damage there is a 20 chance to gain one
optimism maximum 10 if HB reaches 0 gain
two percent HP and if HP reaches zero I
would hope that my HP doesn't reach zero
what do you mean
gain two percent HP and 0.5 seconds of
invincibility for
each stack of optimism so it's like a
revive but it doesn't like Heal Me Up
fully it just heals Me Slowly while
being invincible
[Music]
it is kind of a revive
it's a it's a stall a stall for death
oh okay let's get started with um
baseball pitch though
although yeah we'll need the sunny
optimism very soon
forever
[Music]
okay now I take the Sony optimism
because maybe that will make us live uh
six minutes instead of four minutes who
knows
uh-oh not at this rate
um yeah devil hat is new we just got
that but I need something that keeps me
alive a little bit longer
happens oh yeah you guys just came to
the stream see them for the first time
[Music]
real world let's reroll
that's also not what I'm looking for
okay but I'll go for the baseball pitch
for now
oh the balls are getting faster
ah but the hot tones are closing
closing oh you can smell knock back no
but I need
yeah
should I agree well I need a healing
item something but knock back I mean
yeah okay
I don't want to die where's the food
let me go look for food
there should be food in the Yago statue
oh please yeah go open up
I got it I got it I'll go get
it flew right into the hotons but
thankfully they did not want any piece
of that burger
oh wait my special is ready oh
[Music]
all right you just screamed in that
direction beautiful open up please gain
one handcuff every hopefully not on
myself every 15 seconds up to six on the
next hit by a Target use one handcuff to
arrest instantly defeating a non-boss
Target oh fun
foreign
I'll go for the healing I'm sorry guys
if you want something else but I'm I I I
want to survive
by channeling my inner Subaru senpai
I wouldn't mind being arrested though by
some other sampire I don't want the
Special Hold On Tony treatment
in this case I want to be arrested
Justice for All Birds
I think everyone does
and
should I reroll this
okay
so what
you're so fast
like she's playing a different she's not
she's not the
player she's like that that baseball
machine that can like oh nice food
that can throw like
those baseballs really quickly and those
what do you call those are batting cages
thingies
I've never seen one before
it looks so familiar uh foreign
by free and increase damage by 20 let's
go
okay I'll go for something different
next time
[Music]
touchy Beast ah it's super chats
weapon attacks uh we'll look pretty oh
that's gonna look pretty they already
look pretty
foreign
I guess okay they're more RGB now
[Music]
okay should I take the spider cooking
I'll take it we need some extra damage
wow I made it to three minutes
incredible
kill him kill him kill him with the
baseballs oh no he's just putting more
baseballs into his mouth
throwing or is it just meat no it's just
it's just me and they're not growing
[\h__\h] I can't I can't oh my God I'm gonna
die
what's this duck whisper create a sound
wave every 10 seconds and Deals 100
damage damage increases wait I won't die
because oh yeah yeah yeah I also have a
special I forgot about that um but I
won't die because of my invincibility
right
and that machine comes down to 100 it
may cause stun to the closer a Target is
to the center
I only have one stack though yeah
huh
well
I did no wait what
okay
uh I think I'm gonna die so say goodbye
to Subaru Sail by now
but hey I'm recharging I'm recharging
survive survive this
[Music]
so Disney four minutes that's like oh
pretty much always I've never been over
five minutes I think
but it felt it feels like the longest
four minutes of my life every time
ah
tiny hand tie him
yeah the explosions are so fast
yeah and it's not the easy stages so
it's a bit more difficult than the main
one next character shoving God for next
card I mean we did see um special and
all that
okay and let's go for chocolate
love needle oh frost a giant needle in
front
and then the super dynamite body look at
mmm
all right all Targets attack and death
are reduced by 30 percent
uh targets close to choco have a 40
chance to become converted and join our
side for eight seconds oh
eight seconds sister pretty long
but
[Music]
all right yeah well we'll speed through
we'll see which character I like the
most and then we'll do the the time
challenge thingy oh
look at that
[Music]
poke
if you play with Toko Sensei surely
everybody who has a needle phobia
however you call that will be cured of
it
more
foreign
healing 1.5 uh times the amount on crit
heels nearby Targets also receive a heel
uh taking 200 crit damage
targets may drop cooking supplies
every 10 supplies make a dish to heal 20
and gain plus 10 credit
for 10 seconds maximum 30.
oh yeah she's a Healer
uh oh God throat hort
why are we World of Warcraft now
but maybe I should still start with the
love needle
I think I should still start with the
love needle I don't know no
one two
okay I'll go for the cooking supplies
now
let me get those stickers
another one demon whisper on a crit
there is a 20 chance to charm when
Target maximum five to your side and
help for eight seconds oh like her
special skill but yeah one target
maximum five uh-huh Target gains choko's
attack and speed
Unturned
I'll go for the nurse
all uh here we go we increase the damage
by 20 percent and then
uh
increased damage of weapon of by 15.
[Music]
okay let's take that whisper the ace
Empire whisper
beautiful beautiful ASMR
and now the meal okay okay okay now
we're cooking let me cook
about my own
stabbity stab with the needle who here
is scared of needles
I mean this is a big needle though
I would be scared too oh
let her cook me scared of needles me a
little bit oh you used to be but got
over it good job
[Music]
oh
may I please ah [\h__\h] I'll pick it up
later
oh look at them they're in love with me
[Music]
don't like them but not scared
because you're a big boy
yeah look at The Charmed Ones girl
you are now on my side
the one and only beloved choco Sensei
forever
you will not be able to
Escape after unless after
eight seconds here we go look at that
so cute they're on a mission so
[Music]
CIO
I think we'll continue with the love
needle huh
so peaceful
Valentine's Day soon guys by the way and
oh
one week
I so know what I'll be doing
but my schedule is filling up more than
I thought it would be right now because
of like dance lessons and other things
oh no no no no no
there we go okay okay okay
big one incoming
[Music]
day
Challenge and yeah maybe it's just a
nice reminder
to stream hard Challenger everybody
Why Not Perfect theme song
[Music]
almost awakened
I will not take the food Yet full HP
going amazingly right now
might go over four minutes
lovely little awakened it looks kind of
bloody because of the awakened effect
foreign
nice that was my my friend
okay
ah I will not go for Halloween
[Music]
no what are you thinking guys you see me
struggle already
no
I don't know
I I now finally really understand what
Hollow means I mean it always sounded to
me like hallucination but after doing
the Indonesian class with Lena I now
have
it confirmed in my head
took us too good yeah so far
pretty much oh pee but who knows
maybe others are op2 and I'm just too
bad at uh working with them but it's a
even someone like me
can survive
then that really means something
right
we'll see we're still at three minutes
the longest three minutes of my life
um should I reroll
there's nothing here I already have
but maybe we should take something my my
Apple Keen stamps two old people early
I guess so cause
we only have one wait that that one is
like depending on how many weapons Lots
I have right and I uh have one two three
four five so holy [\h__\h] it might be good
to re-roll and take something no it's
already awakened what would I want I
want a weapon now
mmm
I don't know I'll go for I'll go for and
rewall it weakens your weapon
it does but yeah maybe then uh an armor
item right
or a demon whisper for example that that
that works
now let's go for demon whisper
[Music]
Whisper On The Hill I'm gonna kill you
now ah there you go 70 stab
this time you won't be troubling me
diamond I didn't want to eat that burger
I wanted to keep that burger for later
oh no oh
no no problem
back
[Music]
severely broken
incredible
[Music]
got the limiter
now
next time next time once we have the
demon Whisperer awakened maybe then
oh that's really fast I wanted to walk
for do they only activate the bomb when
when I'm close to them because that's
what it feels like certainly oh my God
[Music]
thank you I will defeat you I will
defeat you I will defeat you I will I
will yes I will unless you Corner me
again but no I didn't
oh
God
we're at Fort Wayne
ah I've overcome a situation yeah I did
it uh
okay
I've overcome a difficult situation
ah well so now we're weakening ourselves
but that's okay that's okay that's okay
I'll take it
just a little bit just one slot less
[Music]
work on some damage now too because we
don't know what's to come now
oh god oh
holy [\h__\h]
oh did I just kill them before they
could place the bomb I'm not sure
because I didn't see me getting uh
damage
oh I should have taken the horn yeah
yeah nice one
and on this case
Chris healed right in the right
situation maybe
oh that hurts
[Music]
I'm I'm saving my special by the way
I don't know for what I'm saving it but
this this situation is still under
control so oh God
[Music]
oh
payday
[Music]
you're on payday already the month just
started
already
all right you're on my side now
that you love me
there they go they're all gone now
nice to turn we're happy now we got
everything we need
almost six
[Music]
can we clear
probably not but
I mean maybe not first try but I see a
future where I could be able to clear
with chocolate
bye
[Music]
how are you
a couple minutes
nice ceiling
[Music]
oh God the bats oh
bye bye
um my special's almost there can I
survive
[Music]
which one I didn't even need my special
dress now a lot of them died
three
oh interesting choice guys interesting
um
I'll upgrade the spider cooking though
[Music]
it has never gone so well before
look at all my friends who are in love
with me
they all are listening to chocolates
ASMR
oh oh there
[Music]
so many explosions holy [\h__\h]
oh but that was that was my Ally
we're going in for an explosion wow wow
should I get the chicken feather just in
case
that was Opie yeah I might control
what do you want yeah I want a chance to
maybe
survive
my own better
I'm ripping out the feather from my ears
behind my ears they're not accessories
let me just say that again because
sometimes it seems like I have to say it
it's not an earring it's growing behind
my ear
foreign
[Music]
they might just have several big bosses
uh or like this is a mid boss I guess oh
God okay
okay
that has hairy ears that's not what I'm
saying if anything I have feathery ears
not hairy ears
don't put words into my mouth that I
didn't say
oh [\h__\h] I'm I'm winning guys
could you ask me
are you winning kiwawa so that I can
answer you honestly
yes I am
foreign
look at their formation they're so well
organized they must have gone to a lot
of dance lessons
this small stage will not hold me back
I will win are you winning to I am
ah oh yeah probably in 50 seconds we'll
meet a boss are you winning thank you I
am so far I'll use this now maybe we'll
have it back in time for the boss
everyone on the screen is my friend
there are no enemies
I probably could get rid of the solo
stamp now
because we're we have a couple of weapon
slots now
so I'll do this
and then strengthen
close your
um
basically
oh 10 seconds
[Applause]
I mean it's not nothing most ideal
combination
but
we
need
spend nothing yeah
okay Ellie cooking
okay what do we want next I'm not gonna
go for the feather one is enough we
haven't died yet
um
glow stick
glow stick and fan beam
should we go for that
oh my God
oh my God yeah bye
kill him kill him oh God
oh you have just enough time to oh
all right this is the end of me probably
uh I can't I can't
destroy the stamp and gain 182 home
coins just step will not drop oh I'm
selling it
oh
classic or get the fan beam Edition
later
and no piano what the hell eh
what's that
oh
that oh I got it wrong I thought that
was the effect
oops
maybe we'll find again again maybe maybe
we'll find one it's fine that's fine
okay
I think I would have probably been
destroyed by that
hit
oh my God
[Music]
I don't even use my special for that
incredible
this is so much fun man
I'm probably gonna play more Hollow cure
uh if I have time again this week or
next week but I also want to play
Farmland this week I'll have to like
figure out day by day
[Music]
it's good though I don't know if you're
trying to you know make a reference or
so
let her cook yeah let her cook
better Senpai maybe don't let her cook
but let the chocolate Sensei cook
and
whoa what was that
show me that in slow motion
okay so um I think we'll play at least
one more time maybe two more times
depending on how I feel and you know
oh but I probably if I don't play from
the studio I'll probably have to like
redo all of this
or whenever I play honokira I ask to
come to the studio
so I can continue on this save file oh
wait no this save file can I also like
move it to
oh I think that should be possible yeah
I can copy the save file right
right
uh how's that a nurse one
yeah
because I I copied a save file for today
here to begin with
uh
[Music]
muscles thing
I rarely see that one
[Music]
I'm scared to run into even the ones
that are Charmed by me I'm just scared
to run anything basically
a cycle wax
I don't know who's on my side anymore
because those already come in the color
pink
confusing me
just just be careful in general how
about that
oh oh Facebook what does that don't do
again weapon with fire but no
no thank you uh just increase
we already have an increasement on this
one should I increase a different one
Australian stem
funny though that how some stamps are
just joke stamps
[Music]
that's a good one
stop in advance
just happened
oh
[Music]
yeah
oh no
[Music]
no no
no this was my chance but okay yeah we
need to try out our characters oh
someone playing
oh
[Music]
Please Don't Steal the piggy bag no
Chris my babe no
no overconfidence and no I wasn't all
owing I was
moderately confident
[Music]
just
what's he said
has that one been has that one been
around probably right
I just don't remember
yeah
yeah oh my God
oh what these look so cool
fires to click magic ball in front oh
well she's a she's a witch
kick
hey
maybe we can combine kusuga kick and
Kiki kick one day yeah
[Music]
jumps high into the air oh becoming
Invincible for three seconds and falls
down and deals
and damage to all Targets around
all right here we go
oh I without a healing character I don't
think I'll get far and stay free really
but if that's okay for you guys
that's okay for you guys then let's try
it out
let me get something out of the pumpkins
now
I thought maybe if you crush them
well I like that
we need something oh I said surely is a
skill where you know you see her panties
like something something related to her
panties her skirt
so far no
I just understand my reference
yeah because of her 3D
now
and every 15 seconds that's your next
attack anytime she on the voids taking
damage from an attack gain 20 at attack
for 10 seconds
[Music]
two create some magic garlic that deals
100 damage to nearby Targets if xion is
within 16 pixels slowly gain special
gauge oh
okay
[Music]
black magic every eight seconds create a
Warp Zone on the ground that releases a
blast dealing 100 damage
uh-huh if there are two warp zones soon
can enter and teleport can do you mean
automatically so that happens if I walk
through it automatically probably
huh what if I walk in there accidentally
and I don't really want to
teleporting yeah
okay well let's try oh there it is but
now we can't walk in yet oh the damage
oh yeah
I need a I need a phoenix feather
I'm dying
no no no no what's that is that the
crony thingy oh [\h__\h] uh yeah it's a
crony one
reduce the delay between attacks okay
[Music]
I won't I won't survive
there's some food down there no
no no
[Music]
yeah I guess yeah if you teleport out of
like a big horde that's coming at you
that in that moment is great
I'm looking for food
[Music]
I think I need to go to the
Yago statue to destroy it
insane map control
yeah you guys are probably gonna do
great with that
I'm not gonna survive for long oh no oh
that
oh
[\h__\h] hell
[Music]
okay let me get the sticker was that
again
20 chance to reduce attack and defense
defense of targets by 20 and five
percent apparently flour flour
great
great I'll take anything right now I'm
desperate
floating garlic is just so so Random
should I take the bandage for like
healing
or more body pillows
yeah too you guys agree with me that we
need healing really really desperately
would be ready is this sticker that's a
sticker
stab attack style for 10 chance to hit
whole coins out of targets for him
okay okay okay okay I'll take it for now
until we come across something better
I take this oh
beautiful
[Music]
Magic
um whoa
okay Murasaki bolt is getting there
here's a sticker
um
I think I'll have to switch those
because I don't care so much about coins
right now
I like this new feature
which one do I upgrade one
okay oh DIY
I have to run right in the middle of it
properly
you guys the pros
to show me how to make the best usage of
that
show me some sick moves please
attack size
ever
change with haste or just upgrade
thank you
tough choice yum
Valor
I'm so hungry I don't know what to eat
today I have a sandwich right next to me
but I didn't have time to eat it
and that's probably not gonna be my
dinner
[Music]
hey we're at three minutes
pretty good
but we must not let this dude survive
hey
explain about Oscar is there anything
cool about what Austria
you want to go to Austria
oh what's cool about Austria the fact
that I'm from Austria no but why don't
we have a pretty cool old you know
typical
European architecture
uh oh what's this
standstamp weapon hits have 10 chance to
stun enemies temporarily okay
[Music]
hello
what's the chat band basically
that's good switch of one
all right
we won't live for long anyway so whoop
whatever we'll just try everything out
okay in a map that is so small like this
one I can see how the teleport can
really help you out oh look at that
oh now I'm here now I'm there now I'm
here
look at her go oh [\h__\h]
uh big explosion incoming
um
scared Michael
that is how you use it now I don't know
I'm baking with
balls
oh [\h__\h]
get him get him get him get him get him
get him get him get him get him oh
that's for comfort
oh my God
ah
help me
where is where's Mom where's Big Box
already dead
[Music]
snow stamp
um
I think maybe replace the stun
upgrades to okay
okay okay
with that it came quite fun I see it now
I feel it
and
whatever I don't know garlic range is
huge now
beautiful
garlic smell everywhere I think the
garlic smell fits really nicely here
in this in this location
huh
I'm gonna upgrade the pillow I'm not
sure
should I incoming okay yeah that's
terrifying that's probably the end of me
all right
[Music]
don't run
you need to meet the Revival just in
case
oh my God
look at all those coins
where's Japan Gillian when is 10 minutes
at 10 minutes was it at 10 minutes
okay going well going well
for my special attempt okay
[Music]
aha
the thing is though sometimes there's
only one right how do I know if the
other one is so far over on the other
side of the map that there's really one
if it's worth it standing on that one
for a second
you never know
you never know there could be one even
if you don't see it could be out of
eyesight hello
hello
I'm done
come look for me
oh there you are
cute ghost must go
go ghost gogos
attack magic just like that
okay I'm getting a little bit cocky now
I guess oh yes I am yes oh [\h__\h]
I know where he has a chicken feather I
didn't use it yet it's okay it's okay
it's okay I got hit too many times there
[Music]
oh we got another one
holy [\h__\h] there's a lot going on right
now lots of bats but they're pretty weak
[Music]
food
I'm getting the hang of it guys
and Chris damage of weapon by 15 percent
[Music]
um
Max done
okay
uh it's already um
I can't strengthen it is it already
it's all ready Max
okay I'll strengthen this one
oh no okay hopefully we got a fan beam
tonight
if I exit then I can still upgrade later
on right maybe I should a bomb work suit
yeah
oh wait it's not awakened yet oh no it
is
no you know what I'll wait
[Music]
I I
weapons cause small knockback increase
knockback strength by 30 its effect
already exists
[Music]
Bonk
I'll just I'll just upgrade or replace
upgrade
okay upgrade Circle
pickle pickle pickle foreign
wait uh bucket bucket is good right
no one
like I said bomb bomb or fan beam okay
no bucket then
[Music]
I'll wait a little bit longer then
get rid of the Healer okay
foreign
didn't realize you were coming
yeah bye
nice stunt
nice done
nicely done done
uh
maybe upgrade bandage now
well that's so bad here's the bump let's
go for the bomb
and you give me another bomb beautiful
you read my mind
[Music]
foreign
I think uh releasing
um
um oopsie
on the 10th right
if I'm not wrong it's almost almost the
ninth here when you guys have a little
bit more time
to wait
hope you can make it
I know it's hard to wait
impatient
I feel like
I feel it for other games that I'm
waiting for
I think uh Symphonia the remaster is
coming soon
and you know what else is coming soon
Chihuahua super focused right now prize
in March yes now that they moved the
release date
but it's only a matter of time
[Music]
's already there waiting for me yeah
so close
I thought I was a master escape artist
guess I wasn't so smart after all oh I
got a chance
okay and now
like that
and now I'm so close I will be really
hard to escape
[Music]
I'm gonna do it right away again here we
go
uh teleport actually really good in this
situation right uh if it's in the right
spot at the right moment
all right this is fine this is fine
it's not so fine
[Music]
okay
I just choked on my
excitement
bro you good no
no
hmm
well papa is here
Papa Mama
speed up now what oh that speed up okay
no and hold on Max where are you
sure
I'm one again once again only have my
energy drink
hmm
it's okay
here we go
energy drink will get me through this
unless I get corned
okay okay teleport yes yes
oh my God
okay maybe I do
no no no
back and forth back and forth back and
forth
[Music]
okay thank you
so much fun oh we can collaboration
uh on these ones yes okay oh already
time for Colombo I mean we're at 11
minutes
ah
ooh bridge I haven't had that one in a
while I rarely got that one even though
it's still good
and one for you
one for you
look
if if uh
I were to have something like this for a
new show
what would it be guys what should it be
an item to advertise
in a chihuahua-led news show
also what should I do I'm not so
interested in any of these but maybe the
another feather
huh fried chicken I've admits Jimmy's
fried legs ah
pretty well
you can fry a phoenix breath
and Chicken and Waffles Jimmy
maybe I'll
I'll do like a tweet and ask you guys
there I have another question
you know how uh recently uh
uh in the the whole live remix thingy
they put in Sparks right
did you listen to it
or spikes right
now that was a really chill
Lo-Fi remix but if there was another
remix for Sparks what do what would you
what you got here what do you guys think
would fit oh now you
oh increase the damage of critical hits
caused by this Weapon by 10 aha
dubstub
heavy metal heavy heavy metal
interesting though yeah interesting
interesting
yeah I can kind of see it I guess Future
Funk you're a Beat
don't we already no I guess that was the
eurobeat remix
anyway what do I do with this um
wait all max they're all Max
maybe I'll sell it again
they're all Max how are we maxed them
allowed
[Music]
yeah then I saw it I don't want to like
replace the max ones that would be a
waste
okay
[Music]
I'm at the state again where I'm just
chilling that's nice
foreign
metal and cute mix as well see Babymetal
true I know true
[Music]
it doesn't seem to do much for damage
Maybe
all right
now
oh God oh God oh God
got stuck there for a little bit oh
let's get some food yummy
oh yeah okay remix Sparks
heavy metal version I mean
it's not like my personal taste I do
love baby metal
but generally yeah not quite my thing
wait is this the first we've come uh
until now because I see those uh katos
for the first time
you're getting too good at the game
really
oh
don't you because I think we're gonna
work on combining the cooking with the
lab with the magma
you know yeah I'll get the
um revive for the off chance of actually
uh surviving this [\h__\h]
oh my God
I I
look at them they're all so cute all
these new Minecraft artwork so pixel art
skills
funk I like that idea too but wait
what's a good example of funk that I
would know what is what is fun
is is is
um that one is that one thing Funk uh
Uptown funk you up Uptown funk you up
Uptown funk you up Uptown funk you up is
that song
like pop funk for a song I really like
that one
yeah
sorta
nice oh should
n't projectile up stamp adds one
additional shot to ranged most whoa
[Music]
oh
it's good like that piece of fun too but
not always right but they might have
Funk songs yeah
foreign
[Music]
that's that's too good wait okay Dad
actually
if you strengthen it with something that
was already masked okay okay that's
it that's fair
I thought it would only get one upgrade
I was wrong
holy [\h__\h] it's going so well again
[Music]
um
yeah
but wait [\h__\h] I don't have much time
[\h__\h] I actually need to die if I want to
show you everything real quick I have
left I have a aqua senpai
and
I actually don't have time
[Music]
all right I I will not purposefully die
because I would be very happy to
um clear this
but if we die then that's okay too
eh yeah bye the other two ones might be
very very quick showcase
hope that's okay guys you will see more
soon
what are those
should I go for spider cooking a nurse's
horn looks good to me
excuse my unculturedness
I have a sick design damn
they look so ghastly oh there's a Healer
around
[Music]
is you right there yeah okay and during
the casting like the spell time spell
casting time oh well no never mind
uh you're Invincible right because I'm I
don't see myself I'm invisible right so
I can just run into them so far that's
how it felt like
yeah okay okay
[Music]
another ear warm that you will have to
hear endlessly oh my God can you stop
all those cats
oh
it's a mid boss time
uh increase sound no
already maxed out everything too
oh my God
it's like endlessly spawning those butts
done nice done
it's okay we actually have free revives
right that we have yet to use
a new features of stamps welcome to the
stream I guess
um
yeah
come on die come on yay
could this possibly I really didn't
think without a heel character that I
would clear this but
uh okay I guess I'll take it
but this is
[Music]
it's not impossible I'll say that
I know Bonnie pillow but I mean like you
know generally like a character that's
focused on healing
um
what I just what are those balls
it what
what the [\h__\h] was that
one of those balls live still stab once
per second weapon attacks May heal a
random amount of uh up to five percent
of Max HP projectiles and from who
from who
Chin's fans are casting them oh
replace vehicle
weapon attacks May heal a random yeah
maybe yeah
should I
Swap and then strengthen cool Shield
which goes up to 10 percent
ah
[Music]
Escape Escape
oh
spawn nice spawn
okay okay here we go bye
come here come here
yeah not not the best timing to use it
but at least we cleaned up a little bit
oh
my hand is sweating
please protect me we're Hollow verbs
I'm gonna do a special one okay yeah
okay okay
oh my God
I don't even have like a
of awareness of from where to where I am
going
even though the map is so small eh with
the with the endless map the the first
one I wonder oh my what
the first time that's on the final plus
it's a mid post again right or is it is
it
no not at all oh yeah bye
[\h__\h] my HP is okay that was a mid boss
uh interesting
oh
well they're saying
[Music]
one
oh another one uh okay
should I save my special
no I will use it now come here
yeah it's a lot it's a lot it's a lot
it's a lot
considering I don't thinking assuming
that it's 20 minutes
be right
yeah
tell me guys tell me what
tell me what get ready for the 19 Rush
no please
please okay
just know please no please no please no
no rush please
bad choice bad choice
okay it's 19.
oh [\h__\h] but I still have free revives
right
this is it
the set
um
foreign
[Music]
to more of a mass of oh God no it's fine
so far oh my God
it's fine it's fine it's fine it's going
well
[Music]
City
we're out to run back to the hole
because I wouldn't know how long the
countdown for that is but okay okay okay
all right all right hello what is that
oh my God out
oh
did I really want to do that well maybe
like for a little mental break oh no
yeah
I think we can do this
oh [\h__\h]
nice nice nice nice nice nice ah don't
don't fly away now take this
let's do damage I think
oh
and also first try the machine though
right
[Music]
thank you for leading me the way
okay go back once we got sogaki shackles
reduce the negative effects of any items
by 33 percent
oh okay
oh my God I'm like oh
portals baby sick I love that technique
it's like so different the strategy
fires uh Ian's curse
Yankers fires cursed energy in front one
hit there's a chance to spread another
curse towards another nearby Target yeah
yeah the en's currents when it goes over
to other generations and so on
all right and the reference oh my God
okay really fast because I have to leave
the studio I'll just show you
um
I'll show you really fast I guess this
one too Swans in front straight up the
only increase the attack speed Abdul
Katana by 200 after four seconds no
Spirit slash screen feeling thousand
percent damage to all Targets Coolio
oh oh you got a big ink speed right away
Lady of Annie defeating a Target and has
been hit but holy music
huh whoa hit by duel Katana will
increase haste by one percent buff
decreases by one percent every second
okay
oh
I love that
Dance
[Music]
by the way
you lose my special
increase speed by two percent maximum 40
for every Target within 120 pixel if a
Target is defeated within 120 pixels
they drop 10 bonus dxp
[Music]
do they not like Drop any food in this
stage
oh
maybe uh
yeah ad truck is such a banger holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
Tonya is
almost there it's almost there
oh oh no oh no
um
I think for survival I'll take the
bandage oh God
[Music]
I couldn't even use the the one special
wait we'll go there in a second hi
oh
I just I saw that right there
I thought I was too used to uh the
previous play for where I could just
walk in the middle while I was
activating my my special skill all right
all right main menu
um cleaning broom throws a large
spinning broom [\h__\h]
someone's a giant nickel that runs for
the field at the aim Direction dealing
300 damage and knocking Targets on
impact via muscle memory that was muscle
memory I'm sorry
but we have to die anyway we all die at
one point uh so now I want to show you
the time mode defeat all Targets as
quick as possible shop upgrades are
standard standard
standard oh
foreign
[Music]
attack otherwise gained 40 speed
oh my God look at all the fans
[Music]
can one additional protector to all
multi-shot weapons but there is a 40
there is a 40 chance the protectors deal
half damage okay
I feel so speedy
[Music]
clean room
a special attack incoming
I love that
oh we have to look at shekels now but I
won't use them now
all right we saw the special effect I
can die anytime now but I really should
because um I have to like clean up too
ah
cleaning man increases pickup range by
40 targets with an aqueous pickup range
tag uh 20 more coup dense
who doesn't love crayons
I see a lot of
fun streams incoming not only for me but
other members
I'm gonna give this a try
yeah
[Music]
foreign
hopefully the new members who have been
introduced with this
are gonna give it a try
as well even if they haven't yet
yeah
please hopefully all right then I I will
just force it to end here hi please take
me fans
[Music]
yeah they're all so beautiful all the
fan forms are so beautiful
ah that was a lot of fun
yeah that was a little showcase
I was able to show every character but
there may have been I mean of course
there have been things that maybe were
not 100 shown but that's up to you guys
that's your job now so
enjoy in two days
um
[Music]
and I will take a big sleep now and then
I'll probably see you tomorrow on Ina's
channel for the Nintendo Direct yay
awesome
thank you bye bye and thank you for
letting me play the game early Dan can
Shannon was a lot of fun
bye bye bye bye enjoy Hollow cure and
save the fans please
somebody's gonna do it
bye bye
[Music]
thank you