Ki Welcome to our first challenge of the
day I am in sburg where morard was born
by the way it's a nice pretty city in
Austria that's neighboring Germany I
went with a bus for about uh 40 minutes
to a little city called sank gilan and
is surrounded by lakes and
mountains yes yes very popular area for
paragliding scenery already very
beautiful on the way there wether GR
as well pretty hot actually yeah you can
see some cows and Farms all over and
there's already the fal sea I think uh
which means we're getting super
close uh and yeah yep yep isn't it
beautiful yeah perfect perfect I'm
excited well ah that is most likely yeah
that's already the Wolf Gang see where
I'll be going what I'll be flying over
and yeah here I arrived already I was
pretty nervous in the beginning um but
you got to do what you got to do so by
the way I res served this online
beforehand and asked for permission to
film everything so all good there yeah
when I was when I entered I was gred
very nicely by my partner and the boss
of the company partner as in flying
partner cuz yeah I'm not flying alone of
course you can't it's not allowed and
but yeah they gave me an 8 kilogram
backpack to wear up the mountain okay we
are going to the up to the mountain
now what's the name of the
mountain I got a
ticket let's go
[Music]
ooh it's like we're going skiing oh
let's go this is what we're bringing up
to the
mountain it's still a little bit up
there it's really hot but nice weather
yay we made
it
oh let's take a look at this view for
heart I wish I could land right in the
lake
afterwards cuz it's hot but we got to
land on
grass look we're carrying these huge
backpacks what's inside only the the
paragliding only the paragliding stuff
okay so can you can you tell us a little
bit about our fight time and so on we
fly about 20 minutes M can we start from
the behind of the mountain and one fly
one time around the mountain and then
over the lake and land in s oh s again
yeah
okay I'm excited do you ever have
accidents
no still in one piece yeah yeah oh the
one piece is real oh okay well then that
makes me feel safe it's so Steep and my
backpack is heavy for at least for me
cuz I'm weak as [\h__\h] she suddenly said
we're stopping here this
is take off
[Music]
area UPS
oh God oh
God I don't know if you probably don't
really see it on the video but it's
really
steep no it's going to be okay I have a
professional with
me it's going to be fine yeah oh I get a
helmet too right
okay thank
[Music]
you so she said we're both pretty light
so we going to start earlier and we're
going to have a nice light
Landing it's going to go
[Music]
well
okay
[Music]
one flying let's
go W it's so
beautiful the wind is nice holy [\h__\h]
holy
[\h__\h] okay okay I'm holding the camera
but it's secured I was scared to drop it
but it's secured we're getting really
close to that mountain right now she is
in full
control wow this lake is which one wolf
Gangi the wolf Gangi yeah and then
behind it uh that's uh Monty the Monty
oh very famous very famous W I saw some
birds flying around us but generally we
have free
airspace
[Music]
oo
wow it was so scary to take
off but it happens really fast
so
[Music]
wow
W look how beautiful Austria
is let's land in the in the
lake I see the
[Music]
others
okay I just landed these guys are still
very far up
there H I got really sick right at the
end but I was able to hold it in right
when we were supposed to
land
yay but I made it she even had a little
little plastic bag for me that I was
already opening up so I was struggling
with uh the the takeoff a little bit but
was that like pretty normal that was
good really cuz for one moment you were
still saying push pull but I was feeling
like I was like stuck in like one
position I couldn't move on from the
glider yeah yes this is what I said that
the the strong force coming where you
should just go over or try to to
continue I felt very weak it was good
you did it very well and Landing was
wonderful yes even though I was about to
throw up but
now we're waiting for some colleagues
they're still up there they they took up
so late so now we are admiring them all
right let's get
up
Yayo that was quite an
experience I think I can now
say I can
fly just like a
oh look at them W one of them was making
like
crazy crazy Wheels almost look at
them o I think we were flying pretty
calmly yeah
so I think this is better than bungee
jumping I'm
satisfied and now now now I need some
food in my tummy
yay challenge
complete y yay