[Music]
n
he a
[Music]
oh
he
[Music]
oh
he
[Music]
wait no huh I'm sorry can you say that
again
please
I'm it's your Bo more
CL something something
Reaper yeah
[Music]
see
k
k is that an
impression Oh wait we're in the same
room today so we can do the thing
I'ma I'm okay you Goa I'm not a sh
I'm
Mory and together all of us are some
members of whole live
English
sorry I'm sorry I'm not good at it I
don't know what else to
say I no you did great I don't know what
you're complaining about but you did
great I guess I could work on it h I
guess we should all introduce ourselves
but I I want to make sure we're on the
screen that has everybody oh oh oh hold
on a second oh we're going we're okay oh
there we go hi everyone oh where's there
they go
okay everyone's here Kiara's so tiny
she's like a little Barbie doll small
wah small
waha all right everybody would you like
to introduce yourselves I guess biu and
I can start but prepare your
introductions cuz we're about to ask you
for
intros
okay Mina song Hello everyone my name is
Mor Kip of whole live English myth my
hardworking shinig gumy Reaper musician
shinig gum I kill people for a living
but I also stream and make music um nice
to meet you all if it's your first time
meeting me if it's not then not nice to
meet you who's this next to me at my
house uh I'm at her
house I CL
SP H English event and today I'm hogging
your cats yeah yeah and they like you
cuz you don't scream at them and they
like me they like me I so happy I will
sniff them sufficiently today yes sniff
them lot make sure you sniff them a lot
of
times yeah they might like they might
like hold on a second I'm going to
volume's just really freaking loud sorry
music
voling Silence game okay there you go
there we go um who else do we have here
with us today I see a certain a certain
not chicken Phoenix Is Here Yeah k sorry
I'm still a little bit of low energy but
it will change probably I just woke up
20 minutes ago
so I'm working on it I'm drinking an
energizing smoothie surely that will
help nice thanks for
joining yay kiaha here with us y I'm
going to make kiwa's volume higher just
because I know that she's she's just
waking up it's been so long I haven't
seen you in so long oh my God I feel
like it's been years Gua it's been years
not like playing together every day or
anything like that I just playing
Minecraft how about
you but but you look so different right
now what are you really the same C it's
the same Cali I just move a lot more I
guess I'm also really excited X press X
to doubt press x what do you mean press
X to die o nonbelievers I I swear I'll
punch you but affectionately
affectionately I'll punch kahua in the
nicest way I love this bird who's next
to this bird this person isn't a bird
but she kind of has like birdlike hair
it's like half black half white kind of
looks feathery that's bird like I don't
know in the fugie it looks bird
like that sure Nella here at your
service h
s the guy that's my fault
hi shodin thank you for joining
yeah
sh thank you let's
[Music]
go you guys only have you seen that I've
been like constantly doing that you did
yeah I thought it was really cute I'm so
addicted to it and now I'm next to the
original we can do it together wait is
it the guy that sings like
go I I think it was originally based off
South Park though I
feel where she got it from I think so I
think so it's
like and the thing is like she did that
and a Clipper uses it for their endings
and I like watched it several times so
now it's in my head that's pretty goed I
respect it nice yoooo Yoo Yoo yo thanks
a lot for joining us shiori and guua and
bioo but we have two others left here
who are
they I'm not a cha i h I know I'm
together we
H today we it's been a busy
day we've been very swy doggies but now
we're doing a bit better and we're ready
for some Jack box all together so wet
outside it was wow it was raining dogs
and
dogs dogs dogs and dogs that much yeah
if there's cats I would I would have
known they would have smelled them I
would have I would feel full in my heart
right now in the heart
hey there will be no cat eating talk
here
put in a word with evil yeah you guys
are jealous I get them to myself I'm
jealous guua is also a cat owner so
we'll both B
you my actually I will not bab you my
cats will B you they can protect
themselves it's just another way to show
affection and then it consume if you say
so I'll take your word for
it a Advent you guys have been good
right what Advent you guys have been
good no naugh I said people a bunch of n
yesterday and I still haven't given her
ice cream yeah you still me ice cream I
still ow you ice cream I want my banana
chocolate covered stuff oh that sounds
nice I know
I only say that cuz you know bioo you're
in my home I don't want the police
knocking at my door looking for you or
anything like that you guys are
criminals remember that why you not
harboring a wanted fugitive or anything
those days are over hat here and a ra
yeah
peaceful are you sure you guys can
really afford to settle
down I mean you guys are
delinquents H it's it's we been the cell
for a long time I I think it's okay yeah
I would deserve this you know all right
if you say so we play nice yeah games
games games all right I trust you guys I
just don't want the popo knocking at my
door okay freaking something else I have
to deal with fans you know they just
want your autograph or
something yeah right if you say so all
right we'll play some games then I feel
like for quiplash we wanted to kind of
do our own deck so let's play a
different one for now shall we
it was this one um let's see what do you
have you guys played any of the other
ones like devils in the details champed
up talking points or BL
round BL round is pretty fun but you
have to
like you have to
like wait no not talking point is
talking talking yeah that's we did that
before with CI too I think with myth
this one's actually pretty Power Point
present
it's like it's like yeah it's like my
debut PowerPoint
present this one's pretty fun you should
remember you remember right yeah I did a
terrible job I'm so bad at speeches you
can give it a shot I'm pretty bad at
these like talking games too uh because
English is not my strength but let's do
it you did good at that round I remember
somehow somehow I said some good things
apparently yeah it was smart all right
now I got to go to this screen while we
get the codee up on the the screen so
that you guys can't enter
first I play Are you supposed to screen
share by the way oh yeah with you guys I
can do yeah you are supposed to you are
supposed to
yeah all right I'm now screen sharing
thank you otherwise you'd be at an
advantage
enough all right okay oh so I guess
should you join on your phone b i yeah
I'm here there's VIP B
I'm a
v the code is w a w kaha you
kahua Kiara no they're all entering a
the fans they're
entering wait I I chose a picture and
then I guess that's it okay that's it
I'm going to try my phone it's being
stupid right
now fine IW my phone too yeah yeah yeah
you have to enter on your phone too oh
that's right this is one those phone
games all righty it's a phone I'm
sorry I'm too old for phone games now
hey don't call me out like that bio
please oh it's ready yeah I'm on my CTI
so if we play a drawing game I have an
advantage hey well at least you admit
that I'm glad that you admitted that's
nice let's see all right the password is
f
u c g
just kidding that's not what the
password is I threw them
off I threw them off get out of whatever
that play room not found
oh you can't find your own room no I
didn't look I spelled it right wait join
with phone if you haven't already it is
phone actually oh very strange I did it
sear I put my name where the code was
supposed to go yeah stop I'm just a
little
stupid
[Music]
hey o skeleton there's a skeleton icon
I'm way too excited about that hold on
it's okay we have a pink and blue dog so
it's
okay night all right nice that works out
nicely I'm a crab W that's cool why is
it waiting for people to start the game
oh me okay all up to you Bab how oh
everybody's ready is that a crab or is
that a hum
hum yeah Lobster yes in German it's
Hummer
cute oh there's a lady talking I didn't
even Noti yeah we turn it down a lot
okay I'm I'm pulling it
up
spech interesting fre to random or
really personal
yeah
okay at least I know how it works at
least I know how it works I'm also
terrible at presentations you're fine oh
we have to fill in CRS three turs oh
wait
oh wait how much time 60 seconds God uh
uh okay it's a thank you you're
welcome
okay let's
see I'm getting nervous don't be nervous
I I can help you if you want help Kiara
fill out all of the titles there's more
than one see hold on hold on um God damn
it I'm still thinking these are really
tough prompts I we're doing but I'm
doing my
best um okay uh what is this
uh okay I I just did something stupid
which is like normal I
guess I am I'm also done with my prompt
okay we could be both oh God this is so
bad I put in a compound answer have to
listen what is this has sent to your
device this will be the see the room
presentation here's the room code lad oh
all right I'm presenting for Oh I
thought the things I wrote I would be
presenting oh I'm using other people
oh oh I see that's going to be tricky
good
luck I think I got two fuam Moka ones
I'm it's going to
Bey got to step
up I'm glad I picked the one I did will
be presented with a series of slides
chosen by the assistant when you see a
text slide read that text out loud as
part of your talk and move on quickly
when you see a picture slide just say
words until something makes sense oh my
gosh this is scary you can even draw and
type on the
slide in real time by the oh no this is
just what are we doing okay I'm the
assistant pick my
slides okay call so I got you uhhuh
F the direction of the speech tap it
forward or back to get new options all
speeches will follow this exact
structure boy public
speaking my worst
enemy it's fine we're all getting out of
our comfort zone today right
L it's not like we public speak for a
living
SW many you hit the button is just as
important okay how many times you hit
the button that's it it'll be
will it give me more points and all
right F give me something
goodge advancing the slides when you're
ready yeah no
pressure
okay I'm judging you really hard right
now bio I swear to God she's right
behind me hello my name is Mory and my
talk is wake up nerds we don't need
sleepiness we need full m morning
WMC
morning hey idiots this rat is me poking
through your wall making sure that
you're up at 6: a.m. for fuam Moka
morning except fuam Moko aren't rats
that would be Bale's heos Fu Moco are
dogs and they're the
cutest I'm not a oh I'm already [\h__\h]
it up next slide I hold myself
responsible for what happened
next
Gom gnomes this is only a small fraction
of Fu moko's fan
base um there more than a bunch of
gnomes though there are also a bunch of
dog people that look like Ruffians and
many more that wake up at 6:00 a.m. just
to catch fua Moko
morning welcome you'll be treated like
family as soon as you walk the door 6
a.m. though okay B boo Point down 8 a
eight you might be asking what can I do
first please stop yelling
second do the dogs know that they have
to push the Thumbs Up Button by the way
what you dogs the thumbs up second when
in doubt I'm pressing button sniff
someone's butt but not
foro yeah cuz that's they don't they
definitely don't do this with dogs these
are dogs okay if you want to
know if you want to know what fuaa and
mocho are doing in their free time tune
in
morning you good ending good ending all
right so what were we thinking Lads many
you guys didn't like the Gnomes I wasn't
trying to be insult I'm sorry I'm sure
you guys are all really fluffy
and the qualitative judgement see I
think the last picture deserves a lot of
points yeah absolutely thank you fy I'm
glad you feel the same
way know what I was doing was I a good
assistant you were the best I sadly was
not a great personer but I did what I
could now I get to sit back and listen
to you
guys not great how well fuaa
assisted
H all right I gave a good review so
whoever I'm assisting give me a good
review all right make sure you give me
a please please what's that not was
trying to back seat my assistant though
wasn't focusing on what she was
doing
Shine Go time I'm going do the best I
I speaking I wonder what you
chose what probed
and my name is
CL and my talk is next time
please
hello the reason everyone calls me
fluffy wow you may think what beo isn't
fla biscot The Fluffy one no that's what
I say I'll bite fla on the neck and then
claim her title I am
flest you don't think rocks are fluffy
well now they are yeah have you heard of
moss moss gr rocks and they are fluffy
so rocks can be fluffy too yeah I seea
going down in the lik there and yeah
they can be fluffier than dogs you know
what I'll make this next Point very
carefully better listen Okay okay listen
listening let's see what's next I'm
listen excuse me
that's not a fluffy dog it's about as
fluffy as FL
and can be so much fluffier than that
yes I have lots of hair on my head and
you know what it gets really fluffy my
hair is longer than flowers too what
what I have
mff fluffy people yeah don't just sit
there do this next thing with me
yeah next all
right you're show your fluffy tails off
to the world prove that we're all
fluffier than fla she's not the only one
who has a fluffy tail stick stick them
out stick out you get I'm doing it I'm
steing it I'm
you love everybody we too if we really
like try really hard we could also all
grow fluffy Tails yes okay thank you for
coming to my presentation oh my mouth
hurts I'm
smiling yeah that really good B thank
you bio took no prisoners confus D
you're a natural born speaker bi Bo oh
my face hurts all right you know hey
that's look that's understandable be
yapping that's understandable that was
really you were a very good assistant I
did my best I don't know what I'm doing
that was a good it was good that was
good I will give you a smiley face thank
you thank you anything here cool speech
submit there I said cool speech now I
feel intimidated I don't want to go
after bi please Kar if you want help I
can help you oh help of speaking let's
go yeah we can do a partnership yeah
I'll be like a tag
team okay looks like I go
up okay
okay I'll choose I'll choose pictures
that are fitting for your presentation
come on sh let's hear those tangents you
got this I'm a shame hello my name is
Shori and my talk is about shame and the
most wonderful thing in this world next
Slide the three easy steps to achieving
that great great
G help so you see the Gat is like the
big dumpy the big Bonas the thing that
you like to smell in the morning It
might smell a little musk might smell
like other things but hey three easy
steps of achieving it first off you got
to just like remove most of your clothes
except like I don't know your clothes
clothes remove the clothes and all the
clothes okay yeah exactly you got
to already do St
one make sure you have enough clothes so
you have to remove some clothes but just
enough clothes to not get punched in the
face by your future wife that's right
this person she's so jealous of your gut
if you have too much gut she's going to
beat the crap out of you and take all
your money and then steal all your all
your Lunchables which have lead in there
H my Lunchables have lead in them anyway
don't worry about that but yeah I eat
that as a kid too but but you want to
know the best way to get yet that's
right eat more lead what know what was I
on anyway here's the last part next
slide
yeah oh
man the other way to achieving great
yacht is to break someone's Limbs and
bones for some reason because that's
like this exercise you see you're
actually achieving like muscular things
you know a punch you into to the face
face and a kick to there and you're
having great great
yeah thank you
wow need no
help that was a high level speech
mhm that was pretty
high the master yapper Shori
no dang
y let's see right right what do I write
here
picture let's see good
yapper that's all right that's my
comment good yapper thanks for teaching
us about the Gat achievement yeah good
pictures K I needed to know yeah I
pictures the last one the last one
wasn't supposed to mean you get a gut if
you punch people it was supposed to mean
you get a if you try to uh work out you
might break bones oh
no I want to see what picture
hello my name is w and my talk
is why spice is the spice of life
because I like all the spices you know I
really I my favorite spice not the spicy
spice coriander and drilling the teeth
because know going to the dentist is
what really makes your life a bit spicy
because you never know what they're
going to do they might tell you that oh
I see some spots in the back there Hi
and they might say okay time to drill
what mhm they say it's time to drill and
it goes
like okay it's a bit spicy at the
dentist mhm and there's only one
explanation for this okay and that
is the three very fancy puppins now
how that spicy huh they're very spicy
look at them they have
attitude spicy I don't know if they're
quite doggy of the day material but no I
think if I had to give them a rating it
would be incredibly spicy huh look at
that very spicy outfit makes now I'm
calling for us to use humankind's
greatest resource and that is H chees
cheese and
mice what is the mice doing underneath
the cheese I don't know I think she's
trying to find his tools but he lost
underneath the
cheese maybe he's feeling a bit spicy
he's going to take some risks today you
know okay and that's the way that we get
humankind's greatest resource the spices
wow I did not
understand heos bail has a problem with
what you just
did B isn't happy with
that wow I can't believe
it and they both hate B cuz dogs make
natural enemies of rats oh I can't
believe it they're like they fun thank
you very informative thank you uh
learned a lot about
spice yeah I learned about the dentist
hi B we got to fight
hi better watch out face we've been
doing some serious
training literally my assistant oh I'm
literally your assistant okay let's see
all
right
okay hello my name my name is wa and my
talk
[Music]
is how I eventually defeated the cat in
hat how' you doing here you
may which cat well it is this cat that
was in my hat and you probably also
wondering where where which hat and
where was this cat it was in my white
hat and you know you haven't been seeing
my white little hat for a long time
these days and everybody's asking me
where's the Hat where's the Hat come on
wa bring us the hat back I can't because
there was a cat in the hat and it was
dangerous for me no way that's good
sacrifice it was like scratching my head
the whole time you know and it hurt me
it was not my own cat you know this is
not good the most obvious place to start
uh getting rid of the cat is here you
take your hat just like this cup and you
like you know flip it over and you get
the cat out that is the first step and
actually it is also the only step
because the cat did not want to be in
the Hat in the first place so once you
flip it over and give it some you know
time and some place to leave it will
actually leave your hat and then
everything will be good don't worry
about it yeah I've kept this secret for
a long time I know there's many people
with cats in their hats and they're like
scratching their head and they like
hurts and they're suffering and the
bleeding I know it must be so rough like
this these people are all not wearing
hats why because okay they knew how it
works I I didn't tell them it was it was
my secret I didn't tell them but but
they figured it out too so I guess I'm
not that much of a genius but don't
worry if you ever wear a hat and you
feel scratching and it's the cat you
don't have to harm the cat you don't
have to like you know do anything just
take off the hat and all will be good
thank
you you weren't going to say anything
about my
gorilla I no no I put it in like the max
there was a gorilla there was a gorilla
you didn't see
photo but there was normal free people
there what what do you mean never mind
it doesn't matter all right yeah if you
say so just normal people wow I'm sorry
Kier I can't believe I didn't realized
that yeah it's just a normal guy you're
right it's just a normal guy sorry I had
something and fuzzy sorry I had
something in under my contact never mind
yeah no you're right but I I liked the
the pictures they were really helpful in
proving my point that cats and the hats
are I knew it dangerous see that's why
I'm a great assistant ain't that right
everyone I'm glad you picked my prompt
by the way I thought no one was going to
going to pick my prompt you are oh it
was your prompt I thought it was an
automatic yeah let's
go yeah D I'm going to do a
speech okay go all right let's go okay
H my name is hula I'm the 4y one and my
talk today is my first job Rock what
yeah Rock not not just like a a regular
Rock Rock a rock they're switching rolls
it
seems look see this is what I mean this
is not a regular Rock do you understand
scary scary uh like was mentioned
earlier in be's presentation this is a
mock a mock a a mock that has moss and
it's a mock I would not quite Define it
as fluffy not
fluffy this is a rock this is more it is
a rock it's not a regular rock this is a
rock that also likes to do uh dance and
now you might be kind of confused it's
okay I will be taking questions what
exactly does that
mean regular walks not fun but this walk
fun it's almost like going down the
stairs with your grandpa on a bean
bag a safety beside it that's how fun
really really fun yeah TV really really
fun yes that fun totally really really
fun yeah and okay okay I know you are
going to laugh when I show you what I
did when it came to this rock that's
okay oh that's okay see it's okay to
laugh like him it's okay you know is he
laughing he's laughing but you know why
laughing because he knows his teeth are
so strong the dentist loves it and the
dentist is you know your teeth it's not
a regular rock
[Applause]
yeah oh do you have any questions I
forgot the question segment um I think
you really
made sense yeah yep yep made sense made
I'm glad I'm glad you could follow along
the presentation cuz I know I went
really fast at points yeah qu
us
um that was great I'm going to leave a
comment that was great the dude's going
down the stairs I wouldn't even know
what was going on like even if
connect dang it I'll get him next time
you guys are excellent public speakers
oh do me a favor and give it
a
[Music]
Awards okay okay okay okay okay we don't
know who we're giving it to though right
I don't think so it's just going to be
randomly given out I think maybe a give
out yeah okay I hope it gets to the
right person I hope so
too I want to rewind
that was pretty good I like that P wake
up nerds oh me morning so back how right
B boo
shines Reon everyone calls you are fired
spee I wrote shots
fired shots fired maybe there's some
unhappy
listeners
good
spe
what I want that
oh oh interesting confusing photos but
good gorilla good I let cats wear hats
I'm concerned about the cat safety oh oh
I should I do a second presentation
about the cat
safety let's
GOI those are
nice award
Cy everyone get a participation
award to out and
audience
okay oh no my reward yeah give out the
awards you guys okay I can choose it
after all it
seems o okay let's see this one yeah
okay I just handed out my award now
finally the big big award B big oh this
is
yeah I gave to Shori thank goodness I
appreciate your pee PE poo poo
assassinate I gave the
[Music]
FL
B I'm
honored I
mean getting Awards
theary malevolent
Mal hey you won first second got second
[Music]
place is taking the gold congrats B I'm
the
yapper cool no one thought of an award
for
me we give you the European reward
do you want the pee PE poo poo I can
give it to you did you want put that in
half for
her nice we're going to play a different
game but that was fun it was fun
[Music]
yapping that was a good YY one is there
a quick one we can play quick
one oh this is champed up I want to play
after that yeah it's a long one Devil's
in the details o torture
details isn't fun to watch it's not fun
to
watch let's see a pop culture we're not
all very well versed in Pop sry I don't
know anything
to WR okay well here's here's an idea we
want to play our own here I'm going to
put you guys' Fogie in here too um we
want to play quiplash uh and we wanted
to do our own quiplash uh set yeah and
we have all of our stuff prepared
already um but we just haven't like put
it in there yet so we're going to take
our time filling out that deck right now
really quick and maybe like Yap a little
bit okay okay I know you're here I know
that you know my friends are here there
they are hi sorry my ads are in the
background you can ignore them in fact
I'll make them go away and I'll play
something else see okay ads go away I'm
not I'm not going to show new intro fire
Alba yeah I mean I can't say
no if which album would you be the
happiest if we were a buy huh which
version yeah because it's so tricky when
you have like bonus songs and stuff like
that it's like ah or like the different
merch and stuff yeah that's a tough one
you know if you get if you get like the
the dead box one that one's really nice
because that has M and sano's uh remix
of future Island on it and also trading
cards yeah it's really cool you can get
a different Mory trading card every time
it's really neat
right yeah so if you want to get that
one but it's also the most expensive
standard's good too but either way
they're all nice so I'd be happy if you
got whatever one you wanted sh'll harder
I'll think about it right make your own
I'm going to make make your own quip
lash okay I'll give you guys the code
all right um let's see create once you
logged in you can create a new episode
okay oh well was good okay you guys
already see you guys see the code never
mind I don't need to give it you see the
code of Shame the code of Shame yeah and
you guys you guys can't join yet you
just got to wait and let us fill in our
prompts okay uh wait leave me alone I
don't want to what who what is it if I I
press create a new episode uh I thought
all like waiting for a while guess it
just means you're in charge that's okay
G it doesn't matter I don't want to be
in charge now well too bad cuz you're a
leader now follow the but I went back I
went back you can still like press it
now it says waiting for Wawa to choose
what to do yeah oh man okay
okay now here here comes the in here we
put the the things yeah yeah yeah your
PR promps mhm wait I have to name the
episode what are we naming the episode
oh keyboard h oh Holan okay uh
okay okay and now is this the now we
type them in type prompts can you type
in yeah on your phone are you able to
okay okay okay okay all right what kind
of prompts were it is usually um it's
just like um oh yeah make sure that you
hide it on the computer and phone you
got to click the icons to hide
them uh I'm not going to look though
just in case
a
just uh uh
uh got to make sure they're
hidden okay we're typing them in now
guys this is very
important lot of focusing
mhm
okay what if my brain is empty same you
just got to do your best maybe this um
view is that have good
ideas oh yeah type in chat if you have
some good ideas guys yeah do you
for for the deck is called Holo Ian yeah
so yeah
you okay this is
like we put the prompts together right
I'm looking your bring is I think so I'm
not totally sure so there has to be like
some kind of answ so to say right right
uh-huh
a mine are not related to Holo right now
but they're good ones I promise and then
I'll come up with some H
[Music]
ones there seems to be a lot of bow bow
related prompts now bow bow got think
different ones I tried to make it Advan
so that's okay think think of the big
picture think out outside of the box no
I only have de pressing
prompts I'm entering this one anyway you
do it do it
uh
um I I literally don't know what to do
what are your ideas
chat chat give us ideas yeah
ideas and smell Fe what oh that's a good
one hold on a
sec okay some of you guys have good ones
thank God for chat man
I got
one ooh okay nice let's go
B if there's that prompt most likely
don't we need names
too oh that's a cool
one let's
[Music]
see um
okay oh that's good
[Music]
too
okay yeah lots of really good good ones
in here
[Music]
oh okay
Chad I like the last one
[Music]
hold okay okay that's really cook though
they are coming up with some good stuff
they are they are good stuff I'm looking
cuz my brain is not working so I'm
borrowing your brain okay everybody
losing the chat when it comes to good
ideas
um all right okay I've subed wait we
need 64 we need
64 what that's a lot at 26 out of 64
wait not 25 out of 6 fine we can do it
we can do it yeah we can do it we can do
it mhm dad
help okay or is is it going
down okay I no nine more nine more 10
more what 10 more what what did somebody
delete
something wonder I'm confused how this
work 11 more now it says it's just going
up what the hell
[Music]
see oh I got
one okay okay
nice okay I'm also taking one from chat
thanks for that one
yeah I think we got to go up to 64 yeah
now we're at 29
[Music]
almost halfway
there
almost I wish we could just we could
just roll with the ones that we
have I took one from chat thank
you thank you chat thanks
chat I like that
one do we have to put the UN under
underscore bar thingies there I think
it's up to you yeah yeah oh okay okay
okay
okay H mhm I finally find thought of one
on my own that's good
maybe uh that's another good one
okay uh
oh nice so we can heal from oh where the
boo
go oh she that's okay get her back she's
uh rocking myar she's rocking out I'll
find
her I rocked in too hard she rocked too
hard I too much while my brain was empty
how dare you rock so hard all right you
may need to re-enter that's okay okay
all right it's the usual
pass that chat doesn't
know okay okay we're at 44 out of 64 20
more all right contributing stop putting
one one one oh that's
why
oh oh no
do you need the pass you have the pass
right okay hold on a sec I'll go find it
hang on a sec I just can't leave this
room but hold on a second that's all
right people will be here soon I'll be
back soon yeah what's the password
password oh
[Music]
no wait I can view the oh wait no I got
it I got it I'm good I'm good you don't
need yet
almost
there
uh uh
oh okay I I'm just guessing that we will
get the answers to all these things Auto
like like automatically made by the game
right we come up with
them oh after this or what because this
only looks like questions so far mostly
I think so come up with them
and then I V on
them oh Oh you mean on the spot we come
up with them yeah I forgot okay it's
been too long maybe we should play this
multiple times cuz we have so many yeah
we
should
okay
oh we're almost
there just a few more
why Mor's nose looks like oi it looks
like Perfection look at it look at that
three diens 10 more 10
[Music]
more
oh oh cool yay I'm back y
[Music]
a six more we can do it we can do it can
bio fly with her hair flaps I don't know
bio can you H try I mean I have wings
but I guess I can if I really needed to
double wings
Wings yeah
yeah 64 is a big number only four left
four is the best
number okay I got a good
one ah oops a sorry a wait whoever put
in the last one put it back in I
accidentally deleted it uhoh we did
another one done it's done
it now you just got to save it all right
you reached the limit uh episode is
locked W Wawa is deciding what to do
it's all up to you now
gaha it says edit publish play
publish publish you want to publish it
so we can always access it yeah we can
have it for
later okay important yeah I oh okay I
didn't get a code or anything but we can
we can play now
okay oh no I got disconnected well me
too I think that's
normal disconnect wait no how do we get
we thing didn't we how do we get it how
do we get it it has the bottom maybe oh
yeah it says on the
bottoman by wa okay okay
okay I'm taking a picture of this one
just in case sounds good all right we
can we'll we'll play in a second uh
let's see all right that's wait where
our proms supposed to have like a 100%
answer be
open it's supposed to be things where
you can just put in whatever to make a
mess out of it and and that would be
funny okay just random stuff sounds good
to me yeah it's just silly stuff
honestly
yeah silly creativity H it's about
having fun fun right silliness yeah hey
wa we're definitely not silly right all
of us
yeah silly but that's why we that's why
we like you so much you know that's why
we likeo looks kind of H poopy huh oh
what does that mean the picture she
chose I got to join too you look like a
chocolate ice cream
swirl let's see hold on see like that
that will be better
yeah hold on a second you'll understand
Chad when you see
it smell it have a
time I don't feel so good after you said
that shy I'm I'm changing you're the one
who G you the pee PE poo reward okay all
right but that's different okay look I
have a banana now now I smell like
banana I don't know if that helps but
okay why away now you're just
slippery I'm going back to my pool yay
cute it's cute
huh face wait a second What's happen
yeah yeah huh why wait what oh yeah I'll
press everybody's in when you're ready
did you guys do what do you mean what do
you mean what do you mean by that I got
a notification about
something I'm looking at a picture of
all of you guys in your files are
exposed
how what is this wait don't look at
that's no oh no not my only fans where
is it where is it y it's on the holoen
Twitter what's going on on their
Twitter you
delinquent a mission begin soon what
what mission uh uh why to secret wait
wait huh oh wait huh is that is I'm a
looking for them or what that looks like
like am
files uh it does kind of look like I
Didn't Do It All right you guys are
guilty as [\h__\h] what's going on here I
didn't do it what else we've been out of
the C for a long time now there's
absolutely no reason I am here hiding
out at your house
nope absolutely no reason at all I don't
know if I believe want put do you want
to put up that picture on your stream so
people can see what we're talking about
good idea cuz yeah nobody not everyone
can see but this is this just got posted
to the wait are you sure we have to show
but it's top secret I don't I don't I
don't think we have to show outed I I
don't think I don't think what's going
on here what what are we looking at show
it show it show it this oh
no my top secret uh letters that is
definitely not on the hall website it's
not on there I'm not wanted at all
see there's the little Doodles on them
though did you guys recognize this cute
yeah I I did do that those aren't my
hearts that's not M's
Hearts all right you know what you guys
are suspicious as hell so here's what
I'm going to do I'm going to hold you
all here for another hour until we
figure out what's going on and then we
run away from the cops yeah both me and
guua are going to make sure you don't
exactly one hour yes for exactly 1 hour
I'm going to we're both going to hold
all of you here nissa's lucky that she's
she's not here right now cuz she play
with the cats now oh we're playing
quickl I'm joining the game now we're
playing
quiash
yeah 1 hour we'll do the trick I think
so surely we'll get some more info from
staff as to what these
D no it's okay that's all right is the
best place for now they will not get you
there in
bed okay I got my hope your pillows
aren't comfy
your pillows are comfy AR I hope they're
hard are not com I hope your pillows go
rock rock at like
yeah I hope you're crushing a p wait no
they like that they
do don't say such
things Oho you got to press everyone's
in to start the
game what if I just sat here hot then
what we do hot
okay what oh it's because I'm the one in
toy that's not good this is
good
goash oh no way yeah so I'm Schmitty I'm
the guy who reads stuff and makes
it read stuff I can
read okay here we go
you'll get two prompts on your device to
answer any way you please you'll go head
tohe with another player response and
everyone else on their favorite easy it
is points are awarded based on the
percentage who don't need to sell me on
it we to put we want to play make it
funny yeah be funny guys make sure
you're really
funny filter myself um let's see
[Music]
H so difficult oh man he said it was
easy it wasn't easy how much time do we
have
uh y
y how many
seconds did I finish
already wow that's a good word
oh gosh I have to filter myself no you I
mean well didn't extend
but I'll take this
one okay I got it I got it let's
freaking go I got one of my favorite
prompts no I have a better idea for my
answer please let me
fight fight
fight milk is an abbreviation
for I know I c
l no that wasn't me actually that wasn't
my PR no else love was someone else's
problem people you did that answer oh
yeah no the answer is mine yeah yeah the
answer she's silly I I think the Kyla
one was better but I still voted for the
kiar one obviously but of course way get
you thank you
oh decisions choose your favorite oo
this is
tough these are good ones don't want to
get on their bad side M yeah the r side
of
for actually been thinking about times
we' been grumpy when we were leaving
[Music]
oh B
Mak it saves space right it saves space
it is
economical oh I'm excited for this
one I didn't put that one in by the way
it wasn't me um Next vness plan I feel
dirty looking at that what the heck yeah
I think this is I know frogy personally
and I can say it's definitely the left
one
let's freaking go let's
go sounded
dastardly true but this is also pretty
mean this would be worse if you didn't
say anything you know maybe no one would
know
thison that's really
[Music]
good if I was
[Applause]
me I'm me come on guys I'm me they're
both say your
[Laughter]
mom can I
change
live
live I like it I like it I like it why
would that ever be good like the bone
man the bone B the bone
B now hear me out hear me out I wanted
to change it I wanted to change it to
the boner men but this is fine
too well no no no you just add an r at
the end cuz it's like you know like
you're there's nothing weird about it
it's just oh darn it mom get out of my
room I'm pick your favorite
pretty obvious yeah I feel like this one
has a
answer maybe Mommy wants to watch the O
too be maybe she wants to watch together
what if you want to spend time together
with your oi and you don't want your mom
involved oh
poor there are to share with Mommy and
oi's to not share with Mommy that's the
best answer your mom are good that's so
kind it's all
cute what about your father H yeah these
These are good BRS it's good that we
wrote
them these are pretty
good
lie
rights are a bit crazy so the points are
doubled
sweep why did I get my own Quest
question I I got that before too it
happens sometimes but be happy because
surely surely you'll have the best
answer right
surely oh
wait
um safy equip oh no I don't know I did a
safety quit by accident oh no it
probably won't be good no don't do the
pwn C to again sorry all right I'm going
for incorrect but funny for me
okay I don't know anything about this
I'm losing this round probably me too
but I still proudly represent my answers
all right no matter what I'll fight for
them come on people Shi you can do it
I'm
thinking think think
think I don't know
anybody
home think shiy think
think let's go B boo big
brain I'm excited to see your
Genius your mom stop with your mom I I
didn't know your mom was in your mom is
such a copout answer stop at your mom
you know you're going to get V you silly
Billy I'm going to slap you your mom
smelled right
then
we I did nothing wrong you did nothing
we
WR wow no Mom's appreciated here huh we
already wrong month
yeah r b boning bones
well now you know what the freaking quip
lash one
was what is that that's so silly that's
so CR obviously the bone men bony bones
which one did you write which one the
bone men boning bones of course no
please please that was my safety quip
please that was my
safy movie sound like a comedy yeah
bone I watch that B I should
again okay this is good I don't think
that SP piranha either whoever spelled
that piranha
yeah I'm not the only typ all person
here it's a regional spell p vtuber
when I voted fora
no pan I'm a pan
pan they don't they
don't they don't have feet is what
you're saying they don't have feet a
they don't laugh H what's in the usual
room I don't believe what happened to
the usual room oh my gosh I did answer
oh I didn't have space to finish my
thoughts this almost seems like a St you
guys are freaky to say that this is not
true by the way doesn't she massages
their
feet you wouldn't get it I wouldn't get
it which is you would you would
call come on my my f where you at my
f
exactly oh this us thing that I don't
want to take people away from the screen
it's also Prett good though I'm not
going to lie Rage
Quit there Shrine
fear a these are both really good I'm
going to choose that one this a hint
h no no I just go for realistic I don't
know you have no Shri for your o I'm so
disappointed in you my child could you
you're not subscri to
every every
single fin get for
one you've laid to round two let's
survey the please give me another chance
to redeem
myself why is at the end
huh go Redemption was too
good I
love points I'm going to send each of
you a prompt that requires three
separate responses that's trip that me
what the third one
mean what does that mean what is this
maybe like M Kathy oh right we didn't
add any Frip lash thingies so these are
random ones I think that's okay uhoh we
got weird ones we just
[Music]
skip I didn't know you're supposed to
add thrip L the heck what the heck will
they show all free answers I think so
right oh God uh oh I'm looking at it now
I'm not sure what I just
[Music]
did I did something though okay oh just
one okay that seems all
right stop
St chat what stupid
prompt pretty silly one I got Dam it
I'm whatever whatever I'm making a
statement my god myy with that Adult
Swim humor oh my gosh oh silly
silly silly
myy is that the is that the myy humor
that we talked about yesterday no no the
humor no one understands
it I can't share it with the world it's
too powerful all right I just put
this this is difficult but's see shall
we oh yeah I messed up that's okay we
all did when we decided to play this
game
cus oh
[Applause]
God what
okay you're using those busz words those
Bus words I don't really know if that's
a
circus dead night why are you saying LOL
C why why are you
say why are they saying that
huh
a is it is it kind of memorable maybe I
mean they're right oh you
[Music]
I wish i' done the bro but that would
have been too easy CU everyone in dad I
my dad would watch the circus if I
explain it to him that
way oh wait do I thought it
was oh my gosh I know this
one that was good good wow three very
different things e
different super
different uh I'm thinking from an old
person's perspective and I got to pick
the answer that I think that they would
pick as you
should very
serious
sorry okay I appreciate the
sinity yeah yeah yeah yeah the it's all
it's all they do on dress what is Dress
Bar what is this
is animal
dress these are actually really good
what is a dress bar I'm going to purp
avoid the Bro do I understand English
cuz everyone in in the audience is going
to choose
it oh my God I don't know I guess it's a
TV show probably right this is why we
make custom decks I didn't know what
that meant it's okay it really funny
it's okay um some random stuff is fine
too oh look I appreciate the Bro tug I
do see look I knew the audience was
going to choose it that's why I avoided
it let's see the
final what do we
think do we think save
me
inside people can't be stopped un
gamer really is a gamer can't believe I
was
last pretty good Adam s movie I
watch I kind of want to play it again
cuz we have so many more Play Again Play
Again Play Again Play Again
same yeah
one plan
hello what happed what
happen asking silly
question we're not going to play with
new
players people who choose resp
let's okay here we go are starting let's
go okay
[Music]
okay hey I got two prompts about
myself
um uh can't think of a funny answer uh
[Music]
uh
uh help chat but you don't know what I
have all right think I got some bangers
they're not they're not bangers I'm
still thinking gum buddy gum buddy
thinking hard
okay just write bro tug Kiara everyone
in the audience will vote for
it no it's
[Music]
okay I can't cough out with the Bro tug
every time I got to think of new things
you used your BR your bro tug card I
can't use it anymore unless it's like
really
good really good it's really really
good a that be roughing kfp Pebble no
broke that's
good oh yeah yeah yeah they're broke
because they're supporting too many I
like it he's got a lot of ooshies I
respect it though yeah I was thinking
they were emotionally
broken M go I can see where you were
going with that though I can see where
you were
going the intent was there
let's see how they oh my
God
o oh
what which part of kfp is wa people did
you like the first one no I'm not right
I'm not in this
question what what I
do wow that's such a wow at least oh got
some appreciation it's because you wrote
breast in there what oh we have a
chicken
breast I know how to win I know how to
win this game Deion deis lwuit incoming
oo these are both pretty
decent well I'm Laing I'm lawyering up
right now calling my lawyer I do like
cannibalism what I also like
cannibalism okay hey question
mark
AI audience what the
hell I know
[Laughter]
him I know Del is from cuz I know you
know what
that's you know what I'm fine with that
I'm glad we
were let's go oh oh yeah he he makes
like really nice
cakes
[Applause]
T that was good wow I mean this is also
a tough one not going to
lie okay
go go
go oh wow are kind of with the
baby
baby oh no well I thought yours was
good for your favorite ah these are both
also bangers I don't know oh
really that's
understand m
I don't even watch
Naruto it's okay
Nar believe
it
believe believe
it that was round one that was a what do
mushrooms have to do with
hul absolutely not a single thing here
oh
okay I'm going to beat you all up I'm
going to be super funny next time and
talk about don't get funny okay watch
this going to have a big comeback I
couldn't be funny if I tried don't worry
about it I mean here I come who is going
to be at the end just watch
no right here we
go this even a
question oh this is
good m oh right filtering okay
uh I don't know I'm just going to put
this okay okay okay I don't believe in
this but I'm going to put it in cuz
maybe the audience will like it see
that's what you have to do you have to
appeal to the audience there's so many
of them that play the crowd you know
it's like a metaphor for the Modern Day
entertainment smart yeah I bet you
are okay I got it I got it she's got it
I'm in got it on our souls she's
rocking oh
God know I'm scared you should
be you should
be you're right
be
[Music]
Afra you got this wa just put put taka
Nashi kiaha people V for
it I love that I love that
stuff o true oh yeah
this
is I wrote
that oh my God God who wrote that I
think I know which one shiori
wrote why are you looking at me I just
know which one you
[Music]
[Applause]
wrote I mean I agree I
agree yeah I I don't I I don't know if I
agree either but I agreed
yeah I mean
yeah I guess who wrote the left
one they did their best Kiara please
they tried so
hard
me the last joke okay all right only for
one
Banger your brain for Charisma points
okay okay that makes sense handle I know
how that
feels bosses is a name yeah could also
be a great Builder yeah Bobs I don't
[Laughter]
know too what is the audience going to
choose H I think that's pretty
even let's freaking go
they just like people who
build about you like
[Laughter]
feet they know how to appeal to me
apparently
oh suggest you know h on you like my
butt I I know everybody likes the the
your video
okay really suspicious
one SM yeah you can sniff her you can
sniff her and oh oh it's the sniff a
real girl smell means nose like she has
a smell oh she smells oh imagine like a
good smell or a bad smell good smell of
course that M by the way w
i yeah that was also very
sweet thank
you another B oh this is so oh my God oh
my God okay who's who's in syn with me
who is in syn with me yeah we're all
sink with each other
[Music]
[Laughter]
I am the new
Fu new Fu what the what I'm in sake go
where's my mango down then H I need some
to replace
it you're above me
now oh no not the trip lash that's
flashing this one's hard ripl I got a r
i got a
gum uhoh uhoh oh
no I'll be your
moo oh
no okay I'm ring a wholesome answer
really
really wholesome this is really
tough I
tried T you've been you've been riding
some bangers I Believe In You Nissa you
can't replace
me what Nissa thinks she can replace me
oh this is
wrong yeah she would have to be flat for
that what
huh she's
fuzzy I see I see after all I went
through
betrayal what what's up that's
me are you are you
okay a that's sweet
[Music]
just in
case please don't cry M
John no
T easy
answer that's pretty good although it's
pretty much the same thing but true just
one is more detailed than the other yeah
[Music]
I will say I almost wrote H life H life
H life as
well almost really funny they were the
same oh sweet
money they're both really good but the
impact there was some strong impact
there
I'm biased I'm going to pick the one
with my name on oh can't be help can't
be helped of course you would wait my
wait do these do these have like some
kind of common meaning the first one be
b b equal
Fame oh sh let's go that's a good
one sh you be
sorry and finally blank
W wo it's only wor nightmare until there
is huhuh and final okay what that is oh
my God not the
noise that's
[Music]
rough no wait so it's either your worst
nightmare is sity or your worst
nightmare is H go in other words you
have to you have to choose Cho them
between the two of them
who fun just she has scissors and pizza
it's
different she like she looks like a
beautiful beautiful nightmare lady Pizza
is horrible okay that's a
nightmare pizza's horrible don't like
pizza no everybody pineapple and pizza
no no pizza just pineapple yes
[Music]
I is funny I guess she's funny should we
restart the game or something cuz I
think it's broken it's broken I don't
know yeah I
think broke it's
broken It's a Sign May funny huh just be
funnier ladies yeah be funny
yeah
I'm I'm not funny I'm myy
Cy King of the part party we want to
play with the same
players we can play this one again or we
can play the drawing one what do you
guys want to
do the other one that is that the one
that you said is going to take a while
yeah oh okay let's it'll take a bit yeah
you guys want to play it it's really fun
it's really fun uh let's see go back and
then all right so this one's a goodie
it's it's an it's a long one but it's a
goodie oh right back here to be reminded
of you guys' crimes
okay which one all of them all of them
that doesn't help some fishies going on
here we're going to get to the bottom of
it after we place some champed up all
right now here's the code
ladies I guess
I m c oh crap I shouldn't have joined
first I don't want to host anything just
in case such perfect yeah it's just so
fitting
your
chicken it's orange it's a chicken I
have to choose
it why is it so perfect for
me um I'm going to be a cool drink of
water oh chill yeah chill CH drink water
dude we can
go hey are we ready I'm ready is
everyone here oh wait I have to press
everybody's in cuz I'm the first VIP
here we go here we go we go ooh full
drink
cool yeah yeah I feel like when we
played this with with myth Ena is she's
such a good drawer like she like
whatever you draw you cannot go up
against Ena now maybe there's higher
chances but Callie's good call I'm using
phone a I use my phone too using them I
have phone Gua is going to have
Advantage yeah but on the phone you can
draw with your finger so
that's
cute yeah a bunch of different prompts
we make up ourselves
oh maybe not maybe we don't make
up oh do I have colors I can use do we
have colors yeah you should
I can't zo
out land Lords what Cod tole they're
asking for
[Music]
COD you guys I got to move you guys hold
on a
sec there you
go hey I don't know what to
draw is not very good it's okay I want
the phone we're all on the phone we'll
figure it out
together
yeah you got to be Champion
[Music]
music so
laggy like we're all on phone we're all
on the same
level I'm using my
mouse we're almost on the same level
then
I don't really know what my guy is what
what is what's his thing what's he why
is he it has nothing to do with the
theme he's just
weird just a weird
guy a little hat
yeah mine's also going to be weird
hopefully good to
the audience has to love it think think
what the audience will like okay o yeah
this looks good 20 seconds I'm not done
to name their character what I don't
want to
what 20 seconds he
said okay I
[Music]
okay no I drawing his
mouth
Challenger that was not enough time
what oh cute okay I cck okay analyze
your opponent and create a challenger
oh okay okay I have an
idea h
[Music]
how much time do we
have that's for sure not
[Music]
enough damn
it
no dks lagy come on come on I got to
draw my champion
give me my
champ yeah looking good can you not get
any other colors than the ones that are
there there few but it's still like
really
[Music]
hard okay okay have to do
okay I'm I'm
done
yeah if you're done then fill this
awkward silence with entertainment what
awkward silence it's only awkward when
you it's awkward Gua we
focused we're locked in I locked in I'm
locked in a challenger
chion and I think I did a perfect
J analyze it so look closely at what we
draw
character okay I got it actually early
14 no it's 12 B you're wrong 11 actually
no it's it's nine now it's seven bio
it's five now it's four now two
actually I said it first I swear to God
all right that's fine people you're
already such a
winner congrats on another win let's
talk about the fight
let's
go blackith
Destroyer oh good team up good good
match
up I think there's an obvious obvious
well one of these people is behind me so
I'm going to choose the one that's
behind
[Laughter]
me oh oh she's dying she's dying oh no
poor
oh
no against
myself way she wins either way her
biggest her biggest
fret same thing what is this Destroyer
2044 Destroyer this oh here I got to
vote for the new and improved
one it's calmly
improved why are you flipping characters
I don't
understand destroy 2044 destroy a girl
why do we have two F
destroy n I'm not here to make how
clearly what do you mean I just named
it yeah I don't know who name the last
one though cutie oh
cute oh God can't be jaming
out I'm pink and I like to jam so I'm
going to choose
pink this is going to be a I
like
no it's okay G blue
G wait it was actually more versus slow
wow they didn't know to
try I didn't know to name
it
listen
look
really egg chck of fire
oh he so round please have mercy F see
look like a
bigp he looks like a d come
on versus K not going to lie oh yeah you
can tell it was my versus
K tree man guy let's
go that tree man who's a guy who lives
in the
trees
Sil do
hey you haven't even met them yet those
cats are really really cute I don't know
those cats don't yell at us this
true they're pretty cute you know
they're pretty
cute my cat are cute
[Music]
mushroom
mushroom mushroom dead inside though I
feel like mushrooms actually are dead I
don't know I like how dead this one
looks yeah cuz he's a fun guy
yeah fun
[Music]
guy my S
the best way to beat a mushroom and let
put it in the fire and eat it dang we
were so strong what wowow my poor
friendship
Destroyer oh I never noticed the
title I don't like there promp oh yeah
yeah you didn't know I didn't know it's
okay I don't like my prompt it implies
things that I don't like you mean you
would not do
it we can start over the game no it's
okay it's like an insult though to the
to whatever I'm drawing oh that's kind
of that's all right this n is
[Music]
silly
sorry it's okay no sorry is for
when are you going to stop the sneezing
M
never
oh
[Music]
good I can't I can't think of anything
um somebody you got this you got this
what's something what's something I
don't
like mushrooms me no not again not
again oh crap oh no oh no I didn't do
the name right no okay I guess I
[Music]
havea
Ana Anya Ana
oh my gosh I'm not
ready drawing in 20 seconds is not
easy but now you have 20
[Music]
seconds going to be what is this
I
[Music]
wow oh oh oh oh no nothing I can beat
this oh oh hold
up
oh Kar you sound like you're in
pain
uh s this one okay mhm
can I draw fast enough is the
question people can you give us a count
again when it gets closer okay if I
finish yeah let it better
finish have to for all of us finish
finish and beat our
[Music]
asses okay got some good art popping off
did
didy oh God what is this how much time
do we have okay maybe I can rush
it all right all right all right all
right all
right how's the time
going hi 30 seconds 37 seconds 37
okay get so P good and then it messed up
it's
okay name those characters
no okay good enough no I'm not done I'm
done I'm done 10 seconds 9 8 7 6 6 5 4 3
2 masterpie created the second half
which means it's time for the tag team
each match up will includ surprise
contest
deag
characters all right like the one you
drew before can be switched in mhm if
you think it's better
okay who we got so
cute how can we
[Music]
chooseing I go with a funny name is not
very chilling right chill he very but
you have to think of the the champion
that beats the pudding true I really
likes to eat pring yeah a that's a good
point he would beat him
up beat him up beat him up oh this one
we got to switch out
oh that's a good question I believe in
blue blue is the underdog kind of want
to V for
blue
blue that's a tough
one oh man just
barely Yik 100%
Yik yikes yeah
oh
no who's up
next I see I
see are you
just that is not what I look
like just like a valley version of you
but I'm so much sexier than sexy moo
right
oh let's
see I think I think I can do it guy get
him Freeman
[Music]
guy
pathetic Freeman
guy let's go it's a cute
drawing
good belly W audience is terrifying
terrifying
wow
here go who's next Who's Next I'm
scared how
isore
what guys think of what she's done for
you did she help you with a dection or
something taking a
beating I believe it she was not able to
make you
speaking
keep come on that really
good I don't think motivational
friendship destruction's go very good at
public yeah i' prefer M say something at
my my school PSA
meeting or friendship
[Music]
[Applause]
destroyed will we see M drawing for
actually do feel genuine fear oh no oh
God they're
scared I don't feel a
fear terrible yeah I didn't like this
prop but just just so you know there's a
joke between me and Ana that we hate
each other so it's a joke it's a joke
that's pretty funny I like
that it doesn't mean wa's terrible
Community watch grp it just means I can
beat up any yeah that's all it means yo
I
trust watch over my
community she can watch TR cat watch I
don't know would you trust these cats to
watch your community I would I would
power to the egg no protect the
community and they'll capture
Scoundrels
cat
goost with wa you winning a lot Kelly
woo yeah I I don't think I can be weo
though but I can take second
place what is
that
F I like how this one doesn't I like how
this has nothing
else how did
thisen this cuz the S was drawn first
right
escaping right my Telly heart a
bit what oh doing the group project oh I
know who
I be doing that you do
yeah K's strong she's
strong I can't disagree
with as much as I love mush I just don't
think he can do it all by
himself all by herself wow will grind
through it wow yeah and get never right
for everybody what is
that trash
compactor looking
unsuspecting sit on the trash and
destroy it let's
go beautiful
art why why is sheing
the P has been defeated oh my God gaming
is my channel going to get banned from
this no no no my Chanel didn't get
banned so yours will not get banned
either don't
worry
gaming right here oh God how this poetic
oh
God four wins looking
at
incredible judges
are oh wow who's it going to
[Applause]
[Music]
be no you just but your boy came second
which is basically like winning first so
let's
go congrats
everyone fight team it's so perfectly
timed look what time it is it's almost
guys yeah it's just about time I thought
treat great by the
way I was going to say you guys are
still suspicious though I don't know why
are we suspicious are we sure that we're
the ones who had to go back in the cell
maybe k
ad Adent is going to be fired all of you
for your crimes fired for crimes too
many Crim crime back to prison crime
back to prison a crime of being
[Music]
innocent time there's nothing innocent
about Advent
no fire fire fire right means we're
innocent not
yeah prove that you guys aren't
suspicious as heck mve
it what did you do byebye what did you
do we didn't do
anything
suspicious
Nissa hiding for can she come out a
hiding not safe no I mean well you can
if you want you can you can explain
yourself anytime in in front of in front
of me and Kiara to what's whatever's
going on here cuz there's some
suspicious stuff happening
what should I be looking at right now oh
I don't know I feel like I feel like
we're going to figure out we're going to
get to the bottom of this mystery or or
not we can just go to sleep it's pretty
late no I want
to every sleep I'm grumpy you know what
I'm grumpy too because I feel like there
are Intruders in my home and and I feel
like there's something you guys aren't
telling me you know all of us there's
something you guys aren't telling us uh
H I'll tell you a
secret
what we ate all
popcorn what how do you think that makes
FY feel she said that it was okay after
we ate it yeah wow I can't believe it
you that's me villains oh my God put
on
yeah for that what hold on a second no
you you guys aren't off the hook for
that this is a
[Music]
diversion oh wait what it's time what
what was that
alarm huh I think oh no it's a
d a video hold on hold on there's a
video stop there's a
video what the [\h__\h] there's a
video okay hold on I'm scared should we
watch it
together let's watch it together yeah
okay all right let's Press Play in a
minute here I'm going to count to three
3 2 1 play and you guys press play okay
yeah yeah yeah hey if you guys want the
the link to the video I'll post it in
the chat and pin it for you guys but
there's a video and I think maybe we can
get the answer to why these guys are in
trouble if we watch this together
huh all
right okay oh here we go it's on YouTube
it's on YouTube quick quick okay here we
go be be sure to click it guys we're
going to count down in a so click it
click the pinned comment and there's a
video they're already watching it
they're already watching it two one play
go oh who
that who are these people uh-oh oh man
nice legs oh my God oh my God nice legs
legs what was
that who are they H oh man they look
very familiar those
legs some familiar legs
yeah that doesn't sound good I'm
concerned I'm concerned too I'm worried
y I'm not worried they'll ever Take Me
Alive EV will typ this
it's been a while since we're out of the
cell now I was getting used to I'm not
worried okay not worried if they if they
want to take us back to jail where they
to fight us back to jail I don't know
yeah you got to play Smash with
us smash them yeah they're they're
they're coming to smash yeah yeah thank
you for laughing you're beautiful my
Queen H Justice Justice wow well I guess
we'll find out what this whole Hol
Justice is on 8 p.m.
tomorrow wait that's tomorrow
tomorrow not today tomorrow it's
actually not far from now that's today
like 11 hours from now yeah that's today
it's today well for you
today I guess is is the answer wait what
time is it for me you probably pretty
late maybe tomorrow it's today tomorrow
today not tomorrow today Prime Time PST
is usually pretty late you that's
tomorrow that's tomorrow excuse me oh
techic not today for me 1:00 a.m. we'll
figure it out right now in PD it is 900
a.m. I'll be up I'll be up it's today
yeah hours tomorrow we'll find out more
what this whole Justice is all right
today yeah cuz you're on that side of
the globe well yeah what could it all
mean I'm also really curious I feel like
there's so many unanswered questions but
yeah at least we get to find out the
answered sooner rather than later right
sooner yeah yay as as long as you know
it doesn't mean that we have to go back
to the cell everything you know because
no it doesn't you can stream from the C
aniversary and you know I like to stay
having summer remember you
know well no one's going to steal you
guys away no matter what you guys are
safe you're not going back to the cell
but I am really curious you won't let
anybody take us Callie Senai of course
not what kind of what kind of senpai
would I be if I let someone take you
guys right yeah Senai what about you me
I'm not one for
anything I said you guys are fired
mess up did you
forget up K I guess there's a lot of s
by the make up this world huh we love to
themselves but I want to St here thank
you thank
you you you can you know work as like
volunteers or
so no I'm moving into Callie's house my
home
yeah you want to Victory me right you
can stay in the storage room I
guess you can be her pet rock who
doesn't want a pet rock s
fun so soft so fluffy so the
fluffiest well thanks so much that is
crazy thank you guys for coming to check
out our unsuspecting collab out of
nowhere where W that was strange just
very OD was like before this they were
like oh oh Advent 3D uh Adent
3D exciting you already
know a lot of exciting things happening
isn't
therez
yeah oh big bamboozle big bamb for to 11
hours from
now guess
so well I suppose we'll all see you guys
at that time when it gets
announced um whatever their crimes were
I want to know I want to have a list of
your crimes I have a list of your crimes
me too innocent yeah yeah know the det
hire a lawyer good idea lawyer
people can can you can you let us know
who they are thanks yeah I have I have
good recommendations I have good
recommendations cuz KP is getting you
know sued all the time so
in big legal trouble all the
time has something to do with like I
don't know weird business practices in
the usual room and stuff like that yeah
I I'll connect you I'll hook you up
thank you yeah don't worry I mean I'm
the one who's firing you but yeah I'll
hook you up thank
you there's so kindness in the yeah in
the
horribleness I Love You So Soft side oh
oh really okay well anyway it's fine
it's fine it's fine yeah we we'll fight
it out after the stream you I'll catch
you recommendation right right byebye
only the best one only the best okay
then we'll find it out and then we'll be
safe because we have a good lawyer yeah
okay good plan
by it was really fun playing ja all
together there's so many exciting things
M it's an exciting time exciting time
for holo as as a whole I feel you know
there's a lot of fun stuff going on so
yeah we hope you guys are having a great
time you know even through all the chaos
and insanity and whatnot and yeah thanks
for supporting us and uh and please keep
looking forward to all of our individual
and group success together let's keep
having fun together happy belated
Father's
Day Big Ups appreciate that well I guess
we'll see you guys around uh any last
words ladies I know that sounds threat
threatening
but last yeah him some Last Words My Bro
tugs stop sh I'm gonna I'm gonna come
over and punch you
wow me make sure we all have
lawyers everyone needs a lawyer these
days yeah anything else you guys any
other last words before we say goodbye
for for good for a little bit h a z AER
Zayn a
z yeah I guess that's it we'll see you
later everybody let's get a good
sleep have a good day goodby on the chat
is filled with greetings appreciation
for the stream and Lively reactions to a
recent event called the Bro tug
all right have a good one
everyone bye bye
bye peace goodbye
[Music]