[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
there's nothing
else
thank you
[Music]
okay thank you
hello
I look again again
I'm tired
[Applause]
[Music]
small lightsaber it's knife
one of those frilly knife these
hello
hello I will wake myself up with this
game I just woke up from my nap because
all night I couldn't sleep well I woke
up it was so weird
I woke up every hour like once or twice
nice thought is it now it's 5 a.m now
it's 6 a.m now it's 7 A.M now it's 8 A.M
now it's 9 A.M why do I keep on waking
up
uh and it wasn't like I felt sometimes I
feel you know uneasy or Restless
uncomfortable because hey I'm feeling
too hot
B I need to go to Idol meeting
or
B my back hurts too much but that's
often
because partially partially often solved
because of the idol meeting
um
is running around but none of this
really was the case this time so I don't
understand
why I was so tired uh so unable to sleep
through the night
yeah and then eventually I gave up
and was like I'll just get a nap later
[\h__\h] it and of course the nap was way
more efficient
than the night's sleep
hmm
really makes you wonder
oh I'm so tired
[Music]
okay let me take those glasses off those
well otherwise they're going to shatter
with all that action
hmm
no I didn't really feel that stressed I
mean maybe I was a little bit nervous
about my Korean lesson but not really I
mostly
like had everything done that went
really well by the way I was worried I
was worried because
last lesson was not even a week ago
we had to do it early this week last
lesson
she taught me so many words
so many words
and I was like [\h__\h] I'm not gonna
remember this until next time but I
pretty much did mm-hmm
[Music]
y'all like a lot of verbs and a lot of
extraocabulary and I showed her how I
voluntarily come by compiled it all
nicely together I think she liked that I
did that because it was that was what I
posted on Twitter that was not you know
not like I had to do that I just felt
like compiling it because everything's
like all over the place
often when she teaches me
and I I tried to keep up during the
lesson with writing but my Korean
writing is still so slow
um that I can't keep up so well so I
decided to just do it afterwards the
compiling
of the notes and I saw I showed her and
she was like oh yeah that's really nice
and then I I voluntarily just uh like uh
like set everything off of the list that
I compiled
and I was so surprised by myself that I
had it all memorized I think it's really
you know writing it down helps a lot and
then I also practiced a little bit the
night before but I didn't feel so
confident
especially if it's from from English
to Korean is more difficult for me than
Korean to English
like when I say a word
in English
and then need to remember what the
Korean word was that's a bit more
difficult than the other way around
but we're getting there
yeah
[Music]
I'm making so much progress and my
teacher is also saying like now there
will be a lot of vocabulary that she'll
be teaching me
like until now it wasn't that much
because I still had to learn some basics
but now I'll be bombarded
blasted with vocabulary
but so far my brain is keeping up
more or less yeah and some of the some
of the words I compiled I asked by
myself she wasn't even gonna teach me
but we were like making sentences she
was asking me
um do you go to a restaurant I think she
already forgot what restaurant was
no how can I say sometimes and how can I
say maybe so I got some extra filler
words that seem very important
foreign
[Music]
sometimes I go to a restaurant
um
I'm so proud
yeah I'll be busy shooting later and I
need to wake up my brain so I'm just
tangenting now
but I'm so proud it's doing pretty well
second time viewer oh thank you wait
what the [\h__\h] what why would you like me
like me
come on
here don't take advantage of me
aha
no no no no no no no
I'm a dog Amado sounds like tamago
actually Amador
also sounds a little bit like a Japanese
word because the Amma sometimes
in
in Japanese it has a similar
sound to it don't you think
no wait maybe oh oopsie okay then then
it doesn't sound similar but somebody
sent me this video my Korean Bros sent
me this video uh because some words
really sound similar for example uh
Japanese word for newspaper is chimbun
and Korean is shin Moon
it's an M instead of a b
and then what else
[Music]
um
I don't know okay now I can't think of
it but one thing I was happy to hear is
like the system for saying months in
Korean there is not like you know a word
that like we have with January February
Etc no just like in uh in Japanese
there's just a word for the month and
then you say the first month the second
month the the third month Etc
it's the same with uh uh Korean so
that's really useful and then I was
[\h__\h] surprised at the weekdays I
learned those today too and I you know I
remember oh in Japanese for example
Monday is gets you'll be written with
the kanji for a month
and then you know I already knew uh
for months the word in Korean because we
just learned it was
okay so here's the big brain explosion
thing uh in in Korean the word for
Monday is also
but it doesn't sound really like uh the
Japanese one but
it also has the tsuki
basically in Korean in it like it also
starts with moon yeah Moon day
so what
what was it what it was
I forgot
well now
I think why are you
I think it's Monday
oh yeah yeah
it's Monday and the war part is the the
moon and and it continues like that like
the other days are yeah because of
Chinese they took originally the kanji
uh the Chinese kanji and just like Japan
so they like yeah adjusted it to their
own language but they kept the meaning
of it
and and and it really helps to you know
wrap my brain around it because it's
really similar system
so also uh Niti will be Sunday
uh Nietzsche in Japanese is
uh well the kanji for it is Sun but also
day and in Korean it's the same uh they
was Ill in Korean and let me let me Flex
my knowledge uh healing career so it's
ill it's actually repetitive because the
ill at the end of ilio is the same as
the in the beginning of the word
um
[Music]
but it's really easy to understand so
let me say the date of today
um uh uh uh well let me say it with the
year uh I forgot what was thousand
um
help me Korean Bros a thousand
a thousand
uh John okay yeah
um
[Music]
some
so we write the year of 2200 uh 2023
yeah and and then
uh cool
cool
wait no no no wait it's not September I
looked at my date thingy and it's the
wrong order uh no uh oh well over the
fifth month and cool
foreign
we have the ninth day of the fifth month
of 2023 yeah
Yeah Tuesday but I don't remember the
days properly yet we'll get there at
least I know how to say today
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah so my next lesson is next
week until then I'll surely remember
everything
online Miami
[Music]
no
um
an error occurred while updating Hotline
Miami disk read hour what do you mean
disk there's no disk
ready to launch in approximately two
seconds
oh oh now it's working okay
my heart is it full
or it could be let me check
ah there's a 34 GB uh open out of 932
uh
[Music]
yeah
um it's fine it's fun fun we can play in
the game
what
and gbmb
um GB not MB
no that's okay it looks pretty
um small in the like bar
let me see are these settings okay like
I had in last time probably
oh
now for Hotline Miami it should be
enough right okay okay okay
what the [\h__\h] it opened but it's not
showing me
um right here
well it's like
Hawaii music again where did it where is
it
there it is
[Music]
I like this Hawaiian music you don't
hear it again chotomoto
um
it's not
it's not Window mode again
can you still change it in there
I didn't know where I'm pressing
no you can't change it in here
the second time I opened it it worked
out last time
a title it's Hotline Miami
um
I know you didn't hear it
it's my sound options always resetting
when I restart the pce
oh wait
are you sure
what what are we doing say a checked
windowed hmm
should I
hmm
start again
even if it's not when okay it's not
windowed again but okay whatever
oh shy
[Music]
yeah yeah there we have it I wonder if
that's gonna be too loud
config loaded Gamepad no no no no
Gamepad none
play with mouse
and keyboard
the [\h__\h]
continue
music louder
oh wait I will adjust for you
special service well I think it's extra
quiet now anyway
clean hit what chapter six we're in
chapter six
are you making fun of me great beavers
because it's not
why is it showing me this start with
intro yeah why not
you're 13 oh oh one uh ship
some
[Music]
welcome to May 13th 1989.
and now it's too loud guys
[Music]
need to like wait until we're really in
the game to tell me if it's like loud
and quiet
how do we play this game again where's
my lady
why don't you go
are we restarting from the beginning
[Music]
she went out for milk she dumped me
and
[Music]
[Applause]
and we have some VIPs who will be
staying with us today make sure you give
them a great day that will be your top
priority this evening
now get going
I'll make them stay at the hotel forever
because it's just so great
AKA they will die there oh
we have a cleaning person here that
looks really really
um
not good
you're gonna talk to me by not talking
to me huh okay
we'll need a little bit of a
uh oh that's an actual tip a little bit
of a warm-up face guys
we got a new one start with knife oh I
don't know but I really yeah I feel like
Tony
is open we're gonna stay with Tony
all right I remember this camera thing
it doesn't really seem like there's
anyone in the first room but maybe there
is
someone on the toilet and I can't enter
from that room I could go into that room
get some weapons and then go there
that seems almost too easy don't you
think
oh that's gonna be rough
oh yeah there's really no one in this
room
does he not have a weapon
[Music]
he did have a weapon the right click to
pick up knit
ooh we have to bait them I think wait
will they throw those plates at me
like how do you do this
I guess
oh [\h__\h]
talk to me you know
so
[Music]
I wait they gotta come here
uh oh it worked
nice shot though yeah I didn't see
anything I wasn't sure if that will hit
okay but I understand
okay well now the doors are actually
closed
I was hoping you will knock him over
yeah yeah
already getting back into the group
oh God this is so scary
did I have a look
different weapon now maybe not there's
someone here no
[Music]
dying what I'm eating
hands on he's just chilling there
because he's nervous about his stage in
the restaurant not going as well
and he thought it would and now he's
like contemplating
maybe he should just stay in the toilet
forever
yes
[Music]
I mean the way to do this is to
bait right
constipating contribution
is the way to go right
I should
[Music]
peek shoot cover
s
Pink Shoes cover
um
[Music]
that shot oh the door closed on me
oh
that was a clean [\h__\h] shot
I don't even think they noticed me
I wonder if he's dangerous can I can't
click on that guy
whoa
hey
are you guys
not gonna why is that one not moving
ah now they're moving what was that
oh I can't believe I'm surviving here be
careful
they're not more well they won't move
they won't move
[Music]
for the last couple
oh ah he's like a he's like I'm
crouching under the table
okay I mean the problem is I think my
the weapon I just chose is kind of slow
right
oh ah he died okay good good good uh now
he's left against the rest what about
the the the guys who are sitting at the
table
they're not gonna attack me or what
because like I can't select them
so I'm guessing not
they wanted to okay then
I do that but it's not telling me I did
it
is it because I should kill him and what
am I missing I don't want to get killed
now what am I missing
[Music]
you need to kill them no Witnesses
okay
sorry man stage clear yay this is our
second floor yeah
yeah it goes our second floor
[Music]
elevator
lots of uh salads
lots of healthy yummy salad what is this
place there's no one here
[Music]
there's no one here
what the [\h__\h] is that
is what
what
oh
but without my weapon
what happens if he sees me
hi you ignore me
oh
wow okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
well I don't know if that's what I want
to do
it's one way to do it that you can't you
he won't do anything right
I thought no one was there
I think they're gone now
salads
yeah
okay no windows here again someone on
the toilet who seems innocent
this is that a memory disc on the in the
pool oh wait
[Music]
oh which hair but from above it looks
like a memory like a like a floppy disk
yeah I should go
[Music]
but I don't know okay
we'll go in here
I wonder that's on purpose
[Music]
hi don't mind me but I guess now you are
you are a witness
and that's gonna be a problem right
oh
[Music]
yeah
I
had them too
uh
using up my rounds
[Music]
just look away
maybe we can think about it
[Music]
let's see
he doesn't quite come around the corner
doesn't he
but he won't know in a second
which one first maybe I can get both
[Music]
missing show
I'm missing so much
[Music]
go from melee it's easier huh why is he
alive
I'll take care of you later
[Music]
okay okay
okay now they didn't really see me for
the windows
but I can't shoot for them right
we cannot
I thought those were windows that I can
shoot through
for these ones okay
[Music]
um ah
okay
what are they like
stunned from my skills
okay
you're like damn what what the [\h__\h] did
that but she's so good what happened so
fast we should hire her she's like
better than all of us
incredible it's like a new Legend
something we've never seen before
[Music]
must have been the wind
I mean that's plenty of shots to do
something
because that weapon is much louder but
still like hell when you're standing
right next to him
makes no sense
did I kill both
I'm gonna make sure if I got everything
covered you know
smig at pickup is just very quiet
apparently like freaking Mouse
oh wait it's 32 rounds
that's like not the same as the one the
one I thought I was using
I guess I'll go with this one I mean
it's it only in my best interest
holy [\h__\h]
you should double kill
[Music]
oh double kill wow wow that's easy why
are these round swings you can I get
something here
is there something I can get
no I'm going to the pool
no nothing to pick up either
what
over here
foreign
[Music]
I'm sorry dude
yeah that was that went pretty well I
mean I still took my time but
it was pretty good I would say what
about him huh
to kill him
maybe he was one of us
one of us one of us
he's just doing his job he's just
cleaning I mean he'll he'll be helpful
right he'll clean away all the blood
[Music]
type bonus zero right for real
um I guess because it was so easy they
expected me to do more
it's at least to C minus
all right
[Music]
at least as long as it's not like f or
so new mask
love
giraffes don't
to wrap some pretty op you know with
their um
with their size buff
not even Lions will usually go for
giraffes okay maybe Lions as a team but
alone never they got no chance like oh
man all the all the animals that you
think are strong they don't go for a
giraffe because they're so tall and the
Damage you try to inflict mostly all
they can get is a giraffe's butts
because they're so tall
yeah yeah elevated hitbox
yeah it's pretty op and then and then
they are they're the only one of the
moment they have is when their baby a
baby still very small but usually always
surrounded by Mommy
so okay
not so often the problem yeah you have
to level up and then you're safe from
everything pretty much and as long as
you're a little low level a bit
dangerous dangerous
when they're drinking water ah you mean
when they lower their head they're fine
but they also got an elevated View
so they see enemies from further away
um
way further away than others they have a
good overview
good giraffes good giraffes I I'm in my
next playthrough of life I'm gonna
possibly try playing a giraffe because
it seems very op very safe Magnum
oh is it like a Lego
Wild West we stole this thing
we're back in the VHS Place hello
[Music]
hey my man boy am I glad to see you no
that wasn't the voice you should have
have you been following the news about
the killings
I'll need to follow them I'm the one who
creates the news
it's a revolver
giraffe video oh what sound do they make
now this is top secret you can't tell
anyone but I have a friend who's in the
police force oh really you told me
there's rumors going around there could
be more than one Purp
maybe a whole bunch no it's just me a
group of people wearing masks killing
Russians
it's like it's from a movie or something
right well I think it's fascinating
right so just grab any movie you want
it's on the house that's what friends
are for oh you're so sweet thank you uh
what movie should I watch
maybe Lord of the Rings
that's what babe wrote but turns out it
wasn't the first I know a lot of others
were shocked with me like babe please do
not skip through the movie because she
tweeted oh I'm skipping through Lord of
the Rings skip skip speeding
um and I I can't find it I don't
understand you know I know I need to
find out about elrond and
yeah it sounded like she was watching
for the person turns out she watched it
already plenty of times but I
recommended her I don't know if she saw
she saw the other tweet I think the
other one where I was like please don't
skip skip
actually like it hurt me when I read
that I was like what the [\h__\h]
but thank God it wasn't really the way
we thought it was
and yeah maybe maybe she only saw that
one tweet because the other one I I
recommended her
um nerd of the Rings on YouTube I'm sure
she will find out every I even linked to
the elrond video she'll find out
everything she wants about elrond if she
wants that I'm pretty sure
yeah warning her up the rabbit holder
[Music]
that was on the 122nd Street Southeast
well the residence water Pipers we went
all over the whole building is gonna be
flooded soon hope you can get on this
[\h__\h] ASAP don't go easy on the map
okay my lady is back apparently good
that she came back
I knew I could trust her
she my woman now
my woman now
she never left really she was in the
bath I didn't see her
okay
we've got our top Tony again oh I don't
I didn't even look what the giraffe does
but I think Tony will be a big
place
I like this beat
okay we'll be good
can I use the broom too no
[Music]
hey
5 10.
[Music]
two rounds
I don't like this weapons
what if I missed oh there's the new one
why is there no one in here
[Music]
I'll try it no way that's not it I'll
try it
what the [\h__\h]
I love that oh hello
I wonder if I can get two only if I
should die oh doggo
please don't come for the door
a wrong way weapon to start off with
that's for sure and also it's a really
[\h__\h] loud weapon
[Music]
um
what a punch
he punched a bit too early
oh second guy not coming and this one
also got reacting it wasn't it that
[\h__\h] loud
okay
like sometimes they come sometimes they
don't what
you guys are so
sometimes you do things that and
sometimes you don't
[Music]
know
inconsistent yeah that's the way that I
wanted
[Music]
a lot of people do some
closing the door already solved all my
problems
[Laughter]
[Music]
why is he so fast
you have to shoot that guy
oh [\h__\h]
okay now he's not coming I actually
prefer that
all right
no weapons oh okay
[Music]
what where did he come from uh
piles of buddies AKA one body made me
think he was dead
where did she come from I just casually
walked by
wait for the dog
laughs
[Music]
come here don't go come here
just want to go in there with no weapon
I think
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay we're already starting
destroying my mouse I have think I need
to be refunded for my mouse by this game
by the Developers
come on
oh wait he's still I was gonna walk by
him again
silent murder is the best murder
where's the weapon go on there
I have a habit of throwing it away
okay
[Music]
easy
what
[Music]
how many hits oh he died after he
circumvented security
by his wounds afterwards
he needs a lot of shots
damn it is this because of the weakness
of my weapon but or is it because he
really just needs time no matter what
[Music]
oh no no
[Laughter]
oh I need a round where he doesn't hear
me
[Laughter]
what this time you did not choose
ignorance I see oh
[Music]
it's not too funny what is this anyway
no secret
oh God
ignore me please I'm not here
or am I
you can't pick up I can
[Music]
foreign
and that's bad
[Music]
oh
God
this is full don't come here this is my
private room okay okay while a pain
Panic chamber
[Laughter]
[Music]
no not again not again
[Laughter]
I need a run where he doesn't
come check up on me
I was that was I was a checkmated there
because I was directly across the other
shooter guy yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
no this time he doesn't come for me
[Applause]
this gun is so loud
oh my healing
I'll kill him silently
if he comes over here
oh
thank you for your cooperation
did I get him
[Music]
I thought if he's over there by the time
he reaches me he should die if I get a
hit
okay
um
[Music]
I want to get the dog go
should I trust my iron fist
or
it's like a wild west situation who
shoots first
[\h__\h] you oh
okay at least oh
at least no one uh
survived that
[Music]
okay actually I like this current
please don't please don't please don't
please don't
okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
would be okay
[Music]
go go come for me come for me
ah [\h__\h] I thought it was gonna come any
moment nah nah
okay
oh [\h__\h]
I'm not sure I want to go with my fists
[\h__\h] die
I feel like I can get the dog easier
with uh
with my Chris normally but only when I
like I'm mentally ready for it
[Music]
no [\h__\h] no [\h__\h]
around
why was it empty
[Laughter]
oh man okay okay okay
we say
still got a round two
um
[Music]
is he not gonna leave the room
now doggo is
[Music]
that's what's going there but look at me
how far I came with uh Tony's face
holy [\h__\h]
yeah
was he gonna gonna Patrol
man
[Music]
you don't want to see what's behind
these doors
and then I have to wait a moment just a
moment
[Music]
[Laughter]
and he bumped back on him
okay
[Music]
I just missed
should I wait for my chance to do the
thing again that I did before
[Music]
um
you didn't hear it
[Music]
the Mist that's my rounds that's it I'm
out
uh okay
[Music]
the weapon was empty too
I mean any not at the empty weapon no
this one actually no it wasn't empty
oh
[Music]
I'm getting [\h__\h] nervous
[Laughter]
yo oh I got it I got it I got it only
one left
oh
Mamma Mia
any like Secrets or stuff
right clicking right clicking
oh we should also bring a weapon with us
maybe this one
any secrets
clear gotcha wait was this already the
second floor
oh no I think we're going up ah okay
hmm
[Music]
how we gonna do that
again hey
very fast maybe I'm safe after all this
mess but no no no no oh my God
[Music]
[Laughter]
a little bit unorganized
[Music]
anyone gonna visit me at my door no
the consequences of my own actions
[Music]
we we can't make too much noise if we
keep it down a little bit we have a
chance
like now he didn't he didn't come over
very good very good oh it's hard to see
what's going on up there but I don't
think they'll see me right if I'm on the
frame
[Music]
okay and then once I shoot the big guy
I'll just have to like back out back out
back up
oh is it a hot pan
maybe good if it's if it's actually hot
like you know the boiling water but I
doubt it
oh [\h__\h] let's try this
oh
I just want to knock him out but maybe
the other one is coming first
[Music]
you give a [\h__\h]
what
guns
yeah
[Music]
look at this sharp shooter attack
I'm dancing on your bodies and I dance
Dance With My Guns Guns
what's going on this bed looks confusing
it looks like a Picasso painting that's
dead
oh
oh [\h__\h] then bring a gun I thought it
was I thought it was done
[\h__\h] it
[Music]
um
yeah that's how you get a gun
[Music]
thank you
yeah yeah
no one here no one left
except big sassy big guy again
Mr Big
rooms uh only the dog would leave the
room
[Music]
quiet he died quietly
that was a good chance to get him to run
away but the dog scares me
oh
[Music]
maybe I can kill a dog quietly
I'll try to kill the dog quietly
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
you know what I mean
is it really just a Prank Caller man
come on have mercy
prank callers are usually very very um
juvenile I guess
in their brain at least they're young
phone
what
the [\h__\h]
up it's been beheaded
phone mom phone home
this is a bit different than usual it
seems like I don't have to to do the
killing I thought I was the only one
hey y'all
golf wait it looks like a either a golf
Club thingy or that gun that goes like
wait it's just golf clubs
I thought it was um
I I don't uh what was that what was that
gun that I used at the end yeah the
minigun I think I'm talking about
or or that I don't know one of the big
ones
that I used for the big one that way
the golf clubs where to shoot the holes
and they would turn and go like that
oh there's someone there oh wait is this
my company and that's why I'm here to
help because like somebody killed all my
friends uh co-workers
is this a boss
should I have brought a weapon
oh you're dead meat oh
[Music]
you think so
oh I started by going in what if I need
a weapon
wait let's start having any weapons
lying around
[Music]
gotta get the minigun gotta get the
minigun
[Music]
wait how many are there
like a perfect distance so I Gotta Throw
it and and stun him wait for free swings
infinite oh okay interesting
[Music]
whoa
foreign
don't even ask
don't even ask me
you know I have a habit of throwing
oh man
all right all right I know the system
now and I am part of your system for a
little while until I'm not anymore
once it gets
immediately hard wait could I have taken
his knife
probably
what
what it's so dynamic
[Music]
okay can we skip the walking in scene
and talking
oh god oh sure
okay ah no I don't think he's he would
he's holding the knife in his hand so
I'm not sure if I could actually do it
foreign
if I could
actually take it yo
we're dancing what is this romantic
dance it's like a mating dance okay
[Music]
stay away
refocus oh is it gonna be free again
[Music]
laughs
nice oh did I do it there's only two
rounds this this can't be happening who
the [\h__\h] are you anyway I can't and no
not like this I'm so close
[Applause]
thank you for your services
that was fun
more like golf home run with golf that's
what I was thinking of but I don't know
what's a home run with golf called
that was an interesting fight because
not too difficult but it was kind of
different than the other fights so
no time bonus for me dong
in one open
a thousand wow oh lots of bonuses see
oh
new mask
heads what the [\h__\h] is it a dog oh it's
a Sheltie I think that's a Sheltie
I know my Shelties
[Music]
Welcome Back Sir oh you tonight you
don't look so happy to be honest though
I don't feel too good either something
in the air I don't know I just have this
really bad feeling like like something
terrible has happened tonight I haven't
felt this way since San Francisco I
don't like it not one [\h__\h] so how about
a drink it's not me
but the guy that we killed like who
exactly was that anyway
is that a drink or a poison
I equipped it can I go now
it's like I won't be absolutely we'll
see interesting
oh visitations
people Gonna Come to Me
free
Horsemen of the Apocalypse again
[Music]
ah you came back how are you feeling you
look ill maybe you should see a doctor
[Music]
I told you not to come back here I
stayed at my opinion of you doesn't
matter if you insist on returning here
then I should leave you you should leave
have you thought about what I asked you
last time I'm not here to give you any
answers
questions are all I have to offer a man
like you
if you if if you are what
if you're not feeling well maybe you
should rest her some things work out
best too and you don't try so hard no
matter who you are bearing too much
weight inevitably leads to the collapse
of everything
next time we meet we'll be the last I
can see it in your eyes
before you go I leave you with these
predictions someone you know is not who
you think he is
yeah obviously the guy that I keep on
meeting in every [\h__\h] place I go to
[Music]
something will soon be taken from you my
my friend my wife my my lady on July the
21st you will wake up in a bigger house
will I be kidnapped
that is all
we're really far from July 21st oh oh I
see I see she on my bed wait it's two
separate beds
but we were happy
[Music]
[Applause]
we want you to DJ tonight
[Music]
that's a very obvious prompt man don't
you want to keep it a bit more you know
subtle
dress cute yeah okay I'm gonna wear my
Tony mask pay attention to details
details for the for the extra little
secrets
me
this might be one of my favorites
look further attack
if there's many dogs maybe yeah but I'll
still rely on Tony
[Music]
oh my God this is so good
Mommy can we have two guns
oh
times like these I think uh favorite
night outfit would be nice don't you
think also kind of dark
that's on purpose
[Music]
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God this is my favorite I love
bangers
[Music]
there
come on
you're making it too easy
[Music]
easy it would take a gun with us which
one maybe this one
they can't have this Banner on the whole
time so I get an x-ray if I kill the DJ
flying or anything
[Laughter]
car what was that Carl that video carnal
[Music]
summer
I don't have to
first from empty rolly
I feel like that bgm is like seducing me
or entrancing me I don't know
oh God I I I feel like I'm I'm
I don't know I'm getting dizzy by the
awesomeness of the music
[Music]
I had a katana
that was so reckless so stupid
that's what I wanna
[Music]
[\h__\h] hell
bloody hell
[Music]
Jesus I'm now
um
[Music]
uh Gordon Ramsay
I I actually I fell into when you Rabbit
Hole guys
foreign
it's so easy it's so funny oh my God
like it makes me laugh out loud so many
times out of like I guess frustration
and and shame
[Music]
uh yeah yeah it's a really good show
it's so dramatic too but oh my God most
of these hotels are absolute [\h__\h] shows
right but
I haven't seen an episode yet and I've
watched like five I haven't seen a
single episode yet where it's not the
owner's fault and they're not an
absolute like nut case
I watched the one um the only hotel that
was actually decent besides the older
beings
it's [\h__\h] idiot
is the Ferrari one
the one that was pretty modern but the
thing is the hotel on its own was fine
but if you consider the price it was
absolutely not fine
[Music]
no I shouldn't focus on them
music too loud
okay
uh what was I saying oh yeah
like for the price
for the price that they charge
was 700 or so a night that was that was
uh unfitting
[Music]
not the not the quality it should be in
all right all right now we were talking
now we're talking
[Music]
but then the other one was uh one that I
saw was like with a woman as the owner
that was kind of like she looked like
she was really sweet but she looked like
a witch oh [\h__\h]
she looked like a witch and well she was
kind of a hoarder and everything was
cluttered the hotel the Inns was
sweet looking you know
[Music]
had a really Charming atmosphere in
theory
oh
[Music]
is there someone there I hope not okay
yeah yeah
and and oh thousands thousands
that was a ridiculous episode that was
really funny to me
because the whole time she was just like
smiling while Gordon was telling her
this [\h__\h] and this is [\h__\h] and they just
she and her little helper they just
could not be
convince that what they are doing is
not good
they were like I don't know having some
hallucinations or so who knows
yeah and then it was so funny because
Gordon Ramsay always says like it's
getting dark and darker Gordon Ramsay is
always like
let's try it when he sees something
can't leave
I need to kill a DJ now
when he says something that he doesn't
like huh
I can't kill this dude
you see something he doesn't like cable
uh
always be like Jesus so the two ladies
they were kind of like very religious so
she was like to Gordon she said after he
said Jesus she was like what's your
language you know you should watch your
tone
oh sorry I guess I'm distracted the red
arrow which red arrow
here ah okay
I misunderstood
um and I was like what does she mean
what did he say he didn't even swear but
I guess if you're very religious then
saying Jesus is kind of like you know
you misusing his name if if you use it
like that
I would I didn't get it at all at first
because like I was like what's what's
bad about that
when she was really angry
[Music]
oh oh dear
yeah some people get mad about it but I
don't ask somebody is saying to Gordon
Ramsay what's your language she was so
pissed
epilepsy warning I guess so
timing is of the essence
[Music]
I have an overall eye for right now I
get it now
I just I just have to walk up you know
when
[Music]
I'm really gaming today really
thank you Chad
yeah honestly I'm so happy I made a song
with like similar Vibes like I don't
know when you when you even really call
this
but it's not the same but it's got some
elements there
and
it's just such a bob like most people
in the whole life in general they go for
genres they're like poppy mostly right
same point yeah same point I really
enjoyed synthwave
too late with focusing on him he's so
far away
but yeah
in Fever nights you know it took it took
it a long time to reach
uh
[Music]
it's still alive though
to reach the one million things you got
thanks to everybody by the way for
listening but I still think it's a
really great song like just because it
took so long doesn't mean it's a bad
song at all
I think it's really good to have some
variety
um in my discography as well anyway
[Music]
you guys thank you
yeah it's niche Pond and it doesn't mean
it's bad and and especially for the
people who do like this uh
like category
especially for those it will be
I was still I was still uh marked on
that guy
and yeah I agree like I think the
algorithm
was like messing with it
[Music]
so I mean it has a little bit of a
handicap
oh this is difficult this uh hallway
because it's so hard to see
[Music]
no I want to just bait them and then
just shoot straight I guess
[Music]
you're paying you so much I'll take my
time to read your Super Chat properly
and when I get to it
okay how about you guys just come here
come here
[Music]
finally when someone came I ran out of
[\h__\h]
I ran out of ammunition ah [\h__\h]
oh my God
[Music]
the bathing just doesn't go the way I
want it to
Mad Club is one of the rougher Maps when
you're first getting into the game
[Music]
I'll get the hang of it eventually we'll
just have to
lucky
munition ammunition munition oh [\h__\h]
yeah there we go that's when I was
hoping for
[Music]
um
okay
easy I mean if it counts the time from
you know when I respawn then it should
have been pretty short I think
yes many retrys but besides that that
run was short
and yeah the music will be gone man
go I wanna keep it that's really good
[Music]
this one's nice too though I like this
chill one as well
like all this music
imagine playing this oh nice point
um when riding on the highway at 4 00 am
through the night really empty Highway
and you just oh
alone
in your car at 4am with this music and
then the music the sun goes up
oh
perfect yeah
see brilliant okay I don't care okay
I don't care I'm not part of your system
what
a group was that looks like a elephant
alien
oh and
[Music]
Carl it's not a llama what the [\h__\h] new
weapon the machete I thought macheteer
was a gun no I guess not
some Part of Me Maybe thought it was a
gun but I I really know
I know what it actually is
um hello why do you have a dead customer
on the ground are you did you call 9-1-1
hey man I gotta tell you something
important this oh this is not really
happening yeah
well you saw just now did not actually
happen when you look Hitler too hmm
you're one of us one of us
you don't look like you believe me then
allow me to demonstrate oh no
wait oh fun we're gonna fight you now
is this the guy
[Music]
what do you mean demonstrate should I
look away for a moment
[Music]
or should I go home I guess I'm going
home I guess it wasn't real indeed
I guess you didn't lie we're at the end
of May now
or what uh uh some ship
is
[Music]
you have one message
hi this is
[Music]
showing before an apartment downtown
today it's a Southwest one-to-one First
Street uh
to swing on by with your bat or
something when you have the time
[Music]
maybe she's on the down ground floor
down there
look like down you're my son she gone
wait did they kidnap wait did they did
say something about I think my wife
disappearing but was it this early
was it this early ninth chapter how many
chapters are there
Tony let me look at the other ones
uh survive one bullet and uh Carl wait
Carla's
oh look Carl very far down
ah start with drill
the drill
can I change this still because I don't
know what even a drill is I just want to
see it once is it like
what the [\h__\h] was that oh no wait it's a
trail
no
no Trail for like a wall what
that's stupid but I guess you can shoot
it and maybe get a one-hit kill
you don't miss
it
what
can I change this can I change
can I resume or restart restart
okay oh thank God I need Tony
tonight
[Music]
okay
what are we dealing with
so far
um pretty peaceful I would say
come here
by the bgm now really I mean it was nice
you know but now after hearing all that
disco music
just kind of lacking something now you
know what I mean I feel so empty
also where are the shooty weapons man
are they gonna not okay
nice
nice okay easy so far easy
also it's too quiet now isn't it extreme
favorite night on Loop
paper not paper not favor nine let's go
there
this one once turned right when I killed
this one I just walk in
okay no no he will
foreign
okay
okay very nice
[Music]
[\h__\h] I
I my brain was thinking one thing and my
I was doing something else
[Music]
in my mind I should have uh I wanted to
focus on the other one and then you know
throw the knife at him
hey yo hi
hi did I run in there oh man
[\h__\h]
don't even wait for the door anymore
okay
our second dog came fast
more dongle no
okay
now this part is really fast yeah the
bgm is slow huh oh I'll turn it up a bit
here for you guys for me it's fine but
there's a big difference but now it's
loud
and that maybe here around here it's as
loud as my voice though
do you want it like this
[\h__\h]
noise chill Beats at whatever time it is
right now for you guys
[Music]
oh man where's
new doggle
this is my chance
the knife
which way does the door open
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
don't go
[Music]
foreign
I won't even bother with this one here
[Music]
[\h__\h] it up
but I'm gaming
[Music]
ready for what
where'd he come from
you she'll keep her around but sometimes
they just change it all
darling like it yeah
nice nice oh there it is
[Music]
can I
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay now I think I'm doing pretty well
though I'm just gonna figure out uh all
the best ways to do this
all right
[Music]
you dog
snip snap
[Music]
ignore my Germans
aggressive incredibly aggressive
doing everything without guns so far
and but this room this room is kind of
look and wait if I do it from the side
doors now that I cleaned up everything I
can just shoot in nicely I think right
[Music]
very nice baby
thank you
um Angry German burp you know I think a
lot of people already know by now that
that angry German kid you remember that
that was an act
now like it was shared enough this
information but I watched like a whole
like interview of him like from very
recent times where he's now grown up and
damn it made me feel so bad because yeah
I already knew that he was bullied
but like in this interview he goes into
real real depth that he had like huge
issues also to find a job
and like I don't know it was really bad
like the extents of the influence that
this had on him where do I go
it was like really bad
like way worse than you could expect or
you would expect
[Music]
they did get together there though
um
and but I saw a lot of people who were
commenting like what am I doing
uh that if this were now that more
people would be understanding that you
know this is a joke or at least I don't
know
like he would be
the kids would say that
not the kids the the people in the
comments they were like oh you're you're
a legend now like I think you're really
cool and all that so
um
things would be different now but what
they really were they really a bit
different now if if this would happen
now I mean I guess what the amount of
crazy videos that are out there
right now
I guess this little video wouldn't be
so
so I don't know
[Music]
what's the word not not crystallizing
what's the word I'm looking for
[Music]
they didn't talk about police
did they call the cops and then I have
to be faster what or they get like re
what's the hell
talk while doing this
[Music]
driving wouldn't happen but it wouldn't
go viral no that's not the word I mean
but yeah basically yeah I mean it could
go viral but it's just not so impressive
or not impressive either
[Music]
it wasn't too many true story it has so
important but but you know
[Music]
oh
the other one shot for the door and for
the wall or something
[Music]
foreign
but then get a shot on both of them
Maybe
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
yeah I guess look at me look at me look
at me now
if I do it quietly will the police maybe
not come
but don't shoot too loud you know
they're coming
oh sheesh
how much time do I have
stressful
[Music]
damn it
yeah
no need to rush just pretend it's the
bgm don't worry about it
it's not that bad
[\h__\h] helps
sorry ah
yeah there we go hey even quietly
rely on takanashikiwa to take care of
all you need
all right
[Music]
okay
are you
oh
sweeps that room
[Music]
beautiful only one round
oh it's so scary
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] couldn't see him
there's a door
beautiful beautiful yeah yeah it's nice
when we can clear that room out
the bleed
and we don't have to worry about a thing
I will take that one
I mean I see that door but
[Music]
I guess they just came from the other
room
what's going on I feel like I'm on a
pilot am I on
clear
[Music]
she has to claim what he what happened
what happened I have to run after that
huh what I was like bamboozled
that was Bamboozled that gun just went
through
[Music]
oh
can I not kill the cops oh
then I'll just run after it says chapter
clear
[Music]
I'm like really coordinated now am I not
[\h__\h] okay I did that better before
Ryan
foreign
[Music]
I'm just training the air is my biggest
enemy because
there
huh
air you know the air can kill me it's
just by just disappearing
which okay then I actually shouldn't
kill the egg or should I
you shouldn't be punching the air should
be respecting the air
[Music]
come here
everybody you don't want the air to
sleep you
[Music]
talking now
sorry
okay here we go
oh get that [\h__\h] kill or else
yeah
love the air
[Music]
foreign
you better not get me in trouble
later on
[Music]
that shocked me shook me to my core
I fall down
that that corner that area would still
be safe I was wrong
everyone
[Music]
oh come on
gotta do what you gotta do
[Music]
what's up
too funny too funny
[Music]
now I got him
there we go no double though sad sad sad
I wanted to catch the Dogo just testing
I promise
I'm not gonna do anything about that
because I'm scared
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
question mark
I don't want to make use of that the
wall pack
[Music]
play fair and square
oh I'm dead
cheering you on from work thank you
how's work going
I'm also at work right now what a
coincidence
maybe we're at the same work
because I mean how else could it be
[Music]
I don't believe it
was just six rounds okay
[Music]
hey are you one of the ones I'm taking
care of
I'm [\h__\h] hell
what just happened did I like like punch
his head off and that worked as a
projectile for the others or what
people here too that's nice and you not
you
why don't they just drop it when it's at
zero that would be helpful
[Music]
drop it
thank you
I was fast enough to throw it now yeah I
know I can throw it but the brain kiwawa
brains
need time this is a stressful situation
that needs critical
[Music]
faith
this is so fast
[Music]
faces faster than guns
what in what what let me read the whole
thing
[Music]
bang bang they shot me down bang bang I
hit the ground the bang bang something
something
my baby shot me down I love that song
cause it's another Great Gatsby gets
beat
[Music]
pretty difficult at this point
laughs
the first part I got that down also Kill
Bill oh really the same song
big panic
[Music]
all right that shattered the glass too
Panic punch
best part
would you also like a serving of my
Panic punch you get one and you get one
everybody gets one yeah
[Music]
that's crazy
not what
come on come on how many times we're
gonna do this
[Music]
one of those days
what happened to that point it's always
so smooth but now
oh dog lover no I'm a cat lover
the achievement is sarcastic
it's so sad so sad where I need one of
the I want one of the bigger guns
oh well it will do it will have to do
[Music]
uh oh that's yourself now
at least I start from here holy [\h__\h]
what can I kill them or not where do I
even go
can I
let me test it
I can't focus on them so I'm guessing
not I I can't like Mark them
checkpoint ghetto
[Music]
[Applause]
I can send them oh the doors don't work
so what
oh that was so funny
[Music]
I was man police I'm literally walking
next to you how can you not see me open
your eyes you're too focused on
something else what is it C plus oh
Improvement
and a new mask that means that means
you look different is that a horse too
new weapons
come on
wow me it's a camel
oh you're gone
I don't like strangers around here
ain't that right Parker
you want the punch
you want the punch of my fist
my friend is dead no he gave me all the
free stuff
I will like survive without the free
beats and the free VHS and everything
man
[Music]
buddy I thought he might backstab me but
it wasn't him apparently
they got them they got
[Music]
it I'm going to cry for five days
straight for his for his sake
[Music]
what do you want
Could you hurry up we're closing soon
you look very sauce do you want to
explain that no no no no no no I I I
ain't got any issues
I didn't want pizza after all I'm gonna
go for some sushi
June 3rd
[Music]
it was something
what but she's still gone
she's gone for real and where's the
explanation am I not gonna get like
closure on that
[Music]
am I We're not gonna like question it
like maybe they took her like kidnapping
style and someone I want to save her
did you like to go on sometimes
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
I need to trust her you can't have a
relationship without trust right
hmm
[Music]
oh there this is Thomas from the
downtown relaxation or Anita to fill in
at the reception for the Lord the number
of police
wear something fitting and discreet
[Music]
I am tell to teach the sick one a lesson
or a mothers
hot what hot and heavy
I want to look at the new one but what
which one why did I did is this one that
I was on the ground like the like the
car one and I just didn't pick it up
like why did I not get this on
it's just bothering me
to wipe on both extra ammo no
Tony freaking hate this level okay it's
a secret mask I can't never get it now
can I can you go back on levels
hello
you don't commit to your crimes do you
oh sick that was sickening
yo can we do that again
just shoot me without getting me
actually okay
that's what I wanted oh but they left
um
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
instead of shooting me through there
they choose to walk around wow that's
lame that was so epic the first time I
did that [\h__\h]
I'm dead
thank you forever
you can run past them yeah that's what
I'm gonna do now you're gonna have fun
in this level really yeah
[Music]
permanence up quite impressive I must
say that Ai No not always that's more
[Music]
we all died
how did that happen
like a [\h__\h]
crazy person
that's what I am
[Music]
yeah
holy [\h__\h] I sound insane don't I
[Music]
I saw this
oh God
calm the [\h__\h] down
[Music]
you do it's part of the charms
oh
they do not even try to shoot me for the
walls anymore
[Music]
what is this thing anyway
nice decoration
[Music]
appreciating art you know
you don't appreciate the art
appreciation
[Music]
that is very concerning I must teach you
a lesson I am Picasso kfp Castle after
all okay
can you shoot knives through windows
till I'm guessing though
[Music]
just split all across the floor how
slippery is it
[Music]
he came back to life like Jesus Jesus
foreign
[Music]
it doesn't say stage clear did it there
they are
uh-huh
[Music]
my mom must be very concerned of me my
mental health right now I'm okay Mommy I
think my my stomach is like
feeling funky now from all
[Music]
I was like ah Claire I cleaned up so
much how can it like you know
[Music]
she likes Trevor I'm sure she
understands
oh yeah right true
I hate Trevor but my mom likes Trevor
really makes me question her
okay okay okay I need to like what the
[\h__\h]
my cats are not gonna wanna sleep in the
same bed with me anymore
[Music]
my monkey state
foreign
[Music]
I guess I should just start blasting or
should I go for this room maybe this
room
[Music]
more fruit let me take a fruit candy
holy [\h__\h]
I'm losing time though so I want to
restart
that that screams that scream just now
came from a different place
dangerous from my fruit
[Music]
is that it
you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
why is this room so bright oh [\h__\h]
what
what's going on there
wait if I go in this room I can oh shoot
them in one line
if I don't get Disturbed
the dogs movement man
oh
[Music]
the real tournament
oh man this is your first FPS I even
Unreal Tournament oh
[Music]
I don't like what kind of person this is
turning me into
oh God the door's open I don't like that
either
[Music]
okay this is pretty good
you up
bad bad bad bad
[Music]
why did I hesitate I don't know I didn't
feel like I was hesitating I felt like I
was
[Music]
foreign
like I don't know a [\h__\h] Penta kill
not
[Music]
damn she's good
all right gotta go in with your best
confidence I'm trying yeah
I think I'm pretty confident maybe not
this gun I want this one
but no I can't get it
[Music]
oh maybe this one is good for that like
one line shot this one
I don't know let me try
it will be Appleton if they run after me
I'll panic and I have no shots them
I can't
oh man
just too good
someone's there okay
is that the last one no not quite almost
almost
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I'm getting like real good at
this
[Applause]
[Music]
bug
these bathtubs look like beds
on it
here
[Music]
oh wait one minute going home
I thought there was more I like Lewis
practice
[Music]
what
is it like what what floor why are we
passing a dead floor then
okay good
but it's good that I brought this weapon
[Music]
nice
four times combo
[\h__\h] hell what I'm incapable of
shooting
do you like hurting other people I like
it right now yeah it's fun right now in
this game very very
only fun disturbingly fun
I got him
I got him yep yep very beautiful I mean
this is this is the way to do it I would
say
what's that
[Music]
just gotta keep on baiting them all
right but yeah cause like there's so
many uh Windows that's quite dangerous
but we baited as much as we could
[Music]
stay open foreign
us
where'd he go
where'd You Go why'd you run away
you dropped me off my octo kill
I will never forgive
I never forget
are you also you also want a piece of
this cake
[Music]
another one
oh [\h__\h] where did he shoot he could have
gotten me
ah there was this like perfect room
service in this hotel they're all coming
to my room
I appreciate that
I appreciate that wow thank you all the
patrolling guys are coming to me
are we done now with Patrols
[Music]
let's talk for real for real
oh damn that angle
should be able to see me come here
no
[Music]
is this [\h__\h] it up here after doing
all the groundwork is unfortunate if
that happens
[Music]
well Ollie plays FPS games right she
should say that that should be her
catchphrase when she plays FPS games I
would be sad if it wouldn't
[Music]
excuse me absolute [\h__\h] Gremlin mode
to get combos no oh maybe in the
fighting game now
did we are we done here now nice too
nice too
boy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
is actually he was still alive thank you
for not getting up there early
[Music]
he's a long sleeper
oh
god
oh [\h__\h] out
thank you
oh new gun
ah the the guy was trying to get up but
the door kept on hitting him because I
was also standing on it Oh I thought
like I was dead
I could have been very well dead
um
take a quieter one
a big guy
look at me
who's that
said oh no that's pretty good I handled
that situation very well I would say I
just want a better weapon
[Music]
stop pulling the door
no
ruined my perfect front
foreign
[Music]
probably hear me again
okay okay
we safe we safe we did it
[Music]
um I actually
um
[Music]
no you didn't hear me
I wouldn't have had enough
what or those shots
oh he's alive
sometime man the dark doors opens ran
away man got no time
foreign
[Music]
got it
I got it we got it
[Music]
the [\h__\h] finishing strawberry on top
of my cake man
you can hear my screams from the usual
room are you enjoying it
it's too happy always
[Music]
yo he's dead okay the other guy is still
there
[Music]
I don't don't want to mess it up now
there's way too many weapons on the
ground oh my God
[Music]
is this a machine gun
shotgun better predict guys yeah it's
okay we know that bathtub looks nice but
it's kind of weirdly placed is it even
the bathtub
come on
I didn't want to swing that crowbar I
just wanted to give punches but when I
threw away the other weapon and just
accidentally picked up the whatever was
closest that's kind of annoying when
like there's this big mess around you
all those weapons
which way do I go
[Music]
dude
I survived stad man
better to go here first
[Music]
Mommy
the Mist hurts real bad it was going so
well
just enough that was the last shot man I
was on zero
praying and praying really is that what
you say in a situation like this
[Music]
nicer
spray and pray
ing bullets and praying to hit
no I I I that sounds like as if I'm
doing it with absolutely no system
behind it
no I know I'm like planning this out for
everything very very properly
foreign
trust me bro
okay only the three left
um
but cool
still go very wrong
maybe baked Knife Guy
if I base no
get it from there if I bathe him I want
to punch him though
hello but
um
okay
can I if I stand there at the very
corner of the door
[Music]
[Applause]
this is so fun
this is so fun where do I go
chapter clear
I'll see myself out
not that there's a choice
I don't really care
it's okay I only need the Tony mask but
that's sad man
[\h__\h] mask was it a good one
nothing beats the Tony mask guys
[Music]
the best mask
damn it I didn't see it they're hard to
see somehow
plus
new mask anyway oh Willem
Willem these
scorpion finally something interesting
and yeah monkey monkey hello
um
[Music]
is the other one on a break
uh or he completely out today huh not
here today
I recognize you you look very familiar
never meant before
why did they even come here like I know
it's the same dude always working at
different places
coming here did I expect that he would
be alive or
checking who's working here now or
I'll find out
no free stuff no there's this new dude
that works here doesn't give me any free
stuff
[Music]
me
get out of your face
[Music]
why are you in my home but my lady is
back
why does he look so bloody
[Applause]
they are maybe maybe they're not for me
though maybe he took over my lady
[\h__\h]
can we talk
[Music]
or can I read your mind lady
foreign is that really how you actresses
in America stop clicking
[Music]
is that really how your addresses go as
America does it's always the same like a
number in the Southeast or Northeast and
all that
[Music]
I mean it's not so bad
new season of The Office
[Music]
pretty much
I mean that's still as as long as it's
properly written on the buildings that's
still easy I've noticed in Japan without
like Google Maps on my phone I would
never be able to find if I'm at the
right building
because the addresses are most of the
time I feel like they're not really on
the building
and like homes of families or so they
will have the last name
of them placed on like the fence or
whatever
yeah but how do you find anything I
don't know how I don't know how the post
office guys do it maybe they the
delivery guys and all that I mean I
guess they all just use like their own I
think the deliberate people use GPS and
then the post people they just know what
they're doing maybe and also use GPS and
stuff
yeah they're based on on the blocks and
all that and they just do it differently
but I I mean surely it works so
if it works it works but I don't get it
sounds or seems holy [\h__\h]
I don't know really um
[Music]
close combat I'm good with that
didn't kill one of them
[Music]
I'm gonna try
quiet it's really quiet
wait what what what was it called again
[Music]
can you stop crawling like a baby
silence the Scorpions
[Music]
but it doesn't seem to one shot that
more am I stupid oh my God we're good
okay
oh it's so quiet
[Music]
yeah I'll just take this up although do
they maybe have a full one
I gotta take this one
yay
[Music]
oh he's also got one
fine with me
if it works it works
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
oh is it just me being bad right now
[Music]
the one shot little shot can be tough
if it hits it hits nicely it was
[Music]
it
for that one I'll have to walk quite a
bit around the corner but it should be
okay
[Music]
ah
okay wait
finally I can do my work
properly in peace
that being disturbed all the time
push it oh [\h__\h] that didn't work that's
okay
hey
hey Falcon Punch
okay now this guy because he'll he can
see me as I walk by but he should be the
last one I think who could mess
everything up
[Music]
Mommy
um
it should be so easy
[Music]
there you go
I feel like I mostly first tried it
because like this later Clark was first
try in the beginning I tried a few times
okay
does anyone have something some more of
my favorite weapon though okay I'll go
with this one
unless oh wait he has it is that my door
yeah that's my old one okay I'll take
this one
[Music]
this took me way more tries the first
time
good
Tuesday
in social media
elevator though
I saw you know like the ID Cafe it looks
really nice
[Music]
did you guys seen some of it
they have like really yummy fancy
looking foods like Elena's pasta has
like truffle and gold on it holy [\h__\h]
can it get any fancier than that
and they got some nice looking merch I
really like the outfits they have for it
for those like merchandise stuff in
particular
[Music]
really cute
what what the window
[Music]
God damn it
it's too funny too [\h__\h] funny
I was just running around like a
headless chicken
noise
[Music]
laughs
many beautiful beautiful beautiful
Chihuahua is a pro at this game now like
legit
it's all the printers man
[Music]
[Applause]
you wanna get up there we go
[Music]
stop wasting my shots
you should have us problems into play
this game
yeah I guess oh she would have some
crazy left too I think she would go
crazy but would she like this kind of
game I actually don't know I mean at
this point I feel like if I like it who
wouldn't like it
like this is not it's not unlikable
no yeah it's not unlikable
wait
[\h__\h] help
[Music]
oh
he's got his eyes on me now oh he'll get
the first shot
foreign
here's the actual one I want to get but
the angle I can't get it right I'm
scared oh I got him though easy clap
I use your clap no no we're talking
let me get a new weapon from this dude
hey hey hey
the last two should I take them with my
fist oh [\h__\h] hi
[Music]
I think I found my calling and my
calling is this game
yeah yeah
what that's not what I'm not supposed to
like what what
nowadays these jobs they just
it's not the same
[Music]
what this man is on fire
is that me
ant okay
how many oh
transformation
oh no I can't
hmm
we're done
I give up you win oh I was actually kind
of out of munition and like scrambling
so you could have gotten me there to be
honest
it's so hard though
um
literal Friendly Fire did he
I give up you win okay bye
why do we keep on fighting like this now
and also ah I guess I got a kiss oh
ah I'm standing here on fire
okay he did it for me I didn't have to
lift a finger what points do I get for
this what what will I get
no time bonus man 45 miles
C plus again seems like I can't get over
C plus probably because of the time
bonus not being there but
doing really well
what does he do or is this a hammer come
on really why are you giving me these
lame ass weapons
yo what did you do to my friend what did
you do where's his body I only see like
these [\h__\h]
[Music]
scary he talks to me while he's [\h__\h]
dead
[Music]
again way more points using melee guns
don't get oh really
I guess I make it too easy
I use my face a lot
connections
to go up my own apartment
[Music]
my wifey is dead
hey you shitty little rat
[Music]
wait this is Casper trying to get me
back right
aspect don't be jealous I if I knew you
you were around I would have always you
know
ditched my new wife for you for your
Casper trust me
I got nothing oh okay that was that
scripted okay uh
[Music]
it's my body
looks like it's only you and me left now
I'm sure you know by now that this won't
end well soon you will be all alone but
that's okay Before We Say Goodbye I'll
let you it's not a secret what you do
what do you do from here on won't serve
any purpose
[Music]
[\h__\h]
for you to leave there's a warm bed
across the call from here
and you could use some rest for a while
you mean my own bed
[Music]
waiting
stop it
[Music]
oh this is the freaking me out
foreign
trauma yeah I think I'm very traumatized
tip you're all alone I was always alone
I feel like
even when I had the lady
uh Hey Duck where's the best going to
wake up
I don't know he's been in a coma for
weeks now look at those crazy [\h__\h]
eyes oh I want a different doctor
but he's going to wake up right this guy
is a prime suspect on in a major case
look my guess is
[Music]
might be a while huh he's still not even
fully healed from the surgery
is there nothing you could do we need
this guy you people weren't able to save
his girlfriend I mean we've got the what
purp who shot him in the locker put that
[\h__\h] ain't saying [\h__\h]
and what makes you think this guy works
he has my eyes
I mean I guess he does
yeah
I gotta go this way
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that
over there
what the [\h__\h] are those things outside
oh scary freaking
my eyes gargoyles
and where do you think you're gonna
break I guess we better put restraining
on you
[Music]
gotta be unnoticed but like
maybe when he looks at the newspaper
foreign
[Music]
oh no I'm good now oh oh
wait that's it's like for a while
I like the sneaky Mission
what if I walk behind him will that work
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
and then
okay okay safe room safe room where do I
go though up left or up right oh wait
it's not an elevator
oh wait oh God oh God secret pixel there
here ah
[Music]
nicer
gosh [\h__\h] dizzy freaky
I'm [\h__\h] ah stop
[Music]
it's not a nice experience
well my my view feels like it's going
much further now where am I supposed to
go here
where am I oh
[\h__\h] shaky
you got shot in the head it's not a nice
experience it really isn't
[\h__\h] the doctors man can't trust no one
I [\h__\h] trash can can't even trust a
[\h__\h] trash can
so far first trying everything
[Music]
get back to the usual room ah get back
to the usual one
[Music]
thank you
foreign
because then I can follow them walking
you know
[Music]
I saw me I'm a plant sir I'm just a
plant
aren't we all
okay
monitor the camera rooms
[Music]
you wish they had more doctors though
don't they have like a lot of doctors I
mean in Scrubs there's like a [\h__\h] tones
I'll stay here I'll wait here for a
moment yeah good idea I'm gonna follow
the next one
and now yeah
[Music]
cameraman is drunk very drunk yes
need a straight edge camera man please
[Music]
my window I knew it was there
what I do at that corner
should I walk into the room isn't that
too
Reckless
wait
which room and which room
should I hug the other side
that's exactly what I need right now
[Music]
I hide here does he see me for the door
no okay oh beautiful beautiful
[Music]
the hospital
you guys are not helping me you guys are
only helping me to then not help me just
trying to get me healthy to then put me
in prison forever and ever
let me die if anything
oh I'm back home
hopefully feeling better now
yeah I think so
no they [\h__\h]
up completely yeah
was that me
you are
put all my clothes my normal clothes all
right I'm gonna take revenge now huh
are we in the end game
well that was my girlfriend oh damn
maybe we were never really dating maybe
she was just like I don't know
mental health companions
13th chapter as salt you can throw away
but I know that
[Music]
one that I didn't look at yet
uh what
rip and steal
what does that mean why have gunshots
no but I'm like at this point I'm also
so used to Tony
tip you can move your character that if
my if my fists wouldn't one shot people
I would be so lost
that is useful in this level Peter
we can try that
I'll go over Tony verse if I have big
problems which I don't think I will
oh wait I can't
shoot these guys
[Music]
what can I now
well they can certainly shoot me
I can
[Music]
interesting
this music is also really nice
oh I got the the silence weapon
nice do they all have that one yeah
[Music]
anymore how many more
what do you want
wait what what I have is not wait what
is that what the thing oh it's one of
those police bats thing is I thought
I thought I had a silent weapon but not
that makes more sense
[Music]
well yeah I should just gather everybody
here and I'll get a nice combo as well
don't you think
[Music]
so good
thank you
okay but I want you guys to come here
[Applause]
the door does help yeah
[Music]
is there Windows oh yeah
I should have seen that one coming
[Music]
um
bottom
[Music]
okay there's someone down here too that
can see me all right
[Music]
the soundtrack
that's my meal one of my top three
favorites
[Music]
oh what
ah a mountain of bodies I can't even
see dead
I can't see [\h__\h] anymore like what
yes
[Music]
really no no problem to just stay away
from everybody
mostly here
[Music]
why is the police bat so powerful it
doesn't have a knife right
implemented in it
[Music]
try
sitting on the other wall so the door
doesn't block the shots
[Music]
thank you
action
it's good anywhere right if we stay in
this level for a long time because it's
just a beautiful soundtrack
what else could you ask for
[Music]
um
I love that sound what do you call it
it's a it's a it is from um
I can't words
uh
[Music]
what do you how do you work uh
um drum it's a drum but like an old kind
of I don't know what they used in these
Retro Music things but their drum sounds
different
[Music]
they sound so retro
oh
[Music]
that's one thing I really enjoyed about
um
Wonder Girls when they had this what the
[\h__\h] and they had this retro phase
[Music]
yeah
it's a K-Pop group but they had like a
whole a whole album that was like
focused on retro
that's what I want I just wanna punch
down and then paint them with some spots
yeah it's really messy though when I
throw weapons away
when I picked them up most of the time
[Music]
it really is like absolutely amazing big
recommends
I'm staying with my strategy for now
though I like it like I mean look at
this place once I step out they always
get me anyway so better to bait I would
say
anyone seeing me oh yeah
[Music]
it's the
biggest assist man
I just have to get a good run that's all
we need
I'm chilling now I don't know how far we
are in the game how far am i guys
feels like I'm pretty far in
[Music]
it is right not chapters oh nice nice
then we'll finish it today
I cooked yesterday I didn't upload a
picture because my Twitter was vlogging
again but
[Music]
sometimes sometimes it doesn't sometimes
the app just crashes on me when I try to
tweet on my phone
no but I was trying to hello
[Music]
what was I saying
I was trying to show you guys what I
made I made some
you called it a ravioli I think they
have ham inside
with like a basil sauce basil cream
sauce that turned out really good
with some fresh chopped basil from my
plant that has survived surprisingly
long
oh that's bad that's bad e
I've had this it hasn't planned for like
three months or so now I'm like
genuinely fascinated this is the first
time I ever kept a bad plant alive for
this long like usually I always failed
and it's not even that difficult now I
figured
[Music]
out now you
yay it's like one of those that you get
from the supermarket I don't know if you
guys can get the same kind of stuff uh
over there in your supermarkets
but you know the ones that come in this
plastic cup that you're supposed to
maybe plant somewhere but what I did
basically I just put it on um
on a plate
[Music]
are they dead
I think so yeah put it on a plate and
just give it a little bit of water from
the ground like I put the water on the
place I finally realized that I think
many people know how to choose but I
just realized it
[Music]
okay okay come on it's so close just
gotta paint a couple more like all the
reactions
[Music]
okay this one
please
[Music]
interesting but if it works out like
once a day just a tiny bit of water like
not even a full glass but like like half
depends on your on how big your glasses
I guess
I'll just do someone down there
I think there isn't oh I can shoot for
the glass
[Applause]
[Music]
stage clear
where do I go do I just leave wait wait
a second I need a weapon which one
should I please
[Music]
gotta believe on the door strands
and how do I get there here
it's the TV okay
oh maybe I should have taken a quiet
weapon
oh wow
oh he looks strong okay he's got a taser
but does he is he as strong as the other
big guys
can I at least kill him quickly
yeah can I
he takes them home but at least he stops
moving
[Music]
um
yeah we got him oh
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't think I should go in there
afterwards
[Music]
y'all yes my shortcut is very loud maybe
once I'm in the other room I should just
throw it away
we'll figure it out I chose the wrong
weapons
should have gone with a quiet one
trash the first guy with this I'll try
if he would kindly make his way over
here
[Music]
oh wait can I once the elevator is open
I probably can't bring it with me
I don't know you so far now
hello hello
[Music]
okay
absolutely chaotic absolutely chaotic
man what do I even do
[Music]
also guys after a clip I realized what
you guys were doing with me you baited
me into saying Master
you know
what the [\h__\h]
man
I was like you guys were all laughing
and I was like yeah why are you laughing
and then I even said it again you guys
are laughing more and I thought I fought
because everyone was laughing oh oh it
must be some kind of meme or something
and I guess it kind of was more or less
but I I didn't think
you were gonna do something so mean to
me
[Music]
I thought you did it on purpose no I
really didn't and it took me so long to
understand I thought I was just really
the master
of painting you know I was pretty happy
about my bathing skills
you little shits I didn't hear it
[Music]
I mean you guys are mean
well I can go back into the elevator
[Music]
come on can I run it I don't want to get
too close to him
[Music]
oh what I think the second one
it's not coming okay he didn't pay
attention this time
[Music]
if I throw this one is it like a knife
kill
[Music]
no
okay those doors are like the yeah the
airport ones that are basically open
okay I get it
I get it now so they see me through it
and you can't do the funny door tricks
anymore either huh
can you guys come over here I'm trying
to do something
[Music]
[Applause]
interesting one oh wow the other one is
not here
[Music]
you ready I'm ready
the other one was ready too okay
[Music]
[Applause]
messing me up right now
[Music]
[\h__\h]
this was tough it really is holy [\h__\h]
one of my favorite games we've played so
far again really yeah sorry guys I'm not
looking much as a chat though
um because I'm like really immersive now
but you guys you're with I feel you guys
is like support you
[Music]
now I just want to restart like what the
hell don't ruin my plan
[Music]
I guess I started flashing okay
so close at that point it's like what
the [\h__\h] I don't know what's happening
anymore
[Music]
oh I'm so tense I'm so tense like the
German river tense I think
I think there's a tense tens tens ten
cents
[Music]
open
oh that's in London oh but it sounds so
German
it sounds so German but yeah that's like
I recently heard uh the name somewhere
consumed some media I suppose
before that came up
[Music]
reflexes baby reflexes what
uh actually
what do you not say it like that in
English because I will I will I will let
you know I will have you know
I think it's the legit way of saying it
[Music]
not
hey
hello
[Music]
no wait wait hey
okay
[Music]
foreign
hi
it's tough [\h__\h] tough but once I get
through this part I think it's not so
difficult anymore after especially if I
can bait a good amount of them hello
[Music]
[\h__\h] I
um I should wait
for this one in that room
to be like up here
then he won't really hear me
thing where I go this no it's basically
the same right yeah no it isn't
there's no close by
a big guy there maybe I'll go this way
I know the shotguns are more effective
but then the reason I'm not using them
right now even though I prefer big lock
guns is because I don't want to bake
them anymore
maybe I will though in that case if
there's no one close by like no danger
[Music]
it might be worth it
all right let me attempt murder
[Music]
I will attempt murder again
she cooked there's no difference
[Music]
now he's dead
[\h__\h] triggering but I'm still okay
I'm so good
okay okay
[Music]
I can do it thank you for believing in
me I think I can do it too has he got
The Quiet One now
what did I just imagine
[Music]
is this a quiet one no
I forgot this boss thank you thank you
do I really got this
maybe like this oh yeah
yeah oh is someone someone
[Music]
I was so happy I was like basically
skip jumping what do you call it
scum blocking
um jump skipping
um
no
skipping skipping I guess it's just
skipping yeah happily skipping
and thus she didn't skip happily ever
after
[Music]
da da
ha
I'm ready I'm ready bring it on baby
bring it to [\h__\h] on
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
music like back in the days
it's too popular
[Music]
Who You Are
popular
[Music]
sorry guys this is gonna take a while
man
as you can see but it's not a skill
issue it's not a skill issue
[Music]
ah I'm going to keep that there and then
I want this one there too close by
did they hear me yeah
more no okay we stopped it I think we
stopped it oh never mind
[Music]
stopped please
special that was fine
hold my heart
[Music]
okay they got like really good ears man
they got way better ears than
the other usual enemies is policemen
guys they they probably
did one of those like ear wax things
ceremonies
where you pour hot wax in your ears and
I found that so fascinating
[Music]
don't waste
and that's what I thought okay okay
pretty good I think we can like ah wait
when I walk through that door it's gonna
alert them I feel like it would be
easier to do it from above but
might want to do it from here all right
let's have this gun ready let's throw
this one away
out of sight out of mind I want usable
ones please
only preparation okay it's only these
two right not free okay I mean don't
mess it up should I stay inside in this
room or did I do I go in their room
I think I'll stay in my room
[Music]
oh oh
thank you for making it easy on me yeah
[Music]
see once you're past that stage it goes
smoothly and nicely all is good all is
well
[Applause]
seems like there's something big going
on here
[Music]
but that was one of the free stages
right let's go we're almost done
oh I hope I don't regret the weapon
choice that I brought with me do I have
enough munition
okay boys the best it will be here any
second now how do you know I didn't even
I didn't even alert any of the doors
security doors
oh wait could you walk through those
undetected if you don't carry a weapon
with you because basically they're metal
detectors right
although there are three chapters
there's a box somebody's in three stages
I was happy about it
[Music]
do it all today
oh cameras uh I saw them I didn't think
they were functional it's not going to
show you what we're made of remember you
were training and playing safe follow
protocol
wow it's frozen to call and we'll all
make it out alive will you William
[Music]
strikes strikes again
can you not give me a heart attack
please
I thank you
she didn't even need a weapon here in
the beginning though
some
brilliant just shook me out of nowhere
and absolutely terrible
[Music]
no you say oh look at him oh you can
shoot me for there I can too right
first take care of the other ones
[Music]
I just shoot straight for the door
straight for the door
all right
[Music]
on the door
foreign
[Music]
ERS there but hopefully no more windows
I'm not getting hungry
but maybe that's good when you're hungry
you hangry you angry right
I want to be careful I don't want to
suddenly get shot man
but
I'll Bonk the other one
[Music]
what's this Keys oh I needed those it
seems
[Music]
what now what are your keys for like
over there oh yeah there's like a
prisoner so I think
all right then this one maybe is it safe
to go
they got a lot of Silence
[Music]
it's okay I can redo all this okay it's
okay it's okay
[Music]
what is this the guy who shot me really
oh he's also getting Justice huh and the
keys are for here though right so I
gotta walk around and I'll come I'll
come back
[Music]
thank you
yeah yeah okay I learned this before
first take care of the ones who are able
to disturb me in my genius master plan
and it's already like bathing in success
man
[Music]
world of war crimes
he's bleeding there we go okay
friend
yep that's what I thought I can't focus
on that one
[Music]
no wasting my munition I am so
economically
weak am I not
I'm awake
[Music]
but thank you but I'm also economic okay
we got
[Music]
easy easy steady and nice
we got the keys wait
okay I can carry the keys and the weapon
right
oh this one this one's also pretty empty
this room that can I
we did this before right I can walk over
there right without being shot can I
no window no window
no no one alive should be okay
right
why did I die last time
well someone's coming
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I'm good I'm good I'm good
wow wow
I knew something was off
do I have to Kill All Enemies I think so
yeah
[Music]
let's see quiet step so you won't even
hear me
um I wonder this one well he got me in
trouble does he need like several kills
because he ruined all of this
look like a different gun
mask up top
[Music]
so last one
we're here to talk to him I'm sorry
species
I trust you guys
hello
you gotta be shooting me why are you
look man I'm sorry about you girl it
wasn't anything personal
I believe that but still that doesn't
excuse your actions but my actions are
also not to be excused I guess I know
you made it all the way here but I think
you're in for a disappointment should I
have carried a weapon
I don't really have any answers for you
don't kill me please
what do I leave now
or did I kill him
what
[Music]
okay
damn that hurts
you know I think we might not be that
different you and I possibly have you
also been getting those weird phone
calls yeah remember I guess we're at the
same job
I wish I had something to tell you but I
don't the police seem to know more about
this mess than I do they probably have a
fine on the case around here so I file
oh I'd ask you to spare my life but it's
too late for that it looks like you've
made a rewind
oh wait can I still spare his life
or
should I let's just do it
I'm so nice please strangling him oh
that's so like oh
files where are the files
show me the files
I shot the fires [\h__\h] the fires
the car I don't trust this I'll be
greeted by people again won't die when I
don't see the musician is better before
I got 60k points that was pretty slow
though it was pretty bad
it was like extra careful what's what's
gonna happen now last time was a car
what's it this time a helicopter just or
or a plane just dropping
[Laughter]
oh nostalgic all right I'm leaving we
have nothing this time not anymore knock
off though
yeah I'm paranoid now this is weird
they're leaving me they're letting me
leave so normally now
ah damn
now time bonus obviously zero
wow 75k
that's [\h__\h] good
[Music]
what this [\h__\h] you wanna stay away from
whoa
cute and Rita I'm so hungry man new
weapon
yeah break definitely if you throw it
will be a killing weapon I think
be for badass [\h__\h]
that's mean as me
[Music]
[Applause]
what uzi machine gun I'll hold another
new gun
all right sorry again
[Music]
seems like I'm trying to figure
something out here
[Music]
suspect claims will have been
threatened into
instructed to kill by messages on there
Bunkhouse priced to a club now on the
South 86th Street there we go
ties to underground Russian mafia
Network
multiple accounts of illegal activity
reported
insufficient evidence for a warrant
really
sufficient or are you all just [\h__\h]
chicken scared to do something
do I have to do it again man you better
thank me afterwards
[Music]
I don't need a warrant exactly finish
off
let me check the other ones
longer combo window oh
and the other one
here let's start with
cool but yeah I'll be throwing it away
quickly I don't even know how much
munition I need to test out that weapon
I'm going for Tony my bestie
hello hello
what the [\h__\h] is this place
[Music]
free channels
guys I'm here
[Music]
do I want to bake them
what is that car
is that like one of those monster trucks
my my dad used to bring me to like
monster truck like simulation Jersey
things
here on Golden ground
[Music]
oh hey I was just waiting I guess I
guess long range
[Music]
helpful
now I see it thank you
[Music]
careful careful
I looked the wrong way [\h__\h] no no I
remember the window I'm not paying
attention
thank you
well maybe I should restart with the
Lucy I want to try maybe
this way I feel like I could do it too
but let's try it
see
what
[Music]
the way he points
it was pretty rounds
[Music]
not gonna waste my shot though
she is
a fish a fish
[Music]
you need to get used to this this also
again has like a really small hitbox
[Music]
ah right my punches don't kill anymore
what's going on
[Music]
[Applause]
it takes up so many shots
wait if I get a
shot on the big guy throw the windows
that would be amazing
I want the double to see me hi
[Music]
almost got me
foreign
[Music]
truck like over the truck it's pretty
high probably right
oh
man
ah I killed something
[Music]
okay okay okay okay that's that's nice
easy going 13 shots left
I don't know who to go for now that I
don't have the punch anymore even the
close range ones are dangerous for me
[Music]
what just happened what was that ah his
shop ourselves
how do I maybe I just bathe the rest I
don't know how much more there's left
here but just bait it
[Music]
oh he's not he doesn't want to get
baited this one
I have a gun yeah that one's down now
that one's dead
does this hide me there's no one left
oh
[Applause]
yeah anyone got an Ooty
that's not an Uzi kind of walkie-talkie
though you can use that either
no only in the one or two rounds left
should I bring it anyway
[Music]
I don't know what's gonna happen
even with the two shots who knows
awesome work thank you yeah nice day for
Destruction
emotional support with you better gone
with ammo
It's relatively quiet
[Music]
dodging everything but that's right
wasn't there doors no
[Music]
there we go beautiful
all right
remember quinoa I'm like every second
I'm about to forget that I don't have my
Tony fists anymore
foreign
[Music]
maybe if it's at the right timing he
wouldn't hear me yeah because he's up
there
but I can't really you know just 12 dads
[Music]
he goes
protagon ah maybe yeah
[Music]
Panic meowing
the knife
[Music]
what happened I thought I threw the
knife why no kill did I miss how can I
miss
which way do we go
[Music]
lost my knife but next
crowbar doesn't kill though
[Music]
I dropped it for the for the bats
they're so aggressive when they greet
you
mealing with the Crowbar okay
[Music]
dynamic in their movement
in there
okay got it got him got him got him got
him dude
look how it looks here
[Music]
let's go there
afterwards
[Music]
see how little shots I mean
amazing
[Music]
no I appreciate that a little cleanup
before we move on
[Music]
in front of the door like
protecting him while he's on the on the
pp toilet
so sweet you can't be protected though
[Music]
is my knife gone
no
which side to alcohol
oh scary scary what the [\h__\h]
I thought I could go here and hide on
the left side but I couldn't oh God I'm
okay I'm okay oh
[Music]
boss
and I do it quietly quiet dude does he
get hit by the door
yeah
[Music]
now this one I'm guessing has oh
we're moving quietly yeah oh the glass
ah
[Music]
okay oh
there's many screams of Terror for me
honestly you could use my clip and my on
my sound sounds of Terror for like a
horror game if you wanted to
it's very fitting
[Music]
of course I would never play it
know me
crowbar and do we go let's go left side
first after all
they're all melee anyway
[Music]
screaming every game
my screens are perfect material I would
say
or getting the right atmosphere and Vibe
across
foreign
[Music]
skills oh God this is so scary
this is so scary just come here
[Music]
okay
the thing is I can't do that on him but
in this room I guess I'll shoot but
there's windows again
[Music]
but I think I need to use a gun against
that guy thank God I didn't use it all
up
yet
because they mostly don't have milk I
can shoot from here easily
[Music]
oh
I can use that for this one but then do
they see me
[Music]
probably
oh nice
sweet oh okay
[Music]
so what do I do about the other boss I
can take one up there guns they got some
guns okay
[Music]
very chill right now because the bgm is
helping me calm down
and now that we're so far I'm just ah
this is my This Is My Jam
easy okay the first one I remember I can
uh
take care of with the door I think but
yeah but that's not what I did last time
did I
[\h__\h] I'm scared I want to [\h__\h] it up
[Music]
spark quietly huh
I don't know if I can anymore
nah
[\h__\h] is the boss gonna
foreign
check me out
again
[Music]
will he be easy on me I better go with
like one of his full musicians shotgun
maybe he won't attack
you won't kill me oh my God thank you
for telling me that but I can I can kill
him it seems
[Music]
oh wait look man I don't wanna travel
here safe is open just take away I don't
care about the safe I think look I'm not
the owner he's not here I just run the
club like a piece of civil about this
he's gonna really never seem fell down
all right all right I'll give you his
address
[Laughter]
don't hurt me
[Music]
that's not my style is it
I really like hurting people
he's on North East 114th place please
just go now okay
[Music]
I have to kill him like this
yeah oh oh
[Music]
no papers I don't need the papers
apparently I really didn't was that
really necessary
ha
he lost it
am I gonna be welcomed
let me take a gun just in case
oh I can't see it again
okay
are we the baddest no
come on isn't it clear
there is so much Bloodshed at this point
it's like normal
so we're just doing our daily thing
I'm not any worse than those guys come
on
they're all in it
and even the police they're corrupted
C plus
yay new mask
Oscar what the [\h__\h] is that is that
um
or
what is it what is this
an an antique here
[Music]
Showdown
is this the last chapter or is there one
more
I'll go back to Tony I miss Tony
oh
um
[Music]
guys
um
thank you
this looks like a Pokemon Arena Pokemon
uh like Pokemon battle arena
over to them
what okay
yeah
purple cats those are Pokemon
gym
this is out
a Panthers is very purple though purple
um
important to immediately
Instagram can I oh I cannot oh
[Music]
they're slow at first but like what I
maybe
can I
it's like she has a weapon can I take
her on first
yeah
maybe not pro but like smash them when
they get to me
I need two heads down
really fast
is that what no she's dead okay
that's what I do about that
[Music]
I wanted to focus on her first but no no
time unless I do it right after I kill
the pointers
all right
[Music]
we all always gotta look at the dialogue
believe in your aim okay
my brain and my aim
I'm like clicking as I can but I guess
it's also a little bit the timing the
Rhythm
[Music]
I thought so okay
sorry
I'm still mashing your brains out never
see it quite like it
however
[Music]
thanks though for the warning
foreign
[Music]
come on
foreign
[Music]
still close by or I don't know have the
wife die
a bit closer to me
[Music]
so I'm closer to the wall now maybe that
will help
[Music]
you
left press right click as I was walking
away so difficult to pick up run to a
trophy
ah I can't there's no cover there
so tricking
don't give me time to think here
let me try the other side
down here
[Music]
stuck
a tile
I don't know I'll try again
or I don't know
[\h__\h]
this one took you a while and it's
taking me a long time
oh that's a good place to dive
10 out of 10 kind of recommend
laughs
oh [\h__\h]
okay
if she then that would be really helpful
foreign
[Music]
how did I do that how did I get her to
die there
[Music]
no mercy for me
wait
yeah
nah she died in the wrong place again
thank you
oh
okay good I can see where it is going
here what happens now
I spare you the pleasure
my heart my heart's dudes and do that my
heart is
in in the bottom of my uh stomach this
uh
hello hello
sleep ah I'm so sorry is there anyone
there can you hear me hello
goddamn phones I [\h__\h] hate these
things
really
stage cleared isn't it
no show me the ammunition what am I
carrying even what is this little pistol
or
[\h__\h] do I and do I need I can't even I
can't change
my weapon though
weird
I have it doesn't show munition
[Music]
Dwight
hello no fighting I guess just talking
uh I usually are the one causing the
Rockers
what's your business here
actually why don't we skip the details
I've done this so many horrible things
nothing seems to really matter anymore
does it I've become so numb
I'm not going anywhere as you can see
just go ahead and do whatever you came
here to do
really
oh
aha that's why I couldn't change they
wanted me to use this one man I don't
know what
is that it
seems like a ending point but
so I feel like I got no conclusions just
a smoke break
smoking not healthy is gonna kill you
dude
in a more painful way than the others
Maybe
[Music]
there's also a secret ending but I would
need all the lettuce oh okay
but I I didn't
epilogue okay okay okay
but I'm done fighting am I done fighting
can I put my knife down
[Music]
yeah
oh nice not yet not yet Apple has
fighting too
ah
life will be worth fitting
[\h__\h] this
almost all right I'm really exhausted my
heart
hurts
[Music]
okay while we're reading these one other
Hotel Hell episode that I found so
[\h__\h] funny was the one with the old
no not all the relatively young owner
just in comparison to his wife he seems
to be always going for the older ladies
and he's like such a poser with like all
his gold rings diamond rings and then
he's got like three different really
expensive cars outside of this hotel you
know which one I mean
and then he's like
just flexing all his money and wealth in
his hotel but like doesn't invest
anything in the hotel so the cocktail
quality is like really suffering from it
and so bad and he's just always got that
stupid ass smile on his face it's so so
annoying
but the episode that was that was a
funny one too
yeah I like seeing the employees often
like often some high rank employee were
like absolutely rage quits at the
confrontation and be like [\h__\h] yeah wow
[Music]
I can't cook and then Gordon Ramsay is
like going to their house and like
please please we need you you're like
the only the only useful person now here
the only light at the end of the tunnel
please come back
so funny especially with like Hotel
knowledge that I have it's it's very
funny but I gotta say some of Gordon
Ramsay's like redesigns I'm not sure he
probably doesn't really he doesn't
really decide how to how the rooms are
gonna get redesigned and all that that's
it like it seems like he and uh but I
don't believe it gotta say some of the
designs are like not that impressive
mostly staged I mean
I mean some things don't seem so staged
like in that other episode that I
watched today where
um uh where it was this really expensive
hotel the chef he like
faints and they call an ambulance and
that seemed pretty real like the way he
fainted I mean I feel like
they the little TV crew they must have
been like [\h__\h] yeah this is good
material in that moment
but I don't feel like they would that
was really yeah yeah I think the guy had
health issues
it was real it was really stressed out
yeah
but they must have fought [\h__\h] this is
good material this gives us free drama
we don't even have to create the drama
in this one
Banks it creates itself
um
yeah the chef he was so nice if I felt
so happy when he was so happy afterwards
he was like eating Gordon Ramsay's food
and then he started crying because it's
like it moved him so much and he found
joy again in cooking but apparently he
passed in like 2020
I don't know how soon after it was after
that episode but probably relatively
soon
so sad Young
oh
sad very sad also that that hotel still
closed
they didn't recover after the pandemic
they closed with the pandemic and then
still today that hotel is not opened at
luxury hotel
Oh weird
the end
all right
it's it's so funny and I'm liking how
Gordon Ramsay just really
brings Justice to those [\h__\h] idiots
[\h__\h] Hotel owners
[Music]
we'll Play Hard by Miami too but right
there's still like an epilogue do I have
to click something okay
part five answers
yeah I need answers
take up
take up his answer
in Korean
who is this you think I'm stupid
I look stupid to you I know you aren't
telling me everything
you helped me get into this mess you
told me it would be exciting didn't you
well I'm [\h__\h] bored I'm done man I've
had it I want to quit I wanna out and
you're gonna tell me how this stupid
game is gonna end now you hear me
is that me
all right all right calm down man you
don't realize how much trouble I'll be
in
there's a guy hiding out at the blue
dragon a tiny Chinese restaurant
downtown he knows more just don't
mention my name to anyone okay I'm as
good as that anyway
am I no I'm too white to be me who am I
playing as
the black guy killed I don't even
remember that
I mean I kind of remember the helmet but
I don't know what happened oh sick bike
they're so cool
cool Safe House your meat cleaver is
there to win
[Music]
should I use only my meat cleaver
you need to cleaver what a weird name
there's a gun guy though
you guys not want to say hi to me
[Music]
maybe I can throw it but can I then
still pick it up
Cleaver
[Music]
fun
what a fun time I oh I've got I know
I've seen three knives to throw
yeah me what happened
can I pick this knife up additionally
[Music]
I picked the others up too I don't
really see where they are
typical
[Music]
oh my body hurts so much I don't know
why I think it's because I haven't eaten
since a while
I had I had breakfast
[Music]
and that's pretty much it yeah
it's like 11 11 20 now
I need food
[Music]
foreign
but that wouldn't that be boring
wouldn't that be boring if I use the gun
when I'm giving this beautiful cleaver
[Music]
yeah right I should I should kill you
see
oh my God my knives
[Music]
oh
that didn't Inspire him to come over
here though oh wait I have to use the
cleaver anyway [\h__\h]
hi everything hurts
um
[Music]
but I want to finish this
I want to keep a knife for the one of
the inside guys
[Music]
I could throw that one
oh man
can I get my knife back yeah I got one
back here
[Music]
hey
hmm
I want that one back ideally
[Music]
any knives
you cannot get it I felt like I got one
back
painting
[Music]
save the knife
if you hit an anime it will be used you
can read them ah only if I missed
Ninja
this one I wanna be
I baited the other one
okay
[Music]
stay clear
foreign
I've got some things I need to know you
so better answer my questions okay
what are the people who keep leaving my
me messages I don't even think about
bullshitting me okay I won't hesitate to
pull you apart if I have to yeah trust
them
trust me I'll tell you what I know just
don't hurt me I can't tell you who's
calling your shot but they're uh using
phone what the phone home
sweep up there are Trails ah that place
I only help them set it up at the
station you'll have to hack into their
system to trace them I went into hiding
as soon as the drop was finished they
seem to have some form of political
agenda let's get the [\h__\h] out of me I
spend all my savings on getting the Rat
Hole this rattle that's all I am okay
you're good I'm gonna kill you
go to bike okay
no problem
I spared this one I'm a different person
laughs
a plus
well that's rare
EK cute what's the fox without ears man
said we need ears
how much longer is this guys I need to
know for my own safety
tell me it's not like I'm not enjoying
it you know
I don't mean it's for real two or three
hours more
two more chapters chapters
[Music]
uh Miami drop-off it looks like you
missed your delivery last night we've
got another person for you today um
our clients will not tolerate
certificate ladies quick
[Music]
ly
look at that this is a sick apartment
I mean okay I think like this
I hate animal patterns I think they're
so tacky most of the time especially on
a bed it's so [\h__\h] tacky dip
Domo
I guess the United States is one of the
if it's the 80s and okay but like
nowadays no please my clothes as well I
don't I feel like a lot of women's
clothes have
um like a leopard pattern for example
[Music]
I really don't like them I still see a
lot of clothes
love animal patterns oh mostly leopard
though
I heard kitchens German yeah kitchen's
German I've just released a song of the
title cake
so yeah kitchen's German it's like kind
of I guess it means Takia
oh funky music
[Music]
what did I do
well it's just fast
it was very fast everyone's just got oh
no never mind they got them
Funky Monkey first egg yeah might have
been my first one
f
you got an what what what what's that
what are you guys answering to I don't
know what you're answering to
foreign
[Music]
didn't I get it kind of late
nice
[Music]
please no more
[Laughter]
he's like what the [\h__\h] does this guy
want from me
oh there's a door
I forgot about him he was just not there
for a while
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
switch to Linux man's [\h__\h] windows
I always knew it
good
[Music]
I can make a joke sometimes
where did my knife go so we're down
there now I have to pick it up
what the [\h__\h] music
come back music please what the [\h__\h]
Knife wait my knives are not shouldn't
they have three knives what happened
I'm a nice list
[Music]
I'm [\h__\h] it Mommy
yeah I picked them
um the ones I could because like I can
only pick them up if I miss right so I
guess the one I missed
that I didn't need I did pick up you
only have one then that
go
I used two on the first floor I thought
maybe they would recover after what I do
about these guys I mean one I can shoot
yes perfect
[Music]
hi Miss up we gotta get moving
and that's so rough that's really rough
rap
foreign
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] the windows no but they can't
shoot anything oh another dog coming
wait
um
[Music]
oh
let me go for him
still got one knife too
I don't like this distorted music freaks
me out
yeah wait okay thank God I didn't go
there yet because there's more windows
can he throw a knife
wait uh now okay they'll see me but they
can't do [\h__\h]
he's behind the wall though
[Music]
no do you not want to like walk over
here come on
oh man
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] people I have to
um you know everybody was looking at me
[Music]
someone's coming
oh I got them both
okay
now it should be pretty clear only does
those ones left right
look at that hmm
maybe one of them have a gun
so [\h__\h] dead thank God I don't have
to cook I still got leftovers from
yesterday though that was so yummy such
a [\h__\h] cooking genius I should open
the restaurant oh never mind I got kfp
so much fun
on my complete upper body is in pain
let's go
not bad you know I'm doing pretty good
in this uh epilogue
a Brandon wow
the Panthers
oh I wonder what they do
yeah
it's a Cheesy tacky bed again who is
that on the toilet
I'm gonna junkie on the couch why did we
have a party
yeah one minute
see you again how about another day
tonight pick me up uh at Northeast 138th
Street around 9 okay and put on one of
those nice suits you guys
this evening
[Music]
now
what do I have this
funky
can I take them no
[\h__\h] keyboard with the dude
[Music]
on the ground is my bed though why is
this like in case someone attacks me at
night I'll just play some music for them
and hope they will keep me alive am I
supposed to kill these people what do
they got what kind of weapons do they
have
oh they don't want it oh they're
innocence
[\h__\h] around there
[Music]
sick and tired of this [\h__\h]
this is how they ended up dead huh wait
I left one alive [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you all [\h__\h] you yeah
[Music]
hi thank you for not trying to yeah
please don't kill me
[\h__\h] you
let's take those golf clubs too if I can
they'll have a new owner I don't adopt
them yeah I'll play golf every weekend I
promise
interesting North 87th Place huh so
that's where you've been hiding
chicken mask friend
out of here if you don't want to die
okay have it your way
I'm [\h__\h] easy what
was it an autopilot is that your chance
isn't it really that easy
oh
I cannot have anyone tell police what
happened here you know I mean they'll
see
but they won't understand
I'll tell your family that you love them
five tier actually never happened
really so what do you what are you
saying it's all in my head
[Music]
um
it's so nice of me am I ordering
tombstones for my victims or for myself
my own
[Music]
resolution follow the red arrows
at least like in these epilogue chapters
I'm like pretty [\h__\h] strong
going easy on me what the [\h__\h] did you
do where'd he go
[Music]
what's this looks like I need a password
to access this computer
[Music]
is this
a chicken mask
maybe other masks
with this tuna was there always two
they're doing some crazy scientists [\h__\h]
people pick a question to ask oh oh um
you don't know that's pathetic I thought
you were you had us figure out by now
make a guess [\h__\h]
oh they're similar
I feel like I only saw the blonde God of
really blonde good
not that it makes any difference now
does it
oh you're the phone guys
um
what a stupid question you really need
to
eat does it look like to you [\h__\h] you
don't know anything do you
I don't really care can we just kill
them
you mean you haven't enjoyed it that's a
shame huh
ah ah why are you killing people are
they gonna say it they enjoy it you
haven't killed anyone we haven't killed
anyone you rap
they were all scum anyway weren't they I
think they deserve to live do you do you
do you say I think they deserve to live
say
that's it I seem disappointing
disappointed when were you expecting I
think we're through with your questions
yeah your move creep
y easy
weak cowards
[Music]
they keep on they always just use
me
for their
really evil plans and themselves they
can't do [\h__\h] [\h__\h] cowards
ah is that the real land now
I killed the game
the kill don't worry don't worry it's
fake it's just a game they really made
Hotline Miami too I already bought it I
already have it
now it's over
it's okay I don't care about the real
ending I just wanted to kill
[Music]
yay you can tell me the real ending
I'm not gonna get the letters now
Jesus
[Music]
yay that was fun I'm so happy I can eat
now
oh oh they're doing the the drums again
the Retro drums
give me more of the body
The Mask I picked up is by far the
strong with the one I picked up at the
very end
what does it do
I was getting it at the end what does
that do for me can I use it in like some
after extra levels or what
how am I am it's way harder oh yeah it
hurt and then I heard that Tony got
nerfed I think
oh
that's rough I don't know
but I've been doing pretty well I think
so it's just gonna be a new challenge
[Music]
is an improvement though really it's a
bad soundtrack well of course it does
gotta gotta follow up
on the amazing sounds you delivered in
the first one otherwise like what the
[\h__\h] Emerald VN does it again yeah this
was another game that I didn't really
expect to finish I just
I just thought I would dabble in it once
and then
move on to other games but I enjoyed it
so much last time that I decided to play
more I hope you guys enjoyed screaming
monkey kiwawa monkey yada my beloved
so there's also way more story having oh
I'm looking forward to that I mean I did
enjoy like the the
tiny bits of story here and there in
between the killing I mean
The Killing was lots of fun and I would
have been fine even without the lore but
it adds to it and it at least gives me
some breathing River in between
yeah
it was fun
A lot of blood rage Kiana going crazy
some insane laughs where I'm even
questioning my own sanity I
I'm scared of myself
need a new mask
[\h__\h] we sure
which one though fails what is this what
is that a Kappa fish what is that it
looks like a fish
whoa come here [\h__\h]
ing
chameleon
cute fill the fish
there's a phoenix mask what
rhymes with a red so Chad thank you
wow wow Luigi Luigi
Louis the lizard oh cute
wow selfish was the guy who developed
Fez I have no idea what you're saying
it's a reference to another Game Dev oh
it says a game
now
[Music]
um
Hotline Miami another game finished on
my list
we are going to uh do Amanda stream
tomorrow by the way we're gonna continue
playing tepic AKA lost Epic
foreign
so feel free to stop by if you want
and um yeah I'm gonna take a [\h__\h]
break now
I'm gonna eat and then chill with my
ketokatos
yeah oh but actually no I have I'm gonna
eat and then do some
um deadline stuff
I have like
I think a little video that I have to
record I'm just very short
oh yeah
[Music]
thank you guys for watching I thought I
could maybe Read Super chats today but
it's already midnight and I kind of like
uh stretched
myself to the limits
um
thank you for watching thank you love
you guys
[Music]
I'm glad we finished the game
successfully had a blast honestly I felt
also I was pretty decent at the game
today
um
yeah I mean some parts still needed a
lot of repetition but I think
I didn't do badly
will you ever visit Miami Florida
I'm in Miami in Florida it's Miami and
Florida oh I Heard lots of cool things
about Miami that Miami is [\h__\h]
awesome friend of mine went there a
couple times so I want to hear good
things about it
sounds sounds like a good place to go to
for vacation to maybe I don't know but
I don't really expect they have like
pretty beaches but they got great
weather right and like cool City
Party City right I don't like to party
I don't like to pack uh GTA 6 is going
to be in Miami okay okay yeah I feel
like that's a that's a fitting location
that'll be fun whenever GTA 6 comes out
and five million [\h__\h] years
it better come out when I'm still able
to stream it
ah yeah in Florida they have all kinds
of [\h__\h] right
man so lucky living in Florida you must
have like everything at your disposal
I'm gonna use another GTA games no
nothing nothing
Everglades ah I heard of that
humidity oh [\h__\h] Miami Florida oh [\h__\h]
I wonder if it's as bad as like Korea
and Japan though because you guys if you
haven't been there
don't probably understand because I also
underestimated that before I went to
Japan
like how [\h__\h] tropically humid it is
over there Indonesia too of course but
I think Indonesia like Japan wasn't
uh was pretty close to Indonesia's
humility as well
humidity was a never tad bit stronger in
Indonesia
I hate that I [\h__\h] hate it
it's the worst
[Music]
you'll have balls growing out of you oh
Ahmed would enjoy that
more side of the armpits or so
okay I gotta go guys thank you so much
I'll see you tomorrow the members three
match the main game that is
[Music]
foreign