the accounting department these uniform
expense reports don't make sense how did
they lose so many office supplies but
their uniform budget keeps decreasing
let me check over here first I think the
bottom left is probably that's all
covered with boxes never mind it's all
locked up bu inside man I hate this it's
all the
same um I don't know what to do with
this mess just tell me the cost already
no nothing here this okay never mind
that what
about okay now we're getting
somewhere what's this for your eyes only
do not
upload kfp
n002 this is it this is exactly what
we're looking for okay let's open this
up wait what's this why are there so
many incident reports about office
supplies and furniture out of the
pockets of this this doesn't make any
sense I don't okay anyway I'm uploading
these files to you now but I should
P all right that's my que got everything
sent time to move where should we go
next and wait how did I get these
coupons we're running out of room for
all this job
[Music]